So, one more thing, right? So, I was
talking about this, but a lot of these
women that only reply to negativity also
always love to play the victim. Like,
maybe I should go on Reddit later and
ask why they respond only to negativity.
Like, they only date guys who hit women
or guys that deal drugs or have tattoos,
right? I send a message and nothing for
three days. The moment I start telling
them about themselves though, I get a
ton of replies. Now, how does that make
any sense? Like, all these guys keep
saying, "Work on your personality,
rattat tata tat, but it never works."
It's not about personality, though.
Like, all these celebs only date bad
guys, so why should I try to act nice?
Like, I won't mention who, right? But
you see this one guy who does drugs and
he has a woman and an ex. Like, how does
that even work? Yeah. So, anyway, I'm
off again for a bit.