Yo, so Arsenal Mark was supposed to show
up at my door and didn't. Right now all
these keyboard warriors like to talk and
talk and talk. None of you are showing
up though. Now I have a court date in
December of 2028.
I'm not going to meet where there are
cameras just so you grasses can try to
fill me in with the police. Nah. All
these people like to talk, but not a
single one of you are going to do
anything about it. Now, another thing,
right? Stop bringing up people on my
channel just so you can try and get me
nicked. Like saying I can't leave the
country because of court. I'll do
whatever I please. Oh, and another
thing. You people keep bringing up this
Twitter stuff from a few months ago. I
am sick of hearing about some woman I
bullied along with her boyfriend. Stop
bringing it up. Anyway, I'm off this
YouTube for a while.