Yo, I woke up. I woke up with it,
too. Oh, I'm so dead. I woke up with it, too. Yeah.
Yeah, it was on my [Music] Oh, that's [Laughter]
Oh, it's funny. I got the giggles. [Laughter]
I feel like they were drunk or something. [Laughter]
Oh mate, that is just
That is jokes, man. So, I thought, [ __ ]
it. Very simple bet today. I only put 20
quid on. I was going to put 10 pound on
it, but I like the look of this bet so
much, I thought I'd chuck a skull on it.
Only 20 pound in it. [ __ ]
it. I got I put some notes in the [ __ ] bank. Yeah.
working some sort of [ __ ] up. I think SC [ __ ] rap [ __ ] SC. Yeah.
[ __ ] Let's go.
I've never been that [ __ ] [ __ ] diamond in
the country annoys me things like me about
this. I feel [ __ ] annoyed about this country. Don't see
Yeah, man. No, I was just saying there's
this [ __ ] this stupid scouse rat,
bro. I'm not going to get into it, but
yeah, she's a
[ __ ] Yeah, this country annoys me,
bro. Sometimes this country annoys me, lad.
One second. I'll I'll be right back.
Yeah, man. Just No, it's just some scout
rap from ages ago.
Anyways, now someone else I'm speaking
about though, not the person I'm talking to. Absolute scout raping
scy man join the
hangouts. Sorry I don't really cover
them much anymore. You don't really see
me. Yeah, I don't really come on here
much anymore. I come on yesterday cuz I
was drunk. Yeah, I don't really come on much
anymore. No, not really. Nah,
bro. Can't be [ __ ] mate. Every single
time you go
live, skin your skin. Your skin. That's
what they say, bro. Same same repeating
people. That's why I don't really come
on much no more.
Same with people it. Yeah,
man. This woman's a scouse rat. someone
else I'm speaking to about I don't know
a football bet though I only put 20 pound this
time I was going to put 10 I don't want
to put more than 10 but this one is like
a double so I thought why
not why the [ __ ] not in
it I think it will I think it will win
man both teams on either team both teams
score on either team to
I got both teams to score. Either team
to win. I just done a double. I only put
20 on it. I've already done 20 pound bets today,
man. Cuz I won some money on fish and
frenzy yesterday at the
pub. Yeah. Why do they give it to you in
coins? Why when you win the pubs, they
give you half in notes and half in
coins? I literally don't get that.
Yeah, you're not spending no four grand
in Mexico, mate. You're not spending no
four grand in
Mexico. So what? You're going to be
spending four grand in
Mexico? What's the m What's the return
on the bet? £162 from 20
quid. I mean, it's a good bet, is
it? It's a good bet if it wins.
Yeah. Probably won't die, but Yeah. 20 on it.
Oh, you're not spending four grand in
Mexico, mate. It ain't
happening. You're not even going to
probably spend [ __ ] a thousand. How
long did you say you're going for? Like
week. I got car and cold chest and h gate and
swindom. Bro, how long are you going
for? A week. You're probably not even
going to spend more than a
grand for [ __ ]
sake. Yeah, I had a few drinks
yesterday, but obviously I'm going away
next week. I should be going away next
week. So, I had to be careful what I was
spending. That's why I didn't want to go
on a session and get hung over. So I
said, "Oh, I'll have a few with my
friend and I want some money on fishing
friends." He done got an escort and come
back and I went more. So I didn't want
to spend any more money cuz I'm going away.
So I should be going away next
week. So yeah, I don't want to I don't
want to waste money, you know. So yeah,
obviously I 20 football back today, but
that's whenever you mind where I'm going.
But I'll put some videos up whenever you
mind where I'm
going. Got to travel all this way to
meet a [ __ ] woman. But it's worth it,
you know. It's worth it. If it works
out, it's [ __ ] worth it, is it? It's
[ __ ] long travel, ain't
it? [ __ ] me. I ain't travel by myself in
ages. But we'll see in
it. But I didn't want to be wasting money.
You know, I don't want to be wasting [ __ ]
money. What am I watching?
I'm not watching
nothing. My mate, that's not my mate.
And he's not back because he never left
and to begin
with. Yeah. He he never left. Uh he's
not back because he never left and he's
not mate. So yeah.
Yeah. You know what I'm saying? Yeah,
man. Yeah, man. I watched this crushing
scene. I might send you the link to this
horror film that I watched and the woman
got crushed. Ew, it was
nasty. That is [ __ ] vile, bro. Oh my
god. I might send you the link for
anyone that cares. It's [ __ ]
disgusting. I went to a cinema and I
watched it by myself, bro. And see this
woman just get crushed. All her blood turn
into that is [ __ ] vile,
bro. The only thing else with horror
films and blood I can take. Yeah, that
was just [ __ ] up, bro. I woke up today
thinking about that. That was nasty. Nasty,
bro. That's nasty. That's [ __ ] vile,
bro. See all that blood? Oh, it made it
gave me like it made my head cringe,
bro. I'm not going to
lie. I watched this thing called Heart
Eyes in the cinema. It was a Valentine's horror. So, yeah.
Yeah, it was [ __ ] disgusting, mate. I
literally watched it. Yeah. And to bear
in mind, blood don't bother me. Blood
me. Um, blood don't bother me. Knives
don't bother me. People getting head
chopped off don't bother me. But that
was that was nasty,
bro. That was disgusting. And I think
the worst thing is you thought she was
going to survive.
That's the worst thing about it is that
I thought she was going to survive. Like she's getting
away and the police got killed and the
other guy got killed. She's about to get
away and she ends up in this [ __ ]
tank and then she gets crushed. Oh my
god, it was [ __ ] vile. But the thing
is with horror films though, yeah, as
much as I like these horror films,
they're so predictable. Like by that I
mean is that we always know that the
main character is never going to die.
Maybe the second main character dies,
sometimes they don't die, but the main
character never ever dies. There's not
enough twist in these horror films, you
know, like Orphan, there was a twist to
it, so it was good. But with these
horror films is they're
so that's it's so um there there's no
twist to it. It's all predictable. It's
like [ __ ] Looney Tunes and [ __ ] Tom and
Jerry. Yeah, who knows, man. Maybe. But
yeah, that was disgusting, bro. I'm not
going to lie, that was disgusting. I was
actually hoping she got away or something,
but And I could just imagine me being
there and then it crushing her. Oh,
that's it's horrible. That is horrible,
man. That's That is horrible, bro.
Yuck, that was too much to watch. I'm
not going to lie to you, bro. Maybe it
was where I just woke up or what, but
nah, bro. Someone getting crushed like
that and splattered into bits. That was vile,
bro. Laney could have never watched
that. Laney doesn't like horror films. I
always say to Laney, "Oh, let's come
out. Let's watch a horror film. Let's
watch a horror film." She won't watch
films. She hates horror films. She will
never watch them. But could you imagine
a lady imagine a lady trying to watch that?
Huh? See it's ever happening,
mate. That's [ __ ]
up. You ever watch that Australian
hobby? Yeah. Cool. Talk to
me. They're like my my I'm not dead.
Well, that was [ __ ] that was creepy
as [ __ ] It was like her mom is dead but
trying to pretend that she's still alive
saying oh there's a madness. Don't know
if you remember that one but it was
Australian. I think it's like 6 months
ago maybe a bit more. Yeah. But S's just gruesome you
know. S was just
gruesome. You know what I hate about the
horror films as well is them sex scenes.
There weren't a sex scene on this one.
Yeah. But it's like the kissing and the
dating. That's another thing I don't
like about horror films is that never
happens where people just meet and then
they save one's life and then the other
one has sex with them. That [ __ ] never
happens. They even when you watch horror
films, it can [ __ ] with your
head. It can really [ __ ] with your head.
Even just like horror films like that,
like the love scenes, the the the [ __ ]
up themes, like someone getting crushed
to bits and all of their blood turned
into [ __ ] fluid. [ __ ] vile, man.
And trust me, I've watched a lot of
horror films. Yeah. And none of them has
ever bothered me. It's called Talk to
Me. It's a It's an Australian horror
film. Go watch
it. She was like, "My my I actually
killed myself. I couldn't take it
anymore. It wasn't an It wasn't an
accident. It's [ __ ] [ __ ] up, bro. Yeah. Yeah.
That's That was vile. But I wasn't the
only one in the cinema yesterday. I went
to cinema at 9:00. So, I was actually
going to go Monday, so I was the only
one in the cinema. Yeah, I was going to
go Monday, so I was the only one in the cinema.
Um, but I was like, "Oh, it's early
enough. Let me go see the first
showing." There was like five people in
the cinema, so it must be the today's
poker. What it's called? Talk to me.
That's what it's
called. Watch this. It's an Australian
over. It's [ __ ] up,
man. That woman got
crushed. That woman got crushed.
We got [ __ ] rush
me. Well, I did like that [ __ ] scene,
bro. It was
nasty. Yeah, that woman was kind of nice
looking in the horror film as well. The
one I saw
yesterday. We yank. That's the thing.
They never make the women look ugly as
well. They always make them look like
decent. That's what I hate about it,
these horror films. And that never
happens. Like the these love scenes, it
doesn't happen like that. Obviously
people go on dates, people have sex, but
it doesn't happen like it does in movies. You
know, that doesn't happen in real life like that.
That's They always do it as
well. They always [ __ ] do it.
Yeah, that one in that heart eye. She
was She was nice. You look all
right. They don't ever make them look ugly, do
they? And then a guy walks out and then
they run and chase the guy and then
gives the guy a kiss. That doesn't
happen in real life,
bro. That [ __ ] doesn't happen in real life.
Yeah. Never happens in real life. That
imagine being a virgin like Sean and to
watch that. Imagine if you was actually
a virgin like him. It'd be even [ __ ] worse,
lad. It would be even [ __ ]
worse. It would be even [ __ ]
worse, bro. That USA easy thing is
getting boring now, bro. It's getting really, really
boring. It's really, really, really
boring now, bro. is like no one's
reacting to it but it's getting really
boring. Take your obsession with my
sloppy seconds elsewhere cuz it's really
getting boring now. You've been saying
this now for the past three four months
and it's getting really boring. Like
that's that's just me telling you how it
is. It's really really
boring. Like you really really really
need to think of some new things.
You really need to think of some new
things to say, bro, cuz respectfully,
that's getting really boring now. That
USA is fire. No, no, no. I'm getting
triggered. Uh, go self-reflect on another
channel. All of this stuff, Steven
Howard, they're all little
self-reflectors. They're all little
self-reflectors. That's what they are.
They're all little self-reflectors, bro.
They call me skin. Yeah. I went around
offering the woman £300. I went out two
times. I went out yesterday. I went out
the last the week before that and a week
before that and I spent hundreds. So how
can somebody that's skinn do
that? These people only know their own
skin lives. That's why none of these
people affect me cuz they don't know
anything about what people
have. You know, they're so spasticated
they can't even come up with new things.
These people ask. That's why no one gets
triggered over them.
Yeah. Why do you keep going on about my
sloppy seconds as well? It's getting
boring now, bro. You're not getting
anyone triggered. You're just boring.
There's a difference between getting
triggered and getting and someone
actually being bored. Like, all you go
on about is my top three seconds. It's
so boring. God, you're obsessed. Like,
it's not even No one's getting
triggered. I'm just telling you how obsessed you look.
Like, it's so obsessed. You know, you
look you look like [ __ ] you end up
like [ __ ] on Shaw's level when you
start doing that,
bro. It's boring as
[ __ ] Like USA is fire. It's boring. All
I was thinking of your meme. Yeah.
Yesterday when I was drinking Gree, I
couldn't stop laughing. You said that
women are here to fetch food. I was
dead. I don't know why. It just gave me
the It gave me the It gave me the
giggles to fetch food.
They're here to fetch food. They were
put on this earth to fetch
food. No, they were put on this earth to
satisfy Peter Belly's
needs. But you see, not to fetch food. To fetch
food. That was funny.
But my mom was like, "I'm out today."
No, I'm not a [ __ ] alcoholic, mate. I
didn't even plan to drink yesterday.
My friend was in town. He wanted to
meet. So I met and yeah, got on it. So I
didn't plan I didn't actually plan to to
go out yesterday. Well, I plan to go.
Well, yeah. I don't really make
plans and to make babies.
Greasy and to make babies.
Yeah, I'm tired, bro.
So, what do you think about this
football bet today? Do you think it's
going to win? Me thinks? Yeah.
Me thinks you? Yeah.
Yeah. I just put 30 pound on the Frankie
and I got it to 110. Actually, you know
what happened? Yeah. I done it. I went
on half I went half with my friend.
Yeah, I withdrew 30 quid and he said
that he was going to give me
£15. So I said so I said
uh so then when it we got bonus and paid
nothing then he said okay if it goes
below this 30 it's your money now not
mine. I said okay. I got to £23 I got
two bonuses and then it paid mad. I bet
he wish he [ __ ] he he he chipp he
stayed chipping in now is
it? Yeah, cuz as soon as he didn't want
to chip in them no more, the bonuses started
coming. And that's how you know it's
rigged as well because how is it that
you get these bonuses in the pub? How is
it that you get these bonuses right in
the pub, but when you do two pound in
the bookies, you can't get a bonus to
save your life? If your life depending
on it, that's how you know even more so it's
rigged. That's how you know even more so
that it's rigged.
Because why is
it why is it that that happens? You know
what you should do? You should go to a
pub with 50 quid £100, sorry, and put
£50 in one machine and 50 in another
machine. That's what you should do and
just go around machines doing that.
That's what you should do. Do like 50 piece
steak, one pound steak, 50p steak.
That's what you should
do. and just do it all day long with
whatever profit you
make. Yeah, that's what you should
do. They were put on earth to fetch food. To fetch
food? No, man. No. So, ask me this
question. How comes you can get a bonus
in the pub very easy, but then when you
go to the cookies, you can't get a bonus
to save your life if your life depended
on it. Can somebody answer me
that? Can somebody please answer me
Huh? I'd love somebody to answer me that.
Mhm. Put on the fetch
food. The fetch
food. Yeah. Well, the bookies
though. the bookies
though. Yeah, I put 30 pound. I think
110. Got a couple more rounds of drinks.
Got an escort. Come back. Got a
curry. Job done in
it. Put some stuff in it.
So, you know what? I don't understand.
Let me tell you all of this stuff right
now everyone's here. Why are these pubs
Why is the jackpot £100? The jackpot
should be £250. If they're letting you
do a one pound spin in a pub, why is it
max Why is it 100 pound maximum
jackpot? What? What are they trying to
say? Oh, cuz of responsible gambling.
Okay. What's the difference between a
one pound spin and a two pound spin?
There's not really much difference. They
lowered the bookie roulette because it
was 100 pound a spin and they now they
turn 100 pound 100 pound a spin to two
pound a spin. That made sense. If you
can do one pound spin in a in in a pub,
why is it capped for
£100? Why is it capped to 100? It should
be capped to a minimum of 250
quid. You know then it shouldn't be £100
in a pub. Why would it be £100 in a pub?
They're letting you do one pound spins.
So why why is our potential capp to 100
quid? I think it should be capped at 300
quid. That's what I think. I think it
should be capp to
250. Why is it
£100 when they're letting you do one pound
spin? No, no, no. [ __ ] all the repeats.
I don't give a [ __ ] about the repeats.
Why is it capped to
a£100? That's what I want to know. I
don't care if it repeats a million
times. Why is Why the [ __ ] is it capped to
£100? That's what I want to know. Why is
it capped? I don't understand. Why is it
capped? If they're letting you do one
pound spins, why is it
capped? Doesn't make sense. And another
thing that happens in these pubs, yeah,
like they give you half the money in
notes and half the money in coins and
then you've got to change the coins up.
That's what I had to do yesterday. They
gave me I think it was £60 in coins and
£50 in cash. What the [ __ ] What the actual [ __ ]
man? Doesn't make sense. You know what
I'm saying? And then you've got to go
and then get it all [ __ ] changed up
and that as [ __ ] Why is
that? It's [ __ ] weird, isn't
it? But yeah, it shouldn't be capp to
£100. It shouldn't be capped to £100.
Who agrees with me that that the pub
machine shouldn't be capped to
£100? Why are they cap to £100? For what
reason? That's what I'd like to know to
be honest. That's what I'd like to
know. They shouldn't be captain £100. What I'm saying? Yeah. [Music]
Yeah, they always make them
good-look. That that one in the queen
eye, she was
good-look. They always make him good-looking.
Yeah, they do it to te They do it to
tease you, Greasy. to tease
you. They do it to tease
you, don't they?
They were put on Earth to fetch
food. They were also put on They were
also They were also put on Earth. They
were also put on Earth to hurt people's
feelings. Music lead people on and hurt their
feelings. To lead people on and hurt
their feelings. You forgot that bit
though, Greg. They were also put on
Earth for that as well. in your face mood.
Yeah. Yeah. They were put on earth to
hurt people's feelings as well.
Oh, so it might you might see some
Blackpool videos next week if this [ __ ]
doesn't [ __ ] flake. Is that okay with you,
boss? Grievy, is that okay with you,
Some fish and chips and a bit of
Frankie. Okay with you, boss. By the
seaside. Is that okay with you,
boss? Make it
so. Okay with you,
boss. Yeah, you'll be you'll be you'll
be you'll be looking you'll be looking
forward to the mad videos, won't you,
boss? Yeah, I don't care if he reports
me, bro. Even if he gets my main band, I
don't care cuz I've got everything from
the channel saved now. So, I don't give
a [ __ ] Tell him to crack on them,
mate. Crack on them,
mate. They report you, they have to get
your channel banned cuz you own them, you
know. Yeah, it's 5 hours from me. So,
why was USA put on this earth then,
Greavesy? Why was USA put on this earth?
To toy with people's emotions. To toy
feelings. Yeah, it's only an hour. Well,
it's 5 hours for
me, but I'll be going to a few different
places. We'll see if this woman don't
flake. I can't hours to make
love. I I literally can't believe it. 5
hours just to make love.
This is This is what I'm This is what
I'm trying to say to like LJ.
Yeah. He was put on for the
streets. Yeah. For real.
Literally, he just
slagged. But listen, bro. Honestly, like
that's what I'm saying.
Five. No, no, no, no, no. But I'm
talking about making love. You can't put
a distance on making love. You know what I'm
saying? I'm going to go and make love,
man. I'm going to see Chinese Izzy since
I'm up that way. Chinese Izzy is still
with Blackpool Manchester, by the way. Steam Howard. Yeah. Yeah. [Music] [Laughter]
I don't understand how just um launch
legs can say that I've got a big nose
when I'm a million times better looking
than him. [ __ ] that big nose thing.
That's getting really really old. You
look like a rat. I'd rather have a big
nose and look like a [ __ ] rat like
you. You ugly [ __ ] You and your fat
girlfriend. Skirt. Skirt. Is that right,
Harry? The thing is I don't need to say
about your nose. I can say you got a
double chin. You can't grow a beard.
You're lanky. You're ugly. You got no
teeth. You can't grow. You're balding.
You got greasy hair. I have loads of
things to say about this ugly
[ __ ] You know, this is why you could
never ever go out with this guy, even if
he was normal, because he'd scare all
the he would scare all the women away
with his ugly face. Even if he was
normal, he'd scare all the birds away
with his ugly rat face and his
autism. He'd scare him
away. You know that [ __ ] has got worse
autism than Timmy. No, no, no, no, no.
He's got worse. He's got
worse he has got right. Yeah. Worse
autism than Timmy. Don't forget Timmy's
got other things. It's not just autism.
Nah, bro. Even Timmy's autism isn't as bad as
that. Timmy Timmy's autism isn't as bad
as that, bro.
Trust. Even Timmy's autism is not as bad
that. Yeah. He says I've got a big nose,
bro. I'm a million times better. looking
than you will ever be. You little rat
bastard. That's why I've had better
looking women than you. I've been had
better looking women than what you've
been. That's what you can't get over.
It's why you thought my floppy seconds.
Not going to get into it again. But
yeah, it's because you can't get them
cuz you're too ugly. I don't I don't
really go out anymore to be fair. You
know what I'm
saying? Yeah. You don't have a KFC near
you, Grezy. You must live in some dead
area if you ain't got a KFC near you.
I've never ever lived anywhere and
there's been no KFC near me.
Nah, nah. You must live in some [ __ ]
area, bro. [ __ ] You must live in like
Yeah, you live in a little village. You
said little village?
Yeah. I've never lived anywhere. Um,
where my sister lives lived, it was a
KFC down the road. My mom lives about
10-minute bus ride from KFC.
Stratford is about is like 10 minutes
away and then you got like
Nah, I don't think so,
bro. Yeah, I had a vindaloo yesterday.
Did you see me eating that vindaloo,
mate? Do you know why I can I can take a
vindaloo? Cuz I'm not some little Kent
virgin. If you catch my gri drip greasy,
everyone saw me munching the the the
vindaloo and I still had plenty of
cocon. I like that little
virgin. Oh, I had a lovely vindaloo,
mate. I gobbled it all up. Greasy saw it
as well. That little virgin couldn't do
it. Little YouTube obsessed virgin.
Virgin. You are a virgin.
Such a virgin. Oh my
god. YouTube obsessed little
virgin. Well, I tell you guys, that's
okay with me, boss.
Yeah. Why am I so sleepy, man?
His name is not Grezy. His name is Daniel. You
understand? His name is [ __ ]
Daniel. His name is Daniel,
bro. Daniel. Daniel. Daniel. Daniel.
Daniel. Daniel. Done.
Daniel, I'm [ __ ]
tired, Right, I'm going. Yeah, I'm
[ __ ] knacking. I'm probably going to
go back to
sleep. Oh, see you when I see you. See