[Laughter] Yeah. [ __ ]
hell. Make myself a tear in a minute.
I could argue with this guy, but I
[ __ ] fully can't be bothered, bro.
has [ __ ] no bad words to say about
women. It's It's [ __ ] a madness. It's
actually a madness. They literally have
no bad words to say about them. It's
That is actually mad. Like they do
nothing but make excuses for it. Oh,
it's [ __ ] [ __ ] pathetic. I must
have not been born with this type of
disease, this sort of white knight
disease. You know what I mean? I I must
have not been born with it. I must have
got a lucky escape.
This guy's messaging me weirdo [ __ ]
man. Oh my
god. Weirdo [ __ ] for real.
They always make excuses for women. I've
noticed that. I have actually actually
proper noticed that. And and it's not
just Reddit, right? It's it's not even
just Reddit. Like they literally don't
have no bad words to say about [ __ ]
women. It's like, you know, with Adman.
Yeah. I don't agree with everything he
says and that. Yeah. and he can get on
my tits sometimes, but he he is so right
about that. Like they have literally not
one bad word to say about women. All of
their actions are justified. You know,
you get told to like delete all of your
approaching videos as well.
Bro, like, no. I was just saying how
like these people just don't have no bad
words to say about women. Like, I'm I'm
not even talking about Reddit. Yeah. So,
I was speaking to this person from the
north. Yeah. Um for like 4 days. Found
him on Instagram. We was messaging back
and forth, back and forth, back and
forth. Right. And um then they gave me
their number and then we texted like
every day, right? And we was actually
planning to meet and then all of a
sudden, right, they blocked me on
Instagram and I've asked them why
they've blocked me on Instagram and then
they tried saying that they didn't when
I was like well I know you did. And when
I told them like I know you've done it,
they've then blocked me on like WhatsApp
as well. Like messages after after
messages after messages after arranging
to meet but they have no bad words to
say about women. Like I I literally
showed people on this uh showed people
this on Instagram and they don't have a
bad word to say about
women. You know, they say that they're
they're not sexist, but they are because
they justify everything that they do,
whether they're in the right or whether
they're in the wrong. Like somebody
would ever sit there and say to you,
"Oh, yeah, they were just a timewasting
cunt." Or, "Yeah, maybe they were just a
bit of a cunt." They would never say
that. They would never ever say that.
They'll they'll literally find things
and make up things to justify why they
do what they do. The time wasting, the
bullshitting, the lying, the leading on.
They literally have no bad words to say about
women, you know? Like literally no bad
words. They have no bad words. Yeah,
something did happen. This [ __ ] [ __ ]
wasted my [ __ ] time for three, four
[ __ ] days. That's what [ __ ]
happened. That's what happened, bro. I
started messaging her [ __ ] family and
everything, but I found her on [ __ ]
Facebook. Don't waste my time and then
lie to me like I'm some [ __ ] Yeah,
I don't I don't know who you deal with
up north. Yeah, but don't [ __ ] lie to
me, you know? Don't lie to me and waste my [ __ ] time, you
know. Is Yeah. What's it like there,
lad? No, I was just talking about this
stupid little [ __ ] Yeah, that's what
happened. And it went on for like
[ __ ] three days. I didn't go out
drinking yesterday, by the way. I told
you I wasn't. [ __ ] this [ __ ] bro. [ __ ] man. Um,
yeah. Don't know what to do today, but
I'll probably just chilling at KFC. I
probably won't even get a roast dinner
today. But yeah, they don't have
no. So yeah, they just don't have no
they just don't have no bad words to say
about women. That's what I just find.
And it's not even just Reddit. It's just
like in general they literally justify
everything that they do. Well, most
people Well, most people do. Most people
do. Just so you know, women want men to
call uh to call out bad behavior towards
them. So, don't be calling these white
white knights. It's actually what they
want. Uh no, there's a difference. White
knighting is basically somebody that
defends women just for the sake of
defending women. And it's pathetic. And
white knights are people that just don't
have a bad word to say about women, you
know. Maybe women don't want it, but
maybe women want it, but normal people
don't want it. We don't want it. It's
not normal, you know. And I don't know
when they will when will they figure out
that white nighting will never get laid.
But yeah, I'm just I just [ __ ] with
their family. I just started messaging
family, you know. I just started
messaging their family, bro. You
know, [ __ ] it, bro. I don't care, bro.
Even if I ain't met him, but I'll just
start I'll just start messaging their family and
that I'm a [ __ ] like
that. Well, what you read is [ __ ]
wrong. So why is it no one has a bad
word to say about women anyways? Cuz I
showed these screenshots about this [ __ ]
wasting my time and they were still
looking for things to blame me. Oh, you
sent two exes. Oh, you asked for a
selfie picture. Like they will literally
nitpick in kindergarten anything that
they can find just to blame you and they
will justify every single action that a
woman does. And it's not just Reddit
either. It's not just Reddit. Like they
literally make excuses for them. Like
it's it's it's crazy. Like the double
standards is the double standards is
horrific. It is. It is. And they don't
they probably don't even realize that
they're doing it as well. You know, they
literally will make up excuses and find
things that are not even there just to
defend the woman or justify what she's
done. You know, when it ain't they're
[ __ ] in this country. They're [ __ ]
in this country. This is why I don't
deal with them no more. You know, I was
only speaking to this person because
they were online and they gave me their
number and that. You think if I don't
see them around Manchester, I'd smash
them up, bro. Are you [ __ ] mad? I'll
do it in front of any [ __ ] man for
wasting my time. I would kick her teeth
down her throat in front of any man,
bro. Trust me, you don't know me. Yeah,
and we'll see what a white knight would
have to say about [ __ ] that, you
know? Just like when I was in that bar
two weeks ago, I said, "I will do it in
front of any [ __ ] man." And I said it
in front of anyone, bro. I don't care.
You know what I'm saying? It's [ __ ] annoying,
bro. You know, Manchester is a small pl.
It's a big place, but it's small at the
same time, bro. Trust me. I know a few
people around there. I know the barbers
around there. I've been there many, many [ __ ]
times. Do you know what I'm saying? It's
annoying, bro. It is [ __ ] damn right
[ __ ] annoying, bro. You know, you
know what? Next time I go to Manchester,
I'm going to put up posters. That's what
I'm going to do. I'm going to put up
posters when I go back. When Whenever I
go back to Manchester, I'm putting up
posters, bro. 100%. I'm putting up
[ __ ] posters and I'm giving a number
out as well, bro. Yeah. And trust me, a
city in England is not as big as [ __ ]
America, bro. Believe that. It's [ __ ]
annoying, bro. Who the [ __ ] do they
think they are, bro? You
know, it's not even funny. It's [ __ ]
annoying. I piss off. That's what I said
to them as well. You know, I'm going to
put all their number out there. I'm
going to make a dating profile, man.
Yeah. Simple. Cuz it's [ __ ] annoying.
Stop pissing people
off. No, didn't get rejected. Just got
this little [ __ ] wasting my [ __ ] time.
Nope. And what do you mean again? I've
had more women than you would ever have,
mate. Just go on my YouTube channel.
Just go on my YouTube channel and it
will show you all you need to know. I'm
just not a white knight. I don't have
that disease. I wasn't born with that
condition. I'm one of the only people
that wasn't born with that condition
where I lick women's
asses. You know, I still, Joe, I want to
be proven wrong, bro. I thought this was
a person to prove me wrong. I want
somebody to prove me wrong. And I will
never ever complain again. I will still
tell these people they're [ __ ] when
they're [ __ ] and they're wrong when
they're wrong. But in terms of me
actually complaining, never again. When
somebody in this country proves me
wrong, I I will never ever say any bad
thing again. As in like I won't vent
about it, but I'll still tell them
they're wrong when they're wrong and
they were [ __ ] when they were [ __ ] I
want to be proven wrong by one person,
by one woman that they're not all like
this. I want the evidence, you know, cuz
I've been hearing now that they're not all the
same. I want actual I want to be shown
different, bro. I want to be shown
different, but I can't because they're
all the same. All these westernized
people are all the same. Liars, devious,
cheaters, money grabbers. They're
literally all the same in these westernized
countries. They are all the [ __ ] same
in these westernized countries. They are
never They're never different, lad.
Yeah, I'll be single for life like you
and I'll be Yeah, but at least I won't
be a virgin like you. And I told you
you're going to be a virgin for the rest
of your life. That's even worse, you
silly little [ __ ] And I told you, G,
that you're going to be a virgin
forever. So stop lying that you keep
seeing this X when you don't see this X.
I [ __ ] told you that you're going to
die a virgin as well. You silly little
[ __ ] You silly little [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, [ __ ] it. I'm on a maza, bro. Like,
trust me. When I go when I go back to
Manchester, I'm doing it, bro. 100%. I'm
doing it. Like I said, I don't know when
I'll be back, but I'll be doing it. I'll
be doing it. I'll be doing them posters,
bro. 100%. Number posters,
everything. I go I know whereabouts
where they live as well. Yeah, he was
with her last night. Yeah. So, why you
on here every day then? If you see an X
every day, why why are you on here? What
if you see X? Why are you why you want
to hear every day then?
as well on here. Bro, I'm not going to
sit here I'm not going to sit here and
argue with you all day, mate, about the
about this subject. There's this gay guy
messaging me, bro. I'm literally I am
literally literally literally not going
to sit here and argue with you all day.
Do you know what I'm saying, Grezy? Some
women are [ __ ] but how can you be
saying all this madness when you make
your intentions clear? You want to make
a do see again you're white knighting
again. See white knighting again. I have
literally shown you evidence of what
these women have done and you're still
trying to victimize them. You're still
trying to victimize them. Okay, let me
let me tell you a story cuz I want I
want Greavves excuse for this one
because they've always got excuses when
it comes to women. And if they don't
have an excuse, best believe they're
going to [ __ ] find one. So, let me
tell you this. This person was speaking
to me for 3 days from Instagram. They
gave me their number. We was talking
back and forth, back and forth, back and
forth, back and forth, back and forth.
They were supposed to meet me and then
all of a sudden they well next week
actually when all of a sudden sending me
voice notes, all of this, and then all
of a sudden they blocked me on
Instagram. And then I said to them, "Why
have you blocked me on Instagram? That's
a bit weird." And they trying to say
that they didn't block me on Instagram.
Ret t um and uh yeah how they didn't
block me and I was like well you did cuz
I'm sat here with my friend. Um so what
I'm going to do and then and then and
then when I told them I know you've done
it then they blocked me on WhatsApp as
well. What was the excuse for that one?
All that leading on all of that was what
was the excuse that time? But I'm going
to go Manchester anyway some point this
year. So, it's it's not a problem. And I
will be putting up
posters, you know, and I can assure you,
you are all the [ __ ] same because
when I'm the day until I'm proven
different, my opinion
stands. Yeah. Waste of my time. Don't
worry, bro. I messaged her family
anyways. You know, I found her family
and I'm going to put up posters of her as
well. You know what I'm saying? I'm
going to put up posters of her when I
come back as well.
So, uh, sorry when I go back to
Manchester, so it's all good, bro. Yep.
Always the man's fault, is it? What do
you mean it takes two to tango? I was
talking to her because she said she
wanted to [ __ ] meet and I thought I
was going to get pro and I thought I was
going to get proven wrong. I I thought
this is the person that's going to prove
me wrong, but that's never going to happen, is
it? That's never going to happen. I'm
never going to be proven wrong. They're
all the same. these westernized people.
I just I said to her family that she's a
slag. Your daughter's a [ __ ] slag.
Little time waster. And
yeah. So that's it. And they they were
the same age as me, same age, same
hobbies. I was like, "Okay, well maybe
this person's a bit different because
they live in Manchester. They don't have
many options." Um so yeah. um uh people
with uh because Manchester, you know,
even if it means doesn't mean that the
person that you you know, you find is
always going to be in the same city as
you. So, I thought, okay, well, maybe
this person that you haven't met all
these years live in Manchester. Like,
and it's so mad cuz like I get I get no,
she didn't know my real name, so don't
start trying to use YouTube as an
excuse. Stop trying to use YouTube as an
excuse when they found out all these
things that I've said because they
haven't. So stop. Don't even try and use
that as an excuse. I know where you're
going with that. Don't even try and use
that as an excuse. So I'm just going to
put up posters of her when I'm back in
Manchester. So it's cool, bro. Don't
[ __ ] take the piss out of me, bro.
Don't take the [ __ ] piss out of
me. You know, you're lucky that I'm not
half an hour away from there cuz I would
have went today and done it. You know,
I'm not a [ __ ] bro. So stop [ __ ]
Anyway, so and I just thought, okay,
yeah, well, it doesn't mean if if
there's someone for you that they're
just going to be in London. It might be,
man. And they weren't even going to be
easy as well. I would have had to go all
the way there. It's [ __ ] long, you
know. Yeah. You keep telling yourself
that, Jill. You keep telling yourself
that. If it helps you play with yourself
at night, you keep telling yourself
that. I'm not listening to none of it
until I'm proven different. My opinion
stay the same. I actually I thought this
person was actually going to prove me
wrong. I actually thought this person
was going to prove me wrong, but nope.
They're the same old westernized [ __ ]
It doesn't matter where it is. London,
Manchester, Liverpool, [ __ ] Scotland,
Wales, they're all the same westernized
[ __ ] Yep. Again. Yep. White Knighting
again. Yep. Here we go. White Knighting
again. Trying to use my after reaction
as to what she's done. Yep. White
Knighting. This is exactly what I'm
talking about. Look. Okay, but ghosting
you is a right decision anyways because
look how scummy you get. See, this is
exactly what I'm saying. This it's white
nighting. They use your reaction to be
having your time wasted as the cause.
See, they do nothing but make excuses
for women. This is exactly what I'm
talking about. They literally will just
defend women all day long. There's no
bad words they can say about them. This
is exactly what I'm talking about. I'm
I'm [ __ ] reacting like this because
this [ __ ] wasted my time in the first
place. You know that's not personality.
That's because I've had my time wasted.
You little s [ __ ] You little white
knight. Because I've had my [ __ ] time wasted, [ __ ]
Yeah, I am scummy. Why? Because I'm
pissed off that somebody wasted my time.
Oh, sorry, mate. I've got I've got a
I've got the worst personality in the
world because a woman took the piss out
of me and wasted my time. Sorry for
reacting to it. By all means, I
apologize. I I I will make a video right
now. Right. I will literally Yeah.
Exactly, Jill. Exactly. And it wasn't
her rejecting me cuz she didn't reject
me cuz she didn't know me. It was her
wasting my [ __ ] time, you know? And
it was her wasting my [ __ ] time.
Yeah. Exactly, bro. Sorry. But like I
said, I'm sorry that I'm pissed off that
somebody wasted my time for 3 days. I am
very, very, very sorry. You know, I will
make a video for like making it 10
minutes long apologizing that, oh, I'm
so sorry. This person wasted my time,
you know. Oh, I'm sorry, bro. I'm very,
very sorry. And Jill, this is the reason
I don't go out no more. This is the
reason I don't go out drinking anymore,
approaching anymore. I was out with my
friend on Friday and we ain't seen each
other since summer. He come down to
London. Yeah. And we was drinking. And I
was like, "Bro, as much as I'd love to
stay out with you, I might need to go to
Manchester next week to meet this
person." You know, I was putting
priorities I was putting putting um
priorities first, right? So, I was like,
"Oh, I might need to like go to
Manchester, so I need to sort of save a
bit of money. I don't want to be on a
little bit of a detox and stuff in it."
And it was hard to leave him as well
because we was having like a good time.
But I said to him like, "Yeah, I would
have stayed out with you all night, bro.
But I don't go out doing this." And you
know why I don't do this anymore? I tell
you why I don't go out approaching
anymore drinking. It's not because that
I've got a boyfriend. I don't give a
[ __ ] about that, you know, because it
saves you loads and loads of time. The
[ __ ] that pisses me off, I've said this
once and I will say it again, is when
you go out drinking, right? You get
these numbers. So, you spent a bit of
money, okay, and you've got these
numbers, okay? And then you message them
in the morning, right? And then they
lead you on, lead you on, lead you on.
And this goes on about to about three
days to about a week. And then all
you've done is spent money, you've got a
hung over, and you're back to square one
again. And so what are you going to go
out every single week and do the same
thing all over again? I'm not doing it.
I'm not doing it again. [ __ ] off. I'm
not doing it. That's one of the reasons
I didn't go out on Saturday. I'm not
doing it again. I'm not doing it again.
Doing this [ __ ] again, approaching
and having to do it again next week,
getting a hangover. I'm not doing it again.
Simple. I'm not doing it again. That's
why I don't bother no more. I need to
get my passport. I need to get my
passport renewed as well. So, like, I'm
not doing it. I'm not doing it for a
very very very very long time, bro. You
think I couldn't go out yesterday
sending it. It doesn't matter what I
think. I'm not getting into this
conversation with you. You're you're a
white knight. You're a s. Go away. No
one cares. And I can show you all of
these combos as well. like if you ever
want to see it,
but and it's like you must be really
really bored and sick in the head to
waste someone's time for 3 days sending
voicemail. You must be really really
really sick in your head. Like cuz no
normal person would do it. Like think
about it. Yeah. Regardless of me and
what I've said and read, you must be
really sick in your head. Like to do
that every day for three, four months
just to [ __ ] somebody else in the end.
Like you must be really, really sick in their
head. They must be really, really sick
in their head. But guess what's going to
happen, Jill? You know what this
person's going to say? I tell you what
this person's going to say. They're
going to say that all men are the same.
Where were the nice guys gone? All you
had to do was meet me outside a [ __ ]
hotel in [ __ ] Manchester. You know,
it wouldn't have cost you nothing. Do
you know what I'm
saying? No, we don't need to we don't
need to react to anything in the correct
way. I am done. Simple, mate. I am done
in this country. Get [ __ ] Literally,
get absolutely [ __ ] Oh, I'm not a
nice guy, am I? Okay. So, I took this
[ __ ] [ __ ] in America for a meal. I
bought them wine. I was nice to them.
all of these other people, but I'm not a
nice guy. Okay. Okay. Why? Because I
because I'm pissed off when people try
to take the piss out of me. Hold on. So,
when people try to take the piss out of
me and I react to it, that means I'm not
nice. Really, bro? Think about what you're [ __ ]
saying. Anyways, you know, you're always
going to defend women and you're always
going to make excuses for women. So,
like there's no there's literally no
point me even even reacting. There's no
point me even talking because you are
always always going to defend women no
matter what. So there's there's no point
when you with these people Jill you're
wasting your time arguing with them.
You're you're wasting your time being a
consistent being a contestant because at
the end of the day these people will re
will just do nothing but defend women
all their life. That's all they have to
their name. So there's no point arguing
with them because we all know we all
know that if I was sat here ranting
about a man, they'd be like, "Men are
pricks. Get up there, son." But then
when it's to do with you complaining
about a woman wasting your time, it's a
completely 360. Oh, you're a scum.
You're an insurer. Like I've I've done
so many experiments on this and the
double standards is, like I said, is
horrific. Is horrific. You know, and
then they blame things like, "Oh, you
want them for sex?" No, I don't. And
what about all the women that want men
for sex? There's a lot of women out
there that want men for sex. What about
them people, uh, Greasy? What about
women that want men for sex? What about
women What about women that want men for
sex? We never hear about them people.
And boy, they're out there. And boy,
they're out there. We never hear about
them, do we? Huh? Another double
standard. And no, we didn't talk about
sex once, me and this person in
Manchester. We was talking about going
out, eating food, and drinking. Yeah,
sex was not even mentioned
once. You know, I literally wouldn't
have cared if they met me and didn't
meet me again because I'm in Manchester
on a [ __ ] Friday. I don't give a
[ __ ] I can still go out and talk to
people. Do you think I would have cared
if I met them and they didn't meet again
or they went I would have just I would
have just stayed and and just started
sending it cuz I'm there anyways. It's
Friday. It's quite cheap, you know. I
wouldn't have bothered if they actually
had met. You know, at least it would
have [ __ ] gave you some hope. I would
have just stayed in
Manchester then went to Blackpool or I
would have stayed there for a little bit, you
know, but nothing will ever change in
this country. I think that's the crux of it.
But yeah, funny enough, I didn't get a
hangover on when I went out on Friday.
Not sure why, but I
didn't. But yeah, they will always make
um a second, bro. I need counseling. I
need better experiences.
mother to say about women. It's [ __ ]
mad. My experience is all a reflection
of you. You would say that you little white
knight. Okay. So, what about all of them
normal approaching videos where they
pretended they have a boyfriend? What
about all of them messages that I put up
where they were completely normal and
then they flaked? That was totally me.
Yeah. What? Every single one of them?
So, every single one of them them
approaching videos and every single one
of them messages was a reflection of me.
That's exactly what a white knight would
say. That is exactly what a white knight
would say. It's not even a simp. It's
just white knighting.
Yeah. Okay. So, so all of the
experiences Okay. Okay. So, all of the
experiences that I've had with women, I
was to blame on every single one of
them. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let's let's let's let's go let's go back
a bit. So, every single one of these
things was because of me. Every single
one of them. Really? And you call
yourself not a white knight? Mate, go
and [ __ ] yourself. Simple.
Every single one of them only creepy
people do approaching. Okay. Do you want
me to explain to you why I do
approaching again? Um because you
obviously are quite a simpleton. Um so
do you want me to explain to you again
why I approach
um simpleton? I don't mind. I've got all
day. It's a Sunday. and I'll explain to
you like the simpleton that you clearly
are despite you claiming that you're
probably not a simpleton. Does Does
Peter want to explain to Simpleton again
what what's the purpose of
approaching? I can explain it to you. I
can explain it to you very very quickly.
Simple Tim, if you want me to explain it
to you, Simple
Tim, I'll explain it to you
again. I don't know why I have to
explain it again, but yeah. Oh, they
rejected me because of me. Oh, okay.
Okay. So, it was my fault every single
time. Whoa, that's hard to believe.
Every single time. Oh, okay. So, every
every single time. Ah, I wonder if I was
gay if you'd be saying that. H I've got
no job and zero social skills. I have
more money and I make more money than
you will ever have. And I've got more
social skills than you will ever have.
So, stop talking about yourself, bro.
You You have got nothing in your life
but white nighting over women. You're
probably still a virgin that lives with
your mommy. Sorry, your mama. You're
your mama. No money, no job, no friends.
M. I get more money than you would ever
imagine. Yeah. That's the crux of not
knowing anyone that you're talking
about. Yeah. You don't know me. You
don't know what friends I have. You
don't know how much money I have and how
much money I get a month. You don't know
nothing about me, bro. You're the one
that sat there with mommy's basement
happened to be a white knight, yet
you're still a virgin. Because isn't it
mad how all of these people that defend
women have never had a woman? And that's
why they think defending women will get
them women because they've got no life
experience. They've got absolutely no life
experiences. Yeah, I'm a bit of loser. A
bit of loser that gets more money than
you. That's had more women than you. But
I've never had to lick no woman's ass.
Anyways, bye-bye now.
Yep. Bye-bye now.
I think yeah it's in like I think it's
in your best interest to just give up in
this country like honestly like honestly
I I generally think right that is your
in your best interests you
know well anyone who's struggling or
most people are struggling I would just
I would just not deal with it anymore
and and that's the reason I didn't go
out yesterday cuz I don't want to deal
with them no more. You know, even if I
get what I want, I want to get away from
it. You know what I'm trying to say? I
want to get away from this [ __ ] You
know, you know what I'm saying,
bro? I wanted to get away from this [ __ ] [ __ ]
But if you notice, they're all the same
scum. Like Morgan, this one from
Manchester, like all of these other
people, like the French one. If you've
noticed, right, over the years, no
matter how many people you met, they
were all similar. Unless they were very,
very, very, very old. Um, you know, like
in their 40s or in their 50s, you'll
notice that they were all literally the
same. And if you notice, like all of
their interests are the same as well.
Cuz if they're not all the same, why is
it so hard to find somebody that's not
an evil [ __ ] time waster? Think of it.
If they were really, really, really
different, why do you meet so many that
are the same? Doesn't add up.
And you'll never find him on the street
either because they all pretending they got
boyfriends. Yeah. I'm not going to lie,
bro. This was pissing me off yesterday.
I was like I was trying to be positive
and think, "Oh, this person is different, you
know? You know what I'm saying? Oh, this
person should be will be different. This
person will be different." But they're
never different. They're never
different. They always prove you right
every single time. Deep down. Yep. Yeah.
Yeah. So that's how it is, bro.
That's how it is, bro. Looking good as
well. But don't it always I don't know
why you always get sucked into thinking
that this person's different, that
person's different. They're all the
same. I think it's deep down you're
you're you're you're lying to yourself.
I think deep down you're lying to
yourself and you're wanting the best,
but you know deep down that it's England
and they're all the same in England,
just like how they're all the same in
America as well. And they will always be
the same. No matter what women that you
come across in these westernized
countries, they will all be the same.
Everything that they do is so
predictable. You can predict it. Bro, if
I if if there was a a bet market in
William Hill or any other bookies and I
could I could put money on what a woman
would do, mate. I'd be like Richard
Branson. I'd be a billionaire. If I
could bet everything, right, I would
know exactly what they could they they
do. Fake interest one day, lose interest
the next day, flake on you. I I know
everything that they do now, you know. It's it's
predictable. Do you know what? I might I
might talk to one of the bookies and and
and offer that to me a bet market, you
know, and I would rinse all of them
bookies because I I already know what
these women are like. I know what they
do, you know.
Yeah. Make a tea in a
minute. So, I need to get that renewed.
So, I'll probably go out one more time
cuz I want to go out drinking
anyways. And then
um and then
um yeah, I need to renew this passport.
Probably do it in the next day. Probably.
Yeah. It's a sad life, isn't it? It's a
sad sad sad sad life. There's two things
that ruin this country. The women and the
weather. The weather and the women, they
completely ruin this country. Ruin it.
You know, it's sad, isn't it? It is
very, very, very
sad. You know, it's very, very, very,
very sad. If the weather was better and
the women were
better, this would be a lovely country.
It'd be not a bad country, you know,
lenient laws and stuff, but them them
two things together just ruin it. That's
why everyone's depressed. That's why the
suicide rate is very high in these
countries. But in Asia, you never hear
about people killing themselves, you know.
have these weirdos messaging me,
bro. No, I don't think it's just the women.
So yeah, no, I don't think it's just the
women. I think it's multiple things they
killed themselves. Weather, women, all of them things, you
know, but you do defend women quite a
lot, Grezy. You do you do defend them
quite a lot. You really really really do.
Yeah, I was really tempted to go out
yesterday and seriously harm
someone. Is the host special needs? No,
but your special needs. Bye-bye
now. Yeah, I was really tempted to go
out and do some damage yesterday.
Uh Grezy, like I was so tempted to do
some [ __ ] damage, bro. I'm not even
joking. To do some damage, bro.
I felt like going out and beating someone up.
know what I'm saying,
bro. So, you you need to go on these
dating apps soon. Uh, Grey, you need to
go on these dating apps
soon. I'm so glad I didn't go out
yesterday, bro. I'm so glad I didn't go out yesterday.
But I think I'm going to have to leave
England, bro, and start a start a life
fresh. See, cuz if it see like if you
like you can live in Manchester. See, if
I met that
person, if I met that person in
Manchester, bro, like for like
theoretically speaking, right, and you
met them, you could have easily just
like rented a house. It's a lot cheaper
over there. It's a city, you know, and
you'd be making so much [ __ ] money.
You know what I'm saying, bro? Cuz it's
a lot cheaper there. But it seems I need
to move out of England and start a new
life somewhere cuz this is this is no
good, bro. This is no
good. Who's we? The spastics off
YouTube. No one cares about the I quote
we. You're all spastics. They ain't got a life.
So yeah. Yeah. Us the spastics. Bye-bye now. [ __ ]
bongos. But yeah, I need to start a a
life somewhere else, bro. It seems
Another boring day, eh?
Yeah. Bye-bye. Now go to church. Why
would I go to church? I'm not religious.
atheist. I'm atheist, bro. Why' I go to
church? Why' I go to church? Huh?
I need Jesus. I need better experiences.
Why do I need Jesus? Because I'm pissed
off because of what women
do, you know? Why do I Why Why would I need
Jesus? Kitty is is mentally ill. I've
I've been hearing about this the, you
know, the first the past couple of days
and stuff. Kitty is actually mentally
ill. I'm just pissed off because of
these negative experiences. I think
that's completely normal. Having your
[ __ ] time wasted having these people
take the piss out of you. Well, Jesus is
wrong. Well, Jesus is very, very wrong.
And that's why I'm not religious because Jesus is
wrong. Cuz if that was the case, then
there wouldn't be loads of people having
kids. There wouldn't be so many couples
if if it wasn't important to have a woman.
So Jesus is very very wrong. Jesus doesn't exist
either. What's my channel about? Um so
I've got a main channel. Just different
things. Gambling, approaching women, all
sorts of stuff, man.
It's just a mixture of things. Yeah.
Yeah, that's nice. Well, women hate me
and gambling. I don't really gamble much
anymore. So, I don't really I I don't
really gamble much
anymore. So, cuz it' give me mood swings and
stuff. Make me going mad. I mean, I do
the football bet every Saturday, but
that's it. on 20 pound I put on the
football but I don't really gamble like
roulette I haven't played roulette in
[ __ ] ages like live roulette and yeah
I don't really gamble more
basically well no it's gambling because
there's gambling content on my main
channel. There's g No, because there's
gambling content on my main
channel. I probably just won't get out
of bed today, bro. I'll just be depressed. Yep. Oh, [ __ ] me.
Yeah, it sucks in it, man. But nothing
you can do,
eh? It's a depressing life here in
England. I tell you that much.
It's a depressive life here in
England. Eat once a day. Probably just
have KFC or something.
Yeah. It's a depressant life here in
England. You tell me. I was speaking to
one for 3 days. We were supposed to meet
and then they blocked me randomly out of
nowhere. We were sending voice notes,
messages, voice notes, messages. And all
of a sudden they just blocked me. They
blocked me on Instagram and I asked them
why they blocked me on Instagram and
then they tried denying it saying how
they've deleted their Instagram cuz they
needed a break from it. But I was like,
"No, I know you've deleted me." And then
when I told her I know she blocked me,
me. So she just wasted my [ __ ] time
and we were supposed to meet next week.
So yeah, it's a depressive life here in
England. I tell you that for nothing.
The women, the weather, nothing ever
changes. That's one thing that's
guaranteed with England. Nothing ever
changes. So yeah, it sucks.
Yeah, plenty more fish and all that.
Yeah. Yeah, there's plenty more fish,
isn't there? Plenty more uninterested,
devious lion fish, maybe, but nothing
else. That's probably about the only
fish you'll get in this country, mate,
is time wasting little liars and people
that pretend they got boyfriends. Just
the same old England. Well, at least I
know what country I'm in. There's no uh
there's no doubt. There's no there's no
doubt about that.
At least I know what country I'm in. I'm
in England. What they call Great Britain
where there's nothing great about
it. Yeah. Plenty more fish.
Yeah. That's that's a banger to be
honest. Like this is why I didn't go out
yesterday cuz I knew it was going to be
exactly the same [ __ ] That's exactly
why I didn't go out drinking yesterday
cuz I know it's always going to be the
same [ __ ] in this country. It will
always be the same [ __ ]
Nothing would ever
change. Nothing would ever
change. Yeah. Hopefully I die in my
sleep today. I was actually feeling
better for a couple of days until this
[ __ ] pissed me
off. Yeah. Hopefully I can die in my sleep.
just to put up some posters. Have I
tried changing my technique and
approach? Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Have
you bothered watching my approaches?
Have you even bothered to watch my
approaches or you just so ignorant that you probably
haven't? Yep. It doesn't make a
difference. They're just not interested in this
country. This is something it took me 27
years to realize and now I'm just about
to renew my passport as well. They're
just not interested in this country.
There's nothing that you're going to
say. There's nothing that you're going
to do that's going to make a
difference. Okay. One second. I'll show
you some of my approach. Oh, okay. Well,
welcome to the channel. One second.
Uh, the channel, right? One
second. I'll show you some approaches,
lad. Uh, with the way that I look, I'm
better looking than you will ever
be. You little keyboard warrior. Yeah,
I'm better looking than you will ever
ever ever ever ever ever ever ever be.
You little self projector. Anyways, uh
to you that's new to the channel, um
here's the approach. The way I look, I'm
better looking than you will ever be,
mate. I'm a model compared to you.
Anyways, Houseb, you said you're new to
the channel. Welcome to the channel, mate.
that one. There you go. That's some approaching
videos. Yeah, Tilly, did you see them
screenshots that I showed
you? I might go to Manchester and put up some
posters. I might actually go out and put
up some posters, but I'm not going to
lie to you,
bro. Not today, but I'm considering it,
bro. It's only like 2 and 1 half hour.
It's like 4 hours away, but it'd be worth
it. Well, I'd probably do it before I
leave. Yeah. What's your opinion on it?
What's your opinion on it,
Chilly? Them uh
screenshots. She's a [ __ ] [ __ ] in
it. It's all right. I'm putting up
posters of them anyways. I'm going to
put up posters of them and put their
number out there. So, it's all good, bro.
I'm going to put up numbers of them and
put up um put put up post of them and
give their number out. Yeah. So, that's one
approach. This is the second approach.
So, you get get the you'll get the you
get the gist of it. Basically,
uh she doesn't have a boyfriend. uh
house bells. Um they use having a
boyfriend as an excuse all the time.
Yeah, obviously you're new to this
channel. Um most of the time when they
say they've got a boyfriend, they don't
have a boyfriend. I'm not going to sit
here and argue with you how I know they
don't have boyfriend because it's a
waste of my time and it's a waste of
your time. Um unfortunately, they lie
about having boyfriends time and time
and time and time
again. Right? And I'm not gonna tell you
how I know. And I'm not gonna get into
this pointless argument because it's
boring, right? I've been doing this now
for years and years and years in
different environments, right? Dealing
these time wasters. And I've come to the
conclusion that all women are literally
the same. They say they're not and say,
but they are because they always they
always prove why would a lie why would a
girl lie to you about having a
boyfriend? Why would a a girl lie to you
about having a boyfriend um to get away
from you, to reject you, so she doesn't
have to give you her number? Cuz she
thinks that she's better than you. So if
she says that she has a boyfriend, then
she thinks you're going to be okay,
whatever. Why would they lie about
having a boyfriend? They're [ __ ]
The women in this country are
[ __ ] No, just they think that
they're better than you. No, not not
because she's not attracted to you. Um,
it's because they think that they're
better than you. That's why they say
they've got boyfriends because they
think that they're better than you. Oh,
this just [ __ ] We're just talking
about this [ __ ] in Manchester that
wasted my time for three
days, you know. No, it's not unlucky.
No, no, no, Tilly. It's not unlucky.
It's just the [ __ ] in this country.
They're just [ __ ] in this country. It's
not about me being unlucky or lucky.
They're just [ __ ] [ __ ] in this country.
And is that really what you want to call
it? Unlucky. What about How about the
women being [ __ ] How about that? How
about that woman from Manchester being a
[ __ ] any I don't think that's unlucky.
I just think that's her being a
[ __ ] I just think that's her being a
[ __ ] Why aren't they ever with their
boyfriends? Because their boyfriends don't
exist. That's why they're never with
their boyfriends because their
boyfriends don't exist.
So that's why you never see their
boyfriends because how can you how can
they be seen with something that doesn't
exist? It's impossible. It's like being
seen with Casper the
ghost. Anyways, it's not my problem
anymore. Anyways, I'm renewing this
passport and I'm leaving this country.
I've had it up to [ __ ] ear with it,
mate. You know, cuz I was getting some
[ __ ] sick nasty thoughts yesterday,
bro. like going out and seriously doing
something to someone and and I shouldn't
have to keep dealing with this. So I
thought, "Fuck it." And man's like,
"They're not worth it. They're not worth
it. They're not worth it. I'm not I'm
not doing this no more, lad.
Bye-bye. Am I a cunt?" Well, why don't
you talk about that woman from
Manchester being a
[ __ ] Why don't you ever Why don't you
ever say these women are [ __ ]
cuz you ain't got a bad
word. Yeah, but I'm not ugly. No, no,
no, no, no. But they can't say that I'm
ugly because I'm not ugly. But I'm not
ugly. So, how can they say that you're
ugly? 30-year-old incel virgin. Oh,
that's self projection. Bye-bye. Go
self-reflect on another channel. You are
a 40-year-old virgin in cell and I'm not
ugly. So, at the end of the day, why
would they say I think you're ugly when
I'm subject objectively not
ugly, you know, and I'm not going to sit
here and argue about my looks, you know?
So, that's the point. No, no, no, no.
Hell's bells. If I was ugly, I wouldn't
I would know where I stand. If I was
ugly, I would know where I stand. But
you're not ugly. So, what's their
problem? They think they're better than
you. It's got to be like they have to
be. It has to be that too many stuck up
[ __ ] in this country. Well, if they
aren't, I'm not going to I'm not going
to get into this conversation. It's
boring now. I'm done with this
conversation. I'm not going to This is
not a conversation about my looks. You
know what I'm saying? I'm not going to
have this conversation again about my
looks. It's boring. It's just boring.
I'm not This is not turning into whether
I'm ugly or not. You know, we're not
having this conversation. I'm done with
it now. It's boring. like it's not my problem anymore
anyways because as soon as I get my um
passport renewed I'm I'm getting out of
here. So I'm not this is not my problem
anymore. This is not my problem anymore,
bro. So yeah, Mikey know I was speaking
to somebody off Instagram for 3 days.
They gave me their number. They gave me
their number and then they we arranged
to meet and then they blocked me on
Instagram and tried and lied that they
blocked me on Instagram and then when I
said I know you've blocked me they
blocked me on WhatsApp
too and this is exactly why I don't
waste my time in this country anymore.
This was only somebody on Instagram as
well. This was only somebody on Instagram.
So it's not my problem anymore anyways
cuz I won't be here when I renew this
passport. So it's all good, you know. So yeah.
So that's it. It's not going to be my problem no
more. They're sick in the head, Mikey.
They lead somebody on and and and waste
their time and your time for 3 days. But
no one has a bad word to say about women.
They were trying to make up all sorts of
excuses because I sent them two
exes. Um, like they would always, what
we were saying earlier is that how they
always defend women, whether they're in
the right or whether they're in the
wrong, they will always sit there and
make excuses for
them. They will sit there and do nothing
but make excuses for them. And it's not
just Reddit. So that's why like when I
know I'm speaking to a white knight, I
just don't waste my time, you know, or
somebody that just don't have no bad
words to say about women. It's
pointless, bro. What you arguing over,
you know? It's stupid, man. You
know, so yeah.
It's a depressing life though. It is a
life. There was a way out of
it, you know.
Well, killing yourself is a way of it, but
yeah. I was trying to be positive as
well, thinking that, oh, this person
might be different, but I always get proven
wrong. I always get proven wrong again. You
know, they're never the same. And these
women in this country will never will
never change. They're all the same.
They're all westernized. It will never
change. You know, all they're going to
do is lead you on. All they're going to
do is lead you on. Even when you get a
number, all they're going to do is lead
you on and ghost you. So, it's like
there's no point even going out and
getting a number. There's no point you
even going out and getting a
number. Um, I would like to know why
they're not interested. Okay. So, I'll
give an example. I'll give an example.
So, I had a one night stand with this um
person that was visiting um from um from
America and like I hooked up with them
and they were leading me on and saying,
"Oh, come to America, see me." All this
false hope and then they blocked me. So
then I reached out on another number and
I said like, "Why are you lying to my
friend?" And then they said, "Oh, I'm
sorry. I'm just not interested." I said,
"That's not good enough." And I asked
them why they're not interested. And
then they didn't give me an answer. So,
I just started messaging their family
and [ __ ] with them. Made them split up
with their boyfriend, made them change
their number. Like, we I want to know
why you're not
interested. And at the end of the day is
you are the same people that moan, "Oh,
where have all the nice guys gone? I
can't find a nice guy." And then when
somebody lo and behold, comes your way,
you say you're not interested. And then
you moan and moan and moan and moan and
moan and moan and moan and moan again.
Sorry. So that's what
happens just like this person in
Manchester. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You don't lead somebody on and then
sleep with them and then try to say that
you're not interested. No, no. And then
be a [ __ ] about it.
Like I ruined her life, bro. I made her
go please for me. I made her change her
number, her WhatsApp number. I literally
[ __ ] her life up, bro. Because that
will teach you forever being a little
[ __ ] ever again. And to be fair, since
then, I should have just gave up. I
should have just gave up from then and
be like, "Oh, I'm I'm giving up in this
country." Like then I should have gave
up. After that, two years ago, I should
have just gave up cuz it was never going
to change. These women are never going
to change. It will always be the same
old. Whether it's a bar, whether it's a
club, whether it's the street, whether
it's a dating app, it's not my problem
no more. You know, it's not my problem
no more. Yeah.
It's not my problem though,
Mar. And no, no, no, no, no. But do you
know what hell's bells? Yes, you are
making experience of men worse. And and
and that's what I want to happen because
I don't want no man to experience what I
experienced with these women. It's the
same thing with that one in Manchester,
right? If I go to Manchester and I put
up posters and I [ __ ] with them, I don't
want them speaking to other men. I don't
want other ever um any other men to get
hurt, you know? I that's that's the
example I'm trying to make so you don't
be a [ __ ] to anyone ever again. Cuz if
you're a [ __ ] and you're a [ __ ] to a
man, right, I don't want you to be a
[ __ ] to any other man. That's what I
want. like what I done with that person
in America. I don't want them to ever
ever do it to anyone ever again, you
know? To the point where I made them
split up with their [ __ ] boyfriend,
[ __ ] change their number. I wanted
all that to happen. So, you learn, you
know what I'm saying? Like these
westernized [ __ ] they need to
learn, you know? They need to learn to
not they can't go around doing this
[ __ ] You know what I'm saying?
So their their experience, but but the
thing is but the thing is is that I was
speaking to somebody on Instagram
yesterday and they were saying about how
you're this but they scumbags are the
ones that they go for. They they go for
men abusers. They go for scumbags. So
they contradict yourself. They
contradict themselves when they try to
say, "Oh, you're this. You're that.
You're this. You're that." Because bro,
if you was really all of them nasty
things, they would be with you because
they only go for scumbags, drug dealers.
tattoo people, [ __ ] scumbags,
pedophiles, they're the only people that
women go for. So going by their logic,
if you was this mad negative [ __ ]
right? Then well, they'd be with you. So
it doesn't make any sense cuz they're
the only people that they go for around
England. They're the only people that
they go for.
It's either a black man, a drug dealer,
a white guy with tattoos all over his
neck, or some [ __ ] nons. That's the
only people that they're interested
in. So, yeah. Yeah. Good. Good. And
that's good, though. And that's good.
Just like we're wary of women because of
their actions. Just like we couldn't get
attached for two years. Yeah. Just like
we couldn't get attached to women for
two years because of their actions. Hey,
tit for tat to catch it on the [ __ ]
mat. Just like they ruined certain dates
for us because of our experiences
because of them. It works both ways.
Yeah, it works both
ways. It works both ways. ways. Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
So yeah, that's why I don't I can't be
bothered, bro. Like they obviously have
the same type in England that they go
for. So [ __ ] it. I need to try other countries.
No, no. I just thought I found somebody
that wasn't a complete [ __ ] [ __ ] you
know, they were the same [ __ ] age as
me and yeah, okay, they live in a
different city. I would have gone to
another city next week. It's not a
problem. And I thought, oh, okay, wow,
finally I've stopped drinking now and
now I found something that seems
genuine, not getting attached. How can I
get attached to someone I don't like and
I don't know? And then look, they prove
to be the same again. They prove to be
again on Instagram. On Instagram, they
reply back to me replying replying. They
gave me I said, "Oh, let's do
something." They gave me their number,
talking for 3 days and out of the blue
blocked me on Instagram, lied about
doing it, then blocked me on WhatsApp.
What's the [ __ ] point,
bro? How can I get attached to someone
I've never met, but I would have liked
to have gone and met them considering
they [ __ ] led you on for three
[ __ ] days, as they always do, you
know? Yeah, there was another French one
that was trolling me the other day.
What would you have rated her out of 10?
Maybe a seven, eight. Yeah, they would
troll you as well, Harry. These women
would also troll you as well. If you
left your bed sit and you started
talking to women, they would troll you
as well. You're no different. You'd
probably even get it worse than me cuz
you're older. You're no different. Your
experience would be no different. Yeah.
Just like 95% of people in this
country's experiences are no different.
you would also get it as well. You would
also get rejected. You would also offer
money and get rejected. You would be the same, you
know. But no, I'm not doing it no more,
bro. I'm not going out anymore to
disrespect myself. I'm getting this
passport, dude, and I'm leaving. End of
end of [ __ ] story.
So it's all so it's all well and it's
all good and well you saying house bells
that oh if you do this stuff yeah that
they that they're wary of men but we're
wary of women. We can't get attached
because of them. We can't get attached
because of them when they do this stuff
to us. We can't get attached because of
them. You not
understand that we can't get attached.
So does it not work both ways? Does it
I offered money to see if money would
work. Yeah. Like last week, just to see. But
yeah. Uh I No, it's not that I don't
want to listen to their advice. Uh Jill,
whatever man's behind that account, it's
just I've heard it all
before. I've just heard it all before.
I've heard it time and time and time and
again. Yes. I wasn't getting attached to
her because I didn't Oh my god. I can't
be bothered, bro, explaining it, you
know. No, I couldn't get attacked
because that [ __ ] in America and what
they done to me. Get it right, mate. Get
it right. Yeah, get it right. I couldn't
get taxed for two years because of that [ __ ] in America.
Yeah, that's what it was. Not because
people wanted sex, you idiot. You
know, come on, bro. get your [ __ ]
facts right. If you're going to say if
you're going to say [ __ ] like the thing
is there's no more advice. It's not
happening in this country. End of you
know that's it. It's not happening in this
country. Take the L and try somewhere else. That's
it. But then you want to say that oh
they're wary of other men. Oh, you're
wary of other You're going to make them
wary of other men, but they make off
wary of getting attached to other
women. Oh, this this [ __ ] in Manchester being a
[ __ ] How come you never stuck with one
woman then had a long-term relationship?
You ask them. Don't ask me. Why don't you ask
them? Uh, bye-bye, Tra. Go send some
more letters. No one cares about your
stupid little letters. If you convince
yourself that all women are the same,
then eventually that will become true.
No, no, no, no, no. Jill, I'm not
convincing myself anything. My
experiences are showing me this. Okay,
I'll give you an example again. They
don't call me Peter the repeater for no
reason. So, this person in Manchester
that I was speaking to for 3 days who I
was supposed to meet, I was like, "Oh,
they're different. Okay, we're getting
somewhere here. They're 27, same age as
me. Okay, this is getting somewhere.
This is getting somewhere now." you
know, even if it's in another city, you
know, um reserve the hotel was going to
go up there next week and guess what? A
negative happened. Even though I was
like, nah, this person is different. You
know, my negative experiences still
stayed the same. Your outlook depends on
your life experiences and it fluctuates.
You do not wake up negative. You do not
wake up positive. You are a byproduct of your life
experiences. Doesn't she have the right
to change her mind and move on? Um,
well, why would you change her mind? If
you're speaking to somebody every single
day for 3 days, no, it wasn't from
Reddit. It was from Instagram. See,
you're making excuses. That this is what
I mean by people that are making excuses
for women. Charlie, right? This person
here is saying, "Doesn't she have the
right to change her mind and move on?"
But the problem with it is is she didn't
change her mind and she didn't move on.
She was [ __ ] with you from the
start. She was [ __ ] with you from the
very very get- go. It wasn't that she
changed her mind or someone coming. She
was being a [ __ ] from the beginning. But
no one will ever say that because
they've not got a bad word to say about
women. So that's it. She led me
on um voice noted me all day long. All
day long all these plans then bam,
nowhere to be seen again. So you can't
justify it by saying, "Oh, she doesn't
have the right to change her mind and
move on." Bro, you were speaking to
someone for three [ __ ] days. You live
in Manchester. Yeah. You had nothing to
lose by coming out and meeting me
outside that hotel. And then they were
moan, where were all the nice guys gone?
I can't find someone. Huh? [ __ ]
pathetic because we all know that in
Manchester they couldn't have had many
options. Like in London I' I'd
understand it a bit more. I'd understand
it a bit more if it was Manchester. Uh
if it was London, right? Okay. I
couldn't get it. You know, because of
the competition, but Manchester, bro,
not much is going
on. You know what I'm saying?
So yeah, they just they were [ __ ]
with you from the from the get-go.
That's not it's not they changed their
mind. So I was positive about that,
Jill. And look what happened. A negative
It was only 310. It wasn't anything.
Maybe she changed her mind. She doesn't
She doesn't Oh, she doesn't owe you
anything. I love it. Oh my god. Isn't it
mad that whenever a woman does something
shitty, they try to justify it? Stop
trying to seek attention on my channel.
Isn't it mad how whenever some woman
does you dirty, she doesn't owe you
nothing? Have you noticed that? Whenever
a woman does you dirty, have you noticed
this? Right. Whenever a woman does you
dirty, they always say the woman don't
owe you nothing. This is exactly what
I'm talking about. Oh my god. This is
exactly what I'm talking about. But if
you're a woman complaining about men,
everyone feels sorry for you. This is
what, bro. This is exactly what I was
telling you about. This is exactly what
I was telling you about.
This is exactly whenever a woman is
wrong and [ __ ] you over, they tell you
they don't owe you nothing. That's no
way of getting out of it. I told you. I
told you, bro. I told you they don't
have a bad word to say about women. This
is what I This is why I don't bother no
more. This is why I don't sit here and
argue all day long because I know they
don't have no bad words to say about
women. So why am I going to argue with
them? Why, bro? You are so stupid to
even put any kind of circumstance on the
internet to do with you and a woman
because you know why? Because whenever a
woman does you dirty, she don't owe you
nothing. But they're not using it in the
right context. They [ __ ] well do owe
you something. They wasted three times.
They wasted three days of your [ __ ]
time. Yeah. And guess what? Oh, let me
ask you this. Let me ask you this
question then. Why is it when women moan
about men, no one tells them men don't
owe them nothing? Huh? Oh, too heavy and
scared. Do you want me to show you all
the messages? Do you want me to show you
all the messages? I can show you all the
messages if you want. I can show you all
the messages if you want. See, maybe
this, maybe that. They have no bad words
to say about women. They have no bad
words. And this is exactly why I don't
even waste my time. I don't say nothing
on Reddit no more. I don't say nothing
because I know that they have no bad
words to say about women and they're
going to blame you for being a man.
That's why there's no point. There's no
point anyone ever even asking for advice
cuz they're just going to make excuses
for the woman and her shitty behavior.
I.e. maybe it's this, maybe that, maybe
it's that, i.e. she doesn't owe you
anything, i.e. this, i.e. that. Anything
but put the blame on the woman. That's
what these people are about. 90% of
people on social
media. Obviously, you probably get 10%
that are not biased, but most of them,
like I've already done this experiment.
I've already done this experiment where
I've pretended to be a woman, moaning
about men, complaining about men, and
not one person told me a woman don't owe
me nothing. You know, why is that? Why
is that? Oh, what is it? Just because
it's Reddit, is
it? No. No. Okay. You you want you want
to give me your opinion, do you? You
want to give me your opinion, do you?
Add me on Snapchat, add me on Facebook,
and I will show you all the messages.
Okay. Okay. You want to get you you
actually want to give your opinion.
Okay. Why don't you come on now and
Yeah, she does owe you something. She
does owe you something. And you know
what? If I keep hearing, oh, she don't
owe you nothing. I'm going to go to
Manchester and I'm going to put them
posters up and I'm going to be like,
don't owe you nothing. Don't owe you an
explanation. Don't wind me up, bro.
Don't wind me up. Honestly, do not wind
me up. Do not push me to do it. And I'll
be like, I don't [ __ ] owe you
nothing. So when these people will start
messaging me asking, why have you put my
number out there? Why have you done
this? Why have you done this? Why have
you done that? Right. I'm going to be
like, I owe you nothing. And we'll see
how that works out for me. Yeah. You
know, since I keep hearing that about a
million [ __ ] times, bro. Yeah. That's
it. So, you actually want to give your
opinion, add me on Snapchat, add me on
Snapchat. Add me on Facebook. Come on.
Come on. Come on.
on. My Facebook is
PJXed. Yeah. So, you want to actually
give your opinion? I'll type it for you.
Come on. You can message me. I'm going
to show you all these screenshots.
Yeah. But yeah, I might I might go and
do some posters, bro. I might just go
and do some posters. And you know what?
Yeah. It's not even just this
experience. Like you'd be mad if you was
to only have one experience and then
like this happens. It's amalgamation of
things. It's like, you know, when people
have a mental breakdown and when people
go mad, it's not because of one
experience or two experiences or they
[ __ ] off for 6 months and they've had
the odd bad experience. It's an
amalgamation of things and it builds up
and up and up and up and up and up and
up and up and up, you know, and then
someone needs to like be told about
themsel, bro. Like, do you know what I'm
saying? Listen, go on my channel, go on
my Facebook and message me now. I'm
going to show you these screenshots. Go
on Facebook and message me now. Yeah,
women aren't all the same. I believe it
when I see it. Yeah, I believe it when I
there you go. Message me on Facebook.
You got my
Facebook. Who the [ __ ] is that?
Yeah, women are the same. I believe it
when I see it. I'll believe it when I
see it. When I am made a believer, I'll believe it.
Bye-bye. Go self-reflect on another
channel. I don't give these people
attention anymore. These sad little
keyboard warriors. These sad little
self-reflectors. They're not even
they're not even worth reacting to, bro.
They just come on here and self-relect
life every day. Yeah. If you're new to
the channel, that's that's what's going
to happen. So if you see me block a load
of people, they're just self-reflectives
that's been stalking me for
years. So yeah, sad little keyboard
lawyers. In other words,
Should I give the [ __ ] a warning to
apologize before I go up there and do
posters? I don't think so.
They don't owe you nothing. Isn't it mad
how whenever a woman does something
shitty, they're told that no one owes him [Laughter]
nothing? This country will
Sorry about these people,
bro. I've already told her my [ __ ] Facebook name,
bro. But yeah, you people don't have no
bad words to say about
women. But yeah, it's an amalgamation of
things. It's not just one experience,
bro. You don't just have one experience
and then go [ __ ]
like go [ __ ] mad. It's an
amalgamation of what you've been dealing
with over the years with these women,
you know? It's not one experience, bro.
It's multiple experiences. Like, I'm
going to go there and put up posters of
her, bro. I swear I'm going to do it,
bro. I will travel there with a load of
posters, like go out clubbing, and then
[ __ ] the next day just put up posters
with her number and that. It's [ __ ] with
them in it, bro. Give them give them
some [ __ ] over the years that they've
gave us. Give them a give them a bit of [ __ ]
Yep. They don't know my name either, so
that's a good
thing. My friend lives in Manchester as
well. The one that come the other day,
he's from London, but he lives in
Manchester. So, it's all good, bro.
every 3 days. Every 3 years, bro. Yeah. How about
that? Why are these people so obsessed
with me, Harry? Like, I just block them.
Like I don't even react to them anymore.
I just block them. Like they make new
accounts. I just block them, man. Look at this,
bro. See, they make fake accounts, bro.
And and just to like comment and get
blocked. How sad are their lives, bro?
lives? Is he? Let me see.
No, he's not
live. They're so obsessed and like they
don't realize that we're just going to
block them. Like, bro, I'm not going to
sit here and react to these people
anymore. Oh, your skin. I've got more
money than you. T like bro, I'm not like
reacting to these people anymore. They
can keep being obsessed. They can keep
getting blocked. I don't care. Sad
little bastards. They're the ones
They're the ones who's I I I live in
their head every day. We're free in it. That's
enough. I'm surprised they don't get
bored of stalking someone every single
day. It's so
boring. Like if you've got a problem
with somebody, you meet them.
Like, oh, he lives near her. Yeah, but
he said he lives in Manchester.
But they say that they're not obsessed,
but they they sit on like with me. I
told you about this person from
Manchester. Bro, when I go to Manchester
again, I am putting up posters of them.
I am putting up posters of them because
I've got a problem with them and they're
pissing me off. You see? You see what
I'm trying to say? But these people are
pissed off with you every day. They're
obsessed with you every day, but they're
not willing to actually do anything to
you. So, how can you make how can you be
mad for that long if you're not willing
to actually do anything? Do you know
what I'm saying? Unless the person lives
in a [ __ ] other country. You know
what I'm saying? So, it's mad. I can't I
can't relate to these people, you know?
Like, I'm going to ruin this woman's
life when I'm back in Manchester. I'm
going to [ __ ] her life up, you know, for
real life, bro. And I'm going to set up
a dating profile of her as well for
being a little time waster, you know?
Like, I'm not going to sit here every
day going mad for months and years like
these little obsessed keyboard warriors.
Like, it's it's
pointless, you know? It's really really
man. You know what I'm saying? How pointless it
is. I don't really fight, bro. No, I
don't really fight. I don't claim to be
a fighter. I don't claim to be no hard
man, but I'm just saying, bro. Is it
like you got a problem with someone,
come and do
something. These people won't. They just
want to be on YouTube obsessed. every
day stalking people that they're jealous
of. So it's like let them have their
life, bro. You know that's what they want to
do. Know what I'm saying?
Yep. And that's what I'm going to do,
bro. [ __ ] hell. Time already.
had a cop today.
Uh, I used to go to a gym, but not
anymore. There's no What's the point of
me going to the gym? It's always going
to be the same experiences with women in
this country. I'm done, bro. I'm done
with life. I'm not doing it no more. I'm
anymore. I'm literally not doing it
anymore. You know, [ __ ] it.
thinking if my mom wasn't alive, I
probably would have killed
myself. Yeah, I probably would have
killed myself to be fair. Like if I had
like no parents alive to be fair, but I
don't want like my
mom having to go through like someone,
you know, it's not my mental health is caused by
women. My mental health is caused by
women. If I had better experiences with
women, I mean, no, I don't even have
mental health. Well, no, I say I say
mental health. I don't even have mental
health. It's these women that are making
me like this. Every single time I have
to keep dealing with him, dealing with
him, dealing with him, dealing with him.
You know, I was fine for like 3, four
days until this [ __ ] pissed me off
again. This [ __ ] [ __ ] in Manchester
[ __ ] started winding me up. You know,
I was fine before
that. Like, no, bro. You're you're the
way you are because of these women. Stop
trying to blame everything else. Stop
trying to blame anyone else, you know?
Really, bro. Really? Re really really stop
it. It is these [ __ ]
women. And when I'm in Manchester
again, I am going to put up posters of
this woman. What do you think to that
idea? Hell B putting up posters of this
woman. Make sure she gets hit or
something. [ __ ] wasting my [ __ ]
time for three days, you silly
[ __ ] Nah, I'm not interested in help.
I'm I'm beyond that. I'm beyond that.
I'm done with it. I don't care. I'm done
with it. I don't care, bro. I'm done living.
So, yeah, I'll just go Manchester, put
up the posters. [ __ ] it.
No. And the only thing that gets me down
is the dating game. The whole women and
how rigged how like dating is rigged
against men. Like it's something I can't
get over. I can't stop thinking
about the amount of bad experiences
you've had. No, it does affect me cuz
I've had enough of them. I've had enough
of them. I've had enough of them. No,
no, no, no, no, no, no. It's not just
one person. It's not just one [ __ ]
person. It's all of them. I've had
enough of them. It's not one person or
two people or someone over the space of
six months. I've had enough of these
[ __ ] wasting my [ __ ] time. I've had
enough of it. It's not one person, bro.
It's not two people, bro. It's an amalgamation of them.
Yeah. And I have to think about it every
[ __ ] day. This whole dating game,
this whole how it's rigged against men.
Yeah. Being the best don't work. Trying
don't work. Putting effort into your
life don't work. None of these things
work. So we're beyond that.
We're beyond that. I'm beyond that. So
yeah, we're beyond that,
bro. Giving up with life is the only way out. It
seems it doesn't matter what you do,
what you try, who you're talking to, you
always end up the same. You always end
way. you know, always end up the same
[ __ ] way. It's
mad, you know, and they all and the
maddest thing about it is how like
people just defend women. Like you saw
that account, oh, women don't know you
nothing. That's all you ever hear. But
when a woman does something shitty, they
always say, "Women don't owe you
nothing." But isn't it mad how a woman
is never told how a man don't owe them
nothing? Crazy, isn't it?
Yeah. I don't owe them nothing when
they're moaning and bitching and
winging. But then when somebody wastes
your time, women don't owe you nothing.
That's all they say to excuse their
shitty behavior. You know, I feel like
I'm the only one in this world that
wasn't born with this disease where I
lick women's asses for no reason. You
know, Yep. [ __ ] being the best, bro. I
want out of this [ __ ] life, you
know. I was fine before this [ __ ]
started wasting my
time. Literally, bro. Literally.
It's a madness, bro.
It's a [ __ ]
madness. And this is a good one as well
cuz they actually live in your country
as well. This one's a good one because
they actually live in your
country. So, I'm going to get my friend.
See, I'm I'm thinking of being very very
nice. I'm going to get my friend to
message them and ask them to
apologize. If they don't apologize or
they just block you, then I'm going
Manchester. [ __ ] it. I'm going
That's it. Made up my mind. So that's
it, bro. And I'm putting up my And I'm
putting up posters of him. I'm putting
up [ __ ] posters of these little
[ __ ] I've had enough of them. They're
all [ __ ] All of them. Not just one of
them. You know what I'm saying? [Laughter]
when I was speaking to this one
yesterday. She seemed all right, but
she's just too fat. She's just too too
Let me make a tea and I'll come back.