Oh my god, bro.
I'm getting these [ __ ] boots again
and I can't keep [ __ ] still. Swear to
God. I was going to go [ __ ] bed, but
I can't keep [ __ ] still, bro. It's
[ __ ] annoying. I just want to smack
up [ __ ] woman. I swear to God, bro.
Like, I'm [ __ ] pissed off today, bro.
And I've got to wait all the way till [ __ ] Friday.
No, it's annoying, bro. It's [ __ ]
annoying, bro. I swear to
God. Get these nasty [ __ ] movements again.
Does anyone else get these [ __ ] stinky little
rap getting raped?
You all hear you as well. [ __ ]
them. They're all [ __ ]
[ __ ] All of
them. All of them, man.
No, no, no, no, no. That's what I say.
Said no. You're all evil. Don't care.
No. Stop trying to convince people. Stop
trying to convince people that they're
not all evil. I'm not interested. They
are all evil, mate. I'm 27. I've been
dealing with them for years. I know
exactly what they're [ __ ]
like. Yeah, I'm getting these mood
swings, bro. Like, I legit want to punch
a [ __ ] mirror. Like, I legit just I
was going to smash that
[ __ ] piss off,
man. And shattered the whole [ __ ]
thing down the [ __ ] bathroom. It's
[ __ ] winding me
up. [ __ ] winding me up again. I can't
even [ __ ] sleep. It's [ __ ]
annoying, bro. I hate him.
I [ __ ] hate
him. I was going to go sleep, bro. I
can't even [ __ ] sleep, bro. I [ __ ] hate the
[ __ ] You know the maddest thing about it, bro?
Yeah. If I had one
wish, if I had one wish, mine would be
to put a woman in front of me so I could
smack the [ __ ] out of her. It wouldn't
even be to get a million pound. No, no,
no, no, no, no, no. What's money, bro?
It would be have somebody like USA Izzy
or this [ __ ] from Manchester in the
front of me. Both of them. And I just
smash them both in. Just [ __ ] smash
the [ __ ] both
in. I smash them both in. [ __ ] give
them a good old [ __ ] ass [ __ ]
whooping. A good old fashioned ass
whooping, mate. Not a piss, not a piss
up and ass whooping. That's what my one wish would
be. Honestly, that's what my one wish would
be. You know, just just [ __ ] them up,
bro. You know what I'm saying? I I wish,
bro. I hate him. I [ __ ] hate that,
bro. You don't understand. I hate him.
You know what I'm
saying? I [ __ ] do, bro. I [ __ ] hate the scum
earth. Can't sense voice. They [ __ ] block me.
[ __ ] stupid little [ __ ] [ __ ]
there. Do us a
favor on one condition. Your mom does me
a favor and sucks my
dick. Yeah, your mom does me a favor and
sucks my dick. How about that one? Maybe
if your mom sucks my dick, I'll give you
a good hush. If your mom sucks my big
fat [ __ ] then I will. I think that
sounds like a reasonable deal. Bye-bye.
Now, there you
go. They're so
evil. I [ __ ] hate
them. [ __ ] evil little [ __ ] mate.
Which one's more punchable, do you
reckon? Say that one for Manchester. I
wonder which one's more
punchable. Which one's more smashable in
their [ __ ] face? Which which one do you
think? You know what I'm saying?
You say it's more smashable in their [ __ ]
face, do you
think? I' I'd like them both just to
[ __ ] them up, bro. Just [ __ ] them up and
just just torture them, you know? Just
torture them. That's what would be my my
wish, bro, would would just be to
torture them. I hate him. Like, you
don't think you understand, bro? Like,
you think that man is bad? I'm worse
than him. I hate
them for for real, bro. I
do. You know what I'm saying?
I take it cuz there's nothing I can [ __ ] do
but cuz when I went to America one
didn't out and I'm going to have to this come
I hate him.
You know what I might do? I might just
go I might just go back to I just might
I just might go Manchester tomorrow.
[ __ ] it. What's the day to What's the
day tomorrow? Monday.
Yeah, I really really want to hurt one.
I really really [ __ ] do. Really
do. I really want to hurt him. Like you
don't understand, bro. I really [ __ ] do. You
know, I want to get this [ __ ] glass
and smack it across the window, bro. I
used to do it all the [ __ ] time.
I hate him, bro.
Imagine you had financial problems on
top of this as well. Could you imagine?
top of this. [ __ ] me, bro. Could you imagine?
Like could you actually imagine your life would be worth
it? It's hard enough even if you have money or
you you get money. That's that's the
thing. Even when you have money and you
get money, it's still bad back now. And
he gets £400 a month. [ __ ] 400 a [ __ ] month.
See, this is exactly what I'm saying,
bro. Imagine having £400 a month, 300
pound a month, and then having to deal
with these [ __ ] on top of it. Your life
would be worth
living. You know what I'm
saying? [ __ ] me, bro. Your life would
not even have money matters anyways, but
it's just the whole stress of it as
well. You'd be [ __ ] You would
actually be [ __ ] bro.
Honestly, grand and a half. Yeah. Two
grand. Yeah. [ __ ] £400 a
month. That's a madness, bro. Imagine
that. Yeah, they do it on purpose. I
think some people are born with a
against them and I'm one of them.
There's other guys as well that out there, you know,
like I used to I must have put my mom I
must have used to put my mom through
[ __ ] hell, bro. When I was at that
house, you know, that's why there's no
point even never going back there
because I know exactly what
I'm going be like when I get these mood
swings. I know exactly what I'm going to be like.
She hear [ __ ] [Music]
scream and no can't [ __ ] hear me. Not there. You
can't. I've got so much screenshots to
show as well. It's
bad. I [ __ ] I actually hate them,
bro. Charlie, I actually hate him, lad.
I went out Friday to meet my friend to
go for a good oldfashioned piss off.
That's why I went out. I [ __ ] hate
him. I [ __ ] do. And I said to Anan, I
don't want to hear about it when you
come back. Oh, how does other people do
it or I don't want to [ __ ] hear it
when you come back? Cuz I'm fed up with
it now, mate. I'm [ __ ] fed up with it
now. So, I don't want to be hearing your
[ __ ] when you come back cuz when you're
back, I'm gone. Simple. That's it. Yep. You
didn't know what I'm saying cuz a
Manchester woman. Yeah. And to be honest
with you, mate, I was beyond that point.
I didn't I I did do one of
them just for the lows. [ __ ] said he was
engaged. I did do
one like sometimes I wish I might as
well just be dead, you know? I feel like
I have I had a good life, you know. This
this is no this is no life for any young
person. I've been on a plane. I've been
abroad. You know, I've done some things.
I didn't have to work for a couple of
years. Like I feel like if I died, I wouldn't
care. I generally would would love to
die, bro. Like I wouldn't honestly
wouldn't care cuz this is no life for
anyone, mate, in this country. This is
no life for
anyone to twiddle your thumbs every Saturday. Same
outcome. It's there's got to be more to
life than this. There's got to
be, you know, there's got to be more to
life than this torment. You know, They're [ __ ]
evil. Yeah. The negative experience
never ended cuz you can't give up. And
then when you keep trying and then when
you keep trying, you get more bad
experiences. And it's never ended. It's never ending.
It's never ever
ended. You can't even pay your way out of it,
mate. See, I I know I I didn't go out
Saturdays because I know realistically
you're going to be sat in a barber chair
for an hour and 20 minutes and then
you're going to go out and you're going
to send it and you're going to hear
about Makeelie Boyfriends. I'm too old
for you. I'm too young for you. I'm not
looking for anyone right now. I'm
engaged. I'm sorry. I can't do this. And
you get a few numbers and then the
numbers don't go nowhere. And it's the
same thing every week. You
know, it's the same thing every week.
It's never ending. This is what I'm
saying, bro. This is why I don't bother no
more. Yo, I went out with my friend, but
I wanted to save some money because I
was supposed to go Manchester next week
and I wanted to save myself, you
know, and even Manchester, bro. Like I
told you ear, I would have been anxious
going all that way by myself. I don't
travel no like, you know, anymore like I
used to. So me going somewhere by
myself, it's not my ends. You know, it's
still a big leap of faith. You know what
I'm saying? So it weren't even going to
be easy even if they would have met
you. So bro, you're out of your ends.
You know what I'm saying? Like [ __ ]
you know what I'm saying? It's a risk.
risk. So even if you went to Manchester,
that's not easy. You still got to pay. I
still had to set put some money aside
for it. You're talking a good couple
pound and I got to go on that train.
It's [ __ ] long as well. But if that's
what it means to make love, then there's
no distance on it, is it?
Manchester, it's not even like it's like
Maiden Head or like somewhere like that.
So either way, they weren't even making
it easy for you even if you was going to be So
yeah, so the only solution is to leave this
country because it's like why should you
have to keep putting yourself through
this [ __ ] Why should you have to keep
doing it? Why? It's not normal. It's
inhumane. What? Go out every day
approaching until you get a number that
doesn't mess you around? I'm not doing
that. And no normal person should have
to [ __ ] do
that. It's not normal, mate. It ain't
[ __ ] normal, is it?
Someone is [ __ ] internet,
man. What is wrong with this
internet? So, what do you do about it?
Hey, Charlie, you're basically [ __ ] aren't you?
Yeah. Yeah. You have to leave this
country, bro. It's the only thing I can see.
discussion by setting up
it. What if I was a black guy, Charlie?
What if I was a black guy?
You know what? If I was a black
guy, Yeah, I know. I know. I
know. You remember when I said to man,
"How's it getting on, man? I ain't heard
from you for a while." He's like,
"How's it getting on?" They've all got boyfriends.
Boyfriend. I went here and I went there
and they all weren't
boyfriends. I've had
enough. I know it's like it does get you
depressed cuz I I've had it as
well. I said, "How's your day going,
man? They've all got friends.
I'll never forget that
love. Yeah. It's not funny when it
happens to you,
though. It's not funny when it happens to you.
Yeah, I don't know how I've not ended up doing
it because I was speaking to this person
in Manchester and I thought, "Oh, this is looking
good. This is looking good, mate." Yeah.
No. I said, "Oh, this is looking good."
Yeah. Is it [ __ ]
mate? Is it [ __ ] looking
good? Yes. This the same old
England. Same old
England. Same old England would never exchange.
No. What do you reckon it is, Charlie? I
I like I personally think it's a it's a
few different things. I think it's like
there's not someone for everyone and
it's the wrong day and age to to start
dating it. I think you're [ __ ] because
social media and there's not someone for
everyone. They say that there's someone
for everyone, but I'm living proof that
there's not. I'm living proof of it. You
know, and there's other people out there
that doesn't have anyone
either. I'm living proof of it. Some
people are just not made for no one. I
don't believe in that. Saying there's
someone for everyone. Nah, I don't
believe it. Cuz if there was someone for
everyone, you would have found them by
now. You've been to Manchester, you've
been to Leeds, you've been to Sheffield,
you've been to Scotland, you've been to
Cardiff. Where is this
someone? Where are they hiding? You
know, there's not someone for
everyone. That is completely completely
ridiculous. There's someone for everyone.
Eh, you do have to laugh,
bro. Yeah. Apart from you, apart from
me, apart from loads of other people.
I'm going Manchester next Friday,
Terry, to do some posters of this
country in Manchester. I had enough of
these bastards. Honestly, it's not it's
not as bad as what Ant-Man with the axe,
but I feel like it's still pretty
badass, you know, traveling all that way
do posters and come back. I've had
enough of these [ __ ] I've had enough
of them to last me a lifetime, mate.
It's the same as people having like a
mental breakdown. You know, when people
have a mental breakdown, it's an
amalgamation of things. Well, me going
to Manchester putting posters up with
this [ __ ] is amalgamation things. So
yeah. Well, do you realize I'll be doing
that next [ __ ] week? [ __ ] sake. You
know, all cuz of these shitty scubby
women again. You can't catch a [ __ ]
break from them, man.
Seriously. You'll be on the number. So,
good luck with that.
Well, get nicked or go to jail for
putting posters on. Well, if I get
nicked, I get nicked. [ __ ] it. Give it a
while. Be worth a try. Ain't it? I would
give it a while. [ __ ] it. Is it? They
don't want to take the piss out of
us. Yeah, I know. It's funny, isn't it?
If you were something like Timmy, ugly,
dispassic, and I'd understand
it. And it's nothing wrong with you.
It's nothing wrong with me. It's just
their standards are unrealistic because
of these white knights and these simps.
That's what it is. It's nothing to do
with you or me. And that's what it
is. You know, it's their standards are
unrealistic and they think that they're
much better than they actually are. That
gives them an ego. That's what it is in
this day and age because you wouldn't be
having these problems in the 70s and 80s
and you wouldn't be having this problem
in [ __ ] Asia. So, it goes to show
like what it really really
is. You know what I'm saying? That's why
I don't waste my time no more. I went to meet my
friend, got a drink with him, won some
money on fishing frenzy, that's it. Got
an escort, come back. I'm not doing this
no more, bro. I ain't doing it no more.
I need to get this passport sorted as
well next week or the week after and I'm leaving. So,
ta. Yep. Cuz my passport. Well, that 10
years went [ __ ] fast, didn't it? 10
years of that passport went [ __ ]
fast. It went fast, bro. It actually So, yeah. Yeah,
exactly. No, it's focused for me as well,
mate. I won't be trying again. This
Manchester was the end, bro. [ __ ] it. You
know, it was good though, guys, you know.
but almost too good to be true as
well. To be true,
lad. Yeah, I do remember
it. At least I went abroad, unlike a
certain virgin. You never been abroad?
Well, I don't suppose you can go through
when you're on a
grump. 27 and being in a relationship.
But here's the thing, Terry. You're
older than me and you're still a virgin.
That tells me a lot about you. That I'm
27 and I have more life experience than
you. That tells me something about you.
I've had more women than you. I have
more money than you. I get more money
than you. I've been to more places than
you. You know, and even if I had a
relationship, you would still tell me I
had I don't have a relationship. So it's
pretty diff, you know, it doesn't tell
me about myself. It tells me about these
women's ego in this country. That's what
it tells me. It tells me how unrealistic
that these women's standards are in this
country. Yeah. You have kids, something
I'll never have. Yeah. Okay. Of course
you do, mate. So you got kids, but
you're on YouTube all the time offering
people have fights. Yeah. Okay, bro. Um,
Yeah. And you offer people out on
YouTube as well. Why do you offer people
out for fights,
bro? Kids and you and you and you're in
your 40s. That doesn't make any sense,
does it? So, yeah. Sorry,
bro. Yeah, exactly. Yeah, it's cuz she's
disabled. Of course. Of course. Of
Yeah, that's it, bro. I saw you. There we
go. Because they know you're not right.
Oh, always making excuses for women. So,
was there ever a time that any of the
women that I spoke to was in the wrong?
Let me let me ask you this question. Was
there ever ever a time where any of the women
I spoke to was in the room. You're a
typical white knight. You ain't got a
bad word to say about women, Terry.
You're most you're like most of these
people on here. You always make excuses
for women. This is what I find most this
society does. They ain't got no bad
words to say about it. That's why I
never ask for advice cuz I know by
default they're just going to stick up
for women. That's why I never ask for
advice cuz I know if you are complaining
about they're just going to use things
to blame you. Not because you're wrong,
because you're a man and they're a
woman. So there's no point even ever
asking for advice. So that's it. So yeah, that's so
yeah, after a few days they don't all
block me. Not not all of them has
blocked me. You're making stuff up. You
pulled out the cow's ass. And a lot of
them do it because they're taking the
piss in the first place. Yeah, a lot of
them are taking the piss out of you in
the first place. But you wouldn't say
that because you ain't got no bad words
to say about women. I love saying that
as well. I love saying that. I [ __ ]
that cuz it's the [ __ ] truth,
lad. I need to go to bed soon as
well. You ain't got no bad words to say
about women. No one does, do they? Sad, is it?
There you go. Anyways, I need to go to
bed, man. So, I'll be back later. Well,
tomorrow is technically later. Yeah. I'm
out of it. Bye. Peace.