Sorry about that, man. I have to do
something. No plans today. Just lie in bed
depressed. Just lie in bed depressed.
Same as every day, every other
day. Life never changes in this country.
It's a mug's game. It never ever changes. Yeah, bro. What the [Music]
hell? Oh, this life is [ __ ] This life
[ __ ] Nothing ever changes.
Yeah. Lying in bed every day looking at
four walls cuz you know nothing that you
do, nothing you try is going to change your
situation. It's like living is is is
actually torment and living is torment. [ __ ]
Sorry. This a [ __ ] life we have to live.
We live, we suffer, we
die. We live, we suffer, and then we
die. What's the fun of that? Live,
suffer, die. It's [ __ ]
pointless. We live, we get mocked, we
get bad experiences, we get tormented,
and we die. There's literally no point
even getting out of
bed. I knew yesterday, today I'm gonna
get out of
bed. I knew because yesterday I'm gonna
bed. Woke up with the mood swings again.
It never ever stops. It never ever ever
ever stops. It's a depressing life
living being alive when you've had as
many bad experiences as I have.
any bad experiences as I have, you know.
Hopefully I can fall asleep in a bit and
not wake up. That's what I was praying
for yesterday. But here we are again.
Awake. Awake for what exactly? Nothing's
changing. Nothing will ever change.
No matter what effort you put into your
life, what effort you don't put into
your life, nothing changes. Everything
is always stays the same. No matter what
effort you put
in, some people are just meant to um
suffer. Yeah. Some people are just meant
to to suffer in
life. It sucks, isn't it? But that's the
way it is.
This a sad life, isn't it? Someone like
me. I'm probably younger than most
people in this
community. Imagine there being nothing
you can do to change your situation.
That's [ __ ] mental. It'd be the same
as staying in bed. There's literally
nothing you can do to actually change
your situation. To me, that's just
that's just so
bad. Giving up is the only way out,
mate. I've tried more than anybody in this
world. I prayed I f I prayed I'd die in
my sleep every day cuz I know nothing's
going to get better. Oh, they don't get
better, mate. Oh, they [ __ ] don't. I
put more effort than anybody in the
world. And nothing ever ever gets
better. Nothing ever changes. All women
are the same. Life is the same. It does
not get better. Nothing gets better. I'm
living proof of it. Somebody that's gone
all around the country trying this,
trying that, trying this, trying that,
being patient. Nothing ever
changes. Literally, I wouldn't be
[ __ ] staying in bed today if I
thought effort would actually change
anything. Effort changes nothing. It
will always stay the same. Life will
always be the same. And that's why I went
out. Oh, it is the bad experiences with
women. Oh, it is. Oh, it is a sexist
life without women. Women bad
experiences. It's that bad. It's very,
very, very bad. When a when women have a
vendetta against you personally and
they've got a vendetta against other men
as well, you know, it's very, very bad.
It's bad enough to off yourself. Having
your time wasted, being took the piss
out of. I'm going Manchester on
Friday. I'm going Manchester on Friday
to ruin this woman's life for wasting my
time. Oh yeah. I woke up today thinking
about it. I woke up today [ __ ] I had
my blood rushing down to my [ __ ]
feet, bro. I would have went today if I
didn't if I didn't book it for Friday. I
would have went
today. I'm going to ruin this cunt's
life. I swear to God, bro. I swear to
[ __ ] God I'm going there Friday,
bro. I I even thought about going today
if I had even booked it. Yeah. Yeah. I'm
sick of these [ __ ] women. I hate
them. They're [ __ ] evil. They're evil
little [ __ ] They're the cause of
people's depression. They are the cause
of it, you know. No, I didn't. I don't get nose
bleeds. I [ __ ] genuinely hate him.
Like you you don't understand, bro. Like
you laugh at it and you think it's
funny. I was thinking of doing some mad
thoughts today, bro. And yesterday I was
thinking of doing some bad stuff. It is
all women. Do you want me to show you
this evidence? Do you want me to show
you this evidence? It is all women. It
I'm telling you that it is all women.
And I will show you the screenshots. And
if it wasn't all women, I would have
been proven wrong by now. But I haven't.
So here we are. It is all
women. Yeah. Well, they Well, it's a
lot. Well, they hate me and I hate them.
Tit for tap for tat. [ __ ] on the mat.
Simple. Yeah. Well, tell them we hate
each other. They hate me. I hate them.
But guess what? I'm willing to do
something about it. I'm willing to go to
Manchester on Friday and [ __ ] and
mock them in real
life. I'm just not getting out of bed. I
woke up with mood swings, depressed,
thinking about the bad experiences with
women. Thinking how nothing's ever going to
change. No, I'm good. Thanks, mate. I've
been like this for the past two days.
Nah, I'm good. Thank you. I've been like
this for the past two days cuz of these
women. You can though, but I won't be
there. I'll be in bed. Roll on [ __ ]
Friday when I got to Manchester ruin
this cunt's life. I hate women. I hate
what they do to people. They're [ __ ]
evil. I went on Reddit and I was talking
about this as well yesterday. Um yes,
well before I went to sleep
yesterday. No, I'm good in bed. Thank
you very much. I don't want any more bad
experiences. Yeah, things will never
improve ever. They will when you're when
I'm dead. They'll improve when I'm dead,
but that's about it. The only time you
get a break from this is when you're
sleeping. Literally is when you're
sleeping. You can't even watch a horror
film and escape it. You can't even go, you
know, you can't even go and watch a
horror film w without seeing [ __ ] up
scenes. Imagine that. Imagine you go to
the cinema to get away from it. And even
then, you can't get away from it cuz you
see sex scenes in the cinema.
So the only way the only time you get
away from it is when you're sleeping.
Well, unless you have a nightmare, but
most times you don't. So the only time
you get away from it is when you're asleep.
is when you're sleeping or, you know,
dead. You know, that's the only time
that Virgin Shaw leaves me alone is when
he's sleeping or in prison or if he ever dies.
So, yeah, I woke up today with mood
swings. I wanted to go out and smash up
a [ __ ] woman, bro. I was telling this
morning about this last night as well,
bro. I said, "I hope you will [ __ ] get cancer.
That's what I said. I said, "I hope you all get
cancer." That's what I said.
So, well, I haven't tried the same thing
over and over again. I've tried
different things. I've traveled. I've
tried dating apps. No, I was actually
thinking of cutting off my dick as well.
I got some mad thoughts like cutting off my
dick. I felt like actually cutting off
my dick, but then that's kind of like
suicide because you're just going to
bleed to death anyways.
So definitely suicide is the only way
out at this
point. It's having the balls to do it
though. That's the thing. It's having
the balls to kill
yourself. Why did God give you a dick if
you can't use it? I don't understand.
Why? Why was you born with a penis if
you can't use it? You know, it'd be
different if you was if you was born
with no dick. I assume you wouldn't be,
you know, you wouldn't get horny then.
But why why would God give you a
dick if um you can't even use
it? Yeah. They tell you to work on
yourself. Work on yourself. It's not the
woman's fault. It's never the woman's
fault. They're giving you the same
shitty advice. Yeah, but I can't
reproduce because apparently all these women have
boyfriends, so I don't even know why I
was born with a dick. I might as well
just cut it off and give it to someone
else who can actually use
it. You might as well have just been
born with a [ __ ] vagina, to be
honest, cuz it's not like you'll be
using that dick anytime soon. You can't
even open your mouth without hearing about Makeelie
Boyfriends. No thank you. I should have
a woman. I don't need a flashlight. With
all the approaches I've done, I should
be with someone
now. I don't need a
flashlight. You need a real thing.
You've tried a [ __ ] enough. You've
wasted enough money. You've been up and
down the country like a [ __ ] [ __ ]
enough times. I swear to God, I'd go to
Manchester if it wasn't for Friday. I
swear to God, bro. I'd go live in the
morning and I would just I would just
travel there on the train and ruin this
little cunt's life. I said, "Have that
for your [ __ ] group chat. Have that
for your [ __ ] taking the piss, you
silly little [ __ ] Have this, have that,
have this, have that, [ __ ] That's what
I'll do, bro. I'm not I'm mad, you know.
Don't underestimate me. Don't Don't
Don't. And this is what these stupid
little [ __ ] rape victim women do, you
know, in their little piss taking
groups. Yeah, I messaged I messaged more
of a family today as well, bro. Yeah, I
swear to [ __ ] God, bro. It's
annoying. Nope, it's not the same. I've
already got a
dog. I've already got a [ __ ] dog, you
know. Yeah, you're going to see I'm
going Manchester, bro. Yeah, I'll say in
front of any man, bro. I said it in the
nightclub like not last week, the week
before that. I'll say it in front of any
man. Yeah, it's the one that wasted my
time for three days. But it's
amalgamation of things. It's not just
her. It's amalgamation of things. Other
people that's wasted my time. The make
believe boyfriends. I've had enough of
it. I've had enough of it, mate. I've
had enough of these [ __ ] to last me a
[ __ ] lifetime. Have you ever heard
that saying? Yeah. These [ __ ] women
are enough to last you. Your bad
experiences are enough to last you a [ __ ] lifetime. Nah.
Nah. No. She only called me three times
and then she never called me
again. [ __ ] stupid
[ __ ] Absolute [ __ ] [ __ ]
mate. I hate women. I hate him with a
[ __ ] passion. I hate him, mate. You
really, really don't understand the word
hate. Yeah, I hate him worse than [ __ ]
Adm. I'm not interested. He had his
chance when I was in Liverpool. He had
his chance when I was in Manchester 10
times. Take it away from my channel.
Your weird [ __ ] drama. Take your
[ __ ] weird drama away from my [ __ ]
channel. Four eyes with no driving license.
Yeah. Oh, she's blocked me. I can't call
her back. She blocked
me. No. So, I
can't even though they can call me. I don't understand
that. No, thank you. No. No. I'm putting up
posters. Yeah. He's trying to white her,
brother. I'll tell you where I am when I
am. You silly little scout [ __ ] You
[ __ ] prick. You [ __ ] prick. Do you
think somebody that talks like that
could ever stand in my face, bro? Come
on. Make another profile. I'm not making
profile. I can't make another profile
cuz once they block you on Instagram,
you're block your IP's
blocked. I know. It's
mad. Yeah, I'm going to ruin her life
anyways on Friday. I'm ruining her life.
I'm ruining her life on
Friday. Yeah, that's nice. I'm ruining
her life on Friday anyways. I don't
care. I'm ruining her
life. Yeah, I know, bro. That's what
they do. They white night. They white
night. They think women like
it. Nah, you can message her if you
want. Nah, you can message her if you
[ __ ] time waste of blocking people
for no [ __ ] reason, you [ __ ]
[ __ ] What's the point of speaking to
somebody for three
days? At least give her a chance. She's
the one that should have gave me a
chance. She's the one that blocked me
for no reason, you [ __ ]
tit. She's the one that blocked me for
no reason, you [ __ ] tit. Not me. She
should give She should give me a chance.
But as usual, all women are the same in
this country. All westernized, all
scummy. So that's not going to happen.
She's the one that should have gave me a
chance. She's the one that blocked me. I didn't block
her. So stop defending
women. Stop defending women for a
change. And you go a day without [ __ ] defending
women. And you go a day without [ __ ] defending
women. [ __ ] pathetic.
Yep. Everyone's wrong but me. 100%. When
it comes to women, everyone's wrong but me.
Nah, I'm all right. Thanks. I'm all
right. Everyone's wrong but me when it
comes to women. 100%. Cuz the thing is
with experiences, experiences don't lie.
It's like concrete evidence. It's like something that's
encrypted. Your experiences don't lie.
It's not about being right. It's not
about being wrong. Your experiences do
not lie. Your experiences with these
women do not lie. End of story. You
know, no, I don't care. I put up poster
of them, bro. I'm going there Friday. I
don't care. And if it wasn't book
Friday, I would have been going
today. Yeah. I've had enough of these
sick [ __ ] sickening head women to
last me a [ __ ] lifetime. And I don't
care what any [ __ ] white knight
[ __ ] says about it. I don't care what
any [ __ ] white knight says about
it. I'm 27. I know more than you, mate.
I'm 27 and I've got more life experience than
you. You know, I'm 27 and guess what?
I've got more life experience than you.
Um, would you meet me? Well, I'm not
going to meet you. I'm going to be in
Blackpool soon as well, which is um like
20 minutes from Preston. So, yeah. And
yeah, I might be 27, but guess what?
I've got more life experience than you
would ever have. And you're probably
more than likely older than me. Yeah,
you can stay in Preston because I'm not
meeting you. I'm not meeting
you. I'm not meeting you.
You can [ __ ] off, you
tit. You can [ __ ] off, you scumbag. I'm
not beating you. I'll [ __ ] end up
[ __ ] beating the [ __ ] out of
you. I'd end up [ __ ] hurting you. If
you come out and meet me, I'd end up [ __ ] hurting
you if this [ __ ] don't come out because
they won't come
out. No, I won't be meeting you. Yep.
you. I'm not meeting you cuz I don't
like women. They're scum of the
earth. Just like this Manchester one,
just like this American one. Just like
this French one. I [ __ ] hate
them. Sometimes I feel like just going
out and just smacking one in their face.
Just one punch. And I know I can knock
him out. I know I could knock them out as well.
just one just just one bang in their
face and that would be it, you
know. I hate him, bro. I hate him. I
hate what they do. I hate how everyone
defends him. I hate the sick, nasty [ __ ]
that they do. I hate him. I generally generally hate
him. I generally generally hate them,
mate. [ __ ] do.
Kevin Kev the Scouser doesn't want it
with me. I've already been to Liverpool.
I've already been to Manchester 10
times. He doesn't come out. He doesn't
want nothing. Yeah. Ask yourself this
question. Why has this guy not come to
London? See, I'm not going round and
round in circles. I'm not going to go
round and round around in circles, mate.
I'm not even going to get into this
conversation. At the end of the day,
I've been to Manchester 10 times. He
ain't come out. I've been to Liverpool
once. He ain't come out. And he's not
been in London. End of. It's not on his
terms. I'm not going to go around and
around in circles. I'm not [ __ ] I
don't go around in circles with spastics here. Yeah.
So, Lizzy will be paying on Friday.
Scumbag. They're absolute scumbags,
these women are. And they're not
different. None of them are different.
And that's the thing with these
women. They're all the same. You call
that fruit king yet again?
Yeah. Yeah. I know. It's a madness,
isn't it? And I'd be [ __ ] rich as
well. Not only that, not only that, but
I'd also be
rich. I'd be [ __ ] rich.
I'd be rich as well if I stayed in
bed. That's another
thing. Too much time and I'm still single.
Yeah, drug dealers get what they want.
Tattooed men get what they want. Women
abusers get what they want and black men
get what they want. If you're not in the
category of them four people, you have
no chance in this country. That's what I
learned. Unless you're like a white guy
with tattoos that is a pedophile that
abuses women or you know you're a drug
dealer or you're a crackhead or you're a
black or you're some black guy, you have
no chance. And that's what I learned
with this country, that this country had
type. That this country had a type for
what they go for. And if you're not one
of them people, you got no
chance. And I don't like tattoos. So
yeah, I'm out of the question. So that's me done,
bro. Nah, I'm all right, bro. You
know, I'm good.
Yeah, it is a depressing life. It's
definitely a depressing
life that suicide's the only way out. I
never ever thought of it like that. I
never ever thought that, you know,
suicide would be the only way out for
such a young person, you know. I never thought it Oh
yeah. I'm not making it a joke. I'm not
joke. I'm not making it a joke. I'm
being serious. This this situation that
I'm in with these women are disgusting.
This [ __ ] American, this French one
last week, this [ __ ] other American,
this one from Manchester. Does it ever
end? When does it ever come to an end?
When does all of this piss taking ever
come to an
end? Can you please tell me when does
all of this come to an end? This is what
I'm what I'm trying to understand.
You know what I'm
saying? No, I'm not, mate. I'm not. No,
no, no, no, no. I'm not. I thought this
person was going to meet me next Friday.
We arranged to meet next Friday. They
wasted my time for 3 days and then they
disappeared. Yeah, we were supposed to
meet on Friday. I went out with my friend on
Friday. I I I um met up with my friend
on Friday and we went for some drinks
only because he was in town and I was
like, "Oh, I'd love to stay out with
you, but you know, I need to save a bit
of money. I need to save myself for next
week." I don't even know why. It's not
It's not one person, it's all of them.
We're not talking. It's Do you know Let
me let me explain something to you. You
know, when somebody has a has a mental
breakdown, do you know it's not one
thing? It's amalgamation of these
things. It's all of these women. It's
not one or two or three. It's all of
them. There was another one as well, a
French one wasting my time. There was
another one wasting my time from the
Thursday that time that I went out
offering money. It's not one person.
It's all of
them. It's all of them. It's
amalgamation of all of them. It's not
just one [ __ ] person, you know? It's
over the years what they've done and
what they still
do. I said it's an amalgamation of
things like it's it's several different
things. It doesn't matter what I want
because I'm never going to get it. Pointless
question. An amalgamation of things
means that it was it's different things.
Yeah, you keep telling yourself
that. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no. Stop trying to justify what
they do as them just rejecting you. Stop
trying to stop trying to sugar sugarcoat
it. Stop trying to sugarcoat what they
do, you know? Stop trying to sugarcoat
what they do, you know? No, you don't go
through that. No, you [ __ ] don't. And
I've had to go out every week dealing
with these [ __ ] you know?
No, because they're all the same. No,
no, no, no, no. Because all these women
are the same. They have the same type of
guy that they go for. So, no. No, no,
no, no, no. Because they're all the
same. Whether you want a relationship or
whether you want sex, you're not going
to get it. They're all exactly the same.
And anyways, yellow man, you you say
that we go through rejection and time
wasting. Okay, go out every week and
deal with it then. Go out with it and
and deal with it every week. Nah, bro.
[ __ ] it. I'm going Manchester next
Friday. It's all booked. I don't care. I
don't care. I don't care. Stop defending
them. Stop making excuses for them. They
know exactly what they're doing. These
little [ __ ] know exactly what they're
[ __ ] doing. I [ __ ] hate him. I
swear to God. Let that [ __ ] come out
next Friday and I will whoop their ass.
Let that [ __ ] come out next Friday and I
will whoop their time wasted ass.
Yeah. [ __ ] off, bro. Stop trying to make
excuses for them. Oh, we all do it. Suck
my dick, [ __ ] How about that
one? So, you're just going to money just
like Scotland and America? H, good one,
mate. take it away from my channel. Uh,
no, I reserved the hotel. It's £75
because it's a
Friday. So, uh, well, I've reserved it,
but I'm only going to stay there a
couple of hours. I'm not going out
drinking there cuz obviously
Manchester's got the same [ __ ] women as
they do here in London. They're all
[ __ ] They're all the same. They're all
of these women are the same. So, I'll
probably just stay there for a couple of
hours and then probably just have a
sleep and come back. I probably won't
even I probably won't even drink to be
honest. I don't want to deal with these
[ __ ] in this country
anymore. Yeah, it probably scared her
off making excuses again. It's always an
excuse, isn't it? It probably scared her off. Always
excuses. Always an excuse when it comes
to a woman, making up excuses for them.
I've noticed that with all of the
experiences that I had in my life,
right, with these women, they always
make excuses for the girl. I've noticed
that no matter what the situation is,
whether I'm right, whether I'm wrong,
whether it's not established, like
honestly, bro, they, you know, that
won't Well, I'm not scared of any man.
Okay, let let me let me let me let me
tell you something, bro. I'm not scared
of no man. Yeah, listen. I was in a club
last uh not last Thursday, the Thursday
before that. This [ __ ] started trying to
give me [ __ ] attitude. I [ __ ]
snapped. I went I was going [ __ ] mad
and I said I will say it in front of any
man right here right now. And there was
people that were taller than me as well.
I said I will say it in front of [ __ ]
any man in this club. And I did. I
[ __ ] did, bro. I did. I said let any
man try to [ __ ] put their hands on
me. That's what I said. And you know
what I said? I said, "You know what? If
I get jumped and if I get beaten, guess
what? It took more than one of you, bro.
Cuz I know that not one of you can beat
me by yourselves." I was going [ __ ]
mad, bro. I was going sick. Do you think
anyone's going to do anything to me,
bro? Are you mad? They'd have to kill me
when I'm in a mood like that. They'd
have to kill me, bro. Are you mad? [ __ ]
off. You know, and I did say that as
well. Yeah. Yeah. You're always trying
to You're trying to understand what's
going on. Of course you do, mate. Yeah.
You always make excuses for women. You
ain't got no bad words to say about
them. It doesn't matter what the
situation is. People love defending
women and blaming men. This is why you
are so stupid to even ask for advice on
any kind of social media because all
they're going to do is defend women
whether they're right or wrong and blame
you. It doesn't It's stupid. It's
[ __ ] stupid. They've got no bad words
to say about women. People say you can't
get rejected because you're a manta and
he has a wife, job, and plenty of money.
Bye-bye now. Don't bring it on my
channel. I've told you about a million
times. Stop bringing this weird drama on
my channel. Bye-bye now. Have I ever hit
a woman before? No, but I will do if
this [ __ ] comes out next Friday. If this
[ __ ] comes out next Friday, I'm going to
[ __ ] whip their ass. I'm going to
whip their ass. I'll do it in front of
any man, bro. Around Manchester City
Center as well. I bet you any money. I
don't think so, mate. I don't think any
man's going to be stopping me. Believe that. Yeah.
[ __ ] believe that. Why they allowed
to be [ __ ] all their life? Why are they
allowed to be piss takers all their
life? Yeah, I want to start now. Yeah.
Yeah. Why are they allowed to be piss
takers all their life and take the piss
out of you all your life? Why is that?
Why is that? Why are they allowed to do what they
want? No, it's not actually not that big
and the city center is not that big.
Manchester is not that big. Not compared
to London and Birmingham. Not really. Everything's walking
distance. I really really despise him. I
really really hate him. Like worse than
Ant-Man. Let this [ __ ] come out next
week and I will whoop their
ass. But they always make excuses for
women. Let me let me let me let me give
you this example for reason. Have you
ever heard a woman get told to work on
herself? No, I don't think I have. Have
you ever heard a woman get told a man
doesn't owe her anything? Nope. I don't
think I No, definitely haven't. But
isn't it mad that when a man complains
about a woman, he's told all of these things?
Sexist. Absolute sexist. Sexist. Biased.
And is And they're not equal at all. You
know, I don't care, bro. Let the [ __ ]
come out next
week. I don't care. I'm putting posters
up of the [ __ ] What are they going to
do? Put me in prison. What are they
going to do? Put me in prison for
putting up posters? I don't think so,
mate. What are they going to do? So, I
pull up poster of this [ __ ] What are
they going to do? Put me in prison. I
don't care, bro. You know, I said I'll
tell the judge I've had it. I've had
enough with these [ __ ] over these
years. Over the years with these [ __ ] You
know, I don't give a [ __ ] I don't give
a [ __ ] about getting arrested. I don't
care. Do you not understand? I'm beyond caring.
No, you don't hear it all the time,
mate. No, you [ __ ] don't hear it all
the time. Cuz I'm 27 and I've never
heard it. A woman is never ever told
she's wrong when she's moaning about
men. I've done an
experiment. Really? I don't care. And I
don't care. Do you not understand? I
don't care. Getting done for harassment
and malicious communication. I don't
care. So there's no point you talking
about all of these grassy things, right?
And no, you don't get the same treatment
because I've done an experiment on this
and I've actually put it on a community
post. Uh, no, you don't get the same treatment.
Um, yeah. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Good. Yeah.
Yeah. I'll get arrested for beating her
up. Yeah. I'll get arrested for saying
I'm going to beat her up. Oh, really?
Oh, wow. That's nice, isn't it? I won't
make it to Manchester. Well, we'll see, won't
we? So, yeah.
Evil little [ __ ] Evil little time
wasting little [ __ ] I've had it up to
here with it. Why do you think I didn't
go out Saturday? I don't know if you follow my
channel. Yeah. Why do you think I didn't
go out Saturday? Because I know what the
women are like in this country. They're [ __ ] They're
[ __ ] They're [ __ ] [ __ ] and they're [ __ ]
[ __ ] I've done an experiment on
this. No, women don't. Okay, I just told
you I've done experiments on this. I've
done a I've pretended to be a woman moaning about
men and I have been a a man complaining about
women. How do I know? Because I
pretended to be a woman moaning about
men. And guess what? Everyone felt sorry for
me. Everyone felt sorry for
me. Literally, everybody felt sorry for
me when they thought I was a woman. And
then when I was a man, they all blamed
me and called me
nailed. Same person, different gender.
I've already done experiments on this.
Trust me, I'm I might be insane, but I'm
right because I've done an experiment on
this. I've also done experiments on
dating apps as well, and I can confirm
that it's rigged against men. And it's
not incel talk, it's real talk because
I've done experiments on this.
Yeah. You can go self-reflect on another
channel. No self-reflecting on my
channel. Exactly, Dregs. You already
know I'm acting like a child. Okay, I'm
acting like a child. Why? Cuz I'm sick
of getting took the piss out of by
women. Why? Because I'm standing up for
myself. Because I don't like these women
keep taking the piss out of me. That's
That's me acting like a child to you.
Really? That's me acting like a child
because I'm sick of these women mocking
me and hurting me. That's me being a
child. Really? I don't think I I I would
see any child moan about that. You know what I'm
saying? Can you get K's number, John
call? Yes, because I'm sick of these
women. Yes, because I'm sick of these
evil, evil, scummy little women. And
people keep telling me, "Oh, oh, oh,
they're not the same. They are all the
same scum. I've been dealing with them
for years. I've been dealing with these
women for years and they are all evil.
They're evil. Evil they are. I know cuz
I've dealt with them for years. I know.
I've spoke to more than anyone in the
world. I know. I know. I know. I've got
approaching videos on my channel. I've
got approaching videos on my [ __ ] channel,
bro. You know what I
mean? And that's it. I know these
things. I know these things. I know what
they're like. They're [ __ ] evil. Evil
scum of the earth. That's literally what they
are. Yeah. M mild psychosis. I don't I
don't think so, mate.
I [ __ ] hate these women. I literally them. You
know, you know what I'll do when I meet
you, Fies? I'll run my dick down your
[ __ ] throat and make you say [ __ ]
sorry. That's what I'll
do. Yeah. I don't give a [ __ ] if I if I
end up arrested. I don't give a [ __ ]
mate. My life's not worth living
anyways, so who
cares? Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] mate.
My life's not worth living anyways. Who cares?
Yeah, I run my dick down your [ __ ]
throat and make you say [ __ ] sorry, little
slag. That's what I'll [ __ ] do. Make
you say sorry, little
slag. Yeah, suck my dick. How about you
suck my [ __ ] dick? How about that?
Yeah. How about you suck my [ __ ] dick? Huh?
Yep. If you didn't know, most of all,
this people are pretty brutal when it
comes again. I've just told you that I'm
not scared of any
man. Um, I've literally just told you
that I'm not scared of any
man. So, I don't know why you're am I
supposed to be scared or bro? I'm not
scared of no man. I don't care. Simple.
Yeah, you have a good point. How you how
can you go and living a normal life when
Sha and Red Star are ruining my life?
Sean and Red Star are ruining my life,
mate. I get more money than both of them
combined. I'm better looking than them.
My mom didn't starve me. I've got teeth.
I've got designer clothes. I get over
three grand a month. Yeah, they're
really ruining my life, bro.
Congratulations. My life is truly truly
truly truly ruined. Someone that gets
over three grand a month, better
looking, have teeth, live in London, mom
didn't starve me. Yeah, my life's truly
ruined, bro. Cry me a river. Stop embarrassing
yourself. Stop embarrassing
Yeah. Again, don't talk about people you
don't know. I think that's the saying there. So
yeah, but bro, I'm not scared of no man
that's in prison. I'm not scared of no
man. Like, yeah, I'm not scared of no man at
all, bro. Like, you people don't ruin
people's lives on here. You're just
repeaters. You don't ruin anyone's life.
You're just [ __ ] repeaters.
like, "Oh, you're generalizing." I said,
"My generaliza my my generalization is
warranted." After all them bad
experiences, your generalization is
warranted. It is literally it is
warranted. After all these bad
experiences, your generalization is
warranted after the period of time. And
if you don't know what that means, then
yeah, I'm not going to jail. I don't
know why you keep saying that I'm going
to jail. I'm not going to
jail. Like, I don't even know why we're
talking about going to jail. I'm not
going to jail. I'm not even getting
nicked. I don't even know why we're talking about it. [ __ ]
weirdos. Yeah, I'll get slashed. Yeah,
good luck with that. Well, I'm not even
going to prison. I don't even know why
why we're even talking about prison. Why
are we even talking about that? [ __ ] hell.
Yeah. Okay. Go do what you want. Do what
want because you're talking about
beating up women. Oh my god. No. They
don't go to [ __ ] Do you know how many
times I've been leaked over YouTube for
talking about rape acid and they never
ever charge me ever, you know? Never
ever been charged. Never. I've been
nicked so many times over this website.
And guess what? It's case closed every
time now. It's why they don't bother.
Stop talking about prison and stop
talking about grassing as well, you
little bongo. Cuz I'll just start
blocking people that keeps talking about
that as well.
Yeah. See, this is the thing, Charlie. I
really want to do it, Charlie. But but
like Antman did. Well, he went around
with an axe, but I don't want to go
prison for them. That's the thing. I
don't want to go prison for these little
rape victims. That's why if I if I do
like if I do like posters, if I do like
[ __ ] posters, then I mean, they can't
really do anything. I mean, yeah, you
could get nicked, but I don't think
you'd go to prison.
But that's I don't want to lose nine
months of my freedom because of them.
Because of them [ __ ] And then when
you're in prison, they'll be shagging
other men anyways, laughing at you. Cuz
that's what they
do. You can message her all you want for
reason. I don't give a [ __ ] She's not a
victim. I don't know why you're going on
like she's a victim. You always take the
woman's side. This is what I mean with
these people. They always take the woman's
side. No, I'm going to do the posters.
No, I'm going to do the posters. I'm
going to do the posters in Manchester.
I'm doing that 100%. I'm doing the
posters. No, I'm definitely doing the
Yeah. No, I'm definitely doing the
posters that she's a pedophile and she
touched up my
kids. Yeah. And you know what? And guess
what as well, Freze? No, no man deserves
to be ghosted and led on. No man
deserves to be ghosted and led on and
gave false hope, but I don't see you
saying anything about that. Yeah, no man
deserves to get his time wasted and be
sexist at 27. But you don't see me moing
about it and crying about
it. No, I'm going to put up posters.
I'll say that she's a pedophile that
touched up my son, even though I don't
have a son. Yeah, I'm a [ __ ] like that.
You be a [ __ ] to me, I'll be a [ __ ] to you.
Really? I don't care. Oh, could I go to
prison for that? I don't care. Yeah, I'm
going to line the posters.
Yeah, this [ __ ] in America that [ __ ]
with me for breeze, I made her change
her number. I've made her um I made her change her
number. I made her
um her boyfriend split up with her. I
made her go to the police on me, you
know. No, I don't give a [ __ ] if it's
way too far. leading somebody on is way
too far. Lying to somebody and taking
the piss is way too far. You don't get
saying about it, mate. I'll tell you
when it's too far. I will tell you when
it's But no, no opinion on what they've
done for Breeze cuz I notic that we're
all talking about what I said I'm going
to do. Any opinion on what they've done
or just completely innocent cuz it's a
woman. Yeah, I thought so. Yeah. Any any
opinion on what they've done and what
other people have done in the past? No.
Completely innocent. Yeah, we'll call
them completely innocent because they're
all women and they don't have a bad word
to say about women in this society. They
ain't got no bad words. They only blame
the man. They don't care about what
women have done. Anything a woman does,
they justify. Oh, maybe they change
their mind. Oh, maybe it's this or maybe
it's that or maybe it's this. They will
literally make any excuse just to defend
women. And no one can tell me I'm wrong.
No one can tell me I'm wrong. Well, they
do. Well, two wrongs are closer to a
right than one wrong. So, yeah. Yeah.
You have no opinion on what they
do. I don't give a [ __ ] if it's You
don't get a say in the matter, but you
don't get a say in what is too much. You
don't get a say in the matter. It's not up for
discussion. Yeah. I don't give a [ __ ] if
it's worse. I'm sick of these [ __ ]
wasting my time and taking the piss.
Why give somebody your number and speak
to them for 3 days if you was just going to block
them? What the [ __ ] And no, it was not
about no hotel. They was not scared. So,
stop making excuses. So, what is it? So,
what is it then? So, what is it then?
Huh? What is it? Stop making excuses for
them. What is it? You
know, I'm going to Manchester, bro. I
promise you I'm going
Manchester. No, there's no starting
fresh. What? What do you mean starting
fresh? How can you start fresh? It's
going to be the same experiences with
women when you try again. Why? What?
What do you mean start fresh? How can
you start fresh? It will be the same bad
experiences with women again. It's never
changing. It's never ever changing no
matter what you do. This is what I'm
trying to say.
And at the end of the day, like,
someone's got to pay for keeping me
single for 27 years. I've been single 27
years because of these [ __ ] Someone's
got to pay for
it, you know. No, no, no, no, no. I will
continue bothering women cuz they they
owe me sex. They literally owe me sex,
you know. They've kept me [ __ ] sexist
for years at a time, months at a time.
They've kept me single for 27 years. No,
I will keep bothering them. I will keep
bothering them. I will keep bothering
them and bothering them and bothering
them every [ __ ] day until I get what
I want. I will I will keep [ __ ]
bothering them, you know? I will keep
bothering them and bothering them and
bothering them because at the end of the
day, these people have kept you single
for 27 years of your life, you
know. Yeah. Okay. Of course you have.
Yeah. Good for you. Good for you. Good
for you. Yeah. Yeah. Good for
you. Like these [ __ ] have kept me
single for 27 years of my life. Imagine
that. 27 years. Someone's got to [ __ ]
pay. You know, someone's got to pay,
bro. Someone has literally got to pay.
He does. He He would have told
everything about on here.
Yeah. Huh? You're another fat [ __ ] as well, aren't you?
Yep. Yeah. [ __ ] you. You're another fat
[ __ ] from the
north. It's me that's kept myself
single. It's me that's kept myself
Really? Oh, okay. So, when I've been on
dating apps and they don't work, I done
that by purpose. When I've approached
women and they pretend they've got
boyfriends or they give me the
runaround, that was all me. Oh,
really? Really? When I went to all of
these places um trying to meet women and
trying to meet this woman in Manchester
next week, that was all me. Whoa.
Okay. Well, at least I found out the
answer. Oh, it was me all along. I
didn't even know that. Oh, you learn
something new every day. It's never the woman, is
it? It's It's never the woman, is it,
Yellow Man? It's always the poor [ __ ]
that's trying everything.
Oh. Oh, it's always the man's fault,
isn't it? It's always the man's fault.
But I wonder if I had a cup between my
legs if people would be blaming me.
No. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. They
give me the negative experiences. They
make me negative. As soon as I talk to
them like this Lizzy and then and then
they give you false hope and then you
get the bad experiences again. It frames
your mind thinking women are all the
same. They are. You have gave them
charts upon charts upon charts to prove
you wrong. And literally every time they
prove that they're all the same. And
this has been going on now for years.
This has been going on now for years and
years and years and years and years.
They are the ones that have made you
negative your experiences with them. Now
I know that I've said this like many
many many times. They are the reason you
are the way you are. If you had better
experiences, you'd be happier. You'd be
positive. You can't be positive when all
you get is
negative. You can't be positive when all
you see is negative, you know. And
that's a quote from Eminem. And that is
a that is a quote from Eminem. How can
you be positive when all you see is
negative? That's the truth. That is
facts. That is facts. There's some other
real quotes out there. If you didn't get
such bad experiences with these [ __ ]
women, you'd be a much better person. a
much happier person with a better
mindset. Isn't that right,
Charles? Um, women have made me
negative. My experiences with them have
made me negative. My experiences with
them has made me no longer be positive
and it has made me more more hopeless.
Every time you get these negative
experiences with women, it makes you
negative and so low and so hopeless.
Nope. Nope. Nope. they are negative
which makes you negative because if that
was not the case that means that you're born
negative that why would no one's born
negative no one's born positive you are
the way you are cuz of these women no
matter what you say I know cuz I've had
these experiences I know what they're
like I know what these women are like at
the age of 23 24 I traveled all over the
country more than anyone my age time and
time and time again and I was proven
right with these women time and time
again. I went to leads. I almost got
into it with a bouncer. I went to
Sheffield. I went to Birmingham. I went
to Middlesbrough. I went to Newcastle.
And literally all of these women are
exactly the same. Like that's what I
that's what I learned over these years.
Every week I'd go to a new city, 6:00 in
the morning, I'd wake up and I was
proven right every time with these scam.
No matter what people said. No matter
said. No matter what people [ __ ]
said. Oh, did your dad say that? Well,
guess what? Why don't you put your Why
don't you put Why don't you put your Why
don't you get your your dad on the on
the Hangouts and I'll explain to your
dad why I'm saying these things, won't
I? I will explain to your dad why I'm saying these
things. I'll explain to your dad all the
bad experiences I keep getting. I will
show your father the screenshots and I
would love to see what he has to say
about that. So why don't you get your
father on the hangouts and I'll say
these women keep playing with me and
messing with me. I have the screenshots.
I've got the evidence and I would like
to see what he says to that. Please do.
Please do. Exactly. You can't. And I'm
sure after that And I'm sure after I
show him what I show him, people will understand. Exactly.
Gone. Go on then. Get your dad on here
and I and I and I and I'll show your
dad. Yeah. Well, guess what? These women
make my blood boil twice as much. Oh,
does it make his blood boil? Well, guess
what makes my blood boil? These women in
this country. These women and their time
wasting their time wasting games, you
know. Yeah. These women are these time
wasting game. They're time wasting
games. And that's exactly why. Yeah. I I
know what it's like to for your blood to
boil, mate. I had it all last night. I
had it when I woke up. I know about your
blood boiling. I would know all about
your blood boiling.
You know what I'm saying? You
know, I know I know what it's like for
my blood to [ __ ] boil, mate. Cuz I've
had it with these [ __ ] for
years, you know? I've had it with these
[ __ ] for [ __ ] years, mate.
Do you know what I'm saying,
bro? Why do you think I didn't go out
Saturday? Cuz I didn't want to deal with
him anymore. I wanted to get away with
it. Get away from it. You
know, do you know what I'm saying, bro?
Like, I I didn't go out Saturday cuz I
wanted to get away from it.
Mate, 27, mate, you do realize that I've
probably done more traveling than you at
the age of 27. I've probably met more
women than you at the age of 27. You
really think just because someone's 27,
they've got no life experience? Come on, man. Come
on. So So yeah.
And that's it,
lad. Uh, if you didn't have bad
experiences in the first place, Lee, you
wouldn't be like this. That them pissed
them taking the piss out of you. They've
made you like this. They're the cause of
it. If if you if you didn't get bad
experiences with them in the first place
and get took the piss out of, you
wouldn't be like this in the first
place. So stop trying to reverse the
psychology. You are like this because of
women, because of these girls. They're
making you like it. If you did not have
these experiences with them, you
wouldn't be like this. There is so only
so much that somebody can take. They're
the reason that you're like this in the
first place interacting, talking to
them. You they're the reason you are the
way you are. If it if it wasn't
listen creepily approaching, there's
nothing wrong with my approaching.
There's nothing wrong at all with my
approaching. You know, he's going
around, they find all this stuff online.
Um, stop stop using that as an excuse.
That would never ever happen. That would
never ever happen. Nero, that would
never ever happen. You
know, that would never ever ever ever
happen. You know, that guy Q, that black
guy, he still talks to me. He's a real
one. He's a real one. You
know, I'm going I'm going Manchester. I
don't care. I'm going
Manchester. I don't care. I'm going,
bro. [ __ ] it. I don't
care. They're not going to [ __ ] find.
I think. Yeah, I did forget about that
TW, mate. Do you know that Twitter? No
one knows about it. Every single person
I've met, they No one knows about it.
Nobody knows about it. Stop trying to
make excuses for [ __ ] women. again.
Look, you're you're doing it again.
Look, that is true. What would happen if
you meet someone, it's all going well,
but they finding stuff online that could
really affect your relationship. You're
just trying to make excuses for women
again. This is exactly what I'm saying,
bro. This is exactly what I was saying
last night. Yeah. In the kitchen for
like about an hour. They just make
excuses for girls. That's all they do.
This is what I'm saying. Anything to
make excuses for them. Whether it's
things that you said online, oh, it's
this. Oh, it's that. Oh, it's this. They
will do nothing but defend women. This
is why I never complain on subreddits no
more. This is why I never go online
asking for advice because all they're
going to do is stick up for women no
matter what they've done. That's why I
don't, bro. You
know, mate, you get a job. I don't need
a job. I don't need a job. You get a
job. All they do is stick up for [ __ ]
women just because they're [ __ ]
women. That's all they ever do.
There's no hope for me. There's no hope
for me. I'm living proof of
it. I'm living [ __ ] proof of
it. You know, I'm living proof of
it. All they do is make [ __ ] excuses
for [ __ ] women, trying to blame
things that you've said, but you've said
the things you've said because of the
bad experiences in the first place.
because of them in the first
place trying to make [ __ ] excuses for
them. Oh, what if they find things you
said or maybe they were scared or No,
no, no, no, no. They're not simps,
they're white knights. No, no. They're
not simps, they're white knights. That's
the actual correct term for them. You
know, stop comparing me to other
people. Oh, this is another thing they
like to do on Reddit. This guy on Reddit
was doing this yesterday. They like to
compare you to other people. They like
to tell you that if one person has met
somebody, that means you can meet
someone. That's not how that works.
That's not the way that life works.
Because in in in life, right, there's
not someone for everybody. And I told
him, what about all of these single men
that's never kissed anyone? Then what
about all these virgins? And they're out
there. It doesn't matter if there's only
very few of them. You know, they're out
there. They're definitely definitely
definitely out there. You know, you
can't compare one person to another.
That's not the way that works.
Everyone's made different. Everyone's
different. No, it it doesn't mean that
it's a you problem because my
approaching videos show that it's women.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. And and I'm
glad that you've said that because my
experiences on my channel shows that
it's women because there's me
approaching people normally. There's
messages that I've put up there proving
that it's not me. And that's all. And
this is what I'm saying, bro. Yeah. And
this is exactly what I am saying. Yeah.
It proves that it is women. It proves
it's women. Okay, for I I'll put I'll
put an approach video up right now.
Right. Listen one second. I will put an
approach video up right now.
Yeah. Me how it is me here. One second.
Let me let me let me link you this
video. One second. One second. You tell
me how it's Yes. They're not interested
because they've got unrealistic
standards. They're stuck up [ __ ] that
think they're better than you. That's my
whole [ __ ] point. Because they think
that they're better than you. Because of
simps. Yes. Yes. Yes. Because they're
evil. They've got unrealistic standards.
They're scum. Yes. I [ __ ] know. And
they're not interested in you either.
You. They're not interested in you
either. And all women need to get raped.
I hope all women get [ __ ] raped. All
of them. They're [ __ ] I hope they all
get raped. They're [ __ ]
Simple. They think they're better than
you as well. That's why you're still a [ __ ]
virgin. And I hope they all get [ __ ]
raped. They see little
[ __ ] And that's it, bro. You know,
it. They think they're better than you
as well. They think they're better than
you as well. That's why you're still a little
virgin. Yeah. Simple. And that's why
you're still a little [ __ ] virgin.
Probably playing with your mom's [ __ ]
every [ __ ] day. You little [ __ ] There you
go. Oh my. That was painful. What is it?
What? What's the excuse this time for
Breeze? What's the excuse this time?
What's the excuse this time for a woman?
What's the excuse this time? said the
wrong things, moved my foot left and not
right. Come on, let's hear these excuses
for women because you've always got a
load of [ __ ] excuses for women. So,
what is it this time? You know, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no. Okay. And Lee, I and
I'll explain it to you again. My
attitude is because of my experiences
with them. So I had these negative
experiences with them, these disgusting
piss taking women and they made me feel
this way after I kept getting these
experiences. They made me like this. The
piss taken, the waste of my time. They
have made me like this. They formed an
opinion on me. Now I didn't start off
like this. I started off normal, nice.
Their experiences with me have made me
like this. Like there's only so much
someone can take. All women are the
[ __ ] same. I have met more than you.
I have met more women than you. Right. I
have met more women than you. They are
all the [ __ ] same. Don't you [ __ ]
dare try and sit there and tell me
they're not all the same. They are all
the same. Scaven the earth, mate. I have
spoke to more than you will ever in your
whole [ __ ] life. Yeah. They are all
the [ __ ] same, bro. Don't you dare
try and sit there and tell me after my
experiences they're not all the same.
[ __ ] off, [ __ ] Suck my dick. How
about my dick not being the same as your
[ __ ] dad's? You silly little [ __ ] You
know, [ __ ] off, you silly little
[ __ ] [ __ ] off, you silly little [ __ ]
They're not all the [ __ ] shame. Yeah.
And again, there's nothing wrong with my
approach. There's nothing wrong with my
approach. She was completely fine. But
again, blame the man. Blame the man.
Blame the man. That's all you can
do. All you can do is blame the [ __ ]
man that's trying to get you [ __ ]
sexist little [ __ ] You're sexist
little [ __ ] [ __ ] That's what you
are. You're all [ __ ] sexist about not
all women are the same. They're all the
same kind of scum. All of my life I've
never been proven wrong in 27
years. Yeah. Well, yeah. Cuz it was
interesting to hear what the excuse was.
I asked for your opinion because I
wanted to hear what the excuse
was. Yeah. Cuz I wanted to hear what the
excuse was. Huh? You always have your
own experiences for women. No. Don't
take drugs. Don't take nothing. Don't
hardly drink. You are [ __ ] unhinged.
You silly little [ __ ] [ __ ] off, you
silly [ __ ] And if I ever meet you, I'll
run my dick down my but down your
[ __ ] throat and make you say [ __ ]
sorry, you silly [ __ ]
Yeah. That's it. Yeah. I come across
this bit creepy. You keep telling
yourself that, you know. I know, bro. I
know. I know. Oh, I know. I know. I
know. I know. They don't
understand. Just the same excuses they
always make. Yeah, I'm I'm creeping
these women out. Nice excuse. Cute little excuse.
Yeah, they always make excuses for
women. All these women can't be wrong.
You know what makes me laugh? You [ __ ]
when compl by a man. Bye-bye now. Change
your attitude and
approach. And I'll explain to you again
that my attitude is because of my
experiences with them. No matter how
many times you explain this, Greavvesy,
they don't get it, do they? Can't be
wrong. All of these women are [ __ ]
definitely wrong. They're all wrong in
this country. They are all wrong. These
these women are 100% all wrong. 1
million%. And that's why I've got my
evidence up. That's why I've got all of
my evidence up to prove that it is
women. Evidence don't lie. Evidence
don't lie. I'm telling you my
experiences are on my channel. It's got
to be women. It's got to be. I have got
all of my evidence on my
channel. I've changed my approach. I've
changed my attitude. It don't make no
difference. It's the same bad
experiences. It's the same bad
experiences. Done this, done that, done
this, done that, done this, done that,
done this, done that. It's the same bad
experiences, women. And this is why I
put this on my channel,
bro. You I'm about to [ __ ] throw this
[ __ ] cup, you
know? Again, I'll explain to you again
that the attitude with it's come from
the bad experiences. Bad experiences,
attitude. Okay, let me explain this
about a million times again. Bad mind
frame come from the bad experiences.
List for example, speaking to the person
for 3 days and wasting my time. That
gave me a bad bad attitude. USA is a bad
experiences. Bad attitude. Bad
experiences equals a bad mindset. Bad attitude. bad
experiences are causing this bad mindset
and this bad attitude because of your
experiences with women. I've explained
it about a million times and you still
do not get
it. And you still do not get it. You
know, bad experiences, bad mindset, bad
attitude, bad experiencing women, bad
attitude, bad mindset.
bad attitude come from a bad experiences
with women. I don't know how many times
I'm having to keep explaining this for
these people to
understand. I I don't understand how how
many times, Greg, if you have to explain
yourself to these
people, but I guess they are white
knights and they are
simply honest. They will always defend
women. It's the same with Reddit.
They'll always defend the women. That's
their [ __ ] life,
bro. It's all about mindset and
personality. Well, yours can't be good
then because you're still a
virgin. Smashing his cup on the [ __ ] window, bro.
I literally feel like getting this cup
and [ __ ] breaking the [ __ ] window with it.
Yeah, I swear to God, bro. But now I've
got to replace the [ __ ]
window. Yeah, I know you're still
virgin, mate. Cuz you got no life
experience. That's why you defend women.
Anyone that sits there all day defending
women, it's not
good. It's not good. All they do is sit
there and defend women, that's why
they're still virgins.
Yeah, that's it.
Yeah, getting licked in it.
All women are exactly the same. They're
all the same. I believe it when I see
it. I will believe it when I see
it. I should explain it again. No
thanks. Yeah, I'll believe it when I see it.
I believe they're not all the same when I see
it. I hope this
guy now you can shout as loud as you
want. Yeah. Bad vibe. Yeah. Yeah.
Probably a bad vibe. It's always an
excuse, isn't it? It's always an excuse
when it comes to defending women. Don't
think I heard that one before. Well, may
maybe. Maybe. That's a new excuse. Oh, I
love these excuses for
women. I don't even think this ball probably do
it. I don't even think it bo probably.
I'm losing my [ __ ]
head. Bye-bye, S. I didn't even bo this.
I'm actually losing my [ __ ] head.
I didn't even know this [ __ ] got me.
Yeah, it's always an excuse for women, is
it? Like this is probably what like
people end up doing for years. They will
go they will they will think it's them
and they'll think oh you're doing this
wrong or you're doing this wrong and
you're doing that wrong and you're doing
this wrong and then you end up like 31
32 and it weren't you all along it was
the women and then when you go to Asia
you don't have none of these problems
and that's how you know that it was
because it was the women in this country
all along or America or Australia or
anywhere else you know anywhere else for
that matter you will know that when you
get on that plane to Asia none of these
problems happen that it happened here in
England. And that's how you would know
that by the age of 31, 32, it was women
all along. And that's how you know. And
know. All of the women the women hates.
No, it's not. It's not immature. It's re
It's reality. It's reality, mate. It's
reality. Maybe I should try a different
attitude. I can't. They've gave me a bad
attitude. I was speaking to somebody for
3 days from Manchester and they took the
piss out of me. They've gave me this bad
attitude because of them and my
experiences with them. That's the 10th
time today I've explained this. I can't
have another attitude because they keep
giving me negative experiences and
taking a piss out of me which has led to
this attitude which has led to this
mindset because you cannot be born
negative. You cannot be born positive.
You're a byproduct of your life
experiences and mine with women have
been negative and that's why I'm
negative towards them and that's the
only way it makes
sense you know. So you should have got
one of them. Have I tried a woman for
lead from leads? I have been to leads.
Yes, I have been to leads. It's England.
They're all the same. They're
westernized. They're [ __ ] It is
England. All the women in England are [ __ ]
No, the matter. My friend is probably
going to think I'm mad shouting all this
[ __ ] out and she's a woman and she's
hearing everything I'm saying. I don't
give a [ __ ] I'm saying to anyone's
face. I'm just sat here ranting about
[ __ ] women. They're the [ __ ] next
to our [ __ ] neighbor. They're [ __ ]
hearing it all. I don't give a [ __ ]
mate. Yeah, they are evil. They are
evil, mate. Have I tried a woman from
Sheffield? I've been all over England.
Does that answer your question?
Is that all over?
Huh? Um, I've been all over England.
They're all the
same. All the same. They're all the same in
England. All women are the same in
England. They're all the same in
England. All the same in England.
Doesn't matter where it is. They're all
[ __ ] They're all [ __ ]
Have I tried a Welsh woman? What part of
I've been all over England? Okay, I've
been England, Scotland, and Wales. Does
that answer your
question? I've been all over the UK
except Ireland. Ah, I think that's a
good one. They're all the same. They're
all the same countries. Wales, England,
[ __ ] America, Scotland, they're all
the same. Women are all the same. Unless
you go to
Asia, they're all the same. All the same
stuff. They give you bad experiences.
They're all the [ __ ] same.
Nope. They're all the same. Westernized.
Westernized. Nope. They're all the same.
All the same scrum. It doesn't matter
where they're from. Scotland, Ireland,
[ __ ] Wales, [ __ ] England, [ __ ]
Blackpool, they're all the same
scum. They're all the same scum of the
earth. Any westernized country, they're
all the same scum of the earth.
They're all the same scum of the earth,
mate. Westernized [ __ ] All the same.
Every single one of them are the same.
It took me a whole two years to actually
find out. I mean, surely to God, if I
was wrong, I'd be proven wrong by now,
Charlie. Think about it logically,
right? If what you're saying is wrong,
then wouldn't you wouldn't you have been
proven wrong by now? We wouldn't be having this
conversation. That just goes to show
that they're all the same. Because if
they really were different like people
make them out to be, you wouldn't be
here having this
conversation. You wouldn't be here having this conver. You
know, they are [ __ ] evil. Like you
wouldn't be here having this
conversation. You wouldn't be. You you
be you generally generally wouldn't be
if you if if I was wrong right and I got proven
wrong then why am I sat here moaning you
know women really really are evil I'm
surprised people don't
know yeah exactly exactly
bro yep exactly and that just goes to
show They're all the same. Do you
remember that time I went to Wales twice
in a week, Charlie? I went to Wales on a
Friday, then I went next and then it was
another Friday, I went again. Do you
remember? And I went
again. Yeah. And I went to And I went
again. Do you
remember? Yeah. Do you remember that?
And it was the same result. Bad
experiences, numbers that go, numbers
that don't reply.
If you meet someone, it's all going
great. She upsets you with something
minor, then you come out with this all
this. Um, you're making uh you're making
stuff up. Um, I've shown messages um
where they haven't even gave me a
chance. I have literally literally g
shown you messages like the one with
that Manchester one, the American one,
the French one, where they haven't even
gave you a chance. So, stop trying to
reverse the psychology and and make it a
pity party for women again. So, you
generally you so you generally not
believe you play a part in all of this.
Uh, no I don't. No, I
don't. No, I don't. Because I've done
nothing but be normal. I've done nothing
but be nice. So, I don't play a part in
all of this. No. Okay. You Okay. Okay.
So, you're trying to say that I I play a
part in all this. Okay. Okay. So, let me
let me ask you this question then. So,
why did USAY do what she done? and why
this one wanted Manchester to do what
she done then. Okay. If I play a part in
all of this, right? Um you tell me what
I done wrong there and you can't. So
there's no point making make accusing
people of things if you can't answer it.
Yeah, there might have been dates you
went on Charlie like a year and a half ago, bro.
Uh, and you might have [ __ ] it up with like
uh the only time it was me Charlie is
when I went on dates with people like a
year and a half ago.
Um, and they uh and I used to go on
about this USA Izzy and it used to freak
them out. That's the only time it was
me. That was the only time that it was
ever me is when I used to go on these
dates and I used to go on about this
[ __ ] when I was drunk and it used to
scare them off. But as far as the
approaching goes and the text and the
texting goes before getting the date,
no, it's definitely definitely
definitely them. I've got all the
messages. I've literally got all the
messages, you know. Bye-bye now. I've
got all the messages proving what I'm
saying is is is true. It's true. So, the
only time it was my fault is when I used
to [ __ ] up the dates cuz of this [ __ ] in
America. And that was like [ __ ] that
was like that whole year. So that's the
only time it was me. Other than that,
no, it's not me, it's them. I've got the
messages. That's why I'm asking for a
constructive criticism, but you can't
like look at Greavves. I showed
Greavvesy. That was you on Instagram
yesterday, wasn't it, Grievy? I showed
him about this [ __ ] in
Manchester. What did I do wrong? Tell me
what I done wrong. Tell me what I done wrong, Greavvesy.
It grieves. You couldn't even tell me
what I done wrong because I didn't do anything
wrong, you know. So, stop trying to
analyze what you've done wrong. No, no,
no, no, no. Cuz you haven't done wrong.
It's the women in this country and you
need to stop going on about it. It's the
women in this country. End of. She just
wasn't interested. But why did she waste
my time for three days then? Why was she
sending me voice note after voice note
after voice note if if you're not
interested? And why do you moan that you
can't find a nice guy if you're not
interested? I made some valid points. So
if you're not interested, you're going
to waste someone's time for 3 days,
right? Like it's like that's that
doesn't cut it, bro. It doesn't cut it
because these are the same people that
it's like I was saying to you yesterday,
they will go on and on and on how they
can't find a nice guy and where all the
good guys gone. But wasn't a guy
supposed to go to Manchester next week
to meet you and you [ __ ] them around?
You you run him through. You run all the
good guys through, you know? So,
yeah. Yeah. I mean, I would take account
for that. Yeah, I would take account for that. But
yeah, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You spoke to me for 3 days and you agree
to meet me. End of
story. End of [ __ ]
story. End of story, mate. Like, you
make an arrangement. You you you know
you you you stick with your plans. You
stick with your plans. End the story.
There's nothing that comes up. No, we
were supposed to meet next
week. So that's it. I don't want to hear
no excuses how they're not interested or
they found someone else. I don't care.
You know, you said that you was going to
meet me on Friday. That's
it. Yeah. Did you really? I don't think
so, mate. I don't think
so. I don't think so.
Yeah, I don't think
so. Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] you
know. And the nice woman and then the
nice woman wasted a nice guy's time. You
forgot you you you forgot to add that
bit yellow. The nice the nice girl nice
wasted a nice guy's time for three days.
led him on. This nice girl led him on.
Led him on and flaked and ghosted
without no explanation. The nice girl done
that. [ __ ] s [ __ ] white
knight. Yeah, good for you. Bye-bye
now. Bye-bye now.
Maybe it proves Nah, maybe it just
proves that she's a [ __ ] and all women are
[ __ ] You know, people love making excuses for
women. They just love making excuses for
It's crazy, bro. They love making
excuses for them, defending
them. Why don't I forget about this?
Because I don't like the fact that
they've g they've kept me single for 27
years. Yeah. Yeah. And you're being
sarcastic, but it isn't me. It isn't me.
And that's why I said if anyone messages
me on Instagram or Snapchat, I will show
them all the screenshots. Grievy, I
showed you other screenshots as well. Do
you remember on Instagram
yesterday? No, I'm not letting it go.
I'm not letting it go. These [ __ ] have
kept me single for 27 years of my life.
I was even showing [ __ ] greasy um
screenshots yesterday from other people from last week. You
know, you love blaming the man. It can
never be, "Oh, this woman's a [ __ ]
She's just never You never hear anything
like that, you know? That's
it. When will I get proven wrong then?
Anyways, so you say that all women
aren't the same and they're all perfect
and their [ __ ] don't stink. Okay. Okay.
So, why have I not met this woman yet?
Let's see what you're about. Bye-bye
now. Yeah. Let you know what I'm
saying. Yeah, they
do. They do, mate. They [ __ ] do. They
[ __ ] well do.
It's sad, isn't
it? It's sad,
bro. It is
sad. Yeah. Get a face tattoo. [ __ ] off,
bro. All my [ __ ] clothes are dirty as well. That's
it. It's a madness,
bro. It's a [ __ ] madness. Yeah.
Well, what are the suggestions? I have
listened to your suggestions. I've took
your advice and it doesn't
work. And it doesn't work. So
what? So what? H.
Yeah. If there was different
women, right? If there was different
women that were like this, we wouldn't
be having this
conversation. End the story.
So, they're all the same. Sad to say,
Lizzy, USA, Izzy, they're just all the
same. And then they moan that they can't
find people. They can't um they can't find nice guys, you
know, and that's what it is. [Music]
Fine. You need a holiday lad. As soon as
the sun comes out, the birds are wet.
Yeah, you keep telling yourself that,
buddy. You said that on Halloween as
well. Yeah, you said that in Halloween
as well. You said that in Halloween as
You keep taking a piss saying that it's
not me. Um, it's women. You You keep
taking a piss saying that, but my
approaches are proving
it. My approaches on my channel are
proving that it's women. As much as you
like to troll and no no, it is actually
showing that it is women. I know you're
trying to take the piss and you know,
you ain't got a bad word to say about
women. No one does in this day and age.
But that's what the videos are actually proving.
No, I don't believe it's not me. I know
it's not me because them videos are
completely completely completely normal.
And you can't even critique the
approaching videos. You can't even tell
somebody what they're doing wrong.
That's how I know it's not
me. I know it's not me. I know it's not
me. Cuz if you watch them videos, Grezy,
you can see that there's nothing wrong
with them approaches. And I've shown you
some messages as well, Grezy. I don't
think there was anything wrong with the
messages. If there is, tell me them
messages I showed
you. Them three messages I showed you,
right? Tell me what was wrong in them
screenshots. Tell me what I said wrong in them
screenshots. You know, you're saying
that I'm wrong. Okay, I'm wrong. Women
are perfect. Their [ __ ] don't stink.
Okay, so tell me what was wrong with
them with with them um
screenshots like the all of them
screenshots I showed you with three,
four different people. Tell
me. Yeah. No. No. No. It doesn't happen.
No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. It
doesn't happen. Okay. Grievous. So, if
we Okay. So, if that's
true, why keep trying when it's just
going to be the same old same old? Okay.
Okay. So, let's Okay. Okay. Let's go by
your logic. And it's not women. Their
[ __ ] don't stink. They're all
perfect. Yeah. We had common interests.
We loved horror films. Um, all kinds of
food. Yeah. We had similar interests.
age, same age, similar interests, everything.
Yeah. Yeah, man. Similar interests, uh,
same age. Yeah. Well, we voice noted. We
were voice noting back and forth, back
and forth, back and forth, back and
forth. Um, so anyways,
but anyways, moving forward, right, I'm
going to play devil advocates advocate
here and there. So, it's never women.
They're all innocent. Their [ __ ] don't
stink. I'm the big bad ugly wolf. So you
like to say so what would you what what
what what where would you go from here?
Oh, it was just voice notes. So do you
expect me to go out every single day,
every single week approaching when I
know these people aren't interested? Is
that what you want? Okay, let's not
blame women. They're all perfect. I'm
the big bad ugly greywolf. Okay, that
[ __ ] don't stink. Okay, so Okay, so
where would we go from here then? Let's
put all of this behind. So, what do you
expect me to go out every week talking
to people, them pretending they've got
boyfriends, me getting the same bad
experiences? Is that what you want? Cuz
I I don't know what it is you actually want, you
know. Well, I'm on dating apps as well, if that
helps. Well, I'm on dating apps as well,
if that helps. Uh,
Grezy, so what do you expect people to do?
If you could explain what you expect
people to do, right, then I could I
could actually understand it. But the
thing is, do you know why I don't I
don't go out anymore and try? Because I
know what I'm in for. I already know
what I'm in for. It's like It's like
jumping into a pool. It's like jumping
into a pool, but you already know you're
going to drown if you can't swim. Why
are you going to jump in the pool if you
can't swim, you idiot? You're going to
drown. I already know. I already know
that if you go out and you try, I
already know what it's going to be. I
already know exactly what it is going to
be. It's going to be I've got a
boyfriend. You're too old for me. If
only you were older. You're too young
for me. I'm speaking to someone. Um I'm
sorry. I just can't give you my number.
And then you get a few numbers. They
either don't reply. They reply, keep
replying, stop replying, arrange to meet
you, then don't meet you. And that would
be all she wrote for a week. That's why
there's no point even going out and
trying. That's not negative talk. That's
real talk. I know cuz I used to do it
every week, so multiple times a week
sometimes. I know how the cookie
crumbles on the kitchen table. So why
would you go out and try when you
already know it's going to be the same old same old?
So you know what I'm saying? And that's
it. Why would you go out and try when
you know it's going to be the same
old? I don't have OCD,
mate. I don't have
OCD. But what annoys me is that they'll
speak to you for three days. You've got
similar interests. who got similar
hobbies then okay they've lost interest
but now they're going to moan where all
the nice guys gone see the thing is
these women they generalize men but they
go for these men they're the only men
that they go for they get chances I
don't get chances so I'm right by saying
all women are the same and I've never
been proven wrong I'm in my rights to
say that they're not actually in their
rights to say that
because when they get an
opportunity somebody wanting to meet
them they flake
They [ __ ] you over, they be a [ __ ] to
you. So, but then they sit there and
then they wonder where all the nice guys
going, where are all the different guys
that don't cheat? That's what I don't
understand to me. That just doesn't make
any sense to
me to me. It just doesn't really make any sense.
Don't know if it makes sense to you, but
it doesn't make sense to
me. Tried telling them that I'm a drug
dealer. Well, there was one in Lucas I met
before. Yeah, I feel special. Yeah, but
that Yeah, but Greasy, to be fair to
you, bro, that's just
nitpicking. Like, to be fair with you,
bro, that's that is literally just
nitpicking. In all respect to you, there
was someone in Newcastle before she said
she liked drug dealers and she started
kissing me because I was from London.
But you do realize that you're actually just
nitpicking. Like, no offense to you.
You're saying, "Oh, is this is what I'm
saying is when it's to do with a woman,
they will make every single
excuse." No, no, no, no, no, no. She
stopped talking to me when I told her I
knew she was lying about blocking me on
Instagram. That's when she stopped. And
she was actually ignored before that. If
you actually look up, she was actually
ignoring before that and I had to
message again for her to reply. But no,
no, no, no. She stopped talking to me
and she blocked me when I told her that
I know you block me on Instagram if you actually look
properly. So, no. And she stopped before
that as well a little bit. They weren't
as constant even though she was on and
off of WhatsApp constantly.
So, no, she stopped talking and blocked
me period when I said like I know that
you blocked me on
Instagram. I don't have
OCD. I don't have
OCD. So, that's when
um that's when they
stopped. Why would they block you on
Instagram and then not block you on
WhatsApp? I don't understand.
But they get away with being piss
takers. They get away with being [ __ ]
all their life. But it's always the
man's fault. You done this wrong. You
done that wrong. All the excuses in the
book. All the excuses in the book you
hear and it's a woman. Oh, don't know if
anyone else noticed that. They always
make excuses for them. Always try to
find things to blame you. And it's every
and it's all of them as well. It's all
of the they do it all the time. You
know, they love licking women's ass
cracks. Must be some sort of
disorder. It's right for them to be cancelled their
life. But you're not allowed to react to
it otherwise you're negative.
sat looking at four
walls. Probably go on Reddit,
sleep, wish I'd have a heart attack.
Just the same old same old in this
country. Same old same old with women
and same old same old in this country. I
reckon I was I was born to have women
hate me. That's what I think. I was born
I was born cursed to have all these bad
experiences to be kept single. Like I
generally generally generally believe
that I was
cursed. I generally believe I was
Like as mad as that might sound to you,
but I believe
it. And I'm just going to go KFC later,
eat once a day as usual, and then that's
it. It makes you give up on life when
you've had all these bad
experiences. Yeah. It makes you give up
with life. makes you not want to go on.
It wouldn't make anyone want to go on,
would it, if they had that many bad
experiences? I don't
think. Yeah. I don't know why I'm not
like less. There's no point even me
going out. Even though I can go out. I
don't even know why I was even put on
Earth. Maybe to
suffer. Yeah. I think I was put on this
earth to suffer. And when I go on Reddit
and I moan about women, they all block me,
Charlie. They all block
me. They They ban me. They ban me from
Reddit. When I say stuff about women,
they ban me on Reddit,
Charlie. No bad words.
They've got no bad words to say about
him. No, the conversation was
fine. Yeah. They said that they were
scared yet they were texting you still
until you said about you. You caught them lying. Yeah.
Yeah. Ask me if I tried dating apps,
lad. Yeah. Well, at least I'm not a 5
foot [ __ ] like you who skint with
[ __ ] shitty trainers. Tell me
terrible ch trainers. At least I don't
let people come to my area and I use
probation as an excuse. Like a [ __ ]
like you. A [ __ ] like you. At least I'm
not a [ __ ] like you. I can I can actually say
that. Yep. Pretty
much. At least I don't let people come
to my area like you do. You little
[ __ ] You little faroot
nothing. You little faroot nothing.
4 foot nothing. It's so mad like how you
like you actually think you're hard when
you're just some little [ __ ] Like
you're just some little [ __ ] [ __ ]
know? That's all you are is some
[ __ ] That's all who you are. Yeah. No
one ran away from you though, did they
mate? No one ran away from you. But I
know I went to your area and you didn't
show up. I know I went to Turnpike Lane
and you didn't show
up. Does anyone remember that Turnpike
Lane? The little [ __ ] didn't show
up. Yeah, you're not about it, Terry.
You are your family. Please stop
embarrassing yourself, man. Please. It's
It's embarrassing. We've all seen you in
turn pike lane. You're not about that
life. Just just just keep keep quiet, please. embarrassing
yourself. Did you turn up? Did Yeah.
Well, did you turn
up? Why didn't you turn up, Terry? That
That would have been a win for you then,
would it? I didn't turn up. No, but why
didn't you turn up?
You said you was going to turn up in the
KFC and then if you turned up in the KFC
then you would have won. So why didn't
you turn up? You can't say I didn't turn
up if you didn't turn up. That doesn't make
sense. Yeah. I'm going to Manchester um
next Friday to do some posters.
Terry, you should tag along for the
ride. You've never been to Manchester,
have you before? You can tag along for the ride.
It's going to be a lovely
site. Put it up, bro. One second,
man. They blocked me on Facebook as
well. Oh, mate. The messages must be
coming through. The messages must be
Terry. Oh, Terry. The messages must coming through,
lad. Oh, they're getting the USA treatment.
Yeah, Timmy. They're getting the USA easy treatment
delayed. Oh, yeah. They must have told
her, is it? I messaged one of their
mates. their little mates, Terry. And
one of their little mates must have told him. [Laughter]
Oh, I'm crazy about
it. Nah, bro. Never groomed a
17-year-old in my
life. But yeah, she blocked me on uh Facebook.
Yeah, I was just messaging that
Manchester Izzy's friends and family and
she's blocked me on
Facebook. Yeah, I woke up in a bad mood
today, bro. Like, I'm lucky. Like, it's
booked for Friday. If if I didn't book
it for Friday, I would have went today.
I would have just jumped the train today
and done something. Yeah, bro. It's like
two two and a half hours to Manchester
Picadilly. I would have done it, bro.
Today, if I hadn't got that hotel
booked and I didn't book it, I I would
have went today, bro. I woke up fuming,
bro. I was going to [ __ ] chuck that
[ __ ] mug on a [ __ ] window. Yeah, I
hate him. I hate him, bro. I'm gonna
prove it as well on Friday. I'm gonna
prove it as well. I'm gonna prove it.
Yeah. If I if I bro I swear down if I
didn't book it I would have went today.
I swear down I was getting these mood
swings since last
night. So I've just been messaging her
family and that family and friends and
[ __ ] Yeah. [ __ ] her, bro. You mad. [ __ ]
off you silly little [ __ ]
Yeah, I [ __ ] hate
women. I hate
him. I actually [ __ ] hate him, lad.
Back. Oh, I'm doing some posters. I'm
doing some posters. Yeah, I won't have
KFC until later because I only eat once
a day. I only eat once a
day. Back to stalking again. You know,
boss, you know. You already know. Yeah. Yep. Pretty much. Yeah, pretty
much. Like these [ __ ] thinking that
they stuff without their family being
messaged and I I don't like that, bro. I
like them to pay for what they've done
to you, you know, like whatever it is. I
like them to be given grief like they've
given you grief. Like when they stop talking to
you. Yeah. It's funny,
bro. Yeah. I don't care. She's ugly. I
don't give a [ __ ] about that ugly
[ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ] about that ugly
[ __ ] Message her if you want.
Well, I don't know how I don't even
remember her number anymore. She changed
it. She's a [ __ ] [ __ ] Look at
her. I put a picture up yesterday. She's a [ __ ]
[ __ ] Imagine somebody that looks
disabled like that being a [ __ ] Imagine
Yeah, imagine that though. Steven
Howard. Yeah, I'm glad. I'm glad I'm
glad like he he left there. Good on him,
mate. Good on him. Because at the end of
the day, that's that's the thing. Like,
you think you're going to [ __ ] with me
and then go back to Charles and then
have some like, no, no, no. You don't
deserve no happy
relationship. You don't deserve to be
with with, you know, with someone, you
know, who I know I could [ __ ] up with.
Like, no, no, no, no, no. You're not
going to do me over and then think you
can get back to your little love life,
you little [ __ ] You know what I'm
saying? No, bro. No, no, no, no, no, mate. I'm
glad I made a [ __ ] change your number.
Don't be a [ __ ] to people in the
future. It's not worth it. Not to
someone like Peter
Belly. See, this is what I mean. All of
these things should have happened. you
should have just met someone left on
good terms or you know went separate
ways or I don't know still be with them.
You notice that whenever you get
involved with women there's always
drama. If you notice there's always
negatives and always drama just like
this [ __ ] in Manchester. Do you really
think I want to be going next week and
putting up posters of this [ __ ] over 200
miles away? No. But that's what it is
every time. It is drama with these [ __ ]
because they think that they can pick on
somebody who they see is vulnerable and
then when somebody gives it to them back
they cry about it. They moan. They
winge. They play
victim. And it's all from getting
involved with women. If you think about
it, it's all from getting involved with
women every single
time. Isn't it madness? with the
hand. Yeah, put in it.
Yeah. What my
quote? What quote? My quote.
She thought she was going to [ __ ] with
people in this country and then get on
with her life with Charles. That would never happen,
mate. Nothing bad, did it,
Grezy? They were put on this earth to fetch
food. Fetch food. be nasty
to they were also put on earth to hurt
people if you didn't know as well. Hurt people's feelings.
Message me on Instagram, wasn't it? Greasy.
I wanted to bang that Lizzy as well. She
was the [ __ ] same age as
me. We was planning to make love and
everything. Make love and have some
babies and stuff. That was the plan. But
I think I was living in fantasy
world. Yeah, I was living in fantasy
there. Is there a reason? Is there a
point of even like getting attached to
anyone? Is is
there? Don't think
so. I thought he was going to have babies. Steven
Howard. N was never out then, was
it? Um, well, I didn't Well, I did tell
her that, Terry. Stop trying to make excuses for
women. Stop trying to make excuses for
women again. No one spoke about babies.
No one spoke about sex. Stop making
excuses for women. I said that was on
the agenda in my head. You little
[ __ ] white knight. Stop making
excuses for women. This is what I mean,
Grezy. They will literally find anything
to make excuses for women. This is what
I mean. This is exactly what I mean.
They will make any excuse to
um to um to to um to fight to they'll
use any excuse to defend a woman and make
you Yeah, I can put these messages up,
mate. I put these messages up with these [ __ ]
Who's right about that
one? Well, how is he right when I when I
wasn't talking about we wasn't talking
about babies. We wasn't talking about
sex. So, how is he right? You've seen all the
screenshots. So, he's not right.
He's not right because nothing in the
messages said babies or sex. You're just looking for
excuses. So, how was he right when
there's no message that said
that? There was no sex talk. There was
no nothing. So, how could he be
right? Okay. Yeah, that's another excuse
then, isn't it? Like, do you really
think I would start talking about sex to
somebody that I've never met? I wouldn't
do that, Grezy. Do you know why? Do you
know why I wouldn't do that? Because
that would be the perfect excuse you
would need to blame the
man. You think I I was like trying to
hold it in things that I wanted to
actually say, but I didn't say it
because I know that if I said it, that
would be your perfect excuse to blame
the poor man that's tried everything.
That would be the perfect perfect
excuse. I'm not stupid. I know what you people do.
interests, places we've been, what we do
for work, where we live, just normal
stuff. We just general
stuff. But you you would always make
excuses for women. Always. You would
always make excuses for women. And if I
spoke about sex, that would be your perfect
excuse. We was talking about several
different things. I thought they were
actually going to meet. Wow.
[ __ ] hate women. I do. They're
[ __ ] I only spoke to this one
because they were messaging back on
Instagram days later and I thought I'll
give them a try. Maybe I'll get proven
wrong. Nah, I'm never proven wrong.
Oh, it's so funny. I'm never proven
wrong. Why am I never proven wrong by
any of these women? I'd love to be
proven wrong and come back on here and
say I was proven wrong. That just tells
you what what they're like in this
country. They're all the
same. They're all
exactly the same. So, you see with men,
men are all
different. Men are actually different.
Different personalities. Women are all
the same. Have you noticed that women are literally same?
Yeah, she's evil. She is She's evil. Yeah, they're
evil. Wish they were different. I wish
they were different in this country, but
they'll never be.
Sh. I know. And it it's just like it
gets it just gets worse and worse and
worse, don't it, bro?
Yeah. Good luck, mate. You won't. You
won't. Women are not all
evil. So, good luck, mate. Good luck.
Yeah, good luck,
mate. You said you were going to try
these dating apps soon, didn't you? Why
not give it a whirl? I can't use dating
apps. It's full of piss takers on
there. Like my in my life now, I just
have to give
up. I just have to completely give up.
Um, that's the only thing that I can do
in my life is just completely just give up with
it. That's my only option. Like, let's
forget about all the past now. You know
that moving forward, it's just going to
be the same old, same old, same old,
same old, same old. So, why even try?
You might as well just give up your
life. That's the way I see it,
bro. I can say I've been on a plane. I
can say I've been abroad. I can say I've
done this. I can say I've done that. I
would have no regrets just dropping
dead. Greavvesy would cuz he's not been
abroad. Greavves has not been on a
plane. But you get what I mean, bro.
Like if there was things I actually
wanted to do, everything that I would
have might I would have liked to have
tried in life is just completely
impossible. Like trying to get a woman,
have kids, that's just completely impossible.
anything that I everything that I would
have might might I may have liked to gave a
try basically. Yeah, it is. Yeah. Cuz if
you go out again next week trying to get
a woman, you're going backwards, not
forwards. That's it. Yeah. You're going
backwards, not forwards. That's the
thing. So, everything that I might have
liked to give a try. See, anything that
I want to do, I do it. When there's a
new film in the cinema, I've done it.
When I wanted to go on a plane, I've
done it. When I wanted to go on abroad,
I When I wanted to go abroad, I've done
it. Everything I've wanted to do, I've done
it. And now I'm at an age where maybe I
want to have a little family, but it's
impossible because it's impossible to
get a woman in this country. Like, you
don't think I would be in the cinema
right now if there was a new horror film
on? Of course I would be, man. I'd be in
a horror film before. You could say
[ __ ] Jack Robinson. But there's no
horror films out now until a month and 11 days.
So yeah, we just have to sit here
looking at two walls, four walls,
sorry. It's not nice, bro. It's not It's
not a nice life, you
know. Can't have kids, can't have a sex
life, can't have
nothing. It's bad. It's It's really bad,
you know. I wish there was a solution for
it, but there is none. You just have to
sit there and
suffer. But the whole my experience is
my experience has proved that there's
just there's just not someone for
everyone. I don't really like
McDonald's. I only get the nuggets like
at like 2:00 in the
morning. Yeah, but guess what, Terry?
I'll always have more money than all of
you. and I'd always be better looking
than all the years you use. So, at least
I've got that going for myself. Get more
money, have more
money. I mean, that's that's good. That
that would always be a good thing.
So, so really, you're just laughing at
yourselves in that in that in that uh in
that respect cuz you have got nothing in
your life but
YouTube. Nothing. You got to [ __ ] all.
So, yeah. I love laughing at you as
well. [ __ ] McDonald's. I don't really
care for McDonald's,
bro. But yeah. Yeah. Fronting benefits.
Yeah. Oh, wish this [ __ ] didn't [ __ ] me
around. I wonder what she looks like in
real life. She's probably really fat in
real life, ain't it? This Lizzy.
Yeah. Probably really fat in
it. So like I said to him I'd meet them outside the
hotel and there was a reason why I said
meet outside the
hotel. How does that creep somebody out
meeting somebody outside the hotel reception?
That's a normal meeting spot. But again,
they're just these all these little
things are all
excuses. It's like what ADM man said.
They want the perfect man. And no one's
perfect. So you're they want everything
perfect. And you're not
perfect. And I'm, you know, no one's
perfect. So they they they want the
perfect. Yeah, man.
I I stopped the approaching [ __ ] didn't
I? No, I just said to them, "Meet me
outside the hotel, the like the the the reception
hotel." Cuz I always stay in the same
hotel when I'm in
Manchester. And there's a reason why I
said that. And I said, "Oh, we can go
from there." So, no, it isn't a weird a weird spot.
It's not a weird spot at
all. But yeah, I was done with these
[ __ ] in this country anyways until like
but only cuz this person messes back. I
was like, "Okay, maybe this is someone
normal." But nah, they're all the same.
They're all the same. I don't even want
to deal with them no more. That's why I
didn't go out Saturday cuz they're not worth dealing
with. None of them are worth dealing
with. their attitude, their [ __ ] I hate him,
bro. No, she blocked me when I told her
like she she was trying to deny blocking
me on Instagram. I said, "Well, I'm sat
here next to my friend and he just typed
your name up on Instagram and you've
come up." So, when I told her that she
was lying, she that's when she blocked
me. Otherwise, she wouldn't have blocked
me, but then she probably just wouldn't
have met you. So, she only blocked me
when I told her that like, "We know
you're lying. Don't lie to me." You know
what I mean?
about you've deleted Instagram for a
bit. She doesn't know the
hotel. Listen, Ibis, it's the same hotel
I always stay at when I'm in Manchester,
when I used to go all the
time. So, yeah,
bro. Yeah, I know. She But soon as I
said that, like, I know you've blocked
me. I know you've blocked me. That's
when she she brought me on um on uh WhatsApp. So
yeah. Yeah, cuz she So what would have
she done then if you kept talking to
her? She wouldn't have met you. Surely
to god she wouldn't have met you. She
blocked you on Instagram. She Why would
she block you on Instagram and not block
you on WhatsApp? It doesn't make sense.
Well, they don't make sense. None of them make
sense. But I'm done
anyways. You just docked the
hotel. Good, bro. I don't
care. I don't really care to be honest.
And there's a few ibises in Manchester
as well. So, which one is it? So
So, oh, is that the hotel I'm staying
at? Maybe it is, maybe it's not. But that's
why I give to pursue these [ __ ] in this country.
Why do you think my when I went when I
went to meet my friend and I won some
money on the fish and
frenzy, I just went to get an
escort after I drunk with him, got an
escort, got a curry. I went cinema that
Friday as well. It was a good day. I
don't want to deal with these [ __ ] in this country anymore. That's
it. That's it, bro.
Yeah, it's madness, isn't
it? So, what do you reckon would have
happened if I didn't mention her
blocking me on Insta? Would have just
kept talking to you and then not met and
then not beat you in
it. Yeah, they would have kept talking
to you and then they probably just
wouldn't have met you, I assume, man.
Terry, you've never been to
Manchester. I don't know what I'm doing,
but I'm giving up in this
country. I don't really have any plans.
I need to renew my passport
um in like a week or two, and then I
need to think about where I'm going cuz
this is not normal, bro.
This is not
[ __ ] had I had it all last week as
well with these piss taken women, time
wasting women. That's why there's no
point me even going out. There's no
point of me even going out
drinking like anywhere far. There's no
point cuz all that's going to happen
is you would appro you will approach a
woman. She's either going to tell you
she's got a boyfriend, that you're too
old for her, you're too young for her,
she's talking to someone. Like, if if I
see, this is the thing, right? You say
that I'm no good at football bets,
right? If you put what women do in
William Hill as a bet market, I'd be a
millionaire cuz I know all what they do.
Despite people saying that they're all
different and they're not all like that,
they're not all the same. Bro, you put a
bet market on predictions for what women
do after they give their number or what
they do on dating apps, bro. I I I'd be retiring at 27. Like so
yeah. So yeah, that's how predictable
they are, you know? It's not like it's
not like football. I could I I'd be
rich. I would be [ __ ] rich. I know
all I know what they're like. I know
what they do.
Yeah. And I could put the correct thing
on what they do as well. Like football's the correct
score. Why would Why would you go to
Manchester? Cuz you're in your 40s. Why
would have you never been to
Manchester? Of course there's a reason
to go. Just going to different places,
different cities. And you say that I've got hobbies. Come on,
man. I said to try and easy easy today.
I feel like going out and hurting a woman.
Yeah, they do make you like
that. They do make you like
that. That it's like why would you even
go out and try when you already know the
result? Like before now,
why why are you going to go out and try
again when you already know the result? It's stupid.
you already know the result. Like that's
why I used escort for like two months. I
gave up for like two months to get away from
it. No, going to different cities is a
hobby. Yeah. Going to see new
places is a
hobby. Is a hobby. But that's why I got
escorts for like 2 months. Football bets
cuz just to get away from
it. to get away from it. You know these
people. They're [ __ ] evil.
My friend Q, the black guy, he's the
real one. He still talks to me after
he's seen all of the things I've said
and that. Yeah. I told him about this
[ __ ] woman [ __ ] pissing me off.
And he said this.
Look. This is what he
said. I said, "Excuse the delayed
response. I was out all day on the
bees." He said, "Yeah, I hear you. It's
mad frustrating, especially when it's
especially Especially when it's for no
reason. And then he was like, "But leave
her to it. No point getting into
shit." No point getting into
[ __ ] Like, he's a real one, bro. Like,
he's still got me on the gram even
though he's heard everything I've said.
It's probably cuz he's met me and he
knows what I'm actually
like. So, like, he knows me in it. So yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Don't know. Don't care. Um I don't
compare myself to other people.
and uh his girlfriend's about 50 years of
age. And I don't know, I don't I don't
I'm not one of these people that compare
myself to other people. And I said to
Antman, you shouldn't compare yourself
to other people as well because you'll drive yourself
insane. You know, we're we're all
different. And just because one person's
met someone, it don't mean you're going
to no matter what the circumstances are.
So, you can't compare
yourself to another person. I'm going to
Manchester to put up posters of that
woman that wasted my time. He just put a
bunch of videos he was
trolling. Yeah. you you comparing
yourself to people will only drive you
mad because just because one person has
done something it doesn't mean you're
going to do
something because there's not someone
for everyone. That's the whole point of
it is that there is not somebody in this
world for everyone. There's not someone
everyone. That's why there's me and
loads of other people. I mean, there's
people that are worse than me. Like,
they've never even kissed anyone.
They've never had sex. There's not someone for
everyone. Some people are made for no
one. Just like a lot of these people on
YouTube as well. Like, they probably
wouldn't have anyone if they weren't big
YouTubers and rich. You know, there, you
know, there's just not someone for
everyone like he did to Sean, but
nothing happened to him. Well, something
did happen to him. He went running to
the police scared. So, I mean, something
did happen to him and he ran like a
little [ __ ] and he come off of YouTube
for three weeks. He come off of YouTube
for three weeks. He ran to the police
and he was screaming. I mean, that was
enough, bro. It was definitely worth the
money and definitely worth the effort.
So, yeah. No, something did happen to
him. If you remember that whole 3 weeks,
he was scared shitless.
He didn't go to the plow and har for
like two months, but then when it all
died down and then he when it all died
down and that he come back to like a big
man. But he didn't get me nicked though,
did he? He didn't get me nicked. He
didn't get me nicked. But the police
picked me up and asked me questions for
20 minutes and let me go. That's not a
nick. That's not a nick. That's not a
win. You know, a win would have you been
meet you come and meeting me. But again,
he's a keyboard warrior. So keyboard
warrior cowards don't do that.
But no, that's not a win. The police
literally picked me up, took me to the
police station, asked me a couple of
questions, and dropped me back. I wasn't
doing anything that day
anyways. So, no, bro. And I wasn't even
putting handcuffs. No, bro. You know,
and that's what cowards do. Get the
police involved. So, but I know what
what's a W now. And me living in his
head rent free every day. He made seven
community posts about me yesterday.
Well, I really that virgin's [ __ ]
head went free. Kind of scary, but cool
at the same time.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm going to [ __ ] a life up,
lad. But yeah, he shot himself like three weeks.
Yeah, literally. Uh, but Mike, it's not
because of one person, though. It's an
amalgamation of things. It's all of
them. It's all of them. They're
[ __ ] They're horrible. They're
evil. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But it's not
just because of one person. It's all of
them. They've been pushing me and
pushing me and pushing me for [ __ ]
years now. All of these [ __ ] Yep. Just
to put a poster up who blocked me. Yep.
Who led me on and waste my time for 3
days? Yep. That's me. I've had enough of
these people. I have had enough of these
people one too many times.
Yeah. Yeah, definitely. They deserve it,
bro. They deserve it. And even if
nothing happens, it's just going to put
them in fear anyways. And if they're in
fear, that's that's all I want, isn't
it? cuz they're quick enough to take the
piss out of you and waste your time and
lead you on. No, bro. It's time for
payback. [ __ ] once in a [ __ ]
while. It's time for [ __ ] payback. So,
yeah. Yeah. He's a weird little virgin
there, bro. He's a weird little
virgin. Weird little virgin, mate.
So yeah, I'm going up north just to do that
bike. Yep. One too many times these
people take the piss. One too many
times, bro. One too many
times. One too many times.
one too many times with these [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah, sucks, man.
Um, no, no, no, no, no, no. And do you
want me to explain why? Because I'm
actually putting myself Okay. And I I'll
explain to you why. I'll explain to you
why. There's a few reasons. A, when I go
out and I do posters um, of that woman,
I'm actually going out there and
actually hand doing them myself. I'm not
hiding them behind the keyboard like
Traile. B, I don't know where that woman
lives. So, I mean, if I knew where she
lived, I'd be banging on her [ __ ]
door and I'm not hiding behind the
keyboard. With Tradal, he knew where I
lived and he still wouldn't come on my
door and he didn't even hand post
himself, making sure that, you know,
nobody would ever ever get him. So, no,
it's not ironic. It's completely
completely completely different because
he knew where I lived for years and he
still took the coward's way out. I don't
know where this [ __ ] lives. I didn't
know where this [ __ ] lives. So, there's
a big big big big difference. Nice try
though. But big big big big difference,
you know, because he knew where you
lived and he stole the cowardly way. I
don't know where this [ __ ] lives, you
know? I mean, I'm going to go to her
workplace. Well, I'm I think I know
where she works. I'm going to go to her
workplace and obviously she's going to
see me face to face. So, no, Tradal is just a
coward. You know, he knew two addresses
where I lived and he'd still rather send
theirs to the posters, which the post to
the neighbors, but the neighbors don't
care about the posters anymore. They're
just chucking. But you get my
point. She's got a brother. Yeah, I
messaged her, brother.
Yeah. Yeah. I messaged her,
brother. Nope, they didn't. Nope, they
didn't. I had an argument with my family
because of something else. Nothing these
people nothing these people have ever
done has ever affected me. They never
worked. They never worked. I argued with
my family for different reasons cuz I
kept making noise and waking the
neighbors up. So, no. The letter has
never worked. Nothing these keyboard
warriors have ever done has ever worked, you know.
Well, it is going to happen to her
because I'm going to go to where she
works and she's going to and she's going
to be scared anyways and she's going to
be scared. So, when I put up posters all
over where she works and that, she's
going to be scared. So, if she's scared
and you know and nothing happens, I'm
happy. As long as she's scared, [ __ ]
these [ __ ] need to pay for what they [ __ ] done,
mate. Pay for what they [ __ ] done.
Yeah, but it's going to put her into
fear cuz she's a woman and I'm going to
do it where she works. Yeah, but it's
still going to annoy her and put her into fear. So, you
know, and Manchester is not that big
compared to London. So, you pull it all
around the city center and that, they're
[ __ ] People will recognize them.
London's a bit different, you know?
So, I'll just make it so she's [ __ ]
[ __ ] scared to go out of her house, [ __ ]
scared to go to work. Like, as long as I
can just embarrass her and make her a
bit scared, I'm happy. Simple.
So yeah, I'm just I'm happy
then. If I can make her a bit embarrassed and
scared, then I'm happy,
lad. Nah, it's not even just cuz I was
blocked. I'm sick of all of them. I'm
sick of all of them. There's only so
much you can take, Nero. There's only so
much [ __ ] that you can take from these
women before you go mad. And that's that
was the final point, bro. And I had
already booked it
anyways. Yeah. It's not even just cuz I
was blocked wasting my time for 3 days
leading me on the other woman from last
week. It's an amalgamation of things.
It's not just one thing. It's an amalgamation of
things. Yeah, it was amalgamation of
amalgamation of things, bro. It's not
just, oh, you just you spoke to someone
and they blocked you cuz then you'd be
doing it to everyone.
Yeah. But you would know cuz you don't
deal with women and you just defend
them. So you What would you know? What
would you [ __ ] know?
What would you [ __ ] know?
Eh, just sit there and defend women all day, sad
bastards. You just sit there and defend
women. All right, bastard.
I wasn't offering money for a day. I was
[ __ ] I was offering money for a
Anyway, I need to go to KFC and I'll be back live
later. Stay Monday. Why does it feel like a
Tuesday? It feels like a Tuesday, don't it?
Yeah. So, I'm going to go
KFC. Everything about Terry, I've got
more money than you. I get more money
than you. I'm better looking than you
and I've actually got a decent pair of
trainers. Everything about you is an
L. Everything about you is an L. And you
say that, you know, your your family's
big, bro. [ __ ] your family, bro. Your
family ain't about nothing about your
family's going to do this. Your family
ain't about nothing, mate. Suck your
family, bro. How about that
one? Your shitty
family. Yeah. Anyways, I'll be back later. Anyways,