Feel like going back with a hammer, bro.
I'm not even joking, bro. And this was
like 5 hours
ago. Oh, it's annoying.
Can't even get into my emails. That's
it. I'm going to ruin my whole day
today. It's going to ruin my whole day tomorrow cuz
uh I probably won't get out of bed to be honest.
Yeah. Probably won't get out of bed to be fair.
I feel like going with a hammer, but I'm not even
joking. I swear to God, bro, I'm getting
these mood swings again over this. I
swear down over this gaming
[ __ ] I swear to God, bro. I swear to
God I am getting these mood swings.
these dirty stinky mooch wings again
that comes with gambling which is
something sick and ass don't tell you it
more evidence for me. Thank
you. I literally just want to go back
with a [ __ ] hammer and smash the
whole place up. I'm not even joking,
bro. This is something secular slots
don't tell you. By the way, this is
secular This is something secular slots
doesn't tell you.
evidence for me. Thank
you. Already gone to the police today as
well. So, keep it coming, mate. Easier
for me, to be
honest. More evidence these people give
me, the better it is for me. I love it,
mate. Keep the evidence coming, you know.
Yeah. Which is why I was actually near
the bookies cuz I actually went to the police today.
We're not going to get into that
anyways. That's why I was out in the first [Music]
plane. Mark, you've lost £100. You got
mood swings. You fell out with people again.
Yay. Secular slots didn't warn me about this.
It's quart 9. We gambled literally about
four or five hours ago. And I'm still
getting these mood
swings. I'm still getting these [ __ ] mood
swings. I'm still getting these mood
swings. And it was only it was only £100
as well. And it's literally impossible to calm
down. I'm about to go back with a
hammer, bro. I'm not even joking. I'm
literally about to go back with a hammer
and just do the whole place in. I'm not
even joking. It's [ __ ] winding me
up. It's winding me up, bro. Just
thinking about it. It's
annoying. Stop asking silly questions
about who would I bang, who would I not
bang. Talking about serious stuff here,
which is gambling. This is serious. This
is why people need to listen, you
know. I literally can't part I I
literally can't calm down, bro. It's
winding me the [ __ ] up
again, you know. And this was about
[ __ ] four or five hours ago. It's
annoying. It's annoying me. Literally,
it's annoying me. No one [ __ ] warn me about this [ __ ] you
know. Oh god. If I had USA Izzy in my
face right now, [ __ ] hell, mate. Give
me [ __ ] five minutes with that [ __ ]
Give me five minutes with that [ __ ] You
see what I mean? How gambling fuels
negativity. Yeah, you kind of get the
point. Give me five minutes with that
[ __ ] bro. I'll risk my freedom. I'm not even joking.
Yeah. Already fell out with
my So, yeah.
That's what it does. It changes people
as a person. This is what we're not
warned about with gambling. Even if it
is money you can afford to lose. This is
what I have to always mention as well.
It even if it is money you can afford to
lose. But you go out, you smash it, pay
get a new
machine, you have to pay a fine, you know.
You have to pay £1,000 fine. That's what
you're going to have to pay. I think the
fine is about £1,000 and then they get a new machine
anyways. That's what will
happen. That's what will
happen. That's literally what will happen,
mate. Know what I mean? They probably
put me in [ __ ] prison. Probably.
Yeah. Wish I did that last week. Wish I
didn't gamble today. Yeah. Even if it
was just £100, doesn't matter. Money's
irrelevant. Money's irrelevant. It's a
mood. It's a mood change. It changes
moods. It causes mood swings. Doesn't
matter about the
money. Doesn't matter about the
money, you know? I'm surprised that I
didn't end up hurting someone badly,
bro. I'm not even joking. And I was fine
before I gambled. Just like I was fine
before I went out last bank holiday
until I socialized with women again and
drunk. I was fine before all of that. I
was fine before all of this [ __ ] Fine
before all of this [ __ ] I swear to God
I was. This brings you down again.
Brings you down [Music]
again. You know what I'm saying? Bye-bye. But yeah,
so you got all the money in the
world. Doesn't matter. Losing is enough.
Do you know what I'm saying?
Yeah. So, I lost a mug, fell out with
someone again, and I wouldn't even say I
lost money because losing £100 is
nothing to me. See, that's the whole
point. It's nothing to lose. It's not
about the money. That's that's the whole
point of it is the whole point I'm trying to
make. It's literally nothing. It could
be 20 pound and I would still react at
the same. It's nothing. I just spent
£300 on the [ __ ] washing machine.
It's just the whole losing on
it. Nothing to me. I don't have a bed. I
got a bed. I got a £500 bed. Don't know
what you're talking about, mate. I've
got a £500 bed and I got a TV that needs
fixing and I can get a TV anytime I
want, mate. I've got a £500 bed. I was
at my friend's house. You've seen my
bed. You've seen my
bed. You know what I'm
saying? You've seen my
bed. What are you all about? You've
literally seen my bed.
So yeah, you've literally seen my bed.
What are you talking about? But anyways,
that's the thing with gambling.
Anyways, anyways, bye-bye now. You've
seen my bed.
Anyways, anyways, bye-bye
now. So, yeah, just wanted to give you
update about Gambling. is
yeah trying to make people understand
about this whole gambling thing but
doesn't seem like people really care. That's
where giving me these dirty mood swings,
bro. I'm not even joking. It's giving me
these dirty dirty dirty dirty dirty
moods. Even though I'm not I know I'm
not going to lose any more for the month, but still
madness giving me the dirty [ __ ] mood
swings, bro. I swear to God. [Music] Yeah. Yeah.
Anyways, police officer should be
getting in touch with me soon anyways
about you harassers. So, which is good.
I show them everything. So, that's a
positive. Positive to end on a
negative. So, yeah, mate. I'm up their
[ __ ] ass, mate, every couple of
days. So, it's all good in the hood,
man. It's all good in the hood.
M. But that's the point I'm trying to
make is like you get pissed off losing
like gambling and people, oh, how much
did you did you lose? How much did you
lose? And then you tell them and they,
oh, it's only£50. Oh, it's only £100.
So, is that okay then? Like, is that
literally okay then? So what? because
you don't lose a big amount of money.
That's okay. No, that's not how it
works. There's been times where I've
lost more money and it hasn't even
bothered me. Like 2,000. And I think I
lost 2,000 before and I've been more
pissed off losing 50 pound depending on on the the whole
um depending on the circumstances
of how it's not how much money you have
left because you can still have a lot of
money left and it would still piss you
off. So it doesn't matter about that.
Yeah, I should be on it
anyways. Yeah, I lost 100 pound
Grezy and I was getting these diabolical
mood swings, like super bad mood swings.
Yeah, I came home, smashed the mug,
smashed the only mug I had, fell out
with Laney again. Um, I had to pay 20
for another mug. Now I'm Now I'm getting these mood
swings. I'm really thinking to go back
to the bookies with a hammer. I'm not
even joking. I'm actually thinking of
going back with a hammer. It was only £100 as
well. Only £100. But it makes I feel
like literally going back with a hammer,
bro. I'm not even joking. And this was
about four or five hours ago. It's
giving me these nasty dirty mood swings
again when I'm in my own head. That's
what gambling does every single time.
Have you noticed it? Every single time it does
this these nasty, dirty [ __ ] mood
swings. I can't even explain them. I
don't know how people do it and don't
get it. I don't understand how people
lose and it don't bother
them. Like I can't believe how like it
don't seem to bother
people with me. I feel like I've got a
[ __ ] I've got a parasite growing in
my body, mate. Mocking me. That's what I
feel like, Grezy. Yeah. Every time you
lose, you've got a parasite. Yeah. In
your body mocking you. I can't explain
it. I can't explain it and it's
impossible to calm down. And it ain't
ADHD, bro. It's not ADHD. Like, my thing
with the women and the drinking was
valid. My thing with the women and the
drinking was very, very valid. The [ __ ]
wasting my time. How else do you want me
to act? I've had enough of it. Yeah. So,
I just said, "Fuck it. I wish I didn't go out.
Whatever." So, it's not ADHD, bro. What
the [ __ ] is this [ __ ] You know, it's boring, man.
It's more It ain't It's not ADHD. I had
a right to be pissed off last week when
this woman wasted my [ __ ] time again.
Yeah. Which is what they all seem to do.
I was fed up with
it. So, you can see how this uh this um
well, you can see what happened. I
smashed my mug up. I lost £100 and I'm
not talking to Laney again. All because
of gambling again. money that I can
afford to lose. There you go, secular
swaps. That I can afford to
lose. And rather than like like you're
seeing the real picture on this and then
you and you prefer to take the piss out
of it when I'm telling you this is what
gambling is. And yeah, it just one
negative thing after another time and
time again. Drinking, shitty women,
shitty gambling. Oh my god. You know, [ __ ]
me. Well, I told you what happened last
week, mate. Well, I told you what
happened last week, mate, when this
woman met me and wasted my time. She
doesn't want to commit. Women are scared
to commit. And I didn't even like her.
Like I've said about a million times.
Yeah. I didn't even like her. It's the
whole principle with what we're dealing
with in this country.
So, I'm probably going to be in a bad
mood until probably midday tomorrow. All
because of gambling. And that £100 is
nothing to me, mate. Nothing to me. I
spent £300. And how you know it ain't?
Because I spent £300 on a washing
machine didn't bother me. H it was a bit
[ __ ] I had to pay a little bit more,
but you lose £100 gambling. All of these
mood swings are coming back again. It's
gambling. It's gambling. And I don't
know why people seem to think you need
to lose loads of money or you need to
lose all your money for it to affect
you, but it
doesn't. It literally doesn't. It
doesn't need to be any of that stuff.
It's just losing on it is
annoying. You know, all these hundreds.
There's not all these hundreds, bro.
I've already booked
Thailand. It's not all these hundreds.
It's not all these hundreds. It was a
hundred. Not all these hundreds. And
that's me done for the month.
So yeah, that's me. That's me done
forever, but hopefully. But it's
definitely me done for the
month. It's not about the
money. Yeah, I booked a flight. I told
you that earlier. It's It's really not
about the money. It really really isn't
money. So yeah,
Greavvesy, this woman last week wasting
my time. What have you got to say about that?
H I can't even have a cup of tea now cuz
I smashed my mug up and I can't have a
cup of tea unless it's in a Spider-Man
mug. So there you go. I've got to wait
for it to
come. I don't know when I'll speak to
Laney again. All because of gambling
Again. Oh man, I need to get back to
normal. Back on the ebike. Giving up
with women. Giving up with alcohol.
giving up with gambling. I need to get
back to this life,
bro. I need to get back to this
life. Oh, she doesn't feel a vibe. There
was nothing wrong with a vibe. She
approached me. She traveled an hour to
meet me. What do you mean you don't feel
the vibe? Yeah. I'm literally
objectively above average looking. What
vibe are you looking for? Romeo and
Juliet. And mate, even if you didn't
feel the [ __ ] vibe, you [ __ ]
approached me. There's people that I've
been with that I I didn't feel the vibe.
But guess what? I [ __ ] stayed with
them. So don't give me that [ __ ]
lad. Don't give me that [ __ ] mate,
about, oh, you you don't feel the vibe.
Well, then you shouldn't be approaching
people and [ __ ] wasting people's time
then. Should you, [ __ ] whatever the
reason was. Oh, and another thing is Oh,
and another thing is, um, Ben, you want
me to pack in gambling and do more cold
approaches? Bro, cold approaches is one
of the reasons why I'm depressed. That
is literally one of the reasons that has
made me depressed. That's what actually
got me back into depression is the cold
approaches and the drinking, which is
why I stopped for for five, six
weeks. Which is why I stopped for five, six weeks.
You know, I stopped for five, six weeks
because of that reason. And I felt like
when I went out that bank holiday, it
all went downhill again from there. Bad
experiences with timewasting women,
alcohol. Mate, listen. Right. I don't
care. You went You approached me. You
traveled an hour to meet me. Yeah. And
she didn't even get to know my hobbies,
mate. The date was like an hour. Yeah.
So, I'm done anyways. I don't want to
talk about it anymore, bro. It's all
negative. I shouldn't have gambled today
anyways. You know, look what it's all
caused again. Look what it's all caused
again. It took 6 months to finally build
stuff up again. And now we're going down
again because of gambling. Gambling,
women, alcohol. Bad, bad, bad, bad,
bad, bad, bad, bad, bad, bad. It's bad
news, isn't it? It really is.
She didn't get to know any of my
hobbies. But my hobbies are good. Like
my hobbies are like most people's
hobbies, you know, like traveling, all
different kinds of food. Most people
would love me because I I've got
different kind of hobbies. I've got a
good personality. So, you can't even use
that. I'm very outgoing. You can't even
use that as an excuse. I don't care what
the reason is. I'm done trying to figure
it out. I told you I'm done in this
country, mate. I'm I'm I'm done trying
to figure this [ __ ] out. It's a waste of
time. Yeah. End
of. They want Romeo and Juliet, mate.
They want [ __ ] people that don't
exist. [ __ ] them, you know.
Yeah. I need to come off the internet, I
think, for like five weeks again. That's
what I need.
Yeah, mate. It doesn't matter, mate. I
know I'm confident. I know I'm outgoing.
I know what I'm saying on these dates.
Like, it doesn't matter what the reason
is. Clearly, you're not going to please
most people. So, why are you why are you
going to go out again and humiliate
yourself by doing these cold approaches?
So, what what do you expect me to do?
keep going out and humiliating myself
until I find someone. No, I don't want
to. I shouldn't have to. I'd rather leave the
country, you know? I'd rather leave the
country, bro. I'm not [ __ ] going to
sit there and humiliate myself just to
get a relationship or just to get a
shag. I'm not doing that. Simple. I'm
not doing that. I'm not dealing with
these timewasting flaky women. You know,
the amount of women that ghost as well,
that's another thing they like to do.
you know, they just I'm not doing it.
I'm You know, I don't want to and I
shouldn't have to. No one should have to. You
know, I've been to USA.
Yeah. Yeah. I got some really bad mood
swings today. Greasy. Really bad mood
swings. I lost 20 pound in a pub.
Yeah, you have to make effort. Effort
don't work. Unfortunately, when you
approach people, they pretend they got
boyfriends. I'd rather not put the
effort in and humiliate myself. I'd
rather give up and call it and save my
money and leave this
country. Yeah, I'm not having this
conversation with brain dead people.
Anyways, I lost 20 pound in the in the pub, bro.
um greasy last no I think it was last
week and I swear to God bro I'm not even
going to tell you the full in my head
like I started speaking to the security
guard and he seemed to calm me down you
shouldn't gamble people like me
shouldn't gamble bro we need to
literally think about this every time we
think about putting money in again we
can't gamble people like me can't gamble
especially now like you know you can't
even win nowadays. It's not like you can
win then you lose the next day cuz well
you you win some you lose some. It's
constantly losing now and I'm scared,
bro. One day I'll lose it and I won't be
able to control myself. And that's what
I'm saying, you know, like I'm not going
to tell you what I felt like doing,
bro. Like, it's not nice. So, that's why I, you know,
Yeah. But no, I'm done, bro. You need to
open your ears and use your [ __ ]
brain. I'm done, bro. I'm not I'm not
going on these dates, these time with
these time racers, Grezy, you know, and
it doesn't matter if she could feel the
vibe or not. Think about the Grecy.
She's 32 years of age. She's hit the
wall. She's five out of 10. Who are you
going to get better than me? Ain't no
one better than me is going to be
interested in you. And that's not even
me sounding horrible. That's me being
real. You know, I don't play Frankie
anymore. was a Horus. It wasn't even
Frankie. It was a Horus, you
know, and it was only £100. If you lose
£100 for the month, that's sweet. But I
tell you what's not sweet is the mood
swings. And that's one of the reasons
why you shouldn't do it again, you know. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, I've done it before messy. I went
back with a weight ball years ago. Done
the whole window
in and I think it was a summer's day as
well. I was hot, sweaty. Yeah. Back. I
had like a 50 lb note. I just went back
with a weight ball. Done the whole
windows in. I'm not even joking, bro. I
swear to God I did. I swear to God.
Like, you might think I'm lying, but I
did. I [ __ ] well did. [ __ ]
summer's day. It was as well. It was a hot summer's
day. No, it's not [ __ ] It's gambling.
It was a hot summer's day. And you know
when I used to do like weight
training like um you know the dumbbells,
they're actually stronger than a hammer.
I just put the whole window in,
mate. Imagine that. Like everyone's
doing like their little bets and that
and then all they hear is a bang. All
bang. Yeah, mate. All they hear is a
bang. They're all doing like the horse
weight races and that in it. It's why
people like me shouldn't gamble if you don't like
losing. Yeah. And now it's worse because
all you do is lose. If I won today, it
was 50 quid. If I won today then lost
tomorrow, I'd be like, "Okay, well, I won
before." If it's winning and losing,
it's not bad. But when you're
continuously losing and it's been for
about seven months, give it a break.
Like, give it a break, mate. You
know, I think it's the continuously
losing. That's what I think it is. But
it's definitely losing. It definitely is losing. It's
nothing. It definitely is losing. I
don't think it's ADHD. That woman last
week generally wasted my time. You know,
if I went out and people kept saying
they have a boyfriend, they have a
boyfriend, I wouldn't have really
cared. It's bad luck. What? Losing seven
months in a row. Guess what? Guess what
else is bad luck? My dick. Yeah, my dick
is bad luck. There's no way. No matter
what luck somebody has, they can keep
losing for seven months. There's no way.
There's no [ __ ] way. I can't remember
the last time I was up from any of these
slots, any of this roulette. Yeah. And
guess what? My my dick is a bad luck as
well. So yeah. Anyway, I don't care what
it is. I'm done with
it. See, this is what I was trying to
explain to you, Greasy. Yeah. When I
weren't going out, when I weren't
drinking, when I weren't gambling, when
I weren't approaching women, I was I was
fine. I was dandy,
bro. I was dandy, bro.
Dandy, dandy, mate. Sweetest person to
be around. Then I thought one day, oh,
let me go out bank holiday and have a
few jars and speak to some women. And
this is where all this stuff come about
again. I shouldn't have went out, bro. I
should have stayed in and stayed with a
routine. Yeah, I went a month without
gambling, but I I done it a lot a few months
ago around December. around
November. Yeah, but you could lose seven
box in a row. Yeah, that'd be bad luck.
Yeah. Yeah, of course it could
be. But yeah,
Grezy. Yeah, 100 pound's nothing to me,
bro.£100 is nothing to me. I got some
money on the side, actually. Yep.
Yeah. But yeah, that's not ADHD about
the date, Greavvesy. Like, anyone would
be frustrated if they've had their time wasted like
that. I don't know, bro. I wasn't going
to do it. I was just [ __ ] pissed off in
it. And I feel like if the if the wrong
guy looked at me, bro, they were going
to get done in. I'm not even joking. It
was pissing me off, bro. I don't [ __ ]
know. It was annoying
me. It was annoying me, bro. And I still
didn't calm down even when I went back
cuz I smashed my [ __ ] cup. I smashed
So no, it was I Horus.
I'm still not calmed down fully,
bro. No. Did Who said I was going to shank
someone? That never come out of my mouth. No, definitely
not. Oh, it was only
£100. Yeah, I did. And I recorded this
one as well. Oh, Greavves. I recorded
this one as well. No, last time. No, no,
no. I tell you what happened last time.
Yeah, I come back here. I was here and
I've got a boyfriend. All night. All
night. All night. I think I did lose
money. I come back here. I smashed the
mug. I pissed all over the floor.
Everything. Yeah. All over the kitchen
floor and everything. All of the
neighbors heard it and
that. And then I had to buy another
Spider-Man mug and I smashed that one
today. So, yeah.
Bro, you need to stop saying that £100
could have got you this. I've got money.
I don't know how many times I have to
say that. It's not this £100 could have
this. This£100 could have that. I have
money. It's not like I have £300 and
then lost £100. I've got money. Don't
worry about that. So, there's no point
using it as examples as this 100 pound
could have got. Oh, bro. No, I have money. Simple.
So that's not relevant to me, bro. It
doesn't matter if it could have, bro.
It's not You can't use that as a thing.
If it was like £1,000 or £,100, yeah,
but not 100 [ __ ] pound. And that's
the point. It's not about the
money. So yeah.
Yeah. So you can't say you can't use it
like that, bro. It's stupid.
You can only use that if it's like your last
£100. Oh, it could have bought you food.
But not £100. You can't use £100 as an
example, bro. Like when I've lost like £1,100
before. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. Here's what I'm trying to say. It's
not about the losing money. It's about
the actual losing. I lost £300 yesterday
buying a new washing machine. Oh well,
you know, happens. I lost 100 pounds
today. I felt like killing myself. So,
you know, it's not about the losing
money. It's literally about the losing.
That's that's literally what it is. It
has to be. I just lost £300 on a washing
machine. I had to buy a new washing machine. Oh,
well. So, you know, it's not about the
losing money. It's it's about losing. It
has to be about losing. Think about it,
bro. Say for example, someone's got two
and a half bags and then they lose £100.
They've still got 2.4K. No.
So, do you know what I'm trying to say?
Like, at the end of the day, it's not
about losing the money. It It's about
losing. It's about losing. It definitely
is. It's the same thing with a night
out. You can go out on a night out,
spend 200 pound. I don't think you'd
really care, would you? No. It's losing.
It's not about the money. It's losing.
cuz I've lost 20 pound and now I know
this because I've lost 20 pound in
weather spoons and I was getting some
mad thoughts mad thoughts. Well, I'm not
even going to share but I calm down in
the end and that was 20 quid. So, it is
it's it's about losing. It is about
losing. That's what it is. It's got to
be about the losing.
It's got to be. No, buying a washing
machine isn't the same thing. Well, it
is the same thing because I could have
done with not buying a new washing
machine. I could have done with saving
£300. So, it kind of is the same thing,
bro. Because I I didn't want to spend
£300. So, it kind of is the same thing.
Okay, let me give you an example, right?
Okay. Okay. Let's just say that's not
the same thing. I could go on the street
and give somebody £300 and I'd be like,
"Yeah, I done a good deed. I gave
someone£300." 650 notes. I would lose
£100 and I would want to smash the whole shop
up. So, okay. Is that a better example
for you? It is gambling. It is actually
gambling. That's what I'm trying to say.
Cuz I technically lost that money by
giving it to
someone. Well, yeah. Okay. Well, I just
gave you another example. Well, there
you go. Well, I just gave you another
example. I'd give £300 to a homeless
person and I would it wouldn't bother
me. If I gave £300 to a homeless person,
it wouldn't bother me. I lost that
£300. And then if I lose £100, it makes
me want to smash the whole shop up and
give me mood swings for two days. So, it
there you go. Is that a better example?
And how I know this is because I've
given people money
before. So, it's about the
losing. You You think it's about the
losing money, but it's actually about
the losing. It is about the losing. Of
course, it's about the
losing. Why didn't she turn up, bro? What's going
on? So, yeah, I went on a downward
spiral when I went out drinking and I
started dealing with women
again. Um, and then the gambling is just
a kick in the teeth.
So, no, it does affect you. No, no, no.
Street approaching does affect you.
Doing it sober does affect you. It does
affect you. The negative experiences,
the make believe boyfriends, the
attitude. No, it does affect you. It
does affect you. Especially when you're
sober. It does affect
you. It does affect you, mate. So, I'm
not doing no street approaches. [ __ ]
that. Uh something come up. What could
have uh possibly come up?
Eh. Yeah. What could have possibly come up?
Huh? What could have possibly come
up? Um do I start green? I start
ranting. I start ranting and going mad
and getting on the drink. So
yeah. No, bro. It does. I'm not doing
street approaches. I'm done with this
country. If I was going to meet
somebody, I would have met someone by now, you
know. Yeah. Sounds like she's ghosting
you, buddy. Welcome to dating in
England. That's why I'm [ __ ]
off. That's why I'm [ __ ] off.
That's why I'm [ __ ] out of here. I
can't be dealing with it anymore. I
don't even like talking about it to be honest. It's
depressing. I was living my best life
when I weren't drinking or talking to
women. I was living my best
life. My best life,
mate. Yeah. Do you like it? I got a few
of it, man. Yeah. I was an hour early
for the cinema, so I thought, "Fuck it.
Let me just go around the mall
approaching." And they're absolute
[ __ ] Yeah, that was that was like a month
ago. How did I get success?
Well, I don't know,
bro. I got like some women from America,
uh, Manchester, some nightclubs ones. I
did get some people. I got an Albanian,
but they were more like in central
London. They were more like central
London. I have had the success, but
the negatives outweigh the positives.
So, I don't really Yeah, I was I was like an
hour early to the cinema, so I thought,
[ __ ] it. Let me just send
it. It's not good. It still affects your
me your mental health.
Hope you like the approaches though.
Hey, do you like
that? Did you like
it? Yep. I'll probably be depressed in bed
tomorrow. More than likely. We're going
to make a burger soon.
Yep. 10 steps forward and 65 steps
back. Yeah. Sad, isn't it? Yeah.
Yeah, they're [ __ ] in this country, bro. They're
[ __ ] I mean, yeah, they don't give
you a chance to talk. That's the whole
point is that they don't go for
personality, which is what I've been saying for
years. They're just they're just
[ __ ] Like, I've been saying it for
years, have I not? That's one of the
reasons I gave up for six [ __ ] weeks,
because of [ __ ] like that. to get away
from it, you know, to get away from
them, to get away from the drink, to get
internet. Do you know what I mean, bro?
Like, but I had to make another channel
now. They haven't found me. I made
another channel. So, hopefully they
don't find that one. But if you ever
want to see more approaches, man, I've
got plenty, man. I've got plenty. So
yeah, I got plenty lads. [ __ ]
plenty. And then even when you go on HL with them,
Gareth. Yeah, they claim they don't feel
the vibe, which doesn't make any sense
when I've got a personality and I've got hobbies, but
anyways. Yeah. How do you think I
[ __ ] feel? If it feel if it feels
hopeless you watching them, how do you
think I feel me doing them? You know
what I'm saying? I approached one in
that mall the same day I went back
there. She gave me her number. We were
supposed to meet and then she just
eventually ghosted. And that's what it
is. It is hopeless. And anyone that
tells you different lad is is
is ting [ __ ] because obviously it's
hopeless, you know. But I just kind of
moved on with my life cuz I knew it was
going to be like this. But like I said,
I went out bank holiday cuz I thought
why not? And look, it caused nothing but
problems. Everything that took 5, 6
months to build back up again, I've lost it
all, you know, and I blame that. So there you
go. But yeah, it's bad, bro. It's bad.
They don't give you a chance to talk,
but yet they go for personality. That's
what I'm saying. The thing is, Gav,
yeah, you'll get people on the internet
that say, "Oh, women go for this, this,
they go for that." And you get all this
advice online like YouTube, Reddit,
whatever platform it is you go on. But
then when you actually go out in real
life, you see that it's nothing like
that. You'll see what you'll see in the
videos that they don't give you a chance
to talk. They've got attitude problems.
Like you that's the that's the real
life. That's real
life. You know, what you see is what you
get. What you hear on the internet is
not true. Oh, they go for confident.
Like you can see my videos, bro. Like,
you know, they they go for personality,
but that's not true because you've seen
videos of a normal approach and you see
how they act. So it doesn't matter what
other what what [ __ ] what other Tom
Dick and Harry has done. You get what I mean, bro? So
So yeah, man. I just thought I just
don't want to deal with it anymore.
So and the brasses in Thailand are
cheap. Yeah. Sorry. Sorry,
bro. Um I'm not having this conversation
again, bro. Um, no I don't think it's me
and that's why I gave up for 6
weeks. No, I don't think it's me. And
that's the whole point of watching the
approaches because it shows it's not me.
It literally is the women in this
country. And I know it's the women in
this country so much is why I gave
up. It's literally why I gave up. So if
I fought any different, I'd still be
doing it. No, think about it. Got the
money, got the time. If I genuinely
thought it wasn't them, I'd still be
trying. It is them. Of course, it's
them. They've got unrealistic
expectations. They want Mr. Perfect.
They don't exist. Obviously, it's them.
Of course, it's them. No, women won't
fix my mood swings. And that's why I
gave up with them because they're not
going to benefit my life. They just
cause nothing but trouble. I've had
enough bad experiences.
USA, Izzy, all of them other people like
it. Don't you think you've had enough
bad experiences to just give up and
they're not going to fix your mood
swings? You know, you've basically been
by yourself most of your life, 27 years.
You know, you can spend another 27 years by
yourself. Do you
know? Nope. Never said it's everyone
else's fault. I'm just saying that I
know it is women in this country.
I know. That's what's mad. Like, bro,
you know the thing is Gareth. Yeah. The thing is,
lad, the thing is, Gareth.
Yeah. It's that like when I approached
that USA Izzy and then she offered me
her number. I never had it again. Never
had it since and I never had it
after, you know? I never had it since
then and I never had it again. It's so rare, bro.
Like I don't know how I got success,
bro. There was a few different ways, but
it is impossible. It's gotten harder as
well. Even since like a couple of years
ago, I've noticed it's gotten
harder. It's gotten harder, bro.
Definitely gotten harder. Like them
dates I went on last week. Like them two
dates. That was the first dates I've
been on in a whole
year. And I went out a few times. I just
got people that said they were going to
meet and they never. But those were the first two
dates. But no, it is definitely women in
this country. It definitely definitely
is. Like my main my mind is made up.
Like I said to the guy in the like the
manager, the Weather Spoons manager.
Yeah. I said, I'm not going to sit here
and have an argument with you in a in a
pub. But I'm not going to sit here all
day and have an argument in the middle
of a pub about whether women are this,
whether women are that. Actions speak
louder than words. I'm done.
That's how confident I am with it. So,
it is them. Clearly, it's
them. It's like what I told you before.
We would go We would date a woman that's
a six, seven out of 10 that's got a
decent personality. A guy that's 6,
seven out of 10, they will
reject. So, who and that's what I'm
saying, bro. Like that date. Yeah. Last
week, they didn't like her that much.
Five out of 10. 32. There was nothing
wrong with the vibe. There was nothing
wrong with what I was saying. There was,
you know, I'm pretty much open to all
things, but she claimed she don't feel
the vibe. But the the point I'm trying
to make is that's the kind of [ __ ] that
you'll be dealing with in this
country. So, and then all the
narcissistic nasty things that they do
as well if it's not that. So, that's why
there's no point in pursuing it, you
know. That's why there's no point in it.
Um, and it's mad that they were 30. It's
32 and they were like average looking
and they still thought they were better
than me even though they've hit the
wall. But it is what it is, bro. That's
why I don't I don't bother with them
anymore. Really, bro. That's why I don't
bother. I don't even do street
approaches anymore. I just done it that
time in the mall cuz I was an hour
early, so I thought, "Fuck it. Send it.
Yeah. Yeah. It's not worth going through
them and and and nothing's good nothing
good has come out of it that like look
at that thing with that USA is he it
ended terribly, bro.
Terribly. It could have ended up with
somebody getting killed. Do you know
what I'm saying? And that was from a
cold approach. Nothing ever ended good.
Even if it went good, it never ever ended good.
I generally can't think of a woman I've
ever met in my life that weren't a
complete [ __ ] And I'm actually being
serious. Women, they meet guys all the
time that are not [ __ ] They're just
not interested in these kind of men.
That's the difference. I genuinely can't
think of any woman in my life that I
have not met that's a complete [ __ ]
weirdo. I I genuinely can't. I'm
thinking of all the women I've had a one
night stand with.
um and stuff, but I can't remember, bro.
I don't think so. But it's not it's not
worth going through all those brutal
rejections. And because I've already had
it, Gareth, like I've had the sex, I've
had the dates, I've had the women, I can
call it. Whereas, if people haven't had
any of that stuff, then they'd have no
choice but to go through all of
that, seeing what all they're missing.
Well, no, it's it's not easy. It's just
American. No, just just American. I had
a one night stand with she turned out to be a
[ __ ] Gave false hope then blocked
me everywhere when she went back to
America. Oh, it's a madness, isn't
it? I was actually telling this date
about that. This woman in Birmingham, it
come up in conversation cuz we were
talking about like dates and she said
that she had a bad date. I said, "Yeah,
I had one as well." I told her about the
date from last week as well. Funny
enough, the person wanted to waste my
time and claim they didn't feel the
vibe, which doesn't make any sense when
I'm like above average looking and dress
good. But yeah, anyways. So
yeah, cuz I'm pretty sure the only time
you would say you don't feel a vibe with
a woman is if and I've had different
kinds of women like fatter, skinnier,
not the best looking,
goodlook. And I would never ever say I
don't feel a vibe with someone. Not the
first time meeting them. So that's what
I mean, bro. So that's how you know
they're the ones that are picky. They're
shadow which is the point I'm trying to
[ __ ] make. You know what I mean? Like
so. But they are they are
evil. They are they are evil, bro. That's it.
But yeah, like I was saying, all you see
on the internet, all you hear on the
internet in real life, it's a lot
different. It's like Gary, if you hear
all the time, you go to bar, you go to
like a pub, you go and speak to women.
What's going to happen if you go and
speak to women in the pub, they're going
to say they got a boyfriend, no one
tells you this stuff until you actually
go and do it.
Uhhuh. That's an example. No one's going
to tell you that unless you actually go
out yourself and do it. And then they
all pretend they got a boyfriend. Not
all of them, but like they'll do
different things like give you attitude
or maybe give you their number and then
[ __ ] you around. So,
but you get what I mean.
Anyways, yeah, they were trying to get
my phone. Grezy old Bill was trying to
get my [ __ ] phone, mate. I was like,
"Mate, if you get my [ __ ] phone, how
am I going to show all this evidence in
court what these people have been doing
to me?" That's one of the reasons why
they wanted the phone. I
think you weren't getting that phone, matey.
Grezy, they weren't getting that phone.
Matey, matey, they weren't getting that phone.
Yeah, it was a good try though. It was a
try. It was a good try.
So, but yeah, that's the Anyways, back
at But yeah, it's not it's not it's not
worth going through them rejections.
No, anyone's worth more than that, bro.
Even if you don't think you are, you are, bro. So, yeah.
Yeah. It's just a saying they can't be
normal. women just can't be a normal
person, you know? It's sad, isn't it? It
is. It is sad cuz you think to yourself
sometimes like, "It's mad." Like, it's
all right. We can be by oursel forever.
It doesn't really matter. But it's crazy
how like finding someone would be
impossible unless you go to Thailand. It
does make you think it is a bit It is a bit [ __ ]
up. Obviously, it's [ __ ] up, isn't it? Like
It's bad, bro. It is bad. But I
basically just gave up on the idea anyways. Um, so
yeah. But yeah, is what it
is. Still there. Greasy. Going to make
myself a hamburger in a
minute. It isolates you as well.
Gambling. Don't know about you. I feel
like it isolates you. Does it isolate
you? Isolates me.
isolates me badly, bro. It feels like
you It isolates you as well from a
crowd. I don't I can't explain
it. And you, you fire acided
[ __ ] Getting arrested over YouTube is pathetic, isn't it?
Yeah. Mine's very different, though. I
can't gamble because how it makes me
feel, not because I lose all my money, you
know. Yeah. It's mad though, ain't it,
Grez? You can lose your
life on the same website you can watch
Kermit the Frog on, eh? Yeah. Madness,
eh? No, that's dodge,
man. Yeah. Let me see.
She applied for a job.
Grezy. Yeah, I've actually applied for a job.
Me your payment
order. Is that cute? Greavves. You have
applied for a job.
Yeah, I think it's quite cute. Do [Music] you
mate to Emma Grezy? Peter Belly's
mama. Do you remember Peter Belly's mama?
Yeah, Grezy, bro. I'm not going to give
you no lecture. Yeah, but obviously
you're the same age as me. And it got to
a point where I can't keep doing this
[ __ ] with this women with these women,
chasing these women, getting these bad
experiences. Like, I need to seriously
travel before I get
old. You know, go to a few places before
I get old, bro. You know, time goes fast
and [ __ ] these women, bro. They're not worth it.
So, this their loss at the end of the
day, bro. I need to start doing
stuff. Um, I just put a few different things
on. But yeah, like I told you, bro, I
applied for this job. I've got an
ebike that I just go to KFC
with. Just do normal things, bro. Giving
up with women was good, man. It felt
good. I didn't even miss
it. That's the only time I'm stable is
when I give up drinking and giving up with women.
Yeah, I think the woman is more is more depressing than
angry. Nope, I'm not a landlord and it's
not delivery either. I'm not saying what
it is, bro. You got too many glasses on
it. No, it's not either of them and I'm
not a landlord either. So
yeah, but yeah, you understand what I
mean though, Greasy? Like you don't get
pissed off. You It's more
depressing. The whole date thing last
week, it did depress me cuz it's like
we're back to this [ __ ] again. Women with unrealistic
standards, you know?
So, how you can approach somebody, come on to
someone, message someone back time
again, meet them, and then claim you
don't feel the vibe. It just
doesn't It just doesn't make
sense. Maybe I'm lost, Gareth, but to
me, it doesn't make sense. I It makes
sense on a dating app. It makes sense on
a dating app, definitely, because people look
different than their pictures. you don't
really know the person. But yeah, like I
said, when you meet somebody in person,
what you see is what you sort of get.
So, it just doesn't make sense to me. It
don't make sense to
me. The only thing that would put me off
somebody is if they were vegetarian. To
me, that's that's just a turnoff. Like
my friend, she doesn't eat red meat, but
obviously she she still eats chicken.
It's fine, you know. But it's sort of
like I don't know. It's like a turnoff, you
know. Yeah, I'm making a cheeseburger in
a minute. I've got cheese. I've got
cheese. I'm going to make some in a
minute. Jalapenos and
that. But you understand what I mean, bro. Like
It's [ __ ] in
it. Yeah, Gareth. So, yeah, we don't
live for women, Greavesy. It was just
the bad experiences that we had last
week. It put us on our ass again. had to
get used to cooking in
again and stuff. It was [ __ ] hard.
It's like the women just brought us back
again, back to our old
ways, you know,
you will never understand unless you've
been through it yourself. You'll never
understand. Even that USA is thing still
pisses me off now that sometimes
greasy. Even that still pisses me off,
bro. Cuz like if them people in America
really if they only knew what I was
about mate like that dam and all of them
bro trust me they wouldn't be running
their mouth they run their mouth cuz
they're across the sea and then when you
go there they don't do nothing but bro
trust me just because they're from
America doesn't mean
anything like it's mad bro it's mad they
really don't know what some people are
about bro they really don't trust
It's [ __ ] up, isn't it, bro? Like, you
see what how these things end
up? Do you remember though, Greasy?
Like, um the the the nons hunters, the
the the man and the black guy, they both got
nicked. That's mad, bro. They both got
nicked. Imagine that. Oh my
god. Creepy. Remember that? That was
funny. The first uh first time I watched
that I was
howling. I was
howling. Yeah, they both got nicked. Imagine
that. That is too funny,
bro. Oh, I found that funny, man. So,
yeah. Anyways, this washing machine's
coming tomorrow. I need to wash some
clothes. Uh, will I be out this week?
No, I'll be out next
week. Like I said, breaks are
imperative when it's to do with drinking
and stuff like that.
Yeah. So, I won't be out this week. Definitely not.
No, not this week. We will you'll be
out. Will you Will you be out, boss?
Yeah. You don't like the heat? No.
Yeah. One day you're going to I I wish
you deal with these women, mate. As much
as I do. I wish you will deal with these
women as much as I do, mate. Then you
can stop defending
them. Then you can stop defending them, eh?
Yeah, there's a [Music]
uh So, how's your narcissistic friend?
And that just goes to show with with
them new laws, bro. If that [ __ ]
actually called the police on me, I
would seriously get done.
I would seriously get done, mate. I'm not even
joking. USA has such a punchable face,
though. You have to admit that, Greasy.
She got such a punchable
face. I don't think she ever met anyone
as crazy as me,
bro. Yeah. No one could come on her
side, bro, cuz I'll just tell them about
themselves. See, the thing is,
bro, it's [ __ ]
up. Cuz the thing is, like, like I told
you with this, bro, these
narcissists, they ain't used to someone
telling them about
themselves. They're used to all these
little weak guys just allowing them to
do what they And then when someone like
finally stands up to them, like it it
throws them back. Do you know what I mean,
bro? Like don't don't get don't get it
twisted, bro. I've probably left the
mark on them. They're probably going to
think twice to be horrible to anyone in
the future, you
know? They see you in a suit, they see
you spend £100, they don't realize
you've got this side, too. You know what
I'm saying, bro? So that's why they take the piss.
You understand? That's why they take the piss.
But at least it's all over anyways.
Greasy, I tell you, just don't argue
with whoever it is, bro. I don't want
you ending up getting [ __ ] nicked. [ __ ] hell,
Grezy. I don't want you to end up getting [ __ ]
nicked. They would had a field day with
me, bro. If they actually come out, they
would have had a field day with me then,
please. I'm telling you, bro. But anyone
she knows would never step to me, bro.
Would never step to me. I don't care
what they have. It's like her dad. Yeah.
Oh, I would I would restrain you with
handcuffs, man. You literally wouldn't
even have the strength to even pull my
to pull my hands backwards. So, how is
that going to
happen? Know what I'm saying,
bro? Yeah. It's not mine anymore. It
weren't. But mine was mine took like two
years, bro. Mine took like two years.
It's not even on mine anymore. But you
still think about it now and then, is
it? Obviously, it's [ __ ] up. But not
24/7. It used to be bad, bro. Mine used
to be bad, bad, bad,
bad. Like [ __ ] 24/7, bro. I used to
[ __ ] up dates because of it and that,
but now I don't really care, bro. Cuz it's
like, yeah, you still figure sometimes,
but not like that. you
know, but yeah, they take advantage of
people they don't they think they can't
that that that won't stand up to
them. You know what I mean? And
yeah, but I still don't think time heals
stuff. See, like I went back to my mom's
um on Sunday to have some food. The
neighbor knew I was there and that, but
he didn't do anything. And I didn't do
anything. Like with certain things, time
hills. But even if I saw that [ __ ] in
London, bro, I'm not going to lie, it's
kicking off. Doesn't matter if it's 5
years, 10 years, it doesn't matter, bro.
I'm not just going to walk past someone
that's done all of that. So yeah, time
heals some things in some
circumstances, but like I wouldn't allow
it. Like just because it's been years, I
wouldn't allow it. I'd still I would
still kick off. I'd still say
something. You know what I'm saying? I
don't know about
you, but yeah. Like even when I go back
there, I'm not even going to stop
because I'm just going to get nicked.
That's what's going to happen. I'm just
going to get nicked,
bro. Then it's just going to be a waste
of time and a waste of money. It's
pointless, bro. You
know, but I just advise leave it, Grezy.
Like I said, I don't want you getting [ __ ]
nicked. You can get [ __ ] nicked for it, Grezy.
know, you're crazy though, Greavesy.
Like, you even said that. You even said
that you'd go to America, didn't you,
Greavvesy? You crazy
[ __ ] You crazy [ __ ] [ __ ] But the
thing is, Grezy, if you done that, they
would lie you. It's it's it's so
obvious, Grezy, that they would law
you. Do you know what I mean by that?
Yeah, they'd lure you, bro. Come on,
man. They would [ __ ] lawyer,
mate. There you go. Washing machine coming tomorrow.
Yeah. Just be careful, man. what you say
in it. With all the new laws coming out,
Grezy, you might find yourself in
court. Might find yourself in So,
yeah. Yeah, bro.
So, should be getting an email
soon from the old bill from the plot.
Uh yeah, it's not been a good week,
mate. I actually thought living in this
area was better for my mental health,
but yeah, I kind of don't want to be around
people. I'm going backwards.