What the [ __ ] was Timmy going on about
yesterday? What the [ __ ] was Timmy going
on about yesterday?
Eh, I should never know. Guyy's an
idiot. He should know more than most
people. He's been gambling for [ __ ]
years. I've still got the mood swings. I
knew I was going to wake up with mood swings again
today. I knew I was going to wake up I
was going to wake up with mood swings
again today because that's the effect it
has on you. It doesn't matter how much
money is. I don't know why people seem
to think that. Oh, it's it's about the
money. Timmy is just a little lamb with
a lot to learn. He's an absolute [ __ ]
idiot. I mean, he's an absolute [ __ ]
£100 can't buy you a food shop. What's
that even mean, bro? That doesn't mean
anything. Doesn't matter what it can or
what it can't buy you. It's enough to
lose. Simple. That's
it. Swear that I woke up. I've got a
good mind to go back there with a
hammer, bro. I'm not even joking. Just
to go back there and give it a good
whacking. Just give it a good whacking
with the back of the hammer, you know?
That's for the [ __ ] seven months of
[ __ ] mood swings that it keeps giving
you, you know, every [ __ ]
time. Then you get it. Then you get a
fine cuz that's what you get. You get a
fine cuz that's what they finded. They
always get a fine. You have to pay back
the machine. It's annoying,
bro. And he says £100 can't buy you a
food shop. Of course it can. You silly
sausage. Also£100 can buy you a [ __ ]
food shop. Not that it's that coin.
Whether it can or whether it can't, it's
just annoying losing on it. Doesn't
matter the amount. That's what makes me
think with these people on here. They
they No, they've got no life experience.
They literally they can't have any life
experience to not be able to figure this
stuff out. Well, well, you know, they
ain't got no life experience. The way
they talk about women, gambling, they
ain't got no life experience at
all. No life experience at all.
Obviously, they seem to think that
because an amount is little, right, that
it wouldn't affect anyone. It won't bother
someone. Just stay in bed depressed from
yesterday cuz the
gambling. Yeah, bro. Before I went to
sleep yesterday at like what 9:00, I was
like, I really want to go back with a
hammer. I was so close to going back to
that bench shop with a hammer. And I
don't care that it's just £100. I don't
care. It could literally be£50 and I
would still feel the same way. It's
irrelevant, mate. If I've lost £100 for
the month now, I'm not back on it full
time. Um, if you lose £100 every month,
I'd say you're [ __ ] winning to be
honest. It's not the point. So, I don't
know why Timmy is doing a video saying,
"Oh, £100 can't buy you a food shop.
That's ridiculous. Of course it can. And
even if it couldn't, and what do that even mean?" You
know, these people, they just talk like
they got no life experience. I know it's
I know it sounds like common that, but
they really really talk like they got no
life experience. They don't know
anything about women. They don't know
anything about gambling, obviously.
That's why they think it's the amount
you lose. But no, I'm not back on their
full time with these weirdos. Yeah. Yeah.
It's just annoying hearing it in it. Oh,
you know you can win. You got garbage.
I've been hearing that for about seven
months. Seven months I've been hearing
that. Oh, you can win. People win. And
you know when you hear it enough times
in your head, you go sick. You don't
understand. It makes you taps. I swear
to God. Oh, it is gambling. It is
gambling. That's what they say. But it's
not gambling because if it was gambling,
you would have won by now. I can't
remember winning in seven months. I
literally can't, you know, no matter how
much money I would gamble a month, £400,
£500 and can't even remember winning, you
know, but he doesn't understand that
like it's nothing to
me, you know, it's nothing to me, but
it's not the point. This is what people
understand. So just like okay let me
give you an example right I'll give an
example again yeah say you got £4,000
backdated money right and say for
argument sake you lose £150 and you're
on a night out it would literally ruin
my whole night out I would literally go
I I would literally get the train back
home I couldn't stay
out I literally couldn't stay out like
that's it doesn't matter about the money
I don't know why people seem to think
it's about the money you need to lose a
lot for it to affect you. I don't know
where that misconception come from, but
yeah, it's not that, mate. Trust me, it ain't
that. No, I don't care. I don't watch
him. I don't watch losers. I don't get involved with
drama. I don't get involved with these
weirdos, you know. I only reply to Timmy
because there I thought I'd make a video
to you, man. I don't get involved with that weird
[ __ ] weird weirdos channels.
That's why I made a new channel to get
away from these people. You
understand? I made a new channel to get
away from these people. And then they
found me and I made another one and they
haven't found me. And they definitely
found me through Instagram because they
found me through Instagram because when
I made another one and I didn't put on
my Instagram, they didn't find me
because I got a lot of stalkers. So
yeah, I made a new channel to get away
from these people.
like Mark Samson, L J. I don't want
nothing to do with these people, which
is why I made a new channel. And when I
do go live on this channel, I I don't
entertain any of them. Simple. That's
it. Cuz people in this community, they
like to act. They like to act. They like
to act the big [ __ ] They like to play
the big man, but then they like to run
to the police at the same time.
So, it's like, why would you even want
to get yourself involved with any drama
when it comes to this weirdo community?
The way I see it is if anyone on here
was really about anything, they would
have been on people's doors. They would
doors. And he approached him today. Um,
have you got brain damage? Did you not
listen to what I said yesterday? I I
literally just told you I'm done with
it. Have you got brain damage? I think
you got brain damage, bro. It's okay,
man. It's okay to have Al Alzheimer's
because that's what it it sounds like
that you've got. I've literally told you
I'm done with it because it's brought me
back again and you're asking me if I'm
doing it again. But you people got brain
damage. I swear now you people must have
brain damage. You got something wrong
with you. Your brain don't work
properly. I've literally said the past
two, three days when I shouldn't have
been on YouTube, I am literally done
with these women and done with this
[ __ ] This is part of the reason why why
I am where I am.
And you're asking me, am I approaching
today on a Tuesday? Bro, have a word
with yourself. Seriously, have a word
with yourself. I said I'm done before.
Yeah, I was done before. I was done for
five, six weeks and I went out because
it was bank holiday and I wish I never
did now. Yeah. And I wish I never did. I
don't care about them, bro. I'm 27. I'll
stay by myself. It's not a problem.
I went out. Yeah, cuz it was bank
holiday. So I went out drinking. I went
out approaching. What? After 6 weeks?
Oh, whoopy woo,
bro. That's annoying,
bro. No, I'm not taking on you. It's not
that I lost a couple of quid. It's just
it's everything. It's not even just
that. So now I need to come off social
media again, give up with women again to
become stable again, and then the cycle
continues. Well, I'm done with them. I
don't care about them, you
know. [ __ ] they're
idiots. Evil idiots. They're all the
same. And yes, I'm generalizing them.
I'm putting them all in one bracket. The
same bracket that you put on the TV. And
when I'm shown different, I'll say
different. That couple of quid could I
pay for a night out in Thailand, bro?
Mark, listen. I'm not Bonty Man. I'm not
Timmy. Please don't come on my channel
like I'm Bounty Man or Timmy. Please do
not try to undercoverly troll me because
I'm far more intelligent than you will
ever be. Please stop it. Like, if you're
blatantly trying to mock and you're
blatantly trying to take the piss, like,
do it, bro. It's funny. I I used to love
them people that blatantly are know
telling you what they're about. But
please stop trying to troll my channel,
bro. Because I'm far more intelligent
than you will ever be. And I can see
what you're doing a mile off. So please,
can you stop it? And if you're going to
do that kind of stuff, go on Body Man's
channel or go on Timmy's channel. Don't bring it here, you know?
So listen, bro. I'm not skint like
Timmy. Yeah. I'm not like these people,
a month. You can't You can't use that as
an example. I've still got money. I've
still got plenty of money with my bills
paid. It's not about that. Oh, £100
could have paid this. I don't care, bro.
I've got many, many more
£100. I've got many, many, many, many more £100, you
know, many, many, many
more£100. It's not the point. It's
annoying losing. But to answer your
question anyways, no, I won't be
approaching today. I had enough bad
experiences last week. Shocker. Shocker,
lad. I paid
everything. And this is what I'm trying
to say to you. I don't know how much
money you get if you're on benefits or I
don't know how much money you get. Trust
me, mate. I am not short a penny. And
I'm telling you how gambling makes me
feel. So all of these people like set,
oh, once you got your bills paid, no,
no, no. It's all fine. Gamble respond to
me. No, gambling's not an option for
people like me. End of story. Look, you
lost £100 yesterday and I was prepared
to go out and give myself 1,500 fine
because it's wiring me up that
much. It's winding me up that much. And
the way you should see it as people can
call you immature all they want. You
can't help it. You can't help it. It's
like having Tourette's. You can't help
it. You know, you literally can't help
it. It's like a parasite growing in your
body turning you into a demon because
it's that annoying. It's literally that annoying, you
know. Yeah. Sounds sounds like typical
English women. Sounds like the same old [ __ ] to
me. Yep. I met somebody from America. I
think it was 2 months ago. We were
supposed to meet on the Saturday on the
Thursday. literally was supposed to meet
and she said something come up. I said,
"Oh no, what has come up?" I'm gonna
give it I'm gonna give it um I'm gonna
um I'm going to give it
um I say I'm going to give it another
try with my
ex. They can do what they want, Mark.
I've got all the evidence. I went to the
police again um yesterday and the police
officer is going to be contacting me.
That's fine, mate. You give it the big
all they want. I've got all the evidence
I need, mate. I've got 100 pages. So,
and stop bringing stop bringing people
like that up on my channel cuz I'm going
to block you. Yeah, we're talking about
gambling. I don't want to hear about
these people like LJ Arsenal Mark. I
don't want to hear about none of them.
So, I made a new channel to get away
from them. Literally, I generally made a
new channel to get away from
them. These little weirdos. So,
yeah. That's why I say to Kevin Murphy,
like, I'm a [ __ ] I say to Kevin
Murphy, I'm the biggest [ __ ] when it
comes to you grasses on YouTube. I'm the
biggest one going, "Hey, at least I
admit I'm this, I'm that." Yep. Yep.
Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Because some when someone's been
arrested 10 times, 15 times from people
in this community. Yeah. I'm I'm
literally like I'm the biggest [ __ ]
going when it comes to you grasses. The
biggest one, you know, because I know
that if people was actually serious on
this website, they'd be going on
people's doors and they wouldn't be
making videos to each other. That's what
I'm saying. But that's why I'm not
getting involved with no drama.
You know, I made another channel to get
away from these people and then they
found me and then I made another channel
and then they didn't find that one. So,
they will never find that new one. I
just got like some videos on there. I I
come on here to talk about gambling. If
I ever do any more gambling videos, I'm
going to put it on this
channel. But that's the only thing you
will ever see on this channel ever
again. Yeah. She said she'll meet you
tomorrow. Well, this one said that she's
going to give it another try with her ex
even though she was in England for a
month. So, yeah. Tell me how that makes
sense. I'm not chasing my
losses. I lost 100 pound yesterday,
lad. No, I got I've got views, mate.
Listen, listen. Um, let me tell you
something. Yeah. Um, I've got views and
I would rather have zero views than have
these spastics watch me. I would wa I'd
rather be sat there talking to myself
with zero viewers than having these
spastics um watch me. And I have got and viewers. So
yeah. So that's it, right? So I'm just
going to go on a new channel now
anyways. I don't I don't want to be a
part of this weirdo community for
several different reasons, you
know. Don't you think if you
make No. No. cuz it's going to be genu.
No, cuz I've got videos to put up. I've
got all I've got videos to put
up. I've got videos to put up. I' I've
been putting up videos on my new channel. It's
fine, you know? I'd rather have [ __ ]
I'd rather have 20 decent people watch
me than 3,000 [ __ ] retards. Like,
that's that's the way I see it, you know?
So yeah, that's why you shouldn't gamble
anyways. You can win, but where did it
like I'm going to I'm I'm curious cuz a
lot of people in this community gamble.
Where did it come from that you think
you need to lose all your money for it
to affect you or you need to lose loads
of money? Says who? I'm living proof
that it doesn't need to be that
way because I don't want to get with
that. I don't I would never get with any
woman on this
community. I would never get with any
woman on this community
ever. You know, I had a comment saying,
"Oh, um uh Monty got with Natalie G, so
that means women aren't the problem and
you are." Yeah. Okay, bro. That that
proves women are the problem and I am
because Natalie G met um Monty man. Yeah. Okay.
Yeah. Yeah. That proves. Yeah. Yeah. [Laughter]
Okay. Yeah. Body could have her, bro.
I'd never get with anyone on YouTube. Never. Never. [ __ ]
that. That proves it, don't it? Yeah.
Yeah. But yeah, there's a lot of reason
I've I've I've quit this community. the police informants,
um the repeating, the self-p projecting.
That's why I wasn't on here for like 3
weeks. Like the grasses and
everything, like the
narcissists. Um and that's that's why I
just thought, [ __ ] it. Call it a day. I
think everyone gets to that point. Yeah.
Like 27, 28, they need to call it a
day. I just sat there thinking like, is
it worth it? Look at all the times these
people keep running to the police. Keep
running to the police. Keep repeating
themselves time and time again. If you
actually think about it, it's actually
bad. But it's almost impossible to win on gambling
now. But yeah, like I was so tempted to
go back with a hammer this morning, last
night. I'm not even joking. I was so
tempted, bro. And I'd get fined as well.
1,500. They will find you about I think
it's about 1,500. Even though they've
got insurance on the machines, I don't
care. Simple. It's annoying. And the
only worst is Yeah. when the booking
staff saying it's it's just gambling.
It's gambling. It's gambling. It's
rigged. It's rigged. You remember in
December? Yeah. The guy that was
painting these nails, right?
the guy that was painting these nails,
he was like, "It's gambling. It's not.
It's rigged." Like, that's what I was
saying, bro. And I had the same
conversation over and over and over
again about these
machines. Yeah, I did. So,
yeah. And then look, you fall out with
your mother again. I've had to buy a new
mug. Yay for
gambling. Big up secular slot.
Yay. Yay secular slots.
Yay. Yay. Secular slots. Big up secular. Yay. Entertainment.
Yay. I this I went I went on a downward
spiral when I went out that bank
holiday. When I went out that bank
holiday. I went on a [ __ ] I went on a
downward spiral. I swear to God, I went
on a downward spiral when I went out
again talking to women, which also goes
to show their problem. They're the
problem because I didn't have any
problems before that, you
know. Yeah, I got the same
one. I don't feel the vibe. Oh my god.
Jesus Christ. I don't feel the vibe. I
vibe. I don't feel the
These people are
crazy. Imagine having a 30 [ __ ]
2-year-old thinking that they're [ __ ]
better than you. E Jesus. What is life,
people? What is
life? Oh, it is funny. You got to laugh
at it, man. At the same time, you kind
of got to laugh at it. They're all the
same, mate. They're literally all the
[ __ ] same. Every single one of
them. Every single [ __ ] one of them.
I put them all in the same bracket.
But I won't be on here anymore anyways.
I just came on here to talk about gambling. So
yeah, and that is it. I'm done with
gambling. Done with women. I'd rather
stay in bed and be [ __ ] bored all my
[ __ ] life, you know? That's
it. So cuz you get to a point as well
where you realize it's never going to
change. this whole like dating scene in
this country is never going to change.
Never going to change because they've
got unrealistic expectations. You know,
I done a lot of research yesterday on
this, you know, Reddit, other places.
It's like they've got unrealistic
expectations. What's the point of even
putting yourself out there? They're
delusional, you know?
I can't leave. I [ __ ] can leave,
mate. [ __ ] watch
me. I can leave, mate. You
know, I can leave, mate. [ __ ] watch
me. I'm done with this [ __ ] place. It's a [ __ ]
community. It's a [ __ ] place full of low
lives. Low lives that ain't got a life.
Uh, no. I don't normally use it, but I
was on it yesterday. That's another
thing I stopped when I was when I gave
up for like five, six weeks. I stopped going on
Reddit. Um, I was just binge watching
stuff on YouTube on another on another
channel. Yeah, I stopped going on
Reddit. I stopped
um drinking. Stop the women [ __ ] Stop the gambling
[ __ ] I'll be lied later. Nah, mate. I
won't be. I'm going to delete this
channel. I think I think I'm going to
delete it. Yeah, that's what I'm I think
I'm going to delete my channel. This
channel. Yeah, I'm going to delete my
channel. I'm going to sub to all the
other things on my other channel and
then delete this channel, I reckon. Call
it a fresh
start. Surprised Timmy didn't reply to
me though, to be
honest. So, yeah.
So, got a new washing machine coming today as
well. Hopefully, it comes quite early. So,
yeah, I think I'm going to be leaving,
lad. If I What do I do with my time?
went on the electric bike, went for
walks, binge watched series. I binge watched the
series. Um, yeah, I was just watching
Inbetweeners. I'm not telling you where
I bought it from, but yeah, I
did. But yeah, I'm actually done, bro.
I'm actually done. I was off YouTube for
two, three weeks. Some of these people
could never do. I'm done. I'm literally
done. Done with YouTube. done with
gambling, done with
women, and I have to be done with social
media at the same time in a way where
like I can watch stuff on YouTube, but
not Reddit or anything like
that. This drugs you down, you know,
[ __ ] drags you
down. Women drag you down. Gambling drag
you down. Drinking drag you down.
They're all negatives. But people don't
want to admit that women are a negative.
They won't admit that. They'll admit
everything else is like gambling,
drinking, but women, nah.
Even though there the proof is [ __ ] out there, but yeah. Sorry,
man. I'm not going to be live later,
mate. So, you'll be waiting
forever. You'll be waiting forever,
buddy, cuz I won't be live later. So,
I'm done with this shitty community with
these shitty people on it. So, yeah.
I am [ __ ] done. Done.
Done. I will see you later. No, you [ __ ]
won't. Right. I need to put some more
stuff on my main channel as well.
Um, anyways, I'm gone. So, see you
never. See you never. See you never. See
you never. Right. I'm done with this
community. See you.