Three
months. Three months for two months. Oh,
too much. Too
much too much. Who wants [Applause] [Laughter]
How's the Wi-Fi good? Wi-Fi.
I was going to [ __ ] do, but I already
got one number I wanted to
get. So, there's no [ __ ] [Music]
point. Yeah, there's no [ __ ] point, was
there? We got it all night, won't we? 100%.
I only got
one. I four people get one number. [Music]
I'm not going to lie, but I want to go
on the table and start dancing about
10. I got one
number. I got one number. I like four so
far. I got one
number. Look at this bro. Got the gums on. 700 pound t-shirt all
night. It's not as easy to pull here,
guys, as it is
Liverpool. They're [ __ ] stuck up there.
London is for the stuck up. I
for I've already got one. I'm going to get
four. [ __ ] hell. All [ __ ]
[ __ ] They're all [ __ ] here.
But we're rolling with it.
It We're rolling with it. We're out
everybody. Looking at a [ __ ] right there. A big [Music]
test number one.
Daz, listen. I showed a bag earlier and
no one could show me nothing. No one
else could show me nothing. Bro, I I
literally showed a
bag. No one could show me nothing.
skin. They're all self reflectors.
They're self reflectors.
Never. That's a [ __ ] excuse to wear.
That's a [ __ ] excuse to the weather [Music]
please. I want to go to that guy.
get more than one. Trust
me with the old
[ __ ] of merch. I'm
saying need to get out of the area
though in this competition which is
going to be our biggest downfall.
Bro, I'm sending it, bro. I got one
number. I went to the Weather Spoons. I
don't know, no said to me, "I'm
married." I said, "You're married. How
old are you?" She says, "She's 16." I
was like, "A, you're not [ __ ] 16. And
B, you're not [ __ ] married." I don't like poor
protein. I got one number so far. It's
hard, bro. But I'm still going to send
it. I'm still on it all. I'm not going
to be out tonight.
[ __ ] I'm going to send them [Music]
all to see [Music]
me. Can I go double round? Yes, please.
Wait till she go.
I got two dates for this place. Very
place here. I've got two dates. How about
we're getting on it, mate. I was going
to go out tomorrow, but because the
weather was so good, I thought, "Fuck
it." Oh, bro, I'm on it. We got it all
night, won't we?
I got two days in this,
bro. There's too many stuck up people in
this country. This is why I booked
Thailand. I booked
Thailand. There's too many stuck up
people here in England. Too many stuck up people.
Bro, I'm going to sit on this table. I'm joking.
Oh, hello. I'm joking. So, [ __ ] four
four. Hey, it's long. We're in for a
long night, mate. Don't you worry about
that. For a long one.
Yeah, she's with these [ __ ]
going on about two showing a merch. You already know,
man. Yeah. Yeah. You keep telling
yourself, buddy. You don't scare me one
little bit. You little keyboard warrior.
Yeah. Yeah. I'll be waiting for you,
buddy. I'll be waiting for you,
bud. Come anytime you want.
Come anytime you want, buddy. You don't
know where I am, and you'll never know
where I am. You're a keyboard warrior.
Let me tell you this, bro.
Listen, let me tell you something, bro.
Yeah. LT, he emailed me earlier. He went
to Arsenal Mark's area. [ __ ] all that,
bro. If this guy was a bad man, he
wouldn't be on
YouTube. Bad men don't come on YouTube
and make videos. You understand, bro?
I'm here for entertainment. I'm here for
the banter. I'm here for the fs and all
the good stuff. Hey, people that are
about that life, listen. Let me tell you something,
bro. People that are about that life,
don't come on YouTube writing stuff.
Come on, bro. I'm here. You claim that
you know where I am. Come on
then. You understand, bro? Like, you're
on YouTube. People that are bad don't
come on YouTube. I'm both like, I'm here.
Yep. Chilling, bro. Come anytime, bro.
You get [ __ ] up anytime.
You understand what I'm saying, bro?
People that are about their life, they
don't come on
YouTube. They're not They don't come on
YouTube, brother. You understand,
brother? They don't come on YouTube. You understand? Yeah.
But Arsenal, he ain't about that life
cuz he's on YouTube. People that are
about that life are not on
YouTube. Like bro, like when I hear
about this Arsenal Mark Yeah. I laugh at
him. It's funny to me. I can't take it serious.
Like the guy is in his 50s. Yeah. And he
is on YouTube making videos. Bro, let me
keep it real you. Yeah, though. This guy
has [ __ ] three different addresses. This
guy has three different addresses and
he's on YouTube making videos, brother.
It don't make
sense. Like, we laugh at it. It's It's laughable,
bro. Like, if you know where I am, come,
bro. Anytime. You're welcome. You're
welcome. No one's scared of you. I'm not
scared of no
one. They don't come on YouTube. making
[ __ ] videos. Yeah, just like that
time I went to America. Yeah, I had it
in my head. It's me or them. Simple,
bro. Like, they come out, I'm going to
tell myself. They get me, I'm done.
Like, you understand what I'm saying,
bro? It's me or them, bro. Like, what I'm
saying? I'm going to keep sending it.
Trust me, I got two legs in the face. Do
you know where I am? Come on then, bro.
No one's moving. We're not scared of
you. You're a keyboard warrior. Allow
it. But please stop
it. I said I did go to America. I said
when I went to America, they didn't come
out. Yeah, that's what I said.
But I said when I went to America, she
didn't come out. Bro, allow it. Listen,
Arsenal Mark, listen,
bro. Stop your YouTube [ __ ] bro. Listen, Arsenal
Mark, stop your whole I'm coming to
here. I'm coming to there, bro. Please
allow it, bro. It's a new year. Yeah,
we're in the summer. Like, bro, you're
not about that life, bro. Like, I know
you're trying to get Listen, bro. I know
you're trying to get like you're trying
to show up for Jade and stuff. I get it,
bro. I get it, bro. Please stop this
whole YouTube [ __ ] You'll get [ __ ]
up, bro. Like, bro, for real. I'm
telling you, bro. Listen. Listen,
bro. You know what I'm
saying? Like, bro, listen. Stop this
whole YouTube [ __ ] please. You'll get
[ __ ] up real life, bro. Trust. When
people try and say, "Oh, Arsenal's
here." Bro, you're going to get the [ __ ]
up. This coming on YouTube. Allow, bro.
Like, please, bro. Like, you want to You
want to You want to mention other
people, bro? You show my people. Don't mention
me. Uh, yeah. It's a bit No, it's not
dead. It's going to pick up. It's
picking up. I want to do her, but she's
with some guy. I think it's her boyfriend. But
yeah, his boyfriend kissing, but bro.
Allow it, bro. You'll get yourself
[ __ ] up real life. Like, it's not a
joke. Trust me. Allow it. Please, bro.
Ask or not. You're not about this life.
Please stop it. You've been embarrassed multiple times.
Yeah. Please. Come on.
So, having a good time, Mark Samson,
this is what you need to be doing,
brother. Having a good time. Stop coming
on YouTube like you're bad,
bro. You got 40 two years ago when I
came to your area two times and you got
bodied. You didn't even count. Allow it,
bro. Please. You're silly now. Yeah.
So it's it's boring now. Come
on. Having a good time drinking. [Applause]
All right. See, I need to wait for these
[ __ ] to leave, bro. Yeah, I'm saying I
only got one number, bro. I don't I got
I done four coaches. I got one
numbers. Stop it. Don't know about that
life. Please stop
it. So many stuck up people in London,
but we're going to work with it. Open it up.
Yeah, bro. Look at this. That
is got one number so far, but I've been
I don't know about
four. Please stop it. [Music]
Yeah. Looking fresh is always worse. I
don't want approach in the weather
spoons. Yeah. She said she had a
boyfriend. No. No. She said she was
married. I said you're married. Yeah.
How old are
you? She said to me she's 16. Yeah. A
you're not 16 and B you're not [ __ ]
married. No [ __ ] way. How? Don't even make
sense. That don't make no sense. I don't
I don't approach
sober. I don't free approaches [ __ ]
sober. I got one number. So, we're
aiming for about three or four. I think
that's as good as it's going to [Music] get.
I'm know what that is, buddy. Don't know
what that is.
Well, I told man I'm going to go on the
table and stop
dancing. I'm going to jump on the table
and start dancing.
Like I told you I'm going to do it. I'm
going to jump on the table and stop [ __ ] dancing.
I'm going do it, bro. I
don't mind my boy, bro. Understand?
He's a He's my boy,
bro. No know where I am. And you'll
never know where I
am, mate. I'm out of London. You would never know
that going to a club with your
boyfriend. It's quite pointless, isn't
it? I'm a London buddy. You don't know
where I am, boy. London. That's where I
am. Bose, mate. Too
nosy. I need to [ __ ] piss. My phone's
on 60%. I'm [ __ ] out of here, son. I
need to get some more numbers. I'm on a
pool today. Yeah. I'm [ __ ] solo, man.
Yeah, I'm out of here. Listen that
terror. Come anytime you want. You claim
you know who I am, but yeah. Come
anytime, bro. You'll get [ __ ] up real
life. Like [ __ ] up real life. Come
anytime you want. I'm out of here. Yeah.
I'm going to get myself some more
bridge. I'm going to pull some more
place and I'm out of here. Catch you
tomorrow. I'm going to come back
tomorrow. Bye. Stop.