[ __ ] god. [ __ ] god. [ __ ] god,
bro. Funny, bro.
Oh my god, bro. I [ __ ] bro. people [ __ ] midnight. [Music]
This is serious, bro. Oh my
god. [ __ ] you. Oh my
Basically, this is between two minutes.
I'm sat here with a [ __ ] buff. Six
numbers. What do you got? Five numbers.
Six numbers. And then I need Oh my
god. The [ __ ] third already,
man. Or just some Mackie.
No. Yeah. Today was to basically prove a
point that these people on YouTube have
got no life. That was the whole point of
proving that they sit on YouTube all
day for what they are and
themselves. That was that was actually
the whole point of it
all of reflection like getting socially
awkward. They're all talking about
themselves. It's nice to see Notorious again. I
thought them [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] drunk. Self
perfection. Self affection of their own
lives on YouTube. Every day can't be no
fun, right? You
know my voice.
Flash. Flash again. Flash again. Flash again. Hold
on. Drinking is not forbidden for no
reason, bro. Drinking is forbidden for
that exact reason. We're not [ __ ] puking and
[ __ ] [ __ ] You know what I'm saying? Oh [ __ ]
Steam, bro. No, I got like five or six
numbers and I come back and I got an
escort and then I'm I just ordered some
McDonald's. Bro, I'm [ __ ] steaming,
bro. Ordered some
Mackis. Yeah. Nah, it was [ __ ]
But I think I only spent
about I didn't even spend that much to
be fair. About 80 quid, 70 quid.
So yeah, I [ __ ] hell. I'm steaming,
bro. Steaming. I'm
steaming. No, I'm not Muslim. How can I
be Muslim when I eat
pork? [ __ ] hell, guys. Bro, this
country is finished. Yeah, I got five
numbers. I think I got five numbers or six
numbers. So that's 60 quid. Bro, this
country is dead. I booked to go to
Thailand for like two month in two
months. I'm out of here, bro. Done. [ __ ]
this country. It's just Bro, listen.
Honestly, yeah. No word of a lie, bro.
I'm wearing about a 700 pound t-shirt,
200 pound trainers, 150 jeans, got money
in my pocket, and you still get [ __ ]
that think they're better than you, bro.
This country is legit finished. And and
and you know, yeah, even if it wasn't
finished, yeah, it takes so much effort
that it wouldn't even be worth it like
when you even got anywhere anyways.
That's the thing with this country. is [ __ ] up,
bro. I got like 40 pound on the side.
Yeah, bro. I withdrew like a one. Yeah,
I withdrew I drew a one. Yeah. Where is
it? I with you one. Yeah. For this
escort. It was like 60 pound. So, they
gave me like 40 quid. Yeah, it
is. It's [ __ ] mad. This is [ __ ]
McDonald's, bro. I'm [ __ ] starving,
Yeah, that's it's it's uh it's very hard
in London, bro. I was going actually I
was going out tomorrow, but I was like,
"Yeah, I'm fucked."
So, yeah, it died today in it. [ __ ] it.
Yeah, I got six numbers. Hopefully, one
of them replies, someone reply be nice,
eh? But yeah, it's uh it's very hard
these westernized countries does as you should know.
Bud. No, bro. I just got an escort.
You're sucking my dick. Cuz it's all
about them [ __ ] and that, is it?
[ __ ] It's all about [ __ ] It's all
[ __ ] So, don't you want to [ __ ] I
was like, nah, I just want a
[ __ ] Um, so I went to Macki. So, I
think I spent about I didn't spend too
much and that's what I want. So,
bro, I'm a steam, bro. I'm steaming.
It's not a joke, brother. I'm
stealing. Steaming, bro. 700 t-shirt on.
I had to get off the train. Yeah, I I
swear I'm going to be sick on that
train, bro. I had to get off the train
and be sick. Yeah, literally. I'm even
joking. I was like, I'm going to end up
being sick on this train, bro. A
joke. But 16 minutes all day, Mackey's. Come on,
Macky's childhood memories and that.
Yeah. You know, I was watching some
traveling videos about I shouldn't even
say this. Yeah, cuz I'm [ __ ] I'm
drunk. I was watching some traveling
videos about a week ago, dad. And it was
it was reminding me, bro. It was
reminding me of that Morgan, bro. I
swear. I don't know why, but man, this
clicked in my head,
bro. Yeah, she got there. [ __ ] her up in
it. I mean, Dad, you should go then [ __ ]
her up, bro. But I don't know why. Why?
Yeah, it's just like cuz it's so forward, you
know. But it's [ __ ] up, bro. This this
this life in the West is is is crazy,
bro. We need to leave, bro. We need to D
That's We need to go, bro. We need to
get out of it, bro. I booked to go to
Thailand in two months. I'm out of here,
bro. I'm done. I don't care. Listen,
nothing's stopping me, bro. This is
[ __ ] up, bro. This today. Yeah, you
should. It should tell you all you need
to know. Yeah, I went out with my hair
done, bro. You know how much my haircut
cost me a lot of money, bro? My clothes
cost me a lot of money. Yeah, and I
still got the same I got a boyfriend
[ __ ] Yeah, I got six numbers. What?
Five or six numbers. But, bro, listen.
This country is [ __ ]
is is actually finished, bro. It is
finished. Manto man telling you right
now it's done. It's over. It's
over, bro. It is
over. It's not even me saying this cuz
I'm tired of pizza drink. This is over,
bro. Yeah, I'm even joking.
I think I should have ate more before I
went out drinking to be
fair. It's serious, bro. Seriously.
Uh [ __ ] uh I sent this woman said to
me the worst pain she ever had was
[ __ ] uh food
poisoning. It says, "You ever had
paranoid tensitis, mate? That is the
worst thing when you got a [ __ ] pain
in your foot. And you're walking on a
limp like a [ __ ] [ __ ] and people
are asking you why the [ __ ] are you
walking like that? Cuz you got a
limp. Yeah. [ __ ] Yeah, mate. Then
then you'll know real pain. You'll know
then. You'll know [ __ ] real pain,
mate. Then you'll know real pain.
Finish this country, bro. This country is a
uh is a lost cause.
I can't believe I drunk that much, bro.
[ __ ] Oh, bro. I feel like I'm dying, bro. I'm
joking. No, it ain't funny, bro. It's
not even funny,
bro. My god. Bang bang
bang. Marching in your head,
bro. Shut up. Shut up. Shut up. Shut up.
up. Shut up, man.
I'll be sitting
here. What the [ __ ] was white? Oh my god. Okay,
[ __ ] This is [ __ ] So
don't for [ __ ]
This is [ __ ] [ __ ] show
you. This is what we show
you. There's a dark side in
here. But this is dark side. Yeah. This
is a dark side. Yeah. Stop. Yeah. [ __ ] No,
buddy. 10 minutes. 10 minutes. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Give me a
chance. [ __ ] it up.
me. Yeah, Monty man was trying to
[ __ ] message me earlier, was he?
[ __ ] real him as well.
Yeah. Yeah, it was a [ __ ] real him as
well. It was a [ __ ] real him,
too. But uh [ __ ] contact me or some
[ __ ] anytime, bro. Anytime.
when I was watching that stop that [ __ ]
the other day with Timmy. I would love
LJ to come for me, bro. I would bad him
up, bro. Like, you don't even
understand. I would I would kidnap the
[ __ ] bro. Like, it's not even a joke.
That's how bad it is. That's how about
it. Get kidnapped. But it's not even a
joke, bro. It's not even a joke yet. I I
swear the guy will get kidnapped. It's
not even a
joke. Well, it is. It is kind of a joke.
It's funny, but it's not funny for
them. That's why I can't take this. I
just come on here to laugh, bro.
Because people like people like Mock
Samson, bro, they're really not about
that life. Like, anyone that thinks,
yeah, like, bro, how many people did
I me, oh, I'm coming to where you are. I
told them, come, bro. Like, you don't
know where I am. Come. they would have
got [ __ ] up. Like they don't know
where I am. People don't know where I
am. What location I'm at. You know what
I'm saying, bro? Like, it's what it's
one of them, bro. Like, [ __ ]
hell. You know what I'm saying, bro? It
is what it is. It's YouTube. But I wish
that LJ would come for me, bro. Oh my
god. He would get kidnapped. Like, you
don't understand, bro. It's not. It's
like another level, bro. Like, you
really don't understand, bro.
Just all this [ __ ] for Timmy, bro. Like,
bro, you come about 3 years ago. I
shouldn't follow my mom. No one's scared
to open the door to you, bro. Come now
and I bet you you will never come back
on YouTube again. You're a
[ __ ] Absolute [ __ ] Just the same as
Mark Samson, bro. They're all [ __ ] idiots,
bro. Trust me. You don't know me or my
temper, bro. You understand? And that's a good thing. Yeah, you
[ __ ] It's like that Morgan. You
call me a [ __ ] but guess what?
You'll never say to my face. Know what
I'm saying? But but here's the actual
thing though, bro. You will never say it
to my face, bro. You know what I'm
saying? Like any anyone can go like
Listen, you don't understand yet.
Anybody can go to another country and
chat [ __ ] I'm [ __ ] lie. Anyone, bro,
listen. You got you don't understand
yet. Anybody can go to another country
and chat [ __ ] when they're back home. Am I
lying? Am I lying, bro? Am I lying?
Like, but bro, you s you you run up your
mouth and you was back in America. Am I
lying? Do you know what I'm saying? Bro,
it's like shifty, bro. I got like six
numbers today. It was hard, bro. I done
nothing. Bro, I told him to [ __ ] off.
It's annoying, bro. Listen, I done
nothing, bro. I told him to [ __ ] off. I
shouldn't follow my mom. Shut
up. You know what I'm saying? Stop
talking about yourself every day. Hey,
bro. Listen. Five minutes. Where are
you, food? I'm hungry.
Um, yeah, he is a he is a virgin. Of
course he's a
virgin. But yeah,
like I'm [ __ ] bro. I am actually
[ __ ] But listen, but the thing is
like, bro, you you don't understand with these people,
bro. It's like even when you got this
like [ __ ] diamond and that, bro, you
would get [ __ ] up. You will not know
what time it is, little bro. Listen, you
work in some little retail [ __ ]
place, bro. You would get [ __ ] up.
Like, you wouldn't defend no one, bro.
Like, because my whole thing is that,
bro, if I'm going to another country,
yeah, to fight someone, as [ __ ] up as
it sounds, it's me or them. You
understand? Like, bro, that's the way
life works. That's the way it is. Any
adult would tell you the same thing.
It's me or them. You know what I'm
saying, bro? LJ come in the door about
two, three years ago. Was it like three
years ago, but I stood in front of my
mom and I tried to meet him again. Yeah.
He is more than welcome to come anytime.
He would get kidnapped around the block.
You don't understand. The guy come at
8:00 in the morning a [ __ ] Sunday,
but the guy was shook. He was [ __ ] himself.
Like, bro, the guy was actually [ __ ]
his pants. this [ __ ] Lord Jay King
force. He is, bro. This guy's got the
most anxiety yet from anyone I've ever
met. Like, it's actually funny, bro.
Like, you got to laugh at him, bro. It
is funny cuz he thinks he's hard, but he
really is not about that life, bro. He
really is not about life. Cuz bro, the
thing is, yeah, I have met people from Ireland
today, and I was telling him about a
woman and that a woman. And he's like,
"It sounds a bit misch." I was like,
"It's not misogynistic. It's the truth,
mate. Yeah. It ain't Mr. Mistic. It's
the truth. It can't be Mr. Chism cuz I
don't care about it. And I told him
like, "Yeah, bro. The Irish are weak,
man. I don't know why they go on like
all this and all that, bro. They're
pussies." Just like Mark Dunson, he's a
[ __ ] Why he's on YouTube, bro? That's
why he's on YouTube. Listen, I guarantee
you, bro, my whole word, bro. Yeah. My
whole life. I promise you. And I'll
never delete this channel. Tell RJ to
come on my door. Yeah. Now I'm by
myself. Yeah. Tell him to start knocking
around my door, around my neighbors,
please, bro. Three years later and he
will get [ __ ] up. Like it's not even a
joke, bro. He would get destroyed. It's
a madness. Like, it's [ __ ] up, bro.
I'm not even joking. Hey, bro. One
sec. He's an idiot, man. He's a [ __ ]
He's a [ __ ] idiot, bro.
He's been to my door and he done
nothing. Yeah. He come on my door and I
told him to [ __ ] off and I stood in
front of my mother about three years ago
and I tried to meet him again by myself.
Yeah. And guess what? He also went to
Timmy's door. Me about three times. Lord
J also went on Timmy's door about three
times. Tell him to come on my door now
the second time and I'm by myself. Bro,
the guy would get leed. Like it's not
even a [ __ ] joke,
bro. [ __ ] my food's here like five
minutes. Be my charger. Bro, listen. How
many times has he gone for Timmy? About
100 times. You come here once, bro. And
I stood in front of the door in front of
my mom and I told you you [ __ ] off
before you down before she down inside
the house. Bro, listen. Come again. Come
on. Let's call it quits. Let's do it a
second time. You'll get [ __ ] up and
you will not come back on YouTube ever
again. Like, you literally would not,
bro. Why do you think you come at 8:00
in the morning, bro? Do you not think
that anybody could go to another
country? Even if it's classes that yet
8:00 in the morning and go home, bro, it's
embarrassing. Please stop it. You know,
it is embarrassing, bro. Even like that
dam. Yeah, that guy in America, he would
get [ __ ] up, bro. The guy works in
retail. Please stop it. You're not about
that life. You're not about shooting
people. You're not about No, you're not
about none of that [ __ ] man. Please,
just stop it. It's embarrassing. Yeah,
you wouldn't know about real life. Even
if it hit you in the [ __ ] face, bro.
Like, just stop this madness. It's It's
embarrassing, bro. Like, please stop it.
Stop it, D. Stop it. Please, bro. You
know about that lie. Same same as Logic.
Please, bro. You're not about that
lie. Because, bro, we all know that when
someone would go back to America,
they're going to call the police again.
Yeah. Like, just just stop it. Please.
I'm begging you, man. I get it. You got
this ego thing. Okay. Just allow it, bro. Yeah.
Please. I need to give you back anyways,
but I need to get my charger and I got
this McDonald's coming. Just please just
give me two seconds. I'm I'm Give me two seconds, bro.
Sorry about that, dude. I had to get my
charger. But yeah, listen. That's that's
the actual offer to Lord J. [ __ ] all
this Leco Garden [ __ ] [ __ ] all this
[ __ ] Oh, I'm going to Birmingham,
bro. Please, come on. This has been
going on for years now and it's really, really embarrassing.
Like please, bro. Stop
it. You're the lad. Yeah. Come on my
door now by myself. Please do it, bro.
Like you don't need to announce nothing
cuz we all know you're scared of London
Taylor. Bro, you're scared of London,
Jevil. You're scared of London as a whole.
That's why you came on Sunday at like
[ __ ] what? Like 7:00 in the morning,
8:00 in the morning. Cuz you're a [ __ ]
Straight ain't it? And it's okay, bro.
But don't come on this YouTube like
you're some kind of bad man. How you
ain't got anxiety, bro? You have got the
biggest anxiety than anyone I've ever
come across on this whole YouTube. Like, it's
[ __ ] Like, please stop
it. Never cop. [ __ ] gardens. What is
all that? Come on,
man. You're actually You're just a weak
[ __ ] That's all you are. You're just a
weak [ __ ] Like when I when I saw that
[ __ ] Yeah. The whole Timmy thing again.
You're weak. Cuz think about it, bro.
Yeah. Who goes from Ireland to
Birmingham? Who goes on holiday to Who
goes on holiday to Birmingham? No one
doesn't. It don't make sense.
you go from Ireland to
Birmingham. I told some [ __ ] um Irish
people about himself today, bro. I said,
they said, "Oh, it sounds misinistic." I
said, "It's not mistic. It's the truth." Simple.
But he seems to think weird, bro. Come
to London anytime he wants and come out.
He'll get [ __ ] up and I will call it
as well. [ __ ]
[ __ ] Right, bro. He's a [ __ ] idiot,
bro. Hey, my [ __ ] McDonald's is
coming as well. What's it
00? I've got the [ __ ] car Yeah.
Dude, you're also imagining like I
actually thought like everybody from
America was about that life. Yeah,
America. Not about who's the one that fall into
peace. What's that though?
Don't trouble with it.
That's why never comes to London cuz he
knows he'll get [ __ ] up. It's just
like Listen, bro. Yeah. It's like that
Mark Samson guy. Yeah. He's He's He's
He's funny, bro. To me, it's funny. Like
when I hear about him making videos, to
me it's a laugh because we all know that
the guy is not about nothing. Cuz if
anyone that's about something, don't
come on YouTube making videos. You
understand what I'm saying? But he's on
YouTube making videos. Bro, don't this
guy have about three different addresses
he can find people? Bro, you're on
YouTube. Stop it. You're embarrassing.
You know, like,
yeah, it's funny when like he comes on
YouTube. Do you know what this Mark
Samson? It's the same with him. Yeah.
He's an old age
pitcher. Ain't got no
life. [ __ ] D cheating on him and all
that all that [ __ ] So he comes on
YouTube trying to get a bit of attention.
the attention you got
right in attention.
You need a [ __ ] [ __ ]
over. Yeah, I'll see you tomorrow. Tomorrow, please.