Okay. Kind of tempted to go on it, but
I'm not going to play
it. [ __ ] question.
It's tempting. It's tempting. Yeah. I
sent one approach. She said she was
married to a woman. That's three approaches.
Yeah, I'll call you ladies, man. The
cash point is full, man. Yeah.
Yeah. So, I understand
that. Yeah. I'm not going to the cast
boy until we go 20 pound to play a
fucking£100 jackpot. I'm not [ __ ] doing
that. [ __ ] that. [ __ ]
that. I'm not doing that. Hell
no. These two people
attempting to get some [ __ ] today. Yep.
Yeah, man. I just don't approach. She
said she was married to a
woman, but it's only 5:00 p.m. on 5:42.
It'll get better as the night goes on. Trust
me. I'm just looking at this slot
machine and it's actually tempting me,
bro. But I I ain't going to the cash
machine to withdraw 20 pounds to play a [ __ ] 100
pound£ 100 pound jackpot. [ __ ] that,
bro. Look, I'm literally staring at it.
I'm not going to the cash point and then
coming back. That's
[ __ ] I was handsome. I said, "Oh, thank
you. That means a lot. I'm not going to
the cash point to put 20 pounds in. [ __ ]
this." But I'm not doing it. No way.
It's 100 pound jackpot, as well. I'm not
doing it, bro.
Yeah, I'm not doing it anyways. [ __ ]
with that. No worries. But anyways, um
yeah, it will get better as the night
goes on. I've already done three
approaches. Two of them are
sober. I was going to do her, but she's
with like six people and she's with like
some guys and stuff and I can't be
[ __ ] I'd rather just wait until the
nightclub. Now there's nowhere to sit
now. She [ __ ] my [ __ ] chair. [ __ ] up.
Yeah. Yeah. Someone took my chair. So, I
ain't got nowhere to sit
down. She's all right. But she's with a
guy. It'll get better as the night goes
on. Believe you me, it'll get better.
Trust me. It's [ __ ] We're in a shitty
weather. So, we're in a shitty
spoon. I'm a little watchdog. Remember
that, Stephen? I'm a little watchdog, mate. Get
more. I'm just going to keep drinking
Guinness. I'm not drinking spirits,
though. I'm not drinking spirits. [ __ ]
that. I'm not drinking spirits
again. I am not drinking spirits again. [ __ ] that
[ __ ] No more spirits from Edy,
lad. Just Guinness. That's
it. I can't deal with the
hangovers with the
spirit. [ __ ] that. Right. Time. Yeah.
How many numbers we predicting today? 2
3 4 5 6. We're definitely getting one.
100% we're getting one. We can't go out
and not get one number. It's
impossible. Whether the number goes
anywhere or not is neither here.
There. Seems like a very hard country to
date. Huh. But yeah.
Five numbers. I don't know about that. About five
numbers. Trying to pushing it. I got
five lost. Five. Maybe. Maybe four.
Three. Four. Maybe. Hopefully they all
reply. Not just one [ __ ] reply. Yeah.
Right. Just chilling here for a little
bit. See if I can see anyone.
Nah, you're not going to see anyone in
the [ __ ] pub. It's going to have to
be night, is it? Right.
I'm going to have one more here, I
think, and then keep it moving.
See what trouble I can get
into. See what trouble I can get into,
mate. Not literally, but you know. Bye-bye.
Now I want to see what trouble I can get
into. What's that?
Right. I'll be back later.