Yeah, man. Just wanted to check to see
if it's just still the same
people live. at your job. Just my little
weekly check in. Those that can't live without
it. Those that can't live without it. Oh god.
Yeah. Just just checking to see if it's
the same people. Hopefully I'll be
talking to myself and no one
joins. You know, talking to myself, no
one joins. That' be good.
That'll be good,
man. I don't know how people can come
with this [ __ ] every day. It's just the same
repeating. You know, you go on the Fruit Mad World's
channel. It's just the same repeating
things that I brought up from [ __ ] years ago.
It's It's just the same repeaters every day. grassing repeaters self-
projection I don't understand how people
can sit on here every day all day every
day must be must be very lonely
people very very lonely people cuz else
they wouldn't be on here every day if
weren't lonely people they got a [Music]
life watching this
Yes, I'm even joking, bro. Yeah. Yeah,
man. [ __ ] hell, bro. It's crazy.
My new channel's looking good though.
Getting some views, getting some likes. Yep.
Literally, I'll just come on like once a
week, once every two
weeks, just to see if it's the same
people, you know, and go
live. Look at me. I've already booked my
fights to [ __ ]
um I've been bullied off
YouTube. In your dreams, man. In your dreams. Yeah.
Really agree off YouTube. Here we go. You
later. See, all of this stuff, right? It
it it doesn't bother anyone. Like, it
doesn't even make people rage like you
saying you've bullied. No, no, no.
Because it's just the same repeating
over and over again that we've heard the same
um regurgitated [ __ ] over the years.
It's just boring now. You know, it's
clear people come on here every day
because they ain't got a life. It's
clear they self-reflect. It's clear they
try to ruin other people's lives because
they ain't got a life of their own.
They've made it crystal clear with their YouTube um YouTube
YouTube what's the word? With their
YouTube activity. There you go. That's
the word I'm looking for. They go live.
That's why they're on YouTube every day.
your job. I ain't got a
life. I ain't got a
Yeah. Ain't got a life, mate. And there
such grasses as well. Who wants to be in
a grassing self-p projecting
repeating weirdo community? Not me.
That's why I made a new channel. I come
on occasionally to see if it's the same people every
day. That's it. And it always is the
same people cuz they ain't got a
life. Ain't got a life. Yeah. So
yeah, anyways that's it.
I won't be live on here longer than 20
minutes cuz YouTube's not my
life. Life outside of
YouTube. These people need to get a life outside of
YouTube doing the world of good.
We've heard that before. That's
repeating. You remember what I told you
about the repeating and not getting a
reaction? We've heard all of this before. It's
repeating. We've heard all of this
before. It's repeating. Do you remember
what I said about how like you how to
get a reaction out of people? Very rare.
Like, bro, if that helps you sleep at
night, then that's good for you, man. Is
it? Yeah. You bully me. Yeah. Yeah. You
bully me. Yep. That's why all of you run
to the police and you can't ever go on
anyone's door. Okay. You bully me. You
want a [ __ ] gray medal or gold medal,
bro. It's boring. We've heard all of this before.
Like at the end of the day, bro, this is
just a back and forth with these people.
We know that these people live sad
lives. We know that these people don't
have anything. That's why they're on
here every day. Am I lying? Like, people
can't even tell me I'm lying because I'm
not lying. It's the [ __ ] truth. You
know, it's the [ __ ] truth, bro. And uh
yeah, you all run to the police and you
all do these this weird [ __ ] So there's
no point even being on here. Absolute.
If I was as much of a loser as these
people in this community, bro, I would
have [ __ ] ended my
life long time ago. I'm not even joking. Proper
losers on our proper losers on
air. Yep. Shifty. And don't you worry
about it, bro, cuz I'm going to win it.
So, you don't need to worry about that,
bro. I'm going to win. Trust
me, when it all comes out, bro, you'll
see. You will see. I'll even give you
the dates if you
want. All of this stuff here where these
people keep coming on. It's It's all
because these people are [ __ ] They're
nervous. They're very very nervous.
Trust me. These people don't know what I
have on them. You understand? And that's
all I'm saying, bro. Let them keep being
worried, you know? That's that's up to
them, bro. Because in the end, trust me,
I'm going to get a last laugh. Trust
me, you know, I wouldn't be saying it
confidently if I wasn't um sure about
it. And I've also reported these people
and they're getting nic.
Ah, so yeah, not a problem,
bro. Bro, they all do it on here.
Anyways, you don't need to worry about
that, bro. Chill. It's all good, man.
It'll all get sorted. Don't you worry
about it. You don't need to worry,
bro. Yeah. End of it will all get
sorted. Don't worry, bro. I'll even give
you the dates two years later if you want, bro.
Don't worry, bro. It's not a
problem. All these people done, all
these people have done is got themselves in
trouble. And even and even if it takes a
little time, bro, that's fine, bro.
We'll wait. It's not a problem. I'm not
worried. I'm not losing sleep. Trust
me. These people have just they've just
opened a can of worm. They've opened a
can of worms for themselves. Trust me,
bro. Trust me on that
one, you know. So, it's all good. I'm
not worried. So, these people shouldn't
be, you know. End
of. I'm just chilling.
Yeah. These people have got no shame on
here, Shifty. You don't understand, bro.
Like, these people, they don't have no
shame running. You know, these people
running to the police, crying to the
police. They've got no shame. It's
proper loser behavior. Like it's it's
it's proper proper loser behavior.
Anyways, but yeah, I'm chilling today,
bro. See, all of this stuff is anxiety
because I'm not
worried. I'm not worried. I've got all
the harassment these people have been
doing to me over the years. Shifty
Trust me, all of this, bro, is trying to
get you to incriminate yourself so they
can get you nicked again. That's what it
is. It's all grassing tactics and it's
I'm not going to fall for it,
bro. I just talking to man. Trust me,
I'm not worried. So why is anyone else
worried? You know, simple. I've got all
of them harassing me, bothering me. You
know, I'll take all of that. All of
that, bro. The breaking into the house,
the posters. I've got everything. [ __ ]
everything. Literally everything, bro.
Like, you don't understand. So, I'm not
worried one little bit.
Yeah. So, I don't know why these people are worried. Oh,
yeah. Ain't got a life.
Oh, shift. I was talking to somebody
today and they [ __ ] ghosted. Yeah, I
booked my flights anyways. So, I'm out
of here in a couple of months. I'm not
dealing with this [ __ ]
anymore. I'm not dealing with this [ __ ] So, yeah.
So I already booked my flights anyway.
So yeah, it's not a
problem. But I don't know
why these people have deleted stuff of
their channel. I've got everything.
Shifty. I've literally got absolutely
everything. Like absolutely everything.
Like I've got a whole album on my
[ __ ] um phone of what these people have
done. So what the [ __ ] Don't know why
these people delete things off their
channel. I've got everything. Literally
everything. Oh my
god. Doesn't matter if I've had any any
funny, mate. I'm not here to talk about
my [ __ ] personal life. me talk about
you silos and you ain't got a life
bro on YouTube every day ain't got a life. So
yeah, that's all I wanted to talk and
and you'll be watching Timmy's videos.
Yeah, and he's he done a 17minute video
this Timmy guy and all he does is all
absolute [ __ ] All repeating literally all repeating.
It's all repeating literally.
Yeah. So, trust me, these pe these
people don't know what I have on them,
bro. Trust me. And that's where all of
this anxiety is coming from. You
understand? That's where all of that
anxiety is coming from because they
don't these people don't know what I
have on them, you know?
Right. And that's what it is,
bro. It's so
good. Never you
mind. Never you
mind. I'll get the last laugh in the
end. Whether it takes a year, two years,
I'll get the last laugh, mate. Trust me.
I wouldn't say it.
So, because they don't understand these
people in this community. Yeah. They
don't understand the definition of a
trial. What happens in a trial, right?
When you go to trial and you show all of
the stuff that these people have been
doing, they're [ __ ] They are literally [ __ ]
Literally. So, I'm not bothered one
little bit. I'm not the one writing
things. Do you know what I'm saying,
bro? I'm not the one writing things. I
don't give a
[ __ ] So, that's what's going to
happen. All the harassing, the goating,
the calling me ugly, all that's going to
come out. I'm not bothered. I'm not
bothered. One little
bit. I can show I'll show everything.
Every little thing I have where these
people have not left me alone. I'm not
bothered. Literally, that's
it. That's it, bro. Not I am not
bothered one little bit. So,
yeah. The old 12 months. No, I don't
think so. That's not the way it
works. No, that's not the way that
works. Anyways, I'm not bothered. You're
not going to give me anxiety. So, I
don't know why you're trying to sit
there give me anxiety. You're not
bothering me one little bit. So, that's
it. So, yeah. You're not going to make
me worried. You're not going to make me
scared. just let them deal with it. Simple. So
anyways, so yeah, I've got literally everything. Literally
everything. So yeah.
Yep. Again, you're not making me scared.
You're not making me
anxious. So, um, stop
it. You're not bothering me one little
bit. So, stop trying to get me anxious
because it's not going to happen. It's work.
Yeah. Here we go. More evidence for
me. More evidence for me. Thank you.
That's add in the harassment f folder.
And another thing, I don't have a
criminal record. I actually got my
criminal record check actually a few
days ago and I have literally no criminal record.
So, yep. Here we go. More evidence for
me. These people don't help themselves. So,
yeah. So, yeah.
There we go. More evidence for me. Yes.
There we go. Yes. And just because
somebody goes to crown court, it doesn't
mean they're going to go to jail. Yeah.
Yes, they can. But that doesn't mean
you're going to go to jail about at
least 12 months. Yeah. It doesn't mean
everyone that goes to compound court
goes to jail. So anyways, what are you
worrying over? I'm not worried. Mate,
why what are you worrying about? You
don't need to worry, man. Chill. I'm not worried. So
yeah, I'm not worried one little bit.
You shouldn't be
worried. And I got my I actually got my
criminal record check the other day. I
don't have a criminal record. Try
again. Try again. Okay, I'll go to jail
if I get found guilty. Okay, you keep
telling yourself that, buddy. Okay, you
keep telling yourself
that. Yeah, you keep telling yourself
You keep telling yourself that. Anyways, you're boring.
Bye-bye. You are boring. Bye-bye
now. So, yeah,
man. So, yeah, I got a criminal record check on um thingy
And I don't have a criminal
record. Not going to tell you how I got
it, but yeah, I needed it anyways. So,
don't have a criminal record.
Nah, don't gamble, mate. Don't gamble,
lad. Don't gamble anymore. I'm not
telling you about my history. I'm I'm
off soon anyways, bro. Just wanted to
check if it's the same people.
And is the same
people. So yeah, same people every day
ain't got a life. So
yeah, people no life, eh?
anyways. I'm going anyways,
man. I'll be off to jail in You Wish
I'll be off to jail, mate. In your
dreams, buddy. In your [ __ ] dreams.
Yeah, in your dreams I'll be going to jail. You
wish. Oh [ __ ] One sec.
Anyway, I'm about see