Oh. Yeah, man. It's my last live stream.
Said I was going to go live a bit later
and that's me done, bro. with this
[ __ ] weird projecting place full of
[ __ ] old age
pensioners. I ain't got a life but
YouTube got a life. So yeah, bro. Oh, what's [Music] [ __ ]
I blame Timmy for getting me on here for these sad
losers. Sad, obsessed, jealous losers. I actually blame
him. He gets the full [ __ ] blame.
Yeah, you're talking about yourself.
I've got way more money than you. I've
had more women than you, bro. I showed
money like the other week, did I not?
You're literally talking about yourself.
You're just talking about your own life.
Self projector got way more money than
you will ever have. You're talking about
your own life.
skin. Not skin like you people, mate.
I've got more money than you'll ever
have. You're talking about your own lives
again. You You've got yourselves confused with
me. You're literally talking about your
own lives. Like, Lee, who's the one
that's been on YouTube every day for
years? Yourself. You're talking about
yourself. You people in here, you talk
about your own skin lives. That's why
you're on every day cuz you ain't got no
money. You ain't got no life. You ain't
got no friends. You ain't got no
future. You are literally talking about your own
lives. You're talking negatively about
yourselves. Literally like what person
Yeah. who's got this good life, all this
money, all this would come on YouTube
all day, every day. Doesn't add up. Zero
and zero doesn't add up. So, like you
prove what you are with your YouTube
activity. Way more. I've had way more
women than you would ever have. I've got
way more money than you would ever have.
I even showed money [ __ ] last week.
So, yeah, you must be talking about
yourself. Definitely definitely
definitely talking about yourself.
Oh, you're definitely definitely talking
about your own
lives, you know, because you only know
your own lives, you
know. You're saying that I got no car,
[ __ ] I've got a provisional coming.
What the [ __ ] you on about? Let's see
your money. Let's see your car. See what
I was saying, is like what I was saying
earlier. This community is full of a
bunch of old age pensioners that has
their lives are ruined. loners, old age
pensioners like Lee, like these other
people. They've got nothing in their
life. So, they come on here to feel
wanted. They got no money, no misses, no
friends. So, without YouTube, they have
nothing. And that's why they come on
here every day because they have nothing
else in their life. Literally
nothing. Like, if YouTube, well, not
even just YouTube, if this community,
cuz no other community would have them.
If it got shut down, these people would probably commit
suicide. That's literally all they have.
YouTube and projecting is literally all
they have. Like, it's it's
sad. It's sad to read these people. You
know, got more money than you.
I've got I get over [ __ ] three grand
a month, but you still call me skin.
Yeah, you're just talking about
yourselves again. And the fact that you
do this every single day, it just goes
to show what you people are just lowife
old age pensioners that's got nothing in
your life. For you people to sit on
YouTube every day doing what you do, it
says a lot about your
life. It says a lot about your life.
lonely. The fact that you even come on
here every day just goes to show you're
all lonely. And when I say this, you
laugh because you know it's the truth.
It doesn't matter what I've been doing.
None of your business what I've been
doing. We're talking about you little
self-reflecting little low lives that
can't get off of YouTube. Not even for
one day. Literally, if you go on L J's,
you will see the same spastics leave for
free. The same skint spastics with no
money, no misses coming on here
projecting their life. You see the same
spackers every day. You see the same
spackers. Like even before this whole
court thing, I left because it's the
same spastics. What's the point of being on
somewhere about themselves? It's
pointless. It's [ __ ] pointless, son. It really
is. Yeah, it's [ __ ] weird. But no, it
is weird though.
skin. Everything these people call you,
they are themselves. Literally, they
they talk about their own
lives. They have
nothing but doing this every day on
YouTube. Same with that red. Same same
with that red star. You know, they ain't got a
life. How did I get on in court? Well, I
basically got basically got away with it.
Yeah. Well, I've got to go to trial in
three and a half years, Grezy. Yeah. I
went to court
yesterday and they said, "Oh, do you
plead guilty or do you plead not
guilty?" And I said, "There's no way I'm
[ __ ] pleading guilty with the amount
of evidence I've got on these people."
And they said, "Okay, you have to come
back to court on the 30th of December,
2028." I said, "That's fine. Not a
problem. I'm not [ __ ] pleading
guilty. [ __ ] that." you know, after all
the [ __ ] these and and like I said,
Grezy, that's one of the reasons you
don't see me on here anymore. Sorry to
repeat, but it's the self projecting.
Uh, it's repeating, the jealousy, the
grassing. That ain't a bit of me, bro.
That ain't a bit of me. I don't [ __ ]
with grasses, so why would I be on a
grassing community? Doesn't make sense.
Like, bro, I'm going to Birmingham next
week to meet this person.
Like I I'm going to in the next week to
meet this person, bro. And trust me,
there's a lot of people on YouTube that
I would love to call out. Prime, Timmy,
all of them, but there's no point
because they're all grasses. So, there's
no point of doing anything on a grassing
community. There's there's literally no
point. They're all grasses. So, makes me
laugh when people still come on here and
argue and talk about fighting even
though they're all grasses on here. But anyways, yeah.
So yeah, three and a half years.
Grieved. Three and a half years. That's
funny. That's crazy, bro.
Yeah. So many grasses. Jealousy not
nice, is it? Gregy. Jealousy is not a
thing. It's like this le no woman, no
cost skin. Keep repeating. Even though
I've proved numerous times I've got more
money than anybody on this everyone on
this community and I've shown more women
than everybody on this community, they
still self-reflect because that's all
they do is self-reflect. That's the main
point. They're a bunch of 40year-old
losers that that their lives are ruined.
That's why they do this every day. Most
of them, we're like the [ __ ] youngest
on here. We're like the youngest on
here. This place is full of losers. Old
age pensioners, losers, nothing in their
life. Literally nothing in their life. Literally, [ __ ]
all. No, no, no, no. It is jealousy. It
is jealousy, Greasy. Because for these
people to stalk a certain person every
day and try to uh ruin people's life
with the police. No, it's definitely
jealousy. It's definitely definitely
jealousy because you need to think the
way they think. No, it definitely
definitely is jealousy. Think about it.
You're younger than these people. You're
better looking than these people. You
got more money than these people. They
hate it. That's why they come in here
and self-reflect every day. It is
definitely jealous. No, it definitely
definitely is jealousy. 100% it is.
Because cuz if it wasn't jealousy, these
people wouldn't be coming on here hating every
day. They wouldn't come on YouTube
hating every day if they weren't jealous
and doing all the extra things that they
do. It is. No, it is jealousy. It
definitely definitely is jealousy. It
has to be. There's there's literally
nothing else it can
be. It's a [ __ ] weirdo [ __ ]
community and just
self-reflectors that that get themselves
um confused with
you. Think about it, Grezy. Is my life
perfect? Oh, bro, my life's not perfect, but guess
what? I have money, you
know? Don't have to work. Get money
coming in. I can do what I want when I
want. These people would love your life.
They would love your life, man. And
you're better looking than them and
young as well. And you got better
clothes than them. Think about it, bro.
Think about my life. I just told you.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm not a millionaire. My
life's not perfect. And then look at these people's
lives. And then look at these people's
lives. There you go, man.
So, just put two and two together, bro. [ __ ] hell.
Two and two together,
eh? But yeah, I was going to go
Birmingham when I was going to go
Birmingham. I was going to call out that prime.
But there's no point. It's a grassing
community. It's not the point that you
went to court and you got away with it.
It's not the point, mate. It's literally
not the point. They're all glasses on
here. And I've proven it time and time
and time again. Not even. It's not the
[ __ ] point, mate. whether it got
dropped, whether it didn't get
dropped. And Terry's the same as well.
They're all the same on
here. I think that Terry is that red
star, you know? Yeah. I was going to go
to Birmingham and call out that Prime
cuz I was going there anyways and say,
"Listen, I'm actually in your city now,
you little [ __ ] Why don't you try and
move me out your city?" But I would
headbutt him in his chin like it ain't
even a joke. And this time I won't have
my dancing [ __ ] um shoes on so I get
[ __ ] up. There's no point. There's
literally no point in talking all of
that stuff cuz it's just extra stuff.
You show £20. Yeah, why don't you show
us £20? I'll put the link
up. So yeah, bro, I'm leaving anyways.
Why don't you show us 20
pound? Yeah. See, it's the same
repeated. This is exactly what I'm
talking about. It's just the same
idiots, the same repeaters. You see what I mean,
Grezy? It's just the same
repeaters, same atmosphere, same
repeaters, same people, same argument.
You know what I'm
saying? Yeah. Oh [ __ ] Why is I doing
that? Yeah. They're just low lives.
That's what they are. They're just low
lives. Just like this Lee. Just a low life.
Red Star, low life. They're all low
lives. No life but YouTube. Sometimes I
come on occasionally, Grezy, to see if
these people are still on YouTube. And
I'll be like, Timmy, you're still on
YouTube. You ain't got no life. You
know, I do do that occasionally. I like
these people are still on [ __ ]
YouTube. No life. And um obviously they
can't say anything about me because I'm
not the one commenting every day. I'm
not the one who's on here every day. I
would literally take two day. Do you
know what I'll
do? So, Merc say these people call me
skin. They say I'm this, I'm that, I'm
this, I'm that. Yeah. Um, and then I'll
be, okay, well, I come off YouTube for
two weeks, right? Um, I come off YouTube
for two weeks, then I come back and I
was like, these people are still on
YouTube. They've got to be talking about
themselves. They're still on [ __ ]
YouTube with no money. You know what I'm
saying? because they literally just talk
about themselves. They're literally all low
lives. They're so jealous of me as well.
It's crazy how jealous these people are
of me. The jealousy. That's the thing I
can't get. And if you're not jealous,
well, [ __ ] off and stop stalking me
then. If you're really not jealous, you
would [ __ ] off and get on with your own
life and stop [ __ ] stalking me. It's
like what somebody said before, you're
better looking than them. You got more
money than them and it kills them. It's
the truth. And he said, just get off of
YouTube and live your life. It's
jealousy. It's so true. Like I actually
thought before Yeah. the guy's just
chatting [ __ ] It It is the truth.
Better looking, more money. And that's
why they go for you. It's the truth.
It's It is the truth. And I'm I'm like I
And I hate using the word jealousy. I
hate it because I just don't like saying
that people are jealous unless they
really are jealous.
But they sit on here every day doing
what they do because they're jealous of
something. Or it must be something that
you have. Maybe if they're not jealous
of you, they're definitely jealous of
something that you have. More money,
better looks, better clothes, more
women, better life. I can name you of so
many different things. Rey, it's not even a
joke. But it is jealousy. It definitely
cuz why would they waste their life
coming on here hating every day if their
lives are so
good? It's because their lives are
ruined and they want to bring other
people down with
them. You understand?
Deleted. They should I think this
person's sleeping now. But yeah, I'm I'm
done with this uh weird
place. But yeah, Grezy, if their life
was better than yours and you're this
and you're that, they wouldn't come on
YouTube hating every day. You
understand? You know, they wouldn't be
doing this every single day. Cuz think about it,
bro. It is jealousy. It is jealousy
because would you waste your life
stalking someone every day on YouTube
that you that you're better than? No,
you wouldn't. So there you go. You got
your answer. Definitely jealousy.
Definitely. Definitely is jealousy. Of
course it is. And they do it all day
every day. And then you got some people
that want to come on here every day like
they're some big [ __ ] hard man and go
running and crying to the police and
then they think that they've
won. You see what I'm saying? It's pathetic.
But then but again they're shorts side
because then people will just stop coming on
YouTube. These people greavves are are
actually really really
thick. Like they're actually really
really really thick these people you
know very shortsighted very shortsighted man.
uh in two
months in July. Very
shortsighted cuz they want to bully
people. They want to torment people and
they want like entertainment but they
don't realize that if somebody ends up
in prison that what what what
entertainment are they going to have?
And also in my case when I find out
someone's a grass I stop [ __ ] with
them and I just don't come on YouTube.
Simple. So they've just basically
defeated the whole purpose really. But again, short-sighted
fickos, low IQ. Well, I don't know about
you people. Would you still do
it? No, that's that's that's that that
just tells me that like I don't I don't
care. And you know, it's like you know
um you know Red Star um you know Red
Star, right? Listen, you've been being
controlled for two years. You can't even
tell me where you [ __ ] live.
You can't even tell me where you are.
You're the one who's being controlled by
me, you little [ __ ] About how you
control what I say. [ __ ] I've asked
you to show me where you are about 100
times, and you can't even do that. Do
you think a man could ever make me
scared to say where I am? Sort it out,
mate. You've been controlled for the
past three um three years, and it's the
grassing. I can't deal with the
grassing. The grassing, the the
repeating, the stalking. It's It's just
weird. It gives me the ick like every
time I'm on here, it's it's such a
creepy weird place full of losers. Like
I wouldn't I wouldn't even call it a
community. It's just [ __ ] [ __ ]
man. And I got a new channel as well. So
yeah, it's [ __ ] It's so
weird, you know? Proper
weirdos. I ain't got a
life. I ain't got to lie.
So few people will be getting arrested soon
anyways. Have to follow up on that. So
yeah, as soon as that mark still come on YouTube.
Um, I can't believe he's still on this.
He should have just made a new channel,
lad. Yeah, your friend. I'm going to
Thailand in two
months. I don't need to be on
here. I don't need to be on here,
bro. Yeah, I'm going in two months. Be good. Yeah.
Yeah. See, and this is what you And
here's the thing as well. You don't get
paid for being on this community. You
don't get paid for being on this
community. It's full of grasses. It's
full of self projectors. Yeah. There's
no point being on here. Literally no
point. There's literally no point on
being on here. Full of [ __ ]
losers. I wish my [ __ ] sister's
boyfriend didn't introduce me to
gambling and I would have I would have
found this place. I literally wouldn't
have found this
place. My biggest regret is ever coming
across this community and gambling.
Well, they go they go hand in
hand, you know, cuz then I would have
found Timmy and I would have found this
community. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, it's such an embarrassing
community. Such a weird atmosphere as
well. I can't explain it. Weird.
Want to be in a [ __ ] community full
of a bunch of grasses. [ __ ]
that. It's mad,
eh? Mad. And how long can they and
another thing is like how long can they
keep this up for like stalking every day
projecting like when when does it end?
Like you sit here and you think well
when does it end? Because they're never
going to meet
you cuz they're scared they don't leave
the house. So what is it just going to
go on forever? The same spastics, the
same repeating every day. Like when when
does it actually come to an end? Because
you'll see these people make four videos
every day obsessed. Okay. Well, when does it
end? [ __ ] jealousy is a horrible
thing, man. It's a horrible, horrible,
horrible thing. Sad, isn't
it? I don't think I've ever been jealous
of anyone in my whole
life. Trying to think.
No, never, man.
It's a negative place for the losers.
I found it in the end, right?
Yeah. Yeah. I had to quit gambling. You
don't end up like [ __ ] Timmy.
I got like some roulette urges
yesterday, but I didn't do it. Like
online roulette. Nah, [ __ ]
that. Yeah. Okay,
man. Good luck in court in 2028. E,
[ __ ] hell. Imagine
that. It's every sense to plead guilty,
to plead not guilty. It makes every
sense cuz you plead guilty. Yeah. You're
going to get a fine, right? Or you're
not going to go to prison. But you say
you get a fine,
right? Okay. But then if you go not
guilty, then it's going to go to trial
in three and a half years and they're
probably going to drop it by then. So
why the [ __ ] would you go
guilty? that especially after all of
what these people have done like that
that just even tells you straight just
just don't like it it makes absolutely no
sense you know it makes absolutely no
[ __ ] sense at
all whereas if it was like criminal
damage and they said okay the trial's in
six months I would just go guilty if I
if I done it then I would just say yeah
I done it and I'll just pay the fine but
no I'm not I said I'm not going to go
guilty when I have evidence of what
these people have done, right? Which it will
literally it will go to trial if it ever
does go trial. That's if they don't drop
it. No [ __ ]
way. And and and you'll get exactly the
same anyways because it's three and a
half years time. It makes no sense [ __ ] going um going
guilty. Makes no sense. It makes
absolutely no sense
whatsoever. Makes no
sense. So yeah, but it's probably just
going to get dropped
anyways. But I guess it's easier for them, right?
So, I've been clued up with how the this stuff works now, you
know, since, you know, 10 years
ago. Said to this woman, I said, "I've
not been to [ __ ] court for 10
years." She said, "Oh, why is that? Have
you just got away with
stuff?" I was like, "No, it's not a criminal." Yeah.
So yeah, and I'm leaving this place anyways.
yeah, with these little stalking,
harassing little low
lives. My sister said it like proper
like she said it like accurately.
They're just low lives.
Low life, jealous people with ruined
lives. That's all they are. Broken
people can't live without
YouTube on a nice pop summer.
So I don't you know what? I don't know
how they can do it for years though.
Like sit online and harass people. I
don't know how they can do it every day.
I don't know. They can sit on here and
do it every day for years. [ __ ] madness. You
know the negative community as
well. That's another thing. We're
not. Nah, bro. Not me. Not me, buddy. No.
Yeah. I can't believe these losers run
to the police and no one says anything
about it. Grezy, I can never imagine
being that much of a loser. Like I know
like obviously no one's going to say
nothing because you're all biased on
here and you have no shame. I get it.
But I can never imagine being that much
of a loser where I start [ __ ] on the
internet every day then have to run to
police. I could never be that much of a
loser. Like I I'd actually feel
disgusted, bro. Like I literally would
go I'd actually bath in bleach if I was
that much of a loser. I would literally
like [ __ ] sit in a bath with a
bleach. I feel dirty. I could never be
that much of a
loser. And trust me, I've took But
again, these people don't have no shame.
But there's no point telling them what
what they what they are, what they
do, you know, proper proper loser
community, isn't it? It's a proper loser
community if you think about it.
You remember when they used to do the
same thing with uh Casai
Mark when they used to like call up the
benefits and say how he needs to get a
job. We're talking like say a good
five a good five six years
ago and like oh he needs to get a job
and and [ __ ] like that and then they
used to hate on him and that because he was on
benefits but the thing is bro it's not
the fact that and that I never
understood because it's like well if
he's not screwing the system someone
else is going to screw the system so
it's like what what are you going to do
stop people screwing the him and then
they'll be like, "Oh yeah, but we work
and we don't like seeing him get money
and wear designer clothes." Don't watch
him then. But then even if he wasn't on
benefits and he was making money
legitimately through working, they would
still grasp on him. So make it make [ __ ]
sense. These these people really are
like the proper retards. like like they
they really are like it's not the fact
that you know you you want benefits and
they work cuz most of them don't work.
It's the fact that you've got a better
life than them and you're not
housebound. That's what it
is. Yeah. So it's weird, isn't it?
They're just self projectors. That's all
they are. They have them because
confused of other people, you know.
So, it's [ __ ]
[ __ ] It used to be worse back in
the day as
well. They hate anyone with a better
life than them. That's what that's the
conclusion that I come I come to.
Yeah. What about you,
Grezy? I thought I going to try to give
you that community
service and [ __ ] Nah.
Yeah, but I'm still following up with my
um police reports even when I'm not on
here. every week. I'm going to keep
following it up. Somebody will be
getting some people will be getting
nicked soon, mate. Trust me. [ __ ] trust
me. True. Ask me. I never thought I had
it in me,
bro. I never thought I had it in
me. Yeah. Trust me, they will. Trust me,
they [ __ ] will, lad.
Yeah, I text the guy. He's
like, I have informed the officer and
they will get in touch as soon as
they're available. These things take time due
resources. I had to send them the
evidence. So, I'm waiting for them to
like um call me back
now, which they will do. They take time
nonetheless. So, I've got plenty more.
Plenty more. Plenty more.
plenty more buddy.
Yeah. Not been out for a
while. I've been out but not out
drinking. I don't care about women anymore.
Greasy. I don't give a
[ __ ] Don't care,
bro. Boring, isn't it? Yeah, man. Had
sex. I know what women are like. Women
are all the same. So, what's What am I
missing, bro? Nothing. really care
anymore. That's how you know you're
getting old it
greasy. I was thinking of going
Blackpool next week, but I don't think
I'm going to cuz obviously the weather's
nice, but there's no point wasting money
in this country.
Yeah. Well, I mean, you can go out every
week and spend like 70 80 pound
drinking, but I mean, there's no point
wasting money in this country, bro. It's [ __ ]
So, I just want to go Blackpool for two days.
Definitely when I come back from
Birmingham, I probably would have done
it from Birmingham just staying away in
it. I just can't be I just can't I just
don't want to spend I can't justify spending
£400. Yeah, I want to I'm waiting for a
new horror film to come out. There's
been no good ones
lately. Obviously, I can spend the time.
No problem. But I just can't sort of justify
it. Yeah, it'll be about like and then
I'll probably gamble when I'm there as
well cuz I've not played live for ages.
So, you're talking like what maybe
£400 train tickets with a hotel? Let's say
180. Yeah, maybe
350400. Can't justify it, bro. I can't justify it.
Not for this
country. You You could book a holiday with
£400. You know, you laugh, you take the
piss, but you can go on holiday for
£400. You can't go on holiday for 70 80
pound. So that's the way you got to look
at it, you know. Yeah.
be a nice holiday for
£400. Not America, but like you still
still book a holiday somewhere. Sure you
could. Sure you
could. But why not just go on holiday
rather than go [ __ ] Blackpool? It
doesn't make sense.
I've done most of the UK anyway.
So, isn't that right,
Grezy? I could go to Brighton for the
day will cost like450 for everything. I
can justify that 50
60 maybe even 70. I could be there all
day and spend 70
pound. I used to do that every summer. I
mean, you can do that,
but anything over 100, 200,
300. But it's like you can't find
anything longterm in this country. It's
like nothing goes anywhere in this
country. Does that make sense, Grezy?
S. Yeah, bro. Wow. Mhm.
Add some pork chops today.
Grimsley. I had some lovely pork chops.
I'll show you them if you
want. There we go. Lovely bit of pork. I
had um I had some police officers for
our um dinner today.
Grievesy, look, that's some police
officers. I'm cooking in a pan. Funny.
Yeah, that's what they do on a grievy.
Have you noticed all the tactics? First,
it's they try to get the black man to do
stuff. Then it's they try to [ __ ] I
don't know, get your benefits stopped.
And if it's not that,
it's trying to get other people to do
stuff. And if that all goes wrong and
that doesn't work, Grezy, they always go
to the boys in
blue. The boys in blue, eh? It's the
boys in blue, mate. [ __ ]
pathetic. Then it's the boys in blue.
Greasy. You know what that
means? I can't believe you're you're
going to watch Stitch
Squeezy. You should have outgrown that Stitch.
You like Stitch? Why do you like
Stitch? He's quite cute, isn't he?
Stitch [ __ ] Stitch. E, he's
cut. Do you remember Stewart Little? I
used to love Stewart Little. do a
little. He's a lovely little character. Yeah.
Remember when he got stuck in the washing machine?
Yeah. Do you remember when he got stuck
in the washing machine? That was
funny. Don't like the summer, man. It's too hot.
It's [ __ ] way too hot in it,
bro. I went to my mama's the other day
and I I was wearing You remember that
teddy bear t-shirt that I've got, Grey?
The Ralph Lauren
one? You know the teddy bear
one? Oh, [ __ ] hell.
70 pound that t-shirt cost
me. I can't believe how much time and
money I've wasted gambling,
bro. That's what made me
quit. That's what made me quit, bro. Like, no
more. No more, bro.
I have ways to make money, grievy. Can't
tell you how. They're actual legitimate
legal ways, but I can't tell you cuz you
have glasses on here, unfortunately. Yeah.
How's it getting on with you and the narcissist? [Music]
Did you just give up?
Yeah, that's what I was trying to do
with that [ __ ]
um Morgan, but her friends weren't
having none of it,
mate. They weren't having none of it. I
think she told them she must have put a
post out that, "Oh yeah, this person
from England's going to start messaging
you and [ __ ]
I was speaking to her sister for a little
bit. Yeah, I was trying that as well. But
yeah, but it never
worked. No, I don't gamble anymore. I'm
leaving YouTube, bro. I don't come on YouTube anymore.
Really? I don't gamble anymore.
Yeah, I would say USA is probably a
prostitute now. She probably sells
herself on the [ __ ]
street. Yeah, agrees with you. She
probably sells herself on the [ __ ] street, man.
So yeah, there's no G videos because
it's a waste of time, waste of money,
and I don't do it anymore. So, and
there's a reason why I have to stop
doing it as well, which I'm not going to
get into. But yeah, [ __ ]
gambling. I think I gambled again. Like
like maybe 10 days ago. I lost like 150
on I Horus. Was it 150? Yeah, I think it was. Was
it? Yeah, it
was. Maybe it was 100. I can't remember.
But it was a lot of Horus. Yeah, it's
just the same [ __ ] There's no money in the industry
anymore. There's no money in the industry anymore.
So, she can get in a landbased casino.
So, I've done well to stop gambling, didn't I, Grezy?
Yeah. [ __ ] pointless, mate.
can't deal with the guilt
and I don't know it's the guilt and
uh you know that money that can be spent
on other stuff and um
like obviously I don't like losing
so why put yourself in a situation where
you're always going to lose and even
when you win you will still
lose so you always lose in the
So that's why it's just
pointless cuz you'll always lose at the end. Ant-Man,
yeah, he doesn't get as much money as
me. He was winning, winning, winning.
Right. We usually listen to this. He was
winning, winning, winning. He got to
about 2.8K and within a two weeks he lost
everything. I've never even lost that
much before and I've gambled heavy
amounts. The most I've ever lost was two
grand, but I still had money
left. And so that would have never
happened if obviously he wasn't winning
winning. It's a trap, you see. You
always lose in the end. So there's just no
point. There's just no point doing
it unless it's like a oneoff in in a physical casino.
And don't forget he it's going to take
him ages to get that money back cuz he
doesn't get as much as me.
So he was bet like a grand on the
football and [ __ ] [ __ ]
that. [ __ ] that.
I've got money in my account where I
actually can gamble online as well. I
online, you know, right now. I can put
big amounts on if I want to, but I'm not doing that. No
way. Not even 100, not even 150, not
nothing. Cuz it's just pointless. I
don't need more money. I don't need to
risk to lose money, you know. It doesn't make
sense. I'm waiting for the Samsung Fold
7 to come out. Grievy, the Samsung Galaxy Fold
7, and I'll be [ __ ] buying it.
Yeah, that bro
What happened to him, man? [Music] Yeah,
man. We'll be live
tomorrow. Might come on next month. See
if it's the same people. I might just do
my little monthly checks wheezy just to
pop on just to see if it's the same
people and then come back again in a
month or so.
My little monthly checks.
my little monthly check to see if it's
the same people. Do you reckon it will
be the same people?
Yep. Same people every
day. Same people every day.
Yeah. Why? Because it's a [ __ ]
community. Crazy. How can it How can it
grow? It's the same people every day,
same arguments. Who's going to want to
come on this community, bro?
from the army says he's never been
nicked. I've been nicked [ __ ]
countless times, mate. I've been nicked
more times than Greavvesy has had hot
dinners. It's just the way it is, eh? Oh
man, you're doing great.
It's going to I need to go to
sleepy. I need to go snoozey
groovy. Do you remember Grevy? Um, women
was put on earth to satisfy Peter Belly's
needs. To satisfy Peter Belly's needs.
The way you just said that
sarcastically, bro, it's funny, isn't
it? To satisfy Peter Bell's
needs. That's funny, isn't it? there.
Bye-bye. Yeah, I'm done with this [ __ ] anyways,
bro. I'm done with this [ __ ] [Music]
Do you want me to go to Birmingham and
call out Prime
Grezy? I'll call out Prime, Provident Loans,
Timmy. I'll call them all
out. Call them all out, mate.
You'd love it in
it. Why you don't like to see
fight? Nah, there's no point, bro.
You'd agree that it's a grassing community then
Greasy. Would you agree? Would you agree
it's a grassing
community? It definitely is.
Definitely is a grassy community, right?
Yeah, but they they're grasses though, is
it? Nah, it's not even it's not even
dry. It's just boring. I can tell you
exactly how it goes.
Right. Pretending to call people out.
Arsenal Mark does a video in his house
pretending that he's trying to meet
people whilst he's making YouTube videos
in his house. You go live. You get the
usual self projectors. It's boring, bro.
It's not even a drama community. It's
actually just boring.
And then it gives you the ick. It's like
a weird vibe. Like if you go on any
other community. Yeah. You don't get it.
But this community is it's just weird.
Just full of
weirdos. You know what I mean? It's just Yeah.
Do we um do pork?
We Yeah, but there's no next chapter
though. That's the whole point, Grezy,
because it's the same [ __ ] every
day. That's the whole point. There's not
a next chapter. It's the same [ __ ] every day. repeated.
Yeah. Grievy, how was you watching me
from the get-go?
Like when I first come on here back in 2020
2021 like you remember the Isabelle days don't you
I ended up in
court. Forgot to say that I ended up in
court. He started telling me stuff. No,
that's the same
[ __ ] Yeah, he was talking [ __ ] about me, bro.
Yeah. He was talking [ __ ] about
me and I went to a store and then he shot
himself. Yeah. And he shot himself and
then he called me a stalker. He told me
to come to his [ __ ] workplace. I come
workplace and then he and then he was
trying to say that I was stalking him
and he used the one that told me to
come. [ __ ] [ __ ] He But to be
fair, he never mentioned my name again after that.
never never mentioned me again after
that. But yeah, no suicide marking stuff
is nothing new
though because he's he's done that
before. Yeah, I get you. And I ended up
in court. I thought I was going to go [ __ ] prison.
But yeah, that's that's a whole another
reason not to be on here
because Did you see that Rick Mace video
brie when he's fighting the fat
guy? Did you see that Rick Maze video?
Yeah, that's Mix
Mace. Yeah, that's the
one. I just don't find the grass and
entertaining. That's when I stop [ __ ]
with things when people start being
grasses. Like that's when I when I just
like, nah, that's
it. Nah, that is it, bro. [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] that, bro.
Uh, no one should be grassing on anyone in this
community. No one, Greasy. No one should
be calling the police on
anyone. Do you think that USA is he
really called the police on
me? I think so.
If she had called the police on me, I
would be [ __ ] You do realize
that with that one, I would actually be
[ __ ] And apparently they don't even
need to attend court
now. Apparently they don't even need to attend
court. That' be hard from doing that
from America though. trying to get
someone [ __ ] prosecuted in
it. Nah, don't think
so. That's quite scary, bro.
You was loving when all that drama was
happening, weren't you, Greasy? You was
loving when all of that drama was
happening. But, you know, out of
everyone. Yeah, I've I've had it the worst on
YouTube. Worse than Rick's, worst than
Monty, worse than anyone if you think about it. police posters, [ __ ] benefits.
Yeah, I've had it. And that's why
there's just no, it's not worth being on
here. I've had it worse than anyone, I think.
Man. Yeah, man. Yeah.
You But you said Greasy that USA Izzy
deserved everything, didn't you?
Yeah, I think so. Yeah. Definitely,
bro. I might have took it a little bit too far,
but I don't give a [ __ ] bro. [ __ ] them in it. It's quite [ __ ]
I just didn't like what they done and
the lying and
um yeah, I just didn't like what they
done. So, I thought [ __ ] it, I'll give
them [ __ ] in it. I don't care,
bro. You know, but there's a point where
it needs to end though. You know what
I'm saying? [ __ ]
hell. [ __ ] hell,
man. I don't think she's ever met her match
before. That's what it was. That's why
she started reacting like that. She's
never had someone tell her about herself
before. That's what some people need.
Grievous is they need telling about themsel, you know. Yeah. So yeah,
man. Grezy, I'll wait. Oh,
wait. Oh, bless you,
Grezy. Bless you.
Do you remember when I started messaging
the dad in that
um and he said if I go in his if I go to
his house share he would restrain me with
handcuffs. He literally wouldn't even
have the strength to restrain
me. He said he would put me in handcuffs
and take me to the
um to the police station. Oh my god.
with who? You wouldn't even have the
strength to restrain me. So, how you
going to put them handcuffs on, idiot? [ __ ]
absolute, man. That was It was some
funny. You got to
laugh. They should have just apologize, man.
You know sometimes greasy people should just
apologize like you want to just
apologize. I was waiting ages. I just
said, "Oh, like can you please
apologize? Please just
apologize." And then they keeping going
on purpose and they were just winding me
up. So I just started messaging their
family. So I gave them chances. I gave
them multiple chances to just apologize.
They didn't listen. So had to get family involved.
Anyways, I'm out of it,
bro. [ __ ] man.