Yeah, I think I can do that.
What about you? comes in,
mate. We're stuck like the same routine,
but it's good for a month. I think this
is a good routine for a month. We like
spreading each other.
just going out [ __ ] about
boyfriend. That's for [ __ ]
sure. One second. Yeah.
Yeah. What they need is it's more
accessible for them. That's what I'm
saying. That's what they need. More accessible for
them. You know what I'm
saying? Definitely not made it easier
for mandating. Definitely definitely
not definitely definitely
not. This country is so
backwards having to try win a football.
Get your needs satisfied. [ __ ] hell.
I wonder if people go around killing themselves
it [ __ ] yesterday on Instagram, bro.
Like, you're not going to change my
mind. My mind is made up. You know, I've
had enough bad experiences to last me a
lifetime and beyond. You know, it's the
end, bro. Stop trying to change me. And
and I would basically say to her as
well, it's not even about the past. [ __ ]
the past. Let's talk about that. We know
that if we go out on a Thursday, Friday,
Saturday, and we send approaches, we
know exactly what we're going to get. I
I done a football bet, bro. And if this
football bet wins, then you know what it
is. Blow drop from an escort. It's the same routine,
Dad. Yeah, you made a profile on
Hinge. Um, yeah, it's not my problem
anymore anyways, bro. I'm just going to
do football bets every week and every
time I win I'm just going to get an escort
and don't have this country
mate. And um do you know what I wish
that the um the betting shops had Steven
Howard? I wish they had um where you
could bet on women. What women do, what
women do after they give their number.
What happens uh what will happen when
you approach a woman. I wish they had
that bet market on the market.
Like I actually wish they had that bet
mark on the bucket. I'd be a
millionaire, bro. I'd be retired at 27
because they're that predictable and I
know all the words, all the stuff that
they do. I'm clued up on it like
geography. I would I would actually be a
millionaire. I'd be
retired. Put women on a bet as a bet
market on um dating apps. I'm sorry. In in the
bookies, you had lots of me you had lots
of messages. Well, good for you, bro. If
it works for you, I'm happy. Doesn't
work for me. I guess that just goes to
show that everyone's different.
Yeah. What team do I have?
Um, I've got
uh Not County, Colchester, and Mark and
Doncaster. So, I'm done anyways. It's
not my problem anymore. Anyways,
but then I know what I've got to do,
but that's it. That's the end of
it. No, no, no,
no. It seems like a super I'm not even
going to reply to that. Anyways, moving
on. So, yeah, bro. Um, that's the
football bets as well. Yeah, I see what
you're trying to do, but it's not going
to work. Anyways, moving on.
Yeah, it's a it's a dating app, bro.
It's a dating
app. Yeah, this is going to be the
routine. I didn't play the machines.
Obviously, I don't do that [ __ ] anymore.
Need to have faith for me. Have faith in
me. And you know what? I walked in.
Yeah. And the guy was like, "You're not
to go on the machines." I was like,
"Don't you [ __ ] work?" Cuz he
remembers me from last time. I'm not
playing with [ __ ] machines. [ __ ] that,
bro. But hopefully this football wins
and you know what time it is. So
yeah, after all the negative experiences
I've had, I don't understand how these
people can try to make you positive. You
know, you're 27. You've traveled
[ __ ] very very far. You tried lots
and lots of stuff. You're in your rights
to give up. It's the best thing for you.
You know, trying does not change your
situation. Like, there's no point even
like moving your [ __ ] arm, bro. All
right, that's it. You might as well just
give up. Give up and not even
try. That's not being negative. That's being a
realist. That's being That's not being
negative. I've been out this month. I
went out this
month. Um £122 from 40. So, that will
get the escort and leave me 50 quid. Yeah,
bro. Just keep trying these football
bets and and if you win, get an escort
and maybe go out in like two months. I
gave up for two months. I I'd done the
same routine for two months cuz it was
pissing me off. And then one day I
decided, oh, I'm bored. I just want to
go for a drink
anyways. So, I just wanted to go for a
drink anyways. And that's I'll give up
for another [ __ ] two months. It
doesn't bother me, mate. It's annoying.
I'm sick of hearing about these mate
boyfriends. It's [ __ ] annoying. The
ghosting and the piss taking. I'm not
dealing with it no more. [ __ ] yourself.
Simple. That man that Manchester one was
the last straw. And people don't
understand. They think, "Oh yeah, you
was only speaking to them for four three
days." It's not just them. It's all of
them. It's the ones that I've dealt with
in in, you know, in the past in the past
month. It's amalgamation of them. It's
not one person. You know what I'm
saying? Like the [ __ ] So that's why
there's like just no point trying. And
then they're going to blame you for
being a man and then they're going to
nitpick and blame you. Like there's no
point, bro. You might as well just give the [ __ ]
up. Just just do these football bets and
just you might think I'm mad, isn't it,
for like happen to win the football bet
first is because I'm not using my own
money. I know it's it's very backwards,
isn't it? It's it might sound uh very
backwards to you, but it's like I will
only do it if I win money. I could have
a million pound in the bank and I still
won't do it unless I win money because I
don't I don't want to pay out of my own
money cuz I shouldn't have to pay. But
obviously if you win money and you take
money from a billion pound company, you
know, that's a completely different
[ __ ] story. Hey, you know what I'm
saying? But not out of my money. I'd
rather risk and and lose and not get it, you
know. No, but what I'm saying is it's
money that No, not really. Cuz it's
different. It has a different feel to
it. I can't explain it. No, no, no, no,
no. I like to know that I've took money
from a billion pound company that's
destroyed many, many people's lives to pay for
it. So, yeah, but it's money you
want. It's it's money you want. So, it's extra money.
So, yeah. Bye-bye, weirdo. Bye-bye,
weirdo. And yeah, that's
it. [ __ ] off, you little weirdo. No
weirdos on my channel
now. No little creep weirdos on my channel.
you little [ __ ] [Music]
weirdos. So, no. As soon as you win,
it's not your [ __ ]
money. It's Yeah, but you're still
winning money. That's what I'm saying.
You're still [ __ ] winning
money. So, that's
it. Why are women so fat now? Cuz it's England.
But anyways, bro, we need to um change
up this channel, bro. No reacting to
these weirdos no more. Anytime they come
in, they project. We block them.
Simple. And I'm talking about a good
three, four people,
bro. You know what I'm saying?