This guy's a [ __ ]
idiot. The [ __ ] proper
me. Oh, I'm just about to have my crunch
bath, mate. And I got this gun at me
unusually. You know what I'm
saying? Get up. Oh boy. [ __ ]
Well, you never guess who skint
Now, not me.
Yo, bro, I just missed your [ __ ]
call. This guy is a [ __ ] idiot. I
told him, "Come to Albert Square
tomorrow at 1:00 p.m. Shut up."
Originally, I said 5:00 p.m., then I
said 1:00 p.m. Like, bro, stop writing
stupid little [ __ ] about me. Yeah. On
other people's channel. And come and say
it to my face, cuz I'm going to end up
going on this guy's door, bro. I swear
to God, I've had enough of his [ __ ] year
in year out. Year in year out, bro. Just
stop it, you know? Like, cuz I'm just
going to end up going on his door.
Simple. Like, I tell you what. Yeah. If
he wants to try to use that as an
excuse, tell him to go live right around Albert Square
anytime. Anytime, any day. Anytime. Any
day. Simple. Then there's no excuse.
Then anytime, any day. He can do it
randomly, you know? As long as it's past
like [ __ ] 9:00 in the morning, then
then what's the excuse? He's an idiot,
bro. And I'm just going to end up going
on his [ __ ] door. I swear to God,
bro. Like, I will end up going on the
guy's door. It's not even a joke,
bro. Oh, that Morgan's skint, mate. She
is [ __ ] skint. I went on her [ __ ]
yet. She's [ __ ] looking for an
apartment with a [ __ ] roommate. Yeah,
you suck dick. You ain't got no money,
bro. Yeah, you ain't got no money, mate.
You're looking for someone. Yeah, you're
looking for someone. You're looking for
a [ __ ] room, mate. You ain't got no
brother. Your skin, man. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay. He's an idiot, man. He's an
idiot. He wants to meet me in my my len
station, which is the opposite way from
both of us. Like, how long is he going
to keep doing this,
bro? How long is he going to keep doing this
[ __ ] You know, [ __ ] hell. Yeah. Yeah. Is
it that [ __ ] has got no money, bro? She
is skin. I swear to
you. Friends on holiday. Um LT and
they're still obsessed with me. Imagine that,
bro. Imagine paying money to go on
holiday. Yeah. And then you're you're
still obsessed with me. Imagine that,
bro. That's a [ __ ] madness, bro. That
is an actual
madness. [ __ ] me,
bro. I was doing that [ __ ] when I was
[ __ ] 23, bro. [ __ ]
me. Yeah, I had a barbecue LT other day, bro.
Look, I don't really go out drinking
much anymore, man. And I can't be asked
with it. Pretty much stunning this
country now, I think.
Bro, too many stabs to the [ __ ] womb,
bro. I'm telling you. [ __ ]
it. Uh, going to have another one next
week. You're invited. LT Sha's going to
be there. I don't really want you near
her cuz you're going to try and get in
knicknacks. You're going to try and get
in her knicknacks,
though. That's what I'm scared of. We
try try get lit nuts.
Yeah. Try and get in their
knickknacks. Their little
knickknacks. Some madness, bro. Yeah.
Oh, how can some people get, eh?
No. Sure. Looking for a room, mate. You're broke.
Simple. You're [ __ ] broke,
mate. You're [ __ ] broke. Oh, you're
broke, man. How can you How can you ask
anyone if they're [ __ ] poor? You are
actually [ __ ] broke, mate. Uhhuh. [Music]
I was I actually look back on that [ __ ]
I'm I can't believe I actually went to
the extremes that I did, bro. You know,
losing my life over some [ __ ] skit
that can't even afford their own weed.
Imagine that, bro. It's like them people
[ __ ] It's like them people that
[ __ ] kill someone and they do a
[ __ ] stretch all for nothing. [ __ ] that, bro.
You was in that position as well though.
Do you remember when me and you used to have beef?
Yeah. I said to Adm, "Did you hear about
that thing in
Scotland?" He said,
"Uh, do you know what he said?" He said,
"Yeah, I have heard about that about
heard about that." Yeah, that was that
was a fish's
attack. That was quite uh that was quite a fish's [Laughter]
attack. Yeah, give me a disclaimer, bro.
That was quite a fish's attack. Adman
said, "Yeah, I have heard about
that. I was dead." He said, "Yeah."
Yeah. Give me a disclaimer, bro. Come
on. Let's hear it.
it. What is it?
Yeah, I think I'm just going to have to
end up going on his [ __ ] door. Bro,
keep trying to say to me, "Oh, oh, he's
almost 30." I was like, "Bro, I'm 27.
You're almost 60." Yeah. It's not my
fault that you have to sniff around my
sloppy seconds. It's not my fault Jane
wanted me. You
know, it's not my fault [ __ ] Jane wanted
me. Yeah. [ __ ]
hell. He's just some old man, bro. Like,
imagine that being your
dad. He's old enough to be my dad, bro.
Imagine your granddad or your dad. Yeah.
Coming on YouTube at his age doing what
he's doing. Like, he's an embarrassment,
bro. He's an actual embarrassment.
He proper is an embarrassment, bro. Swear
down. And I brought up the time when I
went to Hackne two times earlier. He's
like, "Oh, I didn't know you went. I
didn't see it." Yeah, you didn't see it,
did you? Okay. Okay. You didn't see it.
Okay, bro. I've had enough of this
place, bro. This is why I don't come on here anymore.
You know what I'm saying, man?
No, you haven't.
Man, I need to [ __ ] go America, bro.
I'm going that [ __ ] on that dad's
[ __ ] door, bro. Bad him up, brother.
It Yeah, he will know what [ __ ] time
it is. He He will know what time it is,
bro. Trust me, he will know what time it is.
Yeah, but he's a [ __ ] pig, don't it?
I didn't know at the whole time he was
[ __ ] one of the boys in [ __ ] blue.
And that's what they'll do, Ali. They'll probably lie
you. That's the thing. They would
actually probably lie you as opposed to
like give you a fair fight, LT. They'd probably [ __ ]
lawyer. They definitely lawyer, mate.
They definitely loyal, man. No, no one
in that [ __ ] city is about nothing,
bro. Boston is about nothing. Trust
me, there's some [ __ ] bouncer, bro.
He's from New York. I tell him about
himself quite often. There's some black
guy. He's from New York. He's a proper
[ __ ] He works um in Soho. He's he
he's from New York. He's a proper [ __ ]
man. He's a proper [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah. I went, "Oh, when was it a few
months ago?" He said, "Oh, you can't
come any short. You you need to go to
Primark." I was like, "Bro, do you think
you're going to come to my country and
tell me what I need to wear to get into
this premises? Like, I'm I'm I'm not
going to no
premark, which is actually Primark.
Like, you're not going to come and tell
me tell me what I'm
[ __ ] telling wearing, bro.
You know what I'm saying? Just a [ __ ] in
it. Just like that manager from [ __ ]
Birmingham. There's a lot of [ __ ] here,
bro. He kind of looks like you, the bouncer,
out. Yeah, you can tell he was
definitely bullied as a
kid. That's what some bouncers do. They
they like the power of telling people
they can and do this, they can't do that
cuz it's it's it's because they were
bullied as a child. So they like to
uh they like to feel sort of in control so to
speak. Same with police really. Same
with old Bill. Really, lad. Yeah.
But this Arsenal mark needs to
uh stop his [ __ ]
Honestly, you're looking you're looking
for a place to sublet,
bro. Like, so you're looking for a place
to sublet, man. Just I should just go America,
bro. I pretend to be a [ __ ] seller in
it. Open the door to them, bro. Say,
"What the [ __ ] are you saying now?" What
the [ __ ] are you saying now, bro? You understand?
Yeah. Got the money as well,
man. He's been [ __ ] saving, saying
nothing to no one, bro. You are your
dad. That's the [ __ ] that annoys me. You
and your dad would never say nothing to anyone,
bro. Like, you might think I'm trolled
in LT, but I'm actually not, bro. Like,
you never you never would. You never
would, mate. Like, not even your new
boyfriend who you've got who I've seen.
You never would. Trust me.
Yeah, I've got a few enemies, bro. And
you know what? I want that Arsenal M. I
want him to bring that [ __ ] Terry
with him as well. He's getting on my
nerves as well, you know. Why do you
know what? Why don't we all just meet
like properly this time and not no
[ __ ] around? Why don't we all just
meet, you know, for a good oldfashioned
punch up? Why don't we all meet? Me,
you, Terry, Mark. Like being serious
this time, you
know? Cuz then the only one that's going
to meet, bro, is just it's just
like it's just me and you. Cuz it's like
I was telling you about that Terry guy.
He ain't about that life, bro. Yeah. Oh,
I've been in a cell. You've never been
in a [ __ ] You You've never been on
probation. You've never been in a cell.
You've never been in a cell. You're not
about that life. Shut up. Yeah. You're
calling me out that you're saying that
you're on probation. Okay, Terry. Terrible
trainers. You know what I'm saying, bro?
Like, please stop it.
Yeah. And then he's laughing at people
getting nicked. I knew that, Terry. He's
a bullshitter. He's just like Mark. They're all
bullshitt. They're all bullshitters on here, bro.
Yeah. [ __ ] idiots, mate. [Music]
I'll be your [ __ ] roommate. I'll be
roommate for somebody that is that looks
like you. You got a big [ __ ] ego,
bro. Let me tell you that. You got a big
ego for somebody that looks like you
with your [ __ ] shitty [ __ ] tattoos,
bro. Do you know what I'm saying? Your
shitty ass tattoos. Yeah.
Well, is this guy coming tomorrow or what? [ __ ] idiot,
man. A time and a place. So what? What's the
excuse? You know what I'm
saying? [ __ ] idiot. badness. Yeah.
Yeah. You need to send me his address.
I'm going to go to his door, bro. If he
don't come to her, I'm going to go in his
door. Yeah. If he doesn't come to her,
I'm going to come in his [ __ ] door
and I'm going to record the whole [ __ ]
thing. Like, if you want to [ __ ] with
Timmy, bro, [ __ ] with Timmy. But don't
[ __ ] with me. Don't mention my [ __ ]
name, you [ __ ] idiot. Stop mentioning
my [ __ ] name. He was mention He was
on Timmy's the other day as well and
Bondies. He's a sad old man, bro. You
know, he starts on everyone now cuz no
one likes him, you see. So they all
everyone stop everyone starts on him.
Literally everyone starts on him cuz
they know he's not that
nothing. I just said come to Albert
Square because he thinks I live there
even though I don't live there. But
anyways, let him come nonetheless. You know
what? You're looking for a roommate. You
got all this
money. That doesn't make sense. You're a
skint little girl. That's what you are.
And the only reason you was able to come
here is because it's a lot cheaper
coming here than it is going there. Cuz
hotels over there are a lot more
expensive. It's what I need to do. But I
just need to give you a good telling
about yourself, bro. No, no extra [ __ ]
like beating up or nothing. Just a good
old telling you about yourself to your
[ __ ] face. Same thing with this
[ __ ] Arsenal M, bro. That's why I
want to give him the chance to like come
and say what he's got to say to my face. He
won't just say what you got to say to my
face. But you will never you will
never [ __ ] hell, bro.
Yeah, that annoyed me, bro. Looking on
that [ __ ] post. That [ __ ] annoyed
me, bro. I can't Do you know what it is,
L? I can't be bothered with these
[ __ ] no more, bro. I'm I'm I'm I'm
done in this country. I'm a [ __ ] ant,
man. I'm out of here. I'm already
leaving in two months. [ __ ] this [ __ ]
bro. I don't care about these [ __ ] no
more, bro. Haven't for a long time. Why
I don't go out no more? They're actually
[ __ ] They actually make me
sick, you know? I was I was watching
this thing in [ __ ] Liverpool. Yeah.
Where did someone [ __ ] broke into
this girl's house and killed her? Uh,
you was dating a drug dealer. You was
dating a [ __ ] drug
dealer. Yeah, that's the risks it comes
with when you date a [ __ ] drug
dealer. Bro, this country annoys me, bro. Swear
down. Yeah, he's just a [ __ ] idiot,
bro. He's an idiot. You [ __ ]
idiot. I got my provisional come today.
LT. Yeah, I got my provisional
come. Man's been doing stuff, bro. Man's
stuff. That's so funny how you had to
get involved with that Morgan [ __ ] in it
though, LT. It's like I'm the one that's
behind it all cuz you know like people get caught. [Laughter]
Yeah, like for conspiracies and [ __ ]
LT, it's like I'm the one that's behind
it all. You know when you get like the
leader, is it like LT you get like the
leader? That's like behind it all. Oh,
that's funny, bro. That is funny. That
is funny, bro. It's like It's like cuz
you could have got into conflict as
well. Really? Is it? And I'll be the one
behind it all. Yeah, but I'll back up my
talk though. That's the
difference. That's the
difference. That's the difference,
bro. Oh, [ __ ]
hell. Yeah, I can't stand these [ __ ]
no more, bro. I don't want nothing to do
with them [ __ ] talking to them
anymore, bro. They're all sick in the [ __ ]
head. What? What do you mean exactly
what I would do? Bro, I've got I went to
his area two times and he didn't come
out. Yeah, I went to his area two times
and he didn't come out. He claims he
knows where I live. Why is he making
YouTube videos? It doesn't make sense.
Why is he making YouTube videos when he
claims he knows where I live? You see
how it makes no sense? It makes
literally no sense. And I've also gone
to area two times. He didn't come out
when I went live. Yeah, I told him to
come to Albert Square where there's no
cameras, where there's no nothing. Yeah,
I did do that. And what does he do? Tell
me to meet him at a train station again
cuz he's not about that [ __ ]
life. Same as Terry. And I'm going to
keep bringing that Terry up. Yeah. He
said you would run to LT about the
meeting. Okay. Okay, listen. [ __ ] the LT
[ __ ] right? [ __ ] the LT
[ __ ] Yeah. Tell him to come any day
unannounced as long as it's from like
9:00. You can't use LT as an excuse. LT
don't even live in London anymore. Okay.
Okay. Okay. [ __ ] this. Yeah. Tell him to
come anytime he wants and goes live. You
can't use LT as an excuse then, you
know, because LT don't even live in
London. And when he's in London, he
lives nowhere near me. So that that's
your excuse that done. Your excuse is
done. Your excuse is done then. Simple.
Like bro, the guy's a [ __ ] He starts on everyone. Yeah. You
know. Yo, Brick Bong, I was just on that
[ __ ] Morgan's Facebook. She's gone
proper skin, mate. Looking for a [ __ ] roommate and
everything. [ __ ] If I was in America
right now, I would set that [ __ ] up,
bro. You don't even know. I would set
that [ __ ] skin [ __ ] up so badly,
bro. You don't even
know. These [ __ ] make me [ __ ]
sick. I swear to God. They actually make me
sick. You know what? I'm actually
scrapping this going out one once a week
[ __ ] now, you know? I'm actually
scrapping it, bro. I'm just [ __ ]
going Thailand. [ __ ] it. I'm not even
spending [ __ ] 4050£50 a week, bro.
[ __ ] this [ __ ] you
know. They make me They make me [ __ ] sick,
bro. They literally [ __ ]
do. But yeah, that's the LT excuse out
the window. Yeah, all you got to do is
come any day
unannounced. Why is he telling me to
meet him in my linen? That doesn't make
sense. He's just a keyboard warrior. Oh
my god. How long has he been doing this now, man?
How long has he been [ __ ] doing this?
He's a [ __ ] idiot. You see, he even
starts on Timmy
now cuz again, no one likes him.
So, he did it. He did
Huh? What do you
mean? How did LT find out about him? I
don't [ __ ] know because he watches my
channel. He watches my channel obviously.
Yeah. But LG is always used as an
excuse. It's just excuses. Listen, I
don't even know why we're talking about
this. Like, no one on this community is
about anything. I don't even know why
we're even talking about this, bro. This
is We've been doing this now for 3
years. Yeah. And we're still talking
about meeting. Like, no one's meeting.
End of. Yeah. So, it's it's pointless
talking about it now, bro. We're having the same
conversation. We're having the same
conversation, bro. And nothing's
happening. Like, it's boring now, you know?
So, and I think he's a grass as well,
bro. To be honest with you, I think he's a
grass. Think about it, bro. Yeah. If you
knew where someone lived, I'm sick of
going over this over and over and over
and over again.
You would just go on their door. Yeah.
Like you would actually just go on their
[ __ ] door. You wouldn't be making
YouTube videos telling them to meet you
here, to meet you there. You would just
go on their
door. Like, but he has been doing the
same [ __ ] for [ __ ] 3 years. So, it
just goes to show he he's not about it,
bro. It's just It's just
boring, bro. I'm not meeting you at no
train station. I told you this earlier.
I am not meeting you at no train station
where there's police, where there's
cameras. I'm not meeting you at a train
station. Simple. I'm not meeting you at
no station 20 minutes away. So, [ __ ]
off. And you are the grass. Yeah. Why
don't you tell everybody listen? Yeah.
Why do you want to keep me in here,
please? Are you a grass? Are you a grass
or something? I'm running to LT. Listen,
Mark. Yeah. Go live anytime you want in
Albert Square. Anytime unannounced.
Anytime unannounced. So you can't keep
using that excuse. You're a [ __ ]
idiot, man. Get a grip. You're boring,
lad. You're boring.
Yeah. Yeah. There you go. Awesome. Walk.
Deal. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Deal. Simple, bro.
[ __ ] You know what? Yeah, LT, we can
both show him up right now. Yeah. Go on
his door now. Yeah. Go on his door now.
And join a live stream and show everyone
how he doesn't come out.
And then I'm going to embarrass him
tomorrow. You know what you should do?
You should just go in his door now. [ __ ]
it. Yeah. You you you know what you
should do? You should just [ __ ] you
should just go there now. Yeah, you can
come, bro. Come outside. It's not even
my house. But anyways, you don't you
don't even know where I live. But I said
Albert Square because you you think I
live there. Yeah, bro. You can. Yeah,
you can. I'm I'm going to be there 1
p.m. Good. Good. Good. And I'm and I and
I want to see you as well. I'm resting
my foot anywhere, so I'm not going
there. Good, good, good, good, man.
Good. Yeah. No, I'm telling LT, bro, we
can both embarrass him right now. Yeah.
Go on his door right now. Look, he's not
going to come out. And I'm and I'm going
to be there at 1:00 p.m. tomorrow, and
I'm going to embarrass him so that way
we both embarrass him.
Yeah. Simple, bro. Just go to his door
now, ain't it? [ __ ] it. Just join the
Just joining the live stream.
Yeah, you're not far, are you? Hack.
Yeah, go. But [ __ ] it. In
it, bro. If he doesn't call me out, I've
been to his area two times. He's never
called me out in his life. All of these
little YouTube videos is just for
attention. He has never called me out
ever. Yeah. He literally has never ever
called me out, bro. I've been to his
area two times. cuz a little [ __ ]
didn't come out. Yeah. Every time I try
to get him to meet away from a train
station, he doesn't do it. There's no
calling out. He's never called me out.
Don't even put him and calling me out in
the same sentence. Oh, I thought you was
out today, Arsenal Mark. I thought you
was out today. Oh, I thought you was out
today. That's why you couldn't meet me. Yeah, [ __ ]
[ __ ] The He's a proper [ __ ] idiot, bro. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Good. Yeah. Yeah. Do you do that?
You do that and I'll see you as well. I
will see you as well. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I go to LT to fight my
battles. Yeah. Yeah. I'll see you
tomorrow, bro. Yeah. I will see you
tomorrow, you [ __ ] little [ __ ]
Yeah. I'll be waiting for you, buddy.
I'll be waiting for you. Every time I go
I go to LT to fight in my battles. Yeah.
All the time, man. LG fights all of my
battles, man. Yeah. Like when I went to
Mark's area two times, LT was with me.
When I went to Manchester to meet Bomb,
um LT was with me. Yeah. Like when I
went to meet Terry, LT was with
me. Yeah. All the time, bro. Like when
Timmy and Tiger was in London, I had LT
with me. Yeah. LG always fights my
battles, man. Yeah, all the time. He's
always with me, even though we've never
met. [ __ ] hell, bro. Please. Please,
man. But yeah, that's
it. As if a [ __ ] fat old man is going
to beat me in a fight. But I will see
you tomorrow. I will [ __ ] see you
tomorrow, little idiot. Yeah. Who do you
think you are, bro? You're some old man
who's addicted to
cocaine. Yeah. You're never going to do
anything to anyone. Like, please.
Yeah. And I'll show everybody tomorrow
what you're about if you actually have
the balls to come and you don't [ __ ] around.
Yeah. [ __ ] old man.
I'd love you to come, B. [ __ ]
idiot. I want to get this Morgan's dad,
bro. Starting to wind me up again.
I might need to [ __ ] plan something
when I'm done with this [ __ ] mark
greet tomorrow, bro. [ __ ] pissing me off again, bro. You
know, you just know no one would ever
say anything to your [ __ ] face ever,
bro. They never say nothing to your
face, you know? Never,
bro. Even like you're writing on you're
looking for a room. Like, who do you
think you are, bro? Like, where's that
ego come from? Like, you're legit like a
three and a half out of 10 and you don't
even have money. Like, who who do you
think you are, man?
Like it's a madness.
Yeah. Yeah. I I'll disappear, bro. I've
never disappeared in my life from you. Yeah.
Simple. Yeah. Okay. Come here. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Come to Yeah. Come at 1:00
p.m. Yeah. Good for you,
man. Good for you,
bro. Please do come. Please do come.
come. May the only one that disappears
you. And when he when he doesn't come
tomorrow, no one's going to say anything as usual. No, no.
Why speak to
someone? Why? Um because it's
funny. And he didn't rob me either. He's
never took anything from me ever. That bike weren't mine. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'll see
you, man. I will see you. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Put your money where your mouth is. Yeah. [ __ ]
idiot. He didn't take my jumper. He's
never took nothing from me. Yeah.
Yeah. So, you want you want a roommate,
but yet you're the one that's trying to
call other people
poor. Oh my god. So, now you've got a
boyfriend. You got somebody to defend
you now. Yeah. So, now you've got Now
you've got a new boyfriend. You've got
somebody to defend you. And And [ __ ] if
that will stop me. Yeah. [ __ ] if that
will stop me, bro. It [ __ ]
won't. Yeah, [ __ ] if that will stop me,
bro. [ __ ] hell, bro. I swear to God.
Yo. Yeah. Mark, why don't you jump on a
panel? I can come to your house right
now. I'm in laying stone. Like, I'm not
far. Can you Can you hear me? No.
Yeah. Can you hear me?
Can you hear me? Yes or no?
Hey, I'll come back. I'll come back. [Music]
go. Yeah, I could I could hear you, buddy.
And since you speak to GV Arsenal Mark,
bring GV with you as well. Bring GV or
Terry with you. Please do, man. Please
do. Hey, Brit, man. I want to
[ __ ] Oh. Oh,
man. I want to put that [ __ ] [ __ ] in
America place again, bro. I want to put
her in a place again.
Like even the way you're writing like
who do you think you are, bro? You're a broke ass
[ __ ] Like is that what what you're
doing now? Yeah. Like having to find a
roommate, but you got all this money.
Oh, you got all this money
apparently. Oh, you've got all this
money apparently. You need a
roommate. [ __ ] hell. If that doesn't
scream skin, I don't know what [ __ ] does.
That's what they do. They Yeah. [ __ ]
cry to [ __ ] daddy, mate. That's what they [ __ ]
do. That's what these people do, Brit
Bong. They They lawyer. Yeah. They're
supposed to be big and bad in America,
aren't they? Yeah. Yeah. They'll be the
first [ __ ] to [ __ ] lawy you,
though. Yeah. [ __ ] idiot said he was
going to [ __ ] restrain me with
handcuffs. Restrain me with [ __ ]
handcuffs. Oh my god, that's funny, bro.
Restrain me with
handcuffs. Put handcuffs on me. That's
funny, bro. Yeah. You and what [ __ ]
army, bro? [ __ ]
idiots. [ __ ] absolute idiots, bro. [ __ ] Yeah.
How do I get myself in these situations?
Eh, how the
[ __ ] I get myself in these [ __ ] mad ass
situations. Anyone that's in the West,
yeah, you just need to get yourself to
Thailand. That's it. You just need to
get yourself to [ __ ] Thailand, bro.
That's that's all you got to do.
So, I was thinking, yeah, I could go out
tomorrow. I've not been out for a while,
but I feel
like, you know, you get to the point
where you're like, nah, that's it. Like,
I'm I'm ready. I'm ready to go now. You
know, I'm ready to [ __ ] go. I can't
be bothered with the drinking anymore. I
can't be bothered with these westernized
[ __ ] Generally, like just done. You
know, some people people get to it at
like some people are older when they
realize this. Some people are
younger, you know, but you will know
when you're ready, bro. You know what I'm
saying? And I'm at that [ __ ]
point. I'm at that point definitely, bro.
No, I just
I'm going to ask you. One second. Hello.
Yeah. Can you hear me?
You still can't hear me?
What the [ __ ] All right, let me let me try
my Arsenal Mark actually thinks people
are scared of
him. [ __ ] M, bro. He actually thinks
people are scared of him. It's
funny. He's a [ __ ] embarrassment, mate. Yeah,
What is this? Yo,
yo, you hear me? My phone.
Hello. What's wrong with your phone?
Yeah, mate. I will say it to your
[ __ ] I'll say it to your face
anytime, mate. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Bro, you're not going
to snap no one in half, man. Stop
embarrassing yourself. You're not going
to snap anyone in half. Yeah. Can you
hear me now? Yeah, I can hear you, bro.
Who does this guy think anyone's No
one's scared of him, bro. Like, I was
trying to meet him today. He needs to
allow it now, bro. Wait, hold on. So,
he's worried about me. Yeah. He's always
using me as a scapegoat as to why he
doesn't go go to your house in Albert
Square. He lives the closest to you.
Yeah. And he's always using me as an
excuse for for years. Oh, and by the
way, Yeah. He's always telling people in
the background, he thinks I don't know
these things as well. Yeah. He tells
Lord Jay, all of these people. Yeah. He
tells them that I'm scared to meet him.
You see? And he tells people, do you
remember when he was telling people that
I sent five guys to try and stab him and
he battered all of them and all this
type of nonsense? Listen, Mark, can you
forget? Yeah. Two weeks ago, I came to
your house on your own live stream. You
muted everything. You muted it. Soon as
I started screaming and shouting outside
your house, you turned that [ __ ] off and
you stayed inside your house. You did
not come outside. I was there outside
your house for a good half an hour to 45
minutes by myself after you said Mark
that you've got five guys waiting for or
is it four guys waiting for me? I still
came. Yeah. Stop running your mouth on
here talking about you're going to do
this. Come and join this live stream.
I'll come to your house right now. Like
I'm in late and stone right now. I'll
come to your house. It's it's what 20
minutes drive or something. It's less
than that. I can get to your house right
now. I know where your house is. You
know I know where your house is as well
cuz I know you heard me.
Yeah. I'm going to end up going and and
he's sending me emails now as well
trying to backpedal. He just he made a
video calling out my name for no reason.
If he's got a problem with you, then I
don't care about that. Listen, if he's
got a problem with you, I never cared
about that. I've never It's nothing to
do with me. But what my issue is, he
always brings my name in and starts
chucking it and chatting [ __ ] Now he
just said me and my batty boys and all
this nonsense. Bro, I come to your house
the other two what two weeks ago. I got
a video on my channel. I put it on
unlisted. I came to your house. You did
not come outside. You stayed quiet.
Yeah. He's done what you've done before.
Do you know what I mean? Like just he
just stays quiet. It doesn't come out.
So why you come on here trying to mouth
off because you're cuz you're sniffed up
or something, brother. I would slap you.
And another thing is, yeah, this guy's
got the skinniest arms, by the way. I
don't know why why you making videos
talking about, "Oh, yeah, I'm a big
muscular man." No, you're not. Stop
lying. I'll put your [ __ ] out. Stop
lying. Yeah, even Jane was You know
what? She's she's going to stand with
him obviously because that's a that's a
guy. You know this Mark guy? Yeah. He
just forces it in it, bro. He's just a
pretender. Like he's a big pretender.
How come? Yeah. He's always saying, "Oh,
he'll meet you and everything." When I
go to his house, I've gone to his house
twice. One of my mates has gone to his
house, another separate time. Yeah. And
he called he called the old Bill for my
mates, by the way. And the last time I
went to his house, this the last time I
went to his house, which was 2 weeks
ago. Yeah. This guy was talking about,
"Yeah, I've got cameras and all this
shit." Like, so I said to him, "So what?
Like cameras don't stop nothing unless
you're going to use them to document it
to give to the police or something when I come."
He's a person. This guy's a pretender. I
can listen Mark. Mark, let's join this
live stream right now. I'll come to your
house right now and I'll stay on this
live right now and I'll drive to your
house right now. I'll be less than 20
minutes if you're hard like that. Come
on. So, like I don't care what you want
to do to PJ. That's use lost business. I
don't care. But don't come on here
mentioning my name like you're about
something when you're not. I would slap
you old man. I would slap you. I've been
trying to meet you for the last how many
years and you always bottle it.
He's a [ __ ] bro. Guy's a pretender,
man. I'm sick and tired of it as well.
This is why I just leave all these
people alone as well cuz this is it's
always the same. I thought like me being
around Yeah. You know, for the first
couple years, I thought someone would at
least like let me meet them or
something. No, it's all the same. Yeah.
And then they end up trolling afterwards
and it's like they've got short-term
memory loss. They they like to forget.
Yeah. This guy, I've gone to Mark's
house just two weeks ago and he's
already forgotten. He's still mentioning
my name, talking [ __ ] I went to I went
to his area twice. No one mentions that.
this. Why is he not joining the live
stream then? He's mouthing off in his
video about me. He's talking nonsense.
I'm ready to go to his house right now.
He sent me an email as well, you know.
I've just seen it. Yeah, he sent me an
email, but I'm not reading all of it.
He's He's left me paragraphs talking
about, yeah, I'm sticking up for you and
all this [ __ ] That's what they always
say. I'm not sticking up for you. He's
mentioned my name, so that's what it's
about. If you're going to mention me,
then like be about it then, isn't it?
Yeah. And you know what? If he doesn't
turn up tomorrow, yeah, why don't no one
ever call him out when he cuz he always
does this, by the way. He's always
saying, "Yeah, I'm going to come here,
whatever." And he doesn't turn up ever,
right? And no one ever says anything.
Just let it slide. I went to his area
twice. No one mentions it.
So, I saw him in a comment. He's
mentioning my name still. Like, see,
that's what I'm saying. He's the He's
the keyboard warrior now. He's he's
running his mouth about me, but then you
don't want to let me meet you. Like,
what is all this? Everybody is in
London. Yeah. Why is Why does it take
10,000 years? Yeah, cuz I I guarantee
what it is. People People don't want to
really meet up cuz they know where it is
if you meet up. They know where it is if
you meet up. I don't have to say on
here. That's why nobody actually really
wants to meet up like that cuz they know
his problems. They know his problems.
And this guy, he's going to get exposed
if he does try to turn up tomorrow.
Yeah. Make sure you film it for
everyone. Yeah. Because this guy Yeah.
He's a small dude. He's smaller than
you, by the way. Yeah. Cuz Jane told me.
Yeah. He's smaller than you and he's got
skinny arms, bro. Like, don't let this
guy ever try to force it. For years and
years, these people choose to try and
make mad rumors about me. Yeah. And I
should just be quiet like that. Make her
rumors. You know what I'm trying to say?
I've proved it many times and no one
calls this guy out. This guy's a fraud.
He's a big fat old man. Yeah. A fat man
with skinny arms. Guy's a goofy man.
I've talked about your mom. You know,
I've talked about your mom, Mark. How
come you don't ever say, "Oh, yeah. Let
me meet you." Huh? I told you about
that, Terry, as well. It What about him?
He's a [ __ ] bro. I told you about him
as well. We were Listen, he's a [ __ ]
Listen, listen, listen. Me and my cousin
was just speaking about this right now.
Like, none of these dudes actually want
to meet up. It's not That's why all this
time here, they've been trying to like
do this reverse psychology with me. Get
me to get myself in. I don't need to get
myself in any more trouble in this
place. Like, I've got away. Lucky
enough, I got away for a few times. I
don't need to push my luck. For what?
For what? For what? I I know I know if
you was really about it, someone would
have stepped outside the house. How much
time do I need to go to people's houses
for them to step? like what do I need to
do any I don't need to do any more than
that like just like him if he was really
about that he wouldn't let me he he
knows what he done 2 weeks ago yeah he
was on his own live stream and what he's
saying right now about um you come to to
get me and you always telling me no I'm
subscribed to I subscribed to him in the
last what month or something yeah cuz I
was been waiting for him to go live so I
can just pull up like unannounced just
like I did two weeks ago I just pulled
up like he thought I was joking and
everything yeah and he said he's got
four guys for me and all this [ __ ] Yeah.
Where was these four guys? How come they
didn't come outside then? How come they
didn't come outside? And and when have
any when has anyone ever heard me Yeah.
come on here and say, "Okay, I'm going
to go to your city, but um you're going
to have five guys with you." I've never
made these things. If you got to bring
five guys and do that, like, you know
what I mean? I've never ever made these
little stupid excuses. This is what this
guy does just to uh deflect and get out
of not coming to see you. That's all it
is. He's always used me as an excuse.
Why won't he just go to your house
unannounced? It's true. Why won't Why
would he just go there in all these
years? It's always me that's got to go
there. I don't seen anyone else that's
gone there and had to kick off and break
windows and I've done all that and it's
like, "Oh, you've still not done
nothing." That's cool. I don't care. You
know what I'm trying to say? Let someone
see me on this place for real. Let let
someone shut me up like for real and
just embarrass me and let's see what
happens. Everyone's got mouth on here
all the time. Yeah. Just like the other
day, you know, they found my new
channel. Yeah. And all the racist
comments started. They come on my [ __ ]
They started talking underneath my
cousin's comment and stuff saying
madness. Yeah. Bro, none of you will say
it to our faces. I promise you. Yeah. If
you're going to use me as an excuse, oh,
I do videos and all this nonsense. Okay,
what about my cousin then? What about
anyone else that's associated with me
then? If that's the case, you guys are
all frauds on him, man. I've watched it
too many too too long to see now. Like,
you know what I mean? I've wasted my
time. I've wasted my time. So, I don't
even get involved with these idiots
anymore. I'm involved with Mark because
yes, he's in London. Anyone else in
London that's local like that, I don't
mind. I I'll watch them. Do you know
what I'm trying to say? But everyone
else that's all distant and stuff, I
can't be asked anymore cuz you guys are
frauds, man. Then then they call police
on here as well. That's another thing.
You all calling police on each other
like getting each other nicked. What
type of [ __ ] [ __ ] is that? Yeah. Yeah.
And then they are clowns, bro. Like
that's not in my world. We don't do
stuff. And I'm not even like that
anymore. But I'm just saying we don't I
still wouldn't get them involved. That's
that's a joke to me. You're calling
police over YouTube because you can't
confront a man by yourself. That's or
you don't even have to go and meet him
by these guys don't even have to meet
you by yourself. They know where you are
and stuff. What they claim they do. So
why don't they just pull up and they can
have as many people as they want. Give
you a good kick in like that then. Yeah,
they're [ __ ] bro.
They're [ __ ] 100%. All they can do
is I'm sick of it as well because you
know when I've tried to get away from
them. Yeah. They won't let me get away.
They come and they subscribe to my
channel and they still got to say their
negative nastiness underneath not even
just my comments. They're not even
saying it under my They're saying it
underneath my my family members stuff
now and they're talking mad brave as
well. But if you if you want to meet
Yeah. just come and do it. If you're so
scared, I've got a gym in Old Street.
Yeah. Fight factory in Old Street.
Google it. Yeah, you can go there. If
you're so worried about me pulling
20,000 guys, all these excuses that
these guys make. Yeah. Go there and tell
me that you want to go there and then
I'll meet you there. That's it. They're
not going to let me. They're not going
to lose their license for me doing
something. Foul. Dudes don't want to do
that on here. They're just [ __ ]
pretenders, man. I'm sick and tired of
it. It's kind of embarrassing as well
cuz these people are old men. It's old
men. You guys got grays in your beards
and [ __ ] like and you carry on like you
got like allow it. It's perfect. So
Mark, why is he not Is he still in there?
I'm I'm ready to go now. I'm
Is he still there? No, but just go there
cuz I'm I'm I'm going to I'm going to be
waiting. The last time I went two weeks
ago, he was No, listen to what I'm
saying. Listen to what I'm saying. He
done a live stream two weeks ago. Yeah.
I told him I'm about 20 minutes away.
Yeah, he was running his mouth saying,
"Yeah, you're going to get a shock if
you come in." All this nonsense. Yeah.
He He was saying it like he wasn't He
turned off his mic. Yeah. But then he
was typing it in the chat saying, "Yeah,
I'm going to get a shock." And how he's
got four guys waiting for me and blah
blah blah blah blah blah. Right. I said,
"No problem. You can have your four
guys. Just make sure you're outside your
house. Like, I don't care." I pulled up.
Soon as I pulled up, I started screaming
outside of his house. Yeah. And he
quickly locked he locked it off. I swear
to God, I'm not even lying. I've done a
video as well. I put it on my other
channel. I done a video. It's on
unlisted. Yeah, this guy would not come
outside. So, he's a coward and he knows
it. And then what's irritating me is
he's come back today. I don't care if
he's got a problem with you. Let him
handle that with you. I don't care.
Yeah. But then he's mentioning my name
and he's and he's mentioning my boys and
this and that. If I if I show that to my
boys or or or whatever he's calling them
or whatever, they'll kick off his door
and then you'll run to the police and he
knows that. They'll kick off his door. I
don't know why you playing these games
with me, Mark. Cuz you're you're a
chief. You're more than a chief. You got
cameras outside your door. Yeah. That
means you're a chief. Like real talk, I
don't need to have cameras outside my
house. My parents don't need to have
cameras outside their house. Yeah. Like
you're scared for your life because you
know what type of neighborhood that
you're living in, Mark? Yeah. Nobody
there. Listen. Yeah. I'm minding my own
business. Yeah. And I'm saying nothing.
And this guy's starting every time.
Yeah. He's done it to me. I one of Have
I Have I even come on your channel
recently? No. Exactly. So why is he
mentioning my name for And listen
listen. And now people call him out on
his [ __ ] Yeah. He he does it to Timmy
and Monty now because because Oh,
exactly. Yeah. So, it start on the
vulnerable people. I'm sick and tired of
this place. That's another thing I'm
sick and tired of. [ __ ] on here as
well. Yeah. Let's always start on the
vulnerable people and they and they get
laugh. Okay, cool. You've had a laugh
about it. But how long you going to have
a laugh about it cuz this has been going
on for years as well. Let's wind up
Timmy. You know what? Let me not stick
up for people actually, you know,
because no one ever sticks up for me and
says anything. You know what I mean? So,
but I see what it is anyways. Like, it's
a joke on here, man. I don't give a
[ __ ] Like don't don't nobody start
coming and start making excuses. Oh,
LT's PJ's friend and No, it's nothing to
do. I'm just calling it how I see it.
The man's mentioned my name. Yeah, I've
not bothered nobody. I don't bother
nobody. I don't come to anyone's chats.
I don't [ __ ] say anything. Yeah, I'm
out of use lost business. You mentioned
me. Yes, I'm subscribed to him. So, I
saw it myself. You think PJ messaged me
or anything? No, I've not even spoke to
PJ for a while. He hasn't. He's never I
saw it myself and I saw I saw his one
first and then I saw PJ's one and I
watched both of them and I heard Mark
mentioning my name talking about this
and that. So yeah, of course I'm going
to get involved now. It's a Friday
night. I was at my cousin's house and
I'm still just outside and and I'm
seeing where it is. I'm saying Mark like
now that you know that I want to come
again cuz he knows I know where his
house is. He knows that. Yeah. So now
he's gone quiet and he's sending me
emails trying to cop please. Don't cop
please in your little emails to me mate.
Yeah. Don't call up my name and start
insulting me. And then you want to start
like messaging me in the private like,
"Oh yeah, just leave it between me and
PJ. [ __ ] off, man. [ __ ] you and suck
your mom as well, your dead mother. How
about that?" Like straight. No, no, I
don't care. No, I'm getting Aggy now.
Like just I have to say these things.
Yeah. Like come and do something about
it. Let me do something then. Like cuz
you've not said nothing crazy like that
yet. I'm saying it. Yeah. And he's not
he's not got no smoke for me at all.
Yeah. I'm sick and tired of it. This guy
has lied to me so many times. Yeah.
pretended to people in the background
that I'm scared of him. He's tried to
make out to people that I'm scared of
him. I won't meet him. I never show up.
And then he's he's told Jane, but like
years ago, I'll never forget this. He
told her Yeah. that I sent five guys to
try and stab him and he battered all of
them. Is this guy mad? Like if if if any
of my Come on. If someone's coming to
shank him or whatever, they'll shank
him. There ain't going to be no you turn
into you turn into Superman from Clark
Kent and start disarming people. There's
there's none of that. I've never seen
that in my life. Yeah. This guy's a
fraud, man. I'm sick and tired of it.
Yeah, I got
you. So, so he's not in there no more.
No. So, why am I See, that's what I'm
saying. So, 1:00 p.m. tomorrow. Look,
I'll stay out of it. Look, I'm giving my
word. I will stay out of it tomorrow.
1:00 p.m. Yeah. But Mark, let me meet
you. I'll come to you like afterwards.
If he if if he don't show up as well,
everyone should call him out as well. I
I'll stay out of it. Don't use me as any
more scapegoat to not go to PJ's house.
Go to his house at 1:00 p.m. tomorrow.
Yeah. Albert Square, whatever. go there
and go and handle business. Yeah. And I
know you're going to go outside cuz I
know I already know that you're not
worried about it, man. I know. I know
that. So, I'm not scared, bro. I went to
his area twice and he didn't come out.
Do you remember? Oh, and that's another
thing as well. The first the second time
you went to his house, I know you done it consecutively.
Yeah. I messaged him cuz I was cool with
him at that time. I messaged him. And
you know what? I messaged him. I said to
him, "Please go and smack him up." Yeah.
He's at me street right now. Cuz
remember, do you remember when I said it
on your live stream 8 years ago and I
said to you, I know exactly where you
are. You're by the 38 bus stop by by M
Street. Yeah. And then you looked up at
the 38 bus stop and you closed and
that's when you turn the camera off.
Yeah. I said it to him. I said, he's at
the 38 bus stop. Yeah. M street. Like go
and smack him up. And this guy, he
ignored me and then he tried to message
me later on in the day and said that he
was like somewhere else. But you done
that two days consecutively and it was a
Saturday as well. Yeah. Yeah. I
remember, bro. I remember. and he's
never pulled up. And then he tried to
tell me another time that he's gone to
Stratford and he knocked on your door.
He was knocking knocking knocking and he
saw your curtains move. I was broke. But
even that time when even that time when
I knocked or whatever. Yeah. I remember
you came down but you didn't open the
door for me obviously but like you did
come down and you you knew that we was
there. I remember that. So I was
thinking like that would have at least
happened. So this guy's he just ch [ __ ]
man every single time. Yeah. I hope guys
a fraud man. And by the way, I hope he
does come back tomorrow. You know, you
know, he actually tells Jane and she
believes this dumb [ __ ] as well. Yeah.
Like he actually tells her that like
he's he knows all these people, all
these top old school gangster guys in
London and all this nonsense. Yeah.
Well, if you know them, why you worried
about me and my little squad of guys
then? Cuz we're nothing, remember? Like
we're just We called us roadies or
whatever. Yeah. So why you worried about
me then? If you know all of these top
hard men, you don't know no one, man.
And the other guy. Yeah. Like he's a
fraud as well. Yeah. Pretending that
he's a part of some big family. Yeah.
Nah, you're a fraud, mate. I asked them.
Yeah. And you're not. I'm not going to
I'm not going to dox or anything. I'm
not going to dox, so I'm not going to
call out their names or anything, but
he's a fraud as well. Like, I'm just
saying that big time. Big time. And I
can prove that as well. Anytime he wants
it as well. Like, I can prove that. But
yeah, I'm done. Anyways, if he's not in
this chat anymore, what there's no
there's no sense. There's no point in me
coming, is there? No.
So 1:00 p.m. Make sure you're there as
well cuz in like whoever don't turn up
or whatever then you got roast each
other whatever you got to do. I'm not
going to be there. I'm saying it right
now. I'm not going to be there. No one
associated me associated to me is going
to be there. I'm not going to be there.
Let's see if Mark turns up now. Now we
have to turn up. Right. I'll be there.
Yeah. Yeah. That's it. Yeah. Well, I'm
going Huh? Done, bro. Say again. I said
done. Yeah. I'm done now anyways, man.
Like, let me know how it goes tomorrow.
Or is it going to Are you going to go
live or what? He's going to go live and
then I'll just go live. Yeah, he's going
to go live. Well, I'm sub to him anyway,
so I'll see it. Yeah, good. Yeah, cool.
Yeah. All right, cool. I I'll see I'll
see what happens tomorrow then. If no
one turns up here or whatever. Yeah,
just just just drop it out, Mark. Like,
cuz this has been going on for years as
well. Like, he's been calling every Tom,
Dick, and Harry out. Yeah. How many
time? And he just forgets.
The guy just forgets. No, no, no. It's
it's it's actually quite sickening to
see it as well. But you actually forget.
It's not I don't know what it is. Like I
just gone to his house 2 weeks ago and
he still has a cheek to mention my name.
That's cheeky, bro. Like come on, man.
But all right, cool. Handle business
tomorrow and whatever happens, let me
know in it. Yeah.
Cool. I'll shoot you
tomorrow. See you tomorrow, bro. See you
I'm not letting you [Music]
in. Probably have that
B. Yeah, man.
Yeah, I'm going anyways. So, I'll be
back tomorrow, 100