Well, I'm done for a month after today.
After today, I'm done for a month. I'm
going to do a monthly welfare check just
to see if it's the same people in
YouTube every day. You ain't got to lie.
Oh my god. I actually woke up today
thinking this is the same old [ __ ]
We've been doing this now for [ __ ]
years. Arsenal Mark pretends to want to
meet people. Red Star, the keyboard
warrior, who's obsessed but would never
say anything to anyone's face. Monty and
Timmy going back and forth. That's why
you can't really be on here like
constant for more than two days cuz
uh you get um you start getting like
brain damage, bro. You actually start
getting like severe brain
damage with [ __ ] community. I'm done
after today when this [ __ ] doesn't
show up at 1:00 p.m. I'm done again for
a month and then I'm going to conduct a monthly welfare
check. I don't want to see these people
on YouTube anymore. They come on every
day calling people this that and the
other. What don't they call people?
Well, then they should be the ones on
YouTube then when I come back in a month
then should they? Well, they will be sat
on YouTube. 40year-olds sat on YouTube
gossiping, bickering, [ __ ] emailing
each other. [ __ ]
losers. They've got ruined lives, bro.
They've got [ __ ] ruined lives,
bro. [ __ ] hell. This been going on
for [ __ ] years as well. Bors me, man.
[ __ ] bors me. So
boring. Boring, man.
Proper trying to catch Joe.
I'm trying to catch Joe, but I can't find him.
Yeah. But let's see what the excuse is
going to be today when this little idiot doesn't show up.
Oh, you know, it's just [ __ ] autism.
That's all this community screams of is
autism. [ __ ] calling people out. Why
would you do a video, I quote, calling
somebody out when you've got their
address? doesn't even make that just
goes to show they're not about that
life. But to be fair, no one on this
community has ever been about that life.
So I don't know why they still talk they
still talk about fighting and that when
literally none of them are about that
life at all because they're on YouTube
making YouTube videos. Now, I'll tell
you 100% this Mark Samson little [ __ ]
attention seeker is not going to be
going to no Albert Square because he's
making videos on YouTube and people that
are about that life don't make videos on
YouTube. I should be a
[ __ ] psychologist. I know these
things, you know. People that are about
that life don't make YouTube videos,
especially when they know where people
live as well.
Read into that what you
will. It's embarrassing. Proper proper
autistic [ __ ] vibe this community
gives. It's creepy. It's Do you know
what else it is? It's actually creepy,
bro. Proper proper like creepy
vibes. Makes my skin
cool every day. Yeah.