Yeah,
bro. That Arsenal mark is a bottle job.
Changing the [ __ ]
location. Changing the location. I'm so
done with this place, man. I can't
believe I got like dragged into it again.
The guy's a clown telling me to meet him
in [ __ ] Miland when we literally
agreed to [ __ ] Albert swear. I'm
done. I'm so done, bro. I'm going to go
live today later and then I'm done with
this place for a month.
Yeah, same [ __ ] It's just the same
Same people, same argument, same people
pretending that they want to meet
people. [ __ ] my end. Literally nobody
agreed to my end. We agreed. Albert
swear. Now we say my end. [ __ ] off. The guy's an
idiot. Anyways, I'm done.
Yeah. Same spastics every
day. Literally. Yeah.
We got bigger fish to fly as
well. You [ __ ]
do consider booking this, bro. I'm not even joking.
But that pissed me off yesterday, right?
pissed me off today. And his [ __ ]
[ __ ] M guy don't [ __ ] help, does
he? You know what I'm
saying? [ __ ] hell. Oh
man, [ __ ] lawyer though. That's the
thing. The [ __ ] lawyer,
mate. You know about that life. Really know. [Music]
So, um, what are you people in YouTube
going to get lives?
Anyways, let's hope it's uh sometime soon. Huh?
It's basically the
same. It's a nice hot summer's day,
man. Let's hope these people on
YouTube. Like I said, I just come on
here to do welfare checks. I just come
on here to do welfare checks.
Really? Just welfare checks. That's
it. See if it's the same people every day.
It always is.
Nah, bro. He's [ __ ]
um he's [ __ ] around. He was supposed
to come to Albert Square at 1:00 p.m.
Now he's changing the location. He
always does this. He's a [ __ ] house. He
is an absolute [ __ ] house. I'm just
going to ignore him in future now. He
just wants attention. That's all he wants.
That [ __ ] in America's starting to wind
me up again. I'm not even
joking. Starting to [ __ ] wind me up
again, bro. You think an old man like
[ __ ] her father could could restrain
someone like me. Oh, please, man. I
swear in America they're supposed to be
big and bad. So why they why do they talk about
police? You're a police officer. So what
what you're saying is that you you law
someone like I don't mind though, you
know, going back there. I don't I don't
mind. Like I don't I don't literally
mind as long as they're not going to
call the police. That's that's it in
it. [ __ ] hell, bro. I feel like going
there and going on each door, bro. I'm
not even joking. Yeah. I'll be like,
"Bro, [ __ ] make a group chat about me
to my [ __ ] face, old man. You won't
be able to. Bring whoever you want. You
know what I'm saying? Thank you, man.
Yeah, that's it, bro.
Thanks. There you
go. [ __ ] It was pissing me off, bro.
I swear to God. But they just run to the
police, though. This is what I'm saying,
man. You know, do they just run to the [ __ ] police
again like I always do.
What? Stupid little [ __ ]
thumb. Oh yeah. When she was posting
that [ __ ] about how she's looking for a
roommate. She's looking for somewhere to
sub that. Bro, I I wish I was a fly on
the [ __ ] wall, bro. Like if I was
living there, bro, I'd get the [ __ ] to
[ __ ] I'd get somebody to contact
them, get them in the yard, and then
I'll just say to him, "What are you
saying now? What the [ __ ] are you saying
now?" You know, "What the [ __ ] are you
doing now, you stupid little cunt?" No,
I don't want to do it in front of your
boyfriend as well. Like, I want to do it
in front of your boyfriend, too. That's the
thing. I want to do it in front of your
[ __ ] tattoo boyfriend as well. But
I'll say in front of any man's face.
That's the difference. You know what I'm saying,
bro? Just don't run to the [ __ ]
police. If I have it on screenshot that
you're not going to run to the police,
I'm going, bro. [ __ ]
it. I fall out of it. I swear to God. [ __ ]
this. I could be a landlord. Yeah.
Get you in the [ __ ] yard and see what
you're saying to my [ __ ] face when
you're not behind the [ __ ] keyboards,
you little [ __ ] You and your [ __ ]
father. You and your [ __ ]
father. You know what I'm saying, bro?
[ __ ] hell. Annoying, bro. That was
annoying me yesterday. Next
level. And your father's a pig as
well. What I'm eating right now, pimp [ __ ]
[ __ ] Just go straight on your
[ __ ] door, mate. That's what I'll do.
We all know where you live. You know what I mean? [ __ ]
[ __ ] Can't stand women, mate. I
can't [ __ ] stand. Why do you think
I'm on a Coca-Cola today? There's no
going out sending it. There's no
nothing, bro. I can't stand him, bro.
Worse worse than Ant-Man.
Yeah. I was talking to the person on Reddit
earlier. He said, "Oh, he said hate." He
said, "Hate isn't um there's no reason
to hate them." There's 101 different
reasons to hate these [ __ ] I'm saying
101. You know what I mean? [ __ ] hell,
bro. I'll be live today. That's it. I'm
done for a month to do a welfare check. Well,
fresh. Women are evil. Money, money, you
know, women are the root of all evil. bodies,
women [ __ ] know what I mean,
bro. Bad bad
bad. They're bad people in general. Bad
general. If Mr. G was back right on
here, I tell him the same thing, bro. I
say, listen, I've got life experience
now and they are very bad in general. generally bad
people. That's why I don't bother no
more. I can't stand
him. Just do my own thing. You
know, you got to understand in this
life, right, bad people get awarded. You
understand? That's the way it is. Yeah,
I felt sad with him,
bro. I really thought they're [ __ ] evil. [ __ ]
[ __ ] And I want your I want your
boyfriend to be present cuz bro, he will
watch me tell you about yourself to your
face. But I don't care if he's a I don't
care if he's a man. He will he will
watch me do it, bro. Like that's the thing.
Yeah. Little [ __ ] with tattoos. Go
[ __ ] your mom, bro. Yeah. That's why
your dad always talks about [ __ ]
running to the
police. Well, because he's a [ __ ]
police officer himself. is a pig. A pig?
I can't think I can't think of a worse
thing. A pig. No, I don't think I
am. [ __ ] old man.
Yeah. Sorry. It hasn't pissed me off,
but I'm sorry.
See, it's one of them things again where
they'll try and lawyer. It's like what
people on here do. They they want to
wind people up. Yeah.
Right. They want to wind people up, but
then they run to the police. And it's
it's exactly what that [ __ ] in America would do.
Um it's the same as like what that um
that [ __ ] in America would do.
I'd show you a proper owning in your
country. A proper ass whooping. But we
know that you're going to run to the
police. Yeah. Bro, I was on that [ __ ]
Morgan's um Facebook yesterday.
Yeah. And uh she's got this boyfriend
with tattoos. Yeah. And then she's wrote
how she's looking for a
roommate. Bye-bye, [ __ ] Um how she's
looking for a roommate t. I'm thinking,
hold on. If someone's got all this
money, why are they looking for a
roommate? Like, you got the cheeks,
right, to try and ask someone if they're
poor, yet you're the one who's asking
for a [ __ ] roommate. Like, who are
you, bro? Like, you're a [ __ ]
like, but the thing is, bro, you go over
there and you go on her dad's door,
they're going to call the police. He's a
police officer. He's an actual police
officer. They're they're they're [ __ ]
They're [ __ ] bro. I swear to God. You
know, you got all this money, but I'm
the poor one, bro. Do you think I would
ever need a roommate?
Never. [ __ ] hell,
bro. I feel sorry for that poor guy. But
here's this is the thing, the trish.
Yeah. This is why you shouldn't you
should give up in this country. I've
given up now. Like, I haven't been out
for a while. I don't drink. I don't want
to deal with women no more. I can't
stand him, bro. But think about like
this. Yeah. Somebody like that who's
like a three out of 10 is a worst person
in one of the, you know, wor one of the
worst people can just get in and out of
relationships. I don't care cuz I'm I'm
done with the date now. I don't give a
[ __ ] I don't care about them anymore.
But and then you get normal decent
looking guys, but they can't get
nothing. Bad behavior gets rewarded. You understand,
bro? Yesterday. Yeah. I could have
guessed, bro. And you got something like that. Yeah.
And I'm not jealous of people in
relationships. I'm happy for anyone
who's happy, bro. You know, I've got my
life. I'm good by myself, bro. But, you
know, bad behavior seems to get
rewarded. Where? Where did you
approach? Yeah, I'm done with it, bro.
I'm going try that. I'm done with it. Yeah.
I'm going to Thailand,
brother. In two months, I'm going to
Thailand. I've booked my
flight. I can't be bothered with it anymore, bro.
You're talking. I went um I went on a
date. Yeah. Couple of weeks ago, and she
traveled an hour away from She knew what
I looked like. She actually approached
me and you know what she said after the
date? How she doesn't feel the vibe? And
I'm thinking, what do you mean you don't
feel the vibe? You literally approached
me. You gave me your number. You spoke
to me in a nightclub and you've met me,
but you don't feel the vibe. That makes
no sense. And I was like, bro, I just
kind of gave up from there to be honest.
I had two days. I was like, I can't be
bothered with this [ __ ] anymore. This is boring
now. Doesn't make sense.
Oh, and the ghosting as well. I was
speaking to someone a week and a half ago,
right? Do you know what I can't stand
emotional, Thomas? It's the ghosting.
It's the time wasting. It's not even
that, oh, I've got a boyfriend or No,
no, no. Do you know what? It's not even just that.
Yeah. It's the ghosting. is the time
wasting when they'll purposely waste
your time and they'll do it on purpose,
but people will be like, "Oh, well, why
would they waste their time and yours?"
It doesn't make sense. They do waste
your time on purpose, bro. I was
speaking to one for 3 days and they completely
vanished. That's what annoys me. It's
the ghosting that annoys me, bro.
Nothing. And when they go on dates and
waste your time, that's what annoys
bro. So, that's the [ __ ] that annoys me,
just [ __ ] annoy him.
So anyways, imagine a stinking mess who
can't even afford her own [ __ ] flat
or house thinking she's better than me.
Oh, please mate. You're [ __ ] not,
mate. Poor guy. I don't know what he's
[ __ ] in for.
Yeah, I don't have any tattoos, you
know. They've got tattoos. I don't have
tattoos. I don't have one
tattoo. Don't think I ever will, to be fair.
Yeah. I don't like [Music]
tattoos. Don't believe in him.
I love this as well. Yeah,
bro. Throw up the
goblin. Hey got my
friends. I'm not a boyfriend.
Any man that's from a westernized
country, England, America, Canada,
wherever, you should just go to
Thailand. You should just give up here.
Why? Why play a game that's rigged against you?
you? It doesn't make
sense. You might as well just go to
Thailand, bro. Yeah. Notorious. I can go
like two minutes away from where I am
now into a brothel and get my dicks off
for [ __ ] 60 quid. Do you understand?
I don't need to go out doing this
approach and [ __ ] But like literally 2
minutes away from where I am right now,
there is a brothel. And literally
there's a brothel, bro. Yep.
So madness, man.
But yeah, I'll be live again later. And
after today, I'm done for a month. I'll
do my monthly welfare check, see if
people are still on
YouTube. Um, and that's it. I don't want
to see any of these people on YouTube.
No, but you're M. Bye-bye. Yeah. So yeah,
man. Just a monthly um monthly welfare
check. See if it's the same people every
day. Shouldn't be if they've got this good
life, but they're sat on YouTube every
day. I didn't
Well, should I go and put £150 in the
Frank key? Nah, I'm good. I'm [Music]
good. I'm having a barbecue. Um,
Thursday. I might invite LC. I'm not
even joking. I'm having a barbecue on
Thursday. So, um, anyone's
welcome if you want to come. Nice
barbecue. All expenses
paid. Just what I notic about Lord J.
Yeah. When he's when he's exhausted all
options, he he then goes to the He then
goes to the boys in blue. He's a coward.
He's a [ __ ]
coward. Should I have a beer?
Nah, I don't really drink anymore,
man. Know what I'm saying? Yeah.