Yo, we
Mark, you ain't [ __ ] one. Yeah,
firstly. Yeah, I've literally just come
back. I told you to go live. You didn't
go live. And you also changed the
meeting point. You haven't won nothing,
mate. You was camping outside of a
[ __ ] train station where there's
cameras, where there's a police station.
Yeah. Right by where there's a [ __ ]
court. You haven't won nothing. You
ain't won nothing. And you want to talk
about backup? You brought backup with
you. You [ __ ] idiot. This guy. Yeah.
I swear today after today I'm done,
bro. Oh, I swear now. Guy's a [ __ ]
idiot, bro. He's a [ __ ] idiot.
Yeah, he says he's going to come to
Albert Square. He doesn't go to Albert
Square. He goes somewhere completely
different. Then I go to the same place
as him. I tell him to go live and then
he won't go
live. The guy's a [ __ ] idiot. And
he's got backup as well. Yeah, he's
talking about LT. Yeah, he's the one
that's got backup. The guy is a [ __ ]
belt, mate. He ain't about nothing.
Yeah, he ain't about anything at
all. Mark, if you're listening, yeah,
you you're at my land. I'll just come
back from there. You wouldn't go live.
Yeah, by then isn't that far. Why do you
not go come to Albert Square with all
your little friends then? Yeah. You
can't you you can't use LT as an excuse
now. You know, you said that you've got
backup. Yeah. Okay. Come on the road.
Simple. [ __ ] He's an idiot, man. This
is all just He just wants a reaction in
it. That's what he wants. He doesn't
This guy doesn't want to meet anyone.
Nah, this guy don't want to meet anyone.
He doesn't want to meet anyone. And he's
got backup himself. So, and he's still
trying to use you. And what the [ __ ]
bro? Doesn't make sense. You
know, uh, story of your life, in it, Sage.
Yeah. Say these things to his face. I
will say it to his face. He was supposed
to come to Albert Square, but he went
somewhere completely different. I will
say it to his face, and I'll say it to
your face as well. Come to Albert Square
like you kept saying you was coming to.
I will say it to both of your faces.
You're you're more than welcome to come yourself.
Simple. I will say it to both of your
faces. None of you bother me one little
bit. A YouTube hard man making videos on
YouTube. We Listen, listen listen
listen. Yeah, listen. Right,
LT. Yeah. What did we say yesterday?
What was the agreed place yesterday?
Yeah. What was the agreed place
yesterday? Albert Square 1 p.m. Did he
come or not? No, he did not. And I would
have said it to his face. I would have
said everything to his face because he
doesn't bother me. He does not scare me
one little bit because he's just a
YouTube hard man looking for a reaction.
Yeah, I said it. He's a YouTube hard
man. He's only big on YouTube. We said
100 p.m. Albert Square. Then he's going
outside the police
station. But to these little weirdos,
he's one apparently. Apparently he's
one. Think about it, LT. Yeah. If this
guy was really trying to meet, he would
just come on your door. Not the
[ __ ] Yeah. [ __ ] you. Yeah. Let's
get you out of the equation. Yeah. This
guy claims that he knows where I live.
He would just come on your door at a
random time and then just go live, bro.
He would literally wait for you to go
back to where you live out of London and
he would come on your door live and he
would be banging that door down. Why has
this hard man not done this? Why is he
doing videos outside of a police
station? Because he's not about that life. You
understand? It's like what you were
saying the other day. It's all for
reaction. Think about it, bro. Please.
Hey, look. Where is that? Can you see
that? Right outside Miland Station.
Yeah. Yeah. Can you see that? Yeah.
Yeah. Cool. So, I'm walking to the park
where he claims he's at right now. Yeah.
Let me take off my camera, though.
What? What was the What was the meeting arrangement?
Say again. What was the What was the
meeting arrangement? The meeting
arrangement was Albert Square. Yeah. And
And then I said that I won't get
involved. I said I won't get involved if
he goes to meet you at Albert Square.
Right. But now he's this morning he
changed the destination to my lens and
now apparently he's got someone. Okay.
Well, he I'm not complaining. You can
have whoever you want. Yeah. Now I'll
meet you. Now I'll meet him there since
no one else is going to turn up or
whatever. I'll meet him there because
I've got my own problems with him from a
long time ago. Yeah. And he keeps on
avoiding me and he does all this because
he knows you're not going to show up in
my lens. So he does all this. That's why
he won't go to Albert Square cuz then
you're going to have to show up if he
goes to Albert Square. So, I'm here my
land. I've gone out my way, drove down
here, got my car parked up around the
corner, and I'm basically at the park
now. That's how quick I was. That's how
quick I was from the station to the
park. Yeah. Now, where is this little
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro? Tell him to come
and join. Tell him to come and join.
He's giving it all the big yesterday.
Oh, my batty boys and all this nonsense.
Yeah, it's all right for him to be a
keyboard warrior and talk [ __ ] I'm here
now. You've wound me up and I'm here
now. Come, let's get it cracking. There
should be no excuse. Don't talk about
Don't talk about in a boxing ring at
some time because you know that's never
going to happen. Yeah. Well, it would
happen on my end, but he won't never
agree to that. He won't never turn up.
So, I'm here now. I'm at the park. I
don't see him. Tell him to join your
live if he's so about it then. Yeah.
He's with his friend, right? So, what's
the excuse? What's the excuse? So, wait,
wait, hold on. Can you hear me still?
Yeah. Look, I'm going to turn I'm going
to turn on the um the camera
again. It's not even turning on. Oh,
there it is. Can you read that? That's
at the front of the park. Yeah, it's at
the front of the park. This is where he
he's got in his video. Yeah. That he's
here. I'll show the footpath as well.
This guy's a rat, man. Playing these
hide and seek games with these people,
man. Look. Oh, look. We got one here.
You one piece. We all saw he changed the
destination, bro. Yeah. See, look,
that's the first person. Yeah. That's
not biased. That's the truth, bro. That
is the truth. Because we said Albert
Square 1 p.m. Yeah. And then I said that
I won't get involved if he goes to
Albert Square, but because he won't get
involved. Yeah. And because he's changed
the location to my lens, I said, "All
right, [ __ ] that then. I know you're not
going to come to my lens. So, let's not
waste his journey unless I'll turn up
instead then." Now, I'm at the park.
Where is he? He's going to pretend like
he got he don't see your live stream.
He's going to pay these stupid games. If
he if he doesn't meet you, then he's
took two hours today, bro. Simple. Yeah,
cuz he didn't come to Albert Square and
he's not met you. Two different beats there.
So, before any anyone on YouTube, you
know, you're not That's what I'm saying.
That's what I'm saying. And another
thing is, yeah, this has got nothing to
do with me defending PJ. Everybody knows
my thing with Mark stems from a long
time ago and he's always avoided
conflict with me.
Yeah, he DC, bro.
DCDed. So, Mark took two hours
today, you know. Nobody was going to get
involved. Literally, no one was going to get involved, you
know. He's a [ __ ] idiot, bro. He's
not about that life, man. Like I was
just saying to LT, yeah, I don't know
about what your beef is, but listen, if
this guy really wanted me Yeah. Yeah.
He he would just randomly come on your
door like at random time. Think of it.
Yeah. He's using LT as an excuse. Every
single time he's using LT as an excuse.
Okay. Well, he can just come on your
door at a random time and do a video on
YouTube, but he's not. He's on YouTube.
That's the only way he can get
attention. Jay doesn't give him sex. Jay
doesn't give him no
loving. So, he has to come on YouTube
[ __ ] pretending to call people out for attention.
you know, I'm still
here, you know, 15 minutes away from
um my land. What you waiting for? If you
still want to come, I'm here, you
know. So, yeah, the guy's an idiot, but
I'm leaving today for a little bit.
Anyways, so he's took two hours today.
He's not met you and he's not come to
meet me on the arranged time.
Yeah. So, you took two L's today,
buddy. Two [ __ ] L's. Yeah.
Let me ask this L a question.
Why didn't you add me?
I have Why? Why to the boys in blue?
What? Why did you run the LT? Why do you
keep running to the boys in blue?
Why did Why did you run the LT? I didn't
run to LT. Him and Mark might have their
own No, him and Mark might have their
own beef, but how did LT know about it?
Cuz he watched Mark, you [ __ ] idiot.
Mark didn't put up any videos. I did.
Mark, he subscribed to Mark, you [ __ ]
idiot. That's how he [ __ ] knows about
it. How come you're not in my land
meeting him? I never ran to no one, bro.
I never ran to no one. How come you're
not in my land or whatever the [ __ ] it
is? What do you mean? Why am I not in
MN? Because you were supposed to come to Albert Square.
Why was LT going to Albert Square? Why
isn't he coming to Why isn't he? Why?
Why was he? Um, no, no, no, no. One
second. Let me let me correct you,
Henry. Um, I I started running to the
police because they kept running to the
police about me and ended me up in
court. Yeah, that's called protecting
myself. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I ran to the
boys in blue when you people kept
grassing on me and you made me and I
ended up in court. Yeah. Yeah. When you
people made me end up in court, I did
start doing it. Yeah. I admit it. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I did to protect
myself and I'm still doing it. I'm still
doing it every single week. It's going
to take some time, but Yeah. Yeah. I do
now. Yeah. Yeah. Definitely. Definitely. Definitely, mate.
Yeah. Yeah. You made me [ __ ] end up
in [ __ ] Crown Court. So, yeah, I do
go to the police
now, but not or [ __ ] anyone else.
Yeah. Yeah. And I'm proud about it.
Yeah. Cuz I thought, you know what?
Yeah. I've tried doing the right thing
years now, and all you people do is run
to the police time and time and time and
time and time and time and time and time
again. So, I was like, if you can't beat
these people, join them. And if you
can't beat them, join them, bro. Why?
Why do they do this? Why do they
purposely try to make it out like I'm
defending you and I'm No, listen. I said
yesterday I'm not going to Albert
Square. If he if Mark goes to Albert
Square and has and do what I have to do
all this time, Yeah. then I will not get
involved. But because Mark changed the
Because Mark changed the destination
this morning. Yes. I'm subscribed to
him. I subscribed to him for a couple
weeks ago when I had to go to Mark's
house when he was on live stream. And
you know what he done when he done live
stream, Lord Jay? Yeah. The guy muted
his mic soon as I went outside and
started screaming outside of his house
to him to come outside. This guy said
he's with four guys. This guy said he
was with four guys. Yeah. Two weeks ago
when I went outside of his house. Yeah.
And they didn't Nobody come out to do
with me. Nobody. Yeah. I've got a video
of that on my on my channel. Yeah. And
now today cuz I know he's always going
to avoid me. Yeah. He likes to go for
try tried to act tough to spaces cuz he
knows that nobody's going to meet him in
no mile. Yeah. So I've turned up in my
linen. That's it. Like he said he's with
somebody. Okay. Well then I'm not with
nobody. Yeah. Where is he then? Why
isn't he joining us live? I know he's
watching as well cuz I know he's
subscribed to PJ just like how I'm
subscribed to Mark. Yeah, I've been
watching all He's probably in the car
going back home now. What car? He
doesn't drive. He gets a coach. He gets
a coach. The guy broke. Let me tell you
cuz this guy acts like he's he's he's
balling. Yeah. This guy gets a coach all
the way to Cardiff. From Victoria,
London. Victoria all the way to Cardiff.
Eat his skin. Like how the hell are you
getting a coach 4 hours to go to? I know
I know people who do it as well, bro. Go
to Cardiff. You're a chief, mate. I
drive. Like, you think I Listen, this
guy. Yeah, that's what I'm saying. He
ain't in no car. He's not with I I think
he probably is with someone. He was just
in Patty Power. I showed Paddyy Power.
Like, I just showed that I'm outside the
station as well. Where is this guy? He's
a fraud. He's been doing these videos
and messing around and playing
hide-and-seek with people. Now, I'm in
the same park where he claims to be.
Where is he? I'm walking around. I don't
see him. It's It's a big It's a big
field as well.
The guys are blown up. The guys don't
Hey, listen. Don't let this guy come on
and try and call that nobody else ever
again. Yeah. No, no. If he does it
again, I'm going while this is all going
on because the agreement was him to meet
you yesterday at Albert Square. Yeah.
That was an agreement. And then I said
up and he agreed to it and then he
changed it. Yes. And I And I said 100%.
I put a disclaimer out and I said if he
goes to meet you at Albert Square
tomorrow, I will not get involved.
Nobody associated with me will be
involved. Yeah. Cool. He's now changed
it this morning. I saw that video
myself. So stop coming with all the
excuses in the world for this coward.
Yeah. Cuz I don't make excuses for
coward acts. You know what I mean? I
pulled up. I'm here. I'm the only one
that can go live and show where I am.
Yeah. He can't. So that's cool. That's
that's all I've got to say on the
matter. If this guy I'm going to be
watching your live, so if he comes or
whatever, I want to see it. I'm going to
be I'm still monitoring him. Yeah. Next
time he goes live as well. Yeah. The
next time he goes live, I'm now it's
just going to be unfair. But I'm not I'm
not doing none of this oneonone stuff
anymore after today. Yeah. So no, I'm
being I'm being honest. So, I don't
care. So, next time he goes live, I'm
sending people to his door. Like, I'm
joking. I'm not even joking. I'm sending
people to his door. Next time he goes
live, Yeah. just to embarrass that [ __ ]
I'm sick and tired of him acting like
he's tough on it. Yeah.
Yeah, man. He's a He's an idiot, bro. He
took two hours today. Two hours. Yeah.
Yeah. Oh, that's a madness. One second,
LJ. I am just sipping a can of
Coke. Oh my god. Yeah. [Music]
L always runs to the boys in
blue when time gets when times get tough. Oh
mate, do you remember when you got done
for doing a fob tea in you silly man? Yeah. Huh?
Hold on two seconds. Remember
You was greeted by
Al here. I unfort I don't like to admit
this but I agree. We I think El or uh
Mark should just went to your house. I
told him that yesterday. I'm [ __ ]
sick. I said I'm sick and Mark was
messaging me yesterday saying about
organizing a time for you to meet him.
But I told him just to go to your house
and go live. He said to come to Albert
Square at 1:00 p.m. That was the time. I
said just go to your house at anything. Sure.
If you're live, you're in the house.
Your your phone doesn't work outside cuz
you're So when you come out the
hospital, you was greeted by old Bill.
What are you smashing? Remember that
time when you smashed the machine?
Which one? You broke your leg and then
you went to the hospital and then old
Bill was up there. Didn't break my leg.
Well, it was your foot or something. No,
I kicked the boogie door. What? I kicked
the boogie's door
and he was greeted by Anyway, why aren't
you whenever Mark changed the Mark
changed the plan to go to my land? Why
didn't you go? So, it's not like you're
busy or anything. I was wait I was
waiting for him at Albert Square. How
come uh you haven't done anything to me?
Waiting for him at Albert Square. That's
why cuz that's where he said he was
going. A L got greeted by old bail. All
because he decided to smash the machine. Oh,
griezy. I went on that [ __ ] um bitch's
um [ __ ] uh Facebook yesterday, man.
And you know you know how we I don't
think I said this to you before, but
basically the thing is Yeah. is
um the thing is um bad behavior gets
awarded. Now obviously I gave up with
the whole dating and [ __ ] now. Anyways,
I was done like a couple of weeks ago.
I've not been out. I ain't drunk for
ages, man. I went spoons earlier, had a
breakfast even though it's summer. I'm
off the [ __ ] drink. Yeah. And it's
mad how somebody can be like that. Yeah.
Cowardly, evil, [ __ ] disgusting. And
yet they can get like in and out of
relationships and then you got normal
people out there, like normal men that
are struggling to find people. Like I'm
not me because obviously I'm not I'm not
in the dating game anymore, but I'm just
decent people. Decent decent looking
even decent looking people and and and
it's not it's and the thing is greasy.
Yeah. It's not the way that she looks
because you people can't help how they
look. You know, everyone should be able
to like find love and find someone. Look
shouldn't determine that because you
can't help how you look, you know, as as
as mad as it sounds. But you can choose
to be how you are. And if you're a [ __ ]
and you're scum, I don't think man or
woman you you should be able you you
should be with
someone. That's the way I see it. So,
and that's kind of like icing on the
cake cuz the thing is greasy, bro. Why
should I I'm sat here having a can of
Coke. I'm having a coffee cooked for me
later. Why am I going to go out there
today? My friend invited me out dealing
with negative experience. Negative
experience. Negative experience. No, I'm
not doing that. [ __ ] that. I'm good,
bro. I'm leaving this country in two
months. I know what I got to do. I'm
done. Simple. [ __ ] that, bro. That was a piss
take. It's not a fair war. Why do you
think good people die young,
Weezy? Anyways, I think this is Monty.
Yeah. What you
doing? Huh? What are you doing?
This is [ __ ] what what what is it
with these people on YouTube calling
people out money? They don't show
up. That's what they do.
PG not used to it. They not used to that
[ __ ] now. PDF. One second. Hold on.
What's up? What was it? I
just so sorry about that. Yeah. Can you
hear me, Monty? Hello. Monty.
Oh, look. Grievy. As soon as I said to
this woman about how dating is unfair
for men, she replied straight away. Oh,
is that mad? I'm so [ __ ] done, bro. One second. Hello