Sorry about
that. Sorry about that. My [ __ ] thing [ __ ] up. Yeah.
Yeah. I still don't feel as good as I
did a couple of months
ago, you know, when I gave up with
women, but get that again, you
know. Yeah. But then wouldn't even
entertain it again.
This Mark Thompson was supposed to come
to Albert Square at 1:00 p.m. but he never [Music]
strange. That's strange,
lad. Yeah, I told this woman in
Birmingham about like how women are all
the same and [ __ ] All of them are the
same, bro. It's a
madness. Some are worse than others, but
they're all bad.
Yeah. Eat a proper sausage,
man. Yeah. What are you doing today,
Dad? You having a little
drink? I'm off the booze. Me? I'm [ __ ]
They replied to
negativity. I noticed that they reply to Yeah. Yeah.
But just know Yeah. You drinking? I'm
not drinking, bro.
When I had that foot injury, I had to
let it heal and it's like 80% better
now. But I still don't want to I just
wouldn't go out anyways. My friend was
like, "Oh, meet me after work. We'll go
drinking." I don't want to drink. I just
want to leave this country at this
point. Now, I'm just looking forward to leaving. Yeah. Yeah,
bro. Do you know what a part of me was
like? You know, I was near the train
station. I was like, "Oh, I should just
[ __ ] off to Blackpool today. I went to
get some breakfast." I was like, "Oh,
let me just [ __ ] off." And it, you know,
I owe Grievy and Steven Howard that
video, but I thought the footage is not
100% and I want to go all that way. And
then I'm limping as it is. So it's still
not 100% better, but we reckon if you
give it another week, I think it'll be back to
normal. It was quite a vicious
injury and it takes time as well. It's
not something that goes in like a week
or 10 days. It takes time, you know.
So it's very you have to be patient with
it as well. It's very frustrating,
especially the first stages of it.
the first stages of it is is so annoying
because it's like you have to keep off
your foot, but at the same time you've
got to use your feet to to to to walk to
like even up the
road. So, you know, you have to be
patient with it and careful with it and
it's [ __ ] annoying, you know.
So, even though it doesn't sound like a
big thing in shop, it is. It's annoying,
bro. I was waking up at like 4 in the
morning. The [ __ ] thing was
throbbing, mate. Absolutely
throbbing. Go that [ __ ] New York football start [ __ ] start Olympic.
So, but yeah, they respond.
They're [ __ ] up, bro. But yeah,
anyways, God rewards bad
behavior cuz um I even see people
like back when I met like in
2012 and like bullies, people that used
to be quite nasty and speak about dead
relatives and [ __ ] and they're living
quite a good life, you know? They've got
a kid, they've got, you know, a job. I
mean, everyone's got a job.
Um, but like yeah, and then the other
guy that's nice, I still talk to him. We
met when he was 14. His life's [ __ ]
much worse than mine. Like he gets 300
pound a month. He's constantly
depressed. So yeah,
bullies, whether it be women or men or
people that are not very nice people,
they they they get um rewarded in life, I find. Um, you
know, well, like my life's not bad. My
life's good, but you know,
it's I think at this point, you need to
wake up and smell the coffee that a
there's no one for you in this world.
And B, it's going to take so many more
negative experiences to find someone.
And it's just not even worth it. Like, I
don't even I don't even have a sex drive
anymore. I'm so done with it.
You know, I'm just I just can't be
bothered. You been if you've been by
yourself for 27 years, you can be by
yourself for another 27 years. You
know, things weren't like they once
was, I guess.
Yeah. Yeah, bro.
I mean, yeah, I had a few chances to be in relationships,
but you know, I say this to add, man,
like obviously I've had chances to be in
relationships, but the thing is the
amount of effort that I have put in, I
shouldn't have got the negative
experiences that I did. So, I should
have like I should have like booty calls
right now. And if you don't know what a
booty call is, it's basically somebody
that you can just call over and bang
them. Just the amount of traveling and
[ __ ] like. So yeah, I was just lucky I learned at
27. At least I won't wake up with a [ __ ] hangover
tomorrow. Ex numbers that won't
reply. It's not worth it,
mate. The way men have to deal with
dating, it's it's dreadful.
And people make it sound like it's much
easier than it is. It's not [ __ ] easy. It's
annoying. It's just Yeah. Just can't
stand it, bro. And and I'm not even
contradicting myself now either cuz I'm
not going out talking to them. So I
don't want to [ __ ] talk to
them, you know?
So yeah, you'll find that you're
narcissist as well.
Greasy. I don't have no tatto. I got a
load of bruises on my [ __ ]
arms. Lifting that thing, but I don't
have no tattoos.
Yeah, man. Bad, lonely, depressed,
talking about yourself. I've got loads
of friends. Um, I could go out with a
friend today if I wanted to. That's the
story of your life. Bad, lonely,
depressed. I'm not depressed at all,
man. I'm good. I've got money. No, just
the things I'm talking about are depressing.
Yeah, man. No, he didn't show
up. Um, bor, lonely, depressed story of
your life. Well, you're much older than
me. So, yeah, you talk about yourself,
man. My friend invited me to go out
today. I was like, nah, I can't be
bothered. I got friends, loads of
friends. Get them all the time. But, you
know, I want to just stay in, bro. Just
chill on my foot a bit more.
I can make money now doing a certain
thing now as well. So I'm out in two
months. I'm out. I'm out in two months, mate. [ __ ]
this. It's bad, bro. It's
bad. My [ __ ] my I've got two biggest
mistakes share in my life that I regret.
Yeah. One was being introduced to
gambling and through gambling I found
Timmy and then through Timmy
um I found this shitty community. It's
not even so much the gambling itself
that I regret because we had some good
times. Do you know what I'm saying? Yeah.
So yeah, bro. Um
um and then obviously women. So yeah,
it's the beard is it bro? It's the
beard. Even though I ain't got no [ __ ]
tattoos. Yeah, I ain't got no tattoos
though. Never have. Never. Don't think I
ever will. Don't have none
anywhere. Yeah, it's the beard. Is it? It's the
beard. But yeah, anyways, God rewards
bad behavior if you're a man or a woman.
Cuz I was just telling you about them Skype
buddies. They have a miss, they have a
kid. people that are bad get rewarded in
life, you know. So, and then the other
friend of mine on Skype who I've been
speaking to since uh since uh he
since he was we met when he was 14 and
we're the same age now. He lives in
Liverpool. He he immigrated to New
Zealand when he was seven and now he's
back in England and we always used to
speak. Um, and his life is pretty bad,
man. Like, he gets £300 a month. He's
depressed and [ __ ] And there's things
going on in his life. Like, I have life
easy, but obviously it's just the women
[ __ ] So, my life's like
moderate. You know, it's a good
life. New Y, barbecue, money. Yeah, it's
not a [ __ ] life, but you know,
it's Yeah. If you ain't got it in this
country, you ain't got it. And that's
why we got to go Thailand
next. But let's just put it as a whole
because the gambling came with this
community. So let's just call it
gambling and that's why I don't gamble
no more, you know? And I literally don't
do it. Like I know you've heard it all
before. Trust me, I don't gamble
anymore. So I want to be like, yeah, I
want to actually learn at 27 now. I
don't want to learn in my 30s. I don't
40s. So I want to I want to learn now. I
want to know when I was still
young. Oh yeah, sorry about that, bro.
So yeah, he does look a bit like me, but
I just don't have tattoos. I don't have a [ __ ] mullet. So
yeah, guess she wasn't really lying when
she said that was her type A,
Zippy. But yeah,
like Yeah, bro. It's just I can't be
bothered anymore, man.
I don't want to just chill, you
know, cuz that was winding me up, bro.
It was winding me up. And not because
people in a relationship. I'm happy for
people in relationships, bro. I'm not
I'm You know what I'm saying, bro?
Like, I've never been jealous of anyone,
but it's just I feel like people like
that shouldn't be allowed to
like be with people because they're just
scum lads. So, and I had the person's
[ __ ] body for [ __ ] sake. But you
understand what I mean. But
yeah, don't want to escalate stuff workers. Yeah.
Yeah. Some madness,
brother. Rolling up stuff. E
I think it's worse when they look like
you. To be fair, I think it's even when
you was in the dating game and you
struggle. I think it's worse
when cuz obviously I know people that's
got like black
fetishes. Um, and obviously people
someone's got a black fetish then it
doesn't seem as personal because
obviously they're into black men or
whatever it is they're into. But when
it's people that look like you, cuz some
people go for black people, some people
go for all different kinds of people,
but I think it seems more personal if
people look like you. You
understand? It's hard to explain it,
bro. It's it it's hard to explain what I
mean, but I I know what I mean. It's
even when people struggle in
dating like cuz we can just pull off and
say they go for like a black guy
or a Muslim guy, whatever. But when the
people look like you, you be like, "No,
something's going on here. Something's
not right." You know what I'm
saying? Something's seriously not right here. But yeah,
bro. I got a nice beard, bro.
Yay. Yeah, it's a madness,
bro. I still get them [ __ ] urges to
go America, bro. Go a dad. Don't get
Don't get me Don't get it wrong, bro.
Right. But I've got too much to lose.
Even though it doesn't sound like I do.
Trust me, I do. You don't need to have
kids. You don't need to be in a
relationship for you to have stuff to
lose. You know, that's why I thought
that time when when the police come, I
thought I was going to go [ __ ]
prison. I didn't know what the [ __ ] they
come for. You know what I'm saying? And
obviously, if you're just on [ __ ]
benefits and [ __ ] then you're not asked
about going prison or if it's something
that you can go back on to. But when you've got
responsibilities, even if it's not a kid
or a relationship, you've got stuff to
lose. So that's that's it,
bro. Yeah, that's I know what I'm
talking about, though. I know what I'm
talking about. Quite scary, you know.
Yeah. So, yeah, with this community,
I've been through a lot, man. you know,
loads of [ __ ] being arrested, loads
of [ __ ] madness. But like I said,
that came with gambling. So, if I didn't
gamble, I would have had a better life
and I would have been on here. So, but
at least I'm learning
now. It's not too late to learn in it.
So, 27, it's not too late, bro.
Yeah. I don't even get I don't even get
the urges to gamble anymore. Don't even get the
urges. Don't even get the
urges. Like I was saying, I've got it.
I've got money in an account where I can
actually deposit, but I just don't get the urges,
man. Even got my provisional here as
well. Got my
provisional cost £34. Usually ID now.
Get the [ __ ] in. Yeah, bro. So, that's
it. But yeah, I did feel like doing uh
where my little legs going to take me
today and just [ __ ] end up in
Blackpool. I was tempted, bro. I was
actually tempted to go
today overnight. Just plan it. [ __ ] off in it.
Yeah, I'm not doing that, bro. I got it for another
reason. But I will get my driving
license. But even when I get my driving license,
um I won't drive in London. I'll be
getting it for another reason. It's just
nice to have, but I I won't be driving
in London, you know? So, you know, it's
there's no point driving unless you got
[ __ ] kids or you live out of London.
There's no point. There's there's
literally just no
point. I know it sounds bummy and I know
it sounds like people should be driving, but
um you know it it doesn't make sense for
somebody in my position to drive. As
bummy as that sounds, like it would make
no sense me
driving. If you live like somewhere up
north like villages then yeah you know
insurance is cheap you kind of need a
car or if you lived in America like say
you lived in Florida you would need a
car because there's no transport. No I
wouldn't I wouldn't get on a moped bro.
The reason I wouldn't go on a moped I've
seen too many accidents
like I've se and and and the thing is
like say you want to take a trip to
Blackpool or Newcastle. I was thinking
of going Blackpool today, Grezy, but I
was like, I want to rest my foot a
little bit. Just didn't even plan it.
Just went to the train station and
thought, "Fuck it. I might just go in it
just for the
lows." Just cuz, you know, I owe you and
Steven Howard that video. And it is
summer, you know. So, yeah.
Um, but I need my my foot needs to rest
a bit more, bro. It was just quite a bad injury.
waking up at 4:00 in the morning, your
foot's [ __ ] problem. It's not
something that goes in a week, bro, or
10 days. It needs time, you
know? Such an annoying [ __ ]
injury. And it's the littlest thing on
your [ __ ] foot as well. It's [ __ ]
madness, but it's going now anyway. So,
yeah, cuz it's like, oh, I need to go to the shop.
my foot feels fine. So then you go to
the shop and then when you come back it
be it start pounding again because you
need to rest it. You need to rest it,
but at the same time, you need to at
least go to the shop, you know what? You
know, like, so that's why it takes cuz
you need to be on your feet. And I think
it was when I went to central London
that [ __ ] me as well, cuz I thought it
was 100% better, bro. I [ __ ] I was
staying at my mom's, bro. I woke up at 4
in the morning, bro, and it was rubbing
and I couldn't even walk. It was so
stiff. It was like it had been
frozen. Yeah. It's not good, bro. I got
that from running back from the police
station. I think I got that from running
back at the police station. See if my
phone was still
there. But yeah, greasy. Anyways,
man. Yeah. 3 weeks time. He took two L's
today. Anyways, bro, don't worry about
it. He took an L from me and an L from you. So,
yeah. I was saying griezy that when I
when Skype first come about back in
2012, I met loads of like American
people um you know someone like that
immigrated to New Zealand and the people
that were the [ __ ] on Skype, the
bullies, right? Yeah. Like even still to
this day, what they used to say to me
when I was a child. Yeah. I still mess
with them cuz obviously I'm an adult now
and they ain't got nothing to say to me.
Um they've got a good life. like they've
got a MS, they've got kid, they've got a
good job, you know, and they were
[ __ ] Proper proper [ __ ] And
then the one guy that wasn't, his life
is [ __ ] Like his life is absolutely
[ __ ] And my life is moderate. You know,
I've got money, I've got no
stress, got a good yard and that, but
obviously that's how you weigh up
people's life. If they've been bad, then
they have a good if they are bullied,
they have a good life. If they're a good
person, their life
is well, his life is [ __ ] bro. 300
pound a month. He is living [ __ ] and
he's oppressed because of women as well.
And he and he ain't got money to go out. So
yeah, like I said to you, bro, that's
why good people die young, you know?
That's how the saying goes.
So my life is good. It's just the same
about the experiences with women. My
life is good. Got money. Like I'm in a
good position. You know what I'm saying? Like
um my life is [ __ ] good, bro. Like
when it comes to money and [ __ ] [ __ ]
Like it's good. I had a good life for
[ __ ] 3 years.
So, you know,
like trust me, like a lot of people
would like to have my life as mad as it
sounds, but it still doesn't [ __ ]
explain the [ __ ] shitty
experiences. Yeah, exactly, bro. But
yeah, like I said, that did piss me off
because somebody like that should never
ever be allowed to be in a relationship with
someone cuz they're just a [ __ ] You
know what I'm saying?
Right. But and I also feel sorry for
anyone they get with as well because you
know the kind of person that they are
you know they're it's just their next
victim because something will go
horribly wrong. You know because it's
very rare that if someone's like it with
one person they're not like it with the
others. You know what I'm saying?
But just can't be bothered with him no more, bro.
So, so I've just painted them all in the
same brush and I just said at 27,
they're all the same. I'm done.
Simple. That's how what I truly
believe, you know. And when I was going
out every Saturday drinking, it was just
because I wanted something to look forward to
anyways. But yeah, you should have got a
hint when I stopped approaching people
sober. I was like, "Nah, [ __ ] this, bro.
There's there's got to be more to life
than this, you know.
So, didn't even once even [ __ ]
apologize. This woman in Scotland said,
"You know what?" She said, "One day
someone's going to do you in." I said,
"I very much doubt it, mate." Because
you know why, Greavvesy? I'm a crazy
cat. There's not many people that would
be able to do me in, brother.
Yeah, I eat steaks almost every day,
Greavvesy. So, no, I don't think so. But
I carried over I carried a barbecue
back, Grezy, from our goose, the other
day. I carried it all back by
myself. And I'm having a barbecue on Thursday. Everyone's
invited. So yeah, I'll put it on YouTube
on Thursday. [ __ ] it. I already done one
the other day, so you're going to see in
it. Man's like, "Oh, I thought you were
saving money and that." I am. You know,
I spent $150 with a barbecue and a meat,
but I'm not going out this week
drinking. So theoretically, I have saved
money. So instead of going out dealing
with these [ __ ] stupid women, I'm
having a barbecue.
Oh. So it's good, man. Isn't
it? You probably would have spent more
to be honest going out drinking because
I might have done two days. Who knows?
Yeah. So yeah, you go see Greavves in
about seven, eight years. That person
that was [ __ ] with you is going to
have a good
life. But in reality, she doesn't have a
good life cuz she was looking for a
roommate. So it it goes to show that
she's skin. It goes to show that her
life financially is at the pits. You
know what I'm saying? But
Yeah, but you know what I mean? In terms
of like finding someone, I
guess. Do you want me to come next week
or not? Like, it's it's up to you. I
don't I don't mind, you
know? I don't really care. Yeah.
So, if I go to Blackpool overnight,
Greavesy, how much do you think I'll
spend with the train tickets? I'm
thinking maybe 250, maybe 200,
250. I mean, I was saying, is it is it
worth going for one day? I went to
Newcastle for [ __ ] one day overnight. I mean,
yeah, you can.
Yeah, I always said me and Tim should go
Blackpool cuz it's in the West Midlands.
Yeah, probably about 250
maybe. Yeah, I can't believe I used to
do that Newcastle thing overnight. I
should have stayed for two nights in it.
Really? I remember Grezy I went to
Manchester. Remember that time? Yeah. I
went to Manchester to [ __ ] call out
that bomb. He didn't [ __ ] come out
and I come all the way back the same
day. I was [ __ ] bro. For like two
days. I was
[ __ ] Do you know what? I was actually
thinking of starting a series of this,
like going to Birmingham, which I've
done before, and then coming back the
same day, then doing Manchester, then
doing Newcastle, then doing Scotland.
Like, you just get in there for like 11
um like 11 like 11:00 a.m. Yeah. and
then coming back in the night and just
see how [ __ ] you'll be after like
every single one of
them. I think the Scotland one would do
you in. I think the Newcastle one would
do you in the [ __ ] Manchester
Manchester's long enough to be fair.
It's a good little series, isn't
it? I've done Birmingham and back before
and I've done it where I went to
Birmingham not slept. I've done it when
I was 19. I just come back the same day.
Yeah, I'm man's like, "Oh, you will try
again." Yeah, maybe in a 100
years. You got needs, bro. If I've got
needs, I'll just go to a [ __ ] escort.
I don't [ __ ] I don't have a high sex drive anymore. All
right. I think I think all the bad
experiences like killed my [ __ ] sex
drive. I actually think all the bad
experiences killed it. Yeah.
Um, some advice. Yeah, go to the doctors.
I'll be back later anyways.