[Music] [Laughter]
This will be my last live for the month
100%. Yeah, man. Like I said, after this
one, I'll just do a welfare check next
month and that's it. Just to see if it's the same
people. That's it,
man. Just a little welfare check. Like I
said, I'm just going to do a welfare
check every month after um
today. See if it's the same people on
YouTube. That's it. Yeah. It's like I'm
patrolling YouTube. Is it?
Yeah. After after this live. Definitely. Yeah. today. Boy. Yeah.
I see that scooper count on Monty's.
Yeah. Yeah, I saw that for a car in
ages. Apart from
today, I got dragged into this [ __ ]
again cuz that [ __ ] Arsenal wanker. Oh
yeah, he's a one for Yeah.
Told I wasn't going out today. [ __ ]
that. Okay, but you heavily disabled.
Bro, you can't even afford an iPad.
Leave it out, man. about the credits to
God. Bro, listen. Take this L. Yeah. I
came to your country two times. You ran
away and you can't even afford an
iPad. Let let that pro
process and take that L. Bye-bye. What
I've got to say to you. Bye. See you
later. See, people like All Night Mike,
they ain't got a life. They live for um
reactions on YouTube because they live
very lonely lives. No money, no
friends, no family. So [ __ ] sorry. They
come on here to get a reaction because
they need that reaction because their
lives are so [ __ ] that they have to come
on here and get and and and get
reactions from people. They live very
very sad lives. Very sad lives
indeed. That's their life in it. their
life will always be
YouTube. Well, we'll see that on the next month's
um welfare check that I do. Yeah.
So, oh nasty
blister. Have another nice curry today.
Oh, nice curry, mate.
being cooked for
me. Can't beat that, can you? [Music] One sec. That's Yeah, Sunday.
Yeah, I'm having a rush in this
tomorrow. I probably would get one every
month to be
fair. I got both my passports here.
Actually, my new one, my new one, and my old one. Yeah.
Look how many [ __ ] ibuprofen I went
through this foot.
Jeez, I went through so many.
Yeah. Yeah. So I said, "Oh, you want me
to come to Birmingham or not?" She's
like, "Oh, uh, yeah, you ditched me." I
said, "Nah, not really."
Yeah. See, even when I ditch people, I
still keep in contact with them. You
know what I'm saying? Cuz I'm not evil
like women. You see? So, um, even if I do
something wrong, I never ghost. Of all
of the things I've done wrong, I never
ghost because it's just cowardly. It's
the most cowardly thing you possibly
could could do.
Um, and people seem to think that, oh,
like it's better if you ghost. It isn't.
It isn't at all. It just causes more
[ __ ] problems. But yeah, I did this
person anyways, but I never ghosted cuz
I'm not a coward. Cuz you might do
something cowardly in the moment, but
then you you realize that you're not a
coward. So that's why you don't ghost.
You see? Going for [ __ ] losers,
lad. Peg. What? What the [ __ ] does that mean? Yeah.
What was that?
could reply though. It lad steaming
water on a cup of tea. Bro, I don't
really drink anymore. I got drunk for a
couple of weeks. How can I be steaming
on a cup of
tea? Nah, bro. I give up with women in
this country. Give up with all of it,
bro. I don't I don't want to be
associated with evil. [ __ ] that. Why
would I want to be associated to evil
people out all the same? That's a
[ __ ] madness, bro. [ __ ]
that. Nah, I'm good,
lad. Nah, bro.
Nah, my foot's still not 100%. And even
if it was, my friend actually invited
me. He said, "Meet me after work and
we'll go to the club." But nah, I'm I'm
at the age now where like, yeah, I'm
ready, bro. I'm ready to leave here, you
know? I'm ready to to leave and try my
luck in another country. That's not a
westernized country. Some people learn at 30,
32, maybe older. I learned at 27.
Well, I learned younger, but you know, I
I've only started now to like do something about
it, you know, book the flight.
So, when you get to a certain age,
everyone's different. The Antman was 31
when he left, so I'm 27. So, it's a good thing, is
it? Yeah, it's annoying. No, it's not
even a fake boyfriend. It's it's it's
not even that, bro. It's the
ghosting. It's the time wasting going on
the dates. Um the evil [ __ ] they do.
It's not even just the fake
boyfriends. That's just like a small
part of it, I'd say.
Yeah, to be
fair. Yeah, bro.
all the evil [ __ ] they do. They are they
are they are [ __ ] evil. Like at the
end of the day, bro, like I've I've done
some mad things, but I've never done what they've
done. Like ghosting, speaking for three
days, and ghosting. Like, I've never
ever and I've done some [ __ ] up
things, bro. Well, I said some [ __ ] up
things, but that is that's how you know,
bro. If that's their normal, they're not
[ __ ] normal. Simple.
And the dating game is [ __ ] just
rigged against men as well. So like even
evil even evil women can find someone.
Think about it, Slim. Yeah. You could be
a nor you know a decent person, a decent
looking person and you will struggle in
a dating scene. Yeah. An evil
woman can can get a man. So if you know
the game's like that, what's the point of
even what's the point of even trying,
bro? It doesn't even make sense.
you know, to me it doesn't make sense. So,
yeah, that's it,
bro. And if I was to try here, I'll just
try to use them for their body like they
use men. You know how they use men and
you know, that's what I'd probably do.
Just use them for their
body. Yeah. like they use men. So, you
just basically approach them to try and
just get into their knickers
really cuz there'd be no point in trying
anything else. You know what I'm
saying? So, yeah. And what they do,
Slim, they do do it on purpose. Like,
people will sit there and say, "Oh,
well, why would they waste their time
and your time?" Bro, they do do it on
purpose. They 100% do it on purpose.
Like meeting people then claiming they
don't feel the vibe doesn't make any
sense. Or speaking to somebody for three
days and then disappearing, which is a
recent one that happened. Bro, of course
they do it on
purpose. You think they don't have it in
their head that they're not meeting you?
Of course they do, bro. Of course they
do it on purpose. Let's cut the
[ __ ] man. Let's not sugar coat
it, you know? Like, of course they do it on purpose.
Yeah, man. What's they [ __ ]
do? Yeah. Antman's out today, but I'm
not. I can't be asked,
lad. Just like that stupid Morgan
[ __ ] you know? But we all know her
family's [ __ ] they're just grasses.
So, if he was to do anything, they'll
just grasp, bro. They'll just
grasp. You know what I'm
saying? Like I was saying [ __ ]
earlier, I would love to be somebody
showing her around the house a
potential like, you know what I'm
saying? You know what I'm saying, bro? I
would say, "What you saying now, you
little [ __ ] What the [ __ ] you saying
now?" I I would lock the door, bro. I'll
actually lock the door and see what a
[ __ ] has to say face to face and it
would be absolutely nothing with or
without anyone, bro. You know what I'm saying? So, yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, bro. It's a madness. Never
say anything anyone's face ever. Never will. Yeah.
You know if that [ __ ] come on you but
you know if that [ __ ] come on YouTube.
Yeah like what these people do on it. I
would I would have been there three
times now already. You know I've already
been there three times
now. But the [ __ ] knows just shut her
[ __ ] mouth. You
know just like
[ __ ] certain other person that Kenji
he soon shut his [ __ ] mouth as well. Yeah.
I can't stand him, bro. I can't stand him. Honestly, can't, you
know. Yes. It's [ __ ] up, bro. It's up.
Yeah. Yeah, they truly are evil,
lad. Yeah. I was actually getting dark
thoughts of [ __ ] going back there,
Greg. I'm not even joking, but I'm like
getting some mad. But I know like the
thing is, bro, if I go there, it's me or them.
You know what I'm saying? And and you're
risking your life. But that you do
realize that, is it? Like I realize
that like Well, it's not going to be
it's not going to be me. It's going to
them. But you know exactly what they're
going to do. And then the whole thing
just makes no sense because you know
people go that far to go on holiday. We
all know that someone's going to call the
police. You know what I'm saying,
brother? And that's that's not even a [ __ ] excuse. Like,
yeah. So, there's no point, bro. Even a
dad would call the police. Even a man
would call the [ __ ] police. You know what I'm
saying? They start [ __ ] um Grezy, but
they don't like the repercussions. [Laughter]
Yeah. Yeah. They blame me. like they me
when you react. And and the thing is
like bro like my if I'm actually to go
over there like I I want to say it in
front of her boyfriend and in front of
any man she thinks will stop me telling
her about herself to her
face because bro, no one is stopping me.
That's what I'm trying to say. No one is stopping me,
bro. Because it's just not going to
happen. Do you understand?
Yeah. It's a madness, isn't it?
Yeah. I don't know where their ego come
from, bro. Some of these [ __ ] I
don't know where their ego come from, honestly.
Yeah. And don't forget, Grey, the old
stalking card, eh? The old stalking card.
Yeah, that comes into it, doesn't it?
Yeah. I would love to be one of them
landlords [ __ ] she she'll be knocking
on the door. Yeah. Thinking that
somebody's showing her a room, showing
her an apartment or a potential roommate
and then you just come out of nowhere.
[ __ ] hell. That would be, bro, that
would be amazing. That would actually be
[ __ ] amazing, bro. It actually would.
Yeah. So that's why I don't deal with these [ __ ] anymore. So yeah,
yeah, yeah. Well, I tried to do it both
ways, Green, you don't forget. I tried
asking them to
apologize and then that never worked.
Then I asked them again. Then I asked
them again, "Can you just apologize?"
And then they thought they would sit
there and ignore me. So then I just
messaged their [ __ ] family. Simple.
That's it. Like [Laughter]
You know what I'm saying? Grezy, it's [ __ ] up, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. It make no sense for me, bro, to
ever date again, Grezy. It literally
makes no sense for me to like ever
approach a woman again. It literally makes no
sense cuz A, we know what they do. B,
the odds are stacked against you. See,
all of the [ __ ] you've got to go through
before it it makes no
sense. It literally It literally makes
no sense. Do you know how many people I
[ __ ] see when I'm out and about? I
don't approach none of
them. So, I think I'm I'm where I'm at,
bro. Like, honestly, I I think I am, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. The thing is, Gre, you know,
most people when they use the word
stalking, you can't pull Monty. I've had
more women than
you. You can't You can't pull Monty.
I've had more women than you
have. So, and that's that's actually a
fact. But I'm just not scared to say
what I think. I I can't stand them. I
honestly can't stand them,
bro. Like, I think I'll just live by myself forever,
Greasy. You know what I'm saying,
lad? Yeah. Good for him, bro. Yeah, good
for him. Do you want a
medal? Yeah, good for him, bro.
That's nice for him. Now I know what
I've tried. So I'm not comparing myself
to other people and that's why I've
given up. You
know that I was really getting thoughts,
brother of going there, you know, today,
yesterday, got the money, got the time.
Do you know what I'm saying, bro? And I
like, you know what I'm saying?
So, but we know they're just going to
run to [ __ ] old Bill. So, it's
pointless. So, there's two ways about
it. You know what I'm saying, bro? Yeah.
Doesn't matter how many women I've slept
with, but I've had more women than you, Monty.
Yeah. But it doesn't matter anyways,
bro. That's not what this conversation's
about. I happily never have anything to
do with them ever again, Greavvesy.
They're evil. They generally generally generally are
evil. Every single one I've met, no
good's come out of
it. You know, women, gambling, it all
brings you down. These things bring you
down, man. I'm just happy to sit here,
have a cup of tea, lie down, chill, have
a meal made for me. That's the life,
man. I don't need no [ __ ] evil [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah. Is he good for him, bro? Good for
him. Do you want a medal? Yeah.
like that, bro. So, yeah,
Grezy, that's how it is, bro. That's how
it is. And I've I could have been in
relationships if I wanted to. I I
basically was in a relationship. I
basically was in a relationship. And I
also could have been in
um maybe three more relationships if I
wanted to. Yeah, of course I could.
You're telling me out of all of them
people I met, right?
Um I couldn't have been Of course I
[ __ ] could have. And I basically wasn't
one. There's a few people. the one from Nottingham.
Um, so we don't have glasses on my
chat. Anyone that talks about glassing,
we don't have glasses on my chat. So, yeah.
Yeah, man. We don't have grasses on my
chat or anyone that talks about
grass, which one of the reasons I come
off this community to be honest, is
because of the
grass. Um, so
yeah. So yeah, bro.
Um, yeah. So there was a few people.
Anyways, so you're you're talking as if
like I could have
never [ __ ] been in a relationship
when I basically was in one and I still
didn't like it because I could just
sense the entitlement. So, but that's
not the point. The point is the
positives outweigh the sorry, the
negatives outweigh the positives.
after this uh live stream anyways until next
month. So yeah. So that's it. Greasy in
basically. So yeah, it makes no sense me
putting myself in the dating game cuz if
you see how much trouble they have
caused, it's pointless,
bro. I don't even really think about sex
anymore or anything really.
Nah. So I think the bad experiences
killed my sex drive with Grezy. I think
it killed my sex drive.
I think because of the [ __ ] you have to
go through with them to get anything. I
think it just it just killed my sex
drive. I don't really have much anymore, you
know? Maybe because I'm getting old, but
I I think it's the bad experiences that
killed it. I'm not even joking. I don't really
like I used to go escorts all the time
and that. Not anymore. Nah,
because I don't care anymore, bro.
Yeah, I'm talking about it now, but I really don't
care. No woman has ever been out of my
league. Stop self projecting. The only
people that say, "Yeah, women are out of
your league or um men that are
unattractive themselves." It's a common
thing Greavesy men do um to
um to make themselves feel better. I'll
give you an example. Do you remember Tom
Woods right? Do you remember Tom
Woods? I haven't kicked you. I can see
your comments. Do you remember Tom Woods
right now? Tom Woods was trying to say
Izzy is out of my league. Now, have you
seen Tom Woods? And have you seen Izzy?
Right. At the end of the day, yeah, I'm
better looking than Tom Woods and I'm
better looking than Izzy. So, the only
people that say that are men that are unattractive
themselves and they want to bring other
people down. That's the only people that
say, "Oh, this person's out your league
or this person's um
punching." when no, the only way you
would be going for somebody out of your
[ __ ] league, mate, is if you're going
for somebody like Taylor Swift or some
[ __ ] model. They're the only people
out of your league. Because lookswise,
there's no such thing as
leagues. Unless you're going for a
[ __ ] model with loads and loads and
loads of loads of money, then I'll be
like, "Okay, yep. They're out my league." You know? So, yeah.
Well, have you seen that [ __ ] Morgan?
She's [ __ ] stinking. She's like a
three out of 10. Yeah, but the reason I
said Taylor Swift is because she's a
[ __ ] billionaire. So, you get my
[ __ ] point. She's famous and she's a
billionaire. You know what I'm saying? [Music]
Greasy. Yeah, man. [Laughter]
Yeah. Plenty of other women that are not evil.
I've already been in a relationship,
Monty, and I've had chances of And also,
right? Um, and also I've had chances to
be in other relationships. So, try
again. Monty, listen. Monty, listen. I'm
going to say this now cuz I don't give a
[ __ ] because she's been talking [ __ ]
about me. Bro, Monty,
listen. The only reason Natalie got with
you, right, is because of your pip.
Yeah. And she wanted a bit of money off
of you. Let me let me tell you this,
Monty. Yeah. M Natalie, right, went with
Money Mike. Have you seen Money Mike?
Bro, please. Have you seen Money Mike?
She saw her
opportunity. Yeah. She saw your
opportunity, lad. She saw you as an
opportunity and she took it. She's She's
run through. Natalie Natalie G has run
She's actually run through and I don't
care cuz I I caught her talking [ __ ]
about me as well. And at the end of the
day, at the end of the day, yeah, like
this [ __ ] uh what's her face?
Um and what was I saying now? [ __ ] you
made me forget. So that's what it is. Um
and she's trying to say, "Oh, I can wear
what I want and I still can't get
women." Mate, I've had more women than
anyone she's been with. Have you Have
you seen my main YouTube channel? Just
because I'm not scared to say what I
think doesn't make mean someone has no
woman. I wasn't almost crying for nearly
three years, bro. I don't think about
her no more. I don't like her. Yeah. I
just find it it's [ __ ] up how the
world is and how you know the dating
game, bro. Crying about her for 3 years.
It wasn't even 3 years ago. Come on,
bro. Wasn't crying over that [ __ ] you
know, for 3 years.
Come on, man. I just don't like cowardly
little [ __ ] And I guess it just
wound me up that I never fully got [ __ ]
revenge. That's what I think it
was. Cuz there was no real way.
So basically, yeah, I think I have
basically Yeah, I think that's the word
for it cuz I'm not gay. I know people
that are gay. I I think I am asexual now.
Yeah, you know, Antman's out today
drinking. I'm not interested. I'm I'm
good by myself, bro. I'm having a nice
curry cooked for me
today. I think so many bad experiences,
it makes you lose your sex drive. Like,
I feel like a complete different person.
I don't care about it anymore, bro. Literally don't.
Yeah. I'm literally asexual. I actually
feel like I am, bro.
Yeah. Don't use escorts no more. Don't
watch porn. Nothing. Yeah.
You could be shagging tonight. Nah,
mate. I'd rather go to
Thailand. You know, as you get older,
you lose your sex drive. Yeah. And I
think with experience, I think because
you've had so many bad experiences, it
kills your sex drive. I think that's
what happened to me. Because I've had so
many bad experiences, it just it just
kills my sex drive.
and the the the ghost. It's not even
I've got a boyfriend cactus. It's not
even I've got a boyfriend. What pisses
me off? Yeah. Is the ghosting and the
wasting your time when they go on dates
with you. That's the thing that annoys
me. Yeah. Okay. The boyfriend thing gets
a bit annoying. But I mean, that's
always going to happen. But that's what
pisses me off, you know? So, that's why
I just gave up with the whole dating
thing. I'm good, bro. Like, [ __ ] I'm
I'm giving up. I'm done. Yeah.
I got Thailand booked anyways. Going to
start making more money soon. So, yeah, it's good,
man. You know what I was thinking? Who
would I rather [ __ ] [ __ ] Natalie G or
Kaye? Um, and I'm thinking, do you know
what? I think Kaye would be better at
sucking dick. You know, I was telling
someone about this. Kaye looks like
she's way better at sucking dick. So, I
think I'd go for Kaye, you know. Yeah,
of course. I called her out, bro. And
then they blocked me.
I think Katie be better at sucking
dick. Uh, so I choose I would choose Kay.
Yeah, but I wouldn't do that to Monty, man.
Nah, it's crazy. at my age, um I have
been in a relationship and I've had
chances to be in other
relationships. So, um and no, in this
day and age it's actually not crazy. And
I have been in a relationship pretty
much and I've had chances to be in other
relationships and in this day and age
it's very common. And if you actually
had a life, you would actually know that.
So, like you're probably older than me
and you've probably never had sex. So
you you need to look at your own life
before coming on to mine. I have been in
a relationship. I was seeing someone and
also I've had other chances to be in a
relationship as well. A good few
chances. Probably I'd say four, maybe
four. I would No, no, no. I would say a
good four or five. And that's not
counting every single date because some
dates they just didn't go anywhere.
Mate, you've got a wife and kids. Oh, do
you Terry? Yeah. Do you? That's Terry
that counters. Terry, listen. You don't
have a wife and kids. Shut up. It's
boring now. Like, come out with
something original. I can smell your
shitty train as a mile off, bro. Come on
your real account. Yeah. Stop pretending
that you're on probation. Stop
pretending that you know this family. I
can smell you a mile
off. I can smell your mile off, Terry.
Like chips frying. Stop it, bro. It's
annoying. You don't have no wife and
kids. Stop. Stop talking absolute [ __ ]
and you're banned. Bye. My longest
relationship was 3 weeks. How did you
How did you work that one out? 3
weeks. Yeah, it's the real Monty.
Yeah, it is. Is it? It's not. Let me see. Hold
on. It was
Do you know what is that the real Kaye? Hold
on. Do you
know? Yeah, it is. Is
it? Is that the real
KD? Yeah, I'm good, man. I'm just chilling. One
sec. I think me and Kaye would be a good couple, you
know, because you know, like, do you
know how this works? Sometimes you can
be friends with somebody that's with
somebody, but actually you would be
better with the
person. I've noticed that you'd actually
be better with
them. One second. Hold on. I'm trying to find
She looks so happy. Good for her, man.
No one cares. You're not going to w me
up. Oh [ __ ] Hold
on. That is a real Monty. Listen.
Yeah. This Mont Monty thinks and you
know what the only reason I'm talking
[ __ ] about Natalie is because I've
caught her talking [ __ ] about me because
I've caught her talking [ __ ] about me
about I've had no women. Natalie,
listen. I've had more [ __ ] women than
any guy that you've been with. Yeah.
Just because I'm not scared to say what I [ __ ]
think. And you know what? Yeah. Do you
know what I was Bro, listen. Do you know
what I was going to do as well? When I come to
Birmingham next week, I'm going to meet
this person. I would love for you to
smash my head on that table. I would
love for you to try and smash my head on
that table like you did money. Please
try it. Like, bro, it would never
happen. That it would never
happen. Like, trust me, it will never
happen. Yeah, I will see you later, bro.
That's fine. I've caught her talking
[ __ ] about me anyways, so I don't care.
I've caught her talking [ __ ] about me.
Like, and sorry, Monty's just involved.
Like, honestly, yeah, I've c I've
actually caught her talking [ __ ] about
me. And Morgan looks happy with her new
fella. No one
cares. I've already had the bitch's
body. That doesn't wind me
up. If I ever find out who that guy is,
I'm not going to go searching for him.
But if I find out who he is, I'm I'm
I'll ruin that
relationship. Simple. I will ruin
it. No, I will just All I've got to do
is show messages what the cunt's done.
And it's just cuz I I'm the one that
ruined the last one.
Yeah. Yeah, man. I like to protect um
innocent people from evil. You know what I'm saying?
Why do I want to ruin it? Because I
don't like her. She's an evil [ __ ] Bro,
listen. I don't mind people in
relationships. I I like people that are
in relationships, people that are happy,
people getting married. I support
everyone. You know what I'm saying, bro?
Um, you know what I'm saying? I I'm
happy for people, but people like her
should never ever ever be with someone ever again.
And it's not just cuz she's a three out
of 10. It's cuz of how she is. That's
the thing. You know what I mean? But
like anyone else I'm happy for, you
know? And that's it, bro. It's not
jealousy. I guarantee you, bro. I'm a
I'm pretty much asexual now. So, I have
nothing to be jealous of. You know,
people don't know the ins and outs of my
life. Trust me. You know, cuz obviously
that's what it seems like, but it's not.
You know what I'm
saying? You know what I mean? She would
never say anything to anyone's face. I
just want to talk that ego out of her.
Like, just tell her about
herself and and and shut her ego down
once and for all. Anyways,
uh where where do you live now,
Kaye? Nah, I'm not doing that [ __ ] Me,
me, and me and Kaye are enemies. Me and Kaye actually
met. Nah, I don't know who he is, bro. I
is. You didn't put his [ __ ] name
up. But yeah, I I I I prefer you to
Natalie. Definitely prefer you to
Natalie. Don't forget Natalie's run
through. You know, you've been with the
same guy for [ __ ] ages. So, yeah. [Music]
Yeah, man. But yeah, it's how it is,
eh? But yeah, and she and she's asking
me if I'm po. She needs a
roommate. Like, I don't need a [ __ ]
roommate. I'm not a [ __ ] skint.
Morgan is [ __ ] skint, man. No abroad
this year, eh?
No abroad this [ __ ] year.
Yeah. Yeah. She had loads of tattoos on her
arms. She had loads of tattoos on her
arms. She looks exactly the
same. You see? I don't have no tattoos.
Nah. Nah. I don't think we could, Shag.
I probably wouldn't even be able to get
it up. I'm asexual now, so
nah. Bang bang bang bang
bang. Rest the calls. What a weirdo,
man. Anyways, Kayie, where do you live
now? And he's shouting [ __ ] He never
always liked that. That's [ __ ] He
never always used to like that.
That's [ __ ] He never, man. He
[ __ ] well never
because he just never. He just never.
But I don't care. N I've caught N
talking [ __ ] about me, so I don't
care. Oh, Lester, you're not too far
then. You're only in the Midlands. East
Midlands. Yeah, I used to pass Lester
when I used to go Nottingham.
Why don't we meet up in Nottingham and
have a good old piss up? That'll get the
people mad. And you won't need to spend
penny, you know. You won't need to spend
a penny, mate. We got the money coming, eh?
Yeah. I will never get a
tattoo. Yeah, we can go to Nottingham
for a good old piss
up. Yeah, you don't need to worry about
the money, man. And I don't get I don't
get paid every month.
No, I don't have no tattoos, man. Never have, never
will. The guy she's with has got
tattoos. Looks a bit like me, but I
don't. Obviously, I don't have
tattoos, which is kind of rare nowadays.
Most people do have tattoos in it. But
yeah, I'll meet you in Nottingham if you want.
Yeah, I'll meet you in
Nottingham. Go for We can go for some uh
I know a place there, a um seash bar. We
can go for
seash for a good old piss up, man.
Yeah, you can have my number if you
want. My WhatsApp number. Everyone's got
my WhatsApp number. my WhatsApp number.
My other number is different.
So, yeah, everyone knows my WhatsApp
number, but they're not going to message
me on WhatsApp because then it will show
their number. Then they're [ __ ] It's all right.
Yeah. Yeah. We can go um go Nottingham if you
want. Or you can come to London. I show
London. Um there's lots to do here.
You'll like it here, Kaye. You'll never
have to grow [Laughter]
up. That's a Stephen King it [ __ ] quote.
Yeah. Well, it doesn't matter what the
sleeping arrangements will
be, you know. We're not going to get
into that here.
Yeah. No, I actually was I actually was
having this conversation on the phone
with somebody earlier. I'm not going to
tell you who it is. And we said I said,
"Who would you rather get with, Natalie
or Kaye?" And they asked me and I I said
I said I said Kaye. I would actually
rather I would actually rather choose
you. You know, I feel like you've got a lovehate relationship, you
know. I actually would choose you to be
honest. I actually would The thing is
with the thing is with um Natalie Yeah.
is she's she's got no personality. Like
I used to speak to her on the phone like
all the time when I was younger. like 20
22 23. No, I was I weren't 23. I think I
was 21 22. And I always found like the
age thing just a bit weird. And she has
like no personality. Like she has no
personality. Like she's boring, man. Like proper
boring. Yeah. You're I think you're two
months older than me. But she's got no personality.
Like literally no personality.
Yeah. No man, I think I I think I think that is
worse. Think about it. N G went with
[ __ ] money, bro. So
yeah. Yeah, I would if you wanted to.
Yeah, if you wanted
to. [ __ ] it. I've got nothing to
lose. [ __ ] it if you want.
Yeah, I [ __ ] would, man.
I'm not going to get into stuff on here,
but you know, people record this [ __ ] But
yeah, if you stop blaming me for why for
what happened to your [ __ ] kids cuz it wasn't
me. Nah, I don't think Kale Haley's not
a slag. I don't think Haley's a slag.
Nah, she's not a slag, man. I don't think she
is. Not at all.
She's better than Natalie as well. She's
Natalie. You can't get rid of Rice. Look
at Rice's face, Katie. [ __ ] hell.
Look at Look No, I I'm not even just
saying that. I don't actually think
she's she's not a slag cuz she was with
Monty for you know what I'm saying? And
she didn't cheat on Monty. So, I don't
think she's a slag, bro.
But that needs to run you
through cuz cuz if if if H was a slag.
Yeah. See with different people on
YouTube. Why? Why am I doing
blood? That's quite concerning now.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. I mean, if you want
you come to London or come to
London, we can go for a nice steak. Like
I said, you'll never have to grow
up. You'll never have to grow up. You'll
like it down here, Haley. You'll never
have to grow up. [Music]
Yeah, I think she's like she's dirty,
Kaye. As in like if she's with somebody,
she'll do dirty stuff with them, but not like a
slag. Nah, I don't think she'll just get
with anyone, bro. Nah, I don't think
so. Listen, I tell you what, Kayie, I'm
having a barbecue on Thursday. You're
more than welcome to come. My sister's
coming. Some of my friends are coming.
You're more than welcome to
come. You're more than welcome to come
if you want. You know, all the expenses paid
for. You're more than welcome to come.
Brand new barbecue. We're having one on
Thursday. You're more than welcome to
come down if you
want. The more the
marrier. Yeah, I'm hosting it. We can have some
coronas, you know, and everything like Yeah.
Yeah. What would you do if I um wrote
you a poem, Kaye?
H would you like it if I wrote you a
little poem? [ __ ] off, bro. I'm never
writing on a poem ever
again. You must be [ __ ]
mad. But maybe this is a good thing. You
know, me and you would suit each other
like probably Monty Man and Natalie suit
each other. Sometimes when you actually
reverse it, couples work out
better. It it it's true. I'm not even
saying that to try and annoy anyone. It does
happen. It does happen. It really really
Some people just work better with with
with other people. I'm not even I'm not joking.
So yeah, who would you say is Miles better than
Kaye? Yeah, but it's not about um what
they look like. It's the same thing with
that Morgan. What pissed me off is not
because that she's a three out of 10.
It's who the [ __ ] does she [ __ ] think
she is. She thinks she's
[ __ ] She thinks he's who I hate. I
don't like her as a person. Doesn't
matter what people look like, bro. [ __ ]
hell. As long as they're
um they're nice, you know.
So, you know what I'm saying?
I went on a date with a B one from
Birmingham. She was a three out of 10.
That's not why I ditched her. I ditched
her cuz she was trying to [ __ ] use me,
bro. Who have I been
with? Who have I been with that's better
than her? Give me some examples.
Yeah. So, yeah. Kayie, are we going to
arrange this meet up? I can
either come there or you can come
here. I got a rail car
anyways. Just come to
London. Maybe I'll just come on
Nottingham or something. It's only two
stops. We should
be a couple of years.
Go on, left it. Who have I shown that's
better than Kaye? Come
on. That [ __ ] Morgan's covered in
tattoos. He's coming in [ __ ] tattoos, man.
Yeah. Well, yeah. You're better than that anyways. Definitely.
Defo. But one thing, Kayie,
yeah, I'm not going down on you. It's
happening. I don't do that
[ __ ] It's frowned upon on London in
London. So yeah, I don't know who used
to do that, but yeah. Monty goes down on
Natalie. [ __ ] hell.
[ __ ] He goes down on that. [ __ ] hell. [ __ ]
that. [ __ ] that,
bro. That is [ __ ]
stinking. What's your boy What's your
body count, Ka? My body count is five,
excluding um things we won't get into.
Mine's four or five, which I think's normal.
You know, for my age. What's
yours? Organ's boyfriend don't know
about her body count.
Eh, body count means how many people
have you slept with? If you don't know.
Yeah. One second.
body count means how many people have you slept with? Uh
I'll text you my number on your video as
well in case you do want to come to
London. Well, I Well, I just told you
how many people I did. Five.
Yeah. Well, I've slept with five. As
long as you've not slept with [ __ ] 25
[ __ ] people, you're
good. Yeah. Don't tell me you slept with 25
people. [ __ ] hell. Someone that slept
with 25 people just goes to show you that
like it's other people other than
boyfriends. No way. That [ __ ] Morgan
[ __ ] had 25 [ __ ] boyfriends and she slept with
25. I was the 25th.
24 people. So you see with 24 people,
that's [ __ ] insane,
bro. Even though I've done more than
that technically with escorts, but that's
different. You know what I
mean? That's Yeah.
Uh yeah, see this? Yeah. Uh
24. So um Kaye, do do you want to meet
then? Do you want to meet up and go in
piss? Go on the piss.
Haley, we can go under
piss. What do you think of that? [Laughter] One
second. It's all over. No, no, you can't
say I let you know. We just You just
need to come to London on Thursday.
That's all you got to do.
Yeah, I think he's going to be alive now. One sec. Yeah,
bro. Yeah, [ __ ] n [ __ ] snake.
Anyways, I said most of these people
here were [ __ ] snakes in
it. Yeah, most these people in here are
snakes. That's the thing, you
know. That's the thing, man. Let's see. Yeah.
Discord. How How's that going to work? [Music]
Yeah. They won't jump me, mate, cuz I'll
get beat up. So they won't [ __ ] They
won't jump me. No
way. Oh, there's so many self projectors
on this channel.
But after this live stream anyways, I'm
[ __ ] Oh my god. How could these
people call me skint when I've shown
money time and time and time and time
again? These these people must have me
confused with themselves. Left tip. Like
they literally must have me confused with
themselves. I'm I'm actually thinking they
must Yeah. Stop talking about yourself.
Yeah. Stop talking about yourself, man. What's
it? Yeah. What the [ __ ]
Yeah. Who the [ __ ] is
that? Listen, Kayie. Yeah, if that is
you. What happened? Just the same old
[ __ ] He pretends to call people out and
then [ __ ] Yeah.
Well, I'm coming off of YouTube after
this live stream for a little bit.
So, yeah, you can contact me off here if
you want to meet up. If you don't, you
don't. And if you do, you do. That's up
to you in it. But I won't I won't be on
here for a little while. I'm waiting for
some more people to join so I can tell
them what happened. That's why I went
live in the evening. But yeah, I'm done
for a little bit.
So yeah, Kaye, if you want some
uh self projectors get blocked. Um so
yeah, if you want
um if you want to come to the barbecue,
Kaye, you're more than welcome to come next Thursday, you know.
Yeah, but I'm be on it for a bit.
Uh my holiday is not for um two weeks,
sorry, two months. So
yeah, no, it is her account. It is it
is one second. Hold on.
One second. Hold
up. One second. Yeah. Hold up.
Okay. So, I typed to my um I I typed to my uh
WhatsApp. So, um yeah, if you want to
come to the barbecue, you can come. We put on
YouTube. Yeah, I typed it. So, you got
my number anyways if you want to come.
cuz after this live stream I won't be on here,
man. For a little
bit. Yeah. I'm not trying to make um
people [ __ ] jealous. I'm not even
trying to make people jealous, man. But
there's a barbecue next week. You can
come next Thursday. Some people coming.
So, give you the address as well, Kylie, if you want. Yeah.
Yeah, we have some nice
t-bones. So, there you go. You got me.
You got my
thing. Did you get it? Yeah, I put my
number on uh I commented my number on your um
thing. So, it's there if you if you want to message
me. These people won't mess cuz it's
only my WhatsApp number. So they're not
going to obviously message me on
WhatsApp cuz they they call off on loan. So
yeah. Ah, he goes on your channel,
mate. Deleting it,
I Yeah, we can have a we can have a t-bone steak.
Yeah, sorry about
that. Would I? No, we're just
meeting. We'll just go on a date. Me and
Katie just going on a
date. Don't lie, Katie. Yeah. Do you
remember when you saw that steak um
video where I took that American for the
steak? Do you remember? Don't lie. I bet
you wish that was you eating that. I bet
you've never been took for an ice steak
before, have you, Kaye? An ice
steak. But if you ghost me after, I'm
going to come and beat you up.
Yep. Not joking.
If you ghost me, I'll come
there. Yeah. And I'll poke your ears.
I'm not even
joking. Yeah. Do you not do you not
remember that ribeye video, Katie? Maybe
you were on YouTube at that point. It
was a [ __ ] 90 steak,
mate. It was a 90 steak, expensive. Yeah.
Yeah, it was good, man.
Yeah. Yeah. Katie, I'm not a [ __ ]
though. Yeah, I might have been a bit
quiet, but I'm not a [ __ ]
[ __ ] Trust me.
Yeah. I just like didn't really know
what to say, bro, but I'm not a [ __ ]
you know? Trust me.
know. But yeah, we can have some t-bone steak.
Kaye have some t-bone
steak. My own Got my own gaff. New
washing machine. New fridge.
Bailey. Yeah, I helped you with a
suitcase and you told me to come off of YouTube.
Ah, it was love at first sight, was it,
Kaye? Love at first
sight. Yeah. I wish I took you for that
steak now. Not that [ __ ] stupid American. [ __ ]
hell. [ __ ] me,
man. You going to take my virginity?
Well, that'd be a hard thing because I'm
not a virgin. More self projection.
Yeah. No, me and Katie are going to be a couple,
Monty. We're going to be a
couple. Yeah. Do you know Do you know
what put me off Natalie as well? is the
fact that I know I'd be like
[ __ ] like like money might slop
that's money might sloppy
seconds. That's kind of gross,
bro. I'm not going to lie.
Yeah, you Oh
god, you're mad, Monty. You're [ __ ] mad.
Yeah. Nah, I think Katie is better than Natalie.
Defo. I like Katie cuz she's got lighter
hair. She's got lighter hair. Yeah.
Yeah. N Kby, you're better. Well, let me
let me see again.
Nah, I think Kay is definitely better.
Nah, let me see. Haley, if you pick if
you leave your hair down. Yeah. And not
tie it up. You leave your hair down.
You're you're you're you're better than
that. Off me.
You know, 100 fucking%.
Yeah, if you leave your hair down, you definitely definitely
are. Yeah. I don't know how people say
N. I don't think N is better. I'm not
even just saying that, bro.
Nah, these people are [ __ ] tripping,
man. I'm telling
you. Yeah, I'll put the link.
Yeah. And your Pharaoh, which looks
better. So, yeah.
No, I'm not trolling, bro. I'm being
serious. I'm actually being serious. [ __ ]
hell. Well, I don't care. No, I just
said to uh to
um Katie that if she wants to come to
the barbecue, she's more than
welcome. That's it. You know, if she
wants to come, if she can't, if she
doesn't, she doesn't know. You know,
that's what it is.
I would get with Natalie if I had like [ __ ] 10 Guinnesses
maybe. Well, have you seen uh USA Izzy's
new fella, Mr. B? Oh, [ __ ] hell, man.
She just gets worse and worse and worse
with all them [ __ ] tattoos. You funny
bastard. You PJ. You can't take jokes. You lad.
You funny bastard. What you doing?
What do you mean? You [ __ ] can't. You
can't get laid off Kayie now, can you?
Well, I invited her to the barbecue.
Not as nice yet.
Yeah, that's all I I just said. If you
want to come to the barbecue, you can
come. It's next Thursday.
No, I'm all right, PJ. Stick to your men. Yeah. [Laughter]
What do you mean?
Just stick to your men, lad. Just stick
to your men. You still argue with Timmy.
Timmy's never a no. He's a no show. I'm
not even I don't talk about these clowns anymore.
Not even a [ __ ] man. The man in the chat here.
You know, you know I'm on about the man
in chat. PJ. No.
No. Kay. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay. Man. Of course she's a man.
PJ. She's got a bigger dick than you, mate.
But how does she have a child then?
Like come out of her ass, lad. Come out
ass. Don't be silly, man.
No. What you doing, PG? I thought you
weren't coming live anymore. You were
saying, huh? I thought I thought you
weren't coming live anymore. After this,
I'm not going live. No, buddy. I said to
you, well, no, actually, I didn't say it
to you. I'm going to come live every
month to see if it's the same people.
That's all I'm going to do. Every month?
What you said? Like, get what? A couple
of days ago, you're going live and
you're done with it. You can't be ask
anymore. I'm going to do a welfare check
every month. Oh, welfare check. Welfare
checks are like once a week, PJ.
I want to see if it's the same people.
Yeah. So, so you might as well do room
checks. Room checks are pil once a week.
Okay. I'll do it once a week. I will do
it. I will do it every Saturday. Yeah.
Good day. Every Saturday. Every
Saturday. Room check. Yeah. I get it.
They they they sit here and they call me
skin, but they're the ones that start on
YouTube every day.
So, every every Saturday you're going to
do a room check. Yeah.
Yeah, man. But listen to me. Listen to
me. Right. Listen to me. Yeah. There's
been times I've come off of YouTube for
a few weeks. Yeah. These people can't
take one day off of it. So, how can I be
the skin one? [ __ ] no.
Are they not on YouTube every day? They
are in it. You see it?
From the time they wake from the time
they go to bed. Even on a hot summer's
day. Even when it's hot outside. Even
Even on a [ __ ] winter day.
I I went on your live earlier. You was
arguing with someone.
PJ, what's this community about?
[ __ ] no. It's for the spastics, isn't
it? Yeah, it is. You got it completely. Yeah, man.
So, so how many women have you been laid anyway, PJ?
When you were single? Yeah. Listen, I've
never really been single. When I met you
on PlayStation, yeah. Do you remember
when you were single? Did you used to
get jealous of people in relationships?
No, not really. No. Why? Yeah. But you
you used to think like, oh, you wish it
was you and it No, definitely not. PJ.
Yeah, but you were single then. This was
before you've met I met you before you met Katie.
PJ I was PJ I was going out in
relationship before I was even on
PlayStation 3. I come out of I went I
went on PlayStation 3 because I just
come out of a badass relationship and I
thought thought [ __ ] it I can't be asked with women
normal. So I went by so I went on
PlayStation 3 for a while just [ __ ]
around like I did [ __ ] around. Then I met
Kay on there. Look at this [ __ ] Someone
look at look at look at this [ __ ]
still women are all [ __ ] up. Haley
definitely going to take PJ's virginity.
Yeah, that's but I'm not a virgin though. Monty,
I've only seen you have a blow to your
PJ. That doesn't count.
You want you want me to send you a video
of me [ __ ] No, I'm all right. Am I
all right? You can keep that video. Keep
it. Keep it.
Yeah. I'm all right. See, I remember
when I sent you that video. It's funny,
isn't it? No, not really. No. You got
pissed off, huh?
Oh, why would you get You got a small
one, ain't you, PJ? No, you have.
I remember when you used to walk with a limp.
I still do. That's my neck catching my leg. No, seriously.
No, I never walk with a limp. Do you
even know what that means?
Yeah, ped leg.
I was on a date a couple weeks ago and I
was walking with a limp cuz I injured my
foot in it.
Yeah, I injured my leg a couple of week.
She said she said you're walking like a [ __ ] Well, that
is No, no, it was someone else. It was
someone from Birmingham. I was walking
on a limb.
I was like the odd one out, mate.
You obviously one out, pee. Yeah.
Yeah. Obviously, the one out.
Yeah. So, I was I I don't know, man. I
think why did you ask a woman anywhere
about sucking dickly?
Oh no no no definitely not. Definitely
not. You sure? Yeah. I've been
there. I've been there with both. Uhhuh.
What? I'm not saying anything anymore. P
Yeah. Yeah. I'm 100% Pier.
Yeah, but she done good [ __ ] in it.
PG. I'm not talking about my sex life
with any of my ex. It's all I'm not
bringing any of them up. Okay. For
[ __ ] sake, PJ. Okay. What is it with
you, man? What is it with everyone? Are
you sexual frustrated or something? No.
No. How? No. I'm just curious. I'm
sexually frustrated, man. You're just
curious who's the better one who And I'm
not myself. I'm I'm the better blower.
funny. You're crazy, man. I'm a better blower. Huh?
I'm the better blower. Me? Yeah, but why
do you want
Why do you must been getting bump PJ,
man? Cuz he keeps talking about
limps. You walk with a limp. Who's this? Bonjour.
Who's this money?
But you have to admit, yeah, we did used
to have some good laughs from
PlayStation and it Yeah, but I thought
you off PJ.
Yeah, before that it was funny, don't
it? No, then you got me back in your
[ __ ] alive and [ __ ] my life up, you
I didn't [ __ ] your life up. [ __ ] off.
You're You even said No, you did [ __ ] my
life. You should have got me in this community though.
You should have even got me in it. What?
This weird community. Yeah, you should
have even got me in it, lad.
[ __ ] hell, bro. [ __ ] hell, man.
Well, my life was already [ __ ] up, so
I thank you for that either way for save my ass.
[ __ ] gra. You know, you saved my life, PJ.
Literally. Okay. My eyes chopped the
term for another woman, a better woman.
Standing forever now.
I can't say that. Can I say, "Oh, yeah.
Me and Natalie going to be staying
together forever." You don't know if
it's going to work. You don't know what
the pro stay on YouTube forever. Oh
[ __ ] No. No. I'm a [ __ ] I can't be
asked with these clowns
anymore. They repeaters, man. They ain't
got nothing new. They're [ __ ] dead,
boring bastards. They are. They are.
[ __ ] hell. What is it? You got Rice and [ __ ]
um who is
it? Rice and Fell going on at each other
for about a year or so saying they're
going to meet each other. They're going
to go and meet each other. Oh yeah. Meet
me halfway. They both say meet me
halfway. It's I [ __ ] hell. I might as
well put that song on. Meet me
halfway. Meet me
halfway right at the bottom when I'm
waiting for you. For you. That's what
it's like every [ __ ] day. Meet me
halfway. F. You only get paid.
Nothing happens. £300 he gets paid.
Yeah. So I do sent this. Yeah. If Fell
pays for a ticket. Yeah. Let's get real.
Yeah. I already did the sums up before
Fell even put the ticket up. How much
the ticket cost? Yeah. For him to get halfway.
All together. He's got £300.
Yeah. All together. He gets his ticket.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. His ticket is at least
going to cost him. That's [ __ ] That's
[ __ ] for the month, isn't it?
completely. Right. So that that that's
going to last him. So if he gets his
ticket halfway to Rice, bear in mind
that's halfway up country from where
Philly is. Yeah. Bear in mind. So that's
going to cost around about 100 to to 200
quid just for his train ticket. That's probably
for a return back included. 200 quid.
I'm just going to say 200 on the spot either way.
Yeah, that's just halfway through both
feet. 200 quid each.
Halfway. It's going to cost them
probably about 50 quid, probably 60 quid
to meet me halfway.
Yeah. But he tells me to go to E's
house when he's willingly to go and meet
him halfway for 200 quid when he can
save himself a lot more money by meeting
me for 60 quid. [Laughter]
Oh, he tells me to go to his house.
I I couldn't I'm not going to go to no
one's house. Money, I couldn't live off
£300 a month. A
man knows how much I come out with.
Yeah, I I'm not asking, but I'm saying I
couldn't live off £300 a month. Yeah.
Can you not That's what you come out
with. I spent one the other day. I spent
£150 in one day.
Yeah, I I spend I I spend more than that
in one day, PJ. Yeah, that's what I'm
saying. I can't I can't live 300,000 a
month. That's [ __ ] [ __ ] No, I can't either.
Me, Monty, I get about 3k a month. No. Yeah.
No, you don't. I
do. 100% I do.
No, it's cuz you gamble as well. [ __ ]
off. You get 3k a month. Why do you flip
out every day? You lose 100 quid at the
[ __ ] gambling place. You It's
annoying losing. It doesn't matter. It's
annoying. [ __ ] off. Money. I do get
free. The straight on disabilities only
up to 90 quid.
Either way, sorry. I make I make money other ways.
Listen, I make money other ways. Yeah. I
won't be saying [ __ ] on YouTube, you
[ __ ] Yeah, I know. I'm just I'm
leaving it at that money. I'm just
leaving it at that in it. That's it.
Yeah, but you've already admitted it, so
you put yourself up anyways. Yeah, I
make money other ways, man. Legal ways.
Fraud ways. No. Yeah. No, that ain't
come out my mouth.
Like, course it come out your mouth
fraud ways. It didn't come out of my mouth, mate.
So what what do you say something? Yeah.
PJ, shall we talk about? Yeah. Shall we
talk about one second please? Man, if if
there wasn't such grasses on this
community, I I would tell you and and it
is a legit way, but there's too many
grasses on here. So I'm not I'm not
saying nothing, bro. PJ, do do you know to
fraud like you're doing now? Why are you
frauding the system for PJ? Not me, mate. No.
Monty, do you know that time they tried
to stop my benefits? Yeah. They they
showed they wanted a bank statement and
I showed them the bank statement. They
said it was okay. Not me, mate. I'm not
fraud or nothing. Yeah, mate. I bet a
cash in hand is not going to get anyone.
Is it PGS?
No, I don't do fool, mate. Not me. I'm
legit. N a lot of cash in hand. A lot of
cash in hand. It's a little chicken
under the water in a PG. All legit. It's
all the chicken underwater. What a
cashing hand. Yeah. Yeah,
man. One second.
PJ, can I when me and you meet me, can I slap
you? No, you can slap my dick. Why?
No, if I if I me, can I slap you? Nah,
why not? You can slap my dick if you
want. No, I'm all right. I want to slap
you across the face though, PJ. You know
what? You know what? I reckon if you
reck you'd have a sword fight. I'm all
right, PJ. You and
[ __ ] we sit now. You and Shaq
Clariper had a sword fight, you
[ __ ] And Sean Long. You and CJ Hook
had a sword fight.
Nah, you were sat in the lobby with CJ.
Do you think you'll ever um forget um a
TJ Hooker? Nah. Nah, no. You know what?
He gives me nightmares. PJ, I had a
nightmare about him last night. Yeah, he
gives me nightmares, mate. I swear till this day.
Yeah, I can't sleep at night time
because of him. No,
no, no. That will look
[ __ ] I don't I don't know. PG. So
what how much do you get a month? 1,800.
How much I get a month? I told you how
much I get.
All what I can say is that I'm on I rate
I just say that I'm on I rate
disability and I'm on um normal amount of [ __ ] um finger money.
That's all what I'm saying.
Natalie knows what I've come out
with. One more person also knows what I
come out with. probably she doesn't know
what I come out with now, but I come out
with a lot more now. A lot more. Yeah.
So, I'm I'm all
right. Say it's about at least
about almost about a grand. Say about
like a grand probably two grand to two
grand most probably. Think so. About
that. No. No. Good.
No. Do I [ __ ] sell drugs? You used to
like years like back in the PlayStation
days. Yeah. Ages ago. Yeah. I used to go
off. You used to sell crack in it. No,
I've never s crack PG.
I'm joking. I'm joking. I'm joking. You
just sold a bit of weed in it. Yeah.
No, that's all right, man. [Laughter]
You you that's what you smell, ain't it?
Croxy knickers in it. PJ J, have you
ever done cocaine?
No, she's done cracker.
PJ Money, do you remember when we used
to watch the Inet Between Us together?
Never watched in Between us with you,
PJ. She must be on about someone else.
No. Oh, do you remember when the movie
come out in 2014? The the the the new
movie um in Between this movie 2.
Remember we watched it? PJ, can you tell
her to [ __ ] off? Yeah. Why?
Cuz she's stalking, man. How?
She's stalking like she's stalking. How?
She's just a stalker, mate.
Yeah. But do you remember when we
watched it between us? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Me neighbor PJ. You don't like human
ember lad. She's told you plenty of
times. It's all his ear because he's a
stalking lad. You know that. But maybe
me and her can make love money.
Do you know what PJ? That would be [ __ ] awesome.
And it just shows that I'm not asked. Do
you know what I mean? I don't want you
to be I don't want you to be. I'm not
asked. That's the thing. No, I No,
Monty. I I know that you're not like
jealous of any. The only time you was
jealous was like in the PlayStation
days. We weren't even jealous about Clen,
you know, when we fell. Like I said,
like I said, listen. Listen, PJ, do you
know [ __ ] when me and you were
talking to Natalie years ago together
with police and all them? Do you remember?
[ __ ] And when we were chatting [ __ ]
about you on the bus and [ __ ] like that
tonight, do you remember? Yeah. Yeah.
And it and it got told when I was
meeting Timmy that day. I were talking
to Natalie saying that that that she can
do better than you. Meaning
myself. So I've always liked Natalie.
Always. It's only Kaye who's never liked
Natalie and always told me to block Natalie.
Yeah. I've always liked Natalie. I've
always [ __ ] had a little thing for her. Yeah.
Yeah. But Monty, but I think one day.
Yeah. Like say you say you split up with
someone. I'm I'm I'm scared that you
might start messaging all their family
and [ __ ] Yo, listen to this.
Yeah. Listen, PJ, this is funny.
PlayStation, is it? No. This is funny.
Listen, PJ, listen. Listen. Yeah, this
[ __ ] Listen. No. Shut up. Shut up.
Shut up. One second. This is funny.
Yeah. Listen. Just listen. Yeah. I was
having um I was having a wank in the
bathroom. Yeah. And it was um over
Natalie G and Kelly come
in and she caught
me. But I actually offer and said it was
all for me and her. I think instead it
was all for Natalie, man. You know what?
I always wanted [ __ ] Whitehead's
daughter, man. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah. But don't forget, Molly, I was the
same age, you know what I mean? [ __ ]
as his daughters, you know what I mean?
She [ __ ] battered me in the bathroom
and I said it was all for you. It was
all for you. Monty, do you remember?
What? Whitehead's daughter. Daughters. I
wanted them, mate. You're too young for
me, PJ. Well, no, but they were No, I
wanted them. I was the same age as them.
Do you remember?
PJ, you [ __ ] idiot. M I was the same.
I was [ __ ] 60. I was the same age as them.
The thing is, yeah, the thing is, yeah,
I saw them not so long ago, a picture of
the daughter. I think it was like a
year, two years ago that he's got some
sexy daughters, man. Is it?
Yeah. The one who's PJ talking about
Peeps. Yeah. It's a picture of them two
old couple who is set on a set with me
and them lads behind them. Yeah, they've
got two daughters them two old couple.
Not even getting involved. Yeah, they're
too young. Yeah, but they weren't too
young for me. That's what I'm saying.
They're not too young. No, obviously
not. They look your age. Yeah, they're
in the 20s and all that lot now. Yeah,
but like obviously Yeah. But
nah that you know
I don't I don't speak to white heads
anymore. I might add them back actually.
Just like you added me back PJ get in YouTube. Yeah.
No, but Monty I think Yeah. Like I swear
back in the on the PlayStation day days,
one woman like she she she she um she
[ __ ] you over and you start messaging
her mom in it.
No, I swear that was what happened to
her. No, I've never checked no one's mom
on YouTube. No, not YouTube. On
PlayStation. I mean, no. I've never
checked no one's mom on PlayStation.
You sure? Sh.
Why? cuz I thought like you might do
that if someone broke up with me in it.
No, I'm not a career.
Here goes running to my mom. I've never
done that, have I?
What? I've never done that, have I? What
is that? What you do? Run to someone's
mom. Yeah, you run to someone's dad, you
dick. No, I didn't. Did I?
Yes. Yeah. And he got pissed off. He
said, "Don't fuck." He said, "You're
[ __ ] messaging me, Monty." Yeah,
that's what my mom said to Kay. [ __ ]
off. Stop texting me. I don't even know
why he's going to
need that. Yeah. No, no, no. It's
[ __ ] weird. It's weird. It's [ __ ] weird. PJ,
that's why I say you and Kayla would
make a perfect couple. You do like
texting people's family members. Well, I
gave them money. I gave them the
opportunity to apologize.
What? I gave them the opportunity to apologize.
But it's [ __ ] weird, Peas. Yeah.
You're not even going out. You're not
even going out with like girl or nothing
like that. Do you know what I mean?
Is this weird?
It's the same if you're not going out
with someone with someone texting the
ex. How did she know I was messaging her
dad? Her dad must have told her, is it? Obviously.
Yeah. But it's weird though. PJ, if
you're not with somebody, you got don't
go yet and check someone's family
members about a full grown adult.
Kaye does it.
Yeah, cuz she's childish.
Yeah, that's why.
And if she does check, she should be all
about the the children. Nothing else.
Nothing about me. Nothing [ __ ]
mother. Should be about the kids. Did
you saw the videos? What? Did you see
the videos? Did it? Yeah. What? You saw
No, I haven't seen the videos because
it's been going around the person's dad.
What? So, how do you know I messaged the
person's dad then? Because you told me
it cuz you were supposed to go to
America and meet her. Yeah, but did you
see what he was saying? Yeah, but did
you see what he was saying that
PJ low key you didn't actually go to
America, lad, to actually go with it cuz
you would have just shot your head off.
Do you No, no. Do you know what they
would have done, Bonnie? They would have
lorded me. You know what that means?
Lord you lord me. Lord lord. You would
have got arrested. Yeah, that's what
they would have done. Nah, PJ, he could
have ended two ways. One way, yeah, he
could have got arrested or another way
he could have got shot cuz you're
[ __ ] with a man's daughter.
Yeah, but he could have beat me like
just fist money. I'm powerful. I know.
If any man [ __ ] around my my daughter's
I t them up. Mr. B
found Mr. B found it funny. Is it
Mr. B? Yeah, he found it funny, mate.
Yeah, it weren't funny. It wasn't funny.
Only what Americans are going out doing
killing each other on PlayStation. Yeah.
When you was arguing with Alen and then
the boys in blue come your door.
I've never had police at my door on
PlayStation PG. Well, yeah, but Alen was
calling them on you, is it? Alen?
Yeah. Yeah, but I've never had police on
my door off on PlayStation. No, no one
knew where I lived up on
PlayStation. My my address has never got
links on PlayStation. It's only on
YouTube where my address has been
linked. Yeah. Yeah. No PlayStation, just YouTube.
[ __ ] you're the biggest mug going in
love to give you a slap,
man. They can't even slap open a packet
of Chris Blad. I, you know, some of
these accounts have been the same ones
on here for years, man. Yeah, of course
they are. And that's why I can't be as
talking to him anymore with PG.
You know what I mean? They boring. They
[ __ ] boring. They're dead now. They're dead.
It's all boring and dead. Why do you
think Natalie don't go life anymore?
Yeah, it's boring. It's boring. It's
[ __ ] You know, you only get trolled
every day and that's all they want to
see. In fact, they're not even trolled.
They ped the
fails. Look at fell. Look at them all.
Any man put picture of my children up. I
never forgive him. It's all whatever
begs or [ __ ] whatever else like I
never forgive him. [ __ ] that.
You You've never cried after a breakup,
man. You're emotionless.
What do you mean? Like you got no
emotions like no feelings and [ __ ]
What about that? Is that good? No, it's bad.
Why? You've never cried over someone?
No, not really.
No, I've only cried over one woman and
that she [ __ ] that's the one they
[ __ ] started to play PlayStation. She
[ __ ] me over bad man.
And then I went on to PlayStation, never
got in a relationship after that. And
then I [ __ ] thought to get with
someone like Kay, ugly. I thought it'd be
better getting with someone ugly like K.
Cuz every time I get with a bunny woman,
they always [ __ ] me over. Yeah.
So I thought, [ __ ] the bunny with me
off. I try someone like [ __ ] Kayie.
Fell in love with
Kayie, you know. [ __ ]
She just [ __ ] my life up completely
with her. Yeah. Abused me. Abused diesel
and abused the kids. But I sat there [ __ ] allowed
it like a [ __ ]
I should have put a stop when it happened.
Someone called you a s.
Someone is a s in here. No, somebody
called you a s. What's that? It means
where you basically defend women for no
reason and you lick their ass.
I don't offend women. What? What? What
do they mean that that I stick up for
women basically? Yeah. For no reason.
Even Yeah. When they're in the wrong.
Well, I stick for women even if they're
in the wrong. So, who's in the wrong?
Happen weak monger.
Why do they still keep calling you
[ __ ] They need to stop that, bro.
Yeah, it's just what they can keep
calling me. That's all you notice the
same people. PG. Yeah, but they've been
saying that for like four years.
Five years. Five years.
Stone got no life after 5
years. PG. It's the three same names. Skin, Fin.
Yeah. No friends.
[ __ ] pedo. No friends. No kidding. No
friends. Yeah, I think they're just
talking about themselves.
Daily every day they talk about
themselves. Is it? Every day.
See these the play on PlayStation. It
was fun. The drama was actually fun. you
just you know me very open guy very
going PJ tell the truth yeah no [ __ ]
yeah do I have mates in real life yeah
they used to pick you up and take you to Preston yeah see
ps they used to take you money they used
to take you to Preston remember no they
used to take us all over the place. You
used to go everywhere.
I don't know about Preston.
They used to take you to Burnley, Monty.
Burnley. All we can know is where we
went. Oh, we went all over though.
Monty, did you know Blackpool's near Birmingham?
Blackpool near Birmingham. It's nowhere
near Birmingham, you [ __ ]
It's a little Blackpool. Blackpool's two
hours away from Manchester, you clown.
Yeah, but it's near Birmingham. That's
what I'm saying. About two to three hours from
Manchester. No, it's not.
I thought it was near Birmingham. Is it?
[ __ ] And Blackpool's more closer to
Manchester and um Liverpool. Yeah.
Yeah. I went to Liverpool before. It
took me four hours to get there. It was [ __ ] long.
It was long, Monty. I've been Liverpool.
Yeah, I've only been Liverpool once.
[ __ ] long it was. Oh, it's a dodgy
city. That is, Monty. It's dodgy there.
Manchester's next door neighbor, in it. Yeah. Yeah,
man. Oh, money. You should have been on
Coronation Street. Where?
Monty, you should have been on Coro.
Egypt, do you ever itch your ass at
night time and give a good old whiff?
Yeah, I went to the lobster pot, Mr. Be.
It was [ __ ] stinking, bro. It gave me
the [ __ ] That's the time I went to
Liverpool. I was staying in the Travel
Lodge there. Um, and the and there was a
there was a sea and across the sea was
the real, I think. You know what that means?
Yeah. Yeah. You sniff your ass
sometimes. Disgusting. Huh?
You eat your ass and sniff it sometimes.
No, buddy. Have you ever Have you ever
shout out blood?
No. Why? That's not good. That PJ, I've
shouted out blood. You need to You need
to start eating them bananas, PJ.
I tell you them bananas are good for your PJ. Shut up.
One second. Yeah.
No. Every time you say one second, you always [ __ ]
off. I'm here. I'm here. I'm here.
Yeah, Monty. So that's
it. Molly used to fall in love so quickly. PJ.
Yeah. If we had two items in my hand.
M. Yeah. In both in my hands.
Yeah. And I needed a piece so badly. M.
Would you roll on my dick for me?
Yeah, you you [ __ ] tight [ __ ] Why
you t you? Cuz me hands would have been
full. So you would have been lately for
me to piss my pants, man. You [ __ ]
bastard. Why is Timmy Why is Timmy
[ __ ] live talking about you again?
He's obsessed, man.
Fried egg. Stop talking about nonsense.
What you are, lad.
Why does he keep doing videos on you?
Cuz Timmy's a clown.
It's the same like
[ __ ] the egg guy
there. The mo. Yeah, Monty. Listen. Um,
Timmy needs to get off of YouTube.
I phone Jimmy. Yeah,
Timmy's not getting no attention off me.
I phoned him and that's it. I'm done.
I'm done with them
all. They all little clowns and that's it.
You know me, you and Natalie and me and
Katie, we should have a double date.
[ __ ] off. I never meet that woman again.
I' got prison, mate.
I don't think you wouldn't h you
couldn't have prison. I'd
rather go perition for life, lad. Yeah,
but you won't be able to hack prison.
It won't, mate. Better than [ __ ] meeting her.
Yeah, but you wouldn't you wouldn't
hack. Exactly. Exactly. You even agreed
with me. You just said yeah. So exactly
prison will be better and you said yeah.
Nah. See what I mean? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Re back to your chat. PJ never mind. You
might if you went prison you might get bullied.
I rather get bombed by a man. [ __ ] that.
You'd rather get bombed by a man. Oh my
god. Over and over and
over. And that saying something in it.
That saying something. That's mad.
Look, Timmy showing you my
body. He's a clown. [Laughter]
So So PJ, you be on that date on your
own? Yeah, definitely 100% on that doubt
in your own lad.
He done he he he um done a community
post showing this money. One sec.
Is that what is that supposed to mean?
Please come on man. Look. One [Laughter]
sec. Oh man. Someone showing the peep of
a tree again. Yeah.
Yeah. Someone showing the pit money.
Yeah. When I play the money game with
Timmy, he runs away. Monty. Yeah.
I don't ask about money. But when I show
them money, they run away.
[ __ ] knows. Money is just money. What
the [ __ ] No, but what I'm saying? Yeah.
Is they'll come on my live stream. Yeah.
They call me skin. I'll show them money.
Then they don't show me nothing because
they ain't got money. or if they got
money, they're waiting for the benefits
or the pit. Not being funny. Some people
do work in this community. Can't lie
about can't sit there and said that like
they don't work cuz some people do work
in this community, but not all of his work.
No, most of them don't work though.
And it's the same with half of the
[ __ ] women in this community.
[ __ ] they go for [ __ ] for women
jealousy and native for women and [ __ ] like that. And
[ __ ] community pathetic. It's [ __ ]
weird. Yeah. [ __ ] weird. I've got a
new YouTube channel and they haven't
found it yet. It's good. Is it? Do Do
you know what?
What? The actual people who actually
know me for real yet is
Natalie as a person. Obviously, another
person in this community. I'm not really
bringing that person
up, you know, and and that's it.
Obviously them people know me.
They both live with me and you know. Yeah.
So they they both know me. They both
know what person he am in real life.
This [ __ ] on YouTube. It's not me. It's
[ __ ] gay as [ __ ] Yeah.
You want to know who I am? Meet me in
real life. You already met me in real
life. Yeah, I met you in real life.
And you was a [ __ ]
You're a country.
Yeah. This [ __ ] ain't me, man. This
[ __ ] bullying. This [ __ ] [ __ ]
What the do this community? It's not
[ __ ] me. I'm not a [ __ ] bully,
you know. Don't bully me, man. These
people don't bully me. I bullied when I
[ __ ] I bullied when I were younger.
When I were younger. Yeah. I'm not a
bully now, man. I'm a
[ __ ] I've got I got more moles than
these. They're [ __ ] clowns in here.
Yeah. PJ, why did you get me in this
[ __ ] Mongified community? Maybe I'm
the Mong, but these are Mongified.
It is. It is. It is. It is.
The I'm the Mong. Call me a Mong all you
want. People love that name. I'd rather
be a Mong instead of Mongified.
Yeah. You know, I'm the Mong, but use a
Mongifide. Completely spasticated.
Have you seen I'm not being funny. John
West. John West. Have you seen the state of John's
fingers? He's got likey
fingers, but on his fingers he's got
like [ __ ] [ __ ] marks on his fingers. Oh,
he don't like to bite his nails or
stress. That gives me signs of three
things. Depression, loneliness, or
sadness. bite your fingernails or right sign
right for [ __ ]
sake. So if you people have got some why
you all [ __ ] anorexic skinny as [ __ ]
long ass ET fingers
a little bit wrinkled up like they are a
little bit old hands you can tell that
they kind of old hands rarely you
can when he's opening his packet of [ __ ]
um Poundland packet of [ __ ] bacon [ __ ] crisp
they said that you're talking about yourself.
Got an E2 peeps. You want to see my
hands? My hands are lovely and
brown. Lovely and
brown. Lovely and brown. PJ, go on. Yes, sir.
Lovely and brown. Yeah, they're lovely
and brown, peeps. What color is that, PJ? Brown.
Brown. I'm lovely and brown, peeps. I got lovely
hands. I've got lovely hands. What you
on about? I even got a lovely face too,
peeps. Give you a nice little wink
there. You look a [ __ ] I look like a sexy [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. Even PJ said, "Yeah, go on. Put yourself."
How much is that do you think money?
I say about at
least 500. Probably be about five four.
Yeah, probably. Yeah, I have
more. You have more money.
Yeah, I come out with more.
Yeah, but you have 300 pound left now. I heard you
say all together. Yeah,
I heard you. I'm just not
No, I get paid in a couple of more days.
Oh, no. That's not ready. That's not
ready for the month. I get paid I get
paid twice a month. So, I don't get paid
once a month. I get paid twice a month.
So I can spend one
[ __ ] 700 at least and then can spend
at least another 700. But if
you still think it's the same atmosphere
every day on here.
It is the same atmosphere every day on
here. It's weird to think these people
are actually humans though. They're
behind the accounts.
What? It's weird to think that these
people are actually doing this every
day, isn't it? Every day they're
shuffling low. PJ
Yeah, PJ these people. This right I tell
you what about these people.
Yeah. Like I'm clicking on I'm clicking
on you're reading them slowly. You see
you're blur. Yeah.
Yeah. Right. Let me tell you one second.
Let me go and put my phone in charge.
Like my phone's on 5%. Ah
[ __ ] Ah, I just walked into a
door. [ __ ] sake.
But what was the same P?
I said what are you what are you eating today?
I don't know.
What are you going to get a takeaway? Maybe
chops. Do you know what that is? Yeah.
You like them?
Oh, chops. I like onion rings. Yeah, I
have I have steak with onion rings and
mushrooms all the time. Onion rings are
so good, man. I had them
yesterday. Yeah. In a fryer. Yeah.
They're so nice.
They're nice, bro. I love [Music]
Oh, man. I swear, man. Have you tasted
[ __ ] Oh, obviously you obviously,
man. Natalie is a banging banging cook, Really?
Yeah, man. She's [ __ ]
banging. Oh my god.
I wake up every
morning a lovely [ __ ] breakfast in
the morning. That's like what before I
up. PJ saving the baby W for Kaye. What?
PJ saving the baby wo for
Kaye. Hey Monty, do you know do you
remember do you remember when I I got
you to message Izzy? I shouldn't have
done that in it. Nah. Why?
Because look at the [ __ ] it caused it.
It didn't cause no [ __ ] She done that
herself. Yeah, but like you didn't want
to be messaging her. Do you remember
when I told you cuz you messaged her in
it? Yeah, but that got to do with me and
that. It's Timmy's Mr. B. It's Timmy's money.
Well, Timmy's got money. Do you remember Izzy Monty?
Yeah, I remember here.
Was it a funny story? Nah. Yeah. The one
you were in Tyler and you went on
because I told you to go on and then you
got led of a different man.
Is that funny?
Yeah, that is funny. No, seriously. Yeah.
Seriously, why ain't that funny? Come
on. It's pretty funny to be honest. Why
ain't that funny? She said she's going
to go toilet. She text she's you call
home. She's texting me. Have I seen PJ?
No, I don't live in London. Yeah. Why
the [ __ ] I'm going to be seeing
PJ? Only what I know is that I talked to
PJ about two minutes ago and I told PJ to get
on iPad. Timmy sent his iPad for beer
money. PJ. Yeah, cuz Timmy's skin.
Yeah, Timmy got a taxi f now. Timmy, I
don't have to pay for your
taxi. You know what I mean? I offered I
even offered to pay for Timmy's taxi and
everything, PJ, to come and meet me.
Yeah. Yeah. Do you know what I
mean? I I I even offered the offer still
there, but it seems to me he's got he's
got that money there, so he can pay for
his own tax. There's no excuse.
Yeah. And then when he goes
You know, to me, if you don't have no
internet on your phone, yeah, you might
as well get monthly.
It's only like4 a month. It lasts you.
So, you might as well get that on your
phone, get your ass outside and go live.
Show us the location when I'm going to
cook some food in a bit. Yeah. So, I'm
going to come back live or you go live,
whatever. We need to cook some food. I'm
not going live anymore, PJ. I can't be
with these mongos.
Okay. Well, I'm going Yeah. I put you whenever.