Yeah. What have your experiences you bad?
No, she just a person said to me on
Reddit like, "So that doesn't mean you
get to disrespect them." So I said, "But
they can disrespect me and troll me and
waste my time." And to that, she just
blocked me cuz she knows what I'm saying
is the truth, man. These [ __ ] they
like to start stuff, right, with people
that they don't deem as intelligent as
them. But then when you literally win
the argument, they go running
away. Look right here. I just said,
"I'll just go out every Saturday being a
[ __ ] I'm sure that will attract
women. They'll draw on to negativity." I
said, "So on landlords and so on,
landlord, no landlords not allowed
girlfriends." No reply was within the
conversation. I said, "You wanted to
talk about this, so let's talk about it.
Why didn't you give your number to me if
you didn't want me asking you out in a
nightclub?" Come on. you wanted to talk
about it. Let's have a talk about it.
Oh, do you only want to talk about it to
people that you think you can you can
you can manipulate you you manipulate or
you can win an argument against [ __ ]
just complete [ __ ] aren't they,
bro? They are just complete and
utter. Complete and utter [ __ ] I
swear to God they really are,
bro. They've pissed me off this morning.
What are you running away for? You
wanted You wanted You wanted to talk
about it. Come on.
Yeah. Don't start something you can't
finish. What's it with these women
always starting things that they can't
finish? What is it with them? You
know, but I should state my actual
intentions when I ask people for their
number. You're in a nightclub. You gave
somebody your number in a nightclub.
Yeah, we all know what the attention
is. Something to do with [ __ ] dating.
[ __ ] absolute idiots, bro. I can't
wait till I go to Thailand in two
months, you know. I really can't wait,
bro. Really, really, really can't wait. Yeah.
So in other words, they want to talk
about things with people they think
they'll win an argument
against. Anyone that's any bit more
intelligent than them, they run away.
I've noticed that with these women,
huh? I've noticed that with these women.
Yeah. Yeah. I'll be single forever. Just
like you, Harry Freud. I'll be single
just like you. You've always been single
and you're probably still
virgin. Yeah, just like you. But you're
a lot older than me. Self objection.
Yeah, mate. I've already told you
yesterday I've had chances to be in a
relationship. So, I've already told you
and I've already been in a relationship.
What am I talking about? I've already
been in a [ __ ] relationship, you
know. No offense, bro, but you're
probably in your 40s and you've never
even been laid. Don't talk about me,
bro. just because I'm not scared to say what I
think. Yeah. Like, bro, you've never
been in a relationship. You've probably
never even had sex and you're older than
me. Like, let's not talk about me here,
bro. Let's talk about yourself. So, anyways, you
know, so I said to her, "Our landlords
not allowed girlfriends. You wanted to
talk about this, so let's talk about it.
Why did you give your number to me if
you didn't want me asking you out in the
club?" I'm still waiting for this reply.
You said you wanted to talk about it. Come
on. What is it with these people
starting things and not being able to
finish it? Jesus Christ. Jesus [ __ ]
Christ. Oh my god. Why do they start
stuff that they can't finish? I really don't
understand. Yeah. I want models. Yeah.
Yeah. I want models. Even though
somebody I went on a date with last
month was literally a four out of 10 and
she claimed she didn't feel the vibe.
Yeah, bro. I want models. Yeah, I want
models. 10 out of 10 models. Yeah, cuz
all of the people that I went on a date
with are 10 out of 10. Yeah. Morgan's a
10. Izzy's a
10. Yeah, they're all tens. Yeah. Yeah.
All of them are tens, bro. They're all
models. All of these people are models.
No, it's not a tenant. Yeah. I just told
them I'd done that because it's just
something to say. They're just absolute
[ __ ] When are people going to wake
up and actually smell the coffee and
actually do something about this? Like me, I'm
leaving. Yeah. Anyways, I didn't know
these people were
models. I didn't know they were models. News to
me. News to me that these people were
models. They're just evil and they waste
people's time on purpose as well. Don't
let anyone ever tell you that they don't
do on purpose because they [ __ ] well
do, mate. Yeah, they [ __ ] well do do [ __ ] on
purpose. Like meeting traveling an hour
to meet somebody that you've approached
and then claiming you don't feel the
vibe. That is purposely done because
it's not a dating app. Like when are we
going to actually stop like, you
know? So anyways, I'm done talking about
this now. Anyways, but it's it's
actually boring. I just need to delete
these conversations and [ __ ] move on, you
know? So, I'm done with this anyways.
I'm done with this country. I'm going to
Thailand in two months, so I'm probably
just staying for the whole two months to
be honest. [ __ ]
it. Yeah, people need to stop waking up
and smelling the coffee, bro. Stop
[ __ ] defending women. Where's that
ever got somewhere?
Someone. Why are you not replying? You
wanted to This is what I don't understand.
They're just [ __ ] It's just
they're just [ __ ] I'm just sick of
talking about it. It's just negative.
All of it is just negative. And we're
not going through a downward spiral
again. You know, they're all the same in
this country. My main is my mind is made
up. Nothing. I'm leaving. My mind is made
up. When someone's made mind is made up,
that's the end, bro.
They're just ignorers. They're just
bullshitters. They're just time wasters.
ghosters. They're just
everything. It's just literally
everything. They think they're way more
intelligent than they actually are.
They're actually thick as [ __ ]
That's why when you get on argue with
them, they go silent because they're
actually thick as [ __ ] They think that
they're they're intelligent, these
women, but they're really not. And they
think that they're funny, but they're
really not. That's the
thing, you know, same [ __ ] It's why I
don't go out
anymore. It's why I don't go out anymore,
bro. Yeah. Too many negative
experiences. We don't want to hear that.
Or isn't life supposed to be about having positive
experiences? I thought it was, you know, but yeah. Yeah,
man. I can't [ __ ] stand him, bro. I
can't stand him. Like, I'm I'm going to
delete all the conversations and
everything. I can't stand it, bro.
That's why I didn't go out this week.
Can't stand the bastards. [ __ ]
it. I'd rather pay for it and be
considered a [ __ ] loser than ever
waste my time on one of them ever again.
And I'm being deadly serious, bro. I'm
being actually deadly serious. I'd
rather be paid for it and considered a
[ __ ] loser than have to ever
entertain one of them ever again, you
know? And humiliate myself. I actually
[ __ ] mean it, bro. I actually [ __ ]
it properly, bro. Yeah.
[ __ ] headache as
well. I get [ __ ] headache. I don't know why.
Yeah. You went quiet, mate.
Yeah. Yeah. All evil anyways,
mate. Proper evil, mate. Proper evil.
Blows my mind how people defend him, but
they do. They must think he will get him
laid or something. Who knows? Uh
this negative experience, isn't it? So,
like there's no point you saying, "Oh,
you're going to be out on Saturday. Oh,
you're going to be out on Saturday." Cuz
the answer is a big fat
no. A big fat no. So, there's literally
no point even asking it anymore. It will
be a big fat no.
going be a big fat no,
mate. Yeah, I can't be dealing with them
no more, bro. They're [ __ ] evil. I
don't want to associate with evil,
bro. With evil
Yeah. [ __ ] nasty [ __ ] headache.
Where's that come
from? They always quiet.
from? Cuz I hit once or something. I don't know.
Listen up game. How's it going? [ __ ]
bro. I'm fed up with these [ __ ]
women. I said to her, let's talk about
it then. You know, you want to talk
about it? Why are you in a nightclub
giving your number out if you don't want
people asking you
out? Go on, let's talk about it. What is
it with these women thinking that
they're more intelligent than they
actually are? Wait, let me scrap that.
They're not intelligent to begin with.
Like, and then why is it whenever
somebody gives it to them back, they run
away? Have you noticed this with with
these with these women, you know? Like,
who the [ __ ] do they think they are?
Honestly, who the [ __ ] do they think
they are, bro?
[ __ ] hell, man.
Yeah. What do they think they are?
Seriously, that's all I want to say about it.
These women are [ __ ] in the head, bro.
I can't stand
him. [ __ ] seven weeks to go. I'm out
of here, bro. [ __ ]
this. Yeah. What is it,
buddy? I can't [ __ ] stand him, bro. I
literally can't [ __ ] stand a
bit. Hope you anyone else is the
same. [ __ ] evil bastards.
They reply straight away to negativity.
Come on. Are you going to reply or not?
[ __ ] hell. You wanted to have a
conversation. So why are you running
away for? You're the one that said it.
Yeah. They're just [ __ ] in this
country, lad. That's all women are [ __ ] Hello.
What you doing? Just talk about how much
women are [ __ ] Not all women are
[ __ ] All women are [ __ ]
Every single one of them. You don't want
me to go out with you, PJ? Do you feel
alone? I can go out with you if you want
me to. No, I don't need anyone to go out
with me. I'm just stating the truth. You
want me to hold your hand down the
street and that PJ? I can do that. Nah.
Are you sure? Are you sure? Can you just
stroke your leg in that street with you?
You've got a limp. I I I ain't got a
limp. That's my [ __ ] my leg. No, you
got a limp. That's just my dick in my
leg. PJ got a limp.
That's just my leg. Dick hits you my
leg. No, I don't want to meet you again.
You message people's families.
PJ can stroke your leg. PJ.
Nah, you message people's families. I
don't message no one's family. You do? I
don't. I only check people's families if
if they want to get involved with a
freeway PJ. That's about it. Who's family?
I only check people's families if they
want to get involved with a freeway PG.
You're crazy. PJ, can I shut your leg?
No. Why not? Why are women such
[ __ ] anyways? PJ, it's okay to be
gay, you know?
It's okay. Wish I was gay.
Who said that? PJ,
who says that? It's okay to be gay. You
know, TJ Hooker. Yeah. Yeah. You You've
always had a soft spot for me, is it?
I've never had a soft spot for you, PJ.
[ __ ] off. Why you talking gay to me, PJ? Stop. I'm
not stopping RPG.
You're making me blush, PJ. Completely.
You're making me blush you.
So, what color nickies are you wearing today, PJ?
Pink. You're wearing pink knickers
today, are you, lad?
Yeah. Nice. Nice.
Nice. So, what's your post today anyway?
What? Why are you a [ __ ] Cuz I've got a
What's your plans today, PGA?
Just got to go get some food.
What food are you getting?
Don't know yet. [ __ ] knows,
huh? Well, do you want to go? Do you
want to go? Do you want to go on a date
with me, PJ?
We can go. We can go to Greg's for
office get PJ me and you. You're trying
to get my knickknacks. I I am. I'm
trying to getting your knicknacks. Your
pink ones. Why don't you and
he's too ugly?
Really? Yeah. He's too ugly. He's not my
type. Well, you said it's the same
people every day, is it? I like I like I
like a man with with a small dick. PJ
whacks the spot enough for me. I don't
like going too deep.
See the same people every day. Yeah.
Same people same. Yeah. So you said the
same people same argument is it?
No. Me and me and PJ we love as people.
If you didn't know we lovers. We're two
together. That's why PJ hates women.
It's me and PJ are two lovers together.
Aren't we PJ? Tell them. I hate women
because they're [ __ ] evil.
What? I hate women because they're
[ __ ] evil. Do you? Yeah. What? What
about women evil,
PJ? I've never had a girlfriend. Me, PJ,
I've always been single, so I don't know
what women are like. Yeah, they're evil,
man. Are they evil? What do women mean
do? What do they do? I don't know
what they ghost people. They waste their
time. They mock them. All them nasty
things that they do. The nasty bastards.
I'm never ever ever getting a
relationship. Me PJ. Never. [ __ ] that.
L. [ __ ] that. I'm a virgin. Me PJ. Yeah.
Yeah. I only have five wanks a day.
That's about it.
Five wanks a day. I have How many WS do
you have a day, PJ? I never want. You've
never went? Nah.
So why don't you just be mates? I've
never been mates with Tim Pier. Never
been mates with that clown.
Why? I don't even watch his channel.
He's a [ __ ] idiot.
Like I said to him, my paper is taxi to
a local good field. No, no cameras, no
pubs, no nothing. We meet up here and
have a good old wank