And back Yeah.
I was going to do a video about this
date and [ __ ] but for real. Can't
be. Why is she going quiet?
Why? Why do these women go quiet? Why do
they start stuff and then go quiet? [ __ ] absolute
losers. They are absolute [ __ ] losers,
bro. Then they go
quiet. I'm a bit uh bit under the weather
here. Why do they start stuff and then
go quiet? Don't really get that.
Yeah, typical woman,
eh? Typical stopping people that they
think they're more intelligent than
them. When they find out they're not,
run. Yeah. Typical
women. They'll never change in this
country. None of them would ever change
as all the same.
your argument is is so is men. Is that
all your argument is? You ain't got an
argument, do you?
Oh, so is men. So is men. So is men. Why
shifty man? I approached uh sorry I
messaged some women yesterday some
negative things and they replied they
replied first thing in the morning. I
was like oh. So they're drawn to negativity.
Oh, so they ignore normal nice messages
and then they reply to
negativity. Well, I think we're we're
finding out the answers to to this now.
And it weren't like it was two 18y olds
out of about 15 people or two 19y olds.
It was literally about 65% of them that
replied. H strange. They But they moan
that they can't find a normal nice guy. Interesting. abuses.
Yeah, I can't wait to go to Thailand in
seven weeks. I literally can't wait.
I've never been more excited in my whole
life, bro. Get away from this [ __ ]
Yeah. Yeah. They're all the same, bro. 27
counted. Yeah. Listen, bro. Why do you
think there's people in drug there's
there's drug dealers in prison that's
got girlfriends? You not find that a bit
mad how every guy you see with a woman
is either a drug dealer um somebody that does domestic
violence or um somebody covered in
tattoos, a [ __ ] covered in tattoos.
And I've been saying that even before
the Morgan thing, so don't try and say,
"Oh, it's the Morgan thing." Even before
that, I was saying that. But they moan
that they can't find a decent guy. That
is a gender issue. That is women that do
that. Literally, men do not do that. So,
you can't even say, "Oh, well, men do
it." No, they don't do it. Men are the
ones that literally have to lower their [ __ ]
standards. Do you understand, bro? They
have to lower their [ __ ] standards.
Yeah. [ __ ] them. Anyways, bro, I'm in
Thailand in seven weeks, so yeah, I'll
be laughing. I I'll get the last laugh
anyways, bro. I think I'd rather just use escorts.
I think yeah, I'd rather pay use an
escort, get labeled by a loser as these
from these little simps that don't get
nothing anyways than have to pay and
deal with a [ __ ] just to be with a
chance to get some. I'd rather just use
escorts. I'd rather just go to a [ __ ]
house. [ __ ] me, bro. Honestly, I I
actually would rather just go to a house
if this is the trouble that it causes.
I'd rather just go to a hot house, bro.
until then. For them seven weeks, I'm
going for two weeks. I'd rather just go
there, bro. You know, don't have to deal
with all of this [ __ ] from them. I'd
rather just go to a hot house. [ __ ] it, ain't it?
Yeah. I think it makes sense
me. Yeah. I'm going for two
weeks. I've got a nasty [ __ ]
headache, man. But yeah. Yeah.
What time did he say? 6:30. Okay. So,
yeah. Yeah. I doubt very much I'll be
going out in this country
again. I very much doubt it, bro. Well,
I'm going out now to get some food, but
I very much think I'm where I'm at, bro.
I think that's it, bro. I think it's the
the end. I'm not even joking. [ __ ] this. You
know, [ __ ] this,
bro. And then, not to mention, Shifty,
the women that go on dates with you to
waste your time. And this woman on
Reddit said, "Oh, you can't talk about a
woman like that." I absolutely [ __ ]
can. And I'll say in front of any man's
[ __ ] face for that [ __ ] matter.
And and then when I showed her the
evidence of what they've done and [ __ ]
she then blocks me. So, what's the point
typing? If if you're going to be shown
something that you don't like, what's
the point of talking to me? You know,
they don't have no bad words to say
about women. There's still a stigma
against it. I'm fed up with it, bro. You
know, I was fine before I started this
dating [ __ ] again. Before I started
getting involved with women again, but
they claim that they're not the problem.
Yeah. Every single time, bro, that I
deal with them, I get this negativity
again. The same thing as when I used to
gamble. But they claim that they've got
no part in it. They claim that they're
no problem to anyone. They [ __ ] are,
bro. They [ __ ] are. They're a big
problem. Big problem, man.
Yeah. They want a free night out. You
don't get sex. They meet you, claim they
don't feel the vibe when there's nothing
wrong with the way you look and there's
nothing wrong with the way that you
act. So that doesn't even make any
sense. That subject don't even make any
sense. Think about it, Shifty, right?
Would you if you approached a woman,
right, and she was uh and you you was
drunk or for somehow you you forgot how
she looked and she turned out to be a
three or four out of 10, would you
reject her or would you stay with her
and [ __ ] her? You would [ __ ] her. So,
how can a woman try to say to a guy
that's a 6.5, 7 out of 10 how she
doesn't feel the vibe? You see how it
doesn't make no sense? Even if there was
a three out of 10, if I approached
somebody and they turned out to be a
three out of 10, bro, I'd stay with them
to be honest with you and and I'd get
something. And if they were a seven out
of 10, I would [ __ ] stay with them.
So, you see how it don't make sense.
None none of this stuff makes sense. You
see, and you know, there's a stigma on
that they don't do it intentionally.
They literally do do it intentionally.
It is intentional. A lot of the stuff
that they do is
intentional. Don't ask me why they do
it, but they do do it. Yeah, but you get
what I mean.
Anyways, but I was kind of done anyways,
lad. I was kind of done anyways. Um,
after the dating [ __ ] where that person
traveled an hour away, I was like, "Nah,
I'm [ __ ] done here." No, no, I went
out again. Then I had the one speak to
me for 3 days, then ghosted. And I was
like, "Yeah, I'm done now. I'm
definitely done now, bro. [ __ ] it. I'm
[ __ ] done with it. I'm not
humiliating myself anymore. I'd rather
just go to a [ __ ] whole house. Whole
house. I'm not [ __ ] humiliating myself
anymore. What am I doing
anymore? Nothing. We just don't talk anymore.
I don't know, bro. Those them dates I
went on a few weeks ago was the first
dates I've been on in a year, I think.
Was it a
year? Yeah, I think it was about a year.
Wait. Yeah, it was a year. It definitely
was a year,
maybe. So, a lot. But I'm done with them
anyways, bro. I don't want to talk about them. They're
negative. It's a negative in someone's
life. Cuz isn't it funny how you start
having the same problems again when you
start going out again? You
know, just negative, negative,
negative. It's like being depressed and
not taking an anti-depressant, you
know? [ __ ] hell,
bro. I can't stand them. I actually
can't stand them. Like, you really don't
understand, you know? I literally cannot
stand the ground they walk on, which is
why I don't interact with them anymore.
Why do I want to interact with evil
people that are all the same, you know?
It doesn't even make sense to try to get
in their body. For what, bro? For what?
Giving them attention. For what? For
them to do the same [ __ ] again. [ __ ] off,
man. I'd rather pay a I'd rather go to a
wh house and pay than have to pay and
deal with their [ __ ] and [ __ ] up my
mental health. That's That's a good
saying. That's a good saying. You
know, they do. Why is they Why are they
never Why do people never say they do
what they do intentionally? They do do
it intentionally. Yeah, they do do it
intentionally. Of course they do it
intentionally, Shifty. Come on. Somebody
travels an hour away. Somebody that's
approached you, gave you their number, right?
But apparently they don't feel the vibe
an hour away. Please, bro. It's looking
silly now. I had one on here. Yeah. Say
to me, "Oh, maybe you should start your
actual you should state your actual
intentions when you ask people for the
number." H don't like that. Of course,
that's not a normal thing for a landlord
to ask. Also, you ask me out the next
day, which proves it. I said,
"Um, so on land are landlords not
allowed girlfriends? You wanted to talk
about this, so let's talk about it. Why
did you give your number to me in a
nightclub if you didn't want somebody
asking you out? Let's talk about this.
You're in a nightclub. You're giving
your number out. Why is people not
allowed to ask you out? Where have you
gone? You wanted to start an argument.
You wanted to start a debate. Why have
you gone? Where have you gone? Come
back. No one's getting blocked. Come on.
So, you wanted to start a debate. You
wanted to start being a clever [ __ ] You
know what I'm saying? You know, you
wanted to be a clever miss know it all
[ __ ] So, where are you
now? You know, and I'm going to end it
with typical woman runs away when she
knows she's wrong. That's why I'm going
to say it. That's it, bro. Shut up,
Ricky. Man, you're a [ __ ] snake. And
here's another thing, man. If you've got
something to say, come and say it to my
face. I've seen you on other channels
saying, "Oh, this, that, and the other."
I mean, bro, what would you know about
anything? You're a sado. You don't even
leave your house. You have to be a
two-faced idiot on YouTube. Yeah, you
have to be a two-faced idiot on YouTube,
bro. And guess what? You will never say
anything to my face. That's for damn
sure. You know, I've been waiting for
you to come on here as well for a while.
You know, you're a sad little man that's
probably still a [ __ ] virgin himself.
That's why you defend women. I' I've
seen your comments. I've seen your
comments, right? When um you've was it
might have been Red Star's channel and
you chat a load of old [ __ ] bro. What
do you know about life? You don't even
leave your house. What would you know
about life, you little s? You would know
what women are about. You don't know
what women are like. You don't even leave your
house, you know? And then the, you know,
the office still there for you. If you
ever ever want to talk [ __ ] behind my
back, I'll just come to you and you can
say to my face. Simple. Which, come on.
That's never going to happen. You
know, you don't even leave your house.
You're probably a lot older than me.
What would you know about [ __ ] women
in this day and age anyways? Come on now, please.
And then they try to be anyways before I
was rudely interrupted right they try to
be clever [ __ ] but then have you
noticed they run away um they run away
when they know that they're not
intelligent as as someone they think
that they're intelligent right they
think that they're smart when they're as
thick as pig [ __ ] and then when you
completely destroy them in an argument
they run away it's the same thing as
that Morgan done to my friend yeah when
she knew he wasn't buy he wasn't buying
her [ __ ] And it's like this one right
now. It's like what? So a landlord So
landlords are not allowed girlfriends.
Why are you giving your number in a
nightclub if you don't want people
hitting on you? Come on, girl. Let's
talk about it. You know, it doesn't make
sense. Come on. Miss know it all. Mrs. thinks she's
intelligent. Come on. Come on. Mrs.
thinks she's intelligent. What the [ __ ]
Doesn't make sense. Don't start
something you can't [ __ ] finish. I
think I've said that about three times now, bro.
cuz it's happened, you know, a few
times. And then I had somebody message
me this morning and they deleted the
message. I like, "Listen, if you've got
to say something, don't delete the
message. At least let me be able to [ __ ] read
it." You know what I'm
saying? And yes, Ricky, it is people's
choice. But stop moaning how you can't
find a nice guy. Where are all the nice
guys gone? Stop [ __ ] moaning about
it. It's boring. Go back to your drug
dealers and your [ __ ] domestic
abusers that you keep [ __ ] going for.
I bet you I can go to a prison right
now, right? I bet you I can go to a I
could go to a prison right now, a HMP
right now and they've all got
girlfriends. Even though they're in
prison, I swear to you, bro, I bet you I
can go to a prison right now. Yeah.
Yeah. And and literally they will all
have And how I know this cuz I used to
watch prison documentaries. I used to
watch prison documentaries, you know,
and a lot of the time some of them would
even have kids, you know, some of them
would even have children. You know what
I'm saying, bro? No, I just told you.
Listen, listen. Why is she run away? I
don't understand this,
bro. She said maybe you should say your
actual intentions when you ask people
for their number. She's trying to be
smart. Like being smart don't suit you.
Haha. Don't act like that. Of course you
are. That's not a normal thing to ask
your landlord to ask you. Also, you
literally asked, right? He literally
asked me the next day. I said, "Yeah." I
said, "So, our landlord's not allowed
girlfriends." You wanted to talk about
this, so let's You know what I'm saying?
Let's talk about it. Why did you give
your number to me if you if you don't
want people asking you out? You're in a
nightclub. You've gave your number. Stop
trying to be smart. It does not suit
you. Yeah, you might you might be from L
York. You might have gone to UN, but
trust me, you're not more intelligent
than me. Anyone would think that I'm
Monty. Like any these women must think
I'm like Monty, man. Thick in it. They
must think I'm thick like him in it.
Like no no no offense Monty. Yeah. Like
they must they must look at me and think
I'm like you can't read. Like no no no
offense. Like I'm not even trying to
like take the piss out of you, but but
I'm I'm thinking, bro, like why do I get
these women that seem to think that seem
to think that they're more intelligent
than me when they're literally as thick as pigshit?
Like why? Why do I, bro? I think these
women think I'm like you, Monty, brother
or Timmy. They must think I'm a [ __ ] [ __ ] or
something. But guess what? I'm far more
intelligent than they will ever be. Ever be. Trust
me. So that's the thing, bro. And she
was saying stuff like she was saying
stuff like, "No, man. Of course, you're
allowed to ask people out, but if it
makes someone uncomfortable because I
didn't take your number expecting to be
asked out, they're not allowed to reply,
and that's also okay. No, it's not
[ __ ] okay. Yeah, you gave your number
willingly. Yeah. If you did not want to
take anything further, state it and then
block the person. End of. Stop trying to
be smart. Stop trying to be clever. It
does not suit
you. Just state your intentions. Block
the person. Move on with your life.
Not this whole, you know, trying to be
smart. It does not suit you. Like I need
I need to remind this person later on
that I do not have a penis drawn on my
head. Yeah. Remember that. Yeah.
So, and then to ask people if it makes
someone uncomfortable, how does it makes
So, you've gave somebody your your
number in the nightclub and then they've
asked you out and and then I said,
"Okay, well, you didn't reply to um you
didn't reply to the message when
somebody said to you, "Oh, um, how's the
hangover? Stop trying to be smart. It
doesn't suit you. I'm going to tell this
person about themsel, right? You're
another woman who will start something
that they can't finish. Number three
now. Is this number
three? They are such [ __ ] mate.
They are such [ __ ] [ __ ] Like, I swear to God.
Yeah. So, yeah. I'm far more intelligent
than you would ever be. So, please don't
talk to me like you're you're intelligent. cuz you're not. Yeah. So,
yeah. And they do owe you a ply. If they
give you your number, slim, they should
tell you that they don't want to meet or
whatever. You know, there's no excuse
for being an ignorant
[ __ ] You know what I'm saying? But then
they moan and
winge. You know, they moan and winge.
Moan and winge. They can't find Mr.
Normal, Mr. Nice.
Yeah. Right. One second. I want to mess this person.
I just had to tell her about herself,
bro. I just had to tell her about
herself. I just said to her like, "Stop
it." Yeah. You're not You're not more
intelligent than me. You'll never be
more intelligent than me. and sort your
[ __ ] out about, oh, how can a landlord
ask a woman? Like, stop it. You're not
intelligent. Yeah. If you're going to
start a debate and you're going to start
an argument, see it through. I'm sick of
these women, nature, girl. I am counting
down the seven weeks, bro, until I leave
this country, bro. I am literally out of
here, bro. I can't stand women here
anymore. I swear to God, I've not been
out for two weeks, bro. I can't stand
them. You know what I done yesterday?
Yeah. You know them numbers that I've
collected in the past month, right? When
I had that foot injury and how some of
them didn't reply, I said, "Let me do
this test again, a yearly test. Let me
say women are all evil and see how many
replies I get. Do you know how many
replied, nature girl, about 70% of them
replied." I think that says it all, man.
I think that literally says it all, you
know, and contradicts what everyone else
says. That right there, it just proves
everything. You know, they think they're
smart, but they're really
thick. You know, they're actually really
thick as pig [ __ ] but they seem to think they're
intelligent. maybe in their little
world, but they're [ __ ] not. So that
just contradicts everything that they
say in it that they like positivity,
that they like confidence, because as
soon as you say something negative,
they're on it like a ball fly on [ __ ] on a summer's
day. But normal messages, they get lost
in the border of Mexico, lost in transit. Perfect.
Women are way worse than men. And and
the thing is,
right, women are the evil ones. They are
actually the evil ones. Women are the
actual evil ones as well. Yeah. Yeah,
bro. I'm back.
Yeah, I'm not giving you the box, bro.
They must think they're talking to [ __ ] you,
Monty, when they're talking to
me. Yeah, they're just [ __ ]
They're just [ __ ] that think
they're smart, Slim. That's all they are
is just [ __ ] And I just said to
one as well, yeah, I just said
literally, don't write a message to me
if you're just going to delete it. Stop
being a coward.
You know what I'm saying? It sucks
cowards, but it doesn't suit
her about how I'm not allowed to ask you
out. Just stop it. It doesn't suit you.
Just stop it. you know,
said the only reason I reply to your
negative message isn't because I like
negativity, but I've noticed men talking
badly about women recently. I want to
talk about it's not healthy for anyone.
Oh, so you ignore normal
messages, right? And
normal date invites, but you reply to
people talking about women.
Oh, okay. What was the other excuses
then? Yeah, I can't stand them. I'm
never going out of this country again. [Laughter]
I am never going out in this country
again. There you go. You got you got a pinky promise, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. I would never go out of this country
again. Dead serious, bro. That's
serious. What do you think about
it? When you go out in this country, nature,
girl, what do they like to say? Boyfriend. Hey
bro, coming to you. You're not on [Music]
WhatsApp. It's because I'm overweight
and skinn. Uh, you're talking about
yourself. Never been overweight in my
life and I've got more money than you
would ever have. Try again, buddy. Go
self-reflect on another channel. Just
looking at some my
contacts. Yeah, you're literally talking
about yourself there. Never been
overweight in my life and I'm knowing
it's so try
again. Self adapted.
I think that right there. Yeah, I think
I'm going to leave that up. That if even
comes say up. That right there is the
definition of self projection.
Yes, same. That is literally self
projecting. But yeah, I'm I'm done in
this country. I will never go out again.
I don't think here.
No. Never. I think.
Yep. It's about Monday. Yeah. [Music]
But yeah, I think that that's I that's a
eye opener nature girl is that they
ignore normal messages and they reply to negativity.
Yeah, I'm not showing you nothing.
Bye-bye. Yeah, I think that that in
itself what the [ __ ] that in itself
tells you all you need to know. I think
nature girl I think that just says tells
the whole story is
it they reply to
negativity they reply to
negativity anything they can argue with
and think they're right with they they
reply calling me lad
Yeah. Yeah. But apparently they like
they like positive positivity. They're
like positive men, but then they only reply to
negativity. They're [ __ ] evil. I
don't know why people defend them, bro.
Like, why do people defend them when
they're when they're clearly [ __ ] evil? Yeah, I
mean they are [ __ ] evil. Every single
one of them. I'm pouring them in the
same brush. I think that's the saying,
is it Frenchie? I'm pouring them in
exactly the same brush.
Oh, what headache, man.
Yeah, in the same blush, I
think. What do you want, money?
Yeah. What the [ __ ] do you want? Oh my god.
N the [ __ ] does he want, man? What's
your [ __ ] issue? Why you crying so
much? Sitting there blaming me because N
he only asked you for the B to to talk
to you and that and then you sitting there [ __ ]
Then then you're sitting there calling
me a [ __ ] mong. Calling me I'm not
like demon or multi because [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. PJ definitely 100% like me. You've
got a mind like a [ __ ] or lad. You
sit low and you flip out when you can't
get laid. You sit low when you lose
pound on the gambling machine. Yeah. No wonder.
N all women are evil. Not all women are
evil. Oh n. This is where your heads
are. This is where your
heads but the way you sit down and talk
to women where you get your check. Yeah.
Yeah. Then you take it out on everybody else.
So So if I'm the [ __ ] [ __ ] why can
I get laid and you can't PJ? I'm the
[ __ ] [ __ ] You're getting laid. Listen.
Run through. So how's fat and ugly?
Ch coming out. jealous. I'm jealous.
Okay, I'm jealous. Either way, either
way, either way, jealousy straight away.
I'm jealous. Yeah. Yeah. Jealous. I'm
jealous. Either way. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I'm jealous. I've always been getting
laid in my life, PJ. Always. I don't
selfplay when I get turned down. Yeah.
Okay. And that's what you're doing now.
Running your mouth on YouTube because
you can't get your dick wet. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Women are perfect. You know,
can I tell you why women can tell you
why? Can I tell you why women? I didn't
message I didn't message eight people
yesterday and they didn't reply. Yep.
Yep. Monty's right. Can I tell you Can I
tell you the situation you're doing? Can
I tell you the situation you're doing?
Are you sending I'm wrong, man. I'm
wrong. Are you sending women? Are you
sending women dicks and that? Yeah. No.
No. Oh, so when you when you meet them
and you pull it down and then they chat
you after shagging you. I just think
it's funny how they I just think it's
funny how they um reply to negative
messages. Oh, let me tell Grievy this
actually cuz this guy's going to talk
over me. Uh, Grevy before I went to um
sleep uh last night.
Yeah. Um I messaged I think it was six
or seven women. I said women are evil.
Now before this I messaged normal things
prior like how was your day like a month
ago and I thought let me see how many of
these people um reply back and literally
70% of them reply back to negativity.
Greasy. That says it all, bro. It
weren't two 18y olds. It weren't a 19
and an 18y old. It was literally 70% of
these women. They replied back as soon
as you wrote something negative, ready
to argue with you. That's a red flag,
bro. That is literally a [ __ ] red
flag. That is bad, is it, bro?
Yeah, I stick to my guns. I think I
stick to my guns, Grezy, because how how
can you explain that? Let's ask Grezy for some
advice. It's not normal, is it,
bro? No, no, no, no, no. I didn't insult
them. I just said I said women are evil.
So, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. So you
ignore normal messages and then you
reply to somebody saying women are evil.
Shouldn't it be the other way round? I
would have thought it would have been
the other way
around. I would have thought personally
it would have been the other way round
where they reply to normal messages and
block well negative
ones. You know they don't have to reply.
Why do they have to reply? They don't
reply to normal messages.
I don't know. I had this woman tried to
be smart with me, Grezy, as well. I had
her try to be smart with me and I had to
tell her about herself. Bro, where are
these different women? People keep
saying that, "Oh, not all women are like
that." No, no, no, no. Where are these
women, Grezy? 27 and counting. I'm your
age and I've never been shown any
different. Where are these these women?
I'd love to know where these women that
aren't all the same are. I'm still
waiting. I'm still waiting. She wanted
to start a debate with me, Greavvesy,
and then she ran away. This is another
thing they do. You want to talk about
narcissist, Greavves, I tell you exactly
what women do. Do you know what women
do? They start arguments with people.
They start arguments with people, right?
Who they think that they're more
intelligent than. Like, they must think
I'm Monty when they're trying to argue
with me. And when you show them that
you're more intelligent than them, that
you've got like a valid point, they run away. They
literally literally run away. They
literally literally run away when they
know that they can't. They don't have a
point. You know what I'm saying? No, no,
no, no, no, Grezy. They don't give a
[ __ ] about nice people. No, they're the
ones. Listen, I just told you I messaged
them and they didn't reply. So, where
where did you come to that conclusion?
You write normal messages, they ignore
it like an ignorant [ __ ] right? But
then they reply to negativity and you
don't see the problem in that. It
contradicts everything that you say.
to wake up, Greezy. But they're not
strangers because they've gave their
number. Yeah, but they're not strangers
because they've gave you their
number. Anyways, you're always going to
defend women. So, there's no point
having this conversation. I'm done with
this conversation because I know what
I've experienced. I know what these
women continuously do, wasting people's
time. You don't have a bad word to say
about them. I think we should just end
the conversation then. Boring
conversation. This woman said she tried
being funny. Yeah. I said to her, um, in
future, if you're going to write a
message, please give me a chance to read
it so I can defend myself. She said,
send nudes. I said, what are you talking
about? And then I I wrote, me being me,
Grezy, I was going to ask you to send
your nudes, but I like boobs, and your
boobs is as flat as a pancake. I have
bigger ones than you. That's going to
definitely get a reply because it's
something that they can argue against.
They're drawn to negativity. Do you not
understand? That's definitely got to get
a reply. That's just me being cheeky,
you know? You want to take the piss out
of me, I'll take the piss out of you. Simple.
Yeah. [ __ ] they're absolute [ __ ]
How grieves he defends them the way he
does, I shall never know. I shall never
know. But some people just ain't got a
bad word to say about
women. It's been like that for ages. No bad
words. No bad
words. They've got no bad words to say
about them. It's crazy. They just sit
there and defend them. [ __ ]
hell. You justify I find everything they
do, people justify it. Oh, they don't.
They're ignorant because you're a
stranger or this because of that or this
because of that. Like you you literally
always defend them. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Cuz I'm sick of them. I'm
fed up of them.
Yeah. You know, I'm I'm sick of them.
Yeah. Cuz I'm [ __ ] sick of them. You
know, I've got a [ __ ] voice. You
know, you know, they waste people's time
intentionally. They're just [ __ ] They're absolute
[ __ ] The only time they reply is
when it's it it's negative, but then
they ignore normal messages. But yet
they want a normal guy, Grezy. They want
a normal nice guy, but they ignore
normal messages and then mock negative
ones and use it to argue with you. That
contradicts everything you say. Do you
not understand that? It contradicts
everything that you are saying. We want
a decent man that respects us. We want a
man that respects us. And you message
them, no reply. Second message, no
reply. Okay. One month later, all women
are evil. How are we all evil? You start
getting these, they start messaging and
messaging and messaging. Do you not
understand how it contradicts everything
you're saying? They're attracted to
[ __ ] thugs, woman beaters. If
you're getting this much attention for
just being a tiny bit negative, if you
conducted this in the right way, bro, it
would work. Go to a prison, like I was
saying earlier. Yeah. go to a HMP
prison. They all have girlfriends.
They've got kids. You
understand? Most of them anyways cuz
they are attracted to
[ __ ] Yeah. Greasy, I'll tell you
one that was trying to be smart with me.
Yeah, cuz you're here. Maybe you should
say your actual intentions when you ask
people for their number. Haha. Don't act
like that. Of course you were. That's
not a normal thing to for your landlord
to ask you. Also, you was trying to ask
me out the next day, which proves it.
Try to be clever. I said, "So, our
landlord landlords not allowed
girlfriends? You wanted to talk about
this, so let's talk about it. Why did
you give your number? Why did you give
your number to me if you didn't want me
asking you out? Where have you gone? You
wanted to start an argument. You wanted
to talk about it. We're going back and
forth. Why have you run away?" Because
you know that you're not more intelligent than
me, you know? Like, stop trying to be
smart. It doesn't suit you. They are
[ __ ] Like even even that in
itself, they're proper [ __ ]
bro. Proper proper proper [ __ ] I
don't know how people defend them. I
honestly I don't, bro. Proper [ __ ] Seriously. You
know, you know what I'm saying, bro? You
got [ __ ] I know I'm right in it. And
I'm doing the right thing by leaving,
you know, I'm leaving this country. I'm
doing the right thing.
So, you know, and you're above average
looking. I'm above average looking. You
know, you shouldn't have these women
that think they're better than you. Put
the shoe on the other foot. Imagine you
started going on dates with sixes and
sevens and be like, "Nah, I think I'm
better than you. I don't feel the vibe."
Imagine grieving the tables were turned.
Imagine the tables were turned. Oh,
could you imagine? [ __ ] Could you
imagine? Right. Could you imagine if you
went on dates with above average looking
women and you were saying to multiple
how, nah, I don't want to be with you.
Nah, I don't feel the vibe. Doesn't add
up, bro. Doesn't make sense. You know,
and that's the way it should be looked at. You
know, if you weren't a ber, stop calling
yourself a bun. Stop self- projecting.
You are the ba. The YouTube bun. That's
why you don't show your face. Stop
calling yourself a bun. Everyone knows
that I'm the best looking on this
[ __ ] community. Stop calling yourself
a bunter. You a repeater. Stop talking
about yourself. I don't like it when
people talk about themselves like that.
It's not nice to see people talk about themselves like
that. So yeah, that's the way it is,
bro. Like they
uh they will start arguments with people
that they feel it's like that Morgan. He
she thought that she was more
intelligent um than me and my friend. So
when she thought she could try to
manipulate my friend when he wasn't
buying any of it, you know, he's not as
intelligent as me. She then started
blocking. Have you noticed this is what
these cowards do? And it's not just one
or two of them, it's it's a lot of
them. And I even said from day one, give
me five minutes with that [ __ ] in an
argument and I will literally ruin them.
Trust me. You know, they're evil. But
women are they are evil. And let me tell
you something greasy. You want to say
men and women they both do this. They
both do this. They both do this. But
guess what? I can tell you something
greasy that men don't do. Do you want to
know something that men don't do? Men
don't moan and moan. Oh, we can't find a
normal person. Then go for drug dealers
and go for scumbags and go with people
that's got tattoos from their head to
their [ __ ] toes that have been done
for domestic violence. That's not what
men do. Yeah. Men don't do that. And I
and I can safely say that for I can
that. Yeah. Simple. Simple. They do not
go for these people.
Yeah. You know what I'm saying? So that's
it. It's like when I was reading that
that thing to that that person about
that woman in Liverpool getting killed.
To be honest with you, you're dating a
drug dealer. What do you
expect? Like, you probably moan to your
friends, "Oh, uh, I can't find a nice
guy. I can't find a nice guy." Then you
dated a drug dealer and guess what?
Someone broke into your house and killed
you over what? It It's linked. Yeah,
you're with a drug dealer that have to
have to look over their shoulders for
[ __ ] police, rival [ __ ] gangs.
Yeah, it's serious [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah,
there was a good chance somebody was
going to get killed. You know what I'm
saying? It's madness. It's It's actually
madness that even people would have
risked their whole I don't I was I was
watching it the other day that that
thing in Liverpool and obviously I feel
sorry for the child cuz the child's a
9-year-old [ __ ] kid that's innocent.
But the woman what you're with a drug
dealer and you and and people are
shocked that these things happen. You
know what I'm saying? Please, man. It's
looking it's looking silly now. You
know, it's looking really silly now, bro.
you know, doesn't look right. Doesn't look [ __ ]
right. Yeah. One who I know went out
with these proper Yeah. They they only
like scumbags. They only like scumbags.
scum. Bad behavior gets
rewarded. Yeah, bro. They only They only
like these kind of people. Yeah.
Look, do you remember that thing when
that Do you remember when that Twitter
thing went out about me? Yeah. When that
Twitter thing went out about me,
bro. Yeah. That Twitter thing went out about
me. Yeah. Do you remember I got so much
attention and there weren't even people.
Not everyone was hating. Not everybody
was hating. I had women message me and
everything and not all of them were
being rude. A lot of them was, but a lot
of them wasn't. So you you get the drift
that they're they're drawn to [ __ ]
They're drawn to
negativity. You know, that's that's the
point I'm trying to make.
Yeah. Yeah. Exactly, bro. So that's why
I don't even bother with them
anymore. And then you get evil scumbag
women that can jump in and out of
relationships. Why am I trying, bro? For
what reason? Why am I trying? For what
reason? For what reason am I
trying? Doesn't make sense. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. They all reply to
negativity, mate. I messaged about six
or seven and I had about four replies,
mate. And I'm thinking it's not just one
woman. It's not just two w women that
are immature. It's
multiple. It's multiple. That is
worrying, bro. You know,
negativity. It's strange
that yeah, they ignore normal
messages. Like I need to come off social
media soon, bro, because it's going to
start like getting bad again. It's going
to start becoming a bit dodgy again. Do
you know what I'm saying, bro? I need to
come off this this social media, bro. I
think Yeah. As long as you know Yeah.
Do you know what this woman
said? She said, "I'm sorry you've had
bad experiences with women. You are a
lovely guy, so I'm sure you will find
someone great." I said, "If I'm so
lovely, why don't you get with me?"
Perfect exclamation mark. I mean, who
wouldn't want to be with a lovely guy?
You know, somebody would want to be with
a lovely woman, wouldn't they? Yeah.
And I said, she said, "I'm not." And I
said, "You ignoring normal messages is
arrogant behavior." And then she said,
"I'm sorry you've had bad experience
with women. You are lovely, guys. I'm
sure you will find someone great. If I'm
so lovely, why don't you get with me?"
That's perfect. [ __ ] perfect, eh?
Perfect. [ __ ] [ __ ] they are. I'm
deleting [ __ ] Reddit today, bro. I'm
[ __ ] deleting this YouTube app as
well before certain people start getting
a [ __ ] mental breakdown, bro.
I never said I'm a lovely guy. She said
I'm a lovely guy. I said if I'm so
lovely, why don't you get with me then?
If I'm so lovely, you
know, they respond to they respond to
negativity. That is very worrying,
Grezy. It contradicts everything you
say. It contradicts everything you
[ __ ] say. And a lot of them do it as
well. A lot of them will talk to you and
then they will just ghost you and you
never hear from them
again. You never I've got so many
screenshots, bro. Like so many screenshots. It's
unbelievable. You want to talk about
normal behavior. You [ __ ] ignoring
ain't normal behavior. You sat there
ignoring ain't [ __ ]
um you know you ignoring is not normal
behavior. How about that one? You want
to talk about behavior? You ignoring is not normal
behavior. It's [ __ ] It's [ __ ]
arrogant. That's the word I'm looking for.
Yeah. Yeah. So, what's she going to
reply to that? She said that I'm a
lovely guy, Grezy. If I'm so lovely, why
don't you get with
me? Huh? Why don't you get with me then?
But Greavvesy sits there and defends
them. Greavvesy sits there and defends their
behavior. He literally sits there and
and No, I'm not joining his stream. I'm
not joining any stream. I need to go out
in a bit. I got a [ __ ] headache. We
need to get some
painkillers. Don't think I have any
left. I've had a headache all
day. Literally. Yeah. They reply as soon
as you write something
negative. Literally. She said I said I
said don't write something if you're not
going to um and then delete it so I
can't see it. And she said send nudes.
Try to take the piss. So then I thought
I'd take the piss out of her as well. If
I'm such a lovely guy, why are you not with
me? Yeah, I'm terrified, bro. Yeah, I'm
terrified, bro. I'm terrified of Monty.
Yeah. Yeah, you got it, bro. I'm
terrified. Yeah, terrified, bro.
Terrified. Yeah, I'm
terrified. You got it, bro. I'm shaking, man.
Yeah. Yeah. You still use Instagram,
Grezy? You still use Instagram? No.
You need to do self-reflect. Yeah, I
think you need to as well, man. I think
you need to. I think you need to get off
YouTube. Yeah, I think you do as well. I
think you need to get off of
YouTube. Yeah, that's what I
think. Women in the country, women in
this country is definitely the problem.
I swear on my life. And that's why I'm
leaving the country. That's why I'm
going to Thailand because I feel so strongly about
it. I don't go on
TikTok. They are definitely definitely
definitely the problem.
100%. You know what I'm
saying? No, I don't watch Tik Tok.
Yeah. So, they say that you're a lovely
guy, Grezy, but yet they don't want to
date you. Well, they don't want to meet
you. Strange, isn't
it? I'm going to I'm just going to come
off of um social media, I think, bro,
for a little
bit. No Reddit, no
YouTube, just WhatsApp, bro. I
think I don't know who that is.
Yeah, they're all the [ __ ] same, bro.
Yeah, I'm getting these mood swings
again today, Grezy.
I'm getting these mood swings again
today. I really
am. I'm getting these nasty mood swings
again. [ __ ] Are they replying to negative
messages? They've got nothing to say to normal
messages. No, I can't give a shout
out. Not talking about people's kids.
You know what I'm saying? And then
people just sit there and defend them.
Grezy, does that not tell you everything
you need to know? They ignore normal
messages and then reply to negative
ones, but you don't see that as a
problem. Only Greavvesy does not see
that as a
problem. They [ __ ] reply so fast to
negativity. I thought it would have been
the other way around, me. I thought it
would have been the other way [ __ ] round.
You said, "Can you give a shout out to
Rebecca and her
son?" Read what you just
said. So, when will women stop being evil anyway?
Squeezing. When will women stop being evil?
Yeah. When is that? When when we tell
us going to make another Reddit, I
think I'm going to make another Reddit,
I think. Yeah.
Yeah. One second.
Yeah, but I'm just going to go back on it for today.
Yeah, back on it for
today. Some [ __ ] s. Yeah. [Music]
Yeah. Been laid more times than you have
ever, you little s. I've been laid more
times than you've had hot
dinners. Money, more women got proof. Yeah.
Yeah. More times than you've not did
this, mate. I'm nowhere near
30. Anyways, you're bad. All right. Bye-bye.
[ __ ] Root of all evil. Greasy. The
root of all
evil. He will always defend
them. He will always defend
them. Their ignorant, arrogant behavior.
ways to fed women. Just like most
people would always defend women. Sad. Yeah.
Look at all evil.
Yeah, of course you
can't stand [ __ ] women got [ __ ]
standard. More people are giving up with
me. That's fine, bro. I don't give a
[ __ ] That's good for them, bro. If they
give up with me, that's nice. I know
what women are like. I've had the
experiences I've had to wake up to. See,
if I didn't wake up to these messages
today, I would have been fine. They sit
there and ignore messages, normal me, a
normal message, and then they reply as
soon as you're
negative. They're evil. Literally, I
don't know why people keep defending
them. And them messages today [ __ ]
wow me up. If I didn't get their
messages, I wouldn't have
cared, you know?
I need to start calming down brokers
before I get myself in serious serious
trouble. I'm not even joking. Yeah.
Yeah. How they can sit there and defend
[ __ ] women after what I've just said
as well. It's [ __ ] bad. Bad. Add this.
[ __ ] pissing me off, bro. They're
actually pissing me off.
Yeah, [ __ ] off again. I swear to
God, they [ __ ] are, man. They're
[ __ ] so evil. Really are, bro. Really
Negative. Negative. E negative.
Yeah. What the kind of women? Okay. Elab
el elaborate. Elaborate. Elaborate. Okay.
Elaborate. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Elaborate.
You don't know anyone who I've met. So,
how how do you work that one
out? Yeah. And all the women on the
street pretend they got
boyfriends. The high value women as as
you would to call them pretend they got
boyfriends. They are literally all the
same. 27 and counting. Man, I've never
met a woman that weren't evil. I'm not
even joking. I swear to God. I'm not even [ __ ]
joking. Yeah, I'm beginning to [ __ ]
not be able to stand these women again,
notorious. They ignore normal messages
and then they reply to
um they reply to um
negativity. They reply to like negative
messages, but they ignore normal
ones. Like this model.
Yeah. Well, she says he's a model,
right? I said uh in future cuz like a
message at least give me a chance to
read it so I can defend myself. She's
like send nudes. I said what are you
talking about? I was going to ask you to
send nudes but I like boobs and your
boobs is as flat as a pancake. I have
bigger ones than you. Soon she wanted to
try and take the p laughing emoji. I
said you're a proper ignor. She said I'm
not. But you do realize sending someone
a message at 1:00 a.m. saying I'm sick
of women is not normal behavior. I said,
"You ignore ignoring normal messages is
arrogant and not normal behavior. I'm
sorry you've had bad experience with
women. You are a lovely guy. So, I'm
sure you'll find someone great." I said,
"If I'm so lovely, why don't you get
with me?" Perfect. Gone quiet again. [ __ ] absolute
[ __ ] They are absolute [ __ ]
[ __ ] I swear to God.
Yeah. Absolute [ __ ] I swear,
bro. They are absolute [ __ ]
[ __ ] and a [ __ ]
half. But Grevy defends
them. Grievesy defends these women. Yeah.
said to one woman, "I'm starting to hate
women." Guess what? She replied straight
away. Negativity attracts them, bro.
Negativity attracts them. I swear to
God. Yeah, they are so attractive to
[ __ ] and negativity, aren't they?
[ __ ] hell. You know what you need to
do? You need to become a You need to
[ __ ] You need to become a [ __ ]
That's what I was thinking of doing.
Becoming an absolute scumbag
[ __ ] Have you thought about it,
bro? You should You should You should
consider it, bro. You should consider it. Madness. I said heat.
That's about this. [ __ ] balls.
Yeah, you don't know nothing. Bye-bye now. Yeah.
And look, they reply straight
away. Bro, I'm so [ __ ] done. You
know, I'm coming off of social media
today as well for a little bit. Yeah.
Yeah. That far. That far.