Yeah, I've had two more replies when I sent negative
messages. Well, they sure do love
negativity. [ __ ] hell. They sure love negative negative
people. Sorry, man. I just had to go and
get some meat. Same
[ __ ] Same [ __ ] [ __ ]
bro. You had to lift to get some
uh Yeah, but I had some more replies to
the negative messages. Tell you all you
need to know about this country, I
reckon. Tells you all you need to know.
Yeah, they're all [ __ ] They'll reply to
negativity. They say they want a nice
guy. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, bro. They reply straight away to negativity. That's
it. I think I need to get
off before it starts like seriously
winding me up.
Okay. Literally, that's two more replies
in the space I've been out. So they
ignore normal messages, but then they
reply to negative messages.
Strange saying there, but remember
they're drawn to positive people and
positive minds there. Yeah. The only
time you get anything out of them is when
you're is when is when you're negative.
Oh, [ __ ] they're just [ __ ]
[ __ ] in this country. That's what they are.
Yeah, bro. this
August. Who is this [ __ ] [ __ ] on
the [ __ ] screen, bro? [ __ ] it up. [ __ ] idiots,
bro. [ __ ] a proper [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, I've had a few more women reply,
bro, when I started moaning about them
and what they
do. They sure love negativity, don't
they? They sure love negative people. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, they're sure of negativity.
They're all the same, aren't they? I
just went to the butchers. They're all same.
Yeah. [ __ ] I I can't stand him, bro.
I literally can't stand
him. They reply to negativity and ignore positivity.
They've applied to negativity. I'm
getting more messages. They've applied to negativity. Yeah,
they they're [ __ ] evil, bro. They
[ __ ] are [ __ ] evil, lad.
They love negativity,
lad. reported for what,
lad? Yeah, I know, bro. No, I'm careful
with what I'm saying, obviously, bro.
Yeah. No, I know. I know. Yeah, I
Yeah. Oh, Steven Howard, hard man to catch, aren't
you? You're a hard man to catch. Yeah, I
just messaged women some negativity
saying all women are evil and loads of
them replied back. Literally almost all
of them replied back. And now I think I
know why I'm going to Thailand. I think
that tells you everything you need to
know. That tells you everything you need to know.
Yeah. Yeah. I got a life, bro. Oh, I
forgot to tell you, bro. USA Izzy's got a
uh has got a new boyfriend. Yeah. I
thought you'd be uh
interested. Yeah, bro.
I'm just going to start deleting these
conversations, lad, because I'm they're
just going to start pissing me off, bro.
I swear to God. And there's certain
things you can't say nowadays cuz of the
police. So, yeah. You
see, just done with these. Yeah,
man. Yeah. I got a picture. Uh, yeah, I do.
One second. But I'm doing something. Hold
on. Yeah, they all reply to negativity.
Strange. But they like positive people
apparently. Do I have a picture of him?
Yeah, I should have a picture of him somewhere. Where is
he? Ah, [ __ ]
sake. There we go. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm I'm having a curry. I'm
getting a curry made for me. Definitely
today. Yeah, I just need to delete these
messages, bro. Cuz these women are all
the same. There's no point me even
looking on them. They are literally all
the same. There's there's just no point,
bro. There's no point even talking about this anymore.
Yeah, they reply straight away to negativity. But uh
yeah. Yeah. Somebody a few Well, someone
else said he looks like me as well, but
obviously I ain't got tattoos. So, but I
gave up with dating even before all of
that. Before that [ __ ] I had already
given up. I had already given up, bro.
because of the ghosting and [ __ ] That's
why I gave up.
Um yeah, I gave up cuz of the ghosting and and yeah, [ __ ]
Yeah. No, I don't know. I don't care. It
wouldn't [ __ ] with my head anyways, bro.
It wouldn't [ __ ] with my head
anyways. Even if she did, it doesn't
[ __ ] with my head. I don't care. I don't like the [ __ ] So,
yeah. I don't like her, bro.
So, it's wouldn't [ __ ] with my head.
What's [ __ ] with my head is how many
of these women reply to
um negative messages. That is bad, lad. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, I I don't think I'll ever go
out in this country again, Cactus. I
think that generally is me, bro. I don't
think I'll go out in this country again.
And on hot.
Yeah, I generally don't think I'll be
going out in this country ever again.
I'm going Thailand in two months. That's
it. I'll stay in the two
months. But I think that that's me, bro.
Almost covered rec covered with my foot
injury now as well.
So yeah, I'm done,
bro. How else am I going to have fun? Go gym, go
cinema, just grab about. I can't be
dealing with this mobile, bro. This is
no good for anyone's mental health. This
is exactly why I gave
up. This is exactly why I gave up.
Yeah. Nah. Nah. I'm done talking about
it now. Anyways, bro, I'm going Thailand
in two months.
So, yeah. The worst I said on WhatsApp
is I just hate women.
That's what I was basically saying is I hate
women. I can't believe how many of them replied
back to negative messages. That's
unbelievable. That's unbelievable,
Grezy. I've had some more messages come
through and I think that's all you need
to know about women.
I thought maybe two of them would have
replied back. Literally, most of them
reply back. So, they ignore normal
messages, but they reply to negative
ones. I think that sums it up about
women in this country. That alone just sums it
up. Yeah. Just [ __ ] They're just
[ __ ] That's what they
are. Yeah. They're just
[ __ ] Yeah. Yeah, they would have
to stop that as
well. Yeah, they only reply to negativity,
lad. Yeah, they only reply to
negativity. That's crazy, bro.
Yeah, I had some more replies, Slim,
from some more women.
Yeah, I've had some more replies. Well,
they really do love negativity, don't they?
They really do love
negativity. Yeah, I was just saying I
hate women. That's what I was saying.
Yeah. Yeah, they're all the same.
There's no point dealing with them. Uh,
one was like,
um, I think I've just deleted a lot of
them now as
well. One was like, I read that law. Why
are you telling me this? I said, why are
you replying as soon as somebody writes
something negative? Why are all of these
women replying um to negativity when
that's the very thing apparently they
don't like? They say they don't like
negative people. So, why are they replying to
negativity? You know what I'm saying?
Does that make sense? No, it
doesn't. Well, here we go. We got one
here. Oh, she replied
to So, okay. Okay. I I can actually tell you this.
Actually, I can tell you. So, I wrote,
"Hi, it was lovely meeting you yesterday
and talking to you. Did you get back?"
Okay. No reply
whatsoever. Yesterday, I put, "I give up
with dating and women. It's negative."
Well, that triggered a reply. Hi, I
wanted to take a I want to take a moment
to reply sincerely. Meeting you in
London was unexpected. I felt a bit
hesitant at first when you asked my
contact, but I still appreciated the
time we spent walking and talking. Um,
oh, here we go. I didn't feel the kind
of connection unrealistic standards
again. I wanted to take further and I
chose not to respond to you because I
didn't want to give you false hope or lead you
on. I also hope you won't let this
become something negative. Sometimes two
people just don't click and that's
completely normal. Yeah. Two people
don't click because you've got
unrealistic standards and you're looking
for Mr. Perfect. Yes. That's why two people don't
click, you know, cuz it's you.
Let me write this.
Yeah, I just wrote this. Yeah. Yeah,
you're right. Two people don't click
when the woman has unrealistic
standards. You know what I'm saying? I
am so done. I'm going Thailand, bro. Two months.
So yeah, they do it on purpose. They
literally do it on purpose. They do all
of this stuff on purpose, lad. Yeah. One
second. Let me just go on this. One second. Yeah,
lad. That's it, lad. Yeah. I'm done
anyways, bro. So, if I'm live on
Saturday again, there's no point asking
me if I'm out. I'm not going out in this
country no more. Simple. I'm done, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. Somebody said, "This guy
kind of looks like me." I ain't got no [ __ ] tattoos,
bro. I ain't got no [ __ ] tattoos.
But I think your best thing now is just
just to just give up and go Thailand. No
once a week. No.
Um, no counting down the days. Just go,
bro. Honestly, just get out of here, you
know? Please, just get out of here. No,
I can I've already booked Thailand. I
can go out once a week. I've got other
ways to make money, but there's no point
in dealing with them anymore. Let me ask
you this question about the boyfriend
thing as well. Yeah, people keep saying
um oh, I've got a boy, um the people
that say they've got a boyfriend. Okay,
let's let's think about this for one
moment and and let me let me just say
this. Yeah. So, you're telling me all of
these women in these nightclubs that say
they've got boyfriends, right? That say
they've got boyfriends for what? Are
these boyfriends coming home at on
Friday, Saturday, sat there until 7
o'clock in the [ __ ] morning when
they're [ __ ] women when they're
[ __ ] women are slagging it out off
until 7:00 in the
morning? Really, really, really, really.
So, all of these Jack the Lad type guys
are coming back from work, right, on a
Friday, Saturday, and their women are
slagging it out until 7:00 in the
morning. It don't look right. Yeah. Do
you understand? The maths does not add
up. One little bit. Does it add up? You
know what? 7:00 in the morning. I can
tell you this cuz I've got sisters.
Yeah. And I've got sisters with partners
and they ain't slagging nothing up until
7 o'clock in the morning. R boy, so I know this
[ __ ] So what, bro? Come on.
Please. You know what I'm
saying? Yes, some people have
boyfriends, bro, but nowhere near as
much as they say they [ __ ] do. And
the only reason I brought it up is
because I keep going on a channel and
I'm sick of saying it, bro.
about you don't feel a connection. It's
boring now, lad. It's boring now, mate.
We get it. You've got unrealistic
standards. We get it. You like to waste
people's time. Don't [ __ ] moan that
you can't find someone there because you
know what? Yeah. If I go into central
London again and I hear a woman name
moan, where are all the nice guys gone?
I am gonna go up the [ __ ] wall and
I'm gonna get in on that conversation.
Bro, listen. You don't want nice people.
You don't want normal people. Stop
it. You know,
[ __ ] hell. You mean you reply to
negativity. They only reply to
And at the end of the day, yeah, you
weren't interested in the get-go. Like,
you weren't like you, oh my god, I'm not
I'm not going to I'm not going to get
into this anymore, bro. I'm done. I'm
legitimately done. I wish I didn't
message them yesterday saying women are
evil because it gave me mood swings all [ __ ] day,
bro. All day, bro. [ __ ] this. You know
what I'm saying? Yeah. Even look at
Morgan, bro. Three out of 10. Three out
narcissist. Please. Come on, bro. Three
out of 10 narcissist. Come
on. You know.
Yeah. They all
reply. They all
reply when you were
negative. Not two of them. Not too
little immature 18y olds or 19 year
olds. 90% of them. That is a
madness. That is a madness,
bro. That is a madness. I'm done, bro.
I'm done humiliating myself. I'd rather
go to a wh house. I'd rather literally
go to a [ __ ] wh house and be labeled
as a loser than humiliate myself again
and have to deal with these people again
and waste money again. I'd rather go to
a [ __ ] wh
house. I'd rather go to a [ __ ] wh
house down the road for the rest of my
life then entertain any of these clowns again, bro.
Yeah. Know what I'm saying, bro? So
yeah, madness by madness. But yeah, the
the most I said was I hate Will. That's
all I said basically. Yeah.
madness, bro. It I'd rather go to a
house for the rest of my life. You
know, I still miss him. No, I don't gamble no
more. I don't gamble no
more. Yeah. And I think I might do a
video to L J talking about the dating
game. Like that is sickening.
We can't find a nice
guy. Like I would go to America next
week if I knew that [ __ ] her dad
wouldn't call the police. I would go on
his [ __ ] address if I knew he he they
weren't going to call the police. I'd go
there next week. I've got the
money. Yeah, but he's not about it. He's
a [ __ ] bro. That's why he says how
he's going to [ __ ] call the police on
people. Yeah, [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, I was getting some mood swings,
bro. Some mad mood swings yesterday.
Yeah. [ __ ] ruined the [ __ ] party,
bro. Yeah, but leave the [ __ ] old
man. You know what I'm
saying? Leave the [ __ ] old man, bro.
Yeah. Finally recovered from my foot
injury. Yay. It feels a lot better now.
was [ __ ] the most horrendous pain I
ever had in my life. You
know, most horrendous pain, lad.
bro. So, anyways, why does this guy look like me
anyway but with
tattoos? And that's another thing that
only for me cactus. Like, even though I
don't like the [ __ ] bro. Trust me, I
don't like the [ __ ] It's more of the
thing of like, okay, so somebody can be
below average looking, be a terrible
person, and still be able to meet
someone. That tells you what you need to
know as well about the dating game. Cuz
let's not sugarcoat this [ __ ] bro. It's
negative. Let's not sugarcoat this [ __ ]
It is a negative.
Yeah. There's nothing wrong with how I
look. There's nothing wrong with how I
smell. There's nothing wrong with how I
dress. Yeah. Let's not sugarcoat this
[ __ ] You know what I'm saying?
So, I'm done,
bro. Supposed to be get myself out of
[ __ ] trouble. Not get not potentially
get myself in more trouble. Obviously, I
haven't said anything bad to them. I
just said I hate women and that and they
go for drug dealers and [ __ ] But
yeah, I'll be all right anyways. But
yeah, if I had one of these women's
addresses, I would have went on their
door today, bro. I would have actually
went on their door
today. If I had one of these women's
addresses, I would have went on one of
their doors. I'm not even
joking. Like, and that's why I need to
come off this social media and that I
need to um come off social media and and
[ __ ] bro, cuz it will escalate and
escalate and escalate and before you
know it, you end up like [ __ ] Adnab.
And I ain't going to prison for no one,
bro. Because then they get the last
laugh. And yeah, that Yeah, that's the
truth, bro. Some people just are not
meant to. Exactly, bro. It's the way it is.
Yeah. But there is one positive. Like I
said, I learned at
27. That's a positive, is it? I could
have been 32. I could have been 32 years
of [ __ ] age.
I could have been 32 years of age before
I realized this [ __ ] So, at least I'm
still relatively young when I learned
it. You know what I
mean? It was the ghosting and the [ __ ]
up date last month. I was like, "Nah,
that's me. That is me
done." What country would you say this
guy's from? That's Timmyy's thing, by the
way. Oh, she went to Wales. cuz I think she found
someone. She she she found someone else, I
think. So, I'm done anyways in this
country. Imagine that, Stephen. I going
to America next week to go on [ __ ] that squat
floor. Imagine that going all the way
there to go on his [ __ ] door. [ __ ]
mate. That that was going viral, bro.
There ain't no month thing or two
months. Do you understand? Yeah. That
would be [ __ ] that would be ace, bro.
If they were no [ __ ] if they weren't
police informants, bro. That would be ace.
Yeah, probably. Yeah.
Yeah. That would be funny as [ __ ] bro.
But it wouldn't be funny because they're
just going to call the police and that's
free grind down the [ __ ] line. That's
free grind down the [ __ ] drain.
So it wouldn't be funny,
bro. It wouldn't even make sense because
they just got a lawyer. So
yeah. Yeah, bro.
Yeah, he's Mexican, bro. It he's getting my sloppy
seconds. He's getting my sloppy seconds,
lad. Look, bro. Yeah. Still got no tattoos, bro.
Look. Nah, she's found someone else,
mate. No, I got no tattoos on me, bro.
Just I used to get my hair done or whatever,
but none on me, mate.
But yeah, I'm I'm pretty much done in this country,
bro. I might just go to a whole house
today. [ __ ] it. I might just go to a
whole house today,
bro. Nah, I'm joking, bro. My sex drive
is not that high anymore. I kind of lost
my sex drive in the end.
about how people two people don't click.
What that means is when they say two two
people don't click here, it's they've
got Romeo and Juliet in their head. Do
you understand? They've got Romeo and
Juliet in their [ __ ] head. Do you
understand what that means? Like they've
got unrealistic expectations. So, it's
not the fact that you're ugly or you in
fat don't click. They've got unrealistic
standards for when they go on these
dates with people. That's what it is.
It's got to be that, bro. It's got to be
that because how have I got friends all
over the country? How have I got friends
that invite me out all the time who I
make out who I make friends with, bro?
It's because they've got unrealistic
expectations. I know what I'm about,
bro. Yeah. And I'm an outgoing person.
So, you've had it in your head already
that you're not interested. Don't make
it out like you gave it a go. No, bro.
You never like stop
it. Cuz a lot of these women do do these
things intentionally and they they do do it
intentionally. You know, that's
it. You know what I'm saying? [ __ ] off, man.
some inhibitor, you know.
Yeah, bro. But I think this is a wakeup
call to to stop, bro. I think is it?
Yeah. But there's another option. You
could go out every Saturday and just try
to use them for their bodies, but I
don't want nothing to do with them.
That's the difference. They've caused
enough trouble. They've caused enough
trouble in my life. Women,
gambling, enough problems in my life. They've
caused, you know, time and time and and
it's not normal. It's
abnormal. You know what I'm saying? Oh
yeah, if two of them replied back out of
10, I mean, okay, they're just immature.
They're just it's just them. It's not
winning. But the fact that so many
replied back, the same people that
ignored you, that never even gave you a
chance, that doesn't sit right, bro. But
then they moan and win. They can't find a normal
guy. So, or yeah, whatever.
Oh yeah, I'm going Thailand and that's it.
Yeah. So yeah, it started off with the
failed date. Then it was the one that
ghosted me after 3 days. Then it was
just then then I saw that [ __ ]
Morgan. I was like, oh [ __ ] even evil
people can get
relationships, you know? It's like what
the [ __ ] So you know you're just
fighting a losing battle. And if you
know you're fighting a losing battle,
leave. Leave this country. Enough of
like what what is it now, bro? What what
more do you want? Just
leave. Go, man. Do it for your own sake. That's
it. I was living my best life back in
February, March. No women, no. It was
lovely. It was probably about April
time. None of these
problems. Just sat indoors, nice clean
clothes, having food cooked for me.
didn't care about women because I know
that women are evil. Just like money is
the root of all evil, gambling's
evil. No, it doesn't matter, mate. With
my effort, I should be [ __ ]
married. It's like that one that
traveled an hour away. She said, "I
don't feel the vibe." I said, "What do
you mean you don't feel the vibe? You've
literally approached me. You've
literally approached me. What do you
mean you don't feel the vibe? So, they
do do this stuff on purpose. They do do
it on purpose. Trust me, they they they
generally generally a lot of them do do
this on purpose. [Music]
Yeah, she's all right.
Yeah. And then when I went on that date,
I was like, "Oh [ __ ] is this what I'm
in for now? Is this a taste of what I'm
in for this whole
year? Is this Is this Is this what I'm in for?
Yeah, [ __ ] evil they are, mate. I
shouldn't have messaged them. I
shouldn't have messaged them last night, bro.
No, I had two dates. Well, I had two
actually. Um, I had two dates, but
yeah. How long was it failed? Uh, how
it? I think it
was maybe about half
hour talking, opening up. They were
northern. I didn't really like them, but
I thought, "Fuck it. I don't have anything
here." And I was like, "Uh, yeah." It
was the first day. They had to go back
home. I was okay. Uh, when do you want
to see each other
again? She said, "I don't really feel the
vibe." I was like, "Huh? What do you
mean you don't feel the vibe?" I'm
thinking in my head like, "What? You've
approached me. You've traveled over an
hour to come and see me." What? What do
you What do you mean? I was thinking in
my head like I was like,
"Okay, doesn't make any sense." So, they
do this stuff on purpose,
bro. They they they do do this stuff on
purpose. Even though it might not seem
logically logical why they would waste
their own time, but they do because no
normal person would do that. You
wouldn't do that. I wouldn't do that.
Especially if the person's average to
above average looking. No person would do that.
She didn't get turned off by anything,
mate. I know exactly how I acted. I know
exactly how I acted,
lad. I know exactly how I acted and
exactly what I said. So, there was
nothing that could have turned them off.
I'm an adult, mate. I know how to act in
front of people. But anyways, I'm done
with all of this [ __ ]
Anyways, Charles has got a new
girlfriend. Nope, I didn't do the belly
voice. done a normal voice. I'm done
anyways talking about this now. Anyways,
I'm going to Thailand.
So, [ __ ] this. I'm not doing I'm not
doing this [ __ ] for another [ __ ]
year. I'm not doing deal with this [ __ ]
for another year, lad. That's something
I won't be
doing. Nah. No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. No, I don't. I would not approach a
woman who's a 5, six out of 10, meet her
again, and claim that I don't feel the
vibe. No, I wouldn't. No, I would not
because USA is USA Izzy's, right? USA
Izzy is a three out of 10. So, no, I
don't get turned off by a woman that
I've approached. Never. So, cuz it
doesn't it doesn't even make sense cuz
you need to see it how they see it.
Let's just say I'm a five or six out of
10 as an example. Yeah. Let's let's just
say that you're a five out of 10. We're
not going to turn this into a looks
debate. If you met up with a woman that
was a five out of 10 who was outgoing,
you would stay with her. That's the end
of that. So, it's No, no, no, mate. I I
met a three out of 10 the other day and
I ditched her for a different reason.
Yeah. So, I can safely tell you it's
[ __ ] what you're saying. You know
uh so it's not the same way with women.
Women will literally go and meet you
just to pass
time. You know what I'm saying?
like they will they will go out with you
to literally pass time or use you.
That's the only reason they go out with
you to pass time or use you. So
obviously they do do it intentionally
when they don't meet you again. So yeah,
they do they're not looking to date
though. So yeah, she is kind of stinking. Yeah.
Yeah. No, I just don't like
tattoos. No, I just don't like tattoos.
I never have and I never will. So, so
yeah, she's stinking
sad. Yeah. And I'm telling you, Sunny
side up that I still stayed with her
even though she was a three out of 10.
I'm not a three out of 10. I'm like a
[ __ ] five or six or whatever. So why
wouldn't a woman stay with me? That's
the whole point I'm trying to
make. Yeah, that's the point I'm trying to
make. That is the point I'm actually
trying to make to this guy right here.
When I looked at her, I was like,
"Oh, I don't
really like her, man. Like, she looks
different than her
photos." Then we went out. Then she
started coming on to me. Then she showed
me her tits. You know what I'm saying?
And obviously, I don't like the [ __ ]
but the point I'm trying to make is it
takes longer than half an hour to see if
you click with somebody or not. That's
the point I'm trying to
make. It takes a while, bro. You know
what I'm saying? You
understand? So, that's how I know from
experience. You can't know within half
an hour of meeting
someone. So, no, she
didn't. Yeah. So, you understand? Yeah.
Hopefully you understand the point I'm
trying to make.
So, but no, nothing I do puts anyone
off. I know how to
act. I know how to act in front of
people and [ __ ] And And if that was the
case and I'm and I'm turning people off.
Okay. But why are these people replying
to negative messages then? Why are these
people replying to negative messages then? That's it. Yeah.
Yeah, she would never get brave, bro.
She didn't even Bro, I would actually go
there. Listen, bro. If I knew that they
weren't going to call the police, I
would go on the dad's door next week. It
wouldn't be a problem. I've got the
money. I can go over there. You know,
she would never get brave, bro. Do you
think she does that to anyone in
America? No, bro. No. She doesn't do
that to anybody in
America. She never would do it to anyone
in America, anywhere where she
is. She would never get brave, bro.
But yeah, loads of women reply to negativity today. Wow. Wow,
bro. They love negativity. Damn.
Crazy. Oh, guess what? Another thing is
she's looking for a uh roommate.
Sunnyside, she's looking for a
roommate. Oh, you that Rocky Road? Yeah,
she's looking for a roommate, but I'm
the one who's poor. I'm the one who's poor. Yeah.
Okay. Remember that dam was trying to
get cheeky, bro. He get he gets [ __ ] up.
You know, he would get [ __ ]
up. Like, he doesn't understand,
bro. Like, it's not even a
joke. You think just cuz someone wasn't
pro? Please. Please. Who was Who was the
first one that started talking about [ __ ] police? Them, you
know. But yeah, she's I don't like her,
bro. I didn't even think about her. I
just went on their Facebook randomly. It
was just like a random thing. I was
lying in bed. I was like, "Oh, let me go
on their Facebook. See if they put any new pictures up." Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. He will. Yeah. When he knows
he really knows what she's about.
Yeah. Yeah. I had a bad foot injury,
Rocky Boy. It's called Ponail Tens
tentus. [ __ ] It took me like five
weeks to recover, bro. It's there now,
bro. It's there now, bro. But [ __ ]
hell. Talk about pain, bro.
And I even risked my foot injury to go
on these dates with these women just to
waste my time. Just so they could waste
again. Yeah. You can't do that. Yeah.
You can't come back to the same day, bro. [ __ ]
hell. Yeah. Yeah. If you can't come back the same
day, [ __ ] hell. We're all the age
there for a day. They go at the
airport. That's [ __ ] bad, is it, bro?
Wait, Lord. You know, Lord J, that's my
friend. I was cooking up a load of old
Bill yesterday when I cactus. Cooking up
a load of old bill. Yeah,
man. Yeah, they'll be [ __ ] isn't it? They'll be
[ __ ] Yeah, she's a bad person,
bro. We can never go back there in it.
Yeah, never, bro. I was looking up
flight chair last night. It's £420.
to go to Boston and back.
Yeah, you can just stay for a night to
be fair. What have you just stayed for a
night? Make Lord J proud, is in it. Just
stay for a night, in it.
Yeah. All the attention's going to go to
my channel, in
it. Bring back all of these people.
Me and Log are friends. Do you know
that? Me and LJ, we go way
back. Yeah. I used to talk to you when I
used to have a foot
ache. When I used to have a [ __ ] foot ache,
lad. All right. So, shiny side. Are you
rock? Are you rocky
right? Cuz if you are, mate, I need words with you. Yeah.
Yeah. I think you
are. She's [ __ ] stinking,
son. The only good thing she has is tits
and that's it.
That's probably just from [ __ ]
fat. That's probably just from [ __ ]
fat, right? Yeah.
Yeah. Well, I ended up in court, you
know. Uh, Sunnyside. Yeah. I got nicked
and I ended up in
court. Yep. I ended up in court, bro.
I've got to go to trial in three and a half
years. Yep. Three and a half years.
I pled not guilty.
Yeah. Yeah. Won't say too much about it
on here, bro, cuz we know the police
ain't got a [ __ ] life, bro. So, yeah.
Yeah. I went to court and [ __ ] bro.
They're not guilty. They said come back
in three and a half years. By that time,
it will get dropped. Yeah, bro. You need
to stop entertaining people on here,
bro. They're no
glasses. Yep. Yeah. I went to [ __ ]
court because of uh Yeah.
I can tell you off here, but I just said
I do it three and a half years, which
will be dropped in about a year.
So, yeah, that's one of the reasons I
stopped [ __ ] with this uh this place,
bro. If you notice, you don't really see
me on here much. The grassing and that
it can't deal with the
grassing. That's not a bit of me, mate.
That's not a bit of me. So, Yep.
Yeah. Wait a half year though. Okay.
Badness. He's a proper what?
Yeah. Probably a [ __ ] uh artist or
some [ __ ] AZ.
Yeah. Why become
comp? See, they still don't stop.
Um, Rocky Road, they still don't stop.
They still don't stop, bro. They're
obsessed on here, bro. [ __ ] obsessed with me,
bro. Yeah. His name is Grey's Daniel.
Yeah. My head man for going to Thailand, you
know. Yeah. Damon. Yeah. Damon.
Damon. Yeah. His name is Davin
lad. No. Ain't got no
tattoos at all. Don't have any. No plans ever have any? Nope.
Nah. I'm fed up with women. They're all [ __ ]
evil. Stone with him,
mate. Start with him
forever. Thailand, here we
come. Thailand, here we come.
No, I'm going to get with anyone, mate.
I can't stand women.
Yeah. Yeah, all women are the same.
Isn't that mad how they reply to
negativity? I had one trying to be
funny. She's like, "Oh, you're a
landlord and you're asking me out. Um, I
would have gave you my number
if I thought you was going to ask me
out." I was like, "Who do you think you
are? You're in a [ __ ] nightclub
giving your number out and you're trying
to be funny. I I can't stand them,
bro. Honestly, can't stand them.
I notic that more and more and more. Who
the [ __ ] do they think they are? They
need a [ __ ] reality check.
Yeah, I just said that to
her. Yeah, they reply instantly. Yeah.
And another thing is they know that they
can't find normal nice guys, yet the
only guy guys they go for are drug
dealers and scumbags.
That's why in prison men have uh
children, girlfriends, they go for people with tattoos, you
know. Yeah. They're
um they're Yeah, that's Yeah, they've uh
they've got businesses, [Music] kids. Yeah.
Yeah. So yeah, I'm done anyways, bro. So
there's not going to be no Saturday sessions, nothing,
lad. So yeah, I'm done, bro. Cuz I'm
done having the same conversation and
going out every week thinking that
stuff's going to change when in reality
if something was going to change, it
would have changed by now.
At 27 years of age, it would have
[ __ ] changed the same [ __ ] with [Laughter]
Right. I'm good,
man. Yep. I'm done, bro. My dating career is
over. Dating career is over. Yeah.
Yep. It's so
boring. It's so boring.
It's not if you pull over there, you
will pull over there. I'm not lying
about my lifestyle. Who said I'm not a
landlord? You don't know
that. Technically, I live by myself and
technically I work. I'm not going to
tell you what I do cuz too many grasses.
But I'm not telling people cuz they're
the grass on it. I live by myself and I
technically I can work when I want. So
what what can you say to me? See all of
these things. Sunny, do you remember
when people used to say, "Oh, you live
with your mom. You live with your mom."
A woman's not going to go for somebody
that live with their mom. They're not
going to go for somebody that lives with their
mom. They're not going to go for
somebody that lives with their mom. You
move out. Oh, you ain't got a job. You
ain't got a job. You You make money. You
make money. And then there's another
excuse and another excuse and another
excuse. It doesn't matter, bro. I make
money. I get money. It doesn't matter
what I get. I have money. Simple. Money
is not a problem.
Money is not a problem,
bro. It doesn't matter what I get. I
make money, bro. Simple.
Yeah. So, and she's like, "Oh, it's
weird your landlord asking you out." I
was like, "First of all, I'm not your
landlord. Firstly, I'm not your
landlord cuz I don't even know who you
[ __ ] are. And even if somebody was a
landlord, so what landlords can't have
girlfriends? Like they just try to be
smart, but they're really thick. Like if
you notice with these women, they
they'll reply to things that they think
that they can argue against, but they're
really stupid. They actually think
they're intelligent and they're really
thick, you know? Like it's mad. I don't gamble anymore,
bro. I don't gamble anymore.
That's another negative. Women negative,
gambling negative. There's loads of
things that are negative, but dating,
the dating game as a man is one big fat
negative. It's a shame people don't talk
about it as
much. Big fat negatives, mate. Yeah.
Yeah. The best thing to do is just never
deal with women ever again. I think
that's your best bet. That's that's the
that that's what I'm going
with. Yeah. That's that's the route I'm
going to go
down. Yeah. I was thinking s I could go
out every Saturday and spend 70 80 pound
and just be a [ __ ] and just try to use
them for their body. But that means
interacting with them. So why would I
want to interact with
evil, you know? So then I thought, nah,
we'll scrap that idea. Why would I want
to interact with people that are evil,
ignorant? Doesn't make sense.
Yeah. Yeah. I quit dabbling anyways.
But yeah, I quit. I gabbled for like
couple weeks now.
It doesn't matter if there's more people
out. All women are the same. It doesn't
matter if it's winter, spring, fall,
summer. Women are the
same. It doesn't matter what day it is.
The women are just all the same. So it
doesn't matter what day it is. what
month it is, the women are all the same.
So there's there's there's no point. I
am done in this country. I had my friend
say to me yesterday, "Oh, we should go
out." I said, "I'm not going out." And
when I'm in these moods, I won't go out
for like two
months. When I'm in these moods, I will
not go out for like two months. Trust me,
it's negative, bro. So why would you
want to put yourself in a situation
where it's a
negative? The ghosting, the
[ __ ] the the ghosting, the [ __ ]
uh it's not even so much to make many
boyfriends. It's the ghosting them going
on dates to waste your time. Like just
get the point. Leave the country.
There's no one for you. How many clues
do you need? It's like when I used to go
gambling. Yeah. I'd always win money. He
was telling you something. Leave this
country. Leave this country.
Yeah. So, he was telling me to leave the
country. Basically, he was telling me,
"Leave, leave, leave, leave. You're
winning all this money. Leave, leave,
leave, leave. There's no one for you
here. Leave, leave,
leave." So, it was telling me that I
needed to leave this
country cuz I'd win like every week.
Leave, leave, leave. And now, even now,
I'm still getting chances. Leave, leave,
leave. You want another four grand?
Leave this country, bro. There's nothing
[ __ ] for you
here. Oh, someone got me bad cuz I was
speaking [ __ ] about the [ __ ] casino.
How bad is this
family? No, I don't really have
kebabs. Yeah, it
was. But yeah, I don't want anything to
ever do with women ever
again. I was getting such bad mood
swings today. I was going to end up
going and doing some of them, but it's
not even a joke. This is why you need to
come on social media and just stay away from
women, you know? It's the same with
staying on here because, bro,
like it is annoying. It was winding me
up. Like, I've just woke up. Yeah. And
these women are replying all of a sudden
to yesterday's negative messages. Hold
on. You didn't want to know when I
weren't writing negative things. All of
a sudden, you're replying, "Fuck
off." You know what I'm
saying? Bit evil, mate. When I see
different, I'll say different.
So yeah. Yeah, you're still
alive. Go for walks, go swimming.
Uh channel, get food cooked for me. It
might sound boring to you. It might
sound boring to you, mate. I gave up for
seven weeks and I had the best time of
my life being stable. And as soon as I
start getting with women again, the same
problems occur. The same problems occur.
You're stable. You don't understand.
Nothing beats being stable. It might
seem boring to you, but guess what? It's
boring hearing about make load of make money
boyfriends, you know? So, it depends how
you [ __ ] look at
it. I gave up for seven weeks. I
thought, well, wait, [ __ ] this. You know
what I'm saying? Yeah.
Cuz it's the same [ __ ] that gets boring, you
know. Boyfriends, the ghosting, the the
the the the same evil women. It's boring
as [ __ ] It's so
boring. It is so boring.
Nah, the advice is leave this
country. Yeah, the advice is the advice
is leave this country. That told me a
lot, you know.
When I had loads of women reply today,
that told me a lot. That told me a lot,
bro. If they didn't reply, then I was
like, maybe I'll go out next week. Maybe
I would have went out next week, but I
was like, nah, that's me. That just goes
to show how sick in the head they are.
Then they reply to
negativity, but [ __ ]
ignore positive messages. Noble
Yeah. No, I'm good, mate. Yeah. Yeah. This far
Yes. What's the solution?
Eh. Yeah. Reply to negativity.
One second, lad.
Yeah, they're [ __ ] bro. One second.
Yeah, they're [ __ ] evil. These women,
bro. They're proper proper
evil. Who's a one out?
These women are ignored.
Yeah. So, why are women so evil anyways?
Why are they all the same? Huh?
Yeah, sorry about that,
bro. Nah, I'm done in this
country. I am done in this country.
There's no more advice. I'm not
listening to it. I'm done. 100%
done. Done with women. Done in this country. Simple.
Yeah. Yeah. All women are the same. I've
been saying it for years, mate. Since I
was about 17, 18. I used to always say
women are the same. Women are the same.
People used to say, "Oh, no they're not.
You don't know women." I [ __ ] do,
mate. I had a little boredom with him. I
[ __ ] do though. They're all the
same. Yeah. All the [ __ ]
same. Every single and last one of them. up. Yeah. [Music] Yeah. Five.
street. No, I wouldn't do it. That's
weird. Yeah. No more. I've got a
boyfriend. No more fake
boyfriends. A good thing, eh?
just did it,
bro. I'm coming off social media as well. Yeah.
Yeah, I'd rather be bored, mate, than
hear about make believe boyfriends and have negative
experiences. Negative experiences with women.
Boring me a boring
me. How do I know they have make believe
boyfriends? Oh, here we go. Same
question. H same
question. Same question. How do I know
they have makebelieve
boyfriends? Um, how do I know they've
got make believe boyfriends? Maybe
because 80% of men are single and that they
struggle. Maybe because they're in a
nightclub till 7:00 in the morning and
would their boyfriends really be letting
them out clubbing until 7:00 in the
morning whilst they're sat home eating
popcorn watching Netflix by themselves.
The answer to that is literally
no. Of course they've got makebelieve
boyfriends. The maths don't add
up. Yeah. It doesn't it doesn't even make
sense, you know? Why are they never with
their boyfriends in a club in a Weather
Spoons? Is that the kind of stuff that couples
do? I don't know, bro. I don't give a
[ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ] I don't care.
I don't compare myself to other people.
I don't give a
[ __ ] bro. I don't give a [ __ ] how you
got a [ __ ] I don't give a
[ __ ] They don't have boyfriends.
Literally, the people that say they've
got boyfriends, only three out of 10
actually have boyfriends. Only three out
of 10 have boyfriends.
Three out of 10. I say about three out
of 10. What would you say, Steven
Howard? The ones that say they've got
boyfriends, three out of 10.
Definitely. The the the the maths don't
add up. How all these men could be
single. How all these men can be
struggling, but yet all of these women
have boyfriends in a nightclub that
closes at 7:00 in the morning. 6 to
about 7:00 in the [ __ ] morning. Nah,
bro. Doesn't add up.
I need to go piss anyways.
Sorry, but I went to uh I just went to
go piss. So, yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm coming off of social media
anyways after this live stream.
Yeah. So, yeah, you won't be see me for
a little while, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, you bet me £100. Why would I want
to bet you £100, bro? £100 is nothing to
me. And I'm not your mate either. So
don't call me your mate, cuz I'm not
your mate. And I'll never be your mate.
So don't call me a
mate. I will never be your [ __ ]
mate. Nah, mate. You can go and watch
law. I'm done, bro. I need a break from
this social media and this this women
[ __ ] It's too
negative. I can't believe how many
replied back to negativity. [ __ ]
hell. Tells you all you need to know.
I called somebody a child molester and I
said women are evil. Hopefully I don't
get nicked. Nah, I don't think so.
Nowadays you got to be very careful with what you
say. You need to be very careful with
what you say nowadays. But yeah, I don't think that's
enough. You know how people like calling
the police and it hopefully not. So
yeah, no grasses mate these days. I think so. Hopefully not. Imagine. Yeah.
Maybe go swimming on Saturday. Maybe.
Yeah, I was going to go Blackpool the
other day, Steven Howard. Where was it?
Uh, yesterday I was going to go
Blackpool, but my foot weren't 100%. I
was just going to just [ __ ] off there,
but nah, there's no point. No point
wasting money in this country. There's just no
point anything anymore in this
country. Yeah, I was going to just [ __ ]
off and just do some madness, but nah,
just going to make money now and leave in two
months. Yeah, pretty much.
Yep. social media for a bit. But do you
know what? When I was in Newcastle, I
never had these problems that I do in
London. I always had [ __ ] flock to me
when I was in Newcastle. I found it a
lot easier than here.
Yeah. Never ever once when I went I
never ever once went to Newcastle and
pulled. That's the only place I found it
a little bit easier to be fair. Yeah. Yeah, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Uh cuz I live in
London and London they're all stuck up. So yeah. So
yeah, I like women. I think they're I
just think they're evil. personally.
Yeah. No, I'm not moving to Newcastle.
I'm going to
Thailand. No, I'm going Thailand.
No, I'm going to try that.
Hey, what is
I won't be out next week
either. Yeah, I won't be out next week
week. Stop making up stuff on my
channel, bro, cuz I'm not going to reply
it. Stop writing stupid stuff on my
channel trying to create drama cuz it's
just going to get
ignored. Making up stupid stuff to try
and get a reaction and an explanation.
Bro, don't do it on my channel.
Oh, and that's another reason why I
leave as well, cuz these people don't leave you
alone. No, I see
that. I'm just going to delete these combos,
lad. I'm just going to delete these
combos. I don't want to look at them.
They just piss me off, these women. I'm
just going to delete the cop. Call it quits. [ __ ] it. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, just delete the convers. I'm just
going to have a co and ghost sleep and that's it.
Chilling trying to say I can't leave the
country for 3 years. Where does it say I
can't leave the country for 3 years?
What bail condition do I have that can't
that makes me not be able to leave the country?
Yeah. So, I won't be out next
week. Anyways, uh I won't be out next
week. I' got my original license as
well. Steven Howard, I needed it for
something. Not going to say what, but
that's made up,
bro. A bunch of people that ignore you
then reply to negativity. [ __ ] that,
bro. [ __ ] that. I think it's been like a
build up like over the past month of why
you should just completely give up with
dating. I'd rather go to our [ __ ]
house and paid and [ __ ] humiliate
myself. Yeah, I have boyfriends. Yeah,
they got boyfriends, but they would have
come until 4:00 in the morning.
But uh they're in the club till 4:00 in
the morning, but all their boyfriends
are in their house eating popcorn,
watching Netflix while their bisses is
slagging it about in the
club. Yeah. Makes sense, doesn't
it? That makes so much sense, isn't it?
Yeah. Yeah. They've all got boyfriends,
but yet they're in a club till 7:00 in morning.
Yeah. That makes sense.
Yeah, that makes sense, bro.
It's not just England. It's America.
It's Canada. It's France. It's any any westernized place.
Oh, it's any westernized place, man.
It's any westernized
place. They're all [ __ ]
That's what they are. They're just
[ __ ] I just can't believe how so
many replied when I was
negative. So, what do you think will
happen if you go
outside? I've got a boyfriend. I've got
a boyfriend. I've got a boyfriend. I've
got a boyfriend. I've got a boyfriend.
I've got a boyfriend. [ __ ] all that,
bro. Give me a [ __ ] headache. I only
woke up a [ __ ]
headache this morning, bro. about
that. Yeah. Love this country,
right? Yeah. It's drilled into them.
They're like NPCs.
Yeah. Yeah. It's like It's like they're
NPCs. It's literally all they ever
saying my boy. Yeah, it's boring. It's
like it must be Yeah, exactly.
But don't miss this country anyways. So that's it.
Yeah, I don't feel the vibe. That's
because you're not interested to begin
with. That's not because somebody has
said something wrong. It's just them not
being interested and them being [ __ ] as
usual. That's what it is, you know.
So, yeah, they've got a boyfriend in
their club in 5:00 in the morning, 6:00
morning. Not sure, bro. Quite hot.
Not sure exactly
what they've got boyfriend until like
6:00 in the
morning. They ain't got
boyfriend usual initiative. They don't have
boyfriends, you know. Wait
later. I can't wait.
Oh, have some hot and just go to sleep.
My social anyway.
Yeah, they don't have boyfriends, bro. I [ __ ]
know. I assumed I was uh negative. Crazy.
Yeah, I was having a sh. Is it still
bleeding my ass? Hopefully
not. Yeah, my ass is still bleeding,
man. That's quite concerning.
I was quite concerned with it. Must have piled or
something. Maybe all that hot
food. You got one [ __ ] injury and
something else comes up. [ __ ]
s. One second.
Ice. See, my fruit's actually better
now. So, I could actually go
out, you know.
I'm going to call on you.
So what's the chance of USA
getting what's the chance of USA a talk
Hey. Yeah. What's the chances?
Huh? My foot feels a lot better, mate.
That [ __ ] pain was [ __ ] stinking.
That pain was [ __ ] stinking,
mate. It was. It's [ __ ] painful,
bro. I was waking up at 4 in the
morning, Steven Howard. And my foot was
bam, bam, bam, bam, bam, bam. It was [ __ ] throbbing,
[ __ ] It was [ __ ] throbbing.
Frobing, frobing, frobing, frobbing,
throbbing. I said, "What's the chances of
uh what's the chance of USA? Is he getting
pregnant?" No, it's better now. I had an
injury on my
foot and now 5 weeks later. It's
better. Uh, it was just some foot
injury. Yeah, it was [ __ ] stinking. It
was I was walking on a limp. I was
actually walking on a [ __ ] limp, bro. For weeks.
Yeah. Nah, bro. Nah.
So yeah, I don't know what I'm doing
Saturday. Probably just chilling. Maybe go swimming. Yeah. Yeah.
probably. Well, there is no USA [ __ ]
PJ, bro. The
[ __ ] Oh, it's nice,
bro. Be funny, won't it? It'd be
funny. I don't care. I don't like the
[ __ ] bro. I really don't like the
[ __ ] If I did, I would say I actually
do. But I [ __ ] don't like the [ __ ]
bro. I don't like that evil [ __ ] Yeah. Uh maybe
maybe she better want to do it quickly
cuz she's running out of time is it?
She's running out of
time. So she best want to get on that ASAP.
Got a bit of
flare. Yeah, most of the women reply to
that message. Huh. Strange. Strange. That stranger. Yeah, man. bro. Yeah. Anyways, got
eyebrow. Don't know. Don't
care. Don't care about
her. Don't like
her. What do you think of Body Man and
uh Body Man and Daddy J?
Yeah. Yeah. I'm just on Reddit, lad. I'm
Reddit. I can't believe how how much
women reply to negative
messages. It's not even like it's two
out of six. If it was like two out of
six, I'd be okay. Well, they're just
they're just [ __ ] up in
it. But it it it shows it is a gender
issue when most of them have replied
back. Why are they replying back to
negativity? They've ignored your normal
message. Should they be blocking
you? [ __ ] idiots. Can't stand them,
mate. Can't stand
them. No one would have thought. No one Yeah. Oh,
[ __ ] USA is looking for roommate Steven
Howard. She's got to be skinned it.
She's got to be [ __ ] skint.
She is definitely skinned, mate. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah. But yeah, I was going to go
Blackpool yesterday just last minute
just go up there, but yeah, the foot weren't 100%.
So, could do it next week if I wanted
to, but I just don't want to do anything
for a little while, bro.
I get more depressed in the summer, I
reckon. Something like that.
Yeah. Too many bad experiences, eh?
Yeah. It's nice. just lying in
bed. Yeah. She was looking for a
roommate. A roommate back in a room to
share a room with or an
apartment. So, she obviously doesn't have
money, does she?
Yeah, since I've started this whole
dating thing, all I've done is been
tormented. If you think about it, all
I've done is been
tormented. So, you just give up that it
giving up's the best way. It's the best alternative.
One second, bro.
Sorry about that, bro. So, who's
potless? Who's potless, bro? You talking
about body man. What's [Laughter]
Yeah. You see the doggy? What doggy?
boy? Oh, king. Yeah. Uh, yeah.
Yeah. USA. Yeah. He must be potless. If
they're together and they can't afford a
[ __ ] flat or a house, they must have
nothing. Yeah, I'm on Reddit, bro. Yeah. No.
No. Where would you rather go? Thailand or
America? Thailand, bro. Thailand all the way. Eh.
Definitely, bro. What about
you? I'd say
Thailand. Asia is nice, isn't it?
So what would you pick? America or Thailand? [Laughter]
What did you pick? Can you hear
me? Would you pick Thailand or America? One second.
Otherwise, I'll be back later. Yeah.