Yep. Another time already quarter to [ __ ] one. Oh
god. Have I got to [ __ ] go out and
[ __ ] prove it again to this [ __ ]
woman how approaching don't [ __ ]
work. I said, "Okay, in two weeks, two
to three weeks, I will go out again and prove it.
I will [ __ ] prove
it about the make believe boyfriends and
all of that [ __ ] I'll prove it. Just
give me a couple of weeks, mate. I don't
I don't do this [ __ ] every week now.
Yeah, give me a couple of [ __ ] weeks.
Yeah. God, man.
I was trying to explain to the [ __ ] as
well is that you are negative because of
your negative experiences. It doesn't
seem to it doesn't seem to process in
their mind, does
it? It's as if it doesn't suit them, you
know, as it doesn't suit them. It
doesn't suit them to believe it or want
to believe it. It don't suit them. Mhm. Literally,
bro. You guys can't
give. The weather's actually better
today though, to be
fair. Oh, the weather is better today, lad.
Stop calling yourself a
manta. And I saw that Reddit thing.
That's not even me. So try hard again
trying to stalk people because that
weren't even me. So try again and stop
calling yourself a
manta. Repeaters go back to law J. I
told Steven Howard, mate. I told you
Steven Howard. Yeah, I told Steven
Howard that. We're done with these
little weirdo self-reflectors. We're not
entertaining him. And if you are going to stalk
someone actually stalk the right [ __ ]
person cuz that ain't even me. So yeah, crack on.
Anyways, but it's nice to know that
you're still trying to stalk me on
Reddit. Do you know how many subreddits there [ __ ]
are, you know?
Stop calling yourself a bunch as well.
Go self-reflect on another channel. I
told you this is a channel about [ __ ] football bets.
N I was actually thinking before I went
to sleep yesterday, why do you even
reply to these weirdos?
Like just just keep letting them be
obsessed with you every day. You know,
that's all you got to do. You don't even
need to reply to these little keyboard
warriors. These all weirdos, lad.
Yeah, that's it, bro. You know what I'm
saying? That's all you got to do, man.
You know, let them keep making posts on
you and we're better than them, bro.
Like [ __ ] them. Absolutely [ __ ] them, you
know. So yeah, [ __ ] them,
bro. Let them keep being obsessed and
and and you know, that's that's cool, bro. It's
fine. It's absolutely fine with
me, you know, cuz I I was saying to this
Terry yesterday. Yeah. And it actually
really made me think. He was like that
they're ruining your life. But they're
not ruining my life though, are they?
Because everything that they've tried,
they have failed. And then I realize
you're just going back and forth and
back and forth with keyboard lawyers. It's [ __ ]
pointless. You know, like at the end of
the day, if they keep being obsessed
with you on
YouTube despite getting despite not
getting a reaction, they're the obsessed
ones. They're the obsessed ones. If they
keep coming going on YouTube despite not
getting a reply, making community posts
and [ __ ] videos, they're the ones
that are obsessed with you and will
prove it. And that's it without even
mentioning any names. That's it, bro. No
point. There's no point with these
little weirdos, you know? They've got
nothing new to say anyways. I just block the
self-reflectors. I I just block the
self-reflecting bastards. I bro, it's no
biggie to me, you know?
I said to this woman, I'll go out again
in two, three weeks. I'll go out again
weeks and I'll prove it to you. It doesn't doesn't
work. One second. He's just bursting for
a bit. Hold on.
So yeah, bro. That's what I'm saying. These little
weirdos, they just just let them
self-reflecting. Let them keep self
reflecting their whole life. They've got
nothing to their life but doing block
anyways. Same [ __ ] They've been doing
it for years. They've been doing it for
years as well.
Hopefully this football bet comes in
anyways, bro. But yeah. Yeah. Same
mentally ill people, same
self-reflectors. Yeah, that's really
really not going to [ __ ] dissolve. But
yeah, same self-reflecting bastards.
You know how it is, isn't it? Same self-reflectors, same
repeaters. There's no point even [ __ ]
It's the same three people that's been
doing it for about 10
years. Well, I know that because they
were on here before I was on here, you
know, and then they tried to stalk me on
Instagram and tried to stalk me on
Reddit, but guess what? That Reddit post
wasn't even me. So, get it right. You
know how many subreddits there are? I
don't even post on that subreddit
anymore because of you [ __ ]
stalkers. You know what I'm saying?
Bye-bye, [ __ ] Yes. Yeah. Go call
yourself a M somewhere else, you little
sad bastard. Yeah, that wasn't even me.
I don't even I don't even post on that
subreddit. But anyways, crack
on because a you don't know where I live
and a you don't know nothing. So, keep
trying. You are the skin. That's why you
keep bringing up money every day cuz you
are skin. Now go self-reflect on another channel. Bye-bye
now. Anyways, we're not talking about
these little mongos anymore. We're not
giving these people attention. [ __ ]
them, bro. Nah, we're not giving these
little skin reflectors
attention. Who's with me? Steven Howard. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, bro.
100%. Yeah, I think I'm gonna go KFC
later. Yeah, I think I'm gonna go KFC later,
Dad. Every time you order McDonald's,
it's always [ __ ] cold, though. It's
cold. Always [ __ ]
cold. It is literally always cold. Yeah,
man. These all self
reflectors. Oh, one second,
bro. These little skin. It's actually a madness, bro. Like Uh yeah.
Yeah. Why can't I? Because they're
because they're I don't know who you
are, Buzzy. Who the [ __ ] are you, man?
It's because there's too many stuck up
[ __ ] in this country. Too many stuck
up [ __ ] Um people with too many
options thinking that they're better
than you, man. But we'll go out again in
maybe 3 weeks or something and I'm going
to prove to this woman like, "Bro, we're
negative because of negative
experiences." But it's like, no matter
how many times you say you're negative
because of negative experiences, they
still don't seem to understand it. So
that's why I don't bother arguing. I
just said to this woman, I'm going to go
out in three weeks and I'm going to show
you what I experienced. You
know, don't know who you are, where
you're from, but yeah, I'm not
entertaining these little self-reflectors anymore.
So that's it, bro. They're not even
getting a reaction. Not going on any of
their channels. [ __ ] them. They're
weirdos. Stalking my Instagram. [ __ ]
weird, bro. So [ __ ] weird, lad.
What's happening? Nothing, bro. I just
done a football bet trying to pay for
you know what. Yeah, I done a football
bet cuz I'm going to try and pay for you know what
delayed and that we just give up in this
country and [ __ ] So, Oh, that's a nice
comic. You're such a nice, caring,
respectable, reasonable, down to earth
man. No one no idea why you can't get a
girlfriend because there are too many
stuck up [ __ ] in this country. It's that
simple. You wouldn't know unless you
deal with them. When I go out again in 3
weeks to a month, I'm going to show this
woman exactly what I experienced. You
know, don't try and tell me that I'm
negative. You know, we're negative
because of [ __ ] them. One second. Let
me call this person on Snapchat. Mix my
mic when I
So yeah, that's it, bro. And um yeah, we
and there's a change to this channel as
well. We're not entertaining mongos
anymore. We're not entertaining these
[ __ ] self-reflections anymore. Every
time they come on, they get banned.
They're not getting brought up. Not on my
channel. So that's it.
Yeah, they were I mean they stalked me
on everything. Instagram, they tried to
stalk me on Reddit. Even that wasn't
even though that wasn't even me that
wrote on Reddit, but they stalk me on
Reddit. They stalk me on Instagram. They
stalk me everywhere. I live in their
minds. This is exactly why whenever I
meet a woman, Stephen Howard, I
never Instagram because of these little
stalkers, these little weirdos.
That's why it's
all always WhatsApp so these people can
never fire them. these people actively
stalk my Instagram and I don't know how
these weirdos do
it because none
of as far as the
in the same people Instagram they
contacted that from like it's just
weirdo weirdo weird freaky ass behavior
but Instagram are probably worth to make
your Instagram because I don't know how
these people stalk Hey. So,
yeah. M. Yeah, they're all they're all
upset. Yeah, it is what it is.
They're obsessed with me, bro. They
stalk my [ __ ] Instagram as well. This
is why I never add women on Instagram
ever because of these weirdos. Like
people that I meet because of these little
weirdos. See if these pe these people
will always try to [ __ ] things up for
you. These little virgins
like you made money on YouTube. They try
to [ __ ] it up by trying to get your
money stopped. uh women that you've met retry to
[ __ ] things up for you in any way they
like when the last time they found the
[ __ ] someone's Instagram, bro. Come
on. And and the thing me I I'll say that
to you now. They don't ruin my life.
They don't piss me off. They don't
affect me one little bit. But I'm saying
what they do is weird. That's what I'm
saying. I said like, you know, being on
the phone to somebody for over an hour
that you don't know, it's weirdo
behavior. And anyone that you know
knows, you know, that's normal would
know that. Like, so he doesn't have
better things to do. He's a little
virgin. What would he have better to do?
He's a little virgin. He's never been
laid. His girlfriend don't have sex with
him. All he does all day is obsess over
me and my sloppy seconds. That's all he
has in his life. That's [ __ ] mad. You
know, that's why I done like some I done
a football bet today and went for a walk.
I'm going in a bit anyways,
bro. I'm going in a bit cuz I need to go
get some food. I'm [ __ ]
starving. You know what I'm saying? So
that's it, bro. It's [ __ ] up. Weirdos. Absolute
weirdos. Absolute weirdos with nothing
in life but
obsession. [ __ ] madness, isn't it?
That's why I just block them. Block
them. Don't go on their channel. You
don't need to make a new You don't need
to go on your new YouTube channel. [ __ ]
them, bro. Let them be obsessed every
day. It's all they [ __ ] have. You
know, you put new content on this
channel and you ignore them. It will
kill them. It will [ __ ] kill them,
bro. Like, I could actually withdraw out
a load of money right now and show
people. But I said Steven Howard that I
will never show these people money ever
again whether I had it or whether I
didn't have it because that's just part
of their autism and I'm not involving
myself with their autistic little games you
know these all their autistic little
weirdo games you know so you know that's
going on their [ __ ]
level what I was thinking of doing right
is is going to like a bar right
connecting to the Wi-Fi and just sending
it just to piss these people off.
Approaching these women like Sean would
have a meltdown. He'd be like,
"No." He got her number. How's he
kissing her? I can't do that. That'd be
good content on a Saturday. Just stick
the Wi-Fi on. You know, everyone's got
Wi-Fi nowadays, and there's one place I
go to which you're not going to know,
and it's got Wi-Fi just to just to piss
them off. Like, you can do things like
that just to piss them off, you know?
It'd be funny as well. They be like,
"No, I can't do that." So PJ can't do
that. It's funny as [ __ ] is it? We
should do it though. It be It be It'll
be class, bro. It'll be class A in it.
You know, just to piss these little mongos
off, you know? He's always been a little
virgin. Before I even had sex the normal
way, bro. He used to try and tell me
right that I didn't sleep with escorts
when I was 17, 18. He used to say, "Oh,
they ask for ID." He always used to deny
anybody else having sex cuz he's a
little virgin himself. Even though he's
got a girlfriend, he's still a virgin
and he will die a virgin. It doesn't
matter how many relationships he's been.
He done it before um either of us even
met normal women. He used to have this
thing about his erectile dysfunction
little dick that's never been up no one.
And believe you me, it ain't been up no
one, mate. You know, because if somebody
is spending all this life on you, all
their life on YouTube, obsessed over
you, mate, that's not looking right in a
relationship. That is not looking.
So, it is not looking right. It doesn't
even need to. It could just be in
London. Just go to a bar in London and
just I got the number. Just like that,
bro. Even if they don't reply, do
something that his anxiety will never
allow him to do, you
know. But I mean, I think it's a lesson
to be fair. Don't meet somebody with
autism. Do not meet somebody with
autism. And that's that's it, bro.
for you this kind of little bit,
bro. Yeah, just do something like that.
Um, just go to like a bar. It doesn't
even need to be out of London. Just just
something like that cuz obviously it
kills him you seeing you with women
because he can't get a woman. That's why
he's with a [ __ ] and all of the stuff
that I say. I'm not contradicting
myself. I'm just I just don't I'm just
not scared to say what I think about
women being [ __ ] I'm not a white guy.
I'm not a white light, so nothing I'd
say contradicts. I'll tell you that
women are not [ __ ] Women are evil. You
know, I don't give a [ __ ] because I know
they are. But I, you know, I can still
do these things to piss this little [ __ ] off.
So, they're so obsessed. Look what
they've done. They've tried to get my
money stopped. You know, they've done
[ __ ] madnesses. And guess what? They
failed every single time. How bad is that?
single time. But it's mad how they stalk
me on Instagram and Reddit and they
stalk me on the on the wrong subreddits
as well and they think they know things
and it's me and it isn't even [ __ ]
me. Yeah, that one in the Manchester
one, the Manchester one was
me. I've never known somebody to be so
obsessed with your sloppy seconds. I've
never ever known it. I've always thought
like you would not get with somebody
because they they're someone sloppy
seconds. [ __ ] hell. Is that what
happens? I think his autism is so bad,
Joe, that he shouldn't be in public. He should be
incarcerated or given the death penalty
cuz that autism is is off the [ __ ]
scale, bro. That's worse than Timmy.
I've never met anything like it. And
I've met a lo I've met loads of people
that's got autism. It's not even that
rare. And I'd never known anything like
it. It wasn't me. That's what I'm trying
to say. It wasn't even me. That wasn't
even [ __ ] me. I don't even post on
that subreddit anymore. I don't even
[ __ ] post on that subreddit anymore,
bro. So, how the [ __ ] could that be
me, you know? I I I used to I stopped
[ __ ] post on that because of these
stalkers. Cuz I know these people stalk
me on Reddit. I know they stalk me on
[ __ ] They stalk me on madnesses, bro.
That's why I don't I don't I don't post
on that subreddit no more. That's not even me
either. That's not me either.
So, and another thing is why are they
trying to stalk you on Reddit every
single day? That's that that's more of a
question. Hold on a minute. That's not the
thing. Why are they trying to stalk
you on Reddit every single day? That's a
good question. You know what I'm saying?
Every single day. Why are they stalking
you on Reddit? Every single [ __ ] day
they're stalking you on
Reddit and then they're getting even the wrong
subreddits. I I'm not going to tell you
the subre Reddits I post on now because
of these little stalkers, but yeah,
there's millions of subreddits. Well, I
say that as a figure of speech, but
yeah, like it's it's it's mad, bro.
That's why I I I stopped posting on that
subreddit. I used to just message people
because of these little stalkers.
Because of these little stalkers, can't
add women on Instagram because of these
stalkers, you know. So, whenever a woman
would say to me, "Oh, I've got
Instagram." I said, "I don't do
Instagram." Well, there's a few reasons.
A, um, it's not personal enough. They
might not get a message. And B, cuz
these stalkers, you know, so that's why
it's WhatsApp. WhatsApp or it's nothing
delayed cuz WhatsApp's encrypted. These
little stalkers can't get hold of them.
These little stalkers can't get [ __ ]
hold of them. Do you know what I'm
saying? I would I would message that
country in Manchester telling them about
Sean, but I don't care about them. I've
never even met them. I haven't even met
them, bro. I don't really care. Only an
obsessed autistic stalker cares. I don't
care. But and then you're going to say,
"Oh, well, why why why was you so pissed
off? Why was you so pissed off? I was
pissed off cuz it was an amalgamation of
people within that week [ __ ] me
around and I had enough of it, you
know." But I could I could just go on a
new number now and show that. But why
would I care? I'm not
autistic. I can just talk to somebody
else and just and get someone else's
number. I'm not an autistic little bongo
that has to stalk people that other
people been talking to and go on the
phone to them for over an hour. That's
[ __ ] weirdo [ __ ] I can't remember
the last time I was on the phone to a
woman for a [ __ ] for 10 minutes, let
alone a [ __ ] hour. It's a [ __ ] madness.
really really really really is a madness
if there was to ever be one, bro. I swear to
God. Oh, one sec.
And look at these people. Like, they're
so obsessed. Like, I'm even reading this
thing here on this Reddit and it ain't
even me. I'm reading the comments. God,
they're obsessed. [ __ ] hell, bro.
God, they're so
obsessed. It's a [ __ ] autistic
community, bro. They're [ __ ] weirdos.
It's like they think they know
everything and that's why they [ __ ]
your B um you know that's why they
[ __ ] try to stop your [ __ ]
benefits. Bro, when I when I got that
call from this [ __ ] person saying,
"Oh, we heard that you're sublet. We
heard that you're sublet." I was like,
"Well, you want to see my bank
statements? Don't call up my phone
trying to tell me I'm done this done
that, you know, because of some obsessed
little weirdo, you know, [ __ ] making
up fake stuff. Like, these people are so
weird." And it goes to show that these
people I've just I've just read
comments. These people have got no job.
They ain't got nothing in their life.
Look, why they're so obsessed with other
people. Other people, whether they've
got money, whether they don't have
money, why are they so obsessed? It's
[ __ ] weird, bro. It is so [ __ ]
weird. Weird. Obsessed little virgins.
Like, that's not even me being
triggered. That's me telling you straight,
bro. You know what I'm saying,
lad? Uh, but yeah, I've got a lot of
stalkers. A lot. And it goes to show
that they got nothing in their lives for
them for them to do this, right? The
Instagram [ __ ] the thinking that they
found me on Reddit. It goes to show
you've got something they don't have. And
we looks probably not saying I am
good-looking because I'm just I just
look like an old person more money than
them. It's got to be something that's
that's not right for them to sit on
YouTube all day doing this as a
full-time job. There's got to be
something not right in their lives. Even
though they claim that, you know,
they're married, they're this, they're
that, and you're this, and you're that,
well, something's not clicking. It's
like trying to
um flick a light, but the light's not
flicking. There's There's got to be
something seriously seriously wrong with
these people. I'm telling you,
bro, I've got three people, minimum,
that stalk my every move. My Instagram,
they refresh [ __ ] Reddit pages.
That's why I don't post on subreddits no
more, you know. I have to message people
privately. I literally have to message
people privately now. Are you some other
random subreddit because of these
people? Because of these little like, do
they want my ass or something? Like, if
you want my ass, just say you want my
ass, you know? Just say that you you
want my bum crack. If you're a closeted
homosexual, there's nothing wrong with
being gay, you know? As long as as long
as you're open about it, you know, as
long as you are open about it. You know what I'm
saying? And that's
it. And that's it. It's like it's it's
you have something that these people
don't have. I'm telling you, bro. It's
got to be. It's got it's got to be, bro.
this sh just [ __ ] Jamie Thompson
[ __ ] Peter Griffin looking [ __ ] You
know there there's something that like
you that you have that they they're
missing that they want. I'm telling you.
I'm telling you it is. I'm telling you
it is. Cuz I don't know. Yeah. Many of
Well, I'm assuming you know people
that's watching this have been in love.
Have you ever ever acted like this
towards somebody that you actually met
and you actually loved every day? No. So
what the [ __ ] bro? They must be gay for
you. They must be closeted homosexuals.
And and that's probably why they say
that you're by That's probably why they
say that you're gay because they're gay
themselves. Just another form of
projection as as it stands. You know
what I'm saying,
bro? Is literally
it. And that is literally it. Anyways,
I'm gone now. Yeah. I'm going to go KFC
and yeah, I'll be live
later in a Bizzle. Yeah, enough about
like these [ __ ] weirdos. I'll be back later anyways.