[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] Reddit, bro. I
swear to God. Stupid [ __ ]
Reddit. Stupid people on [ __ ] Reddit,
bro. Oh my god. They literally ignore
stuff and and make up stuff that suits
themselves to victimize women. I've
noticed that. That's what they do on this Reddit.
They literally make up stuff to
victimize victimize women. That's
literally what they do. They make up
stuff. That's literally what they
[ __ ] do. They
literally make up stuff to suit
themselves. I've noticed that with this
[ __ ] Reddit. That's literally what
they do on this Reddit.
They very tough to victimize women. Oh,
I see the positives in women. There's no
positive women. They're all
saying one of them. The positives in
women. They're not. They're saying
idiot. [ __ ] it.
idiots. They victimize
themselves. They have to be a victim.
Yeah. [ __ ] idiots,
man. They're screwing no women. They're
[ __ ] all evils. I've been saying it
from day off.
I' been saying this [ __ ]
day all the same
people are [ __ ] ready. Yeah. Yeah.
They just get away with
everything. They get away with [ __ ]
I say they get away with murder. They
even get lesser
sentences. That's another thing. They
have actually have got away with murder
when they I've been watching it. They
actually get less sentences. They get
away with [ __ ]
everything. They get away with being
[ __ ] and everyone defending them,
victimiz victimiz themselves. They
actually do get away with murder
actually. They actually do get away with
murder because they have to get
necessities. Yeah. [ __ ] evil. [ __ ]
Yeah. They [ __ ] evil evil bastards.
You know, and I said to this person on
Reddit here, and this is what I mean by
they they always have to be a victim. I
said, "Oh, you're struggling on you're
struggling in dating, are you?" I said,
"Oh, yeah. I'm I'm struggling. I gave
up. I gave up for two months because of
it and I'm giving up now for six week
minimum." And um I'm talking about this
person replied back as soon as I was
negative. And then they was like, "Oh,
well, why would they?" Again, this is
the way they try to victimize themselves
again. Um, why would somebody want to be
with somebody that says we're not evil?
You've literally reply to that comment.
That's the only comment that you reply
to. Again, hipster stirring,
victimizing. This is what they do. This
is literally what they do. Other women
will do it with other women as well. You
know, it's a form of victimizing their
own actions and blaming everyone else.
Why? They're just an ignorer and they
just only reply to um negative messages.
I was like, "Anything any thoughts on
the ignoring nice messages and replying
straight away to negativity?" No.
Completely cast your mind. I said, "No thoughts on
that." So I said, "No thoughts on the
replying straight away to negativity and
then ignoring the normal message." No
thoughts on that there. just completely
completely uh completely uh uh flipped
your mind. Bash your mind. Yeah, it
would do. Don't suit you, does it? It
doesn't suit them. Your experiences
don't suit these people. But what you
say don't suit these these
people [ __ ] [ __ ] get this [ __ ]
sentences. They get away with [ __ ]
murder. That's that's actual facts as
well, bro. That's actual facts that they
get away with [ __ ] murder.
Yeah, that's actually true as well. It's
a saying, but it absolutely is
true. They are literally there's no
positives in them. They're literally all
[ __ ] What the [ __ ] about positives?
There's literally no positives in any of
them. They are literally not people.
They are inhumane.
You don't see [ __ ] men acting like
this [ __ ] doing it. You don't see men acting like
this, you know? They're not people.
They're literally inhumane. That's what
they [ __ ] are. Like, don't ever ever
try and tell me they're [ __ ] not
people. Don't ever try and tell me women
are [ __ ] people. They are [ __ ] not
people, mate. Those are more [ __ ]
people. They're [ __ ] them. [ __ ] off
people. [ __ ] hell, man.
You know what I'm
saying? [ __ ] people. More like [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying, brother? More like [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] not people, mate. They're They're They're
people. They're [ __ ] evil, mate. Evil
people are not [ __ ]
people. Stop victimizing yourself as well.
Stop [ __ ] victimizing yourself. God
damn, that's so [ __ ] annoying that
is. Stop trying to victimize
yourself. So [ __ ] annoying that is,
bro. Hate it,
man. Yeah, man. I don't give a [ __ ]
about the YouTube [ __ ] This Reddit
thing is pissing me off again. You
know, I've literally explained to this
woman that that is a message that
they've replied to. They ignore normal
messages and reply to negative messages
to is this slipping your mind like have
you got dementia? Like have you got
brain problems or
something? You don't understand how what the [ __ ]
bro times. I was like they are literally
replying to negative messages. I said
I'll tell you what happened the other
day since day as well. This is what is
happening. They reply to negativity.
This is what I mean. and she completely
ignored it because it doesn't suit her.
It doesn't suit her. You understand?
So it's [ __ ] about this guy. [ __ ] idiots, aren't
they? They can never do no wrong.
[ __ ] hell. They want these
gratitudes. Yeah. Thank you. They
said, "Okay, let's try and see the good
in it. Evil
ignorers, liars, people that try to
victimize themselves. Nah. Can't see no
good. People pretending they got
boyfriends, [ __ ] Nah, can't see
the positives. I'll sit here for like
five, six hours, right? Trying to find
the positives. I can't find one single
positive. Even a sex.
Yeah. Yeah. I've lost my sex right now.
I'm I've been trying to think about the
positives. Let's go down memory
lane. Yeah. I can't see the positives.
I'm trying to think of the positives. I
can't think of the positives, bro. I
keep it real with you, you
know. I can't think of the
positives. You literally can't think of words.
Look, you know what I'm saying?
Yeah. No, bro. It's just this Reddit
[ __ ] We know I'm a virgin. Yeah, good
one. Uh, listen, Stiffy, right? I I need
to ask you this thing. Let me just ban
this person, right? I need to
um I need to uh I need to ask you this
question. Oh, that's a good that's a
fair point. So, this woman said that she
was um uh struggling with bacon. So, I
thought I'd hit her up and hit her with
some of my experiences. And I was
telling her yesterday about uh well,
today about the other day about how I
was messaging people and they'd only
reply to negativity.
And uh I said that oh there was somebody
I was spent an hour with didn't even
have the decency to just reply back. And
then as soon as I wrote all women are
evil. Uh she was on it like a cop on it
straight away. And I said what the [ __ ]
is going on? Why do these people keep
replying to negativity? And she said oh
well. She tried victim victimizing
herself again. Another woman trying to
victimize herself trying to say oh well
yeah why would they want to get with
somebody that don't like them? I was
like, "No, no, reread what I just said.
That's the very thing that you reply to.
You ignore normal messages and you
engage with negativity. Why are you
engaging with negativity and you're not
engaging with positivity?" Again, trying to victimize themsel. You
know, I wish one day somebody could
answer me why they reply back to
negativity. That's what I would love to know.
But yeah, the only positivity is you're
more stable when you save money when you
give up with them, when you stay away
from them. Yeah, that good. Good one,
bro. I like
that. You wouldn't want to be some with
somebody that says all women are evil,
yet you reply to it and you ignore the
positive message and you reply to the negative message.
Okay. Oh, Shifty, it's so funny, bro.
And and the funniest thing is she said
she was going to
reply. She said that she was going to
reply even though it was three months
ago. She was going to
reply. She was going to reply. Yeah.
Yeah, mate. And things were going to fly
as well, weren't they? They love
negativity, don't they? Are we not
seeing? Are we not seeing a correlation
here, you know, of what these people
actually like? They like
negativity. That's what they do. They
like negativity. They like [ __ ] scumbs, you
know. Let's not sugarcoat it now, man. Come
on. But yeah, you do save a lot of money,
mate. And you save your mental health as
well. It's not even just about money.
You know, they always do they do
anything they do anything to victimize
themselves. It's like that one in Italy.
Yeah, I think I I did I did get a reply,
you know, because of the context, you
know, spending an hour with someone. Why
you just replied just said, "Oh, you got
home. Thanks. Thanks." Why didn't you
just reply once? It's not like you was
going to see them again. So, you didn't
reply to that, but then you reply to
somebody saying that all women are evil.
Yet, you wouldn't want anything to do
with somebody that says all women are
evil, yet you reply to it. Make it makes
I think these people are actual evil,
bro. Like, I'm not even joking. Yeah.
And they actually do get away with
murder as well. And that's the thing.
They actually get lesser sentences.
[ __ ] entitled, selfish people about
positives in women. There's no [ __ ]
positives and no [ __ ] wig and buff. I
got a [ __ ] E school [ __ ] call me
over me yesterday. I'm not [ __ ]
going. Even if she said, "Oh, I'll do it
for free." I don't even have a sex
drive. I wouldn't even
go. Yeah. One second. I'll send the
link. Hold on. I wouldn't even go. Even
if she [ __ ] paid me. That's how f
even if she paid me. That's how bad it
is. [ __ ] normal, bro. Yeah, they're
all of all [ __ ] ages. They're of all
ages. They're [ __ ] up in their [ __ ]
head. That's what they are,
bro. Even getting their body is not even
worth it, bro. It's not even worth it.
[ __ ] them, bro. I don't want to sit down
today and play the [ __ ]
Simpsons. Might be a video coming, bro. [ __ ] this.
It's a big fat negative. Big fat
negative. No [ __ ] positives in there.
Yeah. [ __ ] that. [ __ ] I've been
trying to ring you. Yeah, I was busy.
What is it? [ __ ] going to meet up.
Why would I meet you? I'm in London. No.
[ __ ] come out for a [ __ ] piss up
in Birmingham and somewhere different.
Why? So you can get So you can get laid
in Birmingham. Nah, I'm all right, mate.
Why not? Just rather stay in London.
It's fol in London.
PJ call in Birmingham is a [ __ ] hole.
Yeah, I know it's a [ __ ] hole, but
I think you and Timmy need to pack it
in. I need to [ __ ] rip his [ __ ]
jar off his face. You know what that means?
Yeah, I know what it means. PJ, stop
arguing. No, PJ. Yeah, like you need to
pack it in, man. [ __ ]
Why don't you meet PJ? I thought you was
coming Birmingham for four anyways.
Yeah, I was going to, but I'm not going
now. I never said it was definite. I
said I was going. Yeah. Yeah. But why?
What? What? What's changed?
Oh, I just got to meet this [ __ ] on the
anyways. Bye-bye, buddy. I'm kicking you
now. I'm not going to Birmingham. [ __ ]
that. So, yeah, they're just [ __ ]
Shifty, they're absolute [ __ ]
Absolute [ __ ] aren't they? I can't
believe how many reply to
negativity. That's so mad. I even had a
32year-old uh Budapest model reply that
trying to take the piss, but they're
trying to say that men are the problem.
Why Why the [ __ ] are you replying? Why
the [ __ ] are you replying to negative
comments? Yeah, bro. It was it I woke up
today feeling good, bro. And then I went
on Reddit and this woman was pissing me off.
I was pissed off the other day, bro,
because I kept [ __ ] because of the
the comments, bro, was pissing me off,
you know, when they were like messaging
me back, trying to be intelligent. That
was it was annoying me, bro. They're
just evil, mate. They are just [ __ ]
evil, bro. Really, really
are. They really, really are all the
same. And if they're not all the same,
why do they do the same? Why do so many
do the same stuff? That's That's a
That's a good question.
You know what I'm
saying? Women are evil. They're evil.
They're ignorant. They're only reply to
Let me ask this Desmond deeds his
opinion. Hey Desmond, I've got a
question. Let me ask his opinion on
this. Anyone can get in on
this. You can get on on this if you want.
replies back. But yeah, so many of them
reply to negativity, but they don't positivity.
Strange. So, u there's this obviously um
so basically I done an experiment um if
you watch my video on uh two days ago.
So, some of them women that I messaged,
a lot of them didn't reply back the past
four or five weeks and they were just
lying about on my phone and just before
I went to sleep, I thought, "Okay, let
me let me write a negative message
instead and see how fast I get a reply."
And I said, "All women are evil." And
90% of them started replying, mate, all
throughout the next day. 6:00 in the
morning, 8 in the morning. There was one
that didn't reply for 3 months. replied
saying that she was going to get round
to replying to me even though it had
been 3 months and then she tried to
victimize herself and blame me saying
women are evil as to why she didn't
reply which is the thing that made her
reply. They are [ __ ] idiots, isn't
it? They love negativity. Like I think
we need we need to spread the word out
there that they love
negativity. They don't love positivity.
Who come out with this rumor? I want to
find out who's responsible for coming
out with that [ __ ] rumor,
bro. Yeah, they're all the same in the
West. Anywhere that's not Asia, anywhere
that's anywhere in Asia really. Maybe
like South America maybe a little bit.
They're all the same. Literally in all
of these westernized countries, they're
all the same. France, Italy, [ __ ]
Belgium, [ __ ] Germany, [ __ ]
Switzerland, [ __ ] Sweden. They're
literally all the same. They're
literally all the same, bro. They reply to
negativity. They're all the same.
They're literally all the
same, you know? That's it, bro. They're
literally all of them are the same. They
all try to victimize themsel as well.
Oh, I didn't feel the connection. Stop
victimizing yourself. All you had to do
was reply to a message. Stop
victimizing. And then when you and then
when you ask them right why they don't
feel the connection, what they say is
not even about a connection. They're
just victimizing the fact that they're
just a stuck up [ __ ] ignuses for
themselves. you know, talking to women
around very different from other
messages. Okay. So, they they so they so
they ignore, "Hey, how is your day
going? Hey, how's the hangover?" Well,
some of them replied, but a lot of them
didn't. But as soon as you say, "All
women are evil." They replied straight
away. 90% of them replied. That's a red
flag right there, babe. That's a red
flag right there.
Um, and no, it's the fact that it was
negative because if you said something positive, you
know, maybe we're not evil and only and
you are a creepy weird loser. Hey, stop
talking about yourself like that. Stop
talking about yourself like that. It's
not nice. It's never going to get you
laid either. But no, no, no. It's not
the fact that it was different from the
other messages because if you wrote a
positive message, they wouldn't reply
back to it unless they can argue with it
or they won't reply back to it. So, say
you you thought of something positive as
a first message. They're not going to
reply back to it unless it's
negative. There's no way like you could
think of things, you could think all day
of things to write them. If it's not
negative, something that they can
victimize themselves with, they're not
going to reply to
it. It doesn't matter if they get it
from load. It doesn't matter if they get
it from loads of men daily. Okay. [ __ ]
all the ones that I met drunk. That one
from Italy should have replied back. I
spent a whole hour with her. I asked her
a normal question. Yeah. A normal
question. You didn't reply back for 3
months. Yeah. As soon as I said all
women are evil, you reply back. Okay.
Let's forget about the ones that drink
and then maybe forget you the next day.
Let's talk about ones that have actual context.
Let's um let's talk about the ones that
have actual context. The ones where you
spend maybe like an hour with just reply
back and say you got home. What's the
problem? But then they reply that and
then you but then you will reply to a
negative message. It doesn't make sense.
Do you understand?
Yeah. So yeah, to me that is just ignorant all
over. So yeah, like that's that's it.
It's not going to change. That's why I'm
leaving in 7 weeks. Of course, it's not
going to change, but that's why I'm leaving this country. So,
they Yeah, they they ignore normal
messages, normal people, but then reply
to people saying, "Oh, all women are
evil." And I had to just delete the
message because it was just winding me
up, mate. And if I knew where any of
them lived, I would have just went on
their door two days ago. I would have
went on any of them doors in front of
any [ __ ] man. Bro, don't [ __ ]
message me back with your [ __ ] cheek
thinking that you're more. It was just
annoying me, bro. That's why I just
deleted it, you know. [ __ ]
sake. No, it doesn't. Then just then
ignore the negative message. Then if
you're going to ignore the positive and
listen, capt. It's what I was saying. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. And it's not even just that,
dog. It's not even just that. Yeah, it's
the fact that 90% of them reply to that
message. Like I was saying on my video,
it wasn't three of them or four of them.
It was 90% of
them. That's the thing was like, no,
it's all women. It's definitely all
women. Cuz some of these women were from
different countries, different ages. Oh,
you're a lovely girl. And just dealing
with them is just pissing me off. That's
why I just had to delete all the
conversations of that, you know. Yeah. It it
it people sugar it. They sugar like
people should be dealing with this
stuff. No one should have to deal with that
[ __ ] No one should have to deal with that [ __ ]
mate. No, they victimize themselves.
They literally victimize
themselves. Oh, they feel bad for not
replying before. Oh, they're just
[ __ ] mate. You know what? I don't
even like using the word [ __ ] I just
call them [ __ ] That's literally
what they are. They all They're just
[ __ ] They're all the [ __ ]
same. You know, if some didn't reply,
you could have used an excuse. Maybe
they can't reply. No, if some of them
didn't reply, I would have been like,
"Oh, well, maybe they just ignore and
maybe they just don't want to reply."
You know what I'm
saying? Oh, it's Oh, it's human. It's
human to respond to negativity, but it's
not human to respond to positivity when
you've spent an hour with someone. Oh,
okay. Okay. Right. Yeah. Well, let me
tell you, three of the women didn't
reply to it. Well, three of the women
didn't reply to it. So, that must mean
your logic [ __ ] So, they ignore.
Okay. But that's fine. Okay. But why
they try to victimize themselves
afterwards? That's the thing that gets
me is why do they try to act intelligent
and then when you're more intelligent
than them, they run away. And why do
they try to victimize
themselves? Oh, I was going to reply
back. It's been 3 months. You was never
going to reply back. But you fast enough
to [ __ ] reply to that message. You
reply to that. You're trying to
victimize yourself. Um, you're trying to
victimize yourself by what you're
writing. Trust me, you're not more
intelligent than me. So, and I even said
to one, I was like, I know you're from
New York and you went to university, but
you're not more intelligent than me. So,
don't even try to speak to me like I'm
somebody, you know. So, no, they they do
it to um they do it to victimize themsel, you
know, and it it it tells me that they
they like [ __ ] They like drug
dealers. They like men that are covered
in tattoos. people that go to prison,
that's the kind of men that they like.
[ __ ] Absolute [ __ ] You
rarely ever see a woman with a nice
person. They're just like [ __ ]
because they are [ __ ] themselves.
You know what I'm
saying? So, no, I wouldn't. No, I
wouldn't because I wouldn't be sat there
ignoring somebody that I spent an hour with. So,
yeah. So, yeah. Somebody said, "Oh, um,
the positives in women, I I woke up
today. My dick didn't even go
up. Their bodies are not positive.
They're not positive. There's nothing
positive about them. I'm sat here trying
to think in this bathroom. And I
literally can't even think. My dick
don't even go
up. My dick doesn't even go up anymore.
They that that many bad experiences, my
dick don't even go up. I don't even have
a sex drive. They completely ruin it.
probably going to be single because of these
women. If they like [ __ ] they like
[ __ ] drug dealers, that's bad. I
can't get one because of them. I can't
get one because of them. They've killed
my sex drive. I can't even think of them
anymore. You know, I think they has to
be more. You have to live close and be
regular otherwise it's easy to ignore.
They ignore regardless, mate. I've gone
around approaching instructor
before and there was this Romanian one I
was speaking to before months ago. He oh
I can't meet uh because it's Easter and
that replying back paragraph paragraph
and never heard from them again. Never
heard from them again. You know Casper
the ghost. That's what I call them. I
call them Casper the
ghost. I call them Casper the ghost.
It's so bad. Like I said, this escort
was like, "Oh, I'm you can come and see
me." Bro, I wouldn't even get with her
if she paid me. Even if she paid me, I
wouldn't even I think I'm asexual now. I
think they've actually turned me
asexual. They've actually turned me
asexual, bro. I'm not even joking. I
don't even think about it no
more. My sex is gone, bro. Cuz of
them. Cuz of them [ __ ] You know what I'm
saying? No, I was speaking to her the
other day, but it's it's another one. I
I wouldn't even get with them. I
wouldn't even get with them even if they
paid me. Bro, I'm not gay. I'm
asexual. Why would I Why Why would I turn
gay? Being gay is not a choice, mate.
[ __ ] sometimes I wish I was [ __ ]
gay, you know? Then you wouldn't be keep
having these bad experiences, these negative
experiences. I see. Yeah. But and and
and also it wasn't the and then No, no.
There's a few reasons why I gave up
again. It was the date them going on
dates to waste your time. The ghosting.
It weren't even the I've got a boyfriend
[ __ ] Then I went on this Morgan's
profile. I think, oh [ __ ] Well, so even
if you're if you're a woman, you can be
an evil person and still find a
relationship. So I was like, why am I
why am I even bothering now? If I have
to deal with people going on dates,
wasting my time, ghosting, which is the
most annoying thing ever, and then evil
women can get into a relationship. Even
below average evil looking women, that's
I I I find my notice in love. That's it.
I'm completely [ __ ] done, bro. If I
can be done with gambling for all that
time, I can be done with these [ __ ]
I can be done with these [ __ ] bro.
Bro, do I only go for nines and tens?
Um, stop asking stupid questions, bro.
There's not even nines and tens in this
country. I go for fours, fives, sixes,
and they're all at the same. They're all
[ __ ] I've got some approaching
videos on my main channel. There's no
nines and tens in this country.
only like Sweden and [ __ ] where's the
other country? There is nine and tens in
not not England. There's no nines and
tens in England, mate. They range from
about four to
about seven. There's no eights. There's
no nines and eight. Sorry. Nines and
eights in this
country. There's another country as
well. There's another country where
there's good looking people, but not here. Yep.
So, I could have dealt with a boyfriend
[ __ ] before I went to Thailand, like in
seven weeks. I could have dealt with it
every week, but I'm not dealing with
their ghosting and their [ __ ] every
[ __ ] week. [ __ ] that. I'm not dealing
with it. And yeah, and the thing is, C
is not because she's uh she's she's
below average looking. It's because of
how she actually
is. You know what I'm saying?
So, yeah. So, that's it, bro. I'd rather
and and like I said, it doesn't matter
what she looks like or what anyone looks
like. The people deserve love. People
are should be in relationships no matter
what they look like. People can't help
what they look like. But when someone's [ __ ]
evil, they shouldn't be able to be in
relationships. You know what I'm saying?
Don't care what people look like, bro.
Happy people, anyone, marry, people that
with money, [ __ ] whatever people do,
bro. You know, but [ __ ] evil people
shouldn't even be in
relationships. And you know, it's a
waste of time in this country cuz look
how much I went out last year when I
used to win that money. You I used to
have that money back and forth, back and
forth. I would know how it is more than
anybody. Do you know what I'm
saying? Like you just need to give up,
bro. Like that's it. That's all you need
to do. I'm going Thailand. I booked
Thailand by the way Joe.
So someone said to me right now, "Would
you rather go America or would you go to Thailand?" Thailand 100%.
100%. You know, it could be anywhere in
Asia. It doesn't need to be a third
world country. It could be anywhere in
Asia. You won't get these experiences
that you get here with these westernized
[ __ ] these [ __ ] westernized women, you know?
I like the trolling comments. It's
funny. E. So
yeah. Yeah. They just give bad
experiences, bro. Bad experiences, you
know. But I've got friends. Here's the
thing, Cers. I've got friends. I've got
people that look up to me. I say people
say to me, "Nah, you're chatting [ __ ]
You're decent looking. You got good
personality." What? You can't find
someone. So obviously it is [ __ ]
women bro. Take take take take take take
a look at your own life it is
them you know for somebody to take it
upon themselves to travel an hour away
just to waste your time and their
time that is serious mental health you
know you know no it's not going to work
unless they weren't born here though
because they're just westernized. I
mean, yeah, I could go
Chinatown. Yeah, I could try it. But if
they're born here and they grew up here,
they're just westernized. It's the same
thing as as as an Indian woman and an
Indian woman that was brought up here,
there's there's a big difference. But
um yeah but if obviously if they if
they've come here then
yeah even with these Indian women you
don't get rude Indian women it it is
women it is westernized women it is
definitely definitely westernized women
and having unrealistic it's got to be it
has to be there there's no other there's
no other explanation you
Yeah, they're just [ __ ] the ones I
can't stand is Americans. Can't stand
Americans. Can't stand Americans. Can't
stand them, mate. Even worse than
British. So, yeah.
I [ __ ] I can't stand Americans,
bro. I had to live remember I had to
live to that date last month. I had to
live with that injured
foot, you know? So, for you to travel an
hour away to waste your time and my
time, it's kind of kind of crazy, isn't
it? Really, she doesn't think anything
of it. She doesn't know anything, you
know? I don't tell her my
business. You know what I'm saying? I
don't turn on my [ __ ]
business. I was thinking of the good
times uh last year, Joe. Right. I was I
was reminiscing to when I used to win in
the casino and I used to go out and I
was thinking, where am I missing it? The
memory. I think it's because you was
winning money. Even though I've got
money, I've still got loads of money,
but I think it's because you was
actually winning the money and you was
taking it from the casino and you was
constantly doing it.
And it's not like I want to relive it
again. I just miss
it, man. I had to limp to that [ __ ]
day like a spacker, mate. Cuz of my
foot. Yeah, I had to limp like an
absolute backer, bro. Cuz I'm thinking
someone's replying back every two
minutes. They've approached you. They
gave you their number. Oh, we're in for
something here. Nah, just the same old
time wasting women.
Just the same old time wasting
women. So, no, just the same. All the
same. I forgot how bad it was. I
actually forgot how bad it was because I
haven't been on a date for a long time.
So, yeah, I don't gamble anymore, Joe,
anyways, cuz you don't win in the end. I
don't like losing. I don't like the mood
swing. So, I just gave up with
it. But yeah, it was fun.
I don't think I'll ever gamble again to
be honest with
you. Nah, can't be bothered,
mate. Problems in my life. Don't need that. So,
yeah. I'm just waiting for a whole movie
to cover her hand. She approached me as
well saying that, "Oh, you're
attractive." She gave me her number. The
[ __ ] was replying every two minutes. He
traveled an hour away to see me. Yeah,
I'm decent looking. I'm out. I'm an
extrovert. And yet, she claims she don't
feel the vibe. Bro, at this point, what
are you actually looking
for? Imagine we approached a woman who
was a five or six out of 10 and we said
that we didn't feel the vibe. It would
never happen. So, it's women's standard.
Do you understand? That [ __ ] Morgan,
bro, was [ __ ] Oh my, bro. She was
stinking, bro. You know when I I can't
remember exactly. Let me tell you
something. Right. And this woman was 32
as well. So it's not like she had loads
of options because she's 32. So she
doesn't have load options. She I can't
remember exactly what her face look like
but it was different to the picture. I
stuck around I stuck around to somebody
with somebody that was below average. So
why couldn't they stick around someone
that's average to above average? It
don't make sense. You understand? That's
the whole point of them having unrealistic expectations.
That's the whole point of it. Cuz that's
that's serious mental health that
is. And it takes longer to know if you
vibe with someone or not. But that's
what I'm saying to you, bro. Like it's
it's [ __ ] Cuz the kind of person
you are, I am. You would get on with
most people. So it doesn't add up. And I
didn't even like her. But it's the
principle. I didn't even like her. But
it's the principle of this is what we're
in for now. these timewasting women have
had to [ __ ] live [ __ ] here. It's
just and I remember going I was I
remember going out on Thursday and these
two people like oh yeah you know be like
a four out of 10 I was like it's not the
point that makes it even worse because
if these women are having these
unrealistic standards being 32 because
32 is old to me
right is old to
me is old to me I'm 27 you're 32 let's
say you're average slightly above below
looking this If this is what we're in
for with people that look like this,
then we have no
hope. Nah, you don't know pretty quick.
Nah, no, no, no, no, no, no. That
[ __ ] Somebody that's as confident
as me, somebody has has got um universal
interest. Nah, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, mate.
Trust me, I'm the kind of person that
has loads of friends. I have friends. I
make friends with everyone. Nah, no, no,
no. and the way I look. No [ __ ] way,
bro. I am not buying that one little
bit. I am not buying that one little
[ __ ] bit, mate. Because I have to
I've had to stick around with a [ __ ]
three out of 10 that from [ __ ]
Birmingham. So, don't give me that [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying? So, okay,
let's just go by your logic. So,
somebody that likes that likes all kinds
of food and ret is not suitable. So,
what is your ideal man
then? I'm not a nice person to be
around. I've got loads of friends. Loads
of friends. I'm a very light person.
Making excuses for women again. I'm not
a nice person to be around, brother. I
had to literally limp all the way to
that date. Yeah. Read into that what you
will. Stop making excuses for women and
their unrealistic expectations. I'm not
a nice person to be around, mate. I've
got tons of friends. I've got people
that look up to me. I have people that
disbelieve me when I tell them about my
bad experiences with women. Stop
defending women. [ __ ] me, bro. Like, do
you have to show each and every one of
my friends and people that I associate
with? Yeah. What What do you want me to
do? Start recording my dates? What do
you want me to do? Start recording my
dates? Bro, I could do it, but you're
still not going to believe it. Okay. Do
you know what? That is actually a good
idea. I could start recording my dates,
but you still wouldn't believe it. So,
there'd be no point, bro. And the reason
I know this is because I used to do with
the approaching videos, and it would go
in one ear, doesn't suit you, go out the
other. So, there'd be no point in even
recording dates. You know, you just make
excuses for women. I've told you the
reason. They've got unrealistic
expectations. That is literally they
waste your time on purpose, you
know. No, I was No, no, I was happy to
go on a date, mate. I was happy to go on
a date, mate. Again, I limped all the
way to the date. Yeah. So, in case
you're trying to I know what you're
trying to do. You're trying to make say,
"Oh, well, you you probably done
something." Cuz it's always the man's
fault. Oh, you done something.
I had to limp to that date, brother,
with about 100 kg weight on my foot. Do
you think I went all that way for a
laugh? Oh, because I told you so to tell
you that I told you so. Think about it
in case you think, "Oh, did you do all
of these stupid? Did you do any of these
stupid voices? What if you said
something?" Yeah. I would limp all the
way there and [ __ ] my foot up just to
say I told you so. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. That's totally me, isn't it? Yeah.
Come on, man. Make it make sense. You
know, I'm limping on a date cuz I had a
foot injury. You [ __ ] idiot. Cuz I
had a [ __ ] foot injury. I couldn't
help it. I was in [ __ ] pain. You know what I'm
saying? So, yeah, I was in [ __ ]
pain. But these Anyways, these women go
on dates to pass
time. And there was one woman that I
ditched. She was from B the free and I
ditched her and that wasn't because of
the way she looked. It's because she was
trying to use me. So I just ditched
her. Yeah. I just ditched her, man.
So you're an idiot, bro. You need some
life experience. You honestly do need some life
experience. So yeah, I mean I could I
there's ways of me making money now as
well. I could go out every Saturday,
spend 80 pound drinking, approaching,
but why? For what? We know all women are
the same. You know, I was even thinking
though, I could be a [ __ ] and just still
not like them and just try and get in
their knickers and just be a [ __ ] and
then that way I wouldn't contradict
myself, but then I don't want anything
to do with them. So then why would I
want to deal with people that I don't like? You
understand? You know, and be like, "Oh,
seven weeks to Thailand, six weeks to
Thailand, five weeks to go to Thailand."
But there's literally no point dealing
with them. I don't like them. So why am
I going to deal with them, bro? Do you
know what I'm [ __ ] saying? I even
stopped the sober approaches cuz I was
like, "This is what it's going to be.
I'm not dealing with it,
bro." Yo, is gambling a negative? Yeah.
Is alcoholism a negative? Yeah. Is
obesity a negative? Yeah. We need to
start talking about the dating game for
men being negative. We need to start
People need to start talking about that more.
more. I think you know what I'm
saying. They need to start talking about
that more. I
think I don't keep trying. I've not
tried for a couple of weeks. Then when I
gave up, I gave up. Well, I can get a
stiffy, but I just have no interest in sex.
Um I um when I was at my mom's uh where
was it? [ __ ] a couple weeks ago when
I got someone's number. We were supposed
to meet on a Friday. I was like, "Okay,
let me uh let me let me let me see if
this person wants to meet on a Friday.
Let me just I'm like just about giving
up at this point." And then and I
remember having this foot pain waking me
up at 4:00 in the morning. And then all
of a sudden she stopped replying. I
said, "Oh, you've gone quiet. You ignore
her. Block me." I was like, I'm
legitimately done. So, I'm like 99%
giving up at this point. And then I went
on that Morgan's Facebook. I was like,
oh [ __ ] even evil people can get in
relationships. That's me done. 100%. I'm
done. I'm out of here. I'm done. I'm
[ __ ] done. No, no more sitting on a
barber chair for an hour, 20 minutes,
cactus. No more sitting on a [ __ ]
barber chair, bro. No more.
No more sitting on the [ __ ] barber
chair for a [ __ ] hour. God, I used to
hate that. [ __ ] boring, is it?
Sitting on a sitting on a [ __ ]
barbers chair for an hour just to hear I've got
boyfriends. Might as well go looking
like a [ __ ] [ __ ] You know, I
actually I I actually done better when I
went out looking like a [ __ ] Do you know that
cactus? Yeah. Yeah, when I went out
looking scruffy and attracted by I I I done
better. I done better.
Me, I think all of these things where
women like positivity, women like
groomed men, all of this. I think it
came from some little nerd that just
made it up in their mommy's basement and
everyone just copies them cuz that is
not what real life
shows. You know what I'm saying? Do I
talk to who and chat? Yeah, but it's just boring.
Yeah, but it's just boring being sat on
the chair for an hour. It's [ __ ]
boring. God, it is boring as [ __ ] Even
when there is TV and then what? You go
out just to hear your boyfriend. [ __ ]
that. [ __ ] all
that. That is boring, mate. [ __ ] bors
me with women that think they're [ __ ]
that think they're better than you when
they're [ __ ] well not. Uh yeah,
man. Fed up with it, man.
Oh, this is LJ, actually. Want to talk
Li? L here. What's this? I hear that the
doorman can Can you Can you hear me?
Yeah. What's this? I hear that doorman
made a contact to you.
Yeah. Yeah. You tried to go into a bar
in shorts and they were laughing at you
and told you to go to premark.
Nah, man. Not me. It's made up.
What happened? Why didn't you put it on?
Are you coming to the barbecue? I
wouldn't go to the back door with you.
Do you remember the Simpsons hit and run
game? I'd be embarrassed going over you.
No. Do you remember the Simpsons hit and
run game? Yeah. Yeah. I'm playing it
later. I've got it on PC. I'm taking the
trip down memory lane. RJ,
congratulations. But nah, I wouldn't be
seen out out in the street with you.
People would think I'm your car or
something. But how do you know the
Simpsons here run? Did you used to play
it as a child? No, I never used to play
it, but I remember the game. Yeah, I've
got it on PC.
Well, laptop, it's actually a laptop.
You should come to the barbecue, LJ.
Why? I'd be I'd be embarrassed to be
seen with you. Huh? Yeah, but you'd be
pulling all those weird faces making
that weird noise. I no you TB LT bring your friends
anytime I be mildly embarrassed to be
seen we byebye now LJ yeah Simpsons here
run I was playing at the other cactus
and I was like oh man I messaged my
mommy I was like I remember being 9 years old
um I remember I remember being 9 years
old and having no strength No worries.
Being a baby Peter Belly, little Peter
Belly, no beard, no stress, no worries.
Just sat in that high chair playing the
Simpsons hit and run. I miss them days.
I miss Laney saying I miss them days.
Those were the
days driving around being Bart
Simpson. Well, I miss them days, Joan. I
actually missed them days. Can't beat
them. You can't beat them, Grezy. You
know, those were the good old
days. Those were the good old
days. [ __ ] good old days. Barbecue at
ladies. Nah, man. Barbecue. Barbecue at
mine. I'm not going to [ __ ] send
people to my [ __ ] mom's house, am I,
bro? No. Barbecue. Barbecue at mine.
Barbecue at mine, matey. It's an open
invitation, you know. Green is invited.
Cactus is invited. Joe is invited. No
women and no Timmy Eldridge. Monty is
invited as well. Just no Timmy. Oh, but
you can't bring Matthew because we don't
want evil around our
food. We don't want evil around our
[ __ ] food, mate. You know what I'm
saying? So, uh,
yeah. This is a life having food cooked for
you. Yeah. All the all the lads. Yeah.
Mark Samson. Telly. Yeah. My first game
going up was Scooby-Doo. And that's
Yeah. Do you remember Scooby-Doo on Game
Boy? Do you remember Scooby-Doo on Game
Boy? Oh, bro. That's like going down
proper memory lane. That is I used to
remember watching Scooby-Doo as a child
at 6:00 in the morning. I love Scooby. I
love Scooby. I love Spongebob.
Yeah. 6:00 in the [ __ ] morning, bro.
I used to go to school. I used to um watch Scooby
do. I've got a question. Yeah. What do
you think is the most um popular
cartoon? I I think it's
um I think it's Tom and Jerry in the
Simpsons. Oh, Tom and Jerry.
Uh Tom and Jerry. I turn into I turned
into a big kid, you know. I turned into
kid when it comes to cartoons. But I
wonder what happened because all of the
people that made Tom and Jerry are dead
obviously cuz it's over 100 years old.
So what happened? Did it pass on to
their family? Did their family start
doing new episodes? Did they start
getting money or
what? That's what I was
wondering cuz obviously they're all dead.
So I'm thinking it just went to the
family, I guess. Yeah,
relatives. I'll be I'll be playing the I
I'll send you the I'll put the video up
if you uh you don't believe me. I think
I've got it. Hold
on. Yeah, we can even play the Simpsons
hit and run together.
L, where is this game? Hold on. I've got it somewhere. be
accepted. There we go. There we
go. Yeah. One second. I'm going to put it up.