Oh [ __ ] Why is the oil is too
high? The oil is too high, buddy. Oh
[ __ ] The oil is way too high. Uhoh.
Good old baby.
You can stay to the
P. He be
like the [ __ ] up.
Mother nice steak, mate. Morrison is
finished. I went to [ __ ] Morrison's
bro and [ __ ] the steak is all [ __ ]
[ __ ] bro. All expired and everything. I
had to go to the
butchers like sirloin onion rings. I
prefer sirloin and
ribeye. I don't know why. Just just do it. steak mushrooms
only. I don't know how people can have
their steak like that, you know.
Bloody have it eat it like
that. Yeah, they're lovely characters, mate.
We have to go [ __ ] butchering some
pork. Well, you don't like steak?
Why? Yeah. Oh, yeah. Same. I Well, I
like mine. I tell you, I like mine. I
like mine a tiny bit pink, but no blood.
It has to be a tiny bit pink, but it
can't have any blood in it. Yeah.
I saw a lot of evil bastards about
today, bro. A lot of evil women being
evil. Evil women walking
around. Yeah. I wonder I wonder what's
going on in their life. I wonder like
who's their victim. Who's their next victim? These
uh Yeah, I know. I kind of changed my
mind cuz I got busy this
week. Yeah, I got busy this week. So, I
changed my mind.
Yeah, it just need to be fine with pink but no
blood. That can't be bloody, mate. Can't
bloody. Can't not be bloody. That's [ __ ] disgusting.
And the low one
now. So there's no such thing as steak
being cooked properly. You can have
steak or if you wanted
to not p chicken. You can have steak
however you want it. Want to add a
little bit more butter for the
m just in case. Always make that mistake.
No, I mean you technically could have it
raw and you wouldn't get food poisoning.
That's what I mean. I wouldn't have it
raw. Obviously not, but it has to be
tiny. But I like mine medium. Well
done. Can't have no [ __ ] blood in it
though. [ __ ] that. Sometimes you go to a
steak restaurant and the [ __ ] still
moving. Still [ __ ] moving, mate. [ __ ] that.
Yeah. I wonder who's their victim
anyways. Uh Greasy, you know these women
walking around. I wonder what's going on
in their life. Like what man are they
picking on? What man are they
using? [ __ ] evil
bastards. I wonder, bro. I really
wonder. What do you
think? If you never see what a fire
looks like, do you
think I put one
now? Yeah, I think
so. Maybe. Maybe not. No, I'm not going
to put one just yet. Not at all. No. No.
You know what? I love the Simpsons
characters, but I just never love the
series. I could just never get into the actual
like program, you
know? Yeah, that makes sense.
Need to cut
the molding sauce,
mate. There you go. You cut the middle of it. It's
a tiny bit pink, but no blood.
Cuz if you over if you overdo steaks
that you ruin it. That's the thing with
steak. If you overdo it, you just ruin it.
Yeah. Probably the other
night. Yeah. Yeah. So, I said to this
woman on the Reddit, you're saying about
leave women alone. And I had to remind
her, I was like, mate, they're not
innocent. Stop trying to make it seem
like they're some them they're some sort of
victim. I speak to a transgender woman
and she lived in Scotland and uh she had
no bad words to say about women just
like most people. But I mean, she
changed she changed her sex to become a
woman. So why would she, you know, even
if she knows what I'm saying is right,
she's not going to exactly agree, is
she? If she gone through a surgical
operation, she become a [ __ ] woman.
Okay. One second. Okay.
and get this thing right
today. Right. Why you go out
fish then? If you don't know why it looks like,
mate, this is what it looks like.
That is what it looks [Music] like. Oh
[ __ ] Mask out. It's fine. All
right, I'm going to cook this and eat it
uh be back later.