Here we
go. Yeah, I was going to go live yesterday, but today
No one still hasn't been able to answer
me as to why they reply back to
negativity. Well, you're on YouTube
early, aren't you, lad? You're on
[ __ ] YouTubes, quite early. Jesus,
some of you need a
life. Nothing's happening, man. I'm just
chilling. Got to buy the barbecue meat
today for tomorrow. So marinate
it and then yeah, just chill. Might be
going out this week, obviously.
Yeah. Yeah, man. Just chilling, bro. Just
chilling. It's your lunch break at what?
10:00 in the
morning. What? 10:00 in the morning. You
got a lunch break?
Seems unusual, but each to the right, I guess. So,
yeah, hold up.
Yeah, there's no point in what going
out. Yeah, I know. There's no point
going out, bro. That's why I don't go
out anymore, obviously.
Give me a second,
please. You start work at 6. You
see? Yeah. something like
that. One second.
Yeah, looks like trying to do something here.
bro. People on Reddit say that you can
meet people through friends. Oh, man.
Like I said, I think all of these things
come from just um somebody living in
their [ __ ] mom's basement and they
just made up a load of [ __ ] and everyone
com and everyone copy
them cuz it it doesn't it doesn't add up
with what you actually experience in
real life. What you hear online is not
what you experience in real life when it
comes to women.
like it just it doesn't add up. When you
hear stuff on the internet about like
anxiety and mental health stuff, you
think, "Oh yeah, this adds up. Oh, this
adds up. That adds up." What you hear
about women, it does not add up. It's
the complete opposite to what you hear.
Like they like confidence. They like
positivity. Yeah. That's why they only
reply to negative
comments. And Joe F was like, "Oh, it's
in human it's our human nature to reply
to negativity." No, it's not. No, it's
[ __ ] not. Think of all of them
YouTubers that ignore negative comments.
So, how do you work that one out? Right?
If it's in our human nature to reply to
negative comments or negativity, why do
you have these big ass YouTubers that
ignore it? Why do most people ignore negativity but
women? So, that's just an excuse to try
and defend women. again. So
yeah, it's not [ __ ] cuz most people
don't reply to negativity. You don't see
big YouTubers replying to [ __ ]
negativity or [ __ ] celebrities when
they see comments. So that's a load of
[ __ ] That's a load. That's just an
excuse. Yeah. I'm not going out this
week. Not going out next week. Nah, bro.
No [ __ ] way.
So yeah, that's it, bro. Yeah.
Hey, because if it was a numbers game,
you would have met someone by now. If it
was truly Okay. Okay. Listen to what
you're saying on Reddit. Right. If it
was truly a numbers game, right, you
would have met
somebody by now. Like I guess the amount
of trying you've done if it was a numbers
game. uh if you if there if it was a
numbers game, you would have found
someone generally. Generally, that would
that that that's what would have
happened. So, I just said, "Oh, there's
there's not everyone there's not someone
for everyone and just women are all the
same." Cuz if they weren't, you wouldn't
be saying it. You wouldn't be sat there
at 27 saying it. Do you know what I'm
trying to say,
bro? You know, you would not be sat here
having the same conversation. And and I
just said that to Aunt Man yesterday as
well. We wouldn't be having the same
conversation if it was truly a numbers
Yeah, nice. Nice trolling, bro. Nice
trolling. I've got people on Reddit
telling me that it's a [ __ ] numbers
game. I've got people on Reddit telling
me it's a [ __ ] numbers
game. They said, "How long you been
doing this for?" I said I've been doing
it approximately about 3
years and still having the same
conversation. Still having the same
conversation, but it's a numbers
game. But it's a numbers game
apparently. Yeah. Things you hear online
about anxiety and stuff like mental
health, it's all correct. But what you
hear on the internet about women, it's
completely the opposite. They don't like
positivity. They do not like positivity
one little bit because then they
wouldn't reply to
negativity. Somebody said, "Why would you give
up?" Why would you give up? Um the
ghosting, the ignoring, the makeelie
boyfriends, the negative experiences. I
don't know. Maybe something like that.
Why the [ __ ] wouldn't you give up?
I've approached more than
anyone in the world, bro. More than
anyone ever has and anyone ever will.
That's the that's the definition of
don't force it, bro. So, and that's
another thing you hear on the internet.
There's someone for everyone. There's no
one for me. Yeah, you might have had
shitty one night stands, whatever you
that that's just God giving you a little
bit back on the effort that you put in,
but all all jokes aside, if you would
have found someone, you would have found
someone by now. Think of it. If you're
27, right, and you had to go through all
of these negative experiences and what,
you got one shitty relationship at most,
whatever. What makes you think all of a
sudden it's going to change?
What makes you think you've been dealing
with this for years and you It's like
dealing with cancer for years over and
over and over and over again. Do you
think all of a sudden one day you're
going to wake up and it's and it's
gone? You've been dealing with this [ __ ]
for donkey's years. For [ __ ] sake,
it's not changing, mate, in this
country. It's why I don't bother, you
know? I can I can go out whenever I
want. I can make the money back. I'm
just not interested in it cuz I don't
want any more negative experiences. And
you know there's a point you need to
throw in the towel. You
know imagine you keep you keep trying
right when you're uh until you're like
35. Imagine you waste all your so say we
keep trying now till about 35 and we
waste all that time and we don't leave
the country again you know just look
back and thought [ __ ] I wish I gave up
at 27 which is one of the reasons I gave
up with gambling you know cuz something like that
Yeah, done a lot of traveling as
well. And like I said, there is a
positive that you learn at 27 and you
can move on with your life. That's a big
positive cuz if you if you try for
another [ __ ] you know 33 35 you
wasted all that time on someone that's
not there somebody that's that's not
that doesn't exist Malcolm you
know what is so hard to to to believe
that some people are just not made for
anyone you know there's other people as
well like you watch them you think this
person's not made for no one. That's the
way it works,
bro. Unless you met somebody years ago
and you're going to find it very hard
now. You know, most people are going to
find it very hard now, you know, cuz the
way the things are time is and that. If
them women didn't if most of them women
didn't reply to them negative comments,
I might have went out this week. But I
was like, nah, this you can't even think
of anything positive about it anymore.
It's the end,
bro. It's the [ __ ]
end. Time wasting dates, the
[ __ ] the [ __ ] uh
ghosting, the [ __ ]
victimizing, you know, all of that [ __ ]
bro. I can't be annoyed with it
all. It's a
negative. It's a [ __ ] numbers game.
It's a [ __ ] numbers game. It's not a
[ __ ] numbers game at
all. Ridiculous. How could it be a
[ __ ] numbers game?
Doesn't even make sense. So
yeah. Yeah, man. I'm not going out this
uh this week either, bro. I'm buying the
meat today for the barbecue to marinade
for tomorrow. But yeah, I won't be going
out. I don't think I'd ever be going out
in this country ever
again, you know, because people's luck
just don't start changing like that, you
know. It's one of the reasons why I I I
gave up the gambling and I mean it. I
have given up
gambling. Like I watch Timmy's video.
I'm thinking, "Oh, this guy is still at
it." Every single [ __ ] day I gave up
for I gave up. I gave up the gambling
me, you know? [Laughter]
Yeah, bro. So, I gave up with
that. I just My friends are, "Oh, we
should go out Saturday." Yeah. Meet me
after work. But I just can't be
bothered, man. I just don't want to deal
with them. You know what I'm saying?
That's the thing. I don't want to deal
with these evil people.
Mate, it's not even that, bro. It's
people trying to tell me it's a numbers
game when I've tried more than anybody in the
world. You know what I'm saying, bro? If
you was going to find someone, you would
have found someone by
now. Like, you would have literally
found someone. Well, I would have
anyways. I don't know about you, but I
would have. If you was going to find
someone, you would have found someone by now,
statistically, you know. So, it's
like I I just And it's not even about
that. It's the fact that like so many
women reply to negativity. Sunnyside,
all women are evil. I wrote all women
are evil. Yeah. And 90% of them replied.
So, like this doesn't logically make any
sense. Apparently, they like positivity,
but they ignore they they ignore
positivity and reply to negativity.
So what you hear is doesn't match real
life. See with with uh like I said with
like anxiety and other things like that,
anything you hear on the internet, it's
pretty uh it's pretty legit. You know
what you hear, you know? Oh, okay. This
makes sense. But what I think some loser
in his mummy's basement made up a load
of [ __ ] about women and what they like
and everyone just copied it. No sir.
and the waste of time going on dates as
well. Like, and this is what this person
was saying on Reddit. No, man. I don't
think she was trying to waste them.
Well, she was if she was the one who
approached you, she was probably not
feeling it during a date. Okay. What
does that even mean? Not feeling it
during a date. when you've got when
you've got two extroverts that's got the
same interests. Please can somebody
explain to me what not feeling something
during a date means because it makes
absolutely no sense to me when two
people are are outgoing when two people
are confident. That makes absolutely no
sense to me. But
um yeah, it logically does not make any
sense. you know, it makes absolutely no sense. So,
yeah, but like I said, I could I could
go out every week, Rocky Road, you know,
every Saturday if I wanted to. I could
still go out and save money, you know, I
could make money some, but I don't want
to deal with them anymore. That's what
I'm trying to say. I can say, "Oh, seven
weeks to Thailand. I'm going Thailand
soon. Six weeks to Thailand." But what
would actually be the point? Because
they're all the same. So why would I
want to deal with all the same, you
know? I don't I don't even drink
anymore. Just sit in the house. I get
food cooked for me. I I go for walks, you
know, watch murder
documentaries. Why would I want to deal
with people that all the same expected
to find people that are not all the
same? You know what I'm saying?
And I was speaking to somebody on Reddit
yesterday. She said, "Oh yeah, my ex
abused me." Yeah, because you go for
these people. You go for these domestic
abusers. What's the chances, right, that
all of these women are going for nice
normal guys and they turn into women
beaters? No, you go for these people and
then you generalize men on the men that
you go for because there's no way that
every single guy is was normal and then
turned into a domestic abuser. You know
what you're It's like they give them
their CV, right? And it's got domestic
abuser on there and they choose them,
you know, because people don't just turn
into [ __ ] domestic [ __ ] abusers. Not
all them people, bro. You know what I'm saying? So,
so yeah, I think they've got unrealistic
expectations and it's like people are
doubting my dates now, Sunny Side, Rocky
Ry, they want to see me go on dates.
What's the point of them seeing me go on
dates, bro? Because they're just going
to make up stuff anyways. Even if I was
to record my whole dates, they would
just make stuff up, just like they do
with the approaching videos. I'm
saying, "Yeah, they're only interested
in drug dealers and
dickheads." Drug dealers and
[ __ ] That's what I would even say
people I wouldn't even say people with
tattoos that much, but just [ __ ]
[ __ ] are drug dealers. That's the
only people that they're that they're
interested in in this country. [ __ ]
and drug dealers. bro. Yeah.
So, no, I don't play the meal. No, I
think even if you paid me, I still
wouldn't go out. That's how bad it is. I
think even if you paid
me, I still wouldn't go out.
Yeah, I still wouldn't go
out. Yeah, I don't think I would go out
even if someone paid me,
mate. That's really bad to be honest.
That's how you know you're really done.
done. It was pissing me off though. uh
two days ago. Rock and Roy bad [ __ ]
who the [ __ ] do they think they're
[ __ ] messaging back sheet to trying
to be [ __ ]
smart. Yeah, I was watching the Timmy
Limes yesterday was he was cracking me
up, love. He's like, "Come on, Bungo.
Bungo." No, mate. I was getting a bit
haughy yesterday. I'll just I'll just
have a wank.
I'll just have a wank. I generally don't
want nothing to do with any of them ever
again. I generally don't want anything
to do with them ever
again. Bro, not
me. I don't even think I woke up with a boner today.
Nah, nah, bro. I think I am legitimately
done for a very long
time cuz I It's like with the gambling.
When I said I was done, I meant it. But
when I actually said it, I actually
meant it. So, yeah. No, I think I am
done. I think I am done, bro.
100%. It's not going to change.
Nothing's ever going to change. And even
if you was tempted to go out, you
know, so um you you still wouldn't get
anything anyway, so why would you go
out? Guess they blocked you after you
went negative. Not that it sounds like
Yeah, I had one the funniest one was the
one from Italy um that I spent an hour
with and all I wanted was a reply back.
three months she didn't reply back to
the normal message and then
um apparently she was going to get round
to messaging me back even though it had
been three months. Then she tried to
victimize herself trying to say how she didn't feel
connection and how she doesn't engage
with people that write misogyny comments
yet she that is the very thing that she
was engaging with. So that never made
any sense because the nice message then
got ignored. So they do anything to try to victimize
themsel like the feeling the connection victimizing
yourself you know that's called victimizing yourself [Laughter]
How do you get with Morgan
Rocky? Why do you get with that stinking [ __ ]
Huh? Why don't you get with that
stinking [ __ ] bro?
What they do, bro, is they will um reply to negative
comments thinking that they're
intelligent. And then when they when you
show them that you're more intelligent
than them, they then run
away. They then run away cuz they think
they're intelligent, but they're really
stupid. And then they run away. when you
show them that you're more intelligent
than them or they're not more
intelligent than you rather, they run
away, you know what I'm saying? They And
that's why I just don't want to deal
with them no more, you know?
Yeah. Could you imagine, bro? You went
to America. Yeah. had a [ __ ]
boyfriend in tattoos started. Like, bro,
I would [ __ ] I would tell that S about
himself any day of the week. I would
tell that S about
himself. Like to see him [ __ ] try,
mate. [ __ ] waste of
money. He's left for about a month,
mate. Then he'll come back. And then
he'll come back pretending to call people out
again. Yeah. For a month or so until he
gets bored. And then he comes on YouTube
pretending to call people out again like he always does. Yeah.
But yeah, it doesn't even matter. Even
if you get horny.
Yeah. Even if you get
horny. Even if you get
horny and uh you want to go out, there's
no point going
out. You're just going to be the same
old [ __ ] same old boyfriends, same old
[ __ ] So it doesn't even matter
even if you you did want to go out
anyways. There'd literally be no point. So yeah.
So yeah, sucks in
it. Pay me to go out again, bro. Because
if you pay me out again, if you pay if I
go out again, I'll end up doing
something that will get me in serious
trouble. So that's why there's there's
no point of me even going out and
dealing with these people no more. If
you see a fit on the street that you
like, bro, I see fit women all the time.
I don't bother with them. I see it every
time. I go in shopping malls. I don't
care. I even I stopped the sober
approaches from a long time ago to be
honest. But yes, I would let it pass by
because I have done it recently. I've
just let them walk past. Why would you
let them walk past, bro? What are they
going to say that they've got a
boyfriend? What are they going to do?
Keep on walking? What are they going to
do? Give you their number and not reply?
I just let them go. Yeah, I see loads of
ones. I saw one yes, was it yesterday?
Yeah. When I had to deposit some money.
Yeah, I saw one yesterday by the gym.
Completely ignored it. I'm not dealing
with them no
more. So, you won't get
reminded, bro. I've got one bail
condition. I've only got one bell
condition that's probably going to be
dropped very soon. And by the way, I'm
following up my police report. So, that
person's going to be getting nicked
soon. Anyways, that reminds me. They
said give them time. I need to follow
that up on Friday as well. Thanks for
reminding me. Yeah, since these people
wanted to keep calling the police, I
know you won't get reminded. There's one
bell condition, one only. I can still
leave the country. I can still do what I
want. So what are they going to remind
you? What for three and a half years?
Bro, you don't get reminded for stuff
like that. But yeah, that's another
thing. I need to go and harass that
police officer on Friday. So what the
[ __ ] bro? You
know, so this they're going to get
nicked. Trust me, Rocky Roy. They're
going to get nicked, bro. And if you've
got any other things, um, you know, send
it to me so I can send it to the
police. Yeah, you never know till you
try. Yeah, I've been trying 3
years. Yeah, bro. I have been going. I
have been going. I have been going. Even
though they deleted stuff, I've still
got it all. And it's it's a woman police
officer and she said like she I've spoke
to her and that she said sent me all the
evidence. I'm still waiting for her to
like contact me back. I've got more and
more and more and more and more like the
posters. I've got everything, bro. I've
got everything. So, and if you've got
any more, just email it cuz I'm going to
keepoundounding them andounding them
andounding them until they do something.
So, I don't care,
bro. I'm not a grasp. But these people
want to call the police on me. [ __ ] it.
You know, that's it.
So, so you wouldn't get reminded what
reminded for three and a half [ __ ]
years. So, what are they going to do?
remind you for three and a half years if
you punch someone, bro. Please stop
it. Doesn't even make sense.
So, but yeah, I'm going to keep nagging
them, nagging them, nagging them,
nagging them, nagging them. That's what
I'm going to do, bro. So, if you've got
anything to show me,
bro. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Don't
worry, bro. Don't worry. It's going to get sorted
anyways. It's going to get sorted. Don't
worry. It takes time, bro. This [ __ ] I'm
still on it. It takes time. Like, it
took [ __ ] 6 months for me. So, it
took 6 months. Trust me, bro. Something
is going to happen because I was going
to the police station like every week.
Every week, every week. And they were
trying to like pour me off. I was like,
"No, I'm not reporting it to YouTube.
I'm [ __ ] reporting it to [ __ ]
you." And I had to say it about a
million times. I said, "Listen, I said
to them in a roundabout way when I
called, I was like, you can't play two
sides of a coin." Yeah, you can't get
yourself You can't get yourself involved
with social media when it suits yourself
and then when it doesn't suit you, tell
somebody to report it to YouTube. You
can't choose when you get yourself
involved as the police. It doesn't work
like that and then they listen and yeah,
it took a lot of like me saying it and
bro, it's hard. So, when these people
call the police on YouTube, Sunny, like
any of them, they f they have to follow
up with this stuff. That's how you know
they ain't got a life. I'm obviously
doing it to protect myself. You know,
these people have got me nicked a
million times. I have to do this. So, I
know how the process works now. You understand?
So, and yeah, I hid my phone in the
garden, bro. They tried taking my phone.
I hid it in the garden. They come to my
yard. Yeah. I said, "You're not getting
that phone." They're looking everywhere
for that phone, mate. They weren't
getting it, bro. They They weren't
getting that phone, buddy. Yeah. You're
going to take my [ __ ] £2,000 [ __ ]
phone and not give it back to me? Are
you [ __ ] mad? Nah, bro.
So, yeah, it's all wrong. The system's
all [ __ ] I'm sure you've like [ __ ]
read stories and that as well. So,
yeah. And you wouldn't get reminded even
if you broke that bell condition. They
probably wouldn't even take you back to
court by then. They probably would have
just dropped it anyways. If you broke
the bell condition, they'll probably
arrest you, question you, and let you
go. You know, they can't remind someone
for three and a half years, you know,
and they wouldn't even remind you even
if you broke a bell condition.
So, so it doesn't work like that, bro.
It don't work like
that. Not even with shoplifterss. So,
yeah, but I get your point anyways. It's
still good to be careful in it.
Yeah, like the other day, bro, if I knew
where one of them women lived, I would
have went on one of their doors. Like,
I'm not even joking. The ones that were
messaging me back and that I wouldn't I
wouldn't have been able to help myself.
And this is why I want to stay away from
them. And then the next day I was I was
fine and then the next day I was fine.
You know, it's just waking up. The thing
that was pissing me off is that, you
know, I'm waking up to people that
ignore normal messages, but they're so
fast to reply to negative messages in in
the way that they're replying back. It's
the way that they were replying back as
well. So, yeah, they really are evil
people in general. They really, really are
evil. You know, 27 years and a half in
counting, bro, ain't been shown a damn different woman. So
yeah. Yeah. I was saying to women on like
uh I said you're evil and I called one
this guy was trying to message me with
his face saying mate. I said I'm not
your mate. Look at your ugly face. You
[ __ ] you look like a child molester.
And I said the woman's I just said this
woman's ugly. Sorry I never said this. I
said you're ugly. But the women the
women I was saying were
evil. I said oh you're evil. All women
are the same. So, I didn't say anything
bad that could have got me nicked cuz
obviously you know what the police are
like nowadays. They're come on people's
doors for anything to do with social
media cuz they ain't got a life and they
can't catch real criminals especially if
it's me. So, I had to still be careful
with what I said cuz you know the police
will find any excuse to come on my door.
So, I was very careful with what I was saying.
So yeah, I just said, "Oh, women are
evil." N that's
it. So So yeah, just want to be getting
[ __ ] nicked. You know what I'm saying?
So yeah, I said to this guy, I said,
"You look like a child molester, man.
Get that ugly face off my [ __ ]
screen." Yeah, it's just the same. I
said, "I'm not your [ __ ] mate. You [ __ ] nerd."
But obviously he was saying stuff back
to me as well. So
yeah. Yeah. I call them piggies. I said,
"What the [ __ ] are you little piggies
doing on my [ __ ] door?" I said, "What
the [ __ ] are you doing?" I said, "What
the [ __ ] are you [ __ ] doing?" That's
what I said to them. I said to them,
"What the [ __ ] are you doing? Have you
got nothing better to do? You [ __ ]
sad bastards. You [ __ ] bully victims.
You [ __ ] pigs." That's what I said to
them. I said, "I want one of you to tell
me to wipe my [ __ ] neck and today. I
want one of you [ __ ] eating [ __ ] to
tell me to w my neck today. I want one
of you [ __ ] pigs to tell me to
[ __ ] w my neck and today." And
that'll be the last thing you do. They
will shut their mouth, bro. They will
try licking my ass on everything, bro.
All of the [ __ ] custody sergeants,
bro. All the I Oh, they're not getting
rude now. Oh, they're not getting rude
now. Why they why they not getting rude now? [ __ ] idiots, you
know, just like before, bro. Cuz
obviously I work with my mom in it this
time. So I could like cuz a lot last
time I was like, "Oh, don't say this.
Don't say that. Don't say this. Don't
say that. Don't say this." And she was
like, "Oh, just like getting involved
and shit." Obviously this time I was by
myself, so no one was stopping me. Yeah,
they did. Yeah, they [ __ ] did.
Yeah. Yeah. You don't know the mad I was
saying mad stuff to them, bro. I was
saying [ __ ] mad stuff to them, bro.
You don't even understand. All
deserved. Nah, I would have just said
wind your neck in, you [ __ ] pig. Who
the [ __ ] do you think you're [ __ ]
talking to, mate? You silly little
uniform. You don't have no authority
over me, mate. Because you're in a silly
little [ __ ] uniform. [ __ ] off you
pig. You know what I mean? Even [ __ ]
even police even the bell even like bell
conditions with the police is not an
actual bail condition. Did I get put in
a cell? Don't ask stupid questions. Why
are you asking stupid questions? Did I
get put in a cell? Are you Are you brain
damaged, bro? Did I get put in a cell? I
I just told you I got arrested. So what
do you think? Yeah, I was shouting and
everything, bro. Shouting and everything.
I'm not scared of them, bro. Not one
little bit, you
know. But anyways, I need to go to the police station anyways on
Friday before my date. It wasn't before
date. It wasn't before a date. I didn't
get nicked before a date. But
yeah, but yeah, but I had to be careful
at the same time because I had stuff to lose.
So I had stuff to lose. So yeah, then I
had to go to court and then the court
let me go. So
yeah. Yeah, it' be funny, eh? Cuz if
they took my phone, I would I would have
took it back off them. Like I would have
physically took it back off them. If
they had found that phone, mate, I would
have personally not been coming out that police station. So
yeah, but lucky they didn't find
it. Yep. I've got my little ways to hide
it. And there's nothing on the phone.
It's just that they weren't going to
give the phone
back because there was no way I was
going to go guilty. So, I wouldn't be
getting that phone back for a very very
long time. And trust me, mate, I would
have got it back. Doesn't Doesn't matter
how how doesn't matter what it took, I
would have been getting that phone back,
mate. You know, cuz you're in my house
now. Yeah. So, yeah. I I would be here now. Probably,
bro. How could I have my phone? Because
they searched my room, you [ __ ]
[ __ ] Because they searched my room,
you [ __ ] to try and find devices, you
[ __ ] idiot. How else? Like, did you
are you being stupid on purpose or something,
bro? How could have I took my phone?
They knocked on the door and I put the
phone in the garden before they ain't
come in the door. You idiot. Obviously.
Duh. They knocked on the door. I put my
phone in the garden. Yeah. I put my
garden. Yeah. And then I opened the door
to them cuz I always do that because I
never know what they were on the door
for. And where they've took so many devices
um before they knocked on the door. I
literally ran in the garden. I stashed
it somewhere. I turned it off. They come
they arrested me and they went through
the whole the kitchen and everything.
They were trying to ring it and
everything, mate. I said, "You're not
getting that phone, matey." Yeah. You
don't come here thinking you're going to
take my phone over a madeup charge and
not give it back. And you should have
saw the look on their face, mate. And
then two days later, I just come back
and took the phone. It was still there.
Luckily, that's how I [ __ ] up my foot
by running back. So,
yeah. Get the voice notes. What voice
notes? There is no voice
notes. There is no voice notes.
Yeah, it's just a grassing community
this, bro. It's a grassing. That's why I
don't get involved with drama or anything
anymore cuz it's just funny to me cuz
they're all grasses on it, ain't they? So, yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Anyways, we're over all that now. [Music] that.
So, that's why I don't really come on
here. It's just the women [ __ ] that was
um pissing me off. That's why I come
back. It's just annoying. And I feel
like this is therapy
sessions, you know, but I don't get
involved with like the drama and stuff
cuz because of the grass and and that so
yeah, and I've only got one bell
condition and the court done me a favor
by giving me that bell condition to be
honest, they done me a favor cuz say
they didn't put put that condition on,
right, I would still be going back and
forth, back and forth, back and forth.
So I thank I thank them for it. I
actually thank them for giving me that
bell condition because it stops me
getting tempted to go back and forth,
back and forth, back and forth, back and
forth. Yeah. You know what I'm saying?
So, in a way, it's a good thing they
done that. I don't want to contact a
[ __ ] I don't want to contact a
[ __ ] grass. That's a [ __ ] good
thing, mate. That's a [ __ ] good. You
know what I'm saying? So, yeah. I'm not
going to get into it, bro. I don't want
to talk about it. It's all
long. Yeah. I don't want to talk about
it, bro. It's pathetic.
Yeah. If they ever come on my door
again, I'm not answering it. So, they're
going to have to get a woman and break the door
down. Well, no, they wouldn't come on my
door ever again. But yeah, but like say
I was involved with [ __ ] I just
wouldn't open the door to him. They'd
have to break the door down, make their
make their job harder.
Not they that they would be coming to the door but
yeah I don't want to talk about it
anymore but I don't want to talk about this [ __ ]
anymore you know it's negative so
yeah I need to follow up definitely sometime this
week. Yeah. Probably going to the police station
again doing this. It's like it's just
like a routine and that.
So, cuz I thought, "Fuck it, bro." Like,
I started to think I let it go time and
time and time again. I was like, "No,
they've come on my door enough [ __ ]
times over made up [ __ ] They've ruined
my [ __ ] trips. They can start doing
some something about these people now."
You know, I'm showing them all the Red
Star [ __ ] and everything.
So, you know, I'm showing them
everything, bro. I've got everything. So, it's
fine. So, just got sick of them coming
to my door. Even over the even over the
trouble now [ __ ] you know. So
yeah, I don't think saying women's evil
is enough to get someone nicked. I think
you'd have to really be saying something
bad and then not saying anything bad to
you. That's why I'm careful with what I
say because of um women also do it as
well. They like to call the police on
people. A lot of people are fast enough
to call the police. So, you got to be
careful with what you say online
anyways. You have to be careful with
what you say online. You can say
anything in the real world. There's no
way of proving it. But with this whole
social media thing when it's come about,
you need to be very careful with what
you're saying. To be honest, you
probably could get nicked for saying
women are evil. You know, it's anything.
You can't even have an opinion on social
media now. But in real life, you could
say anything. You could do anything.
know, I'm not I've done some things and
I've I've got away with it. I'm not
going to tell you what, but yeah, it's
just social media. You know, there's
ways of proving things or
whatever. You can go out right now,
right, to a random person on the street
and be racist, saying the most vile,
foul [ __ ] and literally you wouldn't
get nicked. A cuz they wouldn't care cuz
it's not social media and B there'd be
no way of proving it. You see? So they
there'd be no way of getting you. You
see what I mean?
So yeah, but
obviously Yeah, they are definitely they
are they are evil. Definitely are evil.
Cuz if they weren't evil, you would have
met somebody that weren't like that by
now. I said women are evil. You're all
time wasters. And then this guy tried to
show he sent me his picture trying to
take the piss and they said, "Mate, you
look like a child minister." Like, get
that ugly face away from my screen. I
mean, they could try and nick you for
that, but I mean, saying two things like
that, nah, not really. I mean, they could try,
but nah, that's not enough.
They needed to be needed to be going on
for longer than that.
No, I just said women are evil. They're
all the same and that. So,
um that's not an evil.
No, because now you need to be careful
now because back in the day it was only
threats. Like if you threaten to kill
someone or if you threaten someone, now
it can be anything online. You know, say
you message a woman, oh you're this,
you're that. you get nicked. If they
reported you, you would you would get
nicked. That's the thing. And you
probably would end up in caught. So
that's that's what I'm saying. You need
to be careful with like what you're
saying. And it's the platform you're
saying it on as well. Anything to do
with WhatsApp and Facebook, you need to
be careful with what you're saying. It's
not even threats now. It's anything, you
know, cuz the police have got nothing
better to do. You see? So they can't
catch real criminals. So they just go on
people's door over petty
[ __ ] So you just need to be careful
um with basically what you you say in
real life. You can say what you want.
You can do what you want. You
know on something like WhatsApp you
should be you need to be very careful. You
know, you think I couldn't have said mad
stuff the other day when I was pissed
off, but I know, you know, these grasses
might call the police on. So, I just
said, "Oh, women are evil. Women are
evil." I don't even think I said
scumbags. I said just women are
evil. But that guy did say that he was
ugly and he looked like a child molester
cuz he was trying to troll me. I said that.
So, but in a way what he's but yeah, in
a way what he's doing is sort of
malicious because he's showing his face
trying to get a reaction. So
yeah, but yeah, you need to just be
careful. If you want to say something,
don't say it on social media. Say it in
real life. That's that's what I'm
saying, you know. Don't say that stuff
on social media, matey.
Yeah, but yeah, women are
evil. Yeah, exactly. But I don't give a
bit. Just say women are evil. Whatever.
Yeah, just that's it. Can't be for that.
They are evil, mate. I just can't
believe how many reply to negativity. I
just can't believe it. Like, that just
told me so
much. It told me so much how they ignore positive
messages, you know. Um,
they ignore positive
messages and and reply to negative ones.
Strange. Even if you paid me to go out
and deal with them, I still wouldn't do
it. Even if you gave me £500 to go out
on Saturday, I still wouldn't do it. I
still wouldn't want anything to do with
him, you know.
wish I was born in the 1980s, you
know, and they don't even know what a
connection is. I said to the one in
Italy, why don't you build a connection?
She said, oh, because you asked for my
number. That's not what a connection is.
So, how does that make sense? Because
that is not what a connection means.
This guy is trying to victim, you
know. Look, these this guy's trying to
victimize women again. See, I guarantee
you'll get more replies if you offend
people and call them sus. But will those
will be positive replies that get
anywhere? No, obviously not. You seem
like all you care about is sex and
that's why you want the women. Trust me,
they can sense desperation and
horniness. Again, trying to victimize
women. There's plenty of women, there's
plenty of women in the world that just
want sex. There's plenty of women that
use men for sex. So, that does, that
conversation doesn't even make sense.
You see, it's all backwards. [Laughter]
You know what I'm
saying? So yeah. What's What does she
reply though? The woman from Italy
saying, "Oh, women are evil. We not make
not sleep with you." But
um are you
okay? Um are you okay? I just explained
the normal nice
messages, bro. Do you know these people,
right? Look on Reddit. Yeah. He just
said, "Yeah, what did you reply? Saying
all women are evil will not make them
sleep with you, bro." I was like, "Bro,
are you okay?" I literally just
explained to you about five times that
that is the message that they reply to.
They ignore the normal nice ones and
then they reply to the negative
ones. It my experiences don't suit these
people. So there there's no there's no
point, right, sitting online telling
your experiences when your experiences
don't suit these people. My exper my
experiences don't suit you. They
literally, it completely goes over their
head. Like I've just said, which is the
main mad thing. Yeah. Is that they
ignore normal messages and then reply to
negative ones and then your reply was
saying all women are evil will not make
them sleep with you. Bro, what are you
talking about? I've just said that
that's the message that they've replied
back to again. Victimizing women. And
this is all they ever do on this Reddit,
bro. It's all they ever do is [ __ ]
defend women. You know, there's no point
in opening a [ __ ] conversation if
someone's experiences don't suit
you. You know what I'm saying? I I feel
like my experiences just don't suit
them. You know, so it goes over their head. [Laughter]
Then they make up an excuse that people
only want sex.
Okay, let me uh let uh look at this.
Right. Right. This guy was like, "You
approach them on the street. What do you
think they assume your intentions are?
To play Mario Kart with them?" No, man.
Obviously, you're not interested in them
and they don't know. Uh and they know
victimizing women again. Um I replied,
"Um I don't know. maybe trying to date
and get a [ __ ] relationship since
dating apps don't work. Um, bro, because
it's funny to them and amusing. Bro, they
reply. So, he said he says, "Bro, they
reply to when you say all women are evil
because it's funny to them. It's a
musen." Yeah, you said it yourself now.
H try and stay to stay and get a
relationship having sex, man. You're
just victimizing women
again. That's what I'm saying. You're
again. They ignore normal
messages and reply to negative
ones. You know what I'm
saying? Yeah. Brave of all you want.
Coming from somebody that's probably
never had a woman. Yeah. Women are like
this with you. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay, bro. That's why 80% of
men are struggle struggling. And there's
some people that's never even been in
relationships. Yeah, I know. It's like
it they're like it with me. Yeah. Coming
from somebody that probably doesn't even
leave the house. Yeah. Yeah. Get your
head out your backside, man. Seriously.
Yeah. I'm a creepy weirdo. Well, guess
what, mate? I'd rather be a [ __ ]
creepy weirdo than be a stuck up entitled [ __ ]
um I'd rather be a [ __ ] creepy weirdo
than be a stuck up [ __ ] entitled
[ __ ] I'll tell you that for [ __ ]
nothing. This guy is literally trying to
victimize women on Reddit. I'm on Reddit
right now. He said, "Yeah, what did she
reply though? The women from saying the
women are evil will not make them sleep
with you." I said that you're just
trying to victimize women again because
I've just told you that they ignore
normal messages and they reply to
negative ones. So you're trying to
victimize women and then he says, "Oh,
you approach them on the street. What do
you think they assume your intentions
are to play Mario Kart with them?" No,
man. Obviously you're interested in
Deon. No. I said, "I don't know. Maybe
trying to date and get a relationship."
So he's actually just trying to
victimize women and what you say just
goes over his
head. Yeah. Yeah. That's the point.
Yeah, that's the point. They claim all
Yeah, exactly. They are not interested.
They claim all men are the same and they
can't One sec. They can't find Hold on.
can't. And when one and one one
appears, they reject them. Then then
continue. Yeah. You're Yeah. Stop sugar
coating [ __ ] Like literally stop sugar
coating [ __ ] brother. Yeah. He says
they ignore normal messages because they
are not interested. Yes. That's my whole
point. I said, "Yes, that's the point.
They claim all men are the same and they
can't find a normal nice guy. And when
one appears, they reject them and
continue to to complain." Yes. Yes.
Thank you. You've said it. But these
women are moaning and complaining all
the time. You know, that's funny to
them. You think saying all women are
evil is funny. There's nothing funny
about that. again, victim lies in women,
you know, as if to say that if I didn't
send another negative message, they
would reply. Okay. Say you say you done
a message, you wrote a message abusing
them, laughing about horrendous things.
Would would they find that would that
would they find that funny? No. But they
would reply to it. Again, they're just
trying to victimize women every time,
bro. You don't even get a fair debate.
You literally like it's like the other
day, Joe, right? When it's like, "Oh,
yeah. if you feel like this. Yeah, then
you shouldn't talk to women. Um I said
they said no no they said that you
should leave women alone. I was like
they're not innocent. Don't don't say as
if they're [ __ ] innocent about oh
leave them alone. They're not innocent.
They've caused most of the [ __ ] like all
of the [ __ ] that they've they've caused
over the [ __ ] years or they like oh
if you don't like women stop trying to
victimize them as if they're innocent.
They are not innocent. Like, so
yeah. So, stop [ __ ] trying to [ __ ]
victimize them. Just It's like people
say give up or throw in the towel. Don't
try to victimize them. That's what
pisses me off. [Laughter] Oh
yeah, I'm done in this country. Joe,
bro, you believe it, you don't believe
it. Believe it or don't believe it,
brother. I have got money. I can go out
before I go to Thailand in seven years.
Uh, seven years, seven years, seven
weeks, right? I can make the money back
for the weekend. I'm not doing it. You
can give me £500 right now. You can be
You can be You can give me £500 right
now and I still wouldn't go
out. You know what I'm
saying? You know what I'm
saying? Can't work with Bon today
either. Maybe I did, maybe I didn't. I
can't even [ __ ] remember. You know, I
do not want to deal with them. So, I'm
not contradicting myself and saying
that. I'm not contradicting myself and
saying what I feel about them, but I'm
not dealing with them no more. You know what I'm
saying? Like, they are [ __ ] evil.
They are [ __ ] well evil. Don't
[ __ ] try and tell me how they are not
evil when they [ __ ] well are. Just
get get just just [ __ ] off, man. You
know what I'm saying?
Whatever I say though, whatever you say,
mate, it's what I know, mate. It's not
what I say, mate. It's what I know,
mate. Yeah, that's what it is. It's what I know,
mate. And we all go round and round
again cuz I'm [ __ ] fed up with it.
That's why I'm fed up with them, you
know? Tell me it's a numbers game. I've
tried more than anyone in the world.
They're all the same. They are all the [ __ ] same.
It's like when I used to say to a
certain person, we're not mentioning any
names, right? We're not mentioning we're
not we're not mentioning um a certain
person. He used to say, "You don't know
all women." I said, "I know [ __ ] more
than you." And trust me, my London
accent is is is stronger than yours. You
know, I know [ __ ] more than you,
mate. And I'm saying the same [ __ ] 10
years later, mate. And 10 years don't
[ __ ] lie. Do you reckon these women
just sense that you want sex? Oh, is
that is that the other is that the next
excuse? Oh, is that the other excuse
then? Oh. Oh, is it that they feel that
I just want sex? Oh, is that is that the next
excuse? Oh, is that the next
excuse? Oh, is that the next excuse
then? That you only want sex?
Oh, interesting. Okay, that's a that's
that's an actual that's a new excuse.
Well, what about all these women that
just want sex? Well, let's let's put the
shoe on the other foot again. What about
women that just want sex? And there's a
lot of them out there. So, surely to
God, that doesn't make any sense.
Because if you was just if you just wanted
sex, you would have met a woman that
just wants sex as well.
No. Yeah. I just want sex. Like when I
went on that date on that Thursday when
that woman traveled an hour to see me.
Yeah. I just wanted sex. Yeah. Yeah. I
just wanted sex. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. You got me, bro. I just want a
text. I asked for sex on the date. Yeah,
I got my dick
out. I got my dick out. Yeah, I got my
dick out. Yeah, I got my dick out and
that's what made her run away. Yep, you
got me, bro. Yeah, I said I want to have
sex right now and I got my dick out and
I stood on the table. Yeah, that's why
she didn't feel the vibe. Oh, that's
what it was.
Mindset won't get you anywhere. I said
that mindset is from the negative
experiences. That's how a mindset is
formed. A mindset is formed from
experiences. That's go around in circles
again. Oh yeah. Most women don't want to
be used, Joe. Yeah. That's why they [ __ ]
drug dealers. That's why they get used
by drug dealers. That's why they get
used by [ __ ] Yeah. They don't want
to feel used. Oh, don't they? That's why
there's people in HMP prisons that have
got girlfriends that's got kids. Ah,
yeah. They don't want to feel used, do
they? They don't want to be used. Yeah.
They don't want to be used yet. They're
probably shagging some [ __ ] drug
dealer right now or some domestic
abuser. Yeah. But they don't want to be
used. No. And they don't like they don't
like um they don't like nasty guys. They
only want good guys as well. Yeah, that's another thing.
Yeah. You're an [ __ ] or you're a drug
dealer? Nah, mate. You're not getting
anywhere in this
country unless you're an [ __ ] or you
a drug dealer,
Joe. Yeah. Unless you're a drug dealer, mate.
Yeah. Some sort of criminal.
Yeah. But it's been that way for a long
time in this
country. It's been that way for a long
time in this country. or somebody that
has tattoos or they moan about men being
all the same and complain about men and
then they go with these drug dealers. Yeah, same
old. So, you're talking about mindset.
What is your mindset supposed to
be? Let's just play dumb here. What What
is your mindset supposed to be? That
your experiences are not like that? What
is your mindset supposed to be when
you've had nothing but your time wasted?
You get these ghosters, you get these
piss takers. What is your mindset
supposed to be? Like if you could if you
could elaborate it, I could I could
understand. Is it supposed to be? I'm
just I've just asked that question that
they're not all like that and and live
in denial and live delusional and be
delusional and live in
denial, you know. What do you want me to
be in denial or what? I don't get it. You
know, [ __ ] hell, bro. How about you
wanted a relationship and sex? How about that?
Bye-bye. How about you want a
relationship and a sex and sex? How
about you want Oh, and that woman owes
you nothing. Um, do you know what it is,
Joe? that just tries to excuse their
shitty behavior. That is another um word
invented by a simp um that's used in the
wrong context to defend their shitty
behavior because it's used in the wrong
context. Yeah. It's an excuse for women
doing shitty things. When a woman does a
shitty thing, it's oh well, she don't
owe you nothing. That's their way of
trying to justify their bad behavior.
That's been going on for years as well.
because we've never ever heard a man
doesn't owe you anything. So, it must be
true what I'm saying. We have never ever
heard ever my years on the internet have
I ever heard a man doesn't owe you
anything. It's used to
um defend women shitty behavior and it's
used in the wrong
context, you know. God, that saying is so [ __ ]
annoying, you know.
They they they they they they [ __ ] do
owe you something. They [ __ ] well do.
So yeah, you you just making excuses for
women again, Joe. I gave you a perfect
example of a date that I went on last
month that wasted my time and I didn't
even like her. But it's a good
example. But it's a good example. It's a
You know, they approached you, they met
you, you was normal, you was confident.
Yeah. They didn't even go on a second
date with you, which it would have took
a second date to even get to know if you
vibe with someone. So, this is what
we're dealing with in this country.
Prime example. Then after that was the
[ __ ] ghosting. Then after that, we
see an evil woman in America be able to
get into a relationship whenever she
wants. I'm like, I'm not fighting this
losing battle anymore. [ __ ] this. I'm
not fighting a [ __ ] losing battle anymore, bro.
No, no, no. Obviously, I would have got
with her. Obviously, you know, it was
like I I would have and I would have.
But I didn't have any other option. What
did you want me to do, you [ __ ]
idiot? You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
I'm I'm nowhere near 30. I've already
had a girlfriend. Try again. And I've
had chances to be in relationships as
well. I've also I've also had chances to
be in relation more relationships as
well. And I'm nowhere near 30, mate. So
try again with your boring saying. Um I
listen I didn't have anything else.
Yeah. I didn't have anything else. I
never said I I why I didn't like her. I
meant I would have got with her if she
wanted to keep meeting. Yeah. But I
could have went out and got something
better. But it's the whole point of it.
It's the point of it. You
know, you know, she's [ __ ] 32. I was
better looking than her and she's still
trying to say she doesn't feel the vibe
and there was nothing wrong said. There
was nothing wrong done. There was
nothing. I'd start recording my dates,
but there's no point because you're just
going to make another excuse to defend
women just like you do with the
approaches. You remember when I started
putting them approaching videos out, it
was, "Oh, maybe they do have boyfriends
or maybe it's this or maybe it's that."
So, I just gave up with the with the
pulling approaching videos on this
channel because you're always just going
to make excuses regardless. So, I'd be
wasting my time. I would just be wasting
my time cuz you're always going to defend
women or victimize them at the at the
very least. So, why would I waste my
[ __ ] time? You
know, I'd go on a date and you'd
probably tell me, "Well, one toe was
bigger than the [ __ ] other." You'll
always make excuses for women because
you don't understand. You people are
older. Yeah. You don't know what the
dating game is like now.
And you need to stop saying about how
other people in relationships because
I've been in one. I've been in one. I've
been in one and I've also and I've also
had more and I've also had other chances
to be in them. It doesn't make what I
say any less true. It doesn't make what
I say any less true. It's like uh
earlier when I was on Reddit, this guy
was like, "Oh, you need a good social
circle of friends. I've got friends.
I've got people that look up to me. I've
never met anyone through friends. I'm
not saying no one's ever met anyone
through friends and people don't
nowadays. I'm saying in my experience,
if I waited until I met somebody through
friends, I would be a virgin. Therefore,
it can't be right for everyone. That's what I'm
saying. And then it's like, oh, you need
to get better friends. It's not about
getting better friends, bro. It's
biology. Everyone's selfish. Everyone's
out for themselves. It's not about a
good friend or a bad friend. People are selfish.
Even family are
selfish, you know, like generally like
speaking like even they can be selfish.
So why why the [ __ ] would you be why the
[ __ ] would heterosexual male friends
hook you up with a woman? It doesn't
make sense. You know what I'm
saying? So I've just asked him any my
mindset be I'm still waiting. Come on.
on. It is them. If it wasn't them, I
wouldn't be going Thailand. If I
generally didn't think it was them,
right, why the [ __ ] am I going [ __ ]
Thailand? See, it doesn't make you know
what I'm saying, bro. For the laugh of it. You
know, why did Adman go to Thailand? For
the laugh of it. So, that's why they
they they never [ __ ] you know, fly
again. So, like, what the
[ __ ] I need to go and get some meat for
this barbecue soon. [ __ ]
hell. So, I know they can't sense that
you just How would they sense that you
just want sex from them? So,
so Peter after all this time and
everyone in what advice would you give
to someone starting out? Leave the
country, leave England, avoid America,
avoid Australia, avoid any Westernized
country and go Thailand.
That's what I I used to give this advice
to this black guy. I said, "Use use an
escort and then go Thailand." Simple.
Done. That's what I'd say. Don't even
waste your time in this country with
these [ __ ] women. They're all the
same, mate. You don't want to waste
years of your life like I wasted years
of my life thinking that they were
different, you know? And if and this is
how you know I it's the women in this
country as well because when you go to
central London, that's when you get the
numbers. Even though sometimes the
numbers don't get anywhere, but [ __ ] all
that, you know, it's it's it's it is the
women in this country as well because
when you go around your area, you won't
get no numbers. Yeah. When you go
central London and you speak to somebody
from Russia or [ __ ] where's the other
country again some like France or
somewhere, you will get further than you
would with English. That also tells you
that it's British women. Obviously
French are no good and and Russian are
no good as well, but you get further.
You would get further like than you
would with the British. The British
women are the worst. The Americans avoid
avoid like the plague, you
know. But yeah, yeah, they're they are
the worst ones, you know. That's why
when you go to central London, you get
like French people and stuff, you see.
So like South American, you might get
somebody from South America, you might
get someone from France who you might
get a number from, you know, but
anything to do with Australian,
Australia or America or England.
Nah, Australians claim they got boyfriends as well.
Yeah. Yeah. Thailand, South America even. Yeah.
But you want to avoid America and you
want to avoid um
England. I still think England's worse
than America when it comes to dating,
but who knows? You could be an American
and American say the same thing about America. You understand? So yeah. So
yeah, but I'm not going to move to
Thailand. Why would I Why would I move
to Thailand when I have money? When I get good
money, you know, women are not my life like
man. Joe, you're not going to get a
reaction, buddy. So just just stop it on
this channel. You're not going to wind
anyone up. You're not going to just just
stop it, bro. It's boring now. It's
really really really boring now. Like it
was fun at first. Oh yeah, the windups,
bro. It's boring now. And the thing that
made it even more boring is the fact
that they're grasses. It's boring. Like,
I'm not even going to sit there and say
something about common sense. It's
boring now, bro. Give it a rest. It's
getting It's getting really, really,
really, really old
now. You know, you couldn't even wind me
up when you're talking about somebody
that's a grass, you know?
So just just just stop it, bro.
Please also and that's another thing as well.
Um yeah, but the women are not
westernized. No, it's not westernized
because the women are not westernized.
Westernized people go there for
non-westernized women. So the women are
not westernized. But anyways, um yeah,
like Joe, I could go out every week,
every Saturday, spend £80, make the
money back, and just be a [ __ ] and try
to get into women's bodies and still not
contradict the fact that I think they're
all the same and they're all evil. But
that's a waste of my time because I
don't want to I don't want to I don't
want anything to do with them. So, you
know, why would I why would I do that?
They've proven time and time and time
and time and time and time and time what
they're about, you know? So, why would
you even do that? It doesn't even make any
sense, you know? You could just say you
don't like them and just try to get in
their body, but Nick is. But what's the
point that it doesn't make any sense?
They're all the
same. They reply back to
negativity. I think people just need to
say on Reddit that in these westernized
countries, play at your own risk. Most
of them are not going to be interested.
That's if they had said that, then I'd
be like, okay, well, you can't really
complain. They're telling you what it
is. But they don't say stuff like that
though. Frenchie, French, Frankie. They
want to tell you it's about confidence.
They want to tell you it's about numbers
g. It's a numbers game. If they had
literally lied it on the table in that
in that in that way, then I'll be like,
"Okay, well, you can't really complain."
You know, you see what you see is what
you get. But they want to do anything
but take away the fact that women are
ignorant, that they're stuck up, that
they've got unrealistic expectations,
and that the fact that they should be
interested. They should be interested
just like you would. You
know, this guy this guy um this guy made
a point here, right? This is a good
point. though out in public you'll see
lots of couples on the street. So, every
man with a partner is either a drug
dealer or an [ __ ] He is either a
drug dealer or he's a [ __ ] Yes.
Yes. You're not even making sense. Yes.
100%. Either a drug dealer or a
[ __ ] 100%, bro. I swear to God.
Yeah. Either Either a drug dealer or a
[ __ ] Unless they're old, like in
their 40s or so. Yes. Drug dealer or a
[ __ ] Just like when you go into
Weather Spoons, that's all you ever see
women with is with [ __ ] or
criminals. Literally, brother, that's
the only kind of people that you see
them with. White, tall, [ __ ] cocky
[ __ ] That's the only people you
see them with. That's the only people
you ever see them with. That's why nice
guys finish last. You
see? Yeah. Nice guys finish last, brother. Yeah.
That's all you ever see them with. Yeah.
Not every single one of them is with a a
drug dealer, but the other half is with
with with a [ __ ]
100%. Or a domestic abuser. Domestic
abuser, drug dealer. Uh
yeah. He come from the nice guy. Because
people used to complain that they were a
nice guy and they couldn't get a woman.
So why do you think they take the piss
out of nice guy? It's a way of victimizing women
again, right? And then this guy said to
me, um, be a [ __ ] then. Be a
[ __ ] Why am I going to be a
[ __ ] I can't be a [ __ ] You're
either a [ __ ] or you're not. You can't change
yourself. He said, "Oh, why don't you be
a [ __ ] You can't just be a
you know, you can't just have a dick
coming out your
head, you know. So, and they do like
drug dealers because they they they've
told me as well. They've actually told
me like one in Newcastle before like me
cuz [ __ ] because I was from London and
she thought I was a drug dealer. They do
like drug dealers. Definitely drug
dealers. Drug dealers and abusers. Why
do you think there's so many women
victims of abuse? Because it's the men
that they go for. You feel me?
Well, I'm just going to make myself a cup of
coffee. Hey, Joe, you still there? I
could answer your question, by the way,
if you want.
I can answer your question if you really
want and I could be a bit
cheeky. I just want to make sure you're still
there. How you want to know how how
people like that can hold out a
relationship? I could answer you if you really
want, but I don't think you will like the answer.
No, but I do need to be careful that I I
do need to like stay off [ __ ] I need
to stay off of [ __ ] Reddit and and
stop arguing with these women, bro. Cuz
you I don't know how my temper is. You
know what I'm saying?
So, I won't do some of that ant. I'm
smarter than that. But [ __ ] you
know, it's [ __ ] going somewhere with
an axe and doing 18 months in prison. [ __ ]
that. Throw up that city. Cuz then they
win. Say you done something like that,
then these evil women win. They get
their last laugh. You don't even have
your freedom now. You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, that's what I would say, bro. Just [ __ ]
uh just leave um just leave this
country. Don't even enjoy the drinking
anymore. Well, I do need to go
get you have money. You can be decent
looking. you can have a good personality
and you still can't get anyone. They
don't tell you that on Reddit though, do
they? They don't tell you that on Reddit
that you can have money, you can be
decent looking, you can have a good
personality, and you still can't get
anyone. You'll still get, "Oh, I've got
boyfriend." Oh, [ __ ] You are
s this guy's a
sib you know what he said he I said no
all women are evil I give up he said
okay okay give up that's fine less
competition for me s simp that's
literally what s would say less competition for
Bro, we live in two different countries.
What a [ __ ]
sin, bro. I'm starting to think this
Reddit is for the simp. Less competition
for you. What a [ __ ] sin.
And I And I take it personal when people
say, "Oh, uh, you need you need better
friends. There's nothing wrong with my
friends. None of them are criminals.
None of them has ever been to prison
except for my man, right? Yeah. And
[ __ ] like there's nothing wrong with
the people that I associate myself with.
Yeah. Yeah. There's more Australian
people in Thailand. Yeah, there is.
Adman's told me. But there Australian
men there to get women. Yes, there's
Australian people over there to get
women. To get non-westernized women.
Jose had some nice lamb button last
night. Have food. Cook for you. Get
money. You're living the life. really life. So
yeah, I can't believe people got jealous
over that [ __ ] Borggan. She's [ __ ]
stinking, mate. And that's another thing
uh uh Frenchie Frenchy that evil evil
below average looking women. Yeah, evil
below average looking women. and um can
get a man whenever they want. Now, that
should tell you everything you need to
know about Dane as a man as well, that
you should just give up, give up, give
up, give up, give up, give up, give up. You
know, I'm just happy I'm 27, bro. You
know what's so mad? Certain people are
going on holiday now. Yeah. They're
doing what I'm doing when I was [ __ ]
23. I was doing that [ __ ] when I was 23.
So you you need to see the positives,
bro. Like I was saying to you earlier,
there's a positive in all this. You learn at
27. 27 is not that old, you know? Like
it's not that old, man. you know, even
if you're close to 30, like you learned
at 27 what women are really
like, you know, and and you gave them
every single chance to prove you wrong
every single time you went out. Every
single time you went on these dates, you
gave them chances upon chances upon
chances to prove you wrong. And they
haven't haven't. They haven't. You gave
them so many chances, you know? They
haven't. So they must be all the same. Yeah,
Brazil. Yeah, Brazil's easy as
well. Yeah, it's a non-westernized
country, mate. That's why it's a
non-westernized country declared. So
yeah, all women on the [ __ ] same,
mate. I've been saying it for 10
years. I've been saying it for [ __ ]
10 years, mate. Yep.
Yep. Hey, bro. I'll be back later anyways.