[Music]
Sorry about that, mate.
Probably. Yeah. Antman says, "Why do you
entertain these people? They're
borderline retarded." And you know what? He's so right on
YouTube. Like he's so right. They're [ __ ] idiots.
Yeah. [ __ ] yeah. [Music] That's a big Yeah.
Yeah, I won't be able to get after
today. I don't think [ __ ] pointless pointless
mate. Yeah, it's pointless. [ __ ]
[ __ ] I a [ __ ] self projector
from the back of the world. Selflected. What
about the P?
These people will never stop defending women.
Oops. Why don't rich fans
money. Probably that guy come on here
saying three month is
nothing. He's got to be trolling man.
Well, trying to troll cuz they can't
troll me cuz it's spastics.
Someone's probably heard me say that I
got that. They're [ __ ] absolute idiots,
mate. [ __ ] hell,
man. Why did my sister's boyfriend have
to get me into [ __ ] gambling, lad? You know, bye-bye.
Yeah. No one bothers me cuz I don't gamble
anymore. Cuz I don't gamble. And um I
don't go out
clubbing, but that's where he's got that [ __ ]
um that's where he got that free grand
from, bro. You got it from
me. Probably some idiot living in his
mom's basement. 47 my ass. Gone to
Thailand six times. My ass, mate. Don't
even sound [ __ ]
believable. That that many
times. And he loves Thailand. And he's
talking out of his [ __ ] ass, mate.
Think about it, bro. Would someone go
somewhere six times if it was really
really that mid? No, you wouldn't. I've
been to Amsterdam once. I'll never go again. It's
[ __ ] It's actually [ __ ] bro. I think I
made the most of it as
well. You know, when you actually look
back on it, it's actually [ __ ] Belgium
was [ __ ] as well, so obviously you
wouldn't go there again.
So, you don't like Thailand, but you've
been to Thailand. But you've been to
Thailand six times. That makes sense, isn't
it? Yeah. Doesn't even make no sense,
mate. [ __ ] idiots, man. Absolute
idiots. Absolute [ __ ] idiots. That [ __ ] [ __ ] Oh man.
Oh, [ __ ] bad on you. Yeah. Yeah. Just a
bit. Yeah, they're not people with
different opinions. They're just want to
be trolls. That's what they are,
bro. 3K a month. Where the 3K a [ __ ] month come
from. They're [ __ ] idiots.
So you don't like Thailand, but you've
been to Thailand six times? No.
it. The real question is what the [ __ ]
was you doing in Thailand?
Who's this? Nixie, another evil woman. Probably
Yeah. Turn the man.
Let's see how my main channel's getting on. [Music] Yeah. Heat.
Everybody's gone. My
what if I play some ret now live people join
Nah, it's never happened. It's been a
long time since I've played roulette
maybe. I could give it a little while. No
[ __ ] No, it scares me,
bro. That game scares me, bro. I've had too many uh
bad bad times with it.
Bad memories. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah. 100 pound won't hurt though, would
it? On the old roulette.
Nah, I'm not playing that [ __ ]
I ain't [ __ ] playing that [ __ ] mate. No
way. I was only
joking. Where is that? Yeah.
Yeah, you know what? If it was pounds,
then I might have been tempted to play
online with that. I'm not playing that
euro [ __ ] [ __ ] that.
Nah. Nah, bro. I'm not playing that.
[ __ ] that. All
right. Playing that [ __ ]
I don't want to let more down. Yeah.
Yeah. One second. Okay, bro. One sec.
Monty, I don't defend you cuz N spoke
[ __ ] behind my back. That's why I don't
even stick up for you with the whole
[ __ ] money mic thing of
that cuz I've seen that and you talk
[ __ ] about me on your live stream.
That's why I just leave you to it to be
honest. To be honest with you, bro. I
just leave you to it. Yeah. There you
are, mate. Yeah. Yeah. Don't talk about
nothing on here, please. You know, anything, you know.
Yeah. Have a chill chat. Yeah.
Yeah. [ __ ] Yeah, man.
[ __ ] don't let these [ __ ] just
[ __ ] Yeah, it's hard. It's hard to
say. But yeah, just you see what I sent
you earlier the chat. It's [ __ ]
weird, isn't it? These are all weirdos,
PJ. No, but it's weird what they're
saying. They always It's the way they
talk about people. It's weird, isn't it?
Foundation. You find it. You find it.
Yeah, it is weird. It is weird. It's not
that PJ. Yeah. Money M's been shouting
me out all day. Yeah. I told Money Mark
and Timmy to come to this place where
it's only 15 minutes from rejoin. Yeah,
let me rejoin. I can barely hear you.
One second. Let me rejoin. Hold on. Yes. Yes. Hello.
You might have to kick. Yeah. Are you
Yeah. Yeah. I can hear you. I'm not
staying on for long. Nothing. Yeah.
Yeah. Cuz I've actually I'm not coming
back live anymore. I'm going to I can't
be bothered with it. I can't be bothered
with it. It's not like it's the same repeating people
and you know they just the they the [ __ ]
bags. I've told Money Mike today. Nal's
even told him today come up here where
we are. Well, where we near there's a field near
you know that same argument has been
going on for like two weeks now. Yeah.
Yeah, I know. I know. And I'm getting
sick of it myself. It's not like even
that money m dragging Natalie's mom
involved in it and [ __ ] like that. You
know what I mean? You're just going to
have to ignore it, bro. Like what else?
no. I've been trying to ring him to meet
to meet and that and he's just not
having it and I'm done. I'm done with
playing these little games where money
Mike and Timmy are running around
town because I don't think they want to
fight. I just think they just wanted
look I'm outside. I'm outside. But when
Timmy's on his own, he doesn't leave his
[ __ ] house for anybody. Yeah. Yeah.
Timmy's not done no videos today, is it?
Yeah. Yeah. has done a couple of videos
today. Yeah. I ain't seen it. Yeah.
Yeah. About me and that with money. You
got a new channel?
Um, no. No, he's through Mad World. It's the same.
No, he hasn't. There's nothing on the channel.
You must have deleted them. Yeah,
because I I'll make the video today.
Hey, did you see him having a mental
breakdown the other day when he's like,
"Bonnie, you bacon." I was laughing my
ass off, bro. Yeah. I'm not meeting him
in town or outside pubs where he wants
to meet where this came. I'm not doing
that. I told them come up here like
they're like same repeating people
talking about you're talking about um
Tibby and Mike, is it? Have you found it,
babe? Who are you talking about? Them
two. money. Yeah, money might continue.
No, when you said same repeated people,
you're talking about them, too, is it?
No, I'm talking about the full [ __ ]
community, mate. Yeah, but they don't do
it on yours. I've been on your live
streams. They do on large.
Yeah, this only so many there's because
there's new people in this community.
So, some people some people's had enough
of gone on to talking or or probably
it's a little game they playing. I don't
know these little bastards on this
community. He ain't aware PJ. Yeah,
I had my life. The only good one on this
community is unworthy clock. You know
him. All these are people who who's good
PJ. Some of the trolls back in the day
are good people. I'm not calling all the
trolls prince. Ben was good, but I
thought Ben was good, but he's not good.
So, I don't know who I can't trust
anyone because the No, you can't trust
anyone in the D community. I actually
thought that Ben was I thought that Ben
was all right.
There you get some funny trolls in this
community. I'm not saying that when they
they do troll funny, you know, but then
you get the weird ones what go for your
life and that's a no no for me now. Like
I've got me I've got a family. Yeah.
Yeah. And with that, you
know, and with this [ __ ] money mike
running around getting cherries
overnight on myself, it's it's pathetic.
He's a full grown man in his [ __ ] 30s
or 40s or whatever else like that running around
casinos shouting out for fights and
stuff like that. Yeah, it's mad.
Like P PJ they think I've been kicked
out of Manchester on YouTube. They all
think I've been kicked out of
Manchester. They think I don't have
mates in Manchester or they think I
don't have any, you know, they think I'm
a loner and they really really don't know me
and you know, you know, I got mates.
Yeah. You know, and it's not that I'm
not bringing my mates involved in this
like broke. Look what they say to me
every day. They they call me skin even
though I throw them money.
It doesn't matter PJ. You can show them
all the money in the world. Money
doesn't matter. These people will always
be on about money because they think
that money makes the world go around.
Obviously, it does, but it doesn't.
You know, money is just [ __ ] money.
Everybody gets money. So, I don't know
why they get in on money when everybody
gets paid money. Yeah. Do you know what I
mean? if these actually knew how much
I've come out with and whatever. I'm not
asked either way. I don't come out with
much, but I do come out with much, you
know. But these can sit you and say no
one. You get like two You get like 2K a month.
I'm not really saying how much you come
out with on your PJ. It's got nothing to
do with anyone. I told you I was
actually being serious how much I get,
but you don't believe me. But I'm being serious.
Yeah, I know. I know. But you also
frauding as well. I can also do that.
It's not hard. I can make money. I can
make more money. But I'm not doing that.
Fraud. I don't fraud. It is fraud when you
use private rented house.
No, I don't do that money.
So the house what you living in, it's
your house. Yeah.
So you only renting the bedroom. I don't
rent I don't rent it to anyone.
cuz you do
PD on that anyways. Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Anyways,
change change subjects on that. Anyways,
yeah. It's not that
like you coming on here with your women
and I'm only being a friend, PJ. Yeah. I'm
only I'm only giving you advice. Proper
real advice. Not by these little laws on
EPJ. Yeah, real talk. Yeah, you need to
stop coming on YouTube bringing up these
women and doing whatever you need. Huh?
Getting turned down and whatever. Yeah.
Like I wouldn't do that to me. They just
piss me off. You know what I mean? Yeah.
It's not like you like these on here.
They're not just posting us on YouTube
PJ. They're posting us on different websites. What once?
He don't get it. Does he PJ? No. If you
Google right Google your name in um
[ __ ] Google. Yeah, I have before.
Yeah. Then then all all loads of
different stuff comes up, don't they?
And if you go on to Dre's UK's channel
and that then if you scroll down on I
think it's on um his um post So if you
go to his post and then scroll down and
then you see all these different links
like different websites. Yeah. So
and you know what you're doing on
YouTube, it's not
helping you out. Do you know what I
mean? Trying to tell the best I can. I'm
not doing anything illegal obviously. Is
it? No. No. No. It's not. You're not
doing anything illegal. No. But what you
do it can come across
um people will see it differently like
you got anger issues like proper like
you know like turn you down where with
me if a woman turn me down or said no I
just okay thank you but see you later
waste your time it's not about even
saying I've got a boyfriend I don't
really care about that it's [ __ ]
see I wouldn't go out called approach in
any way. You've not been in the dating
game for a long time cuz you've not
tried for a long time. So, you know what
I mean? So, you Yeah, but PJ,
it's not hard to explain because I know,
you know, I I wouldn't go out called
approach in either [ __ ] way. And it's
not a thing I would do. It's not that I
done that when I was a teenager when um
social media weren't out when [ __ ]
you YouTube weren't out or the internet
weren't out proper know that led then
you you had to go downtown or you had to
go out and call the approach back then
when you were younger but now at our age
we don't do that it's more
social media online stuff and stuff like that
now. And you know, and that's how it is
these days. She just say if I was
walking downtown and I was a woman and
you come up to me and ask me, "Oh, can I
have your number?" I'll be like, "I'm
sorry. I'm not here to get it on. I'm
here to do my shopping or I'm here to
know." Parents want to make you Yeah.
You swimming on YouTube. What a [ __ ]
you know, single and you, you know,
who's this? Who's this fried egg?
The fried egg.
Oh, fried egg. He's always on my
channel. He's always following me around
at Fried Edge.
Yeah, Cactus. I was just about to say
that, Cactus. I was literally just about
to say that.
Sorry about you, Monty. Yeah, that's
that's that's actually uh that's
actually a valid point, Cactus. I was
about to say that. Well, what did you
catch, Chef? He said PJ would be a
virgin if he did it cold approach and
did social media instead. That's
actually true. Well, not not a virgin
cuz I've used escorts. But in terms of
like non-escorts, yeah, that's that's true though.
Not like you
think when I went to Manchester I don't
think no the first well when I went to
Manchester do you remember when I done
that approach and I got laid
yeah and Natalie got it right and
Natalie even said as well why you're not
getting laid either because it's
London you know London it's a city of
stuck up [ __ ] in London. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Cuz it was it was easier in
like Nottingham and other places was
easier than than here. Yeah. Cuz
different areas, different places. Yeah.
But even Americans that come here,
Monty, your [ __ ] do you know you get
Americans in London, you know, because
they've got money, you know, so they
can't control PGA. I'm just being
serious for what I'm see what what I
see. you know, so don't think I'm
trolling you by saying
you go on. So go on um meet me um go on something.
Would you agree? Would you agree that
that even the Americans in London are [ __ ] Yeah.
People see people differently. PGA and
this is what people need to understand.
Like some people will see you as cute
then some people will see you as ugly.
Do you know what I
mean? You know what I'm saying, don't
you? Like people are see differently and in
people you know people go for different things.
Do you know what you know what Antman
said cactus? He said they're just not
interested in this country. That's that's what Antman said.
Is there is there anyone who you know
out there PJ like women who you talk to
like for a long time but never dated
just being a friend or
one but she likes black guys um right
um see the best like Why you ask Monty?
Why don't you ask your friend to hook me
up? I just I'm not going to say his
name, but you just did in a way. You
just did. Yeah, I'm trying. Yeah, but
hopefully they didn't hopefully they
didn't like um do it. But yeah,
he's a m he's he's a [ __ ] dad. He's got
[ __ ] We don't do that anymore. What
about Whiteheads? Can I get with one of
the Whiteheads daughters? I don't speak
to Whiteheads no more.
We should try to get back in contact
with them because they're round about my age, bro.
Well, you can get in contact with them.
I'm [ __ ] not.
Okay. Okay. Yeah, he got my brains last
time I've heard. Yeah, he is. Yeah, but
Cactus, why is that though? There's got
to be a reason though,
Cactus. But yeah, um Monty,
um yeah, [ __ ] what I was saying is um
have you thought about getting cold
approached on PGS?
I've got cold approached last bank
holiday a few weeks ago. I got cold approached.
Well, I was in a club, but yeah. Well,
there you go. So you don't have to go
cold approach and let you get cold. When
I went on the date, she [ __ ] wasted
my time, Monty. I was going to p the
drink. Let me m Let me m Natalie wants
me. One second. And I limp to the [ __ ] date,
cactus. And then she [ __ ] said she
didn't feel the [ __ ] vibe. I was
like, "You [ __ ] what? You cheeky me."
You know what I'm saying? They're just
not interested in this
country. Pride egg.
Yeah. That just sounds mad to say that.
It's the truth, but it's it's mad. Yeah.
So, I have been approached.
It's not like you also you've also got
to think if a woman's been in abusive
relationships, you because when women
have been in abusive relationship, they
they're scared. They're more scared of a
man. Yeah. got money. I got a [ __ ] in
the alleyway from somebody in a club.
That's where you're going wrong. P.
Yeah, man. You're supposed to be growing
up, man. Not getting [ __ ] in
alleyways, lad. You're supposed to be settling down.
But it was funny, buddy.
It's not [ __ ] It's not funny.
Do you not understand that? You know,
when you talk about London Yeah. You
know, Manchester's basically just
getting like London now. You do realize
that? It's getting like everywhere page.
Yeah. No, but when did you last? Listen,
Bonnie. When did you last go to Manchester?
Oh, last I don't know. I haven't been
for years. Manchester.
Yeah. Well, I went it two. No, last
year. Was it last year or the year
before? I still talk to my I still talk
to Lemn. I still talk to Lemma on and
off. Often. Yeah. Yeah. I think I went last summer.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I used to go a lot, Monty, but
it's getting just like London now, man.
I just thought I'd give you advice. Just
[ __ ] just stop just stop it because
you're getting posted everywhere PG and
it's not looking good and if women see
that and then it's a no no. You know
what I mean?
So, I just
just find some just
you I can't help you if you don't need
if you can't if you don't want help, you
know. But just be yourself, PJ. That's
it. Just be yourself.
Yeah. I think we should meet up.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
What? [ __ ] I [ __ ] I don't know PJ.
I don't want to meet anyone off YouTube
to be honest with you anymore, man. I
really don't know. To be honest with
you, it's just [ __ ] freaky fine. Has
Trevor still here? [ __ ] knows. Anyway,
PT, I'm going to shoot off. Yeah, I'll
go. Never mind. Before you go, yeah, he
caused us he caused us a lot of
problems. Not nice about all that.
He hasn't fought my life up anyway. He's
a He's a [ __ ] man. Right. Anyway,
PT, I'm off. Yeah. All right, mate. Just
[ __ ] just try just [ __ ] don't put
[ __ ] on on here about women. Don't cuz
in the you Yeah. Go on. I'll let you go
anyways. But yeah, I'm not see then.
Catch you later, Jamie.
They're just not interested in this country. So, uh,
yeah, London is the worst, but it's like
it everywhere, man.
Westernized. Yeah. [ __ ] hell, man.
Yeah. In cold approach, I'd be a virgin.
I didn't use their schools.
Eh, why you can never compare?
compare? No, never
travel again in this country, bro. There's no
need. They're just not interested in
this country. That just sounds mad when
that man said it, but I think he's right
cuz you see like other people approach,
don't you? And they don't really get anything either.
So yeah, I just don't think they're
interested in this country.
Yeah, there's lots of laws in in this country, but
Yeah. I don't want to
Do you think 3K a month is good for doing nothing, Cactus?
Yeah, that's a lot for doing nothing, is it?
Yeah. Got put down
for Yeah. I had this guy come on here
before you joined trying to say he's 47.
He said Thailand's [ __ ] even though he's
been to Thailand six times which makes
no but even though he said it was [ __ ]
And then he said that he gets three grand a
month and then he's just he's he's a [ __ ] idiot
man. So Thailand's [ __ ] but you've been
there six times. Yeah, that makes sense. Yeah. Yeah.
And he said, "I've been with more women
than you." I said, "You [ __ ] a, mate.
You might be 47, but you
know." Yeah. And he was trying to say it's
nothing. Trying to tell me how much
money I've got. I've got enough money to
[ __ ] go out. [ __ ] go out to my who
I want, you know? Yeah.
It's like Amsterdam. When I went to
Amsterdam, it was kind of
[ __ ] from the escorts and the weed. I
would never go back to Amsterdam ever
again cuz I didn't like it. You know what I'm
saying? If you've been to Thailand six
times, why would you go somewhere six
times if it's [ __ ] So, you just t [ __ ]
mate. It's that [ __ ] Tony account.
Yeah. No, I don't
think I've got about 2K in savings, so
it's not bad. We're getting there again, is it? Yeah.
Yeah. Probably won't be forever though.
3K a month probably won't be forever,
mate. So, I have to start looking at
other things. But money's money, bro. It
comes and goes. It's nothing to really worry about. Yeah. But
yeah, well we got something lined up. So yeah.
Yeah. What do you think of USA is he
cactus? She's a broke ass. She's broke,
mate. She's [ __ ]
broke. She is proper broke.
The audacity asking me if I'm poor. [ __ ] hell,
man. Imagine that cactus.
Sorry about that,
bro. Speaking to
someone found your
mama, bro. You're probably on benefit yourself, mate.
Yeah, you're probably on benefits your
[ __ ] self. So just just
sh Why do you care how people get money
but how people don't get money? You
should worry about your own
life. This is what I need to say, bro.
Why don't you worry about your own life, you
know? Worry about your [ __ ] own life
and stop worrying about other people's.
Where's your friend Tony gone as well?
Yeah, I'm just on
Reddit. I just message these women on
Reddit asking them why they're so bloody evil.
I don't laugh at people that's got a job and pay
bills. Doesn't matter where I get it
from. Cactus Peter Belly's got his
ways. It's hard to afford to go to
America, bro. But it take me about month and a
half. It's uh quite expensive on that.
But um I've got my ways, [Music]
bro. Yeah, cuz he was trying to say 3k a month is
nothing. You were trying to say 3k a
month is nothing. And that guy doesn't even work.
Yep. Literally, Cactus. Yeah. Tony, the
guy that said Thailand is [ __ ] Yeah.
He's been there six times, bro. It's
just a stupid account that probably
doesn't even work. Like, it's it's a stupid
account. No, he's chatting [ __ ]
I should have clocked on when he was
saying about [ __ ] going to Thailand
six times, but yeah, [ __ ] You'd go
somewhere six times. That [ __ ] That
makes no sense
whatsoever. I went to uh Middlesbrough. Complete [ __ ] right? Complete
[ __ ] And uh I'll never go
again. Leads. Complete [ __ ] Never go there
again. The lead is [ __ ]
man. Did I make I make new accounts and
they ban me after like a day or
two? know that Tony is an idiot,
mate. He comes on here, bro, and he
starts trying to wind me up. I'm just
going to go to his
area. I swear to God, I'm going to go
cuz he's been [ __ ] emailing [ __ ]
um and that if he comes on it, I'm going
to his area, mate.
I think that Terry is that red
star. Personally, I think Terry, it was
good, man. It was good.
Um, yeah. I hate when people talk facts. Yeah.
Yeah. They just ban you after 3 days and
No, no one turned up to the barbecue.
The barbecue was nice. Yeah.
No. Yeah. You can't post something.
Yeah. So, you just have to message people.
Yeah. You just have to privately message
people cuz as soon as you post
something, they ban you. Yeah. Sorry, my bad. But um yeah. USA is
he do you remember the dreams
cactus? Do you remember when I used to have
nightmares? Those days were horrible,
bro. Do you remember? Remember when I
used to come and say I had
nightmares? Oh, [ __ ] hell.
Remind me of that Steven King it
clown. That was quite scary,
bro. That's actually scary, bro. Nah.
Nah, not I wasn't waking up at night,
but I was waking up in the morning. I
They were horrible,
bro. They were [ __ ] horrible,
mate. But they went away after a
while. See you in your dreams. Yeah.
They weren't wet dreams. They weren't
dreams. There's no way you're still messaging me.
There's no way you are still messaging me,
lad. I didn't fall in love with
her. I didn't fall in love with that [ __ ]
bro. And yeah, it was that [ __ ] She was horrible,
man. She's a nasty bastard. She's a
meanie. Um, did many turn up? up. No one turned
up except my little mates.
Yeah. Now for years. It's It only
happened two years ago.
Yeah. Yeah. I had friends.
Yeah. Had a load of old Bill,
lad. I had a load of old Bill for
supper. Yeah. Her her and her family are [ __ ] Cactus.
They're the They're the kind of people
that are just
lawyer. They're the kind of people that
are just [ __ ] lawyer,
mate. We're just [ __ ] lawyer. They're
just lawyer, bro. I'm going in um July.
And it's not the Phil It's not the Philippines. It's
Thailand. It was special then, but it's over
now. [ __ ] stinking [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. It's people's biggest mistake
meeting me. Is it
cactus? Ain't it? People's people meeting me, eh? Yeah.
Uh, imagine just going next week,
Cactus, and going on Scott Star, lad. Imagine. Imagine
Cactus just going on Scott Star. That'd
be good content, is it? Nah, it's not
good content, bro, cuz they'll [ __ ] lie.
Yeah. And she should [ __ ] regret meeting me, lad. You
know. Yeah. They should have regretted it, bro.
Cuz they're [ __ ] I told her about
herself in it, lad. So
So, I could say the same thing. Why did
she let me in? Why does she So, why does
she uh sorry, why did she
um lead me on? If I'm this, if I'm that,
if I'm this, if I'm that, I can say the
same thing. I just went along with what she was
saying. Do you remember cactus? They
were laughing at
us and then her ex tried getting [ __ ]
rude. I said, "Bro, you look like a fat
Homer Simpson. Shut your mouth, bro."
Yeah, you work in Urban
Outfitters. [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
pair of [ __ ] in a cactus. A pair of
[ __ ] [ __ ] mate. If you ask me. Yeah. Yeah,
man. It's so mad cuz like remember when
LT was messaging her trying to calm it
down and it's so weird Cactus how like
I'm the one that's behind it
all. You know when
people Yeah. He says, "Oh, you're
talking about how in it fam. In it,
fam." I was like, "Bro, when have I ever
said fam in my life?" Yeah, you talk
like this. Hey, Shiny, get in the shiny
fam. Like, bro, can anyone take you
serious with your whiny [ __ ] accent, you silly
[ __ ] Like, you stupid whiny little
[ __ ] cheeseburger eating
[ __ ] Can we Can Can we Can we
take that accent serious? Please stop it.
But if Morgan's taller than you, you're
not going to do nothing. Shut
up. [ __ ] fat Homer Simpson.
Yeah. Like it is like Cactus. Yeah. So
are you saying I'm the one that's behind it
or cuz you know when you get like you
know when there's like a gang of like a
conspiracy, right, that there's always
one that gets the longest sentence. All
the others are just like ones involved,
right? It then you got like the leader.
But then you've got like the leader. Yeah.
Yeah. Oh, it's funny.
But no, it's funny. It's not Yeah,
funny. Yeah, that's how he speak like, "Hey,
Shotty. Hey, Shy. Let me holler at you
real quick." [ __ ] idiot, man.
[ __ ] That's what I want to say. [ __ ] That's the be. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
But that USA is he deserved it, bro.
Like trying to get rude saying at the
who do you think you [ __ ] are,
bro? [ __ ] I don't understand if they're
[ __ ] half [ __ ]
decent. Oh, he grabbed me. Oh, he scared
me. Oh, that's funny, bro. That's funny.
I wish that was true,
mate. I wish that was
true. I was prepared to make the rumors true,
Cactus. You know, make the rumor is
true. Well, I wish that was [ __ ]
true, bro. I'm not even joking. I wish that was true.
Nah, I don't I emailed her like three
few months ago. Two three few months
I said all you could do is make your
little shitty little group chat, but you
know in in real life you and your folks
are about nothing and you know you'll
never be about nothing. That's all I had to say.
Yeah, I emailed a couple of
Yeah. Who's the real keyboard warrior?
Who's the one that's making [ __ ] chats? Yeah.
Yeah. All from a cold approach,
cactus. All from a [ __ ] cold
approach. What the
[ __ ] That's mad that, bro. [ __ ] hell. That is crazy. Oh yeah.
Remember, Cactus, I'm part of the family
now. Imagine you're part of the
family. Yeah, part of the family, mate. [ __ ]
hell. That's funny, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. They're sat at the dinner
table probably thinking, "Oh, did you
get a message from that guy from
England?" Yeah. Did Did you? Yeah. Yeah.
Obvious mate. You can just imagine.
Yeah. Thanksgiving. Yeah. They're sat on
a table talking about you.
Yeah. I used to message Scott when I was pissed up.
Yeah. Yeah. When I was pissed up. Yeah,
man. See, LT was just an innocent
party, you know. He was trying to he was
trying to warn her own it, you know. Yeah.
I'm funny in it,
Cactus. Oh, it's funny, eh?
Yeah. Oh, the good days, eh?
This woman's from South America, but she
disappeared. She [ __ ]
disappeared. Yeah, if that guy was in
that day, he would have got
killed. If he was in that day, he would
have got [ __ ] killed,
mate. It's not even funny, bro. He would
have actually got killed. Yeah.
all over the same website you can watch Scooby-Doo
on. Yeah, it would have been quite a fishious
attack. A fishes
attack. No, he would have died, bro. Serious. Yeah.
Some [ __ ] had that electric bike away as well.
Yeah. You know when I went on that um
Izzy's address that time, Cactus, I was
actually going to I was going to give a
good seeing to that day.
I was going to give a good scene
to I would have just said want to
play. But I I was [ __ ] in my head back
then, bro. You got understand. I was [ __ ]
up. I would have been like, "Want to
play?" Like I was I was actually just
going to go by like the window by the
accommodation and I was going to be
like, "Want to play?
I was [ __ ] by then, bro. I was [ __ ]
I done a lot of I've done a lot of
calming down since
then. Want to
play? Yeah. Comes a point where you have
to calm down, you know. Yeah, basically.
Yeah, you're sick and twisted, [ __ ]
Do you remember catches? You're sick and twisted,
[ __ ] Oh, another one that replies to negativity.
Ah, you didn't mind s being sat there [ __ ]
ignoring. I even said don't even think
about ignoring me, you little
[ __ ] That's why I said cactus like
proper like green [ __ ] mode. Yeah. I couldn't let I
lie cuz I knew I knew they were [ __ ]
changing their photo on Facebook and I
said all right can you just apologize
and that's it you know I couldn't
lie you know I had to message the family
yeah I messaged her mom, her dad, her
sisters, [ __ ] everything. I was
actually speaking to her sister at one
point, one of
them, and I showed her the like
approaching video in the restaurant
video. She says like, "I'm sick and
twisted." She's actually projecting.
She's the sick and twisted one. She's
the one that has to lead somebody on,
right? and then ghost them and then act
like she's the
victim when you just don't care what
you've just done. You're the one who's
sick and twisted. You are the sick and
twisted one. I done what I done out of
retaliation to you being a
[ __ ] Know what I
mean? Cuz I've met other [ __ ] but not like
that. Most of them were just like honest
even though they were just [ __ ] but just they
were honest kind of or there was no
context. You're projecting you're the
one who's sick in your
head or someone to be sick in their head. Yeah. Yeah,
basically Social Security payment. Eh, [ __ ]
hell. I think some of them messages was
that [ __ ] though. I do think some of them was
her. Some of them were. I
think I don't think I've ever come
across anyone more evil in my life to be fair. No.
I've met a lot of country
women. You remember Sig
Cactus? Good old
Sig. Yeah. All
[ __ ] All proper [ __ ] mate.
Yeah. Why me and Sig fell out is because
I was supposed to go to Nando with her
the next day, but I
never. I was going on about that
American with Sig.
Yeah, I remember going on about that American with
Sig. People must have thought I was
[ __ ] mad when they used to go out with
me cuz I used to go out drinking and
then I'd be in like my own head talking
about this [ __ ] They be like, "What are you talking
about?" They were like, "What are you talking about?" Saying, "Yep.
Yeah, Sig did.
Yeah, I remember I had a one night stand
a week after her as
well in the in the same
club. I had a couple of one
out. I know, mate. She's probably found
someone to be
fair. She said she was going to unblock
me in a week. It's been 2
months. So when you do come back, I won't be
here. Yeah. She used to come around and
that she used to come around and suck my dick and
then go and then come back, suck my dick, go
again. I didn't really like her. I
didn't like her.
She started coming across as [ __ ] like
they do here in the west. Like this
whole I could sense the
entitlement and I've stopped liking her cuz of
it. And she is nutty. Yeah, she is
crazy. But it's not that, it's the
entitlement. Um, and I didn't like it.
So, I don't really feel like I lost
anything. She will come back. She always comes back.
Well, when she comes back again, I won't be here.
So, she hates giving her
[ __ ] but she used to just do it. Yeah.
Who do you think was in the right,
Cactus? Me or USA? Izzy, I think I was
in the right.
Defero. I think I was definitely in the
right. I think they deserved everything
that they got, you know. Definely,
but I'm probably more to be fair. So, yeah. [ __ ]
mate and they're not caring after what
she done. And I sent like proper voice
notes and it's like what the [ __ ] So,
she wanted to play [ __ ] up evil games
and then when someone gave it back to
her, she didn't like
it cuz they don't know what them they're
getting themselves into. They see you as
a [ __ ] and a [ __ ] right? So they do
these nasty things and then when you
react back, right, they play victim
cuz it's the whole point of like
everyone meets their
match or they'll just meet people that
don't like retaliate to them or
whatever. You know what I'm
saying? Cuz you think me look wearing a
suit, I wouldn't have that sign in me
when I [ __ ] do, bro. like
just about going separate ways. [ __ ]
you, bro. About separate
ways. Oh, I'm
sorry. I'm saying like, no, no, no, no. [ __ ] that,
bro. It's the way they done it as well.
Even though we knew that nothing would
have happened and I don't care anyways,
it's the way she did it. Yeah.
Yeah. Teacher, don't come to [ __ ]
other countries and start [ __ ] with
people. You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
Yeah. I said, "What's all about? What's
all this about people grabbing you and
shit?" Cuz I've had my friends show me
screenshots where you're trying to say
people's grabbed you. What are you
talking about? Couldn't say nothing. Just, oh,
uh, yeah. Uh, I don't live in London. [ __ ] off.
Yeah, they're just [ __ ] here,
mate. Really are in
America. Poor guy she's with. Probably
getting cheated on,
eh? But he would probably stay with her
even still cuz he's probably a s just
like most guys are. ain't got a bad word
to say about
women. Not like that would make make
leave her, you know. That's
crazy. Do you think I could have been in
a relationship with Sig Cactus? Yeah, definitely. I think so.
Yeah, we was making out in the club.
Cactus. Me and Sig. We was making out in the
club. She even bought me some chicken.
Yeah, she bought me some
chicken. Good old s.
Yeah, I really did [ __ ] up some things, but don't
I? I really did [ __ ] up some things,
bro. Yeah, she bought me chicken from
the chicken shop on the way
back. Yeah, we had some chicken together.
Yeah. Yeah. She had some big tits. She did. I
remember using them all night.
Cactus and other things. Yeah. Yeah.
Bro, you remember Sig was never your
mommy. I think that's you that said that
in it, Cactus. Sig was never your
mommy. Sig was never your
mommy. Do you remember
that? I think it was you that said that in it. [Music]
Hey, I think you're actually mocking me, bro.
Yeah, baby Peter from Remember I was
talking about babies with
her. Do you remember I was talking about
having babies with her? Do you remember
the video I recorded? It would be baby
Peter from New Zealand. Do you remember
cactus? You remember it? But I recorded
it. Put it up.
Oh yeah, she could have cooked me a load
of old bill in the mornings. Oh, nothing
beats that load of old
bill. Big bit of old bill.
Eh, so who is my mama
then? Who is my mama? Huh?
No, I think she is my mama.
Do you remember going to the fields to
um play the voice
notes? Yeah. Sig is my mama. [Music]
Yeah, good old sig.
E. Oh, good old sig.
We'll see a foreigner cactus for
Yeah, but she's still technically a
foreigner cuz she's from New Zealand, so
she is basically a foreigner, in
it. She's had to go through a lot of
stalking that Morgan, isn't it? Cuz of me, eh? Yeah.
Who? Who? M. She changed her
number. If you're talking about Sig, I
don't have her number anymore. And if
you're talking about USA, she changed her
number. I don't have Sig's
number. She has mine.
Yeah, I don't know her number,
bro. LT does, but I don't
Yeah, I don't have a number
anymore. There was this one before in
the club. Yeah. She said, "What do you
prefer, ass or boobs?" I said, "I prefer
boobs." And we was just kissing and I
was just squeezing her boobs. And she
was touching my dick.
Yeah. No, bro. I've not been to that
club in ages. No, no, no,
bro. What if she still goes to this one? Yeah.
Hey, they won't
get. Was you actually joking, Cactus,
when you said Ant-Man was right when he
said that they're not interested in this country?
No, obviously he's right in it cuz then
it wouldn't be so
hard. Yeah, obviously he's right.
Duh. But it's hard to believe since
like, you know, you can be decent
looking, smell good, have money, and still
struggle. It just doesn't really make any sense.
That's the bit that don't make
sense. Like you can look good, smell
good, have money, and you're still going
to get I've got a
boyfriend. Well, 90% of people, 85, 90%
people. 15% of people. See, I understand
what that man's saying. He says some
people can do it, like 18%.
But it's hard to believe if I can't do
it that many others can in this day and
age. I mean starting from now cuz you
know you got designer clothes, you smell
good, you got money, you're confident.
If you can't do it, it seems very hard to believe
that many other people
can, you know. So obviously mo and and
and how you know it's them because most
men struggle. If it wasn't them, most
men wouldn't struggle.
But most men
struggle or they have to do madnesses to
even find someone. So that's how you
know it obviously is
them cuz of like how many people
struggle with it. So it wouldn't happen
if it was you.
But strange though. It's strange as
hell, you know. Remember I used to say
Cactus, I might as well look like Timmy
Eldridge. I might as well look like [ __ ] Timmy
Eldridge. It's all to do with luck. You
need to get extremely extremely
lucky. And it's [ __ ] rare. Key.
Yeah, it's just it's just highly unlikely,
bro, in this country. But I might as
well look like Timmy
Aldridge. What makes you say that
they're not interested in this country,
Cactus? Is it stuff you've heard or
stuff you've seen or
Is it what you've heard or what?
Yeah, there you
go. You need to be a [ __ ] You need
to be like a [ __ ] or a drug
dealer. Cuz if you notice that criminals always have
girlfriends. Like have you ever watched
20,000 police custody and you know oh
they've got lucky and met someone you
know a few years ago but
yeah and it's always meant they have to lower their
standards. I can't believe that USA Izzy
was such a [ __ ] Like she is [ __ ] stinking,
bro. I stayed with her, bro, cuz I
didn't have anything else. What else did
you want me to do, bro? I went along
with everything she
said. And you got people like that
thinking they're better than you. You
got people like her thinking she's
better than you, bro. And that 32y
old. You have these women that think
they're better than you. So,
like all that does is make you lose hope even
more. It's like what I was saying to
these two black lads the time I went on
the date last month. She's like, "Oh,
she's a four out of 10. Like, you
shouldn't care. You just went on a date
with her just now. It was the date I
went on last month." I said, "Yeah, but
that makes it even worse." Cuz if you
have people like that thinking they're better than
you and them kind of people being that
hard to get, then what does that leave you
with? Do you understand?
So, and it wasn't I like that person
last month. It was the fact that they
just wasted my
time. It doesn't matter what they look
like. They could be a [ __ ] two out of
10. It would have still pissed me off
cuz they're wasting my time.
So, which delayed my [ __ ] foot
recovery. So, my foot injury recovery.
So, that sucked. That injury, bro. [ __ ]
hell. That injury sucked badly, bro. Oh
my god. Imagine that. Waking up 4 in the
morning and your foot is pounding, bro.
Oh my god. Eneo
tentonitis. How the [ __ ] you pronounce
it? [ __ ] shocking injury, bro. Pounding,
bro. In the morning, your [ __ ] foot
is pounding, waking you up. That's some madness, bro. Nasty injury,
bro. And it feels like it's never going
to go, but it does. It just takes a really long
time. Takes a long time to heal that, brother.
I don't know if I hit it or I got it
from running. I might hit it in my sleep
or maybe when I ran back from the pool
or something, but maybe I hit it. I
don't know. But [ __ ] knows,
mate. It's only just got better after
like 5 weeks. But they say it can take 6
to 12 weeks, mate. It's not a joke. It
doesn't just heal like that cuz it's
your foot in it. So there's less blood
supply on your feet. So it takes longer
to heal than the rest of your
body and then you'd walk on it and then
it would it' get you at the night. It'd
get you at night. Yeah. Just before
you're sleeping. It would just start
pounding and then you'd [ __ ] go to sleep.
Um, and then you'd wake up 4:00 in the morning, it
pounding, and then you you literally
can't even move. You couldn't even move
your foot. It was like [ __ ]
swollen. So, yeah, lucky it's not like that
anymore. Yeah, it was stinking, bro. It
was [ __ ] stinking.
So, I might hit it in my sleep or something.
But yeah, anyways, at least it's better
now. [ __ ] painful. It was
Yeah. Yeah. I was limping. Yeah. Not
anymore, but I was
then I was [ __ ] limping.
like a spacker, mate. Yeah, not
anymore. But yeah, it's a long recovery
to get 100%. It's not a week, two weeks. It's very slow. Yeah.
madness. And I went on a date with a
woman who was just wasting my time. Imagine that. [ __ ]
hell. Imagine that.
I'll be blocking you again and I'll keep
[ __ ] doing it. Do you remember that
cactus? And I'll keep [ __ ] doing
it. I'll be blocking you again and I'll
keep [ __ ] doing
it. I love it,
bro. You love it, Cactus. I love it,
man. And I'll keep [ __ ] doing
it. And I'll keep [ __ ] doing it. That
bit sounded funny, is
it? Oh, all right. All right. You know
what I'm saying? Yeah.
Yeah. I know this is you, Cactus. I know
this is you.
I know this is
you. Good times, brother. It was good times, man. [ __ ] hell. Nah,
bro. I did um when the the the foot was
hurting. Yeah, but not
now. I had to, mate. It was [ __ ]
killing me, bro.
I should have to take it easy now for a
bit. Why did you call me a sick and twisted
[ __ ] I didn't even do anything.
Tactus, what did I do that was sick and
twisted? What? Defend myself?
Huh? What? Defend
myself from a bully? You
know, you're sick and twisted,
[ __ ] But how am I sick and twisted? Huh?
She was getting scared, you know, like
she was messaging LT. Not scared, but
she was worried in it. You know, the
first time I said, "I'm [ __ ] coming
in it." Yeah. She got a bit
wary. Bit wary in
it. [ __ ] hell,
bro. That is a madness, eh?
Yeah. Then I gave up for dating properly
for like a year and a half even though I
was still going out. And now when I when
I fought to try to get back into dating [Music]
um you know all women are the same so I
can't win. So when I wanted to give
dating a try again all women are the same. I'm sick. Yeah.
Yeah. And LT was like, "Oh, yeah. You
got your friend to message her. Why did
I get my friend to message her?" Cuz she
had blocked me. So, it all stems from
her. If you think about it, it actually
all stems from her. You
know, you could have easily said you
didn't want to take it further and not
block or just say it and then block, but
you didn't. So, like at the end of the
day, it is you. As much as we want to
joke around about
it. So, the whole point of my friend
messaging you in which you block me. So,
it is you end of that's it.
So yeah, she's evil,
bro. If I ever saw her again, I would
literally not be able to h hold myself
in, bro. You know, like I'm not See,
with the neighbor, my mom's neighbor,
there was not really any beef there. So
whenever I'm there, it's just nothing
cuz we don't really know each other. So
it's not like But if I ever ever ever
come across her, bro, in any country,
she's getting it, bro. I'm not even
joking. I don't care how many years it's
been. Cuz they say time is a healer,
bro. But it [ __ ] will never hit, bro.
If I found out that she moved in next to
me, I would have thought Christmas had
come [ __ ] early, bro. I'm not even
joking. Yeah. After Charles. Yeah. Uh [ __ ] madness,
it wonder how they met dating app.
Baby, I wish I never had anything to do with women,
bro. Biggest regret in my life, getting
introduced to gambling and speaking to
women. Who knows where I'd be now, mate,
if I didn't do any of them two
things. This community's been negative.
Caused me a lot of problems. Gambling's
caused me a lot of
problems. Women have caused me a load of
problems. I could turn back time, bro.
Yeah. Oh, it was one meal. Do I owe him my whole
life? Like, bro, you mad? What the [ __ ]
Who even says
that? Why did you even bring up money either?
could never speak to me oneonone though,
could you? Cuz you know I'd [ __ ]
destroy you, mate, with my
words. See, my friend, he's not really
into arguing, you know what I mean,
Cactus? He's not as [Music]
um he's not as intelligent as me.
So, you know, he can
get people can sort
of see more kind of like vulnerable. You
know what I
mean? Try and argue with me,
mate. You won't win. That's
me. Cuz she's just a big bastard, isn't
it? You need to think goodbye. Big
bastard. What do you tell? Yeah.
Where did I even
find? Where do I ever find these people for, bro?
Let's go over there, buddy.
Go sleep soon.
I'm out of time to go to sleep. Peace.