Yeah. Yeah. That's funny. Super.
What's popping, bro? Nothing. I just
stayed in today. Just been uh chilling,
bro. I didn't go out. I thought, "Fuck
it. I don't want to go out, man. I just
want to chill. Done in this country. Go
in Thailand in six weeks." So, yeah. I
don't really care, bro. I didn't go out
yesterday. I didn't go out today.
Oh, so yeah. Oh, I sent a USA
message yesterday. Um, early hours of
this morning, Steven
Howard 3:00 in the morning, but I sent a
long ass paragraph,
bro. Yeah, I sent her a long ass paragraph on
Facebook. Yeah, it was funny, bro.
at 3 [ __ ] a.m. brother.
Yeah. [ __ ] hell, it's funny. Yeah.
Yeah, this [ __ ] uh [ __ ] Steven
Howard didn't bother going out today,
bro. Drinking. [ __ ] that.
Yeah. Yeah, bro. I don't care. I don't
like the [ __ ] but I just told her about
herself. I said, "Listen, mate. Just
give me a day next week. Give me a day
next week and I'm
there." Yeah. I'll tell you about
yourself in front of your boyfriend and your [ __ ] dad.
Yeah. Crazy [ __ ]
It crazy. I am Steven. Okay. Love.
Yeah. Yeah. It's funny, bro. It is funny.
I think it was a good thing me giving up
in this country though. It's definitely a good
thing. Who's this me? Who's this
anime? Who the [ __ ] is
that? Someone off YouTube. [ __ ] is where [ __ ] [Music]
Yeah, I don't care if she did or she
didn't, bro. I don't give a [ __ ] mate.
I don't like
her. I just [ __ ] told her about
herself again yesterday before I went to
sleep. Oh, yeah,
bro. I said I'll come there next week,
mate. No back and forth
[ __ ] Ah, [ __ ] me.
Yeah, to be honest with you, I would
probably just rent an
apartment. Just go there [ __ ] rent an
apartment to be fair.
Yeah, she's actually I think she's
actually [ __ ] in her head, bro. I'm
not even joking. Like, how somebody can
just turn like that? It's got to be
mental health in it.
It's got to be mental health for
somebody to switch like that cuz I've
seen how they were replying to other
comments and it's like how do how does
someone just switch like
that? I don't know,
bro. It's strange. Is it strange?
Was I the one who was behind it all? Steven
Howard. Was I the one behind it
all? Yeah. You got to be nuts to be
[ __ ] making up [ __ ] stories like that,
bro. Screw this. Definitely got a screw list.
Yeah, I'm the one that find it all.
Yeah, I just said give me a day next
week and I'll be there. Simple. Cuz
obviously I've saved some money up from
not um going out drinking. So I could
easily go there next week, bro. It's not
a problem. I got the Wa Steven got the [ __ ] WA
lad. It's not a problem, you know.
Yeah. The [ __ ] didn't want it with me, bro.
bro. Yeah. I don't have any tattoos,
matey. Not me, matey.
I don't have any toys.
Do you remember her dad, Steven
Howard? Oh, that's funny, man. That was
funny. That was funny, bro. Wasn't it? Yeah. [Laughter]
But who's the one that got family
involved? Steven Howard, it wasn't me,
it? And you had London Taylor messaging
her, trying to warn her. Like, how did
all of that come about?
Like who was the one that was behind it
all? Cuz I wasn't I wasn't even
involved. You know what I mean? [ __ ]
Yep. Yeah. How How did I was behind all
that? How do you know that?
It's funny about it.
So, what happened then? If you saw it
all play out, what
happened? I'm the one behind it
all. Do you want me to read what I wrote
to her last
night? Well, early hours in the morning,
Stephen Hour. Do you want me to uh read what I wrote? All
right. One sec. What's
that? The one behind it
all. One second. Where the [ __ ] is that,
bro? Hold on. Uh, one
second. One second. Where is it? One second, bro. What's
here? Yeah, I said, "Uh, why you stupid
coward little [ __ ] I I've noticed you
still haven't replied to my email. Laugh
my ass off. You're such a lame keyboard
worrying [ __ ] like Daddy Joe. But all
you can do is make group chats about
people. makeup stories then block it
must run in the family. Funny how you
was begging a black man on Instagram to
do your dirty work because I spoke about
his kids quids his kids in quotation
mark in an argument that had [ __ ] all to
do with you. Listen up, [ __ ] I've
violated you. I've made you change your
number and your family countless times.
And you and no one you know has done a
thing about it, but keep blocking every
time I've tried to meet you. He's
already heard this. You even told your
father to tell me he was in California
when I said I was there last time.
Pathetic. Also, has your new boyfriend
found out how much of a hoe you are yet?
And that's why no man says just like how
Charles left you. It's so sad. It's so
bad. I wouldn't even need to lie about
anything I say about you. All I need to
say is your body count and you told me
you had an STD. Does he know you can't
afford your own food for food and weed?
Listen, I'll show you and your pig dad
how much of a keyboard warrior I am. I'm
prepared to come next Thursday or
Friday, which day works for you, and bring your
uh and bring your stupid dad and your
Mexican looking boyfriend and see if any
man stops me putting you in your place
and teaching you some madness. I tell
your short ass ex Damian to come as well
since the fact he tried to get him brave
with his stupid whiny accent. and let's
see what you or anyone you know will do
before preaching to others about what
they should be doing to me. You're just
a broke ass worthless skank. I'm not
scared of you or anyone you know and
I'll make sure by the time I come back
to the UK everybody in America knows
what you're about. Anyway, pick a day
next week. Still have a game of the day
next week and I'll be there. This time
though, pretend you're in California
again. For [ __ ] sake. Let's show your
father who the real keyboard warrior.
Who is the real keyboard warrior and
what you or
anyone will actually do when I'm in your
country instead of begging a black man
in England. You [ __ ]
Anyways, play next week. Chop chop chop.
Don't be keyboard warrior like your father
says. No response. Ah, bro. They're
[ __ ] Absolute [ __ ]
Phil. No, I wasn't I wasn't being
racist. I said her Mexican looking
boyfriend. I wasn't being racist.
Yeah, that's what I said. No reply cuz
she knows, bro. I will actually go there
like next week. It's not It's not a
joke, bro. That's one of the reasons I
put that out
there. [ __ ] me. I'm not even joking, bro.
Yeah. She not about that life, bro. No
one she she knows is about that life. So
yeah, that's it.
But didn't even need to be abusive.
Really didn't make up stuff. Wasn't abusive.
So she she probably got me down to be fair.
No, she hasn't blocked
me. Let's get a reply. You won't get a reply, bro. M
He ain't about that life
ba. I'm a good text. I Steven Howard
What do you
think? I think it was pretty good.
Yeah. Thursday or Friday. I can go there
Thursday or Friday. Good day, though.
Yeah. Will cost me an arm and a leg,
mate. But I can do it.
Remember Steven Howard, if you don't
find share contract, you're gay. All
right, that's just
copying. That's just trying to fit in.
is YouTube is all you have. Stop talking about
yourself. You're on YouTube right now.
Stop talking about yourself. You're
alone on YouTube right now. yourself
projector. Um, yeah. If you don't find
chevel co attractive, you're gay. No, that's
copying. That's literally
copying. That's what people say to fit
in. Insecure people. Yeah, that's just copying. That
is Yeah, that was a trend that went on for ages,
mate. Copying. Literally
copying. I don't even find that funny,
mate. That's just being a copycat.
Copycat. Literally a
copycat. Yeah. YouTube is all I have.
You're talking about yourself,
mate. I can go out and do what I want.
I'm going Thailand in six weeks, so [ __ ] Yeah. Yeah.
She was begging a black man. By that I
meant she was like saying to London
Taylor, "Oh, why don't you do this? Why
don't you do that?" Like anyone she
knows would ever do anything to me, even
if I was there. Do you know what I'm saying? So
like that's what I meant by she's
begging a black
man. You should whoop his ass. Oh, you
when you no one you ever know would ever
do anything to me. That's why I was
willing to prove it. You know what I'm
saying? [ __ ] idiot, man.
I know why USA
PJ and I started getting some tattoos. Stephen
Howard, it would never happen. I'm never getting a tattoo.
Never. No. Never, bro.
Never. I wonder if she's still deceiving
people with [ __ ]
filters. I think so, bro. [ __ ]
filters. See the people
I love these videos. Me [Music]
scary. No, no, no. Hold on. Somebody
said your voice
Somebody looks like me.
E looks like me.
Mate, it's quite weird, isn't it,
mate? Yeah, it's weird, eh? It
feel really think that guy looks like
me? I've got no tattoos,
bro. I've got no [ __ ] tattoos,
though, bro. So, yeah.
What makes you say that he looks like me? [Laughter] [ __ ] you. That
money. Yeah, but I've got more money. Steven
Howard, I got more money. Yeah, I [Music]
clear lower deck. Yeah. [Laughter]
Yeah, [ __ ] probably saw that comment
and thought, "Oh, here we go again. Two
two years later, mate." Yeah. [Laughter] He's USA.
Yeah, it's my [Laughter] bro. Yeah.
Oh, I'm so dead. But one sec.
Yeah, she's going to she's going to end
up having a uh she's going to end up
um a um baby soon, I reckon. Me? What do
you think, Steven Howard? Yeah, I can
sense these things, bro.
And people have had a few
partners, you know.
Yeah. I think so.
Me? I think
so. Got a feeling.
Yeah. I wonder what happened with
Charles. Wonder what happened Steve with
Charles. Yeah, man. Yeah. [Laughter]
Ah, not me, mate. No, not
me. Nah, not like that. Oh, no. No.
Women are evil. Um, Steven
Howard, they're [ __ ] evil. Women
are. I don't have anything to do with them anymore. Yeah. [Laughter] Oh,
[ __ ] I never forget that.
Ah, I'll never forget that, bro. I woke
up, bro. There was like someone
downstairs talking and it was all night
long. It's not even an hour. It was all
night long. It was It was like somebody
was was in in my [ __ ] room, bro. I
swear down. It was like coming from
downstairs. I woke up at 5 in the
morning. It woke me up at 5 in the
Ah, mate. Why would the [ __ ] Yeah.
Oh, it's funny, bro.
Yeah. Hello, bro.
I'll never forget that, mate. I'll never
forget it. It was all night
long, Steven. It was all night long,
mate. All night [ __ ]
long. Do you know what that means? All night long. Yeah.
Yeah, no one want to [ __ ]
sleep. It was all night long, mate. 5:00
in the morning, woke me up. I said to my
friend, "Can you hear that?" He He was
already awake. He already woke him up.
He was already awake. I was like, "Bro,
what the [ __ ] is that?" No, it's coming from
downstairs. Yeah. It was like it was in
my [ __ ] room. I swear down. [Laughter] Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] hell. Maybe maybe
bro could do but is there any point?
I don't think
so. It's a waste of like £300,
bro. It's a waste like three400 pound
though, isn't it?
So, what's the what's the [ __ ]
point? What is the actual point,
man? No, bro. Um, I had macaroni
cheese. No, macaroni cheese I
had. Yeah, I was just telling um Steven
Howard how [ __ ] that guy woke me up
at 5 in the morning. Remember
A couple of months ago, Griezy was all
night long. I went to wake my friend up
to tell him, but he was already awake.
Griezy 5 in the [ __ ] morning, mate.
[ __ ] hell. Just talking.
Yeah. No, it was all night long.
Absolutely all night long, mate. Greasy's
Daniel. Do you remember when I was
waking up at 4 in the morning with my foot throbbing,
Greavvesy? When I had that foot injury,
[ __ ] me. 4 in the morning. Frobbing. Absolutely
throbbing. That was quite a vicious
injury, wasn't it, Grezy? Quite a vicious
one. Do you know what? Me, Grezy, and
King should go for McDonald's. Me, Grezy, and
King. Oh, what a lovely site. Me, Greasy, and
King having McDonald's.
Oh, yeah. So, that' be so cute. Me,
Grezy, King, and Baby Peter from Somalia.
Ah, what a lovely site, Grezy. What a lovely site.
E, you love McDonald's, Greezy. I don't
really care for
McDonald's. I need to really fancy it
and I order it when I want it. But I
don't You're mad for KFC. You are. McDonald's. You
are. I don't really care for it, man.
had it yesterday. I had it um the other
day before the barbecue cuz I was
hungry. Um and I don't really have
McDonald's that much. I had KFC today. KFC fillet burger. Yeah. Yeah.
Yep. Greavvesy wants to go to
America. Greavvesy wants to go to
America. Boozy told me he wants to go.
Remember Grey women was put on this
earth to satisfy Peter Belly's
needs. To satisfy Peter Belly's
needs. That is [ __ ] funny, bro. [Laughter] Bless
you. Bless you. Greasy.
Yeah. Imagine Greavvesy in
America. Are you scared of flying,
Greavvesy? Be honest. grieves you. Are
you scared of going on a
plane? Bless you. [Laughter]
Yeah, but you don't want to do it though, do [Laughter]
you? You wouldn't want to do that, would Bless you,
Grezy. Bless you in
life. It's a very terrifying experience
at Greavvesy. One that I never wished to
repeat. How cute is that?
Yeah, I've been on a plane and it's and
it's an experience I wish to never
repeat. It was a dreadful experience,
one that I wish to never go for ever
again. Oh, how cute is that,
Grezy? I think you like the Amsterdam
videos, didn't you, Grezy? They were quite entertaining.
Ben and Jerry's cookie dough. Um, today
as well, Greasy. Have you ever had Ben
and Jerry's cookie dough? Oh, I love it,
bro. You need to have that after a good
McDonald's. Ben and Jerry's cookie
dough. I paid £550, but they're on sale
when weight rose £3.75. So, I'll
probably get two tomorrow. You can't
beat them that Ben Jerries,
bro. I've been I've been having that since I was
17, you know. So, I prefer the chocolate
one, but I just I just love I just love
it. But I haven't
really been having it since I left my
since I've left my mom's. I've been
having it more and
more, you know.
Yeah, but I went off it for a while. Not
that I just not that I didn't like it. I
just didn't bother buying it. But I do
like it, bro. I do like it. It is nice.
I had probably about three this week to be
fair. It is nice
that I want to go cinema soon, bro. But
there's still no horrors on. Go
cinema. Have some popcorn, some coke, pick a
mix. The going to the cinema always used
to remind me of USA. Is he doesn't
anymore? But it used to for quite a [Music]
while. It was strange.
It was a strange
thing. Oh yeah, Greavesy. I get what you
mean. If I I turn into I turn into a um
I turn into silly mode when I play the
Simpsons. I always say, "Bart Simpson,
leave your mother alone. It's not your
mama that's done anything to you. It's
It's Homin Simpson. I used to watch
Homin Simpson strangle you. Even when I
was a child, he used to strangle you
till your little tongue come out. I used
to sit there and watch it. Hamilton
Simpson, leave him
alone. You know, it's not your mama, you
know. And if you if you if you if you
keep picking on your mama, Bart Simpson,
I'm going to come to Springfield and
kick your ass. I'm not playing anymore.
You know, I used to watch Tom Hamilton
Simpson and he used to strangle you.
Strangle you till your little eyeballs
popped out. You know, [ __ ]
hell. I might do that, you know, just do
a series of Simpsons hit and run Mr.
Magcoo mode, like a walk through Mr.
Magcoo version. I think that's something
Grezy would like. Leave her alone, B.
She's done nothing but look out for you. You
know, I think you would love that in it,
bro. I get nails on you. Yeah, they're
lovely little characters,
mate. Leave them alone. Leave them alone, Hamilton.
Yeah, I can't believe Greasy. That game
is 22 years old.
22 [ __ ] years
old. What? It doesn't even look more
than 6, seven years old, mate. And it's 22 years old.
[ __ ] That is
uh It's very old.
Greasy. Grand Theft Auto San Andreas was
made in 2004. I'm
sure is very old,
bro. Greavvesy hates women as well. Don't you,
Grezy? I'm sure it was 2004. Yeah, it
2004. 24th of October 2004. I knew it
was 21 years old. [ __ ] me.
[ __ ] They're nasty pieces of
work. You don't want to speak to women,
mate. They're a devil.
Mama alone, Bart, she's done nothing but
looked out for
you. You know, it's Hamilton Simpson
that used to abuse
you. Oh, that's cute, is it?
Grezy. Nah, they're not friendly, mate. They're evil.
Nah, they're evil women are Simpson. Uh
yeah, Mr. M. No, they're not friendly
women, Greasy. They're just nasty pieces of
work. I'll never be friendly with any of
them here. I just see them as Satan, the devil.
Well, I'm basically asexual like you and El Greasy.
Anyways, who needs [ __ ] women when
you can play the Simpsons Hit and
Run? You know, all the little characters
are on there. You got Stitch, you know. Yeah.
Yeah. Do you know what the Simpsons is? Steven Howard.
Simpsons. Simpson did it. Simpsons did
it. Simpsons did it.
We Simpsons did it. Simpsons did it. Remember that.
Yeah. Family Guy was always trying to
beat Simpsons. Do you remember that,
Grezy? But they could never do it.
They always for years the creator of
Family Guy always wanted
to make it beat the Simpsons or even
make two to try and overtake the
Simpsons but never happened. It will
happen. Family Guy was a good
try but they will never beat the
Simpsons like in terms of like cartoons.
You know what I'm saying?
Do you agree with me? Uh, Grezy
You didn't answer me, Steven Hour. Do
you know what The Simpsons
is? Oh, I asked my um niece, "Do you
know what The Simpsons is?" Greasy. Do
you know what she said? She says, "Yeah,
it's the yellow
people." Oh, that's cute, isn't it? The yellow people. I'm
dead. Bro, I remember when she said
that. It was so funny.
Was what meat 100%
beef? Yeah, the meat. All the meat I
have is 100%
beef. So greasy, I think Simpsons is
more popular than Family Guy and South
Park because kids can watch it as well.
See, with Family Guy and South Park,
obviously kids can't watch it, but
adults and kids can watch
Simpsons. You understand? So that's
why with Simpsons you sort of like grow
up with it. You know what I'm saying?
And that's why I think they can they'll
never be able to beat it for that
reason. Does that make sense? I'm
guessing I think I'm right in it.
Grezy, what do you
think? Cuz you can be an adult and watch
Simpsons and you can be a kid that
watches the Simpsons, but you can't be a
kid that watches Family Guy and you
can't be a kid that watch South Park.
Even though I watched it when I was a
kid, but you get what I mean. So that's
why I used to love South Park. I used to
love South Park, bro. I don't know if
you was ever into that, but I used to be
really into South
Park more than Family Guy. Defa.
Yeah. Yeah. Good times, bro. Fun
fact, South Park is two year is two
months older than
me. Ah, what a lovely
site. Yeah, I'm going to do Mr. Mcoo
Simpsons. Oh, did you like it when I was
doing that voice?
Grizzly about Bart Simpson. Bart
Simpson, leave your mother alone. It was
Hamilton that used to strangle
you. I used to watch it when I was a
when I was a child. He used to abuse you.
Hamilton Simpson is your father.
Yeah. Bless you, Greasy. You're so
mature, aren't you?
Leave him alone before I come to
Springfield and kick your
butt. Yep. I'm looking at flights right
now. I do that with my when I'm speaking
to my mom. I say that. She says, "You're
so silly." I said, "No, I'm playing Simpsons." You
know, uh, when it was I remember playing
that game when I was [ __ ] 9 years
old, grievy without a care in the world,
without a worry in the world. Before I
knew all women was evil. Yeah. Yeah. Ah,
Crusty. What do you want me to complete
it or? I can complete it, but it'll take
me about 6
hours. I'll have to do that voice for 6
Greasy. [ __ ] hell. Be a challenge
doing that for 6
hours. Leave your mother alone, Bart
Simpson. She's been She's been there from day
one when she gave birth to
you. Yep. I don't think that voice will ever go
away. No one can do it as good as me, Grezy. No. Yeah,
funny. I like we we just miss being a
kid again, don't we, Grezy? I think you
know, me and you. Yep.
Yeah, there's a Springfield in
Massachusetts, but I'm not sure what
state Simpsons originates
from. Maybe Oregon. I don't know. It's
[ __ ] up though,
bro. It's [ __ ]
up. Wish I could make a cartoon.
Greasy. It [ __ ] take years. It would take [ __ ]
years. It would take years, mate. [Music]
I'm going to sleep in a minute,
bro. I don't even drink anymore. Greasy.
What? The Simpsons has 600 episodes. [ __ ] me. 600 episodes. What?
Oh, rain sounds to help you
sleep. Nice. 600
episodes and each episode is half an
hour long, which means it's so that
would take you 300
hours. So that would take that would
take you literally
months and months and months to watch
all of them. Right,
Grimsy? Curry off some new content. What
content would you like to Well, I'm
doing the Simpsons hit and
run Mr. Mcoo
version cuz Greasy wants to see it.
So, 600 episodes. That would take you a very long
time, Greasy, to
uh to [ __ ] watch them, wouldn't it, Grezy?
Yeah. No, it take months, man. What the [ __ ]
What do you
think? Yeah, that's a long time. It
So you have to be sat there like a
crackhead literally watching
them do Simpsons and run Mr. Mcoo version for
Grezy. That made you laugh, didn't it,
Grezy? Oh, I like making you laugh,
Grezy. Leave your mother alone, Bart
Simpson. It was daddy. It was your daddy
who used to strangle the [ __ ] out of you until you cried.
Yep. O Nelson, leave Bart Simpson alone,
you big Billy, before I come there take
over the school.
Oh, that's so
cute. Anyway, I'm going to sleep. See you.