[Music]
Yo, still haven't closed my account, you
know. That's [ __ ] disgusting, bro.
Say somebody was actually addicted. They
haven't even [ __ ] closed my account.
I've asked for it to be closed, bro.
I was watching Hyperlinks last night.
Shouldn't be watching that. I need to
put not interested in them channels again. Madness.
probably they still ain't closed my
account now. I asked it to be closed
yesterday when I lost that
150. It's mad to think £150 can't even
buy you a pair of trainers
nowadays. That's actually a [ __ ]
madness. Can't even buy you a pair of trainers.
What's about this guys? Why close my [ __ ]
account? [ __ ] hell. It's under
review. All I want is my [ __ ] account closed. Jesus
Christ. So he was actually [ __ ] addicted. [Music]
That's got to be against the gambling
commission and you can't even close your
account when you want
to. 150 can't even buy you a pair of
trainers nowadays. How mad is
that? Even have LJ blocked. Why doesn't
LJ come on my channel anymore?
Yeah, I woke up thinking about 150.
That's a prime example of you can't
gamble responsibly even if you're not
addicted. That's a prime
example. But it's still a step in the
right direction. You lost 150 not 300
going out on the bank holiday. So
probably would have gave you know what I
mean. So we had to give.
So I can stop down for a month. Easy. 6
months. I could stop.
But sometimes you think [ __ ] it in
it. I don't know, man. I ain't drunk for
a month either.
So doubt I'll be trying in this country
ever again. To be honest. I keep saying
I'm going to, but I don't know. I don't
think I'll ever try women in this country
again or any westernized country for
that matter. I think that's me, man.
I've signed my
notice, signed it, dated it, left it. Simple. Yeah.
[ __ ] I'm good, mate.
Mind you of the bad times, you
know. Reminds you of the bad times.
Still ain't close that account up there.
Rob says that you can
gamble. There's such thing as gambling [Music]
responsibly. I'm not sure about
that. You know, even if you had even if
you had five even if you had 600 pound
Yeah. and you gambled 150 with
everything paid, that's still gambling responsibly.
Well, it's still gambling in your
limits. There's no such thing as gambling responsibly.
[ __ ] It's like hyperlinks. I don't
even think he uses real money cuz I bet
like that big on roulette and it's
always next door when I used to do it
back in the day. [ __ ]
man. It is absolute [ __ ]
say that he uses real money. Who knows
really? Who knows really? Yeah,
man. I'm up early. What the [ __ ] you on
about? I'm always up early, you
[ __ ] I'm always up at 8:00,
8:30. You mean I'm not normally on
YouTube this early? Yeah, cuz it's
called having a life. Unlike what these
people have got, they ain't got a life.
They're self projecting. I'm not up
early. I'm not my normal time. This is
the time I wake up. 8:00.
Yeah, they still haven't banned my
account after losing 150 yesterday. I've
been trying to get this account banned,
but still a closed it down. Yeah.
Secular slots is a mug. As long as you
got your bills paid, as long as you got
food, I had lots of food yesterday, then
it's all okay to lose
money. Sounds like something somebody
that uses fake money would
say. Yeah, sounds like somebody that
uses fake money would say, eh,
defo [ __ ] idiot that he is.
He's a [ __ ] Scottish idiot. That's
what he is.
Yeah, that's what he is, mate. So, yeah, [ __ ]
today. Yeah, I don't think I'll be going
out this week either. [Music] Desmond
des any women. Uh I literally told you
I've given up in this country. It seems
that you people really don't listen to
anything I say. I've literally told you
I've given up. Well, I given up for a
minimum of 6 weeks. And then you ask me
if there's any women knowing down that I
despise them and I don't want anything
to do with them.
So, I guess you really don't listen to
anything I say. I've literally told you
how I feel about them and I've given up
on them. Like, I'm not even going to go
out this week. This is a perfect
opportunity to go out this week. I don't
care about them anymore in this country.
I can't just give up. I can just give
up. Watch me. I can't just give up.
Watch me. I'm almost 4 weeks in. So,
trust me, I can give up. When somebody
like me that's gone all over the country
that have dealt with these women and
know exactly how every single one of
them's like, trust me, I can give up
quite easily. I can and I will. And I
have, you know, it's deadly serious.
Deadly [ __ ] serious. I'm not even
going out this week
either. I said this week maybe, but nah,
there's no point. There's literally no
[ __ ] point. That's why I wasn't even
I Oh yeah, you might have lost £150
gambling, but you would have lost £350
going out on the bank holiday drinking,
haircut, drinking two days.
So 150 isn't really that bad really if
you see it that
way. It's a one step in the right
direction. Sounds bad though cuz you
gambled. But still, no one's perfect,
eh? I had to go that whole bank holiday
not going out. So which was the Friday,
Saturday, Sunday and obviously the
Monday and then on the Monday I was
bored and yeah you are
spazzing the caliban le you get in the
caliban oh back rest [ __ ] hell
remember when you was trying to say 3k
is nothing mate you never seen 3k in your life mate I'm
saying hardly um yeah it was gone in 10
minutes But it's the point is that you
would have spent more going out and
hearing about make believe boyfriends
and you would have had a hangover. So
either way you would have been at a loss. So
yeah and that's a risk you take. I spent
more than that
this you've never seen three grand in
your life mate. You you live in Wales
and you don't even live in Cardiff. Shut
up mate. It's about5600 pound to rent a
[ __ ] house in Wales. You've never
seen three grand in your life, mate.
You've never seen three grand in your
[ __ ] life. Shut up. Stop being
stupid. Right. Yeah. Okay. It might go
fast. It might not last that long, but
to say that it's nothing, give your
[ __ ] head a wobble, kid. You live in
[ __ ] Wales, mate. You've never seen
three grand in your [ __ ] life. [ __ ]
off. Jesus Christ.
And that's how I know these people in
this community don't have money just the
way they talk about
it. Yeah. You spend three grand every week.
Yeah. So yeah, that's what would have
happened if I went out Desmond. Anyways,
I would have spent about 3 350 quid
hearing about Make
Boyfriends. You skin Mong. I'm skinn.
Yeah. Okay, bro. I'm skinn. Yeah. Okay. So very
poss. But yeah. No, I can give up
Desmond. I generally think I've given up
100%. Um, yeah, I lost £150 yesterday on
roulette, mate, online. I told my mom
and she wasn't even that bothered to be
fair. She wasn't even disappointed. I
just said, "Oh, like I didn't go out the
bank holiday." And she's like, "Oh,
okay. It is what it is." But
yeah, and you can't even buy a pair of
trainers for £150 nowadays. Jesus
Christ. You spend more than £150 on a
takeaway, Lee. Come on, man. You're
being a fantasyist
again. You're being a fantasyist again,
man. £150 can't even buy you a pair of
trainers. That's how bad it is. They
literally can't, man. They're like 180
to about 270 now. But come on, more to
take away. Come on, Lee. You're not a
millionaire. You're a
fantasist. [ __ ] stop being a fantasist,
mate. Stop being a fantasist. You don't
have no money, Lee. Stop it. You're banned.
So, yeah. So, I can give up. When you've
had as many bad experiences as me, you
can give up. And you have to deal with
these time wasters. You can give up.
It's not even fun anymore going out
drinking. It's not even fun, man.
I'm starting traveling very soon, so I don't
care. You know, you're trying to tell me
how I can't just give up. How about you
go out every week and you try and you
and you start dealing with this [ __ ] for
years. Yeah. And then tell me how I
can't give up. Why don't you try it
every Saturday, go out, send it, get
your haircut every [ __ ] week, and
then try and tell me how I can't give
up. Yeah, exactly. You can't do it,
bro. Seeing it from an outsider's point
of view and you're the one that's not
sat there even [ __ ] trying, having to
deal with these [ __ ] So, no, I don't
give a [ __ ] about
them. Like, why wouldn't you give up?
You've been doing this for years. You've
traveled all over the country. You've
been doing this for years. Surely,
there's got to be a point where you're
like, "Fuck off." And you just leave the
country, which which I'm doing in 5
weeks. Surely, there's got to be a point
where you think, "Okay, [ __ ] it. This is
dead now. This country is dead. I'm not
doing this no
more. Surely, there's got to be a point.
You can't be You can't keep trying until
you're [ __ ] 35 and then it's [ __ ]
too late. You're too old and you said,
"Oh [ __ ] I wish I left the country
years ago. It was women all along years
ago. How many years you want to keep
wasting? How much money do you want to keep
wasting?" You know, time you're never
going to get that thinking that it's
going to be different the next time. How
many years are you going to keep wasting
doing this? How much money are you going
to keep wasting doing this? For how
long? What? Until I'm 40 years of
age. I just told you I'm going I told
you I'm going to [ __ ]
Thailand in 5 weeks. I can go out every
week drinking until 5 weeks, but there's
no point cuz they're all the same. This
is what I'm saying. There's there's no
point. I won't be going out this week either.
I'd probably go cinema and watch [ __ ] Peppa
Pig. I'd rather go to the cinema and
watch [ __ ] Peppa Pig, mate. Cuz at
least Peppa Pig won't pretend they got
boyfriends. It doesn't matter what I
will live on, bro. It doesn't matter
what I will live on. I have money. I get
money. But yeah, like there's got to be
a cut off point when you think, "No,
[ __ ] this." You know, and you actually
take pride in yourself and think, "I'm
not disrespecting myself. I'm not humiliating myself
anymore cuz where are we? 22 to 20. How
old are we?
27. So how many years is that? Why are
you asking what I will live on?
Obviously I have money. I'm not being
defensive. What? What do you mean? What
will I live
on? Money that I get. Money that I have.
It's a self-explanatory question, bro,
about what will I live on? Money I have
and get. Otherwise, I wouldn't be
going. It's a [ __ ] stupid
question. So, what do you want me to do?
Keep trying until I'm [ __ ] 35? And
then you realize you just wasted all
your life? Wasted all your
youth? Yes, I get more money than
benefits. Yes, I get more money than
benefits. I get monies. I get money
other ways than
benefits. It doesn't matter though, does it?
So, but yeah, you want to start trying
every week and then try and tell me that
I can't give up. That's not even me
being defensive. Like, that's just me
like just saying that just got to do it,
bro. Like, do it every week for one
month and then try and tell me how I
shouldn't give up. Yeah. [ __ ] this, bro.
What a [ __ ] waste of my last bit of
20s. Oh, you're married. Oh, right. It's
not mad. Everyone on YouTube seems to be
married, but not a lot of people getting
married nowadays. Another one that's
married. You know what? I never hear
about people getting married nowadays.
People that are in relationships, you
never hear it.
Never. Sisters, sisters, friends, people
that I know, you never hear about people
getting married nowadays. Not like you
do in third world Asian countries, but
everyone on YouTube seems to be married.
But good for
them. People do not even get married
like that nowadays. Anyways, but um I
mean that's just a nice
excuse, you know, that why you don't
want to try. So you'd rather me stay in
this country, keep trying, keep dealing
with their [ __ ] knowing that it's
always going to be the same. Come on,
man. Think before you speak. It's always
going to be the same here. Nothing's
ever going to change
here. I've been to Manchester 10 times.
I've been to Liverpool. I've been to
Sheffield three times. I've been to
[ __ ] Scotland. I've been to [ __ ]
Wales. I've been to [ __ ] Leeds. I've
been to [ __ ] Birmingham. I've been to
[ __ ] Nottingham. I've been to [ __ ]
Bristol. I've been [ __ ] oh man, more
places. If you was if it was going to
happen in this country, it would have
happened by now. It's that's the end.
There's no two ways about it. It's not
up for a debate. It would have happened
by now. You know, why would you still
keep trying in this country? What's
really going to happen? You get a number
and they ghost
you. My friend invited me out on Sunday.
I was like, "Bro, to be honest with you,
I don't want to be doing this anymore."
You know, you might have come out of
your break, but I'm not doing this no
more. You know, cuz there's just no
point. You get to a certain point where
you think, "Fuck, but I've tried more
than anyone in the world." So, I can
actually say that I've tried more than
anybody in the world. That's that's a
given fact. So I can give up, you know,
and it doesn't bother me, you
know. Yeah. A bit like here then, is it?
Girls abroad would only want you for
money. Yeah. Just like here then. Just
like here, they only want it. It just
sounds like women everywhere then,
doesn't it? Yeah. Cuz women in America
is not going to want you for money, is
it? Women in England, they're not going
to want you for money, is it? Nah. Nah.
That's never about money, is it?
N. Yeah, you're right, bro. Women here
will love you for you. Women in America
will love you for you. But if you go to
Thailand, they just want your money.
Yeah. Yeah. That's not women in general.
No, that's just that's just Thailand.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Women here, they they
don't want you for money. Nah.
Nah. That's why when you offer them
money, they don't suck your dick in the
Weather Spoons toilet. In it, that's why
when you spend money on them, they don't
give their [ __ ] out. Is it? Yeah. It's
not about money. Nah. Probably just your
personality there, love, is it? Give
your head a wobble, mate. Give your head wobble.
Seriously, it's always been about money with them
[ __ ] Most of the time anyways. 99% of
time. The only free sex I ever got was
somebody from New Zealand and somebody in
Manchester. All the rest I paid.
American I paid. Because you're buying
steak. You're buying them stuff, so
you're you are paying. You are paying to
impress and then ultimately they're
giving you their body, so you're
paying. Cuz you get so many guys, right,
that think, "Oh, I never pay for sex. I
will never pay for sex. I will never
have to pay for sex." Yet, they don't
take these women out on a date, spend
money on them, and even if it's to get
to know them and that, it doesn't matter
because you might never see them again.
You've still paid money before you've
had sex. So, you're paying. Well, the
one in Manchester, I didn't pay. I
bought one drink and that's it. And
obviously, the one in New
Zealand, I bought a drink, they bought me two
drinks. So, I can say that I didn't pay
for that, but most of the time you do
pay because money talks.
So, yeah, I just don't see the point in
in trying in this country anymore. If
somebody could tell me an actual point
it sounds like I have a serious No, I really
don't. What do you mean I have a serious
problem with spending money on them or I
spend too much on them? I can't stand
them. I actually [ __ ] despise them.
I'm not even joking. I actually despise
them, mate. [ __ ] that. sitting on a
[ __ ] barber's chair for an hour,
paying 40 quid just to hear the same
[ __ ] It's my sister's birthday Saturday
as well, and I probably won't even go
out to be
honest. So, we should go for some drinks, but nah. Nah,
mate. Yeah, cuz that's what you do on
dates. because that's what they expect
before they give you punani, you
know, but there's nothing good that can
come out of
[ __ ] you know, you won't even, to be
honest, you don't even really need to go
to Thailand. You could just use escorts
here. It's the same thing. You could just use
escorts. But everyone pays for sex. Everyone
does. I never seen a problem with using
escorts to be honest with you. I've
never seen the
problem. Some people see the problem,
some people don't see the problem.
There's not a right or wrong answer.
Just everyone has a different opinion on
it. My opinion is
that everybody pays. That's my one way
or another. That's my opinion. Some
people agree, some people disagree.
There's loads of people that agree.
There's loads of people that disagree.
It's just one of them, you
know. I've got no life experience. I've
got more life experience than you ever
have. Yeah, stop talking about yourself.
Your butt is Yeah, stop talking about
yourself. That's why I've been seen with
more women than anybody on
YouTube. Yeah, bro. Stop talking about
yourself. Um, handb is an escort. Um 60
to about 100. I'm Butters. Why don't you
jump in the hangouts and show us your
face? Stop talking about yourself. Go
self-reflect on another channel. Not my
one. Off you
[ __ ] Off you [ __ ] [ __ ] Sorry. Um
that's just one of the projectors that
we get on YouTube. Sad, miserable
person. He's late 30s, late 40s, ain't
got a life. So comes on YouTube and
projects. Is that mad? I'm the best
looking person on YouTube and I've been
with more women than anyone on YouTube
and I've been seen with more money than anybody on
YouTube. But yeah, I'm all these things.
Yeah, stop talking about yourself. It's
no good for your mental health, man.
Yeah. So, realistically, you're best off
just using escorts and it's traveling. Really?
Yeah. If somebody could tell me
like the point of going out, then I
would understand it. But for where I'm
sitting, unless I'm wrong, I don't see
no point. I think it's just the same
old. I've got boyfriends, shitty
ghosters, shitty time wasters. I
generally don't see the point in even
trying and spending
money. Yeah, I think I am actually where
I need to be now. I think I have called
it a day in this
country. Generally think I have called
it a day. And then you get all these
people that say you can't give up, but
yet they've never tried in their life.
So it they they wouldn't even last a
week doing this, you know.
So, and you know, the maddest thing is
even if you was to find someone, it's
not even going to be worth it anyways. So
yeah, and I get three grand a month. You
think you can get three grand a month from benefits?
No. [ __ ] benefits? No, you [ __ ] can't. So yeah. So
yeah, I think I am where I need to be, bro. I
think calling me Butters. Yeah, I'm
better looking than anybody on this
community. Self projecting. These people
have been doing it for years, man. These
[ __ ] ugly 30 late 30s, 40y old
spastics. They've been doing it for
years, man. Even before I can grow a
beard. These sad little
spastics coming on YouTube. Maybe they
projecting these sad little spackers.
They ain't got a
life. You would have thought they would
have called it a day, bro. [ __ ]
hell. They've been on YouTube projecting
their [ __ ] life um before I even started
[ __ ] cold approaching. That's how long it's
been. Same repeating people. You know what I
mean? So yeah, bro.
Yeah. [ __ ] tin foil. Tin
foil. What a name. A tin
foil. Yeah. These people talk about
themselves. Have you seen when their
face finally gets out there? They look like monsters.
Have you seen them when these people's
face gets out
there? [ __ ] monster looking
[ __ ] [ __ ] stinking they
are. That's why they call other people
ugly in the skin because it's a
reflection of what they see in the
mirror every day when they wake up. I'm
a That's a banger, bro. That's a [ __ ]
banger. Literally, it's the truth
though, mate. It's not even a It's not
even a It's not even a cuss, bro. It's [ __ ]
facts. [ __ ] old weekly people on
YouTube every day ain't got a life. Yeah.
But that's another thing. Why are they
so obsessed with money as well and calling people
skin? Strange, isn't it? You would have
thought right with these spackers that
in years they would have thought of a
new comeback. But nope.
Nope. No way.
Jose How long do you have to keep doing it for?
this whole approaching
[ __ ] in this country, you know.
[ __ ] I wouldn't even go out if someone paid
me. I don't even think I'd go out if someone paid
me. I swear I don't think so.
Just think of it makes my bones
ache. Makes me feel tired of bacon
soup. I need to go get some coke.
Yeah, you can't give up.
I [ __ ] can watch me. So
yeah, it's true though. Say you try this
country till you're 35 and you think,
"Shit, I wish I left sooner. [ __ ] I
wish I gave up
sooner." That's what happens.
That's why I gave up gambling because I
thought at 27 I didn't want to waste any
more of my life doing it. I think 27,
you know, you're still young. So, you know.
Yeah, I think it makes sense. [Music]
Yeah, I hate them,
man. And uh it's not
mindset, it's reality.
It's not a mindset. It's [ __ ]
reality. That's what I have to keep
telling people on [ __ ] Reddit as
well. It's not a mindset. It's back in reality. Bye-bye.
[ __ ] [ __ ] made a new
account. Another late 30s, late 40s
projector and got alive.