Sorry about that,
mate. Had a uh phone call someone
Yeah, bro. Yeah, we was talking about
Lewisville Slugger being a [ __ ] ain't
got a life. Yeah, I probably shouldn't
say that. He's probably get nicked. Yeah,
bro. Yeah. Lewisville Slugger, the
[ __ ] low life that sits online every
day trying to psychologically troll
people cuz he ain't got a life. That's
what he was talking about, was it? The
[ __ ] ain't got a life. Um, you know
how you can clock him very quickly. He
says, "Man," after uh after every uh
sentence, he's a proper proper [ __ ]
wannabe troll. Ain't got a
life. Just sit online every day
trolling. Imagine your life being that
[ __ ] Like you got to sit on like you
got to make 100 accounts and troll. Like
imagine your life being that [ __ ] Oh
[ __ ] man. Life being [ __ ] One second. [ __ ] stupid
[ __ ] Oh yeah. Yeah. So your life must
be really [ __ ] if you have to steal on
YouTube. Happen to only reply to um
sorry happen to [ __ ] stop there.
Happen to [ __ ] troll. Your life must
be really [ __ ] Lewis Phil
Slugger. He actually thinks he's a good
troll. Imagine your life being that
[ __ ] You have to come online to troll every
day. That's what a loser. Proper
loser. And then have to try to befriend
people, man. This community is just full of losers,
bro. It's full of losers, matey.
This system is very corrupt. That's
another thing that [ __ ] about this
country is the system's
corrupt. Yeah, that's another thing. Be
good to go to Thailand in
weeks. Yeah. How much money I got left? [Applause]
Uh, I should see enough, mate.
They definitely are,
bro. They [ __ ] definitely are, brother. Yeah. What's
up? Yeah, Louisville slug is a low life.
You got you got life, mate.
sat on YouTube behind that Desmond Deeds
account. Sad life you live, mate. Having
to come on YouTube trying to troll like
you're a good troll. Like you're thick
as [ __ ] Get a life, man. People like
that, all you can actually say to them
like actually is just get a
life is actually get a [ __ ]
life. Nothing else you can actually say to him,
mate. Look at me. I'm sick, bro.
I need a trim,
brother. But yeah, them people, they
need to get a life. Look at me, bro. I
need a straight up
trim. But I ain't scared to show my face.
So I'm like Louisville
Slugger. He's a trim
native. Look at that. What the [ __ ] is
that hair about,
bro? What the [ __ ] man? Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. You're um you're Lewisville
Slugger. Desmond Deed. I can smell your
mile off. Like I can It's like smelling
burnt popcorn. I can smell your mile
off. Yeah. You try to be all friendly,
then you try to troll, and then you
start insulting. You're boring, mate.
You've been doing this for [ __ ] ages. You're
boring. You're act [ __ ] boring, man. Telling
you, you're actually boring, mate. You
need to get a
life. Stop saying man at the end of [ __ ] every
sentence. Yeah, I just had an argument
with a [ __ ] police officer.
Yeah, I had to [ __ ] tell her about
herself. I said, "I'll be coming in
tomorrow, mate." Yeah, don't you worry
about that. I'll be coming in tomorrow.
I've had enough of you [ __ ] pigs. It
last me a [ __ ] lifetime. Long story,
but yeah, but we're better now anyways.
Yeah. Nah, you are definitely definitely
Louisville Slugger, mate. Yeah, I can
smell you a mile off. I can smell your
mile off when you say man at the end of
every sentence. Mate, I know it's you.
You give yourself away very
easy. You give yourself away very
easily, mate. We know it's you,
mate. Mate, it's you. Stop it. You're
Louisville slugger. Stop it, mate. Yeah,
we know it's
you. It's you. It's you. Stop it. Stop
it now, mate. I know you better than you
know yourself. Stop
it. Don't fancy a chat. Yeah, bro. I'll
send you my address so we can have a
chat face to
face. Yeah, I will uh give you my
address right now and uh you can come on my address,
bro. Nah, bro. It's just to do with this
whole um I'm not going to get into it,
bro. But I just told her I'll be coming
in tomorrow, mate, and I'll be making a
complaint and I'm going to keep keep
reporting and keep keep reporting cuz
I've had enough of you [ __ ] pigs.
Yeah. So, yeah, it's a long story. It
doesn't matter anyway. It's nothing to
do with YouTube. But
yeah, all I've got to say is these
police Oh, you're talking about
yourself. Listen, Kevin Murphy, um, stop
talking about yourself. Call yourself
ugly, no girlfriend, that's all
yourself. Um, but yeah, all I' all I can
say is, bro, um, police, um, they have
their favorites. This country has got to
be the most corrupt for police. They
they they've got their favorites, bro.
This the system is corrupt. I'm telling
you, it definitely definitely is
corrupt. Yeah. And I said, "Anyhow, you
ever come in my door again, I'm going to
give you an ass whooping in front of the
whole street. I'm going to give you a
good oldfashioned ass whooping, mate,
with your handcuffs. I promise you that
for nothing, mate. I don't give a [ __ ]
about prison. Yeah, [ __ ] that. How
many times have I been nicked? Yeah,
it's it's corrupt, bro, if I'm telling
you. I'm not going to get into it
anyways, bro. But, um, how's the dating
going, PJ? Um, have you got a memory loss? I
literally they side with the They side
with Nazis. They side with Nazis as
well. Yeah, they side with Nazis as
Um, and yeah, you seem to have memory
loss because I literally told you that
I'm done with women in this country. So
maybe you you didn't hear me. I'm sure I
mentioned it yesterday that I'm done
with the women in this country and I'm
sticking to my guns. So yeah. Yeah, they
they they they cyber nons. Yeah, that's
what I've noticed. It's corrupt, bro.
It's corrupt. They like to uh They like
to play two sides of a
coin. Yeah. They like to play two sides of a coin. Nothing,
bro. Yeah. I'm done with women, bro.
They're just They're all the same.
What's the point of talking to people
that all the
same? Nothing, mate. I said to I had
this police officer on on the phone,
Joe, in it, trying to say, "Oh, you need
to send this. You need to send that." I
was like, "Listen, mate." Yeah. I have
sent you enough. enough enough evidence.
And you know what? I'm going to go to
the police station tomorrow. I'm gonna
make um I'm going to make um I'm going
to make another um I'm going to make a
complaint. I'm going to make I'm not
leaving you alone now. Yeah. You've come
on my door enough times. You wanted to
get yourself involved with social media
time and time and time and time and time
and time and time again. Right. I'm
going to come tomorrow. I'm going to make a
complaint. Stop talking about yourself.
I'm going to make a complaint. Um, and
I'm gonna keep keep th my balls on
Golden Bet. No, I don't gamble anymore. No. So,
um, yeah, what I'm going to do is I'm
gonna, and I said, if you ever come on
my door again, it'll be the last thing
you do. I don't give a [ __ ] about
prison, bro. I don't care. I said that
to them as well, bro, cuz of um Yeah,
it's not right, bro. You know what I'm
saying? It's not
right. No, they're not. They're not
normal people with a uniform. They're [ __ ]
pigs. Yeah, they're not. They're [ __ ]
pigs. And I said that to their face as
well. I said, "You come on my door
again. You see what happens to you,
bro." The third time. I mean it, bro. I
will say what I want to cops, mate. Stop
it, Louis F. I'll say what I want. I
call them a pig to their face as well.
You shitty little pig in a shitty little
uniform. That's what I said to them. And
I'll say to them again, they'll get it
proper next time,
bro. Yeah. I swear to God, you can't
play two sides of a [ __ ] coin. Yeah.
And if you if you don't think if you
don't if you don't know what that means,
then go look it up.
Yeah. [ __ ] stupid little [ __ ] nons
lovers. That's what they are. Nons
lovers. I'm telling you, the police are
nons lovers. They're not no normal
people, bro. They're [ __ ] pigs. Yeah.
Look at all the look at the [ __ ] [ __ ]
that happened with the um Manchester
police force where you don't have the
history that I have had with them. You
know, I'm not going to get into it
anyways. It's irrelevant, bro. I'm going
there tomorrow anyways. So, it's not
it's not a problem. Yeah, I've had to
make this video for this police officer
because she kept talking over me. If you
let me answer the question and stop
talking over me, then I would answer
you. She just kept talking over me, over
me, over me, over me, over me again and
again and again and again and again.
You're asking me a question. I'm trying
to answer you. You're talking over me.
So, yeah. I'll see you tomorrow. I'm not
stopping. I told him I'm not stopping.
You wanted to get yourself involved time
and time again. Everyone woke up to you,
bro. Yeah. Yeah, they would do, mate.
They have But they have their favorites.
They have their favorites. But you know,
the maddest thing is, bro, if you if you
was to if you report people, right, they
can never do anything about it. They can
never do anything about it. But as soon
as someone calls the police on you,
right, as soon as someone calls the
police on you, mate, they want your door
before you can say Jack Robinson,
they're they're bent. They're corrupt.
I'm telling you, they're corrupt. I
think it's racism as well. I think a lot
of it is
racism. Yeah, bro. I think a lot of it
is racism as well, cuz they have their
favorites, bro. Trust me, the police,
they have got their favorites. Trust me,
they do. And I'm speaking from
experience. They [ __ ] do. Yeah. Me, I
said women are evil the other day. I'll
probably get nicked. Somebody could
probably try and kill me and then they'd
get away with it. Yeah,
bro. They're They're bent, bro. They're
proper bent. I'm telling you, they're
corrupt. These piggies, I'm telling you,
bro. They're They're bent. They're bent.
They're bent. They're bent. They're
bent. I've had lots of dealings with them, bro.
even though I don't even have a criminal
record, but trust me, they have their
favorites. But I'm going to go there
tomorrow anyways and make a complaint
and just start the whole thing all over
again. And that's what I was advised to
do as well. So
yeah, do you know what I'm saying, bro?
Like it's [ __ ]
up. They're actually [ __ ] up. They
actually have their favorites, mate.
They have their favorites. And I said,
if you ever come on my door again, I'm
not opening the door to you. I'm not
opening the door. So, you're going to
have to break in. I said, "You ever come
on my door again, I'll be I will move
house. I'm telling you." Yeah. You You
can't play two sides of a coin. Yeah.
You wanted to keep getting yourself
involved with social media and taking
people's reports and time and time
again. And I let it slide and then I was
the one that had to start reporting
people. Right. You come on my door
again, I'm not opening the door. So, you
can break the door and you can do
whatever you want. I'll move house, you
know, cuz again, you you you can't play
two sides of a coin, you know? you can't
get yourself involved when it suits
yourself. Um, and she was just making up
like bogus excuses as why she can't
investigate it. And nothing made any
sense. So, I had to make a video to her
saying, "This does not make sense. If
somebody was a murderer, if they killed
somebody 2 years ago, they're still a
murderer." You know, I was watching
somebody the other day. It took them 35
years to catch a murderer. What you're
saying don't make no sense. And we'll
see what your sergeant has to say about
it tomorrow. You know, cuz I've had
enough of it, mate. I've had enough of
it. Yeah. I've had You've come on my
door time and time. I don't give a [ __ ]
if I'll get myself nicked. I don't give
a monkeys [ __ ] I don't care. I'm not
scared of them. It wouldn't be the first
time I got nicked. I don't care. I do
not give a monkeys [ __ ] Literally, I've
had enough of them. Like, you don't know
how many times. Yeah. They have come on
my door, bro. Over social media. Over
social media. Over social media. out of
London taking my devices time again.
They never took it back. I don't give a
[ __ ] about getting a nicked for the 101st
time. You know what I'm saying, mate? I
just said to her like, "What you're
saying doesn't make sense." I said,
"You're calling me off a private number,
then you're hanging up because you're
talking over me." Yeah. And then they're
trying to say I'm being abusive. How am
I being abusive? You're not listening to
what someone's saying. So that's
it. Yeah. But I'll never open the door
to him ever again if they ever come on
my door. Not that they would, but if
they ever come on my door and I'm not
opening it. Simple, mate. I'll I'll give
them the same advice. Go and report it
and [ __ ] off. I'll give them the same
advice that that they give other people
whose crime they don't want to deal
with. Do yourself a favor and [ __ ] off.
That's what I will do.
Yeah. I can't stand pigs. Do you know
what? Yeah. My my my dad, you know what
my dad did when he was younger? He took
one of their eye out with a knife. He
took one of their eye out with a knife
and he only got 5 years. I was like,
"Fucking legend, mate. He's a legend, mate." You
know, and you know what, right? When I
got Nick last time, that's what I would
have said. I would have said, "Mate, I
don't even need to do anything. My old
man done the job for me, mate.
leaving you all eyeless. You [ __ ]
pigs. I can't stand pigs. I I don't like
them, bro. Worse worse than anyone.
Yeah, he took their eye out. [ __ ]
aggravating [ __ ] I can I can see like
how it gets to that point. They're
aggravating as [ __ ] They're so bent.
Bro, they're so [ __ ] bent as well,
lad. Yeah, he did. He He took his eye
out and he he got five years.
Yeah. [ __ ] legend. No, it's not a bit
for, mate. They're [ __ ] aggravating.
I tell you what I tell you what is a bit
for. Them keep coming on people's door,
taking people's devices and embarrassing
people. That's a bit [ __ ] for, mate.
That's a bit for. And then when somebody
reports something you claim that you
can't investigate, [ __ ] off and have a
wank. You know what I'm saying, mate?
[ __ ] off and have a [ __ ] wank. Away
with your [ __ ] self, mate. Yeah. It's
always a bit for when it's someone else,
is it, bro?
Yeah. And they've done it about 10 15
times. I don't know your dealings, mate.
Yeah. I don't know your dealings, but I
I was about to lose my [ __ ] phone
[ __ ] two months ago cuz they were
going to take my phone. Yeah. It's not a
bit too far. [ __ ] off and leave people
alone. Yeah. If you don't want to if you
want if you don't if you want to get
yourself involved with social media.
Yeah. It's not one law one law. It's not
one law for one one law for another.
Yeah. It's it doesn't work like that.
But they seem to think it works like
that. So you are you you want to get
involved or you don't want to get involved, you
know, because when I go tomorrow and I
report them, right? When I report them,
when I tomorrow when I report them,
Yeah. this is what I'm going to say. I'm
going to say, if you don't do anything
Yeah. So you don't want to get involved.
I do not want to see you anywhere near
my door again. If you if you're not
going to do anything about this, I do
not want to see you because you're not
going to come in. I'm not letting you in
no matter what it is. And you're going
to have to break the door now, mate. And
by the time you break the door down, I'm
not going to be there. Yeah. Yeah. Do
you know what I'm saying? So, it's like
you're getting involved or you're not
getting involved. Can't stand police,
bro. I can't stand them. Like, you don't
know the dealings I've had with them,
bro. You don't. Like mine's more severe
than most people's cuz I find in this
country, I don't know about any other
country, but this country, it's one rule
for one. It's what my sister said.
They've got their favorites. They do.
They genuinely do, bro. And it's not just the
rich, you know? I can't stand them, bro.
I I can't stand them, bro. You know, and
I and and I said to when I got Nick last
time, cuz my mom was like, "Shut up."
The last time before that, I said, "Why
don't you want Why don't you one of Why
don't one of you pigs tell me to wind my
neck in?" I'll say, "Why don't you
[ __ ] wind yours in, you shitty cunt?"
Yeah. And I was saying to that [ __ ] I
was saying that to him last time. I
said, "Why don't you [ __ ] wind yours
in, pig? My old man done the [ __ ] job
for me. For [ __ ] sake. You done the
[ __ ] job for me, mate. The [ __ ] you
talking to, you silly little pig?" You
know what I'm saying? Like, you don't
know what the [ __ ] I was saying to them
last time. I was like, "You're nothing
but a bunch of [ __ ] pigs." I was
saying the madest [ __ ] bro. And then
they all tried to lick my ass when I was
in custody, bro. They all started trying
to be nice. I said, "You're nothing but
a bunch of [ __ ] pigs, mate." That's
what I said to
them. You know what I'm saying,
lad? I belong in prison. Oh, do I?
Yeah. But yeah, like the point is the
police have their favorites, mate. Like
they do. They generally do. Like they
generally do. It's one rule for one, one
rule for another in this country. One
person reports one thing, they're on
your door. You report a million things,
they don't care. It's always been that
way. You know, like it's it's been that
way as long as I can remember. So
So do you know what I'm saying, Cold?
Like it's like if you was a murderer two
years ago, so what? Are you no longer a
murderer? Are you no longer guilty for that
crime? You need to I don't [ __ ]
respect them [ __ ] pigs. Are you
[ __ ] mad? I don't respect them silly
little [ __ ] in a uniform. Are you
[ __ ] mad? [ __ ] off. Respect, please.
I don't [ __ ] respect them [ __ ]
pigs in a shitty little uniform. They've
got [ __ ] devices that they ain't gave
back of mine. [ __ ] shitty little
[ __ ] in a shitty little uniform. I
respect I respect a [ __ ] down the toilet
more than I respect them. I respect a a
a down the toilet more than I respect
them. I can't stand them, mate. They've
still got devices they haven't gave back
of mind. Yeah. Trust me, Joe. You
wouldn't respect them. And you've had
them on your door time and time again
for no reason. Yeah. Time and time and
time and time and time and time and time
again taking your stuff. You wouldn't be
respecting them. Yeah. You wouldn't be
respecting, arresting you for no reason.
Yeah. Yeah. But that's the thing. They
don't defend you though, do they? Okay.
Let me ask you a question. They don't
defend you because that time LT come in
the house, I could have got killed.
Where was they then? They were they were
called 15 minutes prior. So they don't
even they don't even save people. So
don't even try and use that excuse. I
can't stand them. I literally can't
stand them. They're not a C. They've got
no [ __ ] authority over you. They're
not no judge. I can't stand them, bro.
And to be honest with you, I don't even
like talking about it. Like that time in
Newcastle when they arrested me for no
reason. Do you think like, bro, [ __ ]
that, man. You know what I'm saying? You
can be arrested for no reason, mate.
Yes, you can. Yes, you can. Because
arrested doesn't mean you're guilty. So,
yes, you can be arrested um for no
reason. Because I got arrested for no
reason in Newcastle. Do you know what
I'm saying? So, I've had dealings with
them. And yes, you can be arrested for
no reason. Um because I have been
arrested for no reason, which is why
I've never been to court except from the
other day. So yeah. So no, I can't stand
police. I can't stand it, mate. I'm not
even going to tell you like some of the
things. Um and they investigate one
person's crime, but they don't
investigate another person's
crime. I didn't call the police. Someone
else called the police. I didn't call
them. I didn't call them. Someone else did.
So, someone else did. Wasn't me. Yeah,
bro. Like, like I said, bro, they've got
their favorites. They've got their
favorites. I can't stand them. Like, if
I didn't have the history that I had
with them, then I wouldn't have uh
because if I had committed a This is my
problem. This was always my problem with
the police share code. I don't know what
your history is. I hadn't committed a
crime. If I had committed a crime, then
I'd be like, "Okay, I got caught. Fair
enough." fair and square. I've been
caught, but it was always for stuff I
never done and it would always one
person would get away with it and I'd
get nicked. That's why I can't stand
them. It it that is the exact reason. If
I was if I was a um if I was a actual
criminal, then I'll be okay, I've been
caught. If I was a drug dealer, okay, I
got caught. You know, that's the life of
a drug dealer. That's the life of a
[ __ ] whatever it is you're doing.
Okay. But what they do is they have made
up charges um to come and arrest me
before while somebody else they will let
off and get away with murder. That's why
I don't like
them. No, it wasn't it wasn't that
Twitter. It wasn't that Twitter thing.
But that's it, bro. Yeah, that's it.
Yeah. I think it's cuz I'm not white. I
think it's racism. Yeah. I was thinking,
you know, when I was in the police cell
last time, right? I think it's racism. I
think it is racism. No, funny enough, I
was thinking the same thing cuz it's
like, okay, yeah, what? So, they're
arresting you for calling somebody gay
virgin. That's not against the law. No,
something's not right here. The police
have come in your door 10 times for
things you haven't even done. Why do
they keep coming on your door and then
when you report someone else, they can
never do anything about it. I'm thinking
it's got to be racism. I was I was
actually thinking that because where I
don't look fully white, it's something
something's not right there. Like I was
saying to Antman this as well. I was
saying this to him as well, like earlier
that it's got to be racism. And the
thing that annoyed me, cold, it wasn't
that they it wasn't that they were only
targeting me. Like, you know, like some
YouTubers, yeah, they get targeted
because they pissed the police off and
they know they're doing things that they
can't get them for. And then when they
can finally get someone, then they get
them. Then I'd be, okay, yeah, you've
pissed the police off. You've pissed the
system off. But again, with my one, it
was like it was like these people can do
what they want to me. And then when I
retaliate, I get nicked. That's what my
whole problem is, you know? Like they
get away with anything and everything
and then as soon as you retaliate, you
get nicked. That's my problem with them.
I don't know what your problem is, you
know? You know what I'm saying? When
they Yeah, I reported someone. Yeah, I'm
reporting someone. I'm still in the
process of reporting someone. Yeah.
Yeah. Cuz you people keep [ __ ]
reporting me. Yes. I've had to report
people because that's what my solicitor
has has has har has advised me and
that's what the court advised me. Yes, I
do hate them. I do hate them. But I'm
I'm going to do it to get these people
nicked because they keep getting me
nicked. Yes. Yes, I do hate them. I'm
doing it for a reason. If somebody
randomly on the street comes and stabs
me now, I won't tell the police. If
somebody comes and steals something from
me, I won't call the police. But with
this community, I'll be more than happy
to keep calling the police because the
amount of times cold stellar these
people have called the police on me,
it's longer than the criminals are,
mate. Yeah. So when it comes to this,
right, when it comes to this, I will
continuously keep doing it. If I walked
out the street right now and someone
robbed me, I'm not calling the police.
I'm not grass. But when it comes to this
community, it ain't even grassing, bro.
It's you protecting yourself. And
everyone knows that. You know what I'm
saying? Everyone [ __ ] knows that. you
know. Yeah. When it comes to these
people, damn [ __ ] right, bro. Because
I've had enough of them keep coming on
my door. And after all, Cole, they want
to get involved. The police clearly want
to get involved over social media. So,
let's get them involved. They clearly
want to get involved, right? So, let's
get them involved. The police want to
get involved over social media. Let me
help them. They've been on my door enough [ __ ]
times. Do you know what I'm saying, bro?
So, I think in my opinion, I'm helping
them. But obviously, I'm going to call
the police. I'm going to keep calling
police. I don't want to pull the police
women. I despise women. I don't like
women. Why do you keep bringing women
up? They're all the
same. Oh, I lost 150 pound on roulette yesterday, Steven
Howard. It didn't piss me off that much.
It just made me feel sick. But that's
the whole thing with this with this
police, bro. Like if it was not this
whole YouTube thing, I wouldn't have had
a problem with the police and I wouldn't
even have a problem if I was a criminal
and got caught. That's the name of the
game. But you're not you're not a
criminal. You're an actual innocent
person. That's the annoying thing. You
are an innocent [ __ ] person. You got
arrested in Newcastle. You didn't do
anything. You know, they still ain't You
know, I had to go all the way back up
there because of
police. Yeah. I lost 150 on roulette.
That was that was in a month. Yeah. I
saved 600 700 by gambling. Do you know
what do you know the gambling thing?
Yeah. When I lost £150. I It's a
positive you know cuz that bank holiday
you would have spent £350 and the past 3
weeks you've not gone out you probably
would have spent about4500. So in a way
yeah you might have gambled but you
still saved a [ __ ] ton of money even
losing that 150. So in a way it's a
positive. That's the way I justify it.
Even the bank holiday, you would have
spent way more than £150 going out,
hearing about I've got a boyfriend. So
the 150 is just something you saved
really because you saved about 6700 by
not going out the past couple weeks. So
you can't really moan, can you? So
that's the way I justify that roulette
thing. And you can't even buy a pair of trainers for
£150. Yeah. I got rejected by police
women. Yeah. Yeah. That's really it.
Yeah. Yeah. What's wrong? I never got
anywhere. I can't stand police,
bro. Maybe if I went on this social
media thing, it'd be a different story.
I just don't like
them. It's just [ __ ] the system, is
it? So, yeah, that £150 I still save though
cuz I still save
money. So, I'm not going to go out this
week either. I'm done with women in this
country. Coach said I don't want nothing
to do with them. They're all evil. I
don't want anything to do with people
that can only reply to negativity, bro.
Why? I don't want anything to do with
people that can only reply to
negativity. That's [ __ ]
bogus. Think about that. They can only
reply to negativity. Do you really want
to be associated with them kind of
people? I'm going to Thailand in 5
weeks. It's set in stone, bro. I'm out
of this country. I'm I'm where I'm at, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. I just don't like him, bro.
I just I just don't like them, bro.
Like, because of my If you had my
history, you would
understand. Told, if you had my history
with them, you would
understand. It's very much one rule for
one, one rule for
another. You know, I wouldn't mind if
you was a shoplifter and you got caught.
Then I'd be, "Okay, I'm a shoplifter. I
got caught." I would understand if you
actually committed a [ __ ] crime and
you was in the you're in the sales when
you shouldn't even be in the sales.
That's what I'm saying.
You know what I'm saying? Even if you
was a shoplifter and you got nicked.
Okay. Well, you committed. What did you
You know, that's the risk you take, isn't
it? Yeah. I don't like them period,
man. I don't like him period,
bro. You know what I'm
saying? I I can't stand police, bro. Do
you know what? When one of the days they
deal with my my report, then I'll change
my mind and let bygones be bygones. Then
I'll actually say, "Okay."
Uh, man, are you obsessed with me? Why
are you [ __ ] stealing my pictures,
bro? Look at that good-looking
[ __ ] I'm better looking than
you, and you will never be able to show
your face. Bye-bye, you weirdo. Oh, look
at these little weirdos, man. Like, it's
not my fault I'm better looking than
you, bro. [ __ ] off, you [ __ ] weirdo.
Got my pictures saved, you [ __ ] creep.
But yeah, [ __ ] creepy
bastard. Guess what though, man? I'm not
scared to show my face like you
people. Not talking about you, cold. I
don't care, bro. I don't care about
women. I despise all of them. They're
all the same. Think about it, bro. If
they weren't all the same, I would have
met one by now that wasn't like that.
I'm 27, bro. Bear in mind, I've met
loads of different women from all over the country.
Never met a woman that weren't a [ __ ]
Strange, isn't it? They say that they're
not all the same, but think about it,
Cole. Bro, I can't stay I can't keep
doing this until I'm 35. I can't keep
doing this until I'm 35,
bro. I can't keep doing this till I'm 35
and then realize like actually
like I should have just gave up at
27. think of that regret. You keep
trying until like you're 35 and you
realize you wasted all them years where
nothing's ever going to change. You know
what I'm saying? Like, you might as well
just give up. Go to Thailand. That's what I'm
doing. You know, you think I'm not got
money to go out? Of course I do,
bro. But I just know they're always
going to be the same. Cuz if nothing's
changed, you are life's biggest loser.
We You all have girlfriends, mate.
You've never even had your dick sucked.
Have I ever? Yes, I have. Oh, yes, I
have been uh stopped and checked. Yeah,
I can actually tell you the story. Yes,
I have once. Your life's biggest loser.
You're talking about yourselves. That's
why you're on YouTube every day hating.
You show us all what you're about when
you come on YouTube every day hating. It
shows what your lives are really like.
[ __ ] That's why you're on YouTube every
day. Yes, I have been um uh stopped and
checked. Yes. Anyways, bye-bye, weirdo.
Um, yes, I have been stopped and
checked. Um, it's the Was it the first
time or the second time? It might have
been that day I met Morgan. Maybe it was
the other Stony I bought. I bought a
Stone Island and a new pair of trainers.
Yes, I do remember this. I bought a new
Stone Island jumper and a pair of trainers and
um I was waiting for my friend and they
stopped me and I'm thinking they must
have thought I was like a drug dealer or
something and they kept me for like half
hour. They searched me, took my phone,
checked my phone, everything. Yeah.
Yeah. It was bad, bro. It was bad. It
was [ __ ] bad. Um, and I'm thinking,
what? So, you don't think people can
afford expensive clothes without drug
dealing? And the money was legit as
well. I won the money from the casino. I
spent about 600 Stone Island, new pair
of trainers. I was like, "Bro, we're not all drug
dealers." Like, they stopped me. Yeah, I
remember it, bro. Yeah, it was bad.
scared the [ __ ] out of me as well cuz I
wasn't um No, they were checking to see
if the phone was mine or not stolen.
Yeah, they jumped on me like nothing,
bro. Like, what the [ __ ] I wasn't
expecting it. It was in central London.
It was by
um it was by Travagga Square. And I said
to my friend, I'm going to be a bit late
cuz these [ __ ] [ __ ] stopped me.
So, yeah, they put me in a van and
everything. I think they were If I had a
knife, I would have been [ __ ]
Yeah, yeah, yeah. It was madness, bro.
It was a
madness. But yeah, I'm going to
Thailand, bro. I'm not like But anyways,
back to the women. Yeah. Um, if there
was a woman that was truly different, I
would have met one by now. I can't think
of one woman that's different that I've
ever met. And how many years am I going to keep
searching? How many years you going to keep searching,
bro? Yeah, I don't need a job, mate. I
get enough money. and your MS is not
very experienced to say that you'll meet
someone when you least expect it. I've
been hearing that when I was since I was
17. I've been hearing that same thing
since I was 17. We can't afford to waste
any more time, mate. We need to go
traveling. We've already got some money
saved up. I'm going Thailand in 5 weeks.
We can't be afford to be wasting any
more time and money. If it ain't happen
at 27, meeting a woman, that's normal.
It ain't happening at [ __ ] 77. So
yeah. Oh [ __ ] One sec.
Hey bro, just on thingy. Um, undatables.
Nope. Yeah, I want to go just Thailand,
bro. Thailand. I just want to start
traveling now before I hit 30, you know.
I start go to some places large I have
never been. But yeah, you you will um I
will never deal with women ever again, bro.
Uh yeah, I will never deal with women
again. I don't think broke. No, I can't
stand them. They're all the same.
They're all the same. They will never
change. All pretend they got boyfriends.
All waste your time. All play victim.
All reply to only negativity. Like there's
literally no point, bro.
There's literally no point in even
trying. Uh, well, you would. I'm just
like I I honestly don't think I'd ever
bother with them again, bro. I'm like,
you know what I'm
saying? Sorry, I just talking to my
friend. So yeah,
basically he says, "What you doing, bro?
I can hear you talking and you were
shouting at a police officer." So yeah,
basically um I don't think I'll ever
bother with them again to be honest with
you. I don't think I will ever bother
with women again. I can't see happening.
We're almost 3, four weeks in and I
don't think I'll ever try again. I can't
see me trying again. I don't see no
point. They're all the same. They've
proved what they're about. What's the
point? For what, bro? You know what I'm
saying? I can't see the sense of trying
again. I've got my Saturday lined up.
Nice takeaway. Nice Grand Theft Auto.
I'm not even going out this week, bro.
It's my sister's birthday. I'm still not going
out. You're not missing nothing,
man. You're not missing nothing. Women
are all the same. They're never going to
prove you wrong. You've gave them chance
upon chance upon chance to prove you
wrong, and they're all the same. Like,
just give up now. It's It's about time.
I just want to go cuz I just want to see
what it's like cuz that man just tells
me everything about it. I'm that
stubborn now. I will never give one a
chance ever again. I'm that determined
and I'm that stubborn. I'm telling you,
bro. Because if I if there was somebody
that weren't like that, I would have met them by
now. Of course, bro. I would have met
one by now that wasn't like that.
They're all the same. That USA didn't
reply back. I even said I'll come next
week in it and tell you about yourself
in front of your dad and your boyfriend.
Got the money. What you waiting for?
Yeah, she didn't reply
back. Didn't reply back. Yeah, I thought
not. You [ __ ] [ __ ] And that's what
you're going to be dealing with as well
if you continue in the stating
game. Trust me, mate. There's no Even if
a woman come in the door now, I I
wouldn't open the door. It's that bad,
bro. It's It's really bad, you know. is
really really bad. I think it was the
the the the the [ __ ] that wasted my
time and the one that ghosted me last
month. I was like, "That is me done. I'm
finished. I'm not doing this no
more." Why? Uh because women have got unrealistic
standards. That's why,
brother. They've got unrealistic
standards and they're stuck up and they
think they're better than they are.
That's what it is, brother. They're just
um they're just they've just got
unrealistic expectations. Like beige,
yeah, I don't know who you are, but I'll
give you a story. Yeah. I went out bank
holiday, not last one, the the one
before that, and this woman approached
me saying, "Oh, yeah, you're good." He
was in a club. "Oh, you're good looking.
We're talking and that. Oh, I'll get
your number." So, I got her number. Text
him back and forth every two minutes.
Text him back. I was like, "Oh, okay. I
finally got a date this this year.
Limped to the date cuz I had a foot
injury. I had a [ __ ] up foot injury. I
limped to the date. Okay, they've
approached you. They texted me. Okay,
we're on to something now. Then I went
on a date. She literally said in half an
hour she didn't feel the vibe. I was
like, "Fuck this, bro." Like, "I know
what I'm about. Yeah, I know I'm
confident. I know I've got interest.
I've got I've got uh universal interest
and universal hobbies." Didn't say
anything wrong, obviously. And I was
like, "Fuck this." That Thursday I was
like, "No, I'm done." So, I just stayed
out. Then I went out two weeks after
that. Then I was supposed to meet
someone on a Friday. They ghost. I was
like, "I'm done with this. [ __ ] this,
bro. It's a waste of my time." So, so
yeah. Yep. I literally have to limp limp
all the way. Oh, talking about
yourself. Talking about yourself, buddy.
Stop talking about
yourself. So that's why I don't have an own
right. They're calling me skin, but I've
got more money than everyone in this
community. That's my
money, but I'm
skin. I think you got me confused with yourself
again. So yeah, bro. That's uh that's
where we're at,
lad. That's where we're at, basically.
is USA PJ. Yeah, she Yeah, he is, but
not for much longer. Can't see it
last. But yeah, after all them
experiences, I'm like I'm like, you
can't even speak to somebody without
pretending they've got a boyfriend. So,
what's the point? You can't even talk to
someone without pretending they've got a boyfriend. So, I
say, "Yeah, I'm not fat,
man. I gained a bit of weight cuz I kept
eating a lot. I need to do some more
walking now. My foot's better to be fair.
And it's just I'm working out,
bro. But um
yeah, just all
that. Do I have moves? Not yet,
man. Almost. But no, I won't I won't get
there, bro. I won't get there. I want to
die or something. I'm needing a lot of
ice cream. It's the ice
cream. Don't dumb me. I need to go to a
[ __ ] gym, bro. Serious.
You don't want to end up like Lord J, bro. [ __ ]
me. Should end up like Lord J. But yeah,
you can't even speak to people nowadays
without pretending they've got a [ __ ] boyfriend.
So yeah, I I think I'll be anti-women
for the rest of my
life. Cuz somehow I feel like I've met
more women than anyone in the world. Cuz
obviously that seems ridiculous, isn't
it? But it's like who could have met
more women than you when you've done
this for a living. You know, I've not
worked for years. I haven't had to work
for years. So I've been around the
country. You know, I've dealt with women
from different countries. So I I think
very much like if women were different,
you would have you would have met a
woman by now that was different. You you
would have met one. I'm sure to god you
if there women were really different,
you would have met one that was
different by now. You know, I've been
Liverpool, Manchester, I've been [ __ ]
Scotland, I've met Americans, I met
Canadians, I've met Australians, you
name it. And it doesn't ring right.
Like, if they really weren't all the
same, then you would have you would have
met one by now that the
same. How was your Yeah, it was tasty,
man. It was very tasty. Any girls show
up? Nothing on the whole I'm anti-woman.
Did that just cross your
mind? But yeah, I'm so stubborn now.
I'll never try
again. I'll never try again. I'll just
continue despising them for the rest of
my life. I reckon I think I'll just
generally be like that. I I will just I
would just continuously despise them for
the rest of my life, bro. Like I actually
would. There's no [ __ ] point anything
else, bro. Who's that guy in the chicken shop?
had a guy. Good job. Got a [ __ ]
belly, mate. It'll be me if I stop eating. So yeah,
bro. Might go for a walk, you know, bro.
I need to start
exercising. But yeah, I think I'll be
anti-woman for the rest of my life. Page
man, I can't lie to you, man. I can't you. Yeah.
There's been a lot of mistakes, bro. [Music]
USA. I need to go police station tomorrow as
well and find out what the [ __ ] is going on. [Music]
Why is Grezy a homosexual? Yeah, I think
he is, bro. Or maybe he's just asexual.
Maybe he's just [ __ ] Maybe he's just
anti-woman, you know? Maybe he's just
completely anti- [ __ ] women. Yeah,
she is skin. And then she tries to call
me poor. And then she tries to [ __ ]
call me poor, mate. Are you [ __ ] mad?
She tries to call me
poor. Yeah. for more money than she would
ever ever have
made. Got question what these people do about it. [Music] Um, one
Come. Yeah. What's up in the voice?
Yeah, I wish USA took me up on my offer,
bro. I wish USA took me up on my offer.
She's a [ __ ] coward, mate. I think
she [ __ ] shadow blocked me as well.
[ __ ] Why do I always end up meeting
scumbags? I don't know why I always end
up meeting these proper
scumbags, you know? [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, I I always end up meeting [ __ ] um scumbags,
bro. Scumbags. [ __ ] hell,
bro. [ __ ] complete that GTA, bro.
Nah, it's not bad luck. They're just all
the same, mate. It's nothing to do with
luck. I going to say it's anything.
They're just all the same, mate. Nothing
to necessarily to do with
luck. Nah, it's not even just necessary
luck. They're just all the
same. All the [ __ ] same. Why? I don't
bother with them no more. Yeah.
Want to make some burgers today.
Or should I have a
toway? Or should I have a
to? Nah, bro. No. What I lost the 150 on
was roulette. It wasn't Frankie. It was
roulette. N can't have a
takeaway. I need to start saving some dollar,
bro. I need to start seriously saving some dollars.
Can't do that. Takeways. [Music]
Good. There we go, bro.
Yeah, it wasn't bar roulette. It was
online. But that's how I know I'm not
addicted cuz I lost 150 and I'm not
going back on it. I think you
learn. Yeah, I think you learn, man. I
do think you learn.
I think you learn when
um you've had enough bad experiences.
It's like with a women thing. Like for
me it was like enough is enough. Like
it's not happening in this country. We
all can, you know, you're going to keep
meeting women that are all the same.
People tell you they're different, but
actions speak louder than words. And you
know, you meet women practically every
week and you've never been shown
different. So, you know, at the end of
the day, it doesn't matter what people
tell you. Oh, they're they're not all
the same. But they are. Cuz every time
you meet them, they turn out to be all
the same. So what someone says is not
what you experience. People can say
they're not all the same till the cows
come home from [ __ ] Australia, but
until you actually see it yourself, you
can't believe it, you know? So then
that's, you know, it will never change.
Even when my friend invited me out
Sunday, I said, "I'm not I'm not going
out, bro." I said 6 weeks minimum, didn't I?
So I just can't see me going out again
this country. I
can't and then only replying to
negativity rising theelves. It's not
anything I want to be involved in, you know.
Yeah, I do need to go for a walk today
and I'm going to try and have one burger
cuz I need to not get fat. Yeah, cuz
Yeah, cuz I was really active before the
foot injury and now the foot's
recovered. I don't feel like I'm as
active. I need to get back into
it. Just join the gym to be honest.
There's not one there's one not far.
So, just join the
gym. But I do eat a lot for [ __ ] sake.
It's that ice cream, bro. Can't be
eating ice cream like that,
man. I had to stop. I was getting
addicted to the cookie, you know, Ben &
Jerry's. It's [ __ ] addicting. It's addicting,
bro. It's not cuz I'm eating. I don't
normally gain weight. I don't really
walk. I need to start being more active
again. I'll be s my ass. Yeah.
Yeah, I have a
boyfriend. [ __ ] me. I've got some
approaches on my other
channel. I just despise him, bro. I
actually do despise them. They're the
ones with no emotions. They're the ones
feelings. You know, looking at stupid
USA, she thought, "Oh, I'll get on with
my life after doing what the [ __ ]
done." So I was I just [ __ ] with her
life. Just message her
[ __ ] You know what I'm saying? Just
message her [ __ ] You know what I'm
saying? But like it's simple. It is absolutely simple, bro.
Yeah. I can't stand him, bro. I literally
can't. I will never try again. Never.
Believe it or don't believe it. I will never try
again. You know what somebody said to me
before cold seller? There was like,
"You're better looking than these people
on YouTube. You got a better life and
you got more money than them. It's jealousy."
I think they're right in it. What do you think,
bro? Yeah, I think they're right. What
do you Well, they said that about me.
That's like you're better looking than
them. You got more money than them and
you got a better life than them. And
that's why they target you. Well,
obviously, bro, of course I got more
money than them. Now, even if you got
£1,500, you got more money than them.
They said it kills them. and they said,
"You should just get off of YouTube and
[ __ ] live your life." And that
comment stuck in my head, you know? I
remember exactly who said it. And I'm
thinking, bro, I think they're right,
you know? I think they're really right.
Like, you should just get off here and live your
life. Yeah, I remember that comment. I
think they're right, bro. Don't come any but
Yeah, it's the truth, is
it? Look at people like Belly. They only
they get like £300 a month in it.
So yeah, but like what he's trying to
say what he's trying to mean is like
you've you're better looking than them
and you got more money than them. And
with with money it people become jealous
when you got more money than them and
you got a better life. So what he means
is you're better looking than them.
You're having a good life and you're
showing money so they're jealous. That's
why they obviously go for you. So that's
what it is. That's why you get these
people like Red Scar not leaving me
alone cuz deep down it is jealousy. Like
as much as they don't want to admit it,
it is jealousy because if they were
better than you, they wouldn't do this.
Obviously, bro, like it's the truth.
It's of course it's jealousy cuz then if
it wasn't jealousy, they would just
leave YouTube and just live their life.
Yeah, I've got about 3K right now. All
disposable. Get more in two weeks. So, I
think that's pretty good. All your bills
paid. Three grand. I think that's good,
bro. Saying that I could make more money
if I wanted to, but I'm kind of lazy.
Yeah. So, obviously that's why I could
go to America, obviously. But it was
hard trying to save that money. It was
hard trying to save that money. Bro, it
took a month, but like maybe a month and
a bit, but it's still hard. Like I had
to not go out and drink and that.
So yeah, I got 3k disposable, bro. It's
not bad, is it? For two
weeks. See, I've not See, the thing is
with me, I've not been skinned for years.
Well, not for years, bro. Not for
years. So, but anyways, I'm going to go.
Yeah, I'll be back later,
buddy. See you later.