Oopsy [Music]
daisy. Oh my god.
[ __ ] gave me £4. They gave me [ __ ]
£4. I went on the root with the4 pound they gave
me. That is [ __ ] addicted, bro. I'm
not I'm not falling into
their into their trap.
I am not falling into their trap, bro. No [ __ ]
way. I covered four numbers and it went next
door. They would always to try and reel
me. It ain't going to work, mate. [ __ ]
that. [ __ ] is addicting
though. I'm coming off this community
soon anyways. I told Mont
Bonty. Yeah, it's just full of weirdos,
mate. And at the end of the day, you
just get like [ __ ] you just get
addicted to the negativity as well.
That's another thing. They're just
[ __ ] weirdos on here, mate. Proper
weirdos. I ain't got a [ __ ]
life. A [ __ ] lot of them.
to my friend, we can gamble in in two
weeks, but I can't do it before then
because I can't justify
it. And if you can't justify it,
then you know, I can't justify losing
300. If I lost, I lost
£300 in two days. I can't justify it.
You see, you can't justify it. So 150
you can justify. I said in 2 weeks it's
fine. You know, try again in two 150 in
weeks. Um or even a month or so, then
you can kind of like limit it. But
nah, I literally can't do I'm not losing
no more. It's the guilt. The only thing
is that whenever I get tempted to do it,
Yeah. I just know how guilty I feel afterwards.
I just feel guilty afterwards, you know.
That's why I don't do it. No, not not
back gambling. No, no, I lost 150 um
yesterday, but I didn't go out the whole
bank holiday and I've not been out
drinking in 3 weeks, so I saved money
really. No, I'm not back gambling. No,
no, not gambling at all, mate. Not at all.
Um, that 150 I lost. I would have spent
more on a bank holiday going out. I
would have spent more if I went out
every week for three weeks. So, no, I'm
not gambling. No, they just gave me£34
and I just put it on four numbers. I'll
never go back to that [ __ ] Oh, thank
you. No thank
you. No, I'm good,
man. I am you. I'm not gambling. Well, I
gambled 150 in a whole month. Wow. Yeah. Okay, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay,
man. But yeah, it was tempting, but I
was able to fight the temptation.
Yeah. But I notic I was watching
hyperlinks yesterday and that's not a good
sign, you know, cuz on my new channel
and this channel, I don't watch any
gambling videos. Uh yeah, we need to try
to stay clear of that
again. 1,900. Jeez. Well, I lost what?
And that's exactly why I don't
gamble. I gambled yesterday. Yeah, I was
bored. I didn't go out the whole [ __ ]
That's exactly why I don't do it
anymore. Weeks and weeks and weeks. It's
the guilt that gets
me. And I'm still having to fight these
urges. But if I can even limit myself
like I have done, then that's fine. You
know, it's better. Don't think I didn't
go out drinking for 3 weeks. I've not
had a haircut for 3 weeks. I didn't go
out bank holiday. So, I was happy losing
the 150. It sounds mad. Well, not happy
losing it, but it's a step in the right
direction. You've gave up with the women
in this country. You've saved money.
You've only lost 150. You You've saved
700 pound really. So, I couldn't really
moan at that to be honest. My mom didn't
say much either. So, I won't be doing it again.
trust me. But this site has got pounds
on it. It's actual pound
coins. So it is tempting, but I'm not doing
it. We get tempted to do a lot of things
in life, bro.
But you need to keep
remembering how it made you feel when
you lost, you know, and how guilty, you
know, it's just not worth it.
So yeah, I won't be [Music]
gambling. No, no, no, no, no, no. I
could do 150 now and I'd still have
money, but then I'd think, oh [ __ ] how
can you justify
losing 300 pound? You can't. So
no, I'm not getting back into that [ __ ] again.
Yeah, cuz obviously I've gave up with
women in this country in it cuz they're
all the same and [ __ ] So
yeah, probably join the gym at some
point as well so I don't become really
fat. It' be all right.
So it's [ __ ] it is tempting,
bro. It's tempting, mate.
But you just have to be stronger in
it and get off this YouTube [ __ ] as
well. That please thing piss me off
today. I don't want no more involvement
with this [ __ ] you know. Yeah.
No, no, no, no. Should get
like 850 to more. So, it's not bad, is it? Yeah. [ __ ]
me. I don't know about you or what
happens when you gamble, but I always
think, oh, you could have just gave the
money to someone. Not 150. I'm talking
like bigger amounts and that's what will always get
me. So that's why I don't do it
anymore. It's [ __ ] [ __ ]
man. Yeah, it's bad. It is bad. You lost
1900 in two days. [ __ ]
that. Yeah, I lost 2,000
once. Never again, mate. Mark my [ __ ] Never
again. How's it feel? You could have
booked a holiday with
that. [ __ ] that, mate. [ __ ]
that. I lost that before as well. 2,000,
but I still had like 1,800 left, so
Yeah, I remember I was home alone, mate.
[ __ ] two hours it took me to lose that like
Yeah. M need to fight the
urges. I think I'm going to have to come
off social media, mate.
We'll have to fight the urges, matey. Yeah.
Who is that?
That's that weird [ __ ] from California, is it? Uh
Back when I didn't think women was all the same, eh? Who's this?
Yeah, I need to go watch this [ __ ] video, [ __ ]
Yeah, [ __ ] that, man.
She got my Insta back
soon. Yeah, I got banned for a week for
calling the women evil. What happened to
freedom of speech? [Applause]
Yeah, I need to go police station
tomorrow as well.
Yeah, [ __ ] hell. That would do me
good though to
walk. Wow, man.
Yeah, it's not let me go for some
reason trying to get me to do my
bollocksing. Ain't going to happen, mate.
I've got more willpower than that, man.
empty. One second. I want to protect
myself as much as I can. One sec.