No, I don't. Thank you.
Yeah, I'm quitting this [ __ ] [ __ ] community. 100%
mate. Same thing yesterday. I'm I'm
quitting this [ __ ] community, mate.
Same people, same repeating every day,
same self projecting every day. And you
know what I was thinking yesterday
before I went to sleep is that have you
noticed how none of these people are
young on this community? Like none of
them are in their
20s? No. any like mid20s, late 20s,
early 20s. Have you noticed that they're all
old? I've noticed that as well in this
community. They're all
old. These little self projectors. I've
noticed that they're all old men. None
of them are
young. And probably, and this is why
they do this self- projecting every day.
It's cuz um that they're too old to
change their life. So, they take it out
on the rest of the world. Um, and that's
why they self project every day. And
it's mad how none of these people in
their 20s or this
community cuz if they're in their 20s,
they'd think to themselves, "Oh, well, I
could actually change my life."
Um, you know what I'm saying? But
obviously they're in their late 30s,
40s, they're [ __ ] Probably most of
their 40s to be honest. And they realize
their lives are over. So they just come
online and self project every day
calling people what they are themselves
skin ugly lonely everything that that
applies to their own life. Um yeah they
just talk about themselves every
day. None of them are none of them are
in their 20s. None of them none of them
are. Are they? None of them are. No. Not even Virgin
Boy. None of them are in their [ __ ]
20s. cuz I think I'm the only one in my
[ __ ] that is bad, bro. [ __ ] hell.
That is bad. I actually am it. I'm the
only one in my 20s on this community. Sheesh. [ __ ]
hell. It's like that [ __ ] uh Joe, he
done a video show in New York was
1650. That heavy breathing.
Every [ __ ] breathing, bro.
Yeah, they're all overweight on here.
All old, overweight, and got a life.
Can't get off of YouTube. They're all
the same. They're the same. But on here,
man. Really, really are the
same. Probably um addicted to gambling.
All of them as
well. Yeah. Yeah. It paints a worrying
picture how none of these people in their
20s probably jealous cuz you're younger
than them as well. Probably they love to
be in their 20s
again. They're just old on YouTube every day sat
projecting. They got a
live. Oh, one second. Yeah,
basically I'm over the gambling now.
Anyways, I was on the wheel yesterday. I
was looking at it. They gave me four
pound. I was like, nah. The thing that
stopped me is as tempting as it is, just
realize all the things it's caused in
the past, the mood swings, the
um the gill and stuff. It's just not
worth it. But it is in pound and it was
tempting. But um yeah, there's no point.
There's literally no
point. It is
uh was quite tempting. Yeah. Oh [ __ ]
Yeah. Well, I'm done with this community
anyways, man. It's [ __ ] It's [ __ ]
This is [ __ ] [ __ ]
mate. I'm going start doing gym videos
on my other channel as well as the other
ones, I think. Yeah. Yeah,
literally. See, even when I was on the
phone to the police [ __ ] I was like,
bro, this is all cause cuz of this [ __ ]
YouTube, you know? I'm nothing to
[ __ ] send complaints, keep [ __ ]
reporting it. This is all because of
these people on [ __ ] YouTube. I like
it's just not [ __ ] worth it. Let them
have their [ __ ] [ __ ] community.
That's what I was thinking. Just let
them have their mongafied community. I
can I can say [ __ ] words better than
[ __ ] anyone else. Just let them
[ __ ] have it,
bro. You know what I'm saying? Let them
keep self projecting all their life, you know? just their life. Yeah.
Yeah. At least I stayed off the roulette.
Yeah. [ __ ] it was tempting though. I
was like, "Another 150 won't hurt." And
then that's 300 pound in [ __ ] two
days. I'm not [ __ ] losing 300 pound
in [ __ ] two days. [ __ ] that.
Yeah. Bad online roulette. Yeah.
[ __ ] Reddit keeps buying
me. They buying anyone who's not a s and
that and anyone that doesn't defend
women. You know what's so mad? Yeah, I'm
still despising them. Even though I've
not gone out yet for a couple of weeks,
I still have that hatred towards them.
And norm normally it would have it would
have worn off by now. But no, I think
it's with me for life, bro. I generally
generally think it's actually with me for
life. I was able to [ __ ] quit
gambling and when I went back to it, I
could control it. But this nah, [ __ ]
that. [ __ ] I never want anything to
do with him again. Ever. I mean it.
Yeah. [ __ ] proper proper mean it. Yeah.
You get to a point where you realize
they're all the same. You know, you're
fed up with it and [ __ ] them. Is it?
Yeah. I'd rather keep my dignity than
ever talk to any of them ever again. How
I That's how I generally
feel. Might sound bad,
but I want to keep my dignity. I keep my
pre to any of them stuck up [ __ ]
again. They're not all the same. You've
not met all women. No more [ __ ] women
than you, mate. Even 10 years [ __ ]
later, I've met more women than you,
mate. You know what? I used to say the
same thing [ __ ] then as well.
I used to say the [ __ ] same thing
back 10 years ago to the little virgin.
I swear to God, I used to say exactly
the same [ __ ]
thing. Say the same [ __ ] 10 years [ __ ] later.
So good [ __ ]
mate. Cut it, man.
Yeah, this community is [ __ ] it's
[ __ ] Literally is
[ __ ] There's no actual point of it.
Like, you know, most communities there's
a point to it. With this one, it's just
a bunch of self projectors
um that just talk about themselves every day.
that create negativity. I don't really
understand the actual point of it or the
actual end goal to this um
community to be
honest. I don't I don't to be honest. really don't.
No, man. I don't
think I'm just still under the
impression that if if women were truly
different, you would have been shown
different at 27. It doesn't matter what
people say. People can say whatever they
want to say. That doesn't mean anything.
You know, actions speak louder than
words. But we know if they were
different, you would have seen different
by now. And you can't believe what
people say, man. Fill them in. Are you
mad? I'm not dealing with anyone on this
[ __ ] community anymore, mate. You all
weirdos. It's [ __ ] Go fill them in.
I'm done with this [ __ ]
community and the [ __ ] people on it
100%. I was like, [ __ ] I've had to call
the [ __ ] police again. I've got them
coming around in a couple of days. I was
like, this [ __ ] is just not [ __ ]
worth it, is it? You
know, like it's it's literally not even
[ __ ] worth it, is it? I'm having to
do all of this because of these spastics
on here. You know what I'm saying? Like,
it's just it's just it's just a weird [ __ ]
self-projecting weirdo ass community.
There's there's nothing else to say about it. you
know, just full of people that just take
their misery out on other people. And
we've all seen what these people look
like when they get exposed as well. That's another
thing. You know what I'm saying?
that roulette was tempting to
play. But yeah, guilt stops me playing
it. I said to my friend, we can do it in
two weeks. I can do 150 in two weeks.
Um, I can do it every like that, not as
frequent, but I can't put another 150 in
cuz the guilt will just eat me up. So,
yeah. And I'd still be fine with money
and everything. That's what I'm saying.
And so, yeah.
But then again, I think I'd rather
gamble than go out and speak to women
again. That's how bad it
is. That's really how bad it is. But how
about just not gamble and just don't go
out? You save even more money.
I could comfortably
lose,000 pound now and I would still
have lots of money.
Yeah. Yeah. All women are the same. All
women are evil. So I'm done with them.
I'm done with gambling. That was just a
one off the other day. So yeah. Yep.
No, I'm not friends with him. I'm not
friends with anyone on this
community. It's just a weird [ __ ]
community. I wish I never got introduced
to it to be honest. So,
yeah. Uh, you can ask, but I'm not going
to be telling you because it's none of
your business. You can ask. Yeah, no
problem. But I won't be answering you
because it's none of your business.
Because my life is my life and your life
is your life. So how about you mind your
own [ __ ] business? How about that
one? You can ask. Yeah, no problem. But
I won't be answering. So mate, worry
about your own life. Don't worry about
what I do. Yeah, worry about your own
life. And this is another thing you
little self projectors do in this
community. You're too asked about what
other people have. You're too ass about
how other people get money. Worry about
your own life. Yeah. You don't see other
people on the [ __ ] street. Yeah. The
[ __ ] pedestrians on the [ __ ]
street worrying about what other people
have or how other people are getting money.
Yeah. [ __ ] me. Why don't you worry about
your own life? Trying to bet your own
life instead of worrying about other people, you
know? That would be a good start. worry
about what's going on in your household.
Yeah, that'll be a good that'll be a cracking start.
Yeah. Yeah, I I can. Yeah. Yeah, I can.
easily. But it's just an example. Yeah.
It's called saving money. I've saved
money. I couldn't walk for [ __ ] three
weeks. So obviously I saved money, didn't I? But um
yeah, I did say that I'm using it as an
example as you can't gamble responsibly.
This is why I don't do it anymore cuz I
was showing my friend roulette yesterday
cuz they gave me a 34 pound and I was
like, "Bro, I'm not putting any more
money in. I already put 150 in the other
day. I can justify that. I can't justify
£300." So that's why I said if we want
to do it, we can do it again in two
weeks. It's not a problem. So, but I'm
not doing it again, you know, because
it's it's too frequent. It don't make
sense. So, yeah. And the guilt will just
eat me up. So, that's
why. But I'm done with women as well. My
hatred towards them is still very raw,
you know, even after a few weeks of me
not even dealing with
them. So, yeah.
I guess what else would you have to
really go on? You've never been shown
any different. They're all the [ __ ]
same. They always will be. So
yeah, I'm just looking forward to just
leaving this country in 5 weeks. I think
I'm going to start the gym from tomorrow as well.
Yeah. And then I'll be my body will be
nice for Thailand. So
yeah. Yeah, that'll be out. So, Um,
yeah. No, I don't understand about you
people in this
community. Yeah. You don't know anything
about women, mate. Trust me. Who would
know more about women? Me or you? Me. Do
you know why? Because I've met more
women than you ever have. And I've and
I've been and I've met women several
times a week. Women only reply to
negativity. They don't like people with
goals. They like negativity. I'm living
proof of it. That experiment I done two
weeks ago told me everything that I need
to know. You can say what you want, but
my experiences will show different to
what you're saying. So actually there's
no point even even I think that's a good
way to put it. You can say whatever you
want, but my experiences will always
show different. So actions speak louder
than words. Anyone can say anything on
the internet. You know how many years
people have been saying that on the
internet? Oh, women like positivity,
women like men with this, women like
that, men with that. But the funny thing
is, real life doesn't match what you
hear online. It just doesn't match. It's
the difference between night and day.
Anyone can make conspiracies online, but
we all know that as soon as you write
something negative, women are there
before you can say Jack [ __ ]
Robinson. But yet they ignore to normal
night. They ignore normal nice messages.
That has been proven. You can make up
conspiracies all you want, but I know
different cuz I have dealt with them unfortunately. So
yeah, what people have said online
doesn't match real life experiences.
None of it matches. So that's what why I
said two weeks ago. It's got to be
somebody that made up these conspiracy
theories in their mommy's basement and
everyone just went along with it because
that is not what happens in real
life, you know?
So probably not be somebody that made up
a conspiracy theory and everyone just copied it. So
yeah. And then you're trying to say how
I don't seem like I've got many goals.
I've literally told you my goals. I talk
about it literally every time I go live.
Well, you might have missed some of them
cuz you're not on all the time. But
yeah, [ __ ] mate.
I'm unemployed and a problem
gambler making up stuff. How am I a
problem gambler? I don't even gamble
anymore, you idiot. And I'm not
unemployed. I have a job. Try again. You
don't know me again. Cons conspiracy
theories. What do you have to offer a
woman? It's nothing to do with what you
can offer a woman. Again, conspiracy
theories does not match with real life.
And I'm not a problem gambler. I don't
even gamble anymore. That 150 was a
oneoff. So what? I didn't go out for 3
weeks. A problem gambler. How can I have
be a problem gambler when I got more
money than you and I get more money than
you? How can I be a problem gambler?
Shut up, man. You're a s. You
know, you're It's like what they used to
say online. If you've got a job and
you've got a house and you've got money,
that will get you a woman. No. The [ __ ]
it will not. If you see what most women
are with, they're with drug dealers.
They're with bubs on benefits. Yeah. So,
stop talking [ __ ] about what it is to
offer a woman, mate. We all know it's
it's like before when people used to
say, "Oh, you live with your mommy." Oh,
mommy. I used to get so fed up with
hearing that. Finally moved out. Yeah.
And then what happens? The same problems
with women. It's a damn problem. It's
not what someone has to I'm not going to explain.
Anyways, so um it's all you used to say
before, oh, you live with your bubby.
It's just another excuse. This is what I
used to say to Ant-Man. These people
don't know nothing about women. They
don't know nothing, mate. Trust me, the
only people who get upset are problem
gamblers. Okay. Well, I'll give you an
example then, Spo. I lost 150 three days
ago. Um, was it three days ago? I think
it was two or three days ago. Yeah,
two two or three days ago. Got all my
bills paid. Had plenty of money left.
I'm not a problem gambler. No. The only
people that get upset are people that
actually use real money. Unlike
streamers. No. No. No. Not at all. No.
You don't know anything. You know,
again, lack of life experience. you
ain't got no life experience. Maybe if
you actually got off from YouTube for a
change, you'd actually get some life
experience. So, no, the only people that
get upset are people that use real
money, unlike um unlike these streamers,
like secular slots. And I'm living proof
of it. But if if he was a problem
gambler, right, I'd have no money left.
I'd have no food. I'd be starving, you
know? And that's also um something that
they don't and that that's also another
conspiracy theory. I should do a video
of these conspiracy theories. People
seem to think that you need to lose all
your money for it to affect you. They
they seem to think that you need to lose
lots of money for it to affect you.
Again, lack of life
experience. Again, what what they say on
the internet doesn't match with real
life experiences. It's a conspiracy theory.
So yeah, you've got no clue about
gambling. You got no clue about women.
Trust me, I know cuz I've met women,
plenty of women, and they're all the
[ __ ] same scumbags, which is one of
the reasons why I'm [ __ ] going to
Thailand. You know what I'm saying? So that's it. So
yeah. Oh, you're an idiot. You're
talking about yourself. Why don't you
have a job anyways? I don't have a job,
mate. Why are you not at work?
work? You don't have a job. Stop talking
about yourself. We was talking about you
kind of people about [ __ ] 10 minutes
ago, bro. You little self projectors.
Isn't it funny, right? How none of you
people in your
20s. Yeah, I was saying this a minute
ago. Isn't it mad how none of you people
in your 20ies, you're all old, you're
all washed up, you all, you're all
self-reflectctors, and you all can't get
off of YouTube. Isn't that a madness?
how none of these people are in their
20s. Have you noticed that? They're all
old. They're literally all old bums with
nothing going for themselves. Yeah, I've
noticed that. I've noticed that. Cuz
when when you when you go on when you go
on different communities, you'll get
people in their 20s, you'll get people
in their 30s. Everyone on this community
are in their late 30s and 40s and and
and probably even 50s. That's not right,
bro. That's [ __ ] weird.
You know what I'm saying? That's [ __ ]
weird. Believe it or not, I'm I don't
need you to help me, mate. I know more
about women than you would ever know,
and I know more about gambling than
you'll ever know. But I appreciate it.
Um, but I know more than you. You know,
you might be 40, you know, or whatever.
But you ain't got more life experience
than me. Not a [ __ ] chance, mate. How
do I know? Because I've had free time.
I've had money to go around exploring,
meeting women, and I know exactly what
they're all like. So, you can try and
help me, but unfortunately, I don't need
your help. Unfortunately for you.
So, yeah, you're talking about yourself
again. I'm unemployed or compulsive.
Bro, you're talking about yourself, bro.
All you're doing is talking about
yourself. You're not getting anyone
triggered. You're only talking about your own
life. You know what I'm saying? Like
you're only talking about your own life
there. Like you're self-projecting.
Again, you've even admitted your age.
You're talking about your own life.
That's why it doesn't bother anyone,
bro. Like, think of it. You 40year-old
losers, you bums have been doing this
for years. Where's it got you? Where has
it got you other than wasting more of
your life? You are all broke. You're all
[ __ ] jobless. You're all loners.
You're talking about your your own
lives. That's all you're
doing. What am I hoping? Just to go on
holiday, man. Just to get away from it
all to be honest. Good question. Just
Just to go on holiday. But yeah, you are
literally talking about your own
life. You literally are talking about
yourself. No job, no money. That's you.
You, you, you. The arrows point to you.
Bum. Bum in these 40s. Why are none of
you people in your 20s? Why are none of
you haters in your 20s? I'm the only
[ __ ] on this community in my
20s. Nah, bro. Nah, you have too many.
Okay, bro. Listen, come back when you
can show it. Yeah. Why? You're you're
you're off work. Yeah. Okay. You're off
work. What if I put the link up, right?
Yeah. Are you going to join, mate? You
ain't got no 2 million. You're a bum.
You're a benefit bum. Your life is [ __ ]
You're on YouTube. You're 40. You're on
YouTube. Get off of YouTube. If you've
got 2 million 2 million assets, get your
fat ass off of YouTube and stop typing.
Your life is so much different. Stop
typing to me then. But again, you're a
40year-old loser. This is exactly what
it's a loser community. It's full of
[ __ ] people with a [ __ ] life that
come on YouTube to feel wanted. That's
what it is. All old, all skin, all
fantasist. is exactly what I was talking
about before all of you joined. All
ain't got nothing going for yourselves.
That's why you can't get off of YouTube.
You're all fantasists. You've been doing
it for years,
man. If you had all of these things, you
would not be on here. You know, I'm
[ __ ] off. You know, after today, I'm
I am generally [ __ ] off. After this
Wednesday, I'm [ __ ] off. And if your
life and if your life was Yeah. Again,
you're talking about yourself, right?
I'm going to put the comment up
again. I live in a bedsit and sleep on a
mattress on the floor. Have a tiny
fridge. You have no money, no job, no
processing. Get a job. Yeah, you're
talking about yourself. That's exactly
why I'm putting the comment up because
you're just talking about your own
life. You are talking about your own
life. I'll pull it up again. That's you
you're talking about, you know, but you
you need to remove the you and put I.
You are talking about yourself. That is
your own life you're talking about. I'm
I'm trying to help you. You know, I've
got I've literally told you that I've
got more money than you will ever have.
You're talking about yourself. You're on
that shitty £300 a month. Look in the
mirror and realize that you're talking
about yourself. You know what I'm
saying? You are literally talking about
your own life. I'm trying to help you. I
live in a bedsit, bro. I live in a
fourbedroom house. What are you talking
about? I live in a four bedroomedroom
house. I got a £500 bed. What are you
talking about, you projector? My house
is bigger than your house and it's worth
more money than your house. What are you
talking about? You're talking about
yourself. That's what you're doing. Stop
talking about yourself for a living, you
know? [ __ ] absolute [ __ ] idiot,
bro. Like I'm I'm tempted to just go to
the bank and just beat you at the money
game again. But there's no point because
every time people show you little losers
money, you run away. You run away. It's
just self-p projecting. Like at the end
of the day, bro. Yeah. Like it's just
self-p projecting. I don't need I don't
need to [ __ ] go to the bank and show
you thousands again because every time
somebody shows you little self
projectors money you run away because
you're talking about your own life. So
that's why there's there's no point
anyone entertaining you because you're
just self projectors and you're banned.
Bye-bye. [ __ ] hell, bro. Self projectors. Bye-bye.
For [ __ ] sake. God, these [ __ ]
retards. When are they ever going to get
a life, man? You
know, when are they ever going to get a
life? Never. Never. They just they
literally like these conspiracy theory.
It's got to be themselves that that
they're getting confused
with. It's got to be. It's got to be
themselves that they're talking about.
It has to be every day coming online
talking about how skint they are and how
they've got nothing in life because
they're on here every day. They can't
come off of YouTube. So, I mean, the
evidence doesn't lie about these self
projectors. I told you all fat, all
ugly, all old, all have nothing. That's
all they are. Not one person on this
community is in their 20s or even their
early 30s now. That's how bad it is
because they're all self
projectors, you know? They're jealous of
anyone that's got a better life than
them. That's facts, bro. Why are they
all old? Why are none of them [ __ ] in
their 20s as well? The [ __ ] It's
weird. All they do is come on YouTube
every day and talk about
themselves. It's sad, isn't it? Sat
there on YouTube talking about yourself
every day. You would have thought that
like you' have got bored of it by now, bro.
But it's [ __ ] mad these cell
projectors. I swear to God madness,
bro. Absolute spastics. I can't get off
of YouTube. Do you remember? Do you
remember that time? Yeah, bro. I took
[ __ ] weeks off of YouTube, bro. Weeks
off of YouTube. These people can't take
one day off of YouTube. How bad is that?
Not even one day off of
YouTube. But they've got this, they've
got that. They they I think Yeah.
Personally, it's the same two or three
people that's been doing this for
years. Generally, I think it's the same
two or three
spastics, you know, cuz they have been
doing this since I was [ __ ]
22. Yeah. They need to really really
stop confusing theirelves with me. Like
it's embarrassing now, man. It really is
embarrassing. They're the ones I've got
no job. They're the ones I've got no
money. They're the ones sat on YouTube
ain't got a life. Ain't even got a
friend that they can call. They need to
stop projecting and get a life. You
know, mate, I own them. Listen. And you
know what's so mad? I was looking at my
stomach yesterday. I was like, "Oh, you
putting on a little bit of weight, bro.
nothing like these people, these fat
ugly people. And I was like, "Mate, we
need to start going for walks, you know,
you this is how you end up like these
people, you know, eating in, you know,
staying in, eating
in, becoming fat, and then [ __ ] you
start hating the world. That's what
these people are." I was like, "Bro, I'm
not liking the this on my [ __ ] body,
bro." You know, nothing like these
people, but I I was just got start
exercising now. Join the gym. I was
like, "Bro, that you need to come off
this site. You're going to end up like
these people, these fat, ugly people
that can't get off of YouTube. Look at
what they Look at their faces as well,
bro. Like, look at when these people get
exposed. Have you seen their face? You
know, they call people skint. How many
times are they going to be shown money
only for them to run away? They're
[ __ ] idiots. That's why there's no
point coming on here. It's [ __ ]
You know what I'm
saying? Um, I
gambled three days ago, £150, but bear
with me. Yeah, I didn't go out for 3
weeks cuz I could barely walk and I
didn't go out that over that bank
holiday. So, I didn't spend like £350.
So, the 150 I saw it as a positive even
though I lost it. I saved like 600 700
not going out in them couple of weeks.
So at the end of the day, I saved more
doing that than I would just going out
and speaking to evil women. So in a way,
the council open, they gave me 34 pound.
I was kind of tempted to put more in
yesterday, but I'm not doing it. I'm
done. I'm done with it, bro. I said to
my friend, if you're going to do it,
I'll do it again in two weeks. But if I
lose another 150, then that's £300. I
can't justify losing £300. I can kind of
justify the 150. You can't even buy a
pair of trainers with it. we saved money
anyways. So, you can sort of justify
that. So, now I have and the thing is I
get tempted. Don't don't get me wrong. I
get tempted. It is tempting. I'm not
going to lie to you. But the thing that
stops me is I I I think about like all
the stuff it's caused in the past, the
guilt that, okay, if I lose this, I'm
going to think, [ __ ] I should have just
gave the £300 to my mom. That that's
what just stops me doing it. And I've
got an account open and everything, but
I won't touch it. Not for at least two
weeks, two to three weeks, not for at
least and and probably even after that
because it's the problems that it's caused before. So,
um that's how I just I just think of the
guilt and that and try to relive it
before doing it again. Just try to
relive that guilt and [ __ ] that it's
caused. So, it seems to help.
But yeah, man. I've saved some decent
amount of money, so I thought, [ __ ] it.
I felt lucky a couple of days ago, so I
thought I'd give it a try. But I didn't win.
So, you have to want you you're going to
want to you want to have to stop, you
know. No, I miss doing them. But I can't
afford to keep doing these gambling
videos, bro. I need to I've I need to
keep this money for traveling, you know.
I've got a main channel. Yeah, I'm going
to start putting gym videos on it. I've
got traveling videos on there. Like, I
can't afford to keep doing it.
Otherwise, I won't be able to do what I
want to do. And it's just a waste of time gambling
anyways. You know, I saved three grand
in 3 weeks. Three grand I saved in 3
weeks. And obviously, I was 150 in that.
So, but I'm just trying to save as much
as I can now. So,
yeah. Yeah, they were fun. They were a blast.
But I don't really like doing them at
the same time because I didn't like
losing and then have to show me losing.
Even though you have to do that if
you're putting up gambling videos, but
you know, I didn't because it gave people
ammo, you know, even though obviously
I'm not going to only show wins, but I
felt like I should have only show wins
because then it gives these [ __ ]
ammo when I lose. But obviously I was a
gambling channel. So I had to show the
losses, you know, whereas when you don't
gamble, there's no ammo. You know what
I'm saying? If you travel, you stay in a
hotel, it hurts them. You eat good food,
it hurts them. You go on a date, you
know, it hurts them. Like at the end of
the day, bro, like anything you do will
hurt these people. You know what I'm
saying? If you lose gambling, you know,
they'll laugh at you. That's what I'm saying.
when he lost. Uh, uh, Nah, bro.
Nah, cuz I'm responsible, bro. Like, I'm
an adult. Like, I I know my limits in
it. So, no, I wasn't.
No, I had urges made like yesterday. I
had urges yesterday cuz they gave me a
34 pound and they're doing everything not to
um close my account now. But
no, cuz I feel like I'm wasting enough
of my life doing it. I'm wasting enough
money, money, enough time. I don't want
to do it anymore. It's not worth the stress.
But no, I wasn't tempted then. But I was
yesterday. Cuz what happen is you'll do
150 and be like, "Oh, 150 won't hurt."
And then that's £300. Then oh [ __ ] just
chuck another£300 that's 600 pound. And
it never ever ever ends.
So that's what it
is. Yeah. I won't be going again,
buddy. Yeah. And this site has pounds,
Jason. The reason I stopped for a long
time as well is because the site I was
using was only doing euros and I didn't
want the euro currency because it's
different than the pound and I don't
want to gamble with euros. I want
pounds. This site has pounds. So, I know
anytime I can just go for a spin if I wanted
to, but I'm not doing it. [ __ ]
that. But I gave up with [ __ ] evil
Willen. So I can [ __ ] give up with uh
so maybe in two weeks I'll try 150. Maybe
yeah, take it. You're still doing your
bollocks in there for you to
ask. Why do you think I was able to go?
ever connect me. Ah, if the [ __ ]
[ __ ] tried her
[ __ ] Cuz the money's there,
lad. I just I just I just despise women.
I just despise them. That's probably why
the police officer didn't want to help
me because she's a woman and she's
probably seen the stuff I've said. So,
I've got the police coming on Friday cuz
I'm not going to let it go. I'm not
going to let it lie. You know, they've
come on my door enough times over the
same thing. So, let's all get involved
now. That's probably what it is to be honest.
Um, it just it hasn't changed my outlook
in any way. I despise them. If they were
any different, mate, I would have met
one by now 27 that weren't like that. I
despise everything about them, you know?
I will never ever ever engage with one
ever again because I've got too much
pride and too much
dignity. So, that's me done. I will
never deal with him ever again.
So yeah, can't see it happening, mate. I'm too
stubborn now. The hatred doesn't even
fade away even the longer it's been.
Like, nah, bro. Trust me, people can say
they're all different. People can say
they're all this, but we have to go by
your experiences as a person. And it
shows that they are all the same. They
only reply to negativity, which is very
concerning how they ignore normal
messages, but they only reply to
negative ones. That's really strange.
And this is a taste of what we're
dealing with, you know, and I don't like the
taste. So that's
it. They're not even different in their
30s or 40s. They're not even different
then when when they get older.
So you will never change my outlook. The
only one the only people that can change
my outlook is them. And they've had
chances upon chances upon chances upon
chances upon chances. But nothing's
changed. So the only ones that could
have helped my outlook was them by
giving you better
experiences. But they haven't. So hence
why your outlook is the way it is. And
your outlook has got no reason to be
anything other than
this, you know.
So, it's like a a a Muslim person that's
been brought up to be a Muslim. They
don't know any different. Don't eat
pork. Don't um you know, don't eat
things that are not halal. Don't drink
alcohol because that's how they're
brought up. They don't know any
different. You know, people can say
women are all different, but I've not
seen it. You know, just like they say
there's ghosts, but I've not seen it,
you know. So all I've seen is the same
[ __ ] saying that they got
boyfriends, the same people meeting you
to waste your time. The same [ __ ]
ignorers but then replying to negativity. You
know, like I keep saying, the only
positive I got was I learned at 27 and
not 31 and 32. I can hands my heart know
that I like I learned at such a young
age and I can still do stuff now before
I'm 30. Like that's the only positive
that's come out of
it. You know what do you want me to do?
Keep trying until I'm 35. Get more and
more more negative experiences. You've
got enough numbers on your phone. You
got enough of them on your phone. If any
of these women were different, you would
have been shown different. Don't listen
to what people say. You know what I'm
saying? So yeah, I'm just done with them
anyways. I can't stand them. the w
[ __ ] rats as well. I said to that USA
Izzy as well um last uh was it this what
no was it it was last week 3:00 in the
morning I said listen I don't mind
coming to America next week Thursday
Friday you know and tell you about
yourself to your [ __ ] face and show
your dad who the [ __ ] keyboard is I
was going mad bro serious [ __ ] [ __ ]
didn't reply I said what day are you
free Thursday come on I said come on you
little [ __ ] bring your [ __ ] boyfriend
as well this is all because of them you
know what I'm saying these these things
is because of them. Do you know what I'm
saying? And other It's other people as
well. It's not just her. It's other
people. It's people recently as well.
It's not just one
person. And then you think like, what
the [ __ ] When are the negative
experiences ever going to stop? They're
never going to stop until you give up.
And that's what I done. So,
yeah. It's like that day. Yeah. When
they all replied back to me, it was
winding me up, bro. I woke up at 8:00 in
the morning. It was winding me up what
they were replying with. I said, "Mate,
if I had one of these people's
addresses, I'd be on their [ __ ]
door." And I would have done it, bro. It
was giving me mood swings all day. I
mean, yeah, okay, some of them was going
to reply. I messaged them. But it was
what they were replying back with,
trying to be smart, trying to victimize
themselves. You know what I'm saying? I
thought, "Fuck this, bro. I'm done with them.
It's not like three three out of 10
replied. [ __ ] they all replied. So
what the [ __ ] How are they not all the
same then? You know what I'm saying?
They're all the [ __ ]
same. They're all the [ __ ]
same. All of
them. So here's what it is, bro.
They can't help your mindset. I feel
like I've met more women than anybody in
the world. I'm not even joking. Cuz I've
not worked for years, had money to do
stuff. I've been traveling. I've been
[ __ ] around everywhere speaking to
women. I think I would
know out of out of anyone what these [ __ ] are
like. They're not nice people in
general. None of them. or any of them.
And your family, they they don't count
cuz they've sort of got to love you
unconditionally. And there's one sister
that I don't even speak to. My other one
I speak to every day, me all the time,
but there's one that I don't speak to.
And your family have got have basically
got to love you in a way. So
So you can't use family me as an example. like cuz
Yeah, because normally when you'd give
up for like a couple of weeks, obviously
I couldn't walk for a couple of weeks
cuz of my foot, you know, you start not
going out, you start saving money and
you think, "Oh yeah, let's try again.
Let's try again." you know, now we can
try again. We've refreshed. Now I'm
still full of hatred when it comes to
that topic. I'm still full of
hatred, you know. So, you know, that's
that just goes to show how many bad
experiences you really have had, you
know. So, why continue to get more, you
know? That's the way I see it. I've
already got my [ __ ] Saturday lined
up, playing the computer, ordering a
takeaway. I love this life, bro. It
might seem boring to you,
but I think it it seems boring to you
cuz obviously you'll get bored
eventually after like eight weeks, but I
think where you keep dealing with their
[ __ ] the break is nice. Just having a
break is is nice and that's why you
don't feel the boredom because you're
having a break from their [ __ ] You know
what I'm saying? You're having a break from their
[ __ ] and that's why you you don't see it as boring.
You know, you're not hearing about
Makebelie boyfriends. You're not dealing
with their [ __ ] It's It's nice. It's
like a weight that's been lifted off
your shoulder. That's why people be
like, "Oh, don't you get bored?" No, I
really don't. You know, and and that's
it, you know. So,
yeah. I just can't stand him, you know.
If it was the only it was if it was only
the boyfriend [ __ ] you had to deal with,
I wouldn't mind. I wouldn't be asked. If
that was the only thing you had to deal
with, I'd be like, "Okay, whatever." But
it's it's the other [ __ ] The replying
to negativity, the ghosting, the [ __ ]
going on dates to waste your time on
purpose, you know? It's that [ __ ] that [ __ ] rattles
me. The boyfriend [ __ ] I could accept,
you know, every week before I went away.
I could accept it, but not that
[ __ ] you know. Not that [ __ ] Sorry.
Yeah. It's quite
standing. Maybe in 6 months I'll change
my mind, but I doubt
it. So, yeah. because you've not dealt
with their [ __ ] for so long. It's nice.
It is just
nice. I was at my mom's for 3 days
couple I think it was about a month ago
when I had this foot injury and it was
so nice. So
nice. Didn't do anything but rest. So [ __ ] worth
it. Yeah. I mean like you could even
It's that bad. See it's like I was
saying you couldn't even pay me to go
out this week.
You couldn't even pay me to go out this
week. There's no positivity left.
There's no positivity left in this
subject. There's no room left. You know,
like even if I put 150 on roulette now
and I got it to £500, I still wouldn't
go out. I still wouldn't go
out. Cuz there used to be a part of me
that thought, "Oh, we'll try again. It's
going to be different this time." The
Michael Jackson used to say, "Oh, it'll
be different this time."
And it's like, how many times are you
going to sit on that [ __ ] barber
chair for a [ __ ] hour? How many times
are you going to keep spending money on
this until you realize, bro, just leave
this country? [ __ ] You
know, yeah, I need to speak to Monty as well, actually.
Yeah, I still wouldn't go that.
Yeah. Hey, Monty, do you know what I
find mad about this community? I was
thinking about this last night after I
um was voice noting you. You know what's
so mad about this community? Have you
noticed not one of these people are in their
20s? Have you noticed
that? That's a fake Monty, man. Have you
noticed there's not one of them?
That's There's a fake you trying to join.
Oh, is you?
You [ __ ] thinking it's a fake. What
Bonnie? Have you have Have you Have you
Have you Have you noticed that? Have you What?
That none of the people in this
community are in their 20s. They're all
old. Have you noticed that? Yeah. Yeah,
of course I've noticed that. Have you
just noticed that? I've noticed that a
long time ago, PG.
And then I I just put it down to I just
I just put it down to they're just fat
ugly people that ain't got a life. Like
that's that's what I put it down to to
be fair. Yeah. No, no, no, no, no.
No, most of these are are old people
older than me and you anyway sat in this
community doing the only one on here in
my I'm the only one on here in my 20s.
I'm the only one. You know, Kayie is
um Okay. Me and Katie. That's No, no.
The name Jayen and J and Jayen's mate.
There's a couple of people who is our
age. Yeah. But 95% of them are not in
their 20s. 95% of them. No, not not our
age. Mine, yours, Natalie's or any of
the rest like the older. It's just that
money. I just went live here before you
I was live here and before you joined
and it's just the same [ __ ] Oh, get a
job. I was like, bro, tell yourself
that. Tell yourself that. Stop telling me.
Yeah. They can't tell anyone to get a
job. They can't tell anybody get to get
a job. They sat on here on YouTube more
times than anybody. Yeah. Yeah. It's a
And even if they at work, even if they
at work, they still got to go live. Even
if they at work, it's to show up. They
got a job. And they're saying how many
times they always tell me to show money.
Then when you show money, they just run
away. Yeah. Cuz the [ __ ] disabled PJ,
the disabled people on YouTube who got
bullied in life. So they on YouTube
bullying other people on you calling
people nons. It's the same as this fried
egg in your chat room. Yeah, I was
reading some of Friday eggs come out
comments out yesterday. Yeah. And first
thing he says is that I'm not a
pedophile. Why would you say I'm not a
pedophile? You know, why would you say
that? Unless you are one. Yeah. Unless
you are one, then you I'm not one. Do
you know what I mean? Yeah.
Money, I could money I could strangle
you for getting me involved with that PlayStation community.
Why? That PlayStation community 10 same
10 times better in this community. Yeah,
but I I met [ __ ] weirdos on it and
you know the weirdos that I met, you
know. No, you met them yourself.
Yeah, but I met them through you. You
didn't meet Sean through me. You met
Sean through you didn't meet that weirdo
through me. You met him through the
[ __ ] community like Anna and all that
lot. Not through me. Yeah. What? Okay.
What about Jack the Ripper?
[ __ ] knows about him, but he's just
another weird one on you on PlayStation.
He's the one who used to jump around on
his bed boll like naked and start
shagging titt titties. You don't go You
don't go live anymore. You don't go live
anymore, is it? No, I've got a live now.
Yeah. you know. Well, it's still go live
or none, but Oh, do you remember? Hey,
money. Do you remember when I showed you
when L goes live? The same people in it.
It's all the same people in this
community from 10 to [ __ ] 15 years ago.
That's [ __ ] weird, isn't it? It is.
It is. They had got no content to make.
So, they sit and make their own content
through and calling people.
Yeah. That's the content they've got.
What did you eat yesterday?
What did they eat yesterday,
man? I [ __ ] had a proper proper We
had Gregs. Yeah, we had three things
from Gregs. Yeah, we had a three
each. Then then we had a pasta each and
a half a sausage roll
each. Yeah. Fat can't it? No. Oh, no.
No. I wasn't thinking. And then then
straight after that, yeah, for tea, we
had um a kebab. What? A we had a
panini and um sausage and chips.
What did you order it? Yeah, we had all
that. Did it all get
How much it cost? [ __ ] knows.
A lot of it. Don't
know. Not a lot. Well, previously you
had McDonald's um yesterday. I had the
um the spicy burger. Do you know the new
one, mate? I woke up and it gave me uh
Yeah. kind of a bit of a [ __ ]
Yeah, I had it last night. It's the
sauce. What's spicy? No, I don't have
the I don't have the sauce. I just had
jalapenos and cheese. I don't have the
sauce in my burgers, bro. Yeah. [ __ ]
hell. I was thinking Greavves. I've got
my Saturday lined up. Nice McDonald's.
Simpsons Hit and Run video coming out
for you. Me and me and Jamie used to
play Simpsons Hit and Run. Never played
Simpsons Hit and Run with you. Yeah.
Yeah, you did. Back on the PlayStation.
It wasn't out for PS3. Yeah.
No, it was No, it was No, no, you can
buy it on PS3 though on the Play Store.
PlayStation store. Yeah, I didn't I
didn't know that. Yeah, you can with
Grand Theft Auto as well.
Yeah, I know you came with GT.
I was playing yesterday. I was playing San Andreas.
Well, yeah. Oh, the old ones. I Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. But it's a banger, bro.
Still to this day. 21 years ago. It's
still a banger. Yeah. But don't don't
you think that it runs a little bit
funny when you when you're trying to run
on it? Yeah.
I I agree with you. I was listening to
the sad song. Yeah. And you know what
they had in the background? Spongebob
with his little sad face. Oh, his little
Quezy. You remember Spongebob, is it,
Jamie? Used to like that. Yeah, you you
kind of remind me of Spongebob a little
bit, PJ, to tell you the truth. With his
little sad face, Crezy. Oh, little
characters. Oh, man. You know who you
remind me of? You remind me of Homer Simpson.
No, it's [ __ ] Who is it now?
Um, Mr. Burns.
That's Rick Mace. Rick's Mace looks like
Mr. Burns. Rick Mace, does he?
Yeah, definitely. Yeah.
All right. I will call you Milhouse Me.
Yeah. I'll call you um Ralph. Do you
know who Ralph is? He
Yeah. the police officer.
Do you know what he said to Brie? Do you
know what Ralph said to B? He said, "My
dad's going to put you in jail.
Is the Simpsons real, Monty?"
No, not all of it. Some of it facts.
No, but is it like a real place with all
the characters? Are they all real?
No, I don't think the place is Springfield.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Babe, is Springfield a
real place? Oh, Google. You never
thought I'm sure that Springfield is a
real place. I'm sure that it is. No.
Yeah. You know, it is a real place. And
I think if you go there, you're just in
the Simpson land. I think Yeah. Yeah. I
think it is real.
No, no, that's a real place. No, there
is No, there is places in America called
Springfield. There is there is some
place. Yeah. Yeah, there will be. Yeah,
that like um in America like you got
some places called Manchester, Plymouth,
London. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, you do.
You have Birmingham as well. There's one
called Birmingham as well in um Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. You got all that as well. So, yeah. ain't it? Yes.
Yeah. Grezy, I'm going to Yeah. Nice
McDonald's with a nice game. Are you
watching Peppa Pig on Friday, Greavvesy?
I'm going to the cinema to watch Peppa Pig. What?
No, it would leave a [ __ ] bowl of water outside.
a [ __ ] I'm going to watch I'm going
to watch Peppa Pig meets the baby G
wey watch Peppa Pig money
[ __ ] off but it's too much [ __ ] Peppa
Pig in my lifetime.
What the kids in it? Yeah. Well, you
don't like it? What? Bacon?
No. Peppa Pig? Yeah, bacon. No, I don't
like bacon. I had I had I had six slices
of bacon yesterday all to myself, Grezy.
It was It was lush.
It was lush. Everybody's taking that
lush word now. Yeah, it was lush, matey.
I was having some police officers for tea.
Did you like your song, PJ?
No. You need to stop bullying me.
No, I'm not bullying you.
I'm taking a piss. I'm not bullying. I'm
I'm bullying you as a friend. That's it.
I'm doing it as a friend, not as a
[ __ ] [ __ ] Believe you as a
bullying you as a friend. Yeah, I'm
bullying you as a friend. PJ, get used
to it. Monty Monty used to be obsessed
with the inbetweeners.
Ah, you remind me of the guy out of
Inetus. The one who always says he can get laid.
No, but you used to be obsessed with it.
Is it? I remember on PlayStation you
watched who's he called? Who's he
called? the one who G. Yeah, you remind
me of Ch. You're the one who can't get laid.
Yeah, really? Well, they all can't get laid. So,
well, they all can't get laid. Neil can.
Yeah, but money I remember you watched
the movie when it first come out, is it?
It's one I watched all of them. The new
one. The one that come out in 2014. The
new one. The movie. Oh, you want about um Australia? Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You watch it as soon
as it come out in it.
A rubber dubdubdub. Is that what he says
in it in the car? Rubber dubdub. You're a hacker.
Who's the hacker?
Yeah. How am I a
hacker? You just it you hack into people's PlayStations.
How can I do that? PJ, you tell me. You do it.
I don't I key to people's PlayStations.
Oh, buddy, you're funny. What? What?
What? Have you ever acted into your PlayStation PG?
Not mine, but other people's.
Oh, do you know
that? Cuz I know these things, Monty.
Yeah, but you shouldn't have known that, PJ.
I do. No, I do. I played some roulette
um the other day, Monty.
What roulette did you play?
Huh? What roulette did you play? Live roulette. roulette. M.
The last thing I got into was John West.
And do you know what I West Porn Ped? Yeah.
Child porn. No.
[ __ ] Ped peed all Rick Naked and all that lot.
Does Does Rice still come on YouTube?
Yeah, Rice is live now.
Really? I don't talk to him. He used to
come on my live and talk to me, but he I
have his number, but he doesn't talk to
me anymore, man. He's got He thinks
she's going out with Kaye.
Yeah, I told Kaye to meet me in it, but
she was trolling me. Yeah, she's a
troll. She's She's a [ __ ] prick on YouTube.
No, I told I told her to give me a
[ __ ] isn't it?
Did you? Yeah. Is that funny?
No, not really.
Monty, you you don't know. You don't
really know what it means. Yeah. When
someone says um how like they said, "Oh,
you you've got my sloppy seconds. How
does my dick taste?" You don't
understand it, do you?
Yeah, of course. I mean, what that means
cuz every person who you slept with,
that person who sex with you with the
people who you slept with, basically. [Music]
So, basically If someone What does it
mean if someone says, "Oh, you got my
sloppy seconds. How does my how how do
my dick?" You know what it means? It
means they dick in it.
It doesn't mean they It means they've
gave a [ __ ] in it.
Yeah. What is it with you on [ __ ]
How do you know, Monty?
I'm getting I'm getting one tonight, mate.
No, you're not. Nothing.
M. If you was if you had yellow skin,
you would just be Homer Simpson if you
put put a donut put a donut in your
mouth. We're basically yellow anyway, PJ.
You're a [ __ ] idiot, man. You're an
idiot. We're [ __ ] yellow anyways.
You're not getting job tonight.
I'm getting a [ __ ] I'm deep throing
tonight. I bet you've never had your ass
licked though in it. I have.
EJ, why the [ __ ] I'm not gay. Why the
[ __ ] would I want my ass all lit? You
want to get your ass all lit if there's
a C going up
there? I like me [ __ ] being tickled.
I like being tickled. I like it being
tickled. That's nice. You're weird. [Laughter]
Oh, have you have you ever had it tickled? No.
No. Oh, that's nice. Getting bit tickled.
Really? Yeah. You should try it,
PJ. Get it tickled. No.
You miss Kay's [ __ ] is it? I'm not
talking about Kayie. I know actually. I know. [Music]
It's funny though, is it? What is
like but she used to give me [ __ ] is it?
What is it with you on [ __ ] man?
You have sex with him, man. You know,
I've not I've not actually had sex for
ages. Just [ __ ]
You know that we might as well just get
a blow up dull MPG
man. It's the same job, man.
Do you know what you [Laughter]
and Ra can meet up for a sword fight?
No, I'm all right. I'll beat him.
Money. Money. If somebody gave you Yeah.
If somebody gave you £10,000, would you
run around Manchester shopping mall
naked? I do it for free.
No, you wouldn't, mate. You'd get nicked.
How would you do it though for £10,000?
I do it for free.
Okay, go ahead then.
Oh, go and do Okay, I go and do it
then. [ __ ] off, P. Yeah.
Why wouldn't you do it? Well, what would
you do it for £250?
No, but I do it for £10,000.
You do it for £10,000. It's not even worth £10,000.
Why would you do it? Why won't I do it for £10,000?
Yeah, because you'd be all over [ __ ]
Google as a
[ __ ] script. Just wear a mask. Wear
mask. I see. Wear a
mask. What a Spongebob mask. Yeah, PG.
I think it might kick me. You know,
Monty, do you remember um Bomb?
Bomb? Yeah, I remember Bomb. He He was
another one that self projected in it.
We all self We all do it. PJ,
we all do it. We all self little pedi
sat on YouTube waiting for all the young
ones to come on. That's what they all do.
All of them are they
fart all the way. They look most They
mostly look like Timmy Eldridge. Yeah.
Yeah, it's true. All [ __ ]
It's a [ __ ] community, Monty.
Yeah, of course it is. Of course it is.
Greavves is a good [ __ ] This guy's a
pretty good [ __ ]
So you never you don't really eat in, do
you, Monty? You just eat out all the time.
What? Me and Natalie? Yeah.
No, we don't eat out all the time. No.
No. Not all the time. No.
We we inside most times. Yeah,
man. She's a
[ __ ] Natalie's a belting cooker, man.
She's amazing. I [ __ ] love Natalie's
cooking. My friend's a good cook. I get
I get my friend to cook for me. He cooks
really nice curry. That's why I don't
really eat out much anymore.
Yeah, makes nice food.
It's banging, bro. [ __ ]
a banging cook. Now I tell you that now.
I love her cooking.
See what I mean? You got me talking
about her cooking. Yeah, but what food? What food?
She can make anything nice. Anything
[ __ ] she can make nice. Yeah.
Bacon. I bet you've never had pork chops, Monty.
Pork chops. Yeah, we had them in the
oven. I think I think it pork chops with
a lot of T-bones in them.
Well, I get boneless ones, but you can
get ones with bone. Yeah.
You're talking about lamb chops, I
think. Yeah, probably lamb chops or
something. Yeah. with a lot of cheese
bones or whatever in them.
I might make some lamb chops today, you
know. May some lamb chops today, you know,
bro them for
ages. Anyway, I'm going Yeah, be back
later, bro. Yeah. Got stuff to do. So,
yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You're going for a one.
Yeah. Only over you, though. Yeah. Oh,
hey Monty. Do you remember PlayStation?
And I was like, "Ah, JB is it?" No, I
was about to say that, but [ __ ] with Sammy then.
We've got Sammy girl. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
You had You had your eye on her, did you? What?
You had your eye on her, did you? I
didn't have my eye on her. No. Did a [ __ ]
No. [ __ ] But that was funny. She wanted
to [ __ ] masturbate with you on camera
and all that.
I told I'll talk to you later.
Yeah. All right. I seen a bit.