Yeah. [Music] on it.
I'll be off this community soon, mate.
After today. Definitely. [ __ ]
up. Definitely, mate. I went for a walk
today. That's what some of you people
should do. Go for a walk instead of
being on YouTube all
day. Work it out.
Good luck gambling again. it.
Yeah. Still won't close my
account. They're trying to get me to do
my bollocks in maybe going to happen [Music] now. Addiction. Yeah. Heat.
Yeah. So after today I won't be on
YouTube. Screen is
[ __ ] It's [ __ ] [ __ ] mate. Yeah.
Yeah, it's so hard not giving into the temptation of
gambling. I got to do it though. Yeah. Please don't.
fighting the urges
delay. Even close your account down when
you asked to get your [ __ ] account closed down.
How good is it? [ __ ]
hell. The nes are no
good. Not going to do it though.
Done with that [ __ ]
mate. At least until the football start again.
You have new
notifications. That man run bad again.
Hey, money. I'm not going to be on
YouTube after today,
bro. I won't be on here after
today. It's [ __ ] pointless, this
community, ain't it, bro? It's [ __ ] lady [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, I would be on offer today. Yeah. You know,
money likes this community in
it. Money likes this
community, man. This community is full of
pedos. Nobody likes this community in
it. No, it's [ __ ] weird as
[ __ ] No, this community is weird. Oh,
mate. My friend's cooking for me today,
Monty. And my friend is a better cook than that.
You know, let me tell you something,
Monty, right? You know, when you say
Natalie can cook.
Yeah. I used to think my sister could
cook and my mom can cook. But trust me,
bro, when you
have a Jamaican person cook Jamaican
food for you, or an Indian person cook
Indian food for you or whatever,
homemade, you won't even know what's hit
you, mate. Trust me, it's so nice. You
won't even have takeaways again.
Like all of this Natalie can cook. Nah,
I just think my sister could cook
because she she cooks nice food. But
when you compare it to actual
people from the nationalities, bro, it hits
differently. It tastes so nice
that you um you wouldn't you wouldn't
want to eat out again, bro. I'm telling you, bro.
You know, cuz my sister used to make
beef curries. Not so much my mom, but my
sister used to make me curries. And then
I had my friend make me a curry and it's just next
level. Like, trust me, bro. It's next
level. And then when you try to eat a
takeaway again, it tastes like [ __ ] So,
trust me, bro. I know. I know the stuff,
White women can't cook. Trust
me. Yeah, I'm getting gambling urges,
Matty Bobo, but I'm not going to do
it. Getting these urges. I'm trying to
fight. Trying to fight these [ __ ]
urges. It's [ __ ] hard.
But I just keep remembering the guilt
and stuff and just makes me feel better again. Mhm.
Yeah. Should go away soon. The urges
anyways. [ __ ] happen isn't it?
Yep. Not falling for
it. [ __ ] gun and [ __ ] urges, man. What the
Uh, yep. That's
him. Monty is is kind of
weird. I'll be off YouTube after today
anyways, so no one will be following me anywhere. Yeah. Leave that. Yeah.
gambling and man says every penny he
gets now he just gambles. [ __ ] that.
that. Yeah, I think I need to stop
talking to him for a little bit, man,
cuz it's making me want to do it. I
swear down. It's making me want to [ __ ] do
it. [ __ ] that,
bro. You actually feel the you can
actually feel your heart going. That's
how bad the urges are. You actually get
like sore heart palpitations. [ __ ]
hell, bro. I should have gambled the
other day, man. Now I'm getting these urges
again. [ __ ] off. [ __ ] annoying. [Music]
Why is gambling so
addictive? So [ __ ] addictive, is
it? No, I know I can play roulette with
actual pounds. It's too addicting, bro.
addictive. But I like to think I'm stronger than
Antman. Trying to be anyways. [Music]
It is bad though, bro. It is [ __ ] bad. Maybe
Anyone else get these [ __ ] gambling, bud? What the heat? Madness,
man. What a white bathroom.
This I'm probably going to go to sleep
to be honest, bro.
Look at these gambling urges. Like [ __ ] off.
Annoying. I might have to go out this
week, bro. If the urges don't stop, I'm
probably going to have to go out
drinking to be
fair. the only
way I maybe try and muscle through this
week and then definitely next week go
out. The urges are [ __ ] bad, bro. I
just want to go and have a
spin. Damn it.
So, I'll be back later in a couple of
hours. I'm probably going to try to go sleep.