Hello
matey. Oh, I fell
asleep. Told you I was going to fall
I was getting severe
urges, but I went to my testicles. Yeah,
man. That's the best thing. I was
watching some Seven Neighbors
before falling to sleep. [ __ ]
me. That guy's got a big gambling problem. He does. Yep.
Oh, she's been
Yeah, man. Why is my fingers so itchy? Yeah. [Music]
I fell asleep, man. I was getting some
damning urges, so I just went to sleep.
They're kind of gone now. Well, I was
watching Seven Neighbors and I went to sleep.
Nah, no, I just woke
up. Going to have some food soon. Some nice
curry. Big cook for me.
My feeling is so
itchy. It's it's it's
yeah after today I won't be on anyways.
Like I said earlier, I won't be
on. This community is
[ __ ] Had to block [ __ ] how many accounts earlier? Jesus.
Um, nothing, bro. Just getting some
gambling urges. So, I went to sleep and I woke
up. Yeah, I was getting tempted to
gamble. Yeah, it's full of disabled
people. Did you see that [ __ ] Tony
account earlier, man? Saying you're
skinn, you ain't got this. You ain't got
that. I was like, bro, you're just
talking about yourself. I'll put the com
I'll put the comment up. I'll put the
comment up for everyone to see. Bro,
you're just talking about yourself,
homie. You're not talking about
me. For the disabled self projectors in their 40s.
Yeah. Low lives, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. I was tempted to play
roulette against Steven Howard,
but I used to push past push past the urge.
Yeah. Gablin is addicted,
bro. Gablin is so addictive, bro. even
though I didn't play
again. But like I said, the thing that
stops me is the guilt. And we all know
what happens after. Oh, you lost this
money. Oh, you could have gave this
money someone. Oh, so that's why I don't do it, bro. you
know, but um I'd love to go on roulette
right now and do 50
spins, which I'd love
to see, if it was two weeks. If it was
two weeks after, then I would do it.
Then I could, oh, it's been two weeks. I
still haven't gone out, but I lost 150
the other day. I can't lose another 150,
bro. Going backwards
again. I was thinking of putting 250 on
and just doing some 50 pound spins,
bro. But nah, I can't justify it. That's
[ __ ] £400 I've lost, though. I'm not doing
it. It's not worth it,
mate. Ad man's been losing all of his
money. He has to have his mom look after his money.
He's worse than me. Definitely is worse
me because when he does it, he does it,
right? Like he lost everything. He lost
[ __ ] six um he lost [ __ ]
2.8K. I've never even lost that much.
And with with him, it's not like he was
getting it back the next
month. You know, I know I can lose three
grand and I wouldn't even lose three
grand then. Maybe the next month I could
save again. He can't do that. I said,
"Bro, you need to stop, man.
And that's the trap. Like he got he had
like three grand which is obviously a
lot and it's even a lot for him because
obviously he doesn't get the same as me
and and and he has to do other things to
get money and he lost it. I said to him,
"You need to stop, bro." Cuz as soon as
as bad as I used to be, I never left
myself with no
money. Only time recently I got close to
leaving myself with no money was last Christmas.
But I still hadn't money and I was still
getting money the next day. But it
doesn't matter. It's It's not good,
bro. Gambling's not good.
Yeah. Yeah. I was watching Seven
Neighbors. It's not a good sign when
you're watching gambling videos,
matey. That guy is a [ __ ] He is
proper addicted at Seven Neighbors. It
doesn't matter whether you can afford it
or not. Do you think I can't afford to
go and put money on right now? Of course
I can, bro. It's not the point really
whether you can afford it or not. Just a
waste of life. I was watching this seven
neighbors, bro. He was doing 1,700
spins. I thought, "What the [ __ ] bro? In a
casino, if you've got all that money,
yeah, why don't you just travel the
world and [ __ ]
I was going to say get some women, but
women are evil.
Um, travel the world, buy a nice car. Oh, something K9.
Yeah, I need to think about Thailand. I
need to think about other things as
well. So, I can't do it. I can do it and
still fall it,
but like I said, if it was two weeks time, I
can if I stayed in
maybe. I'd love a big winner. I'd love a
big hit on Roulette, you
know. It's been [ __ ]
ages. Never heard of him. A9
slots. I'll go to the casino with USA
Izzy and throw her on the
table. Throwing a [ __ ] on number
11. How about that one? Steven
Howard. I'll be throwing her [ __ ]
somewhere else. I [ __ ] tell you that, mate.
I can find the bits on number 11.
Yeah, I'll look into it. But I don't
want to start watching gambling channels again,
bro. And you need to get your mind
completely away from
it. And the urges were so bad early. I
was getting like I was going to get like
[ __ ] I was getting heart palpitations,
bro. You know, heart palp fuckingations.
That's how bad the urges
were. Yeah. Happens, isn't
it? I think you get to a certain age
where you know it's no
good. You know it's not. You just every
time you think about doing it, you just
have to relive all the problems that has
caused you in the
past, right? Because you know how you
it's very easy to forget how it made you
feel before. Whatever that way may be.
You need to try to relive it. As soon as
you think about doing again, you need to
really relive the guilt or the anger,
whatever it is. And in order to stop it,
so you know, oh, you shouldn't do it. You
know, that's what I've been doing.
Yeah. What sort of noise
mate? Have you watched the new Stitch? Steven
Howard. See, alcohol is easy to give
up. We're not [ __ ] gambling, mate. No
gambling. The worst thing as
well. I don't go out anymore approach
cuz we all know they pretend they got boyfriends.
So, [ __ ] and Lilo. It's a
cartoon stick to Lilo. It's a Disney
thing. Remember Frankie? Steven
Howard. Do you remember Frankie? Oh my god.
Yes. So, I've saved 3K in three weeks.
How good is that, Steven Howard? By not
going out, I saved
3K. [ __ ] awesome, isn't
it? It's good, bro.
it. That's good. That
is okay. Thand eh
USA. How could it be USA?
Yeah, from now.
Yeah. I haven't even got my haircut or nothing,
bro. Need too
soon. I can't be bothered trying in this
country no more,
bro. With these [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah.
Six. Why didn't USA Easy accept my
offer, Steven Howard? About me coming
next week, which is this
week. Cuz she's a [ __ ]
[ __ ] Cuz she's a scared [ __ ] Ain't
it, Stephen Howard?
I was going to go and stay with this
[ __ ] woman in New York. I know
someone that lives there. So, I would
have just went there. Could have stayed
in the hotel as I wanted to, but I would
have just stayed with the [ __ ] with that
[ __ ] I got links over there,
bro. But you're not about nothing. You
know, you know what I'm saying, bro?
You're not about nothing. You're a keyboard
warrior. You're a keyboard warrior, matey.
Yeah. Not for long, bro. Cuz if I ever
find out who he
is. Oh man, that is
itchy. Um, he won't be with her much longer.
What PJ do you prefer better, Stephen
Hour? The one with the tattoos or the
one without the tattoos? [ __ ]
itchy. Which one do you prefer?
[ __ ] That's itchy, bro. Ow. Oh,
man. How can it be me when I ain't got
tattoos? Oh man. Man,
mate, it's funny,
bro. Should we play some roulette now? Steven
Howard, should we play some roulette?
Nah, nah. [ __ ] that, bro. Thinking of
putting two 200 pound on roulette. Steven
Howard, what do you think, Steven? 200
pound on roulette.
What do you think?
£50. You're not going to get forward
with £50, mate. So
now cuz you're going to be doing like h
[ __ ] what spins. So you can't even do
that. We'll just leave it. Stupid
idea. Stupid idea,
brother. Nah, you want No.
What about 200 pound Grezy? I'm sorry.
200 pound on roulette Steven
Howard. Now I'm going to have to go out
this week, bro. I think I'm going to
have to go out this week to stop the
urges. I'm going to have to go out
drinking this week, bro.
I think that's the only thing that's
going to stop the urges. Yeah.
You can still get when you're drunk.
Yeah, I'm not doing it, bro.
Yeah, I got a nose. I got spot my
nose. Yeah, spot my [ __ ] nose.
Do you think there's a chance I will win
if I put my body on Steven Howard?
Nah. No chance.
Don't pay K9 slots.
And I have
fruits. I think I do know about
him. Yeah, someone I met in the bookies
told me about him. Yeah, I'm on it now.
If I put 200 pound in Steven Howard,
what's the chances that I will
win? What's the chances I will win?
30%. It's not worth the risk, is
it? Nah, there's no point.
What about in two weeks? Should I try in
weeks? They don't like [ __ ] Antman. Yeah.
I'll be on all day, buddy.
Funny. That's more things to show the
police on Friday. Thank
you. Yep. That's more things to show the
police. Oh, I got a police comment on
Friday by the way, Steven Howard,
because I said, "If you don't do anything about
uh this, I'm going to make a complaint
in." And they soon started calling me.
They said, "Oh, well, we can arrange
police to come to your house." And that I said,
"Yeah, thank you. That's more evidence
for me for Friday.
off me, mate. This [ __ ] is going to get
nicked. I'm telling you, mate. I'm going
to get this little virgin [ __ ] Nick. Watch,
bro. Um, yeah. The [ __ ] know what was
annoying me. Stephen out. That's another
reason I'm coming off this community
because of the whole like police [ __ ]
and that. And she called me up trying to
say how, oh, she got investigated cuz it
was prior to this, prior to that, prior
to this, prior to that. I even made a
video to the police officer. She was
pissing me off. Father, what sh what
[ __ ] are you talking? Yeah, you've been
on my door [ __ ] million times over
[ __ ] YouTube. No, no, no, no, no, no,
no. Then I had to make another report, a
whole different report. And I said, if
you don't do anything, I'm going to I'm
going to make a complaint. I'm going to
write a big nasty complaint and then and
I'm going to
complain. That's what I
said. All right. Well, just get yourself
involved. You're involved now. Simple. Yeah.
about how you're not going to
investigate it. So now I've got police
coming on [ __ ]
Friday. That's not a problem, bro. You
know, they want to see everything. They
want to see everything. And I've got
everything from top to bottom with this little
virgin. So um
yeah, it's all good, bro. Someone will
be getting nicked. Trust me. Believe that, bro.
Even if I have to do it every week.
Every [ __ ] week.
Yeah. She was I was like, "Hold on. That
doesn't make no sense, mate." Cuz a
crime is still a crime. Doesn't matter
if I was arrested before arrested or I
wasn't. A crime is still a [ __ ]
crime. So don't try to sit on my phone
and justify why you can't investigate
these people when you're fast enough to
come on my
door. You know what I'm saying? So yeah,
she just couldn't be bothered. So I had
to report it
again. But but you know, it is racism.
It's definitely definitely racism. I was
saying this to my friend yesterday and I
said it to my mom that it's got to be
some form of racism because as soon as
somebody reports you on YouTube, they're
on your door like 10 times. It's been
several different people. But then when
you report these people, nothing ever
happens. cuz it's got to be some form of
racism. It's definitely definitely
racism. Obviously, my name doesn't sound
English and I don't look fully white.
So, it is it is racism because if you
look at most of the people that they go
after and most of the people that they
let go, it is something ain't right
there. Like, something is not right
there. how I've had to make about five,
six reports in order for something to
happen when I've literally got clear as
day evidence of what this little [ __ ]
[ __ ] virgin has been doing. You know what I'm
saying? This little [ __ ]
virgin. So, like it's it makes you
wonder, bro. There's something not right
there. There's seriously something not
right there, bro. For real. For real.
So, but they'll they'll come on Friday.
I'll show them everything.
Yeah, it's it's not a problem, bro. But
there is something not right
there. And I just basically said if you
ever come on my door again, I'm not
going to let you in. So that's it. If
you don't want to deal with me, my
stuff, I'm not going to deal with your
[ __ ] [ __ ] off. That's that's it.
Simple. Well, not that they ever would
come on my door, but whatever they would
ever come on my door for, I'm not I'm
not I'm not entertaining them anymore.
So, they're going to have to break
in. You can't play two sides of a coin.
They tried to justify it every single
time why they can't investigate
something. Yet, they're fast enough to
come on your door. Like, bro, it's
racism. It's obvious. There's nothing
else it can actually
be. And it goes to show that these
people on YouTube have got no life
because they've had to do this maybe on
a smaller scale as well. when they're
calling the police, the police don't
just act. They have to keep following it
up and following up and following it up
and following it up. I know cuz I' I'm
having to do it. You
know, I'm having to do it. I would
not. And they were like, "Oh, um, yeah,
uh, yeah, but you're the one that got
nicked." I said, "Yes, I'm the one that
got nicked because in this country, you
people like to protect [ __ ]
pedophiles." Yeah. And what people like
to do is report me and delete all of the
[ __ ] that they've done. Yeah, I know.
Yeah, that's what happened, you
know. And I literally got advised by the
courts. I literally got advised by the
solicitor and the courts to report this.
I literally got
[ __ ] got advised to report
it. Like I literally got advised to
report it, bro.
That's what they That's what they
advised me to do. Doesn't From then up
until now, you
know? [ __ ] Yeah, they're idiots. They
definitely They just got their
favorites. That's just what it is, bro.
There's no overanalyzing it with these [ __ ]
pigs. They've They've got their favorites,
bro. There's There's no two ways about that.
I was watching that thing again the
other day where this guy protected his
house from these burglars and he's the
one that went
prison. What the
[ __ ] And the people that tried burgling
this house got suspended sentences.
They've got their favorites, man. And
they had a c they had a criminal history as
well. They actually had a criminal history, too. That's mad, you
know. So, and that's one of the reasons
I don't want to come on here anymore as
well, cuz all of the police [ __ ] and
it's all caused because of this YouTube
[ __ ] and they're repeating and self
injecting anyway as well. It's not just
the police [ __ ] But I'm having this
conversation and having to keep
following this these reports up with the
police because of this
website. So, it's all connected to YouTube.
Yeah. No, they're [ __ ] idiots. That's
what's wrong with them. They're [ __ ] idiots,
bro. I can't believe they gave me a
court date of 3 years and a [ __ ] half.
Three years and a [ __ ] half. No, it's
three years and three
quarters actually cuz December is the
12th month. [ __ ] hell. That is a
madness. That is crazy,
bro. 3 years and three
quarters. What the
[ __ ] How mad is that, Stephen Howard?
Three years and three quarters. The
madness. I'll be
31. 30. 32. I'll be
32. Still would have had a conviction. It's a
madness. It can't be asked by
it. No, the solicitor didn't advise, but
obviously he didn't know um he didn't
know the history. I said, "Yeah, they've
been harassing me. I've got everything."
And I said like I'd rather just take it
to court to trial even if the sentencing
is is higher. I'd rather do that because
you know obviously you've got a good
case. They've been harassing you. You've
got all of what they've done. Trust me,
it is going to be very relevant. If it
if it even went to court, which it
probably ain't even going to go to
trial, but say it did. These things
would matter. You know, they just they
just can't be asked with
it, you know. I'm like, why am I going
to sit there and pay a fine or get a
suspended sentence and a criminal record
when these people have literally been
harassing me? I was like, nah,
mate. Nah. I just said, "No [ __ ]
way." I said, "We'll take it to trial."
Um, and there's only one thing they said
you can't do, and I wouldn't be doing
that anyways. So, it just made more
sense to to to do that. Yeah.
It just made more sense to do that to be
fair. But yeah, three years and three quarters. [ __ ]
me. That is
crazy. I'll be I don't know if I'll be
if I'll [ __ ] be alive then.
Yeah, I've got all of that [ __ ] bro.
I'm going to be showing the police on Friday.
Yeah, they're [ __ ] they're the weirdos,
bro. If I go out on
Saturday. Yeah, I'm No one said it's
unrelated. I'm I'm saying I have got
evidence. I have got evidence, mate. Enough evidence.
So, no one's talking about other
people. So, and the police will know
that on Friday. So, yeah, the solicitor
and the courts basically said, um, yeah,
you need to keep reporting it and
reporting it and reporting it. That's
basically what they what they advised me
and I would have done that anyways even
if they didn't advise
it. You know, it's not it's not one rule
for one, one rule for another as as much
as the police want it to be that. But
nah, [ __ ] [ __ ] the other people. I've got enough
[ __ ] Yes, it is going to mean
something. Yes, it is going to mean
something. When they call a seen that
I've been called 23 times when I've been
ridiculed with people time and time and
time again, trust me, it's it's going to
make people lose character. So yes, it
literally is going to mean something
when there's a history as long as a
[ __ ] criminal's arm. It is going to
mean a lot. So yeah, it is going to mean
a lot cuz it's like what I said to the
the police woman yesterday. No one's got
this evidence of me, boy. What I'm
showing you now, no one no one no one
literally you keep telling yourself
that. Not found. You keep telling
yourself that. Anyways, they are going
to care because they've literally told
me to report it. So, yes, a judge is
really, really going to
care. So, yes, they are going to care,
mate. Trust me. Yeah. And I was saying
to the police officer that um no one's
got this evidence of me. Not one person
can show you this evidence of me. I can
show you evidence of these people
though. But mate, trust me, a judge is
going to care. when it's been reported a
million times and they finally get
nicked, trust me, they are going to
care. They are going to
care. So, trust me, that's the whole
point of a trial. Yeah. So,
yeah. Anyways, end the conversation.
This is in 3 years and three quarters.
It's not even happening. Anyways, I
don't even know why we're talking about
this court thing. It's not even
happening. 3 years and three quarters.
Yeah, right, mate. It's probably going
to get dropped in the first [ __ ]
year. Anyways, let's stop talking about
this. This is not even happening
anyways. But the police thing is
happening every week. I'm telling you
that now. They're coming on Friday. So, ow, my
finger. So, yeah, just talk about this. Anyways,
yeah. Yeah, I've wasted enough time on
this community, Stephen, how it go. So,
I've got to make um the last three years
best. Anyways, I'm not talking about
this no more. So, yeah, it's good, bro. Is
it? Yeah, I'm not talking about this no more.
Anyways, Thailand in five weeks. Soon to be four weeks. Yeah.
Oh, I'm I Oh, bro. I tell you what.
Yeah, I've got another go, man. This
Samsung Galaxy Fold 7 should be coming
out by July. I'm getting it as soon as
it comes out. I'm not buying it. I'll
just get it on a contract and pay it off in a
year. Cuz I'm not paying two grand for a
phone. But yeah, I'm waiting for this to be
released. Yep. I'm waiting for this
phone to be
released. I can't
wait. Do you know what? Yeah, I'm not
even The only thing, yeah, that I'm
materialistic about is the phones. I
don't care about designer clothes no
more. I've already got it. Trainers, I
don't necessarily care about that, but I
like the fold phones, bro. And as soon
as a new one comes out, I'm getting
it. I'm literally getting it. I've got a plan, bro.
Trust. I love these old
homes. Should be out by July.
I can't pay 2K for a phone, matey.
That's ridiculous, matey. You know, just
can't justify it. So, we get a contract.
We can pay it out. We can pay it. We can
just get a contract for a
year and I think it'll be like £200 a
month maybe. So,
yeah, that's almost money a month.
Steven Howard, he gets £300 a month, don't he?
Yeah, I think so. Yeah.
Yeah. Three [ __ ] three years and
three. They'll be looking at you like
what? But it doesn't matter like whether
it's going to court or not. like you
need to keep reporting um these people
regardless like whether it helps it,
whether it don't, whether they're just
going to drop it, like you you need to
keep doing it now, you know? You know,
that's it. That doesn't matter
really. Nah, it's not going to get
called. Yeah, it's three three years and
quarters, you know. But I would just be
like, "Okay, so it's okay for this
little [ __ ] virgin to harass me,
right? Year in year out, year in year
out, but I'm not allowed to defend
myself." I was like, "What?" That's
that's what I'll say.
Yeah, that's that's that that's what
would end up happening. adjourned,
adjourned, adjourned, adjourned,
adjourned. Because my whole thing was,
it's not that I didn't say it
grievously. I said, "Yes, I have said it
because they've been harassing me. Yes,
they will not leave me
alone and I've said this stuff. So, they leave me
alone." You know what I'm saying? So,
and obviously you're not guilty then. If
you've just wrote it to wrote it, you're
not guilty. Simple. Just like what the
solicitor said. So what the [ __ ] are you
going to plead
guilty? You know, hell no, bro. You
mad. That's some madness, bro. That
doesn't even make any sense. Yeah. Even
if you got found guilty, you're not
going to get found guilty for almost 4 years.
So it does it would make absolutely no
sense to plead guilty. It literally
would make no sense when it's probably
going to get dropped anyways, you
know, and then you just go another four
years without a criminal record. It's better really.
So, me mad,
bro. You can come to the courtroom,
Grezy, with Mr. Mcoo and his little
mates. Oh, Grezy, I need to send I need
to send you something. One sec, bro. I
need to put it on the channel. One second.
Grezy, I wish I could stop despising
women, Grezy, but I can't. I despise him.
I despise women with a
passion. I'm sorry to
say. Like I said, I still got I got my I
got my Saturday lined up, bro. I could
probably play The Simpsons hit and run.
I've got a
projector. There you go. Here you go,
Grezy. Hold on one sec.
Wait, what is it under? How do I send this? One
sec. Oh, here it is.
Look at that
greasy. Look at that [Music]
Look. Well, Ralph got kicked the shell off. Ralph.
Do you think my foot injury was funny,
Steven Howard? It wasn't funny. It was quite
painful. It was quite painful.
Greavvesy. Steven Howard, I was waking
up 4:00 in the morning. My foot was
pounding. It was a It was a nasty, nasty injury.
characters. Ah, you gave it a thumbs up, didn't you, Grezy?
Remember, Grezy, women was put on this
earth to satisfy Peterbelly's
needs. That's funny, isn't
it? Yeah, he's always up to mischief.
Bart Simpson, leave your mother alone.
It wasn't your mother that used to do
that stuff. It used to be your father
that used to strangle you. Strangle you
till your little eyeballs fell out.
It wasn't your mother,
Marge. We're such kids, aren't we,
Grezy? Leave your mother
alone. But Simpson, he loves you deeply. Yeah. [Laughter]
Yeah. Greasy, do you ever wake up
sometimes and just want a [ __ ] Be honest.
Wake up in this fight to your [ __ ] No. Really?
What? So you don't want to [ __ ] a woman or anything
grievy or up to miss you. It's funny is it?
Yeah. Yeah. You sound like you're
asexual like me, Grezy.
Are are you um are you at the point now
where you're maybe looking for a relationship,
Greavves? Are you a that point yet? Or
no, I don't want to be with somebody
that can only reply back to negativity. Greavesy.
No, I can't be bothered either, mate. I
can't even be bothered out
anymore. I was gaining a little bit of
weight, Grezy. Do you know
why? Um because of all the ice cream.
All the ice cream and curries, Grezy.
So, I have to walk now and just cut back a little
bit. Anyone can get like that if they
It's that ice cream, bro. I was getting
addicted to that cookie dough, Grezy.
I was getting bloody addicted to that
[ __ ] cookie dough. It's [ __ ]
addictive, bro. I've got chocolate
ghetto for dessert today.
Greasy. Chocolate ghetto. Ghetto. You
know, chocolate ghetto.
Yeah. My life is so good here, bro. Get food
cooked. [ __ ] It's just good life, bro.
Good to play
Simpson. Get free
money. No, I'm not fat. I ain't got fat
belly, but I was kind of gaining weight
because of the [ __ ] ice cream and
[ __ ] Obviously, if you eat and
obviously I couldn't walk for like a
month because of the foot injury,
so you know.
Yeah. There's my You know what I call my
friend? And I call my friend Homer
Simpson cuz he's got a fat belly.
Greasy. I said, "When's the baby [Laughter]
due?" Grezy, when's the
baby? Me, Grezy, and USA. Easy all
holding hands at the
cinear. Oh, why do that? That's
cute. Isn't that cute? Imagine King in
the Cine. Greasy. Greavvesy likes
King. Probably remind you of Stitch of it, in
it. That foot injury, Greavvesy, was
bloody stinking. I couldn't even walk.
My whole foot went stiff. I couldn't even walk,
mate. That was quite a vicious injury.
Do you know what that means, grievy?
Quite vicious. I'd be waking up at 4 in
the morning and
bloody it'd be pounding. My feet would
be pounding, bro. What the [ __ ] bro? I
think I banged it or something. I
couldn't [ __ ] walk. Had to get my
friend to cook for me at at one point
and make me tease Grezy. I couldn't even [ __ ] walk.
That was a stinking injury,
man. I don't have King no more, bro.
It's not my mom's. Go to my
mom's and I don't talk to my sister that
has him now. So, I have two sisters.
There's one I talk to and I meet all the
time, but there's one I don't. So, you
always get that in households, though.
one you call to one you
don't. Yeah, there's one f there's only
one sister I speak to my mom every day
that I just don't speak to one of my
sisters. So, but the other one I
do I say though we should go to get some food um
tomorrow. I'm 59, 510,
Grezy. But seriously, Grezy, if you
think you're putting on weight, bro, you
don't end up like these people on here,
you know? Go go go for a walk, go to the
gym. You don't want to end up like these
people. As soon as I saw me gaining a
bit of weight, I was cutting back, bro,
on the ice cream and [ __ ] cuz you don't
want to end up like these people, bro.
These little self
projectors. Like, honestly, you don't
want to end up like these little self projectors.
That's what how these people start off.
Greasy, you know how me and you are.
That's how these people start off. These little self
projectors. These little self
projectors. Greasy. They're all
overweight. They're all old. All have no
money. So they sit on YouTube and
project. Is that right, Steven Howard?
Yeah, I do need to go to the gym
though. Definitely. I might start
tomorrow while I go to Thailand in 5 weeks. So, yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. You don't want to end up
like these people. I've got a fast
metabolism, but obviously I can still
gain weight if I'm eating [ __ ] ice
cream and [ __ ] I think anyone
can. It's that cookie dough greasy. That
Ben & Jerry's cookie dough, bro. Yeah, I
fluctuate, but I don't get
fat. Like, but obviously I was eat I
didn't walk for a month, bro. Like, so,
you know, it's you're eating ice cream.
It's going to happen to most people
whether you got a fast metabolism or
not. But I got a fast metabolism, but I
still gain somewhat weight, you
know? That makes
sense. What size trainers are you,
Grezy? I'm 10.
You're 36 waist. You're a fat [ __ ]
You're 32 waist. That is fat, bro. I'm [ __ ]
32. Yeah, that is fat, bro. What the
[ __ ] You're 36
waist. That is fat, bro. Cuz I'm I'm 32.
Like, that is that is quite big, bro.
Cuz the fattest of the fattest people
are like [ __ ] 42, bro. So you're
um Yeah, that is that's bad, bro. Like
your leg don't mean nothing. That could
just be how tall you are. But yeah,
that's you need to do some walking,
buddy. B is
fat. I'm 32 and even I'm not [ __ ]
skinny. I'm size What size trainers are
you? Uh, Steven Howard, nine is the most
common. Nine is the most common. I think
I'm, to be fair, I think I'm 9 and a
half to be
honest. I think
now I don't know. I think I'm 9 and a half,
10, but I know I'm definitely not nine.
I don't think I'm nine.
Um, my vapors or tens.
Yeah. No, I won't,
mate. I don't know. I've not I've never weighed
myself. Yeah, that is big though. 36,
bro. What the
[ __ ] And I'm a small in t-shirts. In
t-shirts, I'm a
small, why do they keep following me
about, Monty? I used to think your shoe
size was connected to your weight, but
it's not. It's not connected to your
weight. I used to think like, but I
don't know what trainer size is. It's
just the way your feet are.
Mine's I've always been 10, bro.
Yeah, I'm having cake today, Monty. Chocolate
cake, money, I can make you
laugh. I just sent you something on
Facebook. Oh, I had KFC today, Grezy. I
had a burger and two pieces of
chicken. Yeah, a burger and two pieces
of chicken. It was
lush. It was bloody
lush. No, chips is the
worst. No, chips and onion
rings. No, bro. Chips and onion rings
are the worst.
Go on Facebook, Monty,
ma'am. You had a nice burger. Nice fillet
burger. Okay, let's see.
Anyways, I'll be back later. That