Look at that. It misses everything.
[ __ ] Everything. Wait, how how many
numbers did I have
covered? How many numbers did I have
covered? All right, let me go back on
that. And it misses everything like a
[ __ ] It does it every time. It
It used to do it when I used to [ __ ]
play it. It literally looks and seeks
out that loser. I'm telling you, bro.
100% it does, bro. Look. Yeah. What's
that? How many numbers do we have
covered? 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13
14 15 16 17 numbers. That's almost half
the board cupboard. And it went on zero
section three times in a [ __ ] row.
It's [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah, it's
[ __ ] [ __ ] It attacked the same
zero section again. Here's where where
the numbers are. It's still as rigged as
it ever was. [ __ ] hell, man. It's
still as rigged as it ever was and would ever will be. [ __ ]
hell. [ __ ] spins, bro. [ __ ] I only
put 150 in. It's [ __ ] rigged as
[ __ ] It is [ __ ] rigged as [ __ ] as a
[ __ ] It's so rigged. Oh my god.
People People that say it's not. Yeah.
They're [ __ ] absolutely talking out
their [ __ ] ass. Of course it's
[ __ ] rigged. Of course it's [ __ ]
fixed. Oh my god, bro. Use your [ __ ] brain, you
know. God. And that's money we can
afford to lose as well. Of course,
otherwise we wouldn't have done it. It
is [ __ ] [ __ ] All them people
that say, "Oh, it's a house. They don't
need to cheat." It's bollocks, mate.
I've just gone on it. I've just covered
17 [ __ ] numbers again. Was doing 80
[ __ ] spins when it was up to 200
pound. And the same thing happens again.
Miss, miss, miss. It literally seeks out
that loser. I swear to God it [ __ ]
does. It literally [ __ ] does. I'm
[ __ ] do it for real this time.
[ __ ] close it. It's [ __ ] annoying.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] It honestly is
[ __ ] Stop coming out when you got
no money on them. It's It's the same
old. You never see Zero Section come out that many
times. You never see it come out that
many times. Told you. And And the same
rigged [ __ ] 34 number. And the same
rigged 34. Riged
34. Yeah. Same rigged 3 [ __ ] four.
[ __ ] 34 number. You see that about a
million times as well, right? One
second. [ __ ] a load of [ __ ] mate.
I'm telling you, it
is cuz you people can't lose that many
times when when they're covered half the
board. You know what I'm saying? It's
literally impossible. It's literally
impossible. Well, that's [ __ ]
depressing. And it's money we can afford
to lose as
well. I think that tells you that
secular s is full of [ __ ] Yeah.
Even when it is when it even when it is
money you can afford to lose. It's the
same old rigged pattern that it
continuously seeks out. But you know,
you get people like Scoop saying they
don't need to cheat, but they do cheat.
But they they really really do cheat
because you can't cover 70 numbers and
miss that many times. It's not even
justifiable. You know, there's there's
there's more sections on the wheel. I
mean, yeah, I'll call you back, but I'm
not in a [ __ ] mood. Sorry, bro.
me, bro. Sorry. This has pissed me off.
You always hear about this excuse. This
house edge excuse excuse excuse. I've
been hearing it for ages. This is one of
the reasons I stopped doing this [ __ ]
You'd hear about it for ages. Oh, as
long as you got money, as long as you
got your bills paid, oh, it's all a
okay. That's literally all they ever
say. That's literally all that. I swear
to God, that's all they ever say. They
say as long as you've got your bills
paid, it's all okay to lose on rig
gambling. That's what they
say. Yeah, it's [ __ ] [ __ ]
mate. Just trying to get people
addicted. That's what they're trying to
do. Just try to get people addicted. Oh,
bro. Yeah. Stop talking about yourself.
You are a big- nose virgin. Stop talking
about yourself. Stop talking about
yourself, you disabled
[ __ ] Yeah. Stop talking about yourself, you disabled
[ __ ] Yeah, you disabled little keyboard
warrior [ __ ] Yeah. Yeah. Apply it to
yourself, you [ __ ] virgin [ __ ] Get
off of YouTube, you little low
life. But you win some, you lose some, so they
say. There you go. I just take a picture
of my bet right there.
can cover 17 numbers and you can keep
losing. It's not no [ __ ] house
edge. It ain't no [ __ ] house
edge. It's got nothing to do with with a
house edge. That and the house edge is
completely different. It's not no house
edge, you know. There's no It's nothing
to do with a [ __ ]
my money on that other account, I
reckon. Yeah, they're not getting any
more of my money. They just gave me They
just gave me a bonus.
Okay, I got a bonus on B book of raw.
Okay, let's see what this is going to
pay. 1 80. Okay, let's see what this is going to
pay. Probably nothing. Probably going to
give me a [ __ ] Give me an
explorer. Nope. Gives me the [ __ ]
lion. Yay, a lion, which is not going to show any of their
aces. Okay, that's paid.
Okay. Okay, here we go. We got two.
Okay, we got six
left. Come on. We need more than [ __ ] two, man. [ __ ] hell. Five
left. Two again. What is it with you and these [ __ ] twos? Come on. No.
So again, why is it always [ __ ]
two? So they gave me a bonus.
Okay, but you're not going to get
another bonus again. Let me see if I can withdraw it. Probably
not. Think we're locked in a bonus
now. No. One
sec. Yeah. I think we're locked to the bonus. Yeah.
I don't go anymore. I just thought I'd try again.
Okay. Play some live roulette then.
roulette. Yeah, of course you want with
a bonus. It's all [ __ ] fixed. [ __ ]
this. I'm done after this anyways.
[ __ ] bet you, bro. Right. Okay. Come on
then. Oh [ __ ] 82 spin.
Jesus. 1720. We
need 1720. Any of them really. Any of
them ones are
good. Stay away from the other section.
33 is good, isn't it? No, it's money back. Come
on. Oh, this still two and a half grand
left. Just [ __ ] hell. Come
on. I need to wager
it. Is nothing. So
rigged. How do you cover that many
numbers and you keep losing? It's so
fixed. You got to laugh at it, mate.
Honestly, you got to laugh at it. Can't
even get mad at something that's just so
rigged. They say it's House Edge, but
it's definitely not House Edge. This has
been going on for months, months and
months and months. This has been going
on for legit months. Trust me. Which is
why I stopped doing it. Months and
months and months and months and months
and months and months and months and
months and months and months. Put my
money in my account. Anyways, that's
what I'll be doing.
5 8 11 17
20. Nope. Missed again. See, it's so
rigged. As soon as you take the the
money off the numbers, right, it comes
in. It's so rigged. It is honestly so
rigged. Right. Let me go back to this
thing. Anyways, I'm trying to shut this
[ __ ] down. The day don't shut my account
by today. I'm putting my money in my
other account. [ __ ] this [ __ ] rigged
piece of [ __ ] It It's so [ __ ] fixed.
It's unbelievable. You can't miss that many
times. Send it to my other
account with all my other
money. Yeah, there's no way you can miss
that many times. No way. Not covering 70
numbers and ain't no one going to even
try to justify it because it's been
going on for months and months and
months and months and months and months
and months and months and months. No one
can keep losing that many times.
That's not a house edge. Well, and
that's why I stopped doing
it. 300 pound gone in in the past couple
of days. I haven't done anything, you
know. So, yeah, no one can keep losing
all the kind of money that you're
putting on as well. There's no way.
There's there's no way. Casino
influencers will say it's gambling, but
it's nowhere near gambling. Cuz gambling
you wouldn't keep
losing. Yeah, you've been saying
that. Yeah, you've been actually been
saying that for three days now.
It's [ __ ] annoying, bro. I feel like
going out and smacking the bookies up
with a hammer. Even though it's Even
though it's not a bookies, obviously
it's not a better [Laughter] shot.
Yeah, it's proper fix,
lad. You know, you have low you have low
intelligence. You're the one on here
trying to troll people and be smart at
the same time, but you just suck at it.
That's how thick you are. You can't even
troll. Um, you know what I'm saying?
Intelligence. Don't talk to me about
intelligence, mate. You're thick as
[ __ ] You're on here trying to troll
like a [ __ ] every day on YouTube.
Like, who's the one that's really got low
intelligence? You [ __ ] absolute
[ __ ] [ __ ] spacker of life. Having
to come on YouTube trying to troll cuz
you ain't got nothing in your life. And
you want to try and tell me about
intelligence? [ __ ] hell.
It is a [ __ ] scam, bro. 100%,
bro. We said we're in the process of this now.
Anyways, it's so rigged. This is rigged
as a [ __ ] It ain't no house
edge because people can't would not lose
that many times if it was House Edge and
they wouldn't lose that amount of
money. It is a scam. All of it is a big fat scam.
The death row is 100% it is one second. [ __ ] hell,
right? So, yeah. Well, I forgot how bad
it was. I won't be giving them money
anymore, will I? Obviously, it's [ __ ]
rigged. [ __ ] hell, [Music]
bro. Obviously, I won't be [ __ ] doing
it anymore, will I? Duh. It's [ __ ]
rigged as [ __ ] I've been trying to
close my account for the past [ __ ] how many
days? Anyways, I'm out of here.