[Music] Yeah, man.
mates in [ __ ] London as well. No, I
think I was thinking of going out today,
you know. Weather's nice and [ __ ]
but the weather's nice.
Yeah. Come on.
I was thinking of going out
today. My mates in London as well. See
Oh, that means getting my [ __ ] hair
done and [ __ ] man. I don't know,
bro. Long is
it? I don't if you can stay out all night,
bro. Go away, Louis Phil. Slugger, you
sad. YouTube is very boring. Yeah, get a
life and it won't be
boring. If you can stay out long, then
I'll meet you. But I'm not meeting you to come
back in London. Let me see. You can stay
out until long. I'll meet
you. Nah, you're definitely Louisville Slugger. [Laughter]
Yeah, I might meet my friend. [ __ ]
it. I'll still be going out Saturday
though. I'll have to be going out
Saturday as well. because of
um yeah, I need to meet another friend. Um he
budget these [ __ ] phone charges.
We're not going nowhere,
mate. There you
go. Tracks. No, I'm not meeting you
though because we won't get anywhere,
mate. If I meet you, I want to be out all night,
bro. Know what I'm saying, bro? I want
to be out all night. If I come and meet
you, the point then, bro, cuz you're not
going to get
in most places. So, listen, let me let
me message him. I'm
back. I'm done with women. Yes, but I
want to meet my friend and I want to
have a few drinks. I've not been out for
a [ __ ] month. I am done with women.
So what? Because I'm going out. That
means I'm going to I'm going to get
women. No. I wanted I want a few drinks
with my friend. I've not been out for a [ __ ] month.
Who said anything about women, bro? The
[ __ ] today as well? I want a drink. So,
yeah. 9 hours now. 9 hours now. Okay.
Yeah. You want a madness? So, you're
saying just for me to do a madness?
Yeah. Because YouTube is very boring at
the moment. How about you do a madness
in your real life and get a life? Do a
madness. Yeah. Do a madness and get a
life. That's That That's a good madness.
That's a good madness. You going and getting a
life. Yeah. You'll have the biggest madness.
Yeah. probably be the biggest man Everybody likes
No, I'm not meeting you,
bro. No, I'm not meeting him. [ __ ] that,
bro. If you're not going to wear jeans,
I got meeting you cuz you won't be able
to get into uh most
places. Where is he? [ __ ] Camden. Is
he? I've been Camden for
ages. Is that where you're at?
Yeah. Two times this
week. Well, I don't know what I'm doing, bro. [ __ ] Yeah.
I'm in town. I have not been there for a few
years bush. Okay. So
yeah, one second.
I'll go out
today. I kind of prefer just go
myself to be honest.
Yeah, [ __ ] it. I'll chill
today. Having some food cooked for
me. But yeah, I am done with women.
What's the point of speaking to people
that that the only word they know is
I've got a boyfriend. The only thing
that they can do is reply back to
negativity. [ __ ] negativity of all
things they can only reply back to. Of
course, I'm done with them,
bro. But obviously, I still want to go
out this week and I'm just going to go
out. I probably will go out once once a
week. Spend 5060 a week on beers. Why
not? Nothing else to do.
But I am done with them. 100% done with
them. Evil [ __ ]
bastards. Yeah, he wants this guy wants
to meet me, bro. But it's getting in
places with him. That's the thing.
Um, I don't
know. Should I meet this [ __ ] No, I
not. But then it's trying to get into
places. That's the problem.
My friend wants to meet me on Saturday
after work and then we can actually get into
places. We're just trying to get in
places. I used to have a friend that's a
girl that used to meet me, but she
doesn't meet me anymore. We're just
friends. Used to be nice going out cuz
then I could actually get into [ __ ]
most places with
her. Looks good, you know,
but don't really speak to her anymore. All right. Yes. Next
I'll be back later.