[ __ ] get up there, son. I just got
another number. Three numbers. Three numbers. Three.
Where the [ __ ] are these?
I got another number. I ended life.
I [ __ ] got another
number. Three numbers.
Bang. I haven't got I've got a boyfriend
once. Not once, mate. I've gone out in
the tracksuit. Listen, mate. I've gone
out in the tracksuit, mate. And I've not
got I've got a boyfriend
once. I've not gone once, mate. I've not
got it once. I got about four
approaches. I got three moves. I ain't
got I got go at once, mate. I'm a
[ __ ] I said I'm going out being a
[ __ ] and it works. Just go out and
be a [ __ ] Wear chubby clothes and
mate. Know what I mean? [ __ ]
me. [ __ ] me. Ain't got a boyfriend. once.
Yeah, I'm on the corner. Get up there as
earlier. Got a tracksuit on, mate. Got a
on. Cactus got the tracksuit on.
I need to go and meet my friend
Saturday. So I thought first I'll have a
solo session and send it by
myself. Yeah, man.
Babe, I have not got it once. I'm
wearing anony tracksuit and I've not got
I've got a boyfriend once. I swear to
God, bro. I ain't got it once. They like
[ __ ] That's why I'm [ __ ]
They like [ __ ] mate. I'm telling
you. I've got my track suit on. I got my
jeans in a bag in case they try to wear
my dude, mate. It's been all right. three numbers.
I don't know another approach. I was
speaking to her for 20 minutes. She's a
Muslim. And guess what, Joe? I think I'm
love. I think I'm in love. Yeah. Yeah. I
told her I've got Muslim friends. She
lives near me, too. I've got three
numbers so far. I've done four
approaches. Four approaches. Three
numbers. Hey, it's got to be the
tractor, is it? It's got to be. They're
like [ __ ] in the stretch. I'm a
[ __ ] I'm looking at that one over there. Looks
like I got three numbers on four
approach. I got three numbers. I'm
always eating full plate. I'm always Oh,
action. I'm always eating plate.
Whatever. I'm a lover,
bro. I'm looking at that one there.
But I go and give it a Well,
but then she's got the bigger tits.
I thought I'd have a solo session on a
Thursday. Thought I need to meet people
Saturday and be get
real. USA has got saggy tits.
You must say Izzy has got saggy
tit about that
life about that
life. She's not about that life, bro.
Never. [ __ ] about that life, mate. [ __ ]
yourself when I said I was going to come
next week in it. Yeah. [ __ ] pair of
[ __ ] Pair of [ __ ] mate. [Music]
Gospel is not about that life. Cross
it. She ain't about that
life. She ain't about that life,
bro. The trackies are a banger, mate.
I've not got I've got a boyfriend. What?
Swear this. Why? Why is that? Not
once. Not [ __ ] once. Nope. Not once.
Even in the pub. Even the [ __ ] pub. I didn't get it, man. No. [Music]
No. I'm looking at one,
but give it a low. [Music]
She had some saggy
ass. Do you have any
condoms? That's what she
said. She was like, "Do you have any
condoms?" "Do you have any
condoms?" [ __ ] off. What's your par Kansas? Yeah, mate.
Today I thought I want the tracksuit and
I'll be a [ __ ] And it's worked so
far. I mean, we've not got I've got a boyfriend
once. Tracksuit and be a [ __ ] It
seems to work. I know [Music]
what I'm looking at that one over
there. M when I went to Newcastle.
Yes. She said to me, "Oh, you from
London?" And I said, "Yeah, yeah, yeah."
She started lifting me up. She thought I
was a drug dealer. I was like I was
like, "Who do you like?" She said, "Drug
dealers." She thought I was a drug
dealer cuz I'm from London. Like, uh,
okay. I just went along with
it. Yeah. Tell him you're a drug dealer,
mate. Mate, you you get all the [ __ ] Duck suit,
[ __ ] Hey, no more Mr. Nice
Guy M. No more Mr. Nice [Music]
guy. No more Mr. Nice [Music]
Yeah. Oh, [ __ ] wave. I'll do
it with me. I'll [ __ ] do it. I don't give
a Yeah, it's
Corona. It's Corona. Where the [ __ ] is
this [ __ ] He's pulled me out. Where is he,
mate? Where the [ __ ] is this [ __ ] He
got me out and he's nowhere to be saved. Where is
he? [ __ ] [ __ ] You aren't
fair. [ __ ] you, mate. It's
Corona. I might have to do that one.
She's a bit stinking, mate. Ah, she got them titties.
You never know, Joe. Could be could be hiding behind desk.
Wait, you never know me, mate.
USA is a
[ __ ] I told her, "Yeah, go [ __ ] her
boyfriend. Go [ __ ] I will come to
America next week, which is
today." And then [ __ ] and Saturday
she shut her mouth, mate. She shut her
mouth, mate. She's a
[ __ ] No one she knows about none. I
swear that I messaged a [ __ ] on Facebook. No.
I commented on her post last week. She
ain't about that life. You're not about
that life. Shut up. You know what I'm saying? [ __ ]
hell. Guess what? I've not got I've got
a boyfriend once. I haven't got it once
today. Not once, mate. I'm wearing the
tracksy. I'm being a [ __ ] and I
haven't got it once. I thought, you know
what? Yeah. If you can't beat them, join them.
Yeah. Wear a track to and be a [ __ ]
That's what I've done. And I've not got
I've got a boyfriend once and I've done
several approaches. I got three numbers.
You can't beat them, join them. [ __ ]
you. I'm a [ __ ] now by a whing
trackuit. If you can't beat them,
[ __ ] join them. I done two approaches
so got one number and a couple of drunk
got all their numbers. Yeah. Yeah. In a
pub as well. I'm a [ __ ] Call me the
[ __ ] now. I'm a [ __ ] in a
tracksuit. Yep. And I'm throw cuz it seems to work.
Yeah. You say I dad's a [ __ ]
[ __ ] I told her I will come on
Thursday or Friday next week. Come on.
All I need is the confirmation, [ __ ]
I will [ __ ] come. Come on. She ain't
about that life. She's a
[ __ ] She's a little She ain't about
that life. Her and her little [ __ ]
tattooed boyfriend who looks like me.
Her little [ __ ] [ __ ] boyfriend
who looks like me. But guess what? I'm
[ __ ] better. And I'm not scared of
none of you [ __ ] You know what I mean?
I'm not scared of none of you [ __ ]
I have the [ __ ] lawyer.
Yeah. Yeah. You're a [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, you're a [ __ ] You can't
reply. You don't know no one in no
country. You little [ __ ] mate. You
went scared back home and you started
all your [ __ ]
[ __ ] All you had to say was Thursday or
Friday and I will come and batter you
up, bro, in front of anyone you know.
But you ain't about that life. So, let's
keep it real in it. Yeah.
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] mess.
Yeah. Your dad's a keyboard warrior,
mate. I said I will go on his [ __ ]
door and he said he will call the [ __ ] police.
Yeah. I swear. Who said they were
calling the police? Come on, bro.
Who said they were calling the [ __ ] police?
Yeah, you was calling the police. [ __ ]
[ __ ] Hey, I've already got three
numbers. Another four
approaching. Yeah, I will. Yeah. [Music]
a [ __ ] today. I'm a [ __ ] with a truck suit,
you know. [ __ ] me. I'm going Thailand in
four weeks. So, [ __ ] the lawyer. Who's
going to get the last laugh, mate? It's
going to be me when I go Thailand in
four weeks and you're all [ __ ] still
here. She has got saggy tits. Borggan
has got saggy tits. I sucked all her
tits. I sucked her boobs. Yeah, I was
fingerling a [ __ ] She's a [ __ ]
sk. She's a [ __ ]
sk. That's what she
is. Look at me. I ain't got no
tattoos. Done. Yeah.
I mean, she's got sagging
boobs. Round nipples. That's what she's about.
That you know, you get [ __ ] up. Yeah.
That's why you don't say to me. Yeah, that's right. [Music] [ __ ] USA.
Yeah. You know what I mean, bro? I said,
let give me a day next week and I'll
come. Bro, stop running away. Stop being
scared. Stop being a cable lawyer. You
know what I mean?
You ain't about that life, man.
Yeah. Why are you replying to old men on
[ __ ] Facebook? Reply to
me. Stop replying to old men on Facebook
and [ __ ] reply to me. Reply to me.
Stop replying to old men on Facebook,
mate. And guess what? I tell you a true
story. I was in the Weather Spoons
earlier and this guy saw me. I thought I
chat I think I chat to him on WhatsApp.
I met him 3 months prior. The guy was
trying to weigh me up, bro. He knew he'd
get [ __ ] up. That's why he lowered his
phone down. He lowered his toe down cuz
he knew he'd get [ __ ] up, bro. He knew
he'd get [ __ ] up. And this guy know he
goes to the gym, bro. He was like, "What
you up to?" No, no, no, no, no. He was
talking. I had a guy know he get banged
up even with his friend. Yeah. You're
all upper [ __ ]
tunist. That's what you are. You're
opportunist. Really and truly. Oh [ __ ]
But really and truly, that's what
you opportunist, bro.
Yeah. You're opportunist. You do really
get [ __ ] up, man. Don't don't don't
twisted. Don't get twisted. But you do
get [ __ ] up. Trust me. [Music]
So, go. I need to go in a minute.
Anyways, I need to send more
approaches. I'm going to send more
approaches and then [ __ ]
um and I'm going to go home, go back
live. I should be tuned though.
Even if I've got I've got a boyfriend
twice today, I'll call it lucky,
mate. I've done four
approaches and I've got three numbers.
So, I'm happy, mate. Even if I get it two
times, cuz it tells you, mate, you need
to wear tracksuit and be a [ __ ]
You need to wear a tracksuit and be a
[ __ ] [ __ ] The only thing that
works. Be a [ __ ] and wear a
tracksuit with some white air matches.
There's not any fit ones. There's one
with some big tit. I might do
her. Listen, I'm going anyway, chef.
I'll be back later when I'm back in the
yard. See you.