I'm back in
homeland. So I done four approaches. I got three
numbers. Went back. Got an escort.
[ __ ] [ __ ] was bro. I ran my dick
down her throat, bro. I was ramming my
dick down her [ __ ] throat, man.
Madness. Four numbers. Four four
approaches, three numbers. So yeah, be a
[ __ ] and wear a tracksuit. That's
what I got from
today. Be a [ __ ] and wear a trackuit. 80
quid. Just [ __ ] run my dick down. I
bro down. Reg would love to know about that, wouldn't
he? Yeah. Sorry, man. What I was saying
is I wasn't really um paying attention
to LJ's haters earlier because they're just self
projectors that like skin you got no
friends and that they're just talking
about themselves. That's why I don't
react to it, bro. I don't react to the self
projectors. Yeah, I don't react to the
self projectors me cuz they're just
talking about themselves for a living.
There's no point
um they just talk about themselves for a living
delay. They call people skin cuz they
themselves. They're all old, bro.
Listen. Yeah, I got some money here.
Look, if you want to
see, I got some bum
change. Told you I make money,
bro. I got some bum change here. Look.
Complete a bum change, mate. Nothing
skint about me,
buddy. Never has been, never will be.
Yeah, nothing's good about me,
lad. Yeah, they're
boring and old, man. I'm going to put
the approaching videos up on my main channel.
Nothing about me.
But yeah, I was talking to this
womanistan. I said, "Oh, I've got
Pakistan friends and that. Would I would
I would I convert for a woman?" Nah. I
mean, that means no more piggies. No,
I'm not putting them up on this, bro.
I'm not entertaining these mongos. I'm
not putting up on this
channel cuz of these
mongos, but I'll put it on my main
channel that no one knows about. I'm not
I'm not putting it where any of these
people can do it. [ __ ] them, bro. They're weirdos,
man. And I need to go to the gym. I need
to stop gaining weight, bro. I'm going
to end up like these people fat and
ugly. [ __ ] me, bro. Jeez. But do you
know what? Yeah, I [ __ ] I was live
earlier in the [ __ ] pub, brother.
This guy was like, "Oh, you're gaining
weight." I was like, "You're telling me
I'm gaining weight? Have you seen the
state of you people? You're morbidly o
[ __ ] obese and you're talking about
me gaining a bit of weight. Don't worry
about me, bro. I know my [ __ ] limits.
Look at you [ __ ] you people on
YouTube ain't got a life." You know what
I'm saying, Brit Bong. [ __ ]
hell. Talking like they're not morbidly
obese. [ __ ] hell, man.
But yeah, there's no point putting up
because they're all
um they're just all [ __ ] spastics,
bro. In this community, man. Uh you know what I'm
saying? LJ was like, "Oh, you got your big money
today. You got your big money today,
bro. You don't know how I get money. You
don't know how I make money. Let's keep
it that way." Yeah. So you They talk
like they know people's lives. Why are
they jealous of somebody going out for a
drink? Bro, it's a normal thing people
do. Going out for a drink cuz they ain't
got a life. They've got no
money. You want to talk about people
being 27, 28, not being young. I was
like, "Bro, you people are [ __ ] in
your 40s and you're still on YouTube.
[ __ ] hell. Come on, bro. Get get alive.
They're just self projectors, bro.
That's all they are. They're
just the people in here, bro. They're just self
projectors. One sec, bro.
sec. Come on. Washing up, bro.
That escort sucked my dick good,
bro. Oh my [ __ ] god. She deep
throtted it. [ __ ]
hell. Oh my god.
almost like a [ __ ] alleyway one.
Eh, choked to
death. I need to stop doing this.
Uh, I need to stop doing this [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. I need to actually start [ __ ]
again. I really need to start [ __ ] [ __ ] again,
bro. I ain't [ __ ] in months.
Literally, just [ __ ] straight
[ __ ] I need to really get get out
of doing that,
bro. Like, I almost choked to death. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, I need to cut back on the ice
cream, but it's not just the KFC, it's
the ice cream. And obviously I had I
didn't walk for like a month because
obviously I had that foot injury. So I
didn't walk for like a month.
Yeah, but I need to take this wash out
well. [ __ ] hell,
man. Just can't [ __ ] well. Wash out.
Wash up. Anyways, I'll be back tomorrow.
Yeah, I'm going to sleep. I've got the
police coming tomorrow as well. So, I
got stuff to do tomorrow.