Oh, I got the nuggets. I got the
nuggets. Oh, they're [Music] tasty. M.
M imagine that gre there I'm in court
and you come to the court
hearing and it's all over the same
website you can watch Stitch
on the same website you can you can
watch Stitch on and
Scooby how [ __ ] isn't that
cool like you lose your life and your
kids on the same website you can watch
Stitch on. Isn't that cool? [Music]
You better not be [ __ ] D.
What is that
cool? Kind of tastes like dark coat to me. Yes.
Really? Do you remember the
tweenies? You remember the
tweenies. You might not remember that.
Yeah, I used to sit in front of the TV
all day watching Spongebob
here. Just all day I used to watch Spongebob on
Nickelodeon. It was lush,
mate. I love Spongebob, bro.
If they if they put a new Sponge out, I'd watch [Music] it. I was I
Spongebob. Remember the Spongebob there
in Squidward? He tried to he tried to go
to a new home there to get away from um
to get away from um [ __ ] Spongebob
and [ __ ] Patrick. Yeah. And [ __ ]
um they followed him. They found him. He
went to like a
[ __ ] He went to a squid home.
Yeah. He went to a [ __ ] squid home
thinking he was going to get away from
Spongebob to get a bit of peace, but they found
him. H remember that one if you ever watch
Spongebob. I don't know if you remember that
one. I'm doing
this. You never watch [Music]
Spongebob. You never watched him, did you? Trust me,
bro. Don't underestimate Peppa Pig. It's
got to become famous,
bro. It's already worldwide.
I think they done good for an English
cartoon since most of them are American
and nothing good comes from England. But
I think with Peppa Pig, yeah, you have
to give credit when credit is due. It's
English and it's pretty well known.
Would you agree, Grezy? You go on
YouTube, it's got about 22 [ __ ] million
views. It's uh quite popular. See, when
I was younger, there was no Peppa Pig.
It come out in 2004.
But I weren't aware of it back then. It
was [ __ ] Spongebob and [ __ ] Now
people don't know about less people know
about Spongebob and Looney Tunes now
because it doesn't come on the TV
because the TV subscriptions are the TV
subscriptions are so expensive.
Grezy. So that's why they know about
like Peppa Pig and [ __ ] because it comes
on Nickelodeon and obviously unless you
got a TV subscription. The only way kids
nowadays know about Spongebob and [ __ ] is through
YouTube cuz obviously how expensive is
to get a TV sub.
So that's how
um I didn't know about Peppa Pig when I was
younger. I didn't know about Peppa Pig.
That come out 2004, but I never knew
about it until my [ __ ] um niece kept
going on about it. You right, Cory?
Yeah, very good
skin. I'm having some chicken nuggets.
Nah, bro. He never came back. No.
No. Still about, bro. Still about. do
about you remember Isabelle
Richie. Remember Isabelle Grezy me and
Isabelle holding hands and kissing and
stuff. USA is a M as
well. He's a proper
m. Look at me call me. I get all the
ladies. I got all the ladies.
That's not an old photo or
anything. He had the chips in it. She
like, "Can I have some chips?" I said,
"No, Isabelle. I'm not buying you any
more drinks or anyone or anyone
chips." "No, Isabelle." I put I put my
foot down. I said, "No,
Isabelle." You know, and then she threw a tantrum.
Music. Yeah. She She then threw a [ __ ]
tantrum. This Coke is dodgy, man. It
tastes like [ __ ] Diet Coke Grezy.
It's [ __ ] stinky,
man. Can't stand. I think I might have
some coke downstairs. Do I? That is dodgy,
man. You can taste the difference as
well. It tastes like [ __ ] Have normal
Coke and It tastes like [ __ ] Diet Coke.
taste that [ __ ] diet
[ __ ] I can't be bothered to go
downstairs, but I'm going to Oh,
lovely. Got some proper now.
Oh, yeah. I got some proper folk now, lad. [ __ ]
hell. I got three nuggets left. before
it's left and I'm [ __ ] stuffed.
Groovy, you're trying to get me
fat, I know what your game is. You're
just trying to get me fat. Yeah.
Whoa. I'm stuffed, mama. One second,
bro. Yeah, I've got two nuggets left.
So, did Monty lose his kids over YouTube,
boozy? Oh, that's madness,
bro. How can you lose your kids over the same
website used to watch [ __ ] That's
mad. That's [ __ ]
mad. Yeah, but I almost got killed with it.
If I was in that day, Non Taylor
come, I might not be here
now. When I told my sister about that, I
was laughing. She said, "It's not even
funny." I like there would have been a
murder, bro. We would have actually been
a murder, mate. Like the whole house
would have like been boarded up. It's
quite scary. Yeah.
But what makes me laugh
is that Tom and Jerry will still be on
YouTube. Stitch will still be on
YouTube. All of these things will still be on
YouTube. So even when I get killed over
YouTube, they'll still be on it.
Yeah. They'll never get off YouTube,
mate. Anyways, I need to go. Yeah. Bye.