[ __ ] hell, mate. Oh
my. Oh, [ __ ]
me. Long day awaits, eh?
A [ __ ] long day awaits.
Yeah, a long day today,
matey. [ __ ] hell. You don't know what
a [ __ ] wet dream is,
mate. Start to think you're [ __ ] special needs,
man. Yeah, I'm going to be [ __ ] busy
all day today. [ __ ] spy as
well. That's the joys of having a life.
Something that these people need to get
on YouTube. They need a life. Sat on
YouTube all day. A nice day today as well.
Yeah, I'm going to have to eat some coffee
then tomorrow as well.
Jesus. Oh, what a lovely
site. Got sore throat as well.
Bro, I don't want to try and sleep though. [ __ ] [Music]
hell. Got to wear a nice track suit and
trainers tomorrow. Oh, this lovely
day. Can't beat it, can you? You know,
Do you know all of this
um you know I found with these little
mongos on this community? Yeah. This
whole uh you're almost 30. I I do you
know why they do it? I know why they do
this. You're almost 30. It makes them
feel better about the fact that they're
old and their lives are over. You know
what? Yeah, I just clicked off of this
and I was like, it makes sense
now cuz they they think that you're
becoming one of them fat, ugly, no life
YouTube. Um that that's why they say
that you're almost 30. Yeah, cuz cuz
these people that say that are all in
their late 30s and 40s, it's to make
themselves feel better, but the fact
that they're well past 30 and they're
like, "Okay, well, he's going to be 30
soon. Oh, he's gaining a bit of weight,
so he's not four of us." That's
literally what they do. It's like when
you It's like when you gain a little bit
of weight, they all get excited when
they're the ones that are literally morbidly
obese. Yeah, that's what it is. Just
another form of self projector. Really
just another day on this uh community
for the new self projectors.
like Adidas trainers. I've never been a
fan of Adidas
trainers. I need to get some sleep soon
cuz I'm going out later. So, try and
rest. I feel fat today.
Oh [ __ ] man. So yeah, that's why people
say that you're almost 30. Yeah, it's
because they're well in their 40s and
they're trying to make themselves feel
better. That's why they say, "Oh, you're
almost 30. You're almost 30. You're
nowhere near 30. 3 years is nowhere near
30." But again, they're just convincing
themselves that you're, you know, you're
30. You're fat like them. You're ugly
like them. It's just another form of
self-p projection which is what these
people do on here. You
know, that's what it
is. That's literally literally what it
is. Cuz your mid20s is
25. Yeah. You're literally just past
your mid20s. You're literally nowhere near
30. Literally, you're nowhere near 30.
Think about it. This year you're 28. The
next year you're 29. Then the other year
that's when you're 30. That's literally
three different years until you're 30.
You're nowhere near 30. What madness do
you think you can get up to in [ __ ]
three years, bro? You're literally nowhere near
30. Someone that's near 30 is like 5
months away or 6 months away. Even a
year away is nowhere near 30. Even if
you was 29. But again, another form of
self projection. This is what these
people do on here cuz they got a life.
Yo, sorry man. I was just talking about these self
projectors. And why have they always got
non [ __ ] in their head? Like, okay,
yeah, I went to watch Peppa Pig, but why
do they always think of this these nonsy
things, bro? That's how you know they're
[ __ ] wrongs, bro. Peppa Pig was
good. Yeah, it was good. I need to go
out today, meet some friends. Got to
meet this woman tomorrow.
I was just about to um complain about
yesterday, but then I realized like,
well, I got to meet anyways. So, no,
it's half a
movie. So, you went out Thursday, you
got to meet tomorrow.
Okay. It's better than nothing cuz I'm
going out today. So, I'm going to have
to try and be okay for tomorrow as
well. So, I need to eat the best food I basically can.
It's still a piss take
though. It is still a piss take, right?
Cuz this person replied back. Yeah. Even
though you got one meeting you, right?
There was one that replied back and um
we're talking. I was like, "Oh, we
should go for some cocktails. I know how
to type to people and
then then they just go quiet." It's
like, what? What's the [ __ ] point of
even replying that, bro? But I need to
go out today because I had my haircut
and I need to meet my friends and I am
meeting someone tomorrow. So, but it's
still even still just don't [ __ ]
reply to the [ __ ]
message. Yeah, Italian women are quite
bad. I was saying this to somebody um
earlier actually earlier earlier in the
morning. I've been up since 5:00 in the
morning. Yeah. They're quite bad, aren't
they? Italian women.
Yeah, I need to go out today. I need a
plan B if tomorrow [ __ ] up. So, I need a plan B.
Um, so hopefully I'll be all right. Should
be I do feel a bit [ __ ] though. I'm
not going to
lie. It can't have been from the
drinking cuz I drunk on Thursday and I
didn't get hangover yesterday. I think
I'm just a bit tired maybe.
Yeah. But mate, like I said, even if I
need to call on that date, mate, I'll be crawling there.
Yeah. Well, this almost 30 [ __ ] needs to
stop, bro. It's boring now. 3 years from
30 is nowhere near 30.
Think of it, bro. That court date that I
need to go on because that [ __ ] virgin is uh
31. I'll be whole. I'll be 31.
31. Be 31, mate. That's years
away. What's that? 2028. Well, it's not
happening anyways, but let's just say
theoretically, it's literally years
away. You know what I'm
saying? You know, when you're 30, you're
not even in the same [ __ ] year. You
know, like you say you'll be 30 before
you know it. Yeah. But to say you're
almost 30, you're nowhere near 30.
That's just their way of making them
feel better about the fact that they're old.
you know, old, fat,
ugly on this community and got a life. What's up?
Yeah, this woman doesn't know what a
[ __ ] wet dream is. I said I had a wet
dream about you. So, what's a wet dream?
You don't know what a [ __ ] wet dream
is? But yeah, if I didn't have a meet
tomorrow, I'd be pissed off.
M I would be a bit pissed off. I'm not
going to lie to you. But I'd be lying if
I said I wouldn't
be cuz it's what I was saying to Antman.
I was like, "Bro, I can't even give you
advice." Cuz I I messaged him saying
like, "Oh, you can't expect anything,
but at the same time, you can expect
something because it drains you." I said
to him, "Yeah, you want to do these
approaches sober, bro. By the fifth one,
you're mentally and physically drained.
You have to eat a million times." So in that
sense, yeah, you can expect something
because it's time consuming. It drains
your energy. It's the same as going to
the gym. So you can if you put effort,
you can expect something back from
it. I'm only doing the drinking side of
it today cuz yeah, I can't be bothered.
I'm not doing any sober, bro. I've
already got a beat, so [ __ ] it.
But I should have two meats
realistically. But I know what they're like here.
So yeah, man.
I've got until [ __ ] like 9:00,
so I'm [ __ ] bro. I am [ __ ]
alert delete this woman tomorrow be all
[ __ ] hung over to [ __ ] nah.
Yeah, she wants to meet tomorrow.
So, got that
one. But the other one pissed me off,
bro. Cuz it's like, bro, you type back.
Yeah. And when somebody says you meet
up, you [ __ ] yourself. [ __ ] me,
bro. [ __ ] me. What the [ __ ] bro? It's
madness. Imagine going to do all that [ __ ] hover
over and my like, "Oh yeah, you got this
one. You bagged in it." I don't know
about that, man. And I think they're going to
flake. But I don't think that but he was right. So yeah.
Yeah. Oh, [ __ ] me,
bro. That's why I stopped doing it for a
month because I just it was just I just
can't be bothered putting energy in it,
bro. That's why I stopped putting effort in it.
Hey, stop man.
Looks max anyway. Tomorrow we'll wear
the fresh garments. So be good to go.
Yeah. [ __ ] knocking me.
Yeah, the amount of energy and effort
that you put into
it, it's just it's just not worth it,
bro. It's literally just not worth it.
It's bad, bro. It is
bad. But, I mean, you can't really
complain. You got a date tomorrow. You
didn't get I got a boyfriend once, but
it's still um I mean I mean you only
done four approaches, didn't you? So, we
can't really complain at at the end of
the day. You didn't get I got a
boyfriend once. I'm probably going to
get it today, though, cuz I'm not going
to wear the tracksuit.
But no, I won't be wearing the tracksuit.
So, what the [ __ ] is that? new get
today. What's that? Go up. Yeah.