World. So, it's all basically got around
about the same amount
left. Bro, today was bad. Down bad,
bro. Down [ __ ] bad. I'm joking. Watch it.
Oh, I'm back in the old esticles
now. No, I'm I'm actually not back in
the old esticles now. I'm [ __ ] in the wrong
location. This country is [ __ ] right
backwards. I feel like the more annoying
thing is you couldn't even reach your
potential. I think that was the most
annoying thing. I couldn't even get in
any [ __ ] way. The [ __ ] prices they
were asking was just absolutely
insane. Absolutely insane. Well, I got
this meet tomorrow, so
yeah. Numbers, but ain't the point, mate. [ __ ]
up. No, I went out um with some of my
friends, right? I've done some
approaches. I got two numbers, one
Snapchat. It's not the point. I had to
deal with a lot of [ __ ] today,
which is one of the reasons I need to
leave this country even though I've got
a day today. It's [ __ ] up, bro. I'm
thinking, okay, just a couple of people
going clubbing. Stop asking for [ __ ]
20 to get into
places, £15 to 20 each. I was like, [ __ ]
that. I am not paying that. There is no
way on earth I'm paying that.
Um, and then you have to deal with the
same just the same NPC people. Not even
necessarily saying that they have
boyfriends, but I can't remember what
the [ __ ] they were saying, but it's just
[ __ ] mate. Two numbers. Well, they
probably don't even reply
anyways. This country is [ __ ] bro.
You You should have seen what I was actually wearing
today. Re clothes, bro. The cars are
still lit, bro.
Yeah, country is [ __ ] bro. Country is
[ __ ] It's a [ __ ] business. What? You pay
£20? Yeah, you pay 20 [ __ ] pounds to
get in somewhere that's full of men and
people are probably just going to say
they got boyfriends. What the [ __ ] It's
stupid. I'm done, bro. I'm [ __ ] done,
bro. It's annoying cuz I didn't even get
to reach my potential.
I didn't even actually I weren't even
able to go in and actually drown myself
because of the [ __ ]
fees [ __ ] pay 20 to get into a
[ __ ] club of
£15. That's ridiculous, bro. Even any
more than one
person. And then you got the bully
victim um security because that's why
they joined the job because they're
bully victims and they were bullied as
children. There's this guy where he's
from America and he is a one bully
victim. I swear to God. Yeah. He works
at the staff. He works in the staff.
Can't stand him. I can't stand the guy.
He's such a
victim. Like he he's he's probably not
even like [ __ ] from New York. He's
probably some stupid [ __ ] that lives
the outskirts of New York. He's joined
this job just to have power. He's a
proper victim. Okay, I don't even like
using that word.
I wouldn't mind if I could have actually
got into some places and actually
enjoyed the night, but we walked around
for like [ __ ] about two hours. What the [ __ ]
bro? I need to leave this country,
bro. What? What? What the [ __ ] You
can't even get into a club without
spending [ __ ] 20
quid, you know? Have to deal with rude
people. That's that that's that's the
crux of it. You know, these [ __ ] man
could be got in
places. Have to deal with rude women,
dicker people. No, it's not. No, it's
not cheap to get into a [ __ ] club.
Not to get into a [ __ ] club when
there's four [ __ ]
people. [ __ ] it. I'll just meet this
woman tomorrow and I'll just do some
sober approaches if that's the way it's
got to be.
You know66 pound. Okay. Yeah. Six pound
each. But 1520 pound is not cheap to get
into a [ __ ] nightclub. What the [ __ ]
How much the [ __ ] drinks are? [ __ ] that
one. [ __ ] that. That's [ __ ]
madness. And you have to deal with rude people
anyways. Like look at the people that
you see in
there. Do you know what I'm saying? It's
not like you even have a chance to pull
it in a nightclub. All that will happen
when you go to a nightclub is, you
know, I don't gamble anymore. I don't
know why you keep putting up Frankie.
You know what happens in a nightclub is
yeah, you'll get a number and if you're
extremely lucky, you'll get a date.
There's no point you even [ __ ] Why
would you even pay more money to get to
a nightclub? It doesn't even make sense.
And there's like several different ones.
It's so stupid.
This is expensive. That is mad
expensive. Something like 20 as well. [ __ ] that,
bro. And you're probably going to hear I've got
boyfriends. But I'm done in this country
anyways. I'm going to meet this woman
tomorrow and then just go from there
with a track, too. And that's me done. I
think that's not normal, bro. It's bad
enough you have to deal with rude
people. You got this guy. He was eyeing
me. It's just just a negative
experience. Like, it's just all
negative, isn't it? You should have just
been able to go out and even go to a
club and actually reach potential before
failing. I failed before I even tried
cuz I couldn't even get in anywhere.
There's a stupid price and a stupid
little s rules.
I failed before I'd even tried before
I'd even put my
door. It's a [ __ ] joke, mate.
But to my mom's as well. It's the last
train of my
father. It's what it
is. This country will never
change. Yeah. really powerful for good
night just to hear I've got a boyfriend or some
[ __ ] I was chatting up this woman.
Yeah. And I had this guy. He was staring
at me, bro. And what he don't scare me
cuz I'm not scared of no one. Even like
that bounce of America. It's like, bro,
is this the [ __ ] you got to deal with
every time you want to just go out and
have a drink? You know, you know the aim
weren't even women today was just to
actually just go out and have a drink
with some of the [ __ ]
friends. And it's [ __ ] up, bro. You
can't even have a drink without getting
negative experiences. Imagine
that. I'm so [ __ ] dumb, bro. I'm
going to try and figure out what I need
to do from here, bro. Cuz this is not no
way of living, bro. Tell you, you
know, I didn't even get given a chance
to even fail. That's that's the madest
thing about it.
I want to send my friends this as well
anyways and tomorrow's a new day. Let's
just hope this woman don't waste my time
tomorrow. But can't see it happening,
mate. I can't see that happening,
mate. But yeah, I'm tired. I'm going to
go to sleep.
I've had enough,
mate, to be honest with you. But yeah,
come back tomorrow when I wake up, man.
Bit tired, so I need to go to
sleep. Yeah, I've had enough, bro. Collection number