[Music]
When you're all [ __ ] done in,
mate, you can always [ __ ] rely on
putting your [ __ ] feet up. I am fat. Oh
man. Oh no. I have a little live
stream. Yeah, I went on this date today.
It was quite good.
Perhaps I need to move to a f old country,
mate. Yeah. Oh, I'll put the picture up
for LJ where I went today.
L me and L go way back. I went to the
park to see the little ducklings.
me. I went to see the ducks RJ in central
London. Went for a
little my little bait RJ. Oh
man, I am so [ __ ] Oh, I'm so [ __ ]
Honestly, for 100 years, I'm telling
you, man, I need a
break. A [ __ ] break,
mate. I'm cooking today. AJ
was Yep. I wore a tracksuit, a wor
trainers. She was actually really nice.
We was together for 4 hours. went to
Nandos, went to see the Ducks.
Um, came around my area and
uh, man, yesterday was so [ __ ] man. Oh,
[ __ ] hell, bro. We couldn't even get
into a club without spending [ __ ]
1520. So, we only went to like one club.
I was like, we're not paying 1520 to get
into a [ __ ] club. So, we only went
into one that was free. So, that's
another thing. Yesterday was just
negative, man. [ __ ] it's bad enough
you have to deal with these [ __ ]
[ __ ] in this country. Speaking of
yesterday, then you have to pay to deal
with them. I was like, I'm not paying no
15, 20 pound to get into a club. I was with three
friends, large free [ __ ] friends. And
yeah, I'm not paying that. That's
ridiculous. It's bad, bro. What the
[ __ ] And you will probably go to about
three different clubs, three or four
different clubs. That's ridiculous,
mate. When it doesn't matter what's in
there is [ __ ] man. I got two numbers
yesterday. They didn't reply. So, I've
done quite a lot of approaches. Yeah, it
pissed me off yesterday, bro. I'm not
going to lie to you. It pissed me off.
Proper pissed me
off. This country pisses me off. It
won't even just about the [ __ ] these
stupid [ __ ] women. It's just what the
Like that's madness, bro. And all
they're going to do is and it's all it's
got to be is the same
[ __ ] Same rude people. The [ __ ]
man. I had a [ __ ] woman say to me
yesterday, "I don't want to talk. I'm
I'm with my girlfriend." Like, who do
they think they are?
I wouldn't mind if he actually was able
to try and actually fail. We didn't even
get the opportunity to really try. I had
to do some approaches on the
street, you know, and then got two
numbers, they didn't reply. So, same old
[ __ ] in this country,
eh? lot of [ __ ] in this country. But at
least I had a date today. Um, so
yeah, even call it that.
So, and that's the difference between
people from a third world
country and these westernized [ __ ] like American
uh uh Canadian, they're no good, mate.
You want somebody from a third world
country? Just went to Nando. Went to see the
ducks. I'm taking things slow for a change,
LJ. Now, I'm taking things
slow, you know, a lot of nice new
GS. So, yeah, you need to find people
from a third world
country. These westernized people are no
good, mate. Especially Americans.
[ __ ] Well, they're all [ __ ] really. Australians, Americans weirdos.
Yeah. Why do you think the dating game
is so hard in this
country? Instagram. Dude, that ain't us.
I was looking fresh yesterday. Nice
garments, nice hair done, curly hair.
No, it's not us, mate. Trust me. Instagram, maybe simp.
So, yeah. And you have to pay to get into these clubs. That's
mad. Pay to get into a [ __ ]
club. What the
[ __ ] That kind of money, eh?
Yeah, I can understand why I think he
likes Thailand now. And man, if they're
the women are like that in Thailand, I
can see why he likes them.
It's not even just about looks. It's
about people's whole
attitude. I was telling her about the
last date I went on and she was like,
"That doesn't make any sense." Cuz it
they don't make sense. That's what I'm
saying. These westernized counts don't
make sense. Maybe you just need to start
targeting people that look like they're
from [ __ ] third world countries by
the sounds of
it. Yeah. They're no good, mate. I can
see why he likes he likes
Thailand. That's if that's what the
difference is, you know. Yeah.
Doesn't matter what I have to offer a
woman, mate. We're not talking about
what I have to offer a woman. And it's
nothing to do with what you can offer a
woman, mate. Like, you you already have
your mind made up about people in this
community, bro. So, it makes no sense people answering
you because you've already you already
know everyone's life on here apparently,
even though you don't know anything. So
what what a stupid question to
ask and it it's nothing to do with what
you can offer a woman. My approaching
videos literally shows that and other
people's approach and videos also shows
that. Again, uh online advice and real
life experiences, they don't match.
They're completely different.
So yeah, and there's no point asking me
that because you've already got your mind made
up that everyone's like you. So what's
the point of even asking the stupid
question? You have it in your mind.
Everyone's skinned, everyone's fat,
everyone's ugly, everyone lives with
their mom, everyone has no job. So
you've already made your mind up. So why even
ask? [ __ ] hell. Doesn't matter what
people [ __ ] tell you, mate. Yeah, they're
proper they are proper [ __ ] in this
country. I think I went to bed about
3:00 in the morning, bro. I was like
[ __ ] trying to
uh Yeah, we got a new Izzy, Steven Howard.
met someone today and it was actually
quite a nice
experience not dealing with a stuck up
[ __ ] stuck up westernized horrible
bastard. Yeah, it's actually quite a nice
experience. I wonder man likes [ __ ]
Thailand. They're all like that. [ __ ]
hell. They're all [ __ ]
here. Yeah, I went out yesterday with my
friends and they were trying to charge
£1520 to get into each nightclub. Spend
£15,20 to get into a [ __ ] nightclub.
That's insane, bro. Like, how can you
even justify that? And all you're going
to get is I've got a boyfriend or [ __ ] some
stupidness. I think Fabrics is like £25
now to be fair. Paying all that money to
get into a
club. Nope, not at all.
Well, that's all,
mate. If I offer to cook. So, so the
first date of going for
someone. So, the first date you offered
to cook for someone. But are you a
[ __ ] My honest question. Are you a
[ __ ] If you offered to cook for your
date instead of going to a takeaway,
that would be a stop, bro. You got brain
damage. Like, there's no way you just
wrote that. You can't be that much of a
downy. Yeah. Yeah. Because when you just
meet someone, you be like, "Oh yeah,
come to my house. I'll cook for you."
That doesn't give off [ __ ] murderer
vibes, does it, mate? You would sound
like a complete and utter murderer.
That is [ __ ]
weird when you when you meet somebody
the first time. What the [ __ ] And she
was actually nice. She kept offering me,
"Oh, no. I want to pay some. I want to
pay some. I want to pay some. I feel
bad." I said, "Don't worry about it." You
know? And it kind of reminded me of USA,
is it? You know, you got some fat
stinking [ __ ] American, right?
Thinking that the world owes her
something, not offering money because
she gave her skank ass [ __ ] She thinks
that, oh, she doesn't have to pay for
[ __ ] food. And then you got somebody
who's way better looking than know in every other
way offer and they're from a third world
country. It's [ __ ] madness, isn't it,
mate? I think them two examples right there.
It tells you all you need to know, bro. It's just
madness. It's absolute
madness. Yeah. I can't stand westernized women, bro. [Music]
Yeah, you have no friends. Go away, self
projector. No self projecting on my
channel again. You've got me confused
with yourself. You've got no friends. I
saw you people on YouTube uh yesterday
as well. LJ was on YouTube the whole
day, sat by himself. And I know this
because just before I went out, just
before I went out, I saw it and then
when I come back, I saw it. Yeah. These
people talk about themselves. No
friends, no money. That's literally
them. I was out yesterday with These
people are sat on YouTube every day,
bro. Come on. You've seen it. They show
their life every day. They show their
life every [ __ ] day on
YouTube. On YouTube. They show their
lives every day, bro. [ __ ] hell. They
show us what they're about. Come on,
man. These people have been talking
about themselves [ __ ] for donkeys
years. Everything they say is about their own
lives. You know, it's weird, isn't it? But
yeah, and you know that these people
ain't got no life experience, Stephen
Howard, and they don't have a clue about
women or anything because if anyone ever
dealt with women, they would actually
know what most of them are actually
like. The make believe boyfriends, the
attitude, the piss taken. Anyone that's
got life experience would know this
[ __ ] Oh, we went to the
park. Me and the date went on a went to the park. Um, yeah. Nando
Park. It's just so nice spending time
with someone, you know, that's not a
complete [ __ ] you know.
Yeah. Yeah. It must be it must be. It's
nice, you know. Got a lot of walking
though. I'm just about ready for my
nesticles. Oh, it wasn't a free day,
bro. I went to Nando. I think I spent
about £40 today, but it's not too bad.
Yeah, cuz obviously I'm trying to make a
good impression because I'm done for a
month now anyways. So,
yeah, but the [ __ ] them trying to
charge you to get in
clubs. Yeah, it's madness.
Yeah. Yeah. Madness,
man. Yeah. They ain't got a life, man.
You know, when I was at my mom's Yeah. I
clicked on L's thing. I was watch I was
watching for two seconds. He was sat on
YouTube all by himself. No friends, no
life, no nothing. Like, do you know what
I done today, bro? These people can
never do that. Go out, go on a date, go
get some food. They're just sat on
YouTube all day talking about
themselves. It's mad if you actually
think, oh, none of these people on
YouTube are doing this. They're sat on
YouTube. I went out with a friend
yesterday as well. It was good,
bro. That's why uh LJ always says, "I
have no friends." Cuz he's talking about
himself. I have lots of friends.
Yeah. Yeah. The duck watching is but we
went to Nando and
stuff. I think I might be in love
again. I think I might definitely be in
love again, mate. Oh no, not this [ __ ]
again. No, I can't do, bro. I can't do I
can't do. I'll try not to.
You are so skinny. You waited until
benefit day to go. You're talking about
yourself. Yeah, I waited for benefit
day. Oh, bro. You see what I'm saying,
Stephen? Now, these people don't know
anything, you know, on on benefit day.
Didn't you say my benefit day was last
week? Oh, yeah. I'm waiting for my what?
So, benefit day is every week, mate. I
[ __ ] wish I got [ __ ] benefits
every [ __ ] week. You're talking about
yourself again, mate. Go do it on another
channel. Go do it on my channel, you little
self-reflector. I waited to benefit day.
Listen to what you're saying, bro. Benefits. Hey,
maximum a,000 to,500 a month. That's not
enough for my lifestyle. So, yeah, I'm
waiting for benefit day. Yeah, I've gone
out the past three days. You said my
benefit day was last week, mate. It's
not enough for my
lifestyle. My benefit day. Did I spend
£400? Did I spend £400? Didn't I spend
money today? Did I spend money
yesterday? Did I lose £300 last week?
You get must be getting a lot of money
in benefits, is it, Stephen Howard,
mate? You must be getting a lot of
[ __ ] money in on benefits. If you're
getting benefit money every [ __ ]
week, mate, I got a bit of fun change
again. I'll show you just to piss you
off. Yep. Benefit day.
Benefit day. Benefit day. Benefit day.
Get some more money today. Yeah, I live on benefits,
bro. Yeah, I live on
benefits. Spent over 400 the other day.
Spent money yesterday. Spent money
today, but I'm on benefits. How much is
this benefit is this benefit [ __ ] paying,
bro? How much is this benefit [ __ ] paying?
This is like call the shop bunny, you know.
Hey, how much is this benefit [ __ ]
paying, man? I want in on it, lad. If
someone's getting getting money, bro,
I'm missing, you know? I want to
know, dude. That's madness. One sec.
Someone's a voice now.
Sorry about that,
bro. Yeah, these people talk about
themselves. Stephen, who's the people
that are sat on YouTube every day? These
people are sat on YouTube all day, every day.
Yeah, sorry. I just had to text
someone talking about yourself
again. Bro, these people are [ __ ] sucks.
Spastics, bro. It's unbelievable,
man. These people are proper
spastics. Yeah, proper spastics,
bro. They talk about themselves every day, mate.
Yeah. Yeah. She just text back. I just messaged uh bro Yeah,
bro. That would go crazy if I proper
pulled. Bro, I proper pulled about a million
times. I proper pulled about a million
times. What you What are you talking
about, bro? If I have proper pulled I
have proper pulled a million times.
Yeah, she messaged back as well.
So, that's how I know that the other
person was a time waster. There's no way
you claim you didn't feel the vibe. Time
waster. Absolute time waster.
But you don't feel the vibe when I know
that I'm decent looking. I know how to
dress, bro. I know how to conduct
myself. [ __ ] off. Just westernized
[ __ ] mate. I'm just going to start
targeting third world uh people from
third world countries now.
Yeah. Yeah. That's what I want to start doing now.
Yeah, I did go to see. That's your only
option. Poor woman. You've never been
with a You've never been with a You've
never even been with a
woman. Yeah. Anyways, we're not having negative
um people on my channel, negative
haters. So, [ __ ] yourself. Sorry,
bro. Charles. Yeah, might be wild,
but Stitch is a Disney film. Sorry, I'm
a bit [ __ ] mate. I got some cookie
dough ice cream, Steven Howard. I was
going to start having it once every two
weeks so I don't get fat like these
people. Fat and ugly. But um I couldn't
help myself today. Yeah. Yeah.
I almost pooed myself today. Steven Howard.
Yep. She's slim. She's got nice hair. Yeah. Yeah, she's
nice. Cuz I had Nando and I almost didn't
um make it home in time.
Do you remember Fard? If you don't like
Sher Cole, you're
gay. You little copycat. Copycat.
Copycat. You know you are. You little
copycat. Copycat. Copycat.
Copycat. That is
copying. Trying to fit in with
society. That is proper
copying. Proper proper proper
copying. Think how many women you see on the street,
right? Whether people ever been accused
of being gay or someone not being their
type unless their name was Shel Carl.
That's how it's
copying. People do that to copy each other. ever.
I've actually had three dates from that
[ __ ] um club
now. There's one place I've never had a
date. It's this sort of bar in Soho.
It's impossible, bro. They're all
[ __ ] That's the only place I've never had a
date. I find some areas are easier than
others, but there's some places I'd never
Yeah, I don't know if this
Yeah, it's a stupid name, bro. Anyways,
I'm going to be talking to this woman.
So, I'll be back later, bro. Or
tomorrow. I'll be back later. Or tomorrow, bro.