Yep. Just had a lovely G.
Yeah. See what these little
repeating [ __ ] mongos are saying there. of beautiful.
Oh my say it's [ __ ]
rained. It's [ __ ] raining is
it? It's raining bro. That's no
good. Spider-Man mother
Why is it
Yeah, I'm not going out today even
though it's very tempting. I got nothing to
lose and Saturday or Saturday, but I
want to take a break from it, you know. some
point. Yeah. So, it means I have to get
my haircut again as well.
Yep. I told you we're not reacting to
these videos anymore.
So we got a lot of self-reflectors come
on my channel this YouTube is sorry. So
yeah, I wonder what I wonder if any like
I wonder if one day though would
um half an hour. Yeah, it's about an
hour and a
half. I would go out today, but the
weather's no good, bro. And it's
Thursday and I want to take a break from
it as well for other things to be doing.
So even though I'm in a fairly standard
mood, but nah, I can't be asked, bro.
Yeah, go get a low fade and that. But
no, not today,
bro. It's literally an hour and a half,
mate. It's [ __ ] long. Sat for an hour
and a half, right?
Now, I wonder if these self-reflective
will ever come out with new things, but
your skin all the all of the things they
themselves. I wonder if one day, maybe
one day, they'll just come out with new
sayings, but they can't cuz they're
disabled. So, but like I said, we don't
we don't um react to these weirdos no
more on my
channel. These self-reflectors, they
keep making new accounts and getting
banned. We don't we're not off, mate.
They're the ones that are sat on YouTube
every day projecting, not us.
Done. Yeah. Sitting on that chair for an
hour [ __ ] off. It's long. And I got
to get my eyebrows done as well.
So, not today. Not tomorrow. Need a break from
it. I need a break from it all,
lad. One second. Hold on. Yeah, basically.
So, Charlie, what say happened to my mama?
Charlie, what was the story that
happened to my mama?
The ladies are waiting for you. Said the Indonesian
creep. Yeah, man. I said that Indonesian
creep basically. Huh? Yeah, the ladies
are waiting for you. Yeah. Well, they're
not going anywhere, mate. In London
every Saturday. They're not going
anywhere. So, they have to wait
longer. Yeah, that Indonesian
creep. He cramps my style. I just go out
and send it by myself. [ __ ] it. See, if
you're not with the right kind of
person, they actually make you look bad.
You know what I'm saying? They actually
make you look bad. You need somebody
that's the same as
you. Like this guy last week, he was a
bit of a tit. He's a good guy. He's a
good friend and that, but he's you
really want to be doing this stuff like by
yourself. I mean, Q was okay to go out
with, but he's too laidback. He's
normal. He's not embarrassing, but he's
too laidback, man. I'm
Yeah. Oh, I saw that self-reflecting person coming
again. Yeah, bro.
I was speaking to some more people on
Reddit. You never know your luck, do
you, Charlie? You never know your
luck. Never know your
luck. But just make sure these weirdos
never find them. Obviously, Instagram's
out question. Saying that I need to make
I actually do need to make a new
Instagram. I don't even feel like
there's a point of even going on my new
YouTube channel. Let these people be
obsessed. let them make videos. They're
only tormenting themselves. They're not
bothering no one else. So, I feel like
in a way you should just just let them
crack off. You know what I'm saying?
That's that's what I think and just post
gambling videos on here or whatever. But
I feel like you you
know maybe have another channel for the
approaches. Just don't record the
approaches. I don't need to record
approaches anymore. I've got enough
recorded. But these people are going to
look back one day and then they're going
to look how upset they've been with
Peter Belly and they've wasted their
life on me.
But did they really appointed actually
even what I'm saying? Oh my
god. I'm saying music.
So I mean all of the things that all the
self-p projection things they've said
they've said it a million times before
lad you know skin their skin disabled
they're disabled like all they will
really do all day is talk about
themselves like they can't even roast
anyone and that's the thing is that they
can't even roast anyone to save their
life and that's the thing they can't even roast
you just let them crack on me you know
being obsessed every day on YouTube.
It's nothing really, bro. I just went to
Gregs and got a bacon and cheese wrap.
I'm in a send it kind of mood today. I
feel I could actually approach any [ __ ]
in this shopping center, but I'm taking
a break off of it. So, yeah, I just went to
Greg's. Yeah, the first person that come
on my channel was a
self-reflector. Yeah, back to days you
go. You little self-reflector.
Uh, no. I moved for a while, bro.
Nah, must be not playing Frankie and
uh playing Frankie and playing
um roulette. Can't remember the last
time I played live roulette. [ __ ] ages
ago. Cuz I just realized, like I said,
there's no money in the
industry. I'll try in the pub again at
some point. I'll put 40 in one machine,
40 in another, and we'll see if we get
any uh any bonuses and [ __ ] I think
that would be a good video. 40 pound
and£40. What do you
think? Okay with you,
boss. There's no there's no money in the industry anymore.
Nah, I can't I can't believe Martin
didn't score though um on Tuesday. I
could believe that. [ __ ] hell. It was
looking so good as well.
That that was looking so [ __ ] good as
well. Yeah, that was looking good,
bro. That was looking very
good. I wonder if I'd have Do you know
what? Yeah, my dream has always been to
get three both teams to score and I
haven't had it
yet. Haven't had it yet. Even I've never
had three. Never had three. Cuz when I
see it with three, I don't do three
teams because I feel like three is just
too much and then it just becomes mug's
game. What's the point of doing three
teams? You know what I mean? Like what's
the point of doing three teams,
bro? It's too much.
No, three teams is too much
now. It's too much, bro. Oh, no. I was
actually thinking of betting on the
Scottish league on Saturday actually cuz
Scottish has a lot of goals. Yeah, the
Scottish they have a lot of
goals. Yeah, they have a lot of goals in
the Scottish Scottish
league. Yeah, they do. I remember
winning a few times on that. But it's
all just a mugs game really, isn't
it? It's just not even worth betting, is it? Really?
Unless you're in a pub.
Yeah. Just put £40 on two machines or 30
on two machines. See if you get a
bonus. See if you can you can rinse them
machines in the
pubs. See different machines. There's
no, you know, wouldn't it be cap to 100 then? Would it?
Yeah, it is a Mugs game though. It's
better than football. It is a Mugs game
because a it's rigged. It is of course
it's a Mugs game. If it wasn't a Mug's
game, they wouldn't exist. There
wouldn't be billion pound
companies. No, it is a Mugs
game. It is. It
is. Of course it is. Where has gambling
ever got you? Think about it. Where has
gambling ever got you? Think about it.
Nowhere. It's got you nowhere in life.
So what? How is it not a mugs game?
That's the way it's gave you mood swings
and [ __ ] all sorts. So it is a mugs
game and and the thing is there's no
money in the industry anymore. You can't win online.
The book is you can't win. [ __ ] the
only thing you can win on is football
bets and and an actual physical
casino. No, mate. I was I was getting
enough money to already be doing that. I
was already getting enough money to be doing
that. You know, I was already stacking
money to already get all of that stuff.
But even still, the industry is dead.
Unless you can go to a physical casino,
the industry is dead.
like it's dead unless you go to an
actual phys like honestly.
Yeah. I never used to moan and say the
casinos was rigged when I'd lose in the
physical ones. I'd be like, well, you
can't really say that cuz you won
thousands and you won thousands. With
that one, you can't really say it is.
Even though it probably is, but not
compared to online. I mean, bro, you've
you've rinsed these [ __ ] almost every
week. You know, you can't moan really
when you lose. But it did give me boost wins, though.
you know, I just would go and have a
drink up the road or somewhere, but the
only thing you can really win win on is land
base. That's the
only that's the only only thing you can
actually win on. Or maybe like the pubs arcades
dead. You can't there's no money in the
industry no more.
And since they and since they turn and
and since they changed the
terminals since they swapped over the
um you know you you can't even [ __ ]
get a bonus on the [ __ ]
So and I can never get into land base anymore.
Maybe if you tried three, four years.
Eh, I wonder I wonder I wonder if you
tried what what do you reckon would
happen if you tried to go to the hippodrome
again? And how did money get me women? I
got I got women my [ __ ]
self. Unless you mean
escorts, but either way doesn't really
matter, does it?
It's a tricky one,
man. But I'm going to when I do a
football on Saturday, I'm just going to
put 20 pound on it and try and get like
a both teams to score. No
draw or Yeah. three teams, both teams to
score. I don't [ __ ] know. Something like
that. I know. I'm [ __ ] bro. Hippo
drone. They know me straight away. If
they let me in, I'm done. They they kick
me out. I used to love going to that
place after drinking, bro. Or before
drinking. Oh my god. The world was your
oyster, mate. You're in central London.
Loads of places to drink, loads of approaching
opportunities, banging escort. Like so
many opportunities, bro. When you have
that kind of money in your [ __ ] hand,
know? It's a shame. It
is. You can't get in there
anymore. It's a shame. A crying
What? Maybe I'll go not him again? I don't
know. What do you think, Charlie? Do you
reckon eventually they'd let you back in?
How is it face recognition for bored
them years ago
though? Cuz I look different than I did years
ago. Probably. Man, there's loads of
people that look like me in
London. As much as I hate London, I love
London at the same
time. I don't know. I don't know how
they done that. I don't know how they
So I have to get used to life. No
gambling. Just have to stop gamble forever.
Yeah, they could get banned from one
casino. How long do you reckon it would
take for them to let me back in? But
funny enough, you know, the Horizon's
casino, I I rinsed them before they ban
me. So, I was already banned for all the
others. They let me in the Horizons.
They let me in the horizons, right? And
then when I tried to go and I I rinsed
them and then when I tried to go back,
that's when they didn't let me in. The
the alarm went off. But I already rinsed
them, bro. I put six I was I was I think
I was like4 60 in. I was down to my last
60. I got to
£1,100. They didn't want to pay, bro. Trust me.
They them [ __ ] did not want to pay.
So, but they had no choice. So, yeah.
Then when I tried to go back in Glow, I
can't get in. I've not ever been to a
GL. I've not been to a Glosser since I
was 18, no 19 when I was in Birmingham.
But I just walked through it.
I don't know,
bro. It's strange, isn't it? [Music]
Yeah. So, I don't know what to do today.
Probably get KFC cuz uh it's [Music]
um what is
it? It's [ __ ] cold outside, raining,
bro. So drinking and an option.
I know, bro. This is what it is with
these people of this community, bro.
They're just jobless little fat skinned
little mongos that just self- affect
their life on the view. That's literally
all they are. Like most these people
just look like JB Thompson and they
found power in hiding behind the
keyboard. They feel powerful. They Yeah.
They tell you to get a job, but they
don't they don't have a job themselves.
They tell you that your skin you got
more money than them. It's madness. And
like you said, bro, do you remember that
time I told these people that I worked in Foot
Locker. Yeah. And then they they called
up every single Foot Locker in the area
to try and get me sacked. So what's the
point of telling people to get a job
then? I think what it is with these
people is they hate anyone having money
and they hate anyone having a life. And
that's what they do every sing and this
is why they do what they do every day
because they hate people not being like
them skin on benefits. So instead of [ __ ] telling
um they just call themselves instead of
telling giving themselves this
advice, they give you this advice. One set.
on. Sorry, bro. Morning,
bro. Yeah. So, they tell you to get a job. Um, yeah.
Yeah, bro. His name's not Grey. His name
is Daniel. Did you know this [ __ ] bro? Come on
now. Bro, you know what I'm saying?
Yeah. I'm Steven
Howard. Oh, that's funny, bro.
Uh was looking at USA's pictures
yesterday. Uh bless you. I was talking
to about um sorry know my friend on
Instagram a bit mad. Just wanted to pop
on and say
hi. But yeah, it's funny. They tell
people to get a job and then when you
get a job they try to make you lose your job.
I know. It's funny, isn't
it? Uh, I know, man. They're just
self-reflectors. These self-reflectors
don't bother me no more, Greasy. I said
there's no point in me going on my main
channel. Well, they never bothered me to
begin with, to be honest. They're just
repeaters, but I just said that there's
no point in me going on my other channel
now. I might as well just stay on this
channel because it's just the same
bastics every day anyway, isn't it? So,
same up people. So, yeah, man.
Yeah. Go a bit, bro. Just finishing this copper [ __ ]
I do feel like going out today and getting pissed
off, but I'm not going to. I'm being
good. I'm being very good.
pretty much, man. I mean, I could go out
and send it today, but that means get my
hair done and go and get my clothes and
it's just not working, bro. I'd rather
just chill today.
Yeah, man. Anyways, I'm going, bro. I'll
be back. Maybe later. Who knows? [ __ ]
knows, bro. But most