Oh my god, bro. One
second. [ __ ] hell, bro. This is some
funny [ __ ] I just see on Timmy's
channel. He's actually being
serious. Imagine, bro, this is how I know.
Yeah, these people in this community are actually like proper
skin. We can do free tabs. That's
actually going to be interesting. This
is how you know these people in this
community are [ __ ] skimp as [ __ ]
300. He's showing 300 [ __ ]
pound. Oh my [ __ ] god, bro.
He's I'm kind of tempted to show him
[ __ ] money, but I'm not even joking.
I'm tempted to show him [ __ ]
money. A [ __ ] idiot
back. 300 [ __ ] pound.
100 [ __ ] pound, bro.
Oh my god. Imagine showing, bro. My trip
to the [ __ ] shopping mall cost
[ __ ] more than that. [ __ ] £300. He's showing
£310. Oh my [ __ ] god. This guy is a [ __ ] joke,
bro. He is a joke.
Why is he showing
£310? What a [ __ ] idiot. But I might
just go to the
um ATM and start embarrassing these
people again, bro. Really?
Really? Your life, bro? Honestly.
[ __ ] 300. What the [ __ ] bro? He's an idiot.
Absolute [ __ ] cool.
Bro, he's an idiot, man. One
sec. £3 fucking10. That is nothing, man.
I spent more than that in the shopping
mall. Yeah, I lost £300 last week as well.
Bro, he's older than me and I've got
more than him. And even consider to some
people what I've got is actually [ __ ]
£310, bro. I might take the trip. I
might take a trip to the ATM and start
embarrassing these people again with a
money game. Semi- tempted, you know,
even though I said I weren't going to
show money again. I'm kind of
tempted, you know. Aren't you kind of tempted?
own these people again, bro. Like I
always do, you know.
Yeah, it's embarrassing, bro. It really is. Really? 300
lb. Oh my god.
[ __ ] Try go to the ATM and embarrass him. [Music]
tempted, you know. Tempted.
Yeah. What is it with this community
though and uh talking about money
and none of them even leave their
[ __ ] house. So, I don't understand
this disabled place if I'm honest.
Yeah. Crazy, is it?
might go to the
ATM. Yeah, I might be.
Yeah, I might do it, you know.