Sorry, man. I'm just on this [ __ ]
Reddit [ __ ] Yeah, 300 quid is nothing, man.
I was going to [ __ ]
um I was going to [ __ ]
um go to the [ __ ] point and withdraw
a load of money and
just there's no
point. Look at this woman on [ __ ]
Reddit trying to say, "Oh, you'd have a
better chance in pubs and clubs." just
because you have a better chance in pubs
and clubs because the do you know this
is what these people don't understand
right the these women right you know how
they say oh we've had bad experiences no
and we've gone on dates and
no and yeah that's happened but do you
re do you realize why it doesn't bother
you is because you don't have to put any
effort into it you don't need to go
around the country approaching
approaching approaching putting effort
in and then when it doesn't go your way
you have to start all over again. That's
why it doesn't affect you when a date
does not go your way. You know there's a
big [ __ ] difference. There's a
massive massive massive
difference. You know what I'm saying to
you, bro? It's like a kid in a candy
shop. You know, if two people don't
match, they just find somebody else to
go on a date with. Whereas whereas you
or any any other most men, they'd have
to keep approaching and approaching and
approaching to then get one again. You know, [Laughter]
understand try again but
uh trying to give me advice. Trying to
tell me to go to a [ __ ] to go to a
rave. As a woman, I put ridiculous
amount of effort. Oh, no you don't. into
how I look. I come across to people. But
you make effort, mate. You You put
effort into how you look is for
yourself. That's not for dating. I I
gym. I eat well. I look after my skin.
That's what you should be doing anyways.
always make sure I dress well and do
what I need to do to feel attractive.
Everyone should be doing that anyways.
This is what a lot of pe women go
through. Effort goes a long way and it's
very attractive to women. Put more
effort into yourself. Try a new
environment. Start a raving. No, no, no.
You're putting into effort into yourself
for yourself. But you don't need to put effort into
dating. That's the difference. That's
the big big [ __ ] difference.
You know, you know what I'm saying,
bro? These people on Reddit piss me off.
They have no clue about about dating,
bro. It that's what pisses me off. You
know, if these women done 1% of what you
done, it would [ __ ] kill them. They
just sit there getting what they want
any day, whenever they want, bro. Do you
know what I'm saying? You know what? I'm
going to go out this week, bro. [ __ ]
this. I'm going to I'm going to end up
just giving up for a month
again. You know what I'm
saying? Cuz I was listening to Ant-Man
properly, bro, and he was saying like
it's just going to keep being the same
result. you know, you continue to try to
to try in this country, it's just going
to be the same result. The only way it's
going to change is if you leave, which
I'm leaving in four
weeks, but he says that that's the only
way this is going to change. You
know, really, it is. He said if
something was going to miraculously
change, it would have by
now. The truth, it is honestly the
truth. what he's
saying. It pisses me off, bro. I'm going
to give up for a [ __ ] thing
again. It pisses me off, bro. I don't
even like talking about it. I don't like
even getting involved with this [ __ ]
anymore, bro. It's just annoying, you know?
Mate, I'll find something else to
do. Cuz all you're going to do is is get
bad experiences again and again and
again and again and again and again and
again and again. And it's never going to
end. It's never ever going to end until
you leave. Trust me, it won't. It
won't. A woman trying to give me [ __ ] advice.
You know, I was getting some sick
thoughts earlier. I'm not even going to
tell you what it was. Not anything like
Ant-Man, but I was getting some mad sick
thoughts. Bro, this is why I don't like
getting into this dating thing anymore.
You know, cuz it it turns you into a
complete different person. This is what I'm
saying. Trying to tell me, "Oh, you need
to put effort, mate. I've done more than
anybody in the [ __ ] world.
It's just [ __ ] annoying, bro. And
I'll just end up going out and just
doing someone in. Like, I'm not even I'm
not even joking,
bro. You know, it's not
funny. Yeah, bro. Literally. Yeah. This
is why I don't want to get involved with
this [ __ ] anymore, this dating thing
anymore. It's [ __ ]
annoying. You know what I'm saying, bro? It's
annoying. These women don't have no clue
why they sat there giving advice when
they have had everything given to them
on a silver [ __ ]
spoon. Everything given to them on a
[ __ ] silver spoon and they're trying
to sat there giving you advice. What?
Because they take care of their
appearance. That's what everyone should
be doing anyways for themselves. But
you've never had to put effort into getting
dates. You've never ever had to put
effort into dating ever. So stop giving me advice. You
know they Bro, I'm I'm so done with
talking about this now. [Laughter] So
Yeah. Yeah. I'm starting to
like Yeah, bro. You know what I
mean? Yeah. I'd rather stay, but I'd
rather I'd rather sit there. I know
you're trolling and that in it. And I
don't mind when someone's blatantly
trolling, but I'd rather sit in and and
be bored because I don't see it as
boredom, but I see it as a break. See,
with you, you see it as boredom because
you don't do this [ __ ] But with me,
it's a break. And I like having a break.
It's like trying to recover from an
injury. You might think, "Oh, yeah,
lying down playing a game is boring."
But having that break and not hearing
about Makebelie Boyfriends is [ __ ]
lovely for at least a month. That's why
it doesn't get bor That's why it don't
get boring. That's literally why it
doesn't get boring because it's the
break that you're having from it all.
Does that even make
sense? And it doesn't matter if these
people get ghosted or rejected or no no
no no because they can just move on to the next
person. You have to approach a million people
to to even get somebody to go out with
you and [ __ ] Sir, you know what I'm saying,
bro? I'm gone in four weeks anyway, so I
got to give a
[ __ ] Tell me to go to a bar club.
So yeah, I'm not doing this, bro. I ain't doing
this. It's not about money. It's not
even about money. Saving money cuz
you're not even saving that much money
by not going out. But it's
just you know how it's going to end.
It's like what Ant-Man says. You know
how it's going to end. [Laughter]
You know what I'm saying, bro?
I got an alo in my [ __ ] mouth.
Yeah. Take off this [ __ ] bro. Yeah. I
can't do more than a week.
Yeah. It's like, you know,
It's like when they only reply to
negativity. It's like when they only
reply to negative messages. That should
be like the red flag right
there. You know, when they only reply to
negativity, that's proper sticking ahead.
You know what I'm
saying? I have to always say about a
million times, lad. I will be in I will
be home all day. Watch me. I was in for
a month because of this
[ __ ] Yeah, there is four. I I already
took a four week
break when I went out Thursday. I was in for a
month. No, it's definitely definitely
another four week break, bro. But I'm
going to Thailand in four weeks. So, but
I'm going to go out this week, next
week, week after.
Done. I I'll do it, bro. Watch
me. I said that to other people. But I
didn't believe me because it there's no
point you going out and just dealing
with the same [ __ ] over and over and again. You
know, there's no point you dealing with
the same [ __ ] over and over and over and
again. Only one or three things is going
to happen. It ain't ever changing. Trust
me, this country will never change with
these shitty [ __ ] women in it, mate.
So, but I don't want to talk about it
anymore cuz it's a negative. As much as
people on Reddit don't want to keep
admitting it's negative and I would just
end up going out and just hurting
someone, bro. You know what I'm
saying? I don't want that, bro, cuz I
don't want anything to do with it
anymore, bro. But I know I've got a temper. So
simple. You know what I'm saying, bro? I
know my temper. That's why I stay away from these things. You
know, I'm done with this conversation.
and stop typing to
me. For [ __ ]
sake, stop texting me. It's so annoying.
All you're going to do is just keep
[ __ ] depending women just like most
people do. Just stop [ __ ] texting me. It's [ __ ]
annoying. Stop [ __ ] texting me talking
[ __ ] You know what I'm saying? [Laughter]
Yeah. Don't know what I'm saying, bro.
It's [ __ ] annoying. Stop [ __ ]
texting me, man.
[ __ ] annoying as [ __ ] You
know, you know, when I lost money
gambling last week, I weren't even
pissed off. You know, I was pissed off
for like five minutes and I was like,
"Whatever." You know what I'm saying?
That not even worth it,
mate. I actually hate him, bro. Like,
you think Antman's were I actually hate
them. And it's not this person I went on
a date with. I literally hate them.
Yeah. Oh yeah, bro.
No wonder I'm so [ __ ] negative. If
all you've had is negative
experience, but Saturday as well, bro, you
know? Nah, because I've never been shown
different. See, when you're not shown
different, it's all you know, you know.
It's like when you go up to It's like,
you know what I'm saying?
Do you know what I'm
saying? Yeah. For your mindset to
change, you need better
experiences. You know, it's all you. You
know what I'm saying? And if women were
truly different, then you we wouldn't be
having this conversation.
You know what I'm saying? We wouldn't be
having we would not be
having we would not be having this
conversation. People can tell you what
they want until the cows come home. Oh,
women are different. Oh, you've not met
all women. They can say all of that
stuff, but at the end of the day, bro,
we wouldn't still be having this
conversation, you know.
Um, we wouldn't be having this
conversation cuz you would have been
proven wrong a long time ago. Okay.
Yeah. Sorry about that.
Yeah. In this country. Yeah, 100%, bro.
100 1 million% I have. That's exactly
why I'm not going out this
week. Cuz it's just going to be the
same. It's just going to be the same
[ __ ] You know what I'm saying? I can't
stand him. I'm starting to hate them
again. And it was from the other day,
bro. So, yeah. I definitely definitely
have. And I gave up anyways. It's just I
hadn't been out for a month.
I actually hate them like worse than
Ant-Man. Like you don't understand, bro.
I've done See, this guy moans, but he's
not tried more than I have. 1% more than
I have. I hate them with a
passion. Like, you really don't understand, you
know? I can't stand him. I hate them.
Like, you really don't understand, bro.
Like, you really really don't
understand. I hate them. I hate the the everything about
them. You know, why do you think I was
so anti them for like a for like a whole
um month and I still am anti them? You
know what I'm saying? You know, the
reason I went out Saturday is cuz my
friends wanted me to go out.
I felt like [ __ ] but I wanted to stay
in. You know what I'm
saying? And I know I'm right. As
illusual as that sounds, I know I'm right.
Because if I didn't think I was right, I
wouldn't be on here saying it if I
thought I was
wrong. You know, we've seen the
evidence. Cactus, evidence don't lie. Videos don't lie, you
know, because what what what what now?
go out on the street and do it all over
again. Get the same old thing all over
again. I'm not doing that. I'm not doing
that. I shouldn't have to do that. And
women don't do that. So, you know, they
don't have to do
that. They don't have to do any of that
stuff. Do you understand?
You know what I'm saying? You
know, I have dates every day of the [ __ ]
week. Nasty mood swings again, bro.
All of it is a catch
22. I swear to God if somebody tells me
they've got a boyfriend one more time, I
will throttle them,
mate. Like, I'm not even joking, bro.
That's why there's just no point in me
even going out, mate. I'm telling you.
And all people do is just defend women.
So there's no point even having a debate
about it, bro. It's just boring
combo. They just defend women. So
there's no point you
even there's no point you even having um
like a debate about
it. That's what I'm saying. Bro, I
[ __ ] hate him,
bro. It's not about her. It's not even
her. Nothing to do with her. It's It's
It's an amalgamation of
things. It's not one, two. It's just an
amalgamation of things.
cuz the only people that can change your
mind is them. You understand, Cactus?
The only people that can change your
mind is is
them by like better experiences and stuff.
They're the only people that can change
your mind. Talk is cheap. Actions speak
louder than words. Words they can say,
they're not all the same. Blah blah blah
blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah
blah blah blah blah blah. That doesn't
mean anything. You unless you see it for yourself. I'm
saying. Yeah, man's getting old,
bro. Yeah, man. I probably just stay in
bed tomorrow, bro. Probably put you into a depression again.
Yeah. Got a taste of what it was like a
month later again. And I'm not liking it.
You know what I'm
saying? Yeah. Anyways, bro.
Yeah. We live, we get bad experiences, then we die. Yeah. It's
madness. We live, we get bad
experiences, then we
die. It's [ __ ] madness, is
it? There's no combat women dead as well.
So, back to these mood swings
again. This is all because of dating.
All because of dating women. This is
again this is all cuz of dating
again. You just go around and around in
circles. You just go around and around in
circles. Never ends, bro. Never
ends. Hopefully, I go to sleep today. I don't wake
up. I don't want to be thinking about
this again. Uh when I wake up, bro. That's
[ __ ] Well, I could just fall asleep for
a year and then
just not wake
up. How long is this going to keep
happening for, bro? Don't say Yeah,
man. I'm getting some serious serious
mood swings, bro. It's not even a [ __ ]
joke. It's not even a [ __ ] joke, bro.
Anyways, I'll be gone. I hope I don't wake up.