They won't let me [ __ ] go [ __ ] Oh
man, how do I'm still out here about five or
six? I haven't I haven't done any since
I've been drinking to be
fair. Yeah, I haven't done any since
I've been drinking.
That's good. Since I've been drinking,
just getting a bit dizzy now. Say [Music]
char. How we doing, man? How we
doing? I [ __ ] sat here just [ __ ]
drunk a burger [ __ ] beer
now. Ain't going good. But night is
still young. Well is still young for the
night yet. But uh
yeah [ __ ] going pretty [ __ ] to be
there. But hopefully the night makes up
for it. Can't see it happening.
So, like I previously previously
said, this has been going on for three
or four [ __ ] years. So, at this
point, uh, expect it to go any
differently, you're [ __ ] delusional.
You know what I'm saying? [ __ ]
delusional, mate. Must be delusional,
man. If you expect anything but [ __ ] If
[ __ ] I've done some sober. Yeah.
Nothing, mate. I've got a boyfriend.
people that were just
unenthusiastic. This time two in the pub
before I started drinking. I'm just
drunk now. This is my second one.
Haven't done any since drinking. And
yeah, just the same
old hopefully later
night. Hopefully later tonight is better. But
yeah, just the same
old. Oh, what a lovely couple walking past,
mate. Same old. say more bro never
change in this
country to expect it to be any different
in this your man don't bro don't
encourage that [ __ ] on my [ __ ]
channel bro don't
don't encourage that [ __ ] on my
channel okay that person actually had a
boyfriend but a boyfriend ain't better
than me bro it doesn't really matter bro
who does who
doesn't run off you know most of the
time they're talking [ __ ] [ __ ]
So, you got two numbers today, bro.
Yeah, I done [ __ ] so many sober, bro.
I even done a two together
sober. But I'm only here for three weeks
and I'm [ __ ] off again, so doesn't really matter,
man. It'll always be the same old, bro.
Always. This country will never change.
But hopefully when it gets a little bit
later, people be more open. Oh yeah, I
spoke to America. She had
attitude attitude problems
problems. And uh yeah, I'll be [ __ ]
tomorrow, but I just go tomorrow. But
yeah, this was my whole this was my
whole sort of point. This is the [ __ ] we
got to go through and do all of this all
over again. It's [ __ ] up,
bro. They have it so easy, bro.
Yeah. Well, obviously I was bored today,
so I had nothing better to do. I'm not
going to spend much money. So, I
thought, why not? But having some food
cooked for me later, so
yeah. And yeah. Okay. This person might
have had a boyfriend. Yeah. But they
could have still been defending you.
Networking and stuff. Okay. Say they did
generally have a
boyfriend, you know, fair enough. Okay.
Say you're telling the truth. You're
right. Okay, cool. But, you know, you
could still be friends with
people. You could be looking for
friends. It's It's not even dating or
numbers working. It's hard nowadays to
even get a conversation out of someone.
Even like trying to get a conversation
out of someone is impossible. in this
city. They're all
NPCs. So unless you met someone when you
was at school or you were lucky at work
or whatever, you're pretty much
[ __ ] to be fair.
Yeah, but you're pretty much screwed.
You're pretty much screwed pretty
much. [ __ ] wavy now.
W it will never change
ever. Have you ever heard a saying, bro? Never
potter. Yeah, that's very uh solid.
So I need to [ __ ] sit down, man. I'm
charging my phone whilst being [ __ ]
live. Like you can't I stand up and try the machine.
I never sit
down. I swear to even get an empty
seat, but you know it is the
same to be fair.
Yeah, we can send
it. Send it [Music]
[ __ ] a chasing [Music] all. Yeah. Yeah, that's
actually hopefully, like I said, when it
gets a bit later.
So, once I'm out of this pub, send it. Yeah. No problem. Yeah. second down
to you know I'm seeing people I just
want to approach but
yeah in the club is the only thing that
can save us today to be fair
if anything. Yeah,
I think that's the only
thing about messages. I wonder where he
is. You shouldn't be telling me to get
the fog people. You know I'm done with that [ __ ]
now. Seems a bit
uh seems a bit too early. Yeah, I've
been sending them sober, bro. I done
quite a few sober,
but nothing, bro. Same
old same old [ __ ] NC's not with it at
all. Same old. Same
old never change.
But sad day. I said I was going to get
three numbers there. Hope it still
happens. Definitely will still
happen. Will definitely still happen.
Even if it takes all [ __ ]
night. You're going to the pub, man.
Come to this pub. Come and join me, bro.
We have some Guinnesses together.
I've done so many sober, bro. Before I even start drinking [ __ ] [Music]
There we go.
Open. There's more people coming out.
It needs to be more busy. When I got
fire, I'm just going to send it. Send
it. Send it. Send it. Send
Send [ __ ] cinema
somewhere. At least
go. That was a deep sip.
So many, bro. Even the one in this pub
sober was start drinking. I had a burger. [Music] on number [ __ ]
dreadful. We will do though. We
definitely will. We have to
Steven got a bag with me still.
It should be
getting should get be getting
busier now. It should be getting busier now. Yeah.
Oh man, what the [ __ ]
want to try and get a date for Saturday with their
luck. A bit of
luck. Let's see how today goes. It's not
looking good. I'm not saying
Now I want to get now spirits but I
can't take spirits but the
hangovers literally [ __ ] me up
spirits. Yeah. No
way. Start. Start.
Start. Start now.
Yeah. I'm just running a little session.
Done about six approaches sober. Same
[ __ ] I've got a boyfriend. I've got a
boyfriend. I haven't even done any drunk
yet. I've already just
started. That's my second third one, I
think. Third one, maybe.
Yeah, just by go by ourself, see what
fish we can catch
today. But nothing so far, but it's all early,
so I think every time you go out, you lose hope,
man. I think you lose hope. Every time
you go out, you lose hope more and more
more to realize it's never going to
change in this country ever.
your boyfriend. Yeah, man. I got it
um maybe two times today. But
yeah, got it twice, I think. Yeah, but
they were sober when they're done.
So, trust me, I'm going to smack it,
bro. Let time go on. I only about six
over I can see people walking past the
part of me just want to jump straight
and go for it. But I'm going to go out
and then come back. [ __ ] that. When I go
out I'll send them on the way to the
club. But it is getting busier now.
Start getting busier now. [ __ ] me. That
was thinking of doing that one there. Straight
off the knees connected. I ain't pick
them. Let's go
see. I just put a door on the street and
send it. But I'm not doing it. But not
now. Trust me, it's going to get very busy.
want to try and get three numbers. Wish me
luck and coach archiving.
Archiving. Very nice, bro. [ __ ] SC
here now. Now this is the time all the
kids are showing go to bed. All the
adults are coming out. So this is a good
thing, isn't it? [Music]
Anyways, I'm going and I'll be back
later. Definitely be back
later. Try and get a coach on the [Music]
street. One sec. Hold on. I'll be back later.