Don't play. Go.
Go clean up and do it.
We smashed them. Smashed them. We
Hey, we both done it. How long we done
with them? 20 minutes. See the Yeah, I
got a date with Huh? I got a date with
her on Wednesday. On where date on
Wednesday. Wednesday, mate. Huh?
[ __ ] Hey, bro. [ __ ] me. Oh, shut up. Fine, bro. I'm dead.
Let me sit down. Let me sit
down. I got three numbers. Yeah,
boy. Three numbers. Get up.
Three numbers. Three numbers. Three
Yeah. I call number Oh,
perfect. Speed it.
I think I'm in love [Laughter]
again. I'm in love [Music]
again. I'm in love.
I'm [ __ ] going
Australia. I'm going
Australia. I said this woman for Australia [ __ ]
time. [ __ ] you [ __ ] [Music]
Australian. I made this woman from Australia. Yeah.
Go. I met this woman. She's from
Australia. She's She's Australian, but she's
tired. Hey, bro.
[ __ ] We're talking for like 20 minutes,
bro. All right, bro. We're talking for about 20
minutes. I'm [ __ ]
dead. I was talking to her for like 20 minutes. [Music]
Are you good? [Music]
She was lame from [ __ ]
Australia, bro. Where was the one you was talking
to? Where is she from? the one using
this [ __ ] B of Australia, man. A
[ __ ] been sending him send I'm
taking mate. I'm [ __ ] Australia,
mate. Hey, I got
number 20 minutes. I'm going Australia.
[ __ ] man. [ __ ]
[ __ ] criy, man. [ __ ] cat.
Backy. I'm going Australia, boss, mate.
I'm going [ __ ]
Australia. We're going Australia
and you're not free,
mate. I got three numbers. I was just
talking to from
Australia. I got three numbers. I b in Australia, mate.
[ __ ] a [ __ ] barbecue. [Music] How many times
you getting it, bro? We're getting
100%. This funny old man, bro. I'm [ __ ]
Qu. Hey [ __ ] cat. Come ony
m Australia. I got this Australian
bird. I think I love her
JJ. I think I love
her J. I got three numbers. I got three
numbers. I got three numbers. I think I love
her. I sent my friend to Thailand. He's
He's been four times in a year. I think
I love her. I love you. Hey, listen. Me
and you go way back. Come on. Come on,
mate. Me and you go way back. We go way
back. Come on, mate. Look at that.
No, come on, man.
Hey, I think so. I'm going, mate. No, I
think so. I'm going mate. I'm going
Australia. Off Thailand. I'm going off.
I'm going Australia. I
understand. I'm going Australia,
mate. Three numbers. I got three
numbers. We ain't shopping. We ain't
giving up. Five. Five of each. Oh, [ __ ] load this. Yeah. Friday as
well. Oh, she weren't having none of it.
She weren't having it for
puppy. Lord, she wasn't having it for
coffee. Lord, she wasn't having it coffee. Oh, it wasn't for me.
Lord Jay, you've never been to Australia.
You've never been Australia and you've
never been to
Asia. You've never been to Australia and
you've never been to Asia and you're 41.
[ __ ] off, man. [Music]
My son Antman has been to Thailand four
times in a
year. He's been a Thailand. Four times in a [Music] year. Anyone
around. Three numbers. Three
numbers. I got three numbers.
You've never been to Asia all day. You
never You've never been to Asia and
you're 41 42. What's going
on? I'm going to freewin. What? That's the only numbers.
Hey, them over there. They're going to definitely be
100%. What you say
Saturday? What you say Saturday? Huh? You got
my We sent it well over there. We sent
it back. We done it.
I bet you. [Music]
Make sure you clock that [ __ ]
ass. Make sure [Music] [Laughter]
I'm in love again. [Music] Love it.
love I'm in love with
these. I'm in love with somebody from
Australia. I'm in love with something from Australia.
I'm in love somebody from
Australia. She's T from Australia,
mate. I'm in love. I really like
you, mate. I'm in love, bro.
It's time for [Music]
trial. I'm going Australia. I'm
Australia. I'm going Australia.
Hey, what did you Wow. [Music] Wow. 7:00. Bye-bye.
I need to provide
to walk away, right? What? [Music]
How are you?
I got three numbers. Three
numbers. I've got three
numbers. Got three numbers. Three [Music] All three. I got
three. I got number. I got it. Yes.
No, mate. No. [Music]
I need to go on the street and approach it. Yeah. [Music] Oh, I want you. on it,
boy. going here. [Music]
I need to go on the street. I need to go [Music]
Man, I was standing up for about half an hour, mate.
I half an hour,
babe. Half an hour,
malf. [ __ ] half an hour. [Music]
I want that one over there. [Music] It's right.
You will never I'm going to go away. I'm
going to go. But if she comes back, I'm
going to do
her. Lord J's never been to Asia.
Listen, Lord J has never been to
Asia. Lord J has never been to
Asia. I'm going to Asia in three weeks.
My boy has been to Asia four times in a year.
Four times of the
year to Asia. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Hey, by the [Music]
way, Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Come on. I want to spend it. [ __ ]
you. That [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] I'm going
to spend it. [Music]
I'm going Australia. I'm going Thailand.
Australia. I'm going Australia.
Thailand. I'm going
Australia. I'm going Australia and
Thailand. [ __ ] watch. I'm going to do it. Australia. Watch.
Yeah. Look at
myself. You ain't got no life for YouTube.
I'm from [ __ ] Australia, mate. She
wanted to get an accent. She wanted to
get an Australian accent. I'll do one
for you. You're [ __ ] from [ __ ]
Australia, mate. [ __ ] quy mate. Qu I
done it for you. How
about there for about half an
hour? Half a [ __ ]
houry, mate. You [ __ ] cy,
mate. How's that? How's that? [Music] [ __ ]
bar. What [ __ ] [ __ ] do this? That's how
they f that's accurate. [Music]
[ __ ] got a [ __ ] bike in a [ __ ]
Barbie, mate. I'm a lion. Is that all the
accent? That's the [ __ ] accent, mate. Yeah.
[ __ ] done a [ __ ] dirty on me, cat.
Yeah, that's the
accent. That's the accent, by the way. Yeah.
Oh, free number. That's what's [ __ ]
going on, man. [Applause] [Music]
You're [ __ ] in a [ __ ] Barbie camps, Max. [Music]
Oh, you [ __ ] want to [ __ ] jump on
a [ __ ] bar, mate. Oh,
greasy. Hey, Grezy. Not a [ __ ]
barbecue champ. [ __ ] Mikey a [ __ ]
Barbie mate. Tell me a good Australian
accent. Tell me a good
accent. You talk about yourself.
Bye-bye. I think I love
her. I think I love her, man. She's on
[ __ ] Australia, man. But she's tired. She's from
She's from [ __ ] Australia, [Music]
mate. From [ __ ] Australia, man. Down
on the cat. Yeah.
[ __ ] I'm going to [ __ ] Australia. Go to [Music] after I Australia. Bye-bye. day.
I got three numbers. I told
you I'm going Australia. Hey, good. I'm
going Australia. Peacef
Australia. Off the tire. I'm going [ __ ] Australia. Oh, mate.
This destroy the [ __ ] noise.
He's just [ __ ]
Hey, open the same ones I put on
it. Oh, [ __ ] me.
I don't think they are. [ __ ] hell. All right.
No. I'm going to [ __ ] go and send
it. I'm going to go [ __ ] send it. Hey
mate, there is no way them were the same [ __ ] people. Oh
[ __ ] mate. I need some WS
here. Oh, [ __ ]
hell. All right.
Oh [ __ ] man. She's doing [ __ ] Hey I don't
know. All right. [Music] Stephen,
let me ask you a question.
Should I go over the process over there?
If you say I'm going to go do
it, I'm going to [ __ ] do it, mate. If
you say yeah, I'm doing it.
If you say yeah, I'm going to do it. [Music]
What's your name?
Where are you from? Whereon?
Huh? London. Liia. did it. So, did you
move for work? Oh, no. I moved here for my
Oh, where do you live in London?
East like where
that's where I
live? 100% 100%. Yeah. Most of people
that I I meet they live in like L or
South or whatever. Yeah. I
definitely What's your plans for today?
Huh? What's your plan for today? I don't
know. My friend right now. Okay. Yeah.
What's your name?
Okay. Well, I'm going to go back and
finish my case. But another
time, can I get a bag of water?
I'll miss you. Really? All
right. None of it,
mate. None of it, mate. I tried so hard.
[ __ ] You won't give her a number.
my tried. I tried. I tried. Oh
my. She lived in the same place as me. [ __ ]
I tried. I tried. I tried. I
tried. I tried, mate.
Yeah. B. Hey, you talking about
yourself? I'll get someone else. Don't
say someone else, but don't worry. There you
go. She me as
well. She lives near me. [Music]
Yeah. [ __ ] She liv as
well, babe. What the [ __ ] [ __ ]
I might do her in the
Tus. I'm going to send it. But
what I go back, I'm going to send
it. I love Aussie. I love Aussie. Easy.
I'm going to [ __ ] this. I'm [ __ ] I'm
going [ __ ] Australia, mate. Going to
[ __ ] I'm [ __ ] going [ __ ]
Australia, mate. How's that an accent for you? Oh god.
Wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait. You want me to say
that? Yeah, I'll give it a
while. Cactus, you want me to give it a
whirl? You want me to give it a whirl?
Yes or no?
If you want me to give it a whirl
there, I give it a whirl. [ __ ] it. Yeah,
I would. You want me to give it a
whirl? Oh, [ __ ] it. I would. Yeah. Excuse
me. I like your tattoo.
What's your name?
Where you from?
Denmark. I've never been to Denmark
before. What brings you to London?
Oh, really? So, do you come to England a lot?
And how long are you here for? again.
I've never been to Denmark. I have
friends in Denmark. It's
good. So, where are you staying in London?
You're rich. It's an expensive area.
Yeah. So rich.
Okay. Yeah, maybe I'll go to Denmark
maybe this year.
So when I go to Denmark, can you show me around? I love
I mean like if I travel all the way to
Denmark, maybe you can show me around.
Yeah. What's that? What do you have?
Huh? Snapchat. Okay, I have you on Santa.
I got a snap. I got a snap. I got a Snapchat. Hey,
no. I got a Snapchat. [Music] people [ __ ] Denmark. I
got I'm picking my moment. I'm picking
moment. Well, what about that one over
there mate? Got one over
there. Got her sub. She had to be
back. Three numbers. One. Oh, [ __ ] me. Over
there. We're doing it. We're doing
it. I love that Aussie Bubbers. That Aussie,
bro. Bro, I'm loving that Ty brother. [Music]
Yeah. I might have to give that one a little
second. I might have to give that one a little love.
I might have to give it a while. I love that. Okay. Byebye. I'm
a dream. I'm a
dream. I'm a dream.
[ __ ] That should be fun.
I'm going to one on the right. Let me go
piss. Let me go piss. Go piss.
I'm going to
dry. I'm going to do that, bro. I'm that. Yeah. [Music]
Yeah, Excuse me. Sorry.
Okay. What's your
name? Stop it. Stop
it. Stop it. Stop and crunch. Nice.
I'm a [ __ ] bastard. Stay in this
coffee, mate. At this rate, mate, I'm
gonna have to get a night
bus. I I'll send you Oh
man. Hey, bro. Do you see me just talk
to that girl over
there? Do you see me just approach
someone over there? Oh, I just went it.
She wasn't having none of
it. Where you from? Yeah.
East where you where you
make your friends. makeup. Makeup
line. I'm [ __ ] mad. I'm a crazy
boss. I'm a crazy
bastard. I'm a [ __ ] crazy. I'm a
[ __ ] I need to go on the streets soon.
I'm going to have to go in the street.
I don't think I I don't even think I got my keys,
bro. Mate, I ain't got no
cheese. I ain't got no cheese. [ __ ]
C. [ __ ] a cat. You want me to [ __ ]
come [ __ ] Australia, mate? I'll come to
Australia. I'm coming Australia.
I'm going to Australia. I'm going. I'm
[ __ ] going, bro. I'm going to Australia. Bob.
Oh my god. Oh my god. Come on.
This of USA Healing. This song reminds me of
USA. I don't know [Music]
why. I want [Music]
[ __ ] America. [ __ ] it. All
right. I got to get some food. That's fine.
watch when I go out on the street.
You're going to see man.
Watch what you see on the street. I'm
going to [ __ ] mad. I'm going
Thailand. I'm going to Thailand in two
weeks. I'm going to Thailand in three [Music]
somewhere. He's never been He's never
been to Thailand. He's never been to
Australia cuz he got no life
experience. He ain't got none. He ain't
got none. He's from a [ __ ] He's never
been to Asia. He's never been
Australia. He's never been there cuz
he's got a life experience.
Hey, ain't good experience. [Applause]
Yeah, as long as I go to Asia, I'm a
happy boy. I'm
happy. Three weeks. I'm there. I'm
there. Three weeks. I'm going. Three
weeks. I'm [ __ ] out of here. I'm out [Music] I'm going
Australia, Bob. I want to go Australia.
I want to go and meet that woman in
Australia when she goes back. I'm going Australia.
Where the [ __ ] are these pants? [Music]
Wow, I'm [ __ ] [Music] Check this. Shut
up. Oh, [ __ ] [Music]
I'm going to try it. [Music]
I learn Australian China. [Music]
There's no one there.
I'm going to say that I like your hair.
What's your name?
Yeah. Peter. Peter. Where you from? Australia. London.
Yeah. Brings you London.
What brings you London? London.
London. Let me guess. Really?
I've got loads of friends been.
Yeah, of course. Yeah. So, how long you
been in London for
here? And how are you finding it?
Really? Yeah. I'm I'm going to Thailand
in three weeks and then from there I'm
gonna go to Australia. [Music]
Um probably like three weeks to be fair.
Yeah. But like by the time you do the
jet lag and stuff like it's fine jet Sydney. Yeah.
Sydney Melbourne to me some friends. Yeah,
I feel like when you go to Australia,
you can't say a week cuz the
deadline three weeks minimum.
It was so hard. Like I came back where I
am. So, do you have any plans to go back
to Australia? Um, not really. I'm just
like struggling working and I think of my heart.
What would you for what? I'm a teacher.
Really? For English, science? Yes.
I'm a teacher. Really? I remember being
when I was younger and I hated it. A
really you don't get a lot of
Australian always seem to be very friendly. Yeah.
How often? How
Our summer is so embarrassing. Like it
was rained for like 3 hours and it's
supposed to be so hot.
I was going to
say one more time.
I didn't have WhatsApp.
I deleted it two months ago. I
had I had your WhatsApp. I'll message
you if you straight up. Yeah. Okay.
phone number. Phone number
My number, mate. Come to me. She's from [ __ ] Australia,
man. She's from [ __ ] Australia, mate.
It's [ __ ] Australia, mate. Oh,
man. All right. Can I get corner,
please? Corner, can you squeeze the line
in there, please? [Music]
I got a [ __ ]
[ __ ] Did you hear it, Stephen? How did
you hear it? Did you hear it?
Tell me you heard it. Tell me you heard
it. Tell me you heard it. Tell me you
heard it. Tell me you heard it. Tell me
you [ __ ] heard it, [Music]
son. Tommy Hood,
[ __ ] [ __ ] Tell me. Tell me you
heard it. Tell me heard it. Tell me
it. [ __ ] heard it. You [ __ ] heard [Applause] [Music]
it. [ __ ] Australia,
mate. A [ __ ] Bobby Tap. Y boy.
I'm about to say I need to go through. I
need to go home. I need to go home.
You better [ __ ]
I got four numbers. I'm [ __ ] out of this.
Yeah, [ __ ] Australia, mate. You're in
a [ __ ] [ __ ] barbecue. How
about four numbers? Four
numbers. Four numbers.
Ricky, you don't know nothing. You're a
[ __ ] mate. I've told you this about
a million times. If you got something
for saying this, say it to my [ __ ]
facial weirdo. You're [ __ ] coward.
Yeah, you're a [ __ ] all
shim. You're [ __ ] sick. I've seen you
coming on other channels. You're nothing
but a [ __ ]
S. Let's go,
boy. Let's go. You're [ __ ] sick. Stop going on
channel. Come and say to my [ __ ]
face. I said I said you can be sober. Yes. I said [ __ ]
Australia. Listen, cactus. Australia is
not approved. Australia is not approved.
It's not approved. Australia is not
approved. Mate, you're a [ __ ] [ __ ]
Come meet me tomorrow. I'll bang you
out. I'll bang you out, bro. You know
what time it is. You ain't about
you. You know what I'm saying?
Mate, Australia is not abroad. [Music]
Yeah. Come on. Get it down.
You get it down. Get
[ __ ] I got four of me and one. [ __ ]
yeah. I'm getting some KFC. I'm getting
[ __ ] I've said it, but I'm f [Applause] [Music]
I'm gonna wake up my friend. Get it down
you. Get it down. [Music]
See you tomorrow.
I want to go. I'm going to go Australia.
I know that time woman from Australia.
Not the north one. The second one. I
love her. I'm going to
Australia. I am [ __ ] going [ __ ]
I'm going Australia. I'm [ __ ] going
[ __ ] down under, mate. That's why I'm
[ __ ] going, Chad.
M. I can't. I'm [ __ ]
knacking, mate. You're unemployed. Bomb.
I got more money than you'll ever get,
Ricky. Mate, listen. Ricky, let me tell
you this. Give me your location. I will
come to you anytime. I will come to you
anytime. Give me your [ __ ] Listen. Do
a video. Show me where you are. I will
[ __ ] send it. Tell me where you are.
I'll come to you. You're a little bum.
You're a little [ __ ] You're a little
[ __ ] boy. You ain't about that life,
I told you a million times. Tell me you
are your [ __ ] I'll slap you up. It will
be real life, bro.
Yeah. Come on, boss. Well, listen. Why
not? Shut up, man. I will [ __ ] wind
your mom up in my bed. How about this,
bro? I'll wipe your mama up.
Wind your mother. I'll wind your mother
in her face. You little [ __ ] [ __ ] of
us. Yeah, I will [ __ ] wind your mama
in your [ __ ] bed. [Music]
Oh, she ain't safe. [Music]
Good day you son. [Music]
Oh where the [ __ ] are these? They were
supposed to be here [ __ ] 20 minutes
ago. Where the [ __ ] are these?
Where the [ __ ] are these [ __ ] Leave. [Music] I'm getting
[ __ ] down, dude. [Laughter] Get some tasty [ __ ]
You got a boyfriend? There [Applause]
is. There we are. Where is he?
I'm going to
cinema. I'm living that American dream.
I'm living that American dream. Yeah. [Music]
dream. I'm [ __ ] from a [ __ ]
Australia, mate. You [ __ ] [ __ ]
from Australia, mate. [ __ ] twies. Got
to [ __ ] put a [ __ ] Barbie. Yeah. Yeah. I'll [ __ ]
up will get [ __ ] up. Talk about
yourself again. I'm talking to myself.
Razor Razer ain't about that life.
Fraser a [ __ ]
idiot. Crazy is a [ __ ] [Music] Bye. Yeah. Yeah. That's [Applause] yeah,
[ __ ] I'm [ __ ] going to
Australia, mate. You [ __ ] cry in a
[ __ ] bar. How's that? How's that for you? Grieving.
Grieving. Hey, how's that for you?
You're [ __ ] going to [ __ ] do it on
a [ __ ] Barbie, mate. How's that?
How's that? How's that
for you, mate?
Yeah. Tell me a good
accent. A good accent. You're [ __ ]
going [ __ ] down under, mate. Tell me that good
accent. [ __ ] sausage on a [ __ ]
Barbie, mate. I am [ __ ] on a [ __ ]
Barbie. The [ __ ] sausage can, mate.
You tell me I can't do an Aussie accent.
Tell me. Tell me I can't do
it. Listen, USA. I know it. USA easy. I
know you want me. You're [ __ ]
screwed. I messaged you three weeks ago,
two weeks ago on Facebook. I'll come
America again. I'll come I'll you up,
man. Where are you? [ __ ] You shout
[ __ ] You aren't saying nothing. I will
come to America Thursday or Friday and
you shut your pants. Wait about that
line. You're not about it.
Listen, I can show you the 2K right now.
2,000 £2,000 shave. You're not buying
none of her life in your cage. She shut
her pants. You made a bad eye.
ass. You know it. You know you're not
bad. Come on,
bro. You know you're not in my life,
bro. Come on. Come
on. How? Listen. Listen to me. Who's the
one behind you? Who's the one behind it
all? This whole USA easy [ __ ] Who is
the one behind it
all? Who is the one behind it
all? Who is the one behind it? Who's the
all? Who's the one behind it all? Come on.
Yay. Let's spin
it. I need to go.
[ __ ] I need to go. I'm done. I'm
done. There's one
snapshot. I'm out of here. Go live later, maybe.