Just knock me out. Just probably
Listen, man. Just want to say something,
right? This Ricky Millington account. I
shouldn't even be entertaining it. Bro,
listen. It's not that your brother's got
autism and that's how you apparently
know that I have it. You've got autism.
That's how you know all the telltale
signs, bro. Just like all LJ's little
followers. Sad, fat, lonely, old,
autistic, [ __ ] repeating wrongs.
That's all you see on on that channel,
bro. You see the same people every day
writing the same self-projecting
comments year in year out, year in, year
out. It It's proper spasticated. Like I
don't I don't know how someone can just
sit there and then watch it all day,
bro. Once a bunch watch a bunch of old
losers. When I go to the gym in two
days, I'm going to do a video talk about
this before I enter in the gym. How not
to end up like these little mongos on
YouTube. These little self projectors.
Yeah, 100% bro. That will trigger them
much. These people are [ __ ] low lives, bro.
Guys, I got two replies by the way. Um,
Bong talking to talking to
them. I need to go out tomorrow before a
detox. I'm still [ __ ] bro. That
[ __ ] The spirits [ __ ] you up, bro.
They [ __ ] you up differently, bro. Them spirits
Uh, nothing can be promising in this country,
bro. Nothing can be promising in this
country. You don't know when someone's
going to ghost. You don't know when
someone's going to
flake. It's it's a norm. You don't know.
It can end anywhere.
So, yeah. I just like my
uh just like my little approaches. Oh, [ __ ]
me. Yes, I'm going to say
uh do you know why that is? Cuz they
can't leave the house. They've got
anxiety. That's why, bro. It's cuz
they're fat, ugly, autistic people that
can't leave the house cuz of
anxiety. Yeah. whatever spirits
were they [ __ ] you
up. You feel hungry, sick at the same
time and only thing you can do is try
sleep. I should be fresh tomorrow. So, I'm
hoping. Yeah, they're just self projectors,
bro. Nah, I don't even need to mix
drinks. Just rum. Anything to do with rum,
whiskey, it will it will it it will [ __ ]
me up. But you don't think about that
when you're drinking it and it's 2
pound50. You understand? You don't think
about the next
day. You get paranoia. No, you can't
explain it, bro. It's [ __ ] up.
Yeah. And now I'm eating a curry. Hot
dog, steak, and now a
curry. Now a
curry. Oh, [ __ ] me. [ __ ] bro. Oh
[ __ ] See, it's like when these people
try and call me skin, they're just
talking about themselves.
These people probably get bullied every
time they try and leave their house,
bro. These people are proper bully
victims on this community,
lad. Proper bully victims. That's why
they come over there and try to bully
other people cuz they are the proper victims.
Yeah. Was you the one Brit that said
always fake boyfriends?
I just haven't man yet. Isn't it mad how
when we was younger we was never warned about this?
Like we were never told that we'd only
hear I've got boyfriends or the [ __ ] we
have to deal with and that
like I did like that Taiwan from
Australia though. She messaged back.
Yeah, exactly. That's how it should be.
You've got your own life to think about.
Yeah. And that's how it should be, bro.
But these people don't have a life which
is why they're on here every day calling
people what they are themselves.
But yeah, I like that Tai one, bro, from
[ __ ] Australia. Oh my god, I messaged
her. She messaged back with love heart
and [ __ ] [ __ ]
me. I think it's cuz we was talking for so
long. Bit far though, is it
mate? It's a bit
far and you can't immigrate to Australia
either. It's almost
impossible. That's why people immigrants
come here cuz trying to immigrate to
Australia is just it ain't happening
mate for anyone.
So Australia is the first
favorite. Then it's America, then it's
England, you see. And that's how people
end up in England cuz it's easier to get
into, you see.
Yeah. But yeah, man's eating good,
bro. But I have a skin
apparently. Apparently I'm a skin,
bro. I just feel [ __ ] You don't understand,
bro. Them spirits, it's
like when you drink beer on a scale to 1
to 10, your hangover is maybe about two
out of 10. When you do the
spirits, eight out of 10, bro. Telling
you, like you, it feels like someone's
It feels like people You feel like
someone's breaking in the house, bro.
That's how paranoid you
get. It's [ __ ] up, bro. I swear it's
[ __ ] It gives you like intrusive
thoughts and [ __ ] What the
[ __ ] That's why I tried to stick to beer
now. It's a
winner. Less money, less anxiety. Uh,
wait. Less money, less
hangover, and it's cheaper. Yeah. So,
that's why beers I think beer the
best. It's not promising, bro, cuz she's
going back to Australia. She don't she
don't live. She's only visiting. But I
know I had another Australian
message. Practice. Yeah.
I'm going out sending it tomorrow before
I stop for two weeks. But I was going to
do another series series tomorrow,
Cactus. I was going to start though
wherever Peter Bailey's little legs take him
again. Just never know where I can end
up. Obviously, I'll video it all, you
know. Flip a coin, jump a train
somewhere. Thinking of bringing it back, man, tomorrow.
Oh, [ __ ] me. Spirits. Just do not drink
spirits, bro. I'll drink a right white
rum. Yeah. What do you think of that?
Where these legs take him? Wherever his
little legs are going to take
him. I know you mock me, man. But at
least you're like honest about it. You
don't try to hide
it. No, this one's an Australian number.
She actually is
Australian, bro. She actually
is. No, she actually is. She's got Australian
number. But yeah, I remember that one.
That was in Liverpool Street. Yeah. Worst
area. So, what happened to Sig Cactus?
Why did me and Sig lose contact?
What did you think when you heard Peter
Bennett falling in love
again? But yeah, this country will never
change, but it's just fun to go and do something in it.
Yeah, it's fun to uh go and do something, you
know. Yeah, I'm doing it tomorrow.
That's even if I can make it tomorrow. I
might I might be still hung over
tomorrow. It can take two three days
when I'm on spirits. But whether
it's tomorrow, I'm going to send it all
night long. Then I'm done for two weeks.
Need a detox, man. I need to go to the
gym. Don't want to end up like these fat [ __ ] on
here. Why is she not my mama? Who is my mama then,
Cactus? Yeah, I don't mind you. You're
blatantly mocking me, is it? It's banter
in it. But with this Ricky Millington.
Yeah. [ __ ] Ricky Millington.
But this Ricky Mill, right? Um he
uh he tries to do it behind people's
back just like that. Louisville slugger.
He's behind about a million accounts cuz
they ain't got a
life. But the gym video is going to be
dedicated to these people. How to not
end up like these
losers. The first step is the gym.
Tactus. Nah, I'm not getting [ __ ] at the
end of the night. It made me sick. I
woke up and I was sick, mate. It's too
greasy. You need a nice curry,
mate. No. You need like a curry, bro.
our pizza. It's too
greasy. It's too greasy,
bro. It's a nice curry. That
is so my mama
cactus. She's not your mama. Nope.
Yeah. Who's my mama? Catch
this lady in
it. I told my friend about you how you
come on YouTube and you mock
me. You come on YouTube and you keep mocking me.
Yeah, they're just not interested in this
country. Bro, you keep [ __ ] mocking me,
bro. Why you keep mocking
me? You keep
coming. You keep copying everything I
say. Um, went out center
yesterday, man. Australian Tai who I
think I'm in love with. I messaged her
earlier. She messaged
back. I think I might be falling in love again.
Yeah. You are rocking me, mate. Yeah. I
bet you laugh at me. I bet you'll be at
work sometimes and you just think of me
and laughing it.
Lane is at her house and you just be
laughing at what I've said in
it. Oh mate, I am [ __ ]
bad. Yeah, I think I'm definitely in love,
matey. She said she showed me around Australia,
Cactus. I can't go all the way to
[ __ ] Australia. What the [ __ ] What
if it's for
love? And I always said I don't like
Thai women or Filipino women,
but yeah, I don't
know. Doesn't mean
anything. Yeah, you can fall in love with
anyone. Um, she's at her
house. Probably sleeping.
Yeah, maybe another poem might come
up. Oh no, maybe another poem, bro.
Maybe another poem. Oh no, not
again. Yeah, proper. We was talking for like 15
minutes. Oh no, man. If my heart gets
broken again, I think it will just stop
completely. I've already had three,
well, two heartbreaks. I think the third
one I'll be
kaput. Yeah, two two Australians
messaged back. Two of them did. Both a I
got four numbers and two replies back,
which half an emo.
I still feel like I'm
drunk. I feel like I'm [ __ ] drunk,
bro. I ain't drinking spirits again, brother.
Oh, that bro.
Yeah, she did. I didn't even know about
her being a teacher. I was so drunk. I
can't even remember. I know what me and
the other Australian was talking about.
I know what we was talking
about traveling and doing things before
we died. Now, you didn't hear that one,
but I can't even remember her being a
teacher. Yeah, but yeah, she did reply.
I must have been that drunk. I don't
[ __ ] I don't forget anything. Maybe
where I've done so many maybe because I
remember some of the conversations I
had, but I don't remember that one.
I'm absolutely [ __ ] bro.
Jesus. I like Filipino one
better. Who said she didn't have
WhatsApp? No, she does have WhatsApp.
She don't know. She No, she never said
she don't have WhatsApp. She said that.
Do I have Instagram? I said I don't have Instagram.
You never have WhatsApp. He
said I said I don't have
Instagram, which I do, but I told her I
didn't. So, I said, "Can I get your number
instead?" But yeah, I don't take people's Instagrams, bro. It's
either number and if they really don't
want to give their number, but they want
to give something else, then
Snapchat. I don't do this Instagram
[ __ ] I don't like the app to be honest.
The only reason I [ __ ] go on there is
to speak to them army
lads. I need to have a [ __ ]
mate. To speak to them army
lads. She was the nice man out with that
Taiwan. We was talking for ages.
Yeah. But yeah, I feel better tomorrow.
I'll be sending it tomorrow with my
friend. We're going to go
out. But then after that, I need a
[ __ ] detox, man. What the [ __ ] You
just drink beer. You don't get this. I
don't get hamburgers, man.
Yeah, I made loads of
friends. Yeah, Australia. We can we can
have a pet
kangaroo. She find in like one minute
with a lava
hop. Yeah, that's cute. That's really
cute. And you know when I'm in love, I
don't even think of sex. I just think of
being with a person cactus. It's not
even about the sex, just a bit of love.
I was in the cinema earlier and what's
so mad is that there was an older woman,
older than me, not an older woman, but
older than me, not like dating material
at all. We was talking for about 15
minutes about how
um you know, we both love horrors, but
obviously she's not dating or she's
older. She wears glasses. It's not like
that at all. But see, she's in the
cinema by herself and then there was a
younger woman in the cinema by herself.
So, what uh we're going to be
again. We're going to be again. I'm just
happy to just have her as a friend and
then just I'll just try to move to her
and there is people that most of them
all about themselves. There was three of
us. I went to the cinema, bro, and it
said screen 19. I'm looking for screen
19. Let's go and elevate. I've been to
that cinema hund times over the years,
and I didn't even know there was an upstairs
bit. I didn't even know there was an upstairs
bit. That's bad. to
to man Thailand now. I'll be there in a couple
weeks. Now, all of this is for fun, bro. Like going
out. The chance of actually meeting
someone. It's is unlikely.
Like you need to be eyeing check at the
same time as we can laugh at this. If
you can barely get a conversation out of
someone, how would you expect you're
going to even date someone? Big amount
of practice. When you go out on the
street and they say, "Oh, they've got
boyfriends." Or they give you some NPC
reply. If you can't get any more than
that out of someone, you're not going to
be able to make even a friendship with
someone. This is why I didn't [ __ ] this
Muslim girl off because it's so hard now to come
by, you know, friends that are women.
And that's how you know you're [ __ ]
down bad, bro. Is when you're accepting
the friend zone. But, you know, I just
figured it's better than nothing. People
might change their mind, whatever.
Cuz it's not as easy as that. It's not
that. Like approach and then just just
take it, bro. Like, take what you can get. But yeah, my
mind think about before I went to sleep
when I woke
up. Yeah, I need to stop thinking about
this bro cuz we get too deep into this again.
See, I like it when people pay me
attention. When they give me attention
cactus, I like to be loved. I like to be hug and
stuff, you know.
Yeah, there won't be.
But I don't know this guy before
you he was from where he was from, but
he came here for some boxing
things. No, I don't even want her to
suck my dick. I just want to be kissed and
hugged, you know? with sexual
stuff just like spooning, you know. And
he said, "Oh, if you ever Australia, hit
me up." I was like, "Yeah, if I ever
Australia, what the [ __ ] would I be doing
there? What would I be doing in [ __ ] Australia,
bro? That is [ __ ]
madness. That is [ __ ]
insane." Oh, imagine that. Steven
Howard. Me the baby. Me. Me the Chinese
Aussie baby and a pet kangaroo wearing
the stony. What a lovely
sight. What a lovely [ __ ]
site. You remember when USA Izzy
um Oh, I forgot to tell you. You know,
when I was on this date the other day, I
felt something in my
toa. I felt something in my
to that that that the the Muslim um guy.
I swear to God, I felt something in my
to and I had to hide in
here. I I threw anything in my toger.
I remember when I used to say that to
19y old. She said, "Why the [ __ ] do you
keep calling it that?" Well, I didn't
feel anything in my
to what the what the pet kangaroo
um Steven Howard with a
Stony play GTA 6 in it. My
Todd. Hello. Do you remember Ant-Man
said? Yeah. Ant-Man said, "Even if I
have to [ __ ] their kids to [ __ ] them."
You mean he used to say that? I was
dead. He said he said he This is what he
said. Yeah. He said, "Even if I have to
[ __ ] their kids to [ __ ]
them." That's funny that Why is he
saying stuff like that? Is it? Yeah.
[ __ ] it. Yeah, I remember when USA Izzy
came on to me kissing me greasy. I felt
something in my todder. You know, I wasn't expecting
it. Then I started grabbing her
boobs. Then I started Then I started grabbing her
boobs. But do you know what? Yeah, I'm
going to start
[ __ ] I'm not getting a new PS4. I'm
PS5. But no, what? Oh, you made me
forget what I was going to [ __ ] say
now. [ __ ] sake. You always do this, you
[ __ ] Made me forget what I was going to [ __ ]
say. Oh. Oh, yeah. You know Lord
J. You know Lord J. I'm going to start
[ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ] now about
his uh if anyone talks about his kids
cuz he's the one that's bringing family
into it now. He's the one that brings
family into it now. Oh, I meant PS5. Oh,
did I? I meant PS5. Why did I get a PS4,
bro? I have to get a PS5. Oh, [ __ ] Yeah. Um, yeah.
PS5. PS5. Sorry. Why the [ __ ] Yeah,
bro. I went on L J's and he starts
bringing up family. See, this guy brings
up family, bro. He starts it. No, no one
speaks about anything. He's the one that starts it,
bro. I'm going to be like, bro, I'll
just play for the guys to come here in
it. And everyone should start, everyone
should start like blaming him for not
coming. If he doesn't come yet, everyone
should start blaming him, bro. Know what I'm
saying? Know what I'm saying? He is a
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. When on his live, he
[ __ ] starts talking about [ __ ]
Ramy. But yeah, he never do anything to
anyone's face, though. You can only go
for Timmy. He's a [ __ ] bro. Even that
time in London, he was scared. He's a [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
Yeah. [ __ ] hell. He's the one that
brings up family. Why does he do that? Yeah. Yeah.
You know, funny enough, the first person
I had a crush on was somebody was an actual Thai
person. Some of them are are nice to be fair. But
yeah, I think the only one I don't like
like I see attractive is maybe black women
maybe. Even I've been with one. But
yeah, great man.
Yep, I sure have. I love Thai food, bro.
I love Thai food. I like Chinese
food. Am I a pool lover,
Cactus? Am I a pool
lover? I bought a new phone today. £400 it cost
me. Yeah, I can finally start calling
people again outside. [ __ ] But do you
know what? Yeah, it is fast, but it will
never be as fast as the fold.
These fold phones, they never slow down.
It doesn't matter how long you've had
them for, they don't slow down. But
obviously, I could have bought a fold,
but I'm not spending two grand on a
phone and I'm not and I'm not getting a contract out.
So, that is not happening. Not getting a
contract and it's risky because
obviously the phone can get stolen. So,
you're best off just getting a [ __ ]
four or 500 phone like I did. But in
terms of the RAM, they never slow down.
These folds never slow down, man.
They're fast as
anything. The RAM is very
high. They can't slow down, but you
can't justify two
grand. And then it's two grand. And then
what happens is they'll bring a phone
out again next
week. You'll get me in prison.
Nah, I'm never going prison, matey. to
prison. Yeah, they shut down my phone.
They blocked my whole phone. That's why
I got a new phone and I need my phone to
do something as well. I had to get a new
phone for several different reasons. So,
yeah, they did. No, you can use this
phone on Wi-Fi. The phone I'm using is
the fold phone now. You can use on
Wi-Fi. You can call on
Wi-Fi and you can use internet on Wi-Fi,
but you can't use it outside the house.
I'm sick of having to connect to Wi-Fi
and [ __ ] connecting [ __ ] the
emails. Like, [ __ ] all that. I just buy
a new one cuz I don't ever want a contract ever
again. I don't ever want to um I just
never want a contract again. I don't
believe in them. You know, I paid £600
up front for that phone and they still
blocked it. You know, half the phone
basically was mine and they still
blocked it. So, I'll never get a contract ever
again. And I've got this fold. So, you I
can just use that at home and then just
use that one to go out
with. But yeah, the RAMs on the folds
are [ __ ] banging,
bro. The RAM on on these folds is
another level. But
yeah, they're not safe to even have in
London. You get
robbed. If it was £1,000. Yeah. Okay. £900.
Okay, whatever. But [ __ ] almost two
grand for a [ __ ] phone. Like, come
on. I'm not paying that,
bro. That is insane. only for them to
bring a new one out the next
year. When the seven comes out, will I get it?
Nah. And that's the thing. When you buy
your own phone, they can't block it cuz it's
yours. I like stuff to be mine. You can insure it,
but it will cost another £300. You can insure
it, but it's going to cost like 2.1K,
2K, 2.2 2K. So there's no point. You can insure it. Um
but yeah, I just wouldn't ever pay that amount of
money for for a phone. It just doesn't make sense.
As much as I love them and I love my
Samsung phones, I can't I can't, you
know, even if
like the only thing you probably could
do when the seven comes out, I might do
this if I can get enough money. The only
thing you probably could do where it makes sense
is, but I don't like contracts. Maybe
get like a contract for a year and pay
like £200 a
month. Obviously, you'd have to be earning
and you could do that maybe, you know,
that's the only way I see it as as
feasible to be honest. Buying it, it's
too expensive. Not worth it. Threeear
contract, you're [ __ ] You're tied in
a contract for 3 years. So, maybe if you
got it for like 12 months, you know, a
year is nothing if you're paying every
month. Maybe you could get like a just
pay it off every month, maybe. cuz it's
the same as I guess paying off every
month. Um, and it's only a year. So
maybe you could do that. That's the only
way I think you could do
it, which is basically like paying in free installment payments.
But it's like even if you wanted to work
in London with the phone, you you're
going to get it nicked. Trust me. So you
you will get that phone nicked.
So it'd be like you'd be paying 2.2K and
then you just have to be so careful with
it. There's no point. With this one,
it's £400. I'll be careful with it.
Yeah. But I'm not like going to be
conscious all the
time. But with a fold, you would just be
conscious all the time. Unless you're a
[ __ ] millionaire, you can't justify them prices,
bro. But at the same time, I didn't want
a really cheap one where it feels [ __ ]
in your hand. I I didn't want a really
expensive one, so I thought the one I
got was good. You don't feel plasticky
and cheap. You know how some people
don't care what phone they get.
Um, I care.
So, obviously that one's in the middle
on it, I
guess. But what the [ __ ] is a RAM on this
fold? Got to be high numbers, bro. So
yeah, you could you could I could get
the fold and then just pay it off,
but every month, but like I said, I like
things to be mines and because they and
they can block the phone as
well, which is
bad. Then they block it and then there's
more charges and [ __ ]
like so things
happen. Things happen. Do you remember
when I bought a new phone to message
USA? Izzy. Oh, it was like £60 that
phone. It was
[ __ ] I bought a phone for £60 to
message USA, bro. And the phone was so [ __ ]
bro. Oh, [ __ ] me. I was a bad bastard. I
mean, I think it was 50 or 60 quid I
paid. I was, "Oh, yeah, I'll buy another
phone." See, I was always a crazy [ __ ]
Even back then I was a crazy [ __ ] You
know what I'm saying? Yeah.
Yeah. some crazy fun
mates. A lap towel,
huh? It was a Samsung, but it was just
[ __ ] The RAM on it was just [ __ ] mate.
It reminds me the [ __ ] skin
days. Would you pay £1,700 for a phone
Steven Howard if you got 3k a month? Nah.
Nah, mate. There's no way there's no way
of even justifying that.
Like, there's no way that [ __ ] will be
outdated in like 8
months. That is
insane. That is insane. £800. You could
justify it. Really? You could justify
800, but even that's a bit still
like No, I think the most 800 maximum,
but even then, no, I'd say maximum 400.
450 4. Yeah, I'd say 4 450. But these
folds are so
fast. They're so
good. I love it, bro. I love it. These folds. Yeah.
Or you could pay £200 a month.
Yeah. Yeah. I might get a seven. I might
do maybe, but I'm not paying the money
for it. I'll just have to pay off for
That's the only really thing I'm into. I
went to the Samsung shop today to buy
the phone. I love Samsung, bro. I've always loved
Samsung. Always have and always will.
So, it's very old, you know, very old
brand. I know most people prefer iPhones,
but I love these [ __ ] folds, man.
They're [ __ ] ace. I've had this one
since November, December, and it's still
fast. Fast as anything. They don't slow
down. Yep. I've got 136 now.
Everything's backed up. Yeah, bro. That
was the worst time of my life. I was
like, "Oh [ __ ] I've got to start all
over again." But the good thing was is
that people still had my number.
So, obviously when I got the new phone,
I was still under the same number. So
anyone that would message me, I'd get
their number again. I think the Somalian
messaged me, my Italian friend messaged
me, a few people messaged me. So
obviously I got their number back, but I
lost a [ __ ] ton of numbers. I lost everything. I
phone. You know what I'm saying? Yeah,
it was [ __ ] bro. Had to get a new
phone. I couldn't sleep. I saw it was crazy, bro.
Yeah, but all my stuff's backed up now.
So, what do you mean? Sigs not my mama
cactus. I was playing with Sigs
boobyongs. I was playing with Sigs boobs cactus. Yeah. Yeah. [Music]
Oh, Sig not your mama. I should have
stayed with Sig. Sig bought me
chicken. Yeah, Sig bought me chicken and
we was watching the Elf Stewart parodies
together. Ah, what a lovely site.
Yeah, she was a pretty good [ __ ] weren't she,
Sig? She wouldn't suck my dick though,
unless I ate her out. I'm not eating you out. That's
disgusting. I'm not I'm not I'm not
licking your mini. You know what I'm saying?
I'm not licking your your
miniature. Oh, just a New Zealander that
I had a one night stand with. Not licking your
mini. You filthy
animal. No, [ __ ] that,
bro. That's what that USA is. He
probably wanted me to do looking at me
like I'm not [ __ ] doing that,
brother. You mad. That's [ __ ]
disgusting, mate. That's frowned upon
where I'm uh where I'm
from. That's frowned upon where I'm from,
mate. The name for that.
Yeah. She bought me chicken and I said I
was going to take her to Nando, but I
never. So, she had the ump. Yeah.
So, she's got the
um so Cactus. So you're not taking a
piss here where you when you think when
when you said that Ant-Man's right,
they're not interested in this
country. Really? Is he actually right?
No, he doesn't. I've got more experience
than him, mate. I've approached more
women than him. I've been up and down
the country like he would admit himself.
No, no, I've got more experience than
him. I've got more experience than him.
And I said, "Oh, it took you 31 to go to
Thailand?" And he said, "Yeah, cuz I
didn't have the money that you had when
I was your age." When he was my age, he
had nothing. Like, he was eating cold
beans. Like, he had literally
nothing. Now he's in Thailand. So, you
know, you done a good thing leaving
YouTube. He doesn't have more experience
than me, bro. Trust me. Trust me, he
doesn't. And he would admit it himself.
He He would tell you himself straight.
He would have say, "Oh, you've tried 10
times more than me." No, no, no. He He
would tell you this, bro. I'm sorry,
Yeah, I'm not kid, man.
Who do you think maybe Peter would look like,
Cactus? It feels like that, don't it,
Cactus? It does feel like
that. And all I got was a few one night stands. Wow.
My friend from here, he said he's sick
of the I've got a boyfriend. He says
that's why I don't try anymore. It's
always I've got a
boyfriend. I just ate, bro. I just had I
just had an Indian.
What baby Peter look like at this?
Ah, still got the baby going stuff. Oh,
yeah. Still got the baby going stuff.
What a lovely sight.
Yeah, baby baby LT and baby Peter playing
together. Oh, what a lovely
site. What a lovely site.
E, that's cute, isn't
it? Still got the baby
clothes. I come out with the best saying, isn't it, bro?
What's What's your favorite saying of
mine? Mr. Mcuny's ugly little mates.
Hey, Greavves. I had an
Indian. Imagine that in Australia. me
with a Thai woman with a baby and our
pet and grew with a baby grow playing
GTA. That is a lovely site.
Grezy having a barbecue. Yeah, I got
that from Green Street though. I got I
actually copied that one. Well, I said
that yesterday. Where the [ __ ] are these
[ __ ] I actually did say that the other
day, man, cuz I was waiting for the
police. I was like, where the [ __ ] are these
[ __ ] They were supposed to be a 20
minutes ago and I had stuff to do as
well. Yeah. Where the [ __ ] are these
[ __ ] in a
greasy? But yeah, me
um Australian Izzy with the Thai baby
and the little kangaroo
cactus by the barbecue. Grezy having a
barbecue playing GTA 6 outside. What a lovely sight.
load of old bills. Now, my favorite
saying is from Ant-Man. How's it going,
bro? You got anything? He's like, "How's it
going?" They've all got
boyfriends. I was like, "Calm down. Calm
down. Calm down. What's happened?" He
says, "They've all got boyfriends."
I'll never forget that, bro. I will Yeah.
Oh, I will never I will never ever forget that,
bro. He says it doesn't matter if you're
wearing a million pound suit, you're
still going to get her. I've got a boyfriend.
Yeah, they've all got
boyfriends. Yeah. I said to I said to
Cactus, "Yeah, sorry, Cactus." I said to
I said to him, "Yeah, if a if a woman
says it to me, I'm going to jump on the
table in Weather Spoons and be like,
"You got a boyfriend, do you?" And I'm
going to send it to him. I start dancing
on the table. He says, "Yeah, do it and
send me it." I actually did dance on the
table like a month ago, but you couldn't
see. I was actually on top of the table,
but I did do it. Yeah, boyfriend. Yeah.
Yeah. Then I start dancing on the
[ __ ] table in
it. So, Gregy, would you come to
Australia to see me and the baby and the pet
kangaroo and Oh, that's so cute. No.
No, I slept with your mom
yesterday. What do you mean no? Greasy,
you wouldn't come and see me and the
baby. What do you mean
no? You would be his
uncle. You would be his
uncle. Do you remember my daddy
Tam? Oh, Greavvesy. But you'd be his
uncle. Oh, Cactus. Remember Do you
remember that time? my daddy who abandoned
me. Oh, I got
abandoned. Cuz I said to uh Laney the
other day, it's like, isn't it mad how
you got three kids, both of them's got
kids? They're kind of like normal. I
just live normal lives, not that they've
got kids, and then you got me a complete
crazy person. I'm sure you've um you got
the wrong child from hospital. That's
why I say to G. I said, "I think you
brought the wrong child home." Cuz I'm completely
nuts. Ain't it,
Grezy? I'm completely
nuts. Grezy, listen, bro. I'm starting
to gym. I'm starting the gym on Monday
and I think you should join
me cuz, bro, if you don't, you're going
to end up like these little
self-reflectors. But I don't mind Grezy.
He's not bitter or rude or anything.
He's a pretty good [ __ ]
I like Grezy. I like unworthy clock as
well. You're going to end up like these
people, bro. If you if you don't stop,
you end up like these fat, ugly [ __ ] in their
40s. So, I'm starting the gym on Monday, bro.
Yeah, I'm starting the gym for sure.
Do you remember Greavvesy, you calling
evil? The person on Reddit, do you
remember Greavvesy? You calling me
evil with a little
avatar? I said, yeah, you're all evil.
You women are all evil.
Yeah, I said that they're all evil. It
to see my child,
Grezy. But yeah, you end up like these
fat bastards, Greavvesy. You don't want
to end up like these people. Greavvesy,
go Scotland, man. You've always wanted
to go Scotland. It's the
summer, you know. Do do some things in
the summer, man. Go Scotland.
Go Edinburgh, go Glasgow. [ __ ] might
as well. You got nothing to
lose. You always wanted to go Scotland.
So yeah, I'm I'm definitely going to gym on Monday,
bro. Oh, there's no way I'm ending up
like these people.
L, [ __ ] that. No way.
You're going to Spain. Good, man.
Good. Yeah, I wouldn't go Spain if you paid
me. Oh, you know what? Ant-Man said to
Cactus that they say they got boyfriends
in Spain as well. He said you get
English people there. They say they got boyfriends.
I don't know what I
am. Yeah, I wouldn't go Spain if you paid me,
lad. Yeah, I flew from Scotland. I flew
Scotland. Not Scotland, sorry, from
Gatwick. It was quite a terrible
experience. Scriezy one that I never wish to
repeat. No, I'd rather go Thailand than
Spain. Different culture, a lot cheaper.
You can actually get
women even if you don't pay. I I'm I'm
defin I'm going in 3 weeks, bro. You [ __ ]
mad. That's part of the reason why I
need to go gym as well, so my body looks a bit
better. Spain and England.
Yeah. Yeah. And Australia is part of the UK as
well. Uh, Spain is Yeah. Spain is part
of England and Australia is part of the UK.
Yeah. You can get a bus to Australia.
LJ's not been to Asia, has he, Cactus?
Nah, cuz he's got no life
experience. He's got no life
experience. Thailand. Uh, half an
hour from Heathro.
Yeah. He's not been to Asia though, has he?
Cactus. No, it's not in Wales. Uh
But as long as they've been to Asia, I don't think
so. Cuz you would have seen it. You
heard you would have heard about
it. It's so weak.
Jeez, I don't have that much money, mate. [ __ ] hell. Yeah. Um,
listen. Has Lord J been to Thailand? Steven Howard.
Yeah, but I want to go see my daddy in
Scotland. Uh, Cactus. What happened to
my daddy? Daddy Tam. Daddy
Tam with his little kilt movie.
I was going to kiss her this Australian
yesterday, but the time weren't right. I
thought like giving her a
kiss. Is that cute? Greasy. Just a little
A n's never been to Asia.
Stephen, if you had to pick America or
Asia, you'd pick Asia in
it. The the Celtic
fan in Weather Spoons, remember him and
his friend? He started turning dodgy
Tam. You know Tam from
Glasgow? The one when when Celtic was playing. So,
nope. She wasn't nice at all. Who do you think is
uh if you had to pick? Yeah. Steven
Howard, would you pick America or
Asia? Yeah. He said that I think you can
benefit from see getting some help. You
He said you should talk some some things
through with a psychologist.
I'm going to back down to that
[ __ ] Yeah, he was being he was being
weird, bro. I said, "Hold on, lads. I'm
just going to do this approach." And she
said she has a boyfriend. And I went
back to him complaining in
it. But he's my daddy. Daddy
Tam. Yeah, he was a [ __ ] He was His
friend was all right
though. His friend was actually all right.
Yeah, I speak to some uh transgender
woman in Scotland. She's I like her
personality. I might go up there and see her. Yeah, she's
transgender. But well, it is what it is,
isn't it? [ __ ]
it. Well, you'd want to go to both,
Stephen Howard, but which one would you
pick first? Asia in it
100%. Can't believe Ant-Man's been there
four times in a year. That is insane,
bro. Yeah, she looks all
right. Four times in a [ __ ] year. That's insane,
bro. That is insane, is it? Four times
in a year. I know he's not coming back.
That's That's a lot, bro. Four times in
a [ __ ] year.
Cactus. Do you remember the fingering in the pub?
Yes, mad four times in a year. Jesus.
Living a life, bro. Living a
little. Can you imagine L in Thailand? Nah. Nah,
bro. Oh, don't don't remind me, mate.
Don't remind me.
Don't don't don't remind me, mate.
Please. I might not do 12 bars. I might
just meet my friend at
8. He saves up, bro. He just booked a
flight, which is like 7800 pound, and
then you just need like three grand for the month.
time. He books it months in advance and he just
saves. It's not that hard. Thailand's
hard. America's hard though, but not
Thailand cuz once you're there, it's cheap, isn't
it? Yeah. But don't depress me, mate.
No, he doesn't borrow it. Yeah, he either wins
it. Um, the one he won five grand one
time, so he was able to go cuz he won
five grand on a bet, so he just went as
soon as he won that money. But yeah, no,
he shoplifts. Well, he doesn't do it anymore,
but he used to shoplift and made like an
extra two-300 pound every week and
it so that's how he was able to do it. Benefits and
shoplifting. Well, obviously he can't
shoplift anymore cuz if he gets caught,
he'll probably go prison. So, even
though he gets away with it most of the
time, if he uh if he gets caught doing
it again, he'll probably go prison.
There's a high chance. But yeah,
shoplifting. So, two300 pound extra a
week on top of the uh benefits. That's
how we can do it. So,
yeah, obviously just book the flights and
yeah. Yeah, man.
Would you shoplift Steven
Howard? I've been to prison. It's not
that bad, you
know. I've been to
prison. It's not that
bad. But I'm going to win money gambling
when the season starts again on the both
teams to score. Trust me, I'm going to
win some money. That's the only thing
I'll be gambling on now.
I don't play the slots no more. Barely
play roulette anymore. Don't even do it
anymore. But when the football's
back, I'll stop, bro.
Watch. I've been to prison. It's not
that bad. Steven Howard, I've been
prison. I've been to prison before.
used to make me stop gambling is when I
actually worked for the money. I
remember before when I worked years ago
and I never gambled cuz I couldn't
gamble money that I worked for.
So then you think, "Oh, you've had to
put the hours in to get that
money." You know what I'm saying? It's
uh I couldn't do it when I worked for
it. But obviously when you don't work
for it's a different story. I have been
prison. Is that right,
Cactus? Yeah, I have been to
prison. No, I've been to prison as well.
I really need to find a candidate for baby
Peter. Hopefully I got this one that meets
me. Really want to candidate baby
Peter. That would be cute.
Do you know what's so mad? You don't
really see pregnant. This is how you
know the dating game's [ __ ] in this
country. You don't even really see many pregnant people
anymore. You walk around, you don't even
really see pregnant women
anymore. That's that's the thing I've
noticed being out a lot seeing so many
people. You don't even see people get pregnant
anymore. You know what I'm saying?
No, you never see anyone. Yeah.
Where am I going to get a baby Peter from though? Access.
Yeah, they must be all. Bro, you don't
even see him nowadays,
bro. It's mad to think there was
actually people getting
sex considering it's so hard to meet
people and even get conversation a lot
of the time. It's hard to believe, isn't it?
But I think Ant-Man trolls me,
bro. He always says, "Oh, well, other
people like he he does this stuff to
troll, bro. He's a troll, bro. He
definitely is a
troll." No, he definitely is a troll,
bro. I'm telling you, he
is. So he went to Thailand because
they're not interested in this
country. Definitely trolling,
bro. He definitely is trolling with some
of the things he says.
Yeah. Look, you know, if you go on LJ's
chat, what do you see? us. If you go on
LJ's channel, what do you see every day?
But if you go the live
streams, you see the same people every day, ain't
it? You see the same people every
day. I got a projector in my room.
You see the same people every
day. I wonder why Monty likes me again.
Huh? Monty likes me again.
Yep. Nah, bro. That's
all. So, what's this? USA is his problem.
I owned her, bro. I owned her really hard on Facebook.
Yeah. People think I'm the one that
needs help for saying this stuff. No, I
don't think so, bro. I think that [ __ ]
deserved it. She actually met her match.
She wanted to be a [ __ ] and she met her
match. Plain and
simple. She met her [ __ ]
match. That's what it is. And you
decided to play
victim. I said I will come there next
week. Like two weeks ago at 3:00 in the
morning, Thursday or Friday. What days
are you available? I was being serious,
bro. Why wouldn't I be serious, bro?
What the [ __ ] I commented on the thing
at 3:00 in the morning, which you
[ __ ] shut your mouth though, didn't you? You
[ __ ] [ __ ] pair of [ __ ] In it, cactus.
Yeah. See, once you meet Peter Benny,
you can't get Peter B out your
life. Nah, Terry's a little [ __ ]
No, Terry's a little [ __ ]
mate. Do you want my opinion, Zippy? Uhhuh. Daryl
[ __ ] You remember that one? Do you
want my opinion, Zippy? Daryl [ __ ]
Yeah, USA. He likes to be sucking her boobs.
She come onto me like an
animal. She liked it a
lot. He got caught
cheating. But the kiss tasted kind of
stale at us.
It was quite a stale tasting
kiss. Does that make sense? Kind of like a stale
kiss. All of a sudden, all I started
seeing is tongues coming towards me.
Cactus someone on my nose as well. I'm not
sure. There were motherly kisses in it.
Cactus. The slower the better.
better. USA. There's no USA, bro. There's just
me. Yeah. The slower the
better. Do you remember Scott Cactus?
remember? No, I don't have any
tattoos. Yeah, she came on to me
first. I was thinking, "Oh, I've got to
make a move here somehow." But then she
done it for me. She said, "I'm not
scared to make the first
move." Who else has come on to me? Oh,
Izzy's come on to me as well. So, both
of them actually come on to
me. Isabelle come on to me. I said, "I'm
not buying you any more drinks,
Isabelle. I'm put my foot down. We need
to speak about your trolling behavior on
YouTube with me and Craig. You're not
getting any more drinks." I had to put my foot
down. Then she she had a tantrum. I
said, "No, Isabelle. No. You listen to me." Yeah.
They're the two biggest [ __ ] talkers,
but they're the two that's come on to
me. No one else has ever come on to me, I don't
think. Trying to think.
No. Yeah. Do you remember that
cactus? But you know, LT was messaging USA Izzy.
Yeah. But who was behind it all? Cuz
without me, there'd be no them two
talking and and [ __ ] I said to her, "I
noticed you like to beg the black man to
do your dirty work as
well. Meanwhile, you've been violated
about a million times and you're not
about to say
nothing. But you're fast enough." They
always run to the black man, don't
they? It's they run to the black man. If
that don't work, they then run to the
benefits. If that don't work, they run
to the neighbors. And if that don't
work, mate, it's the boys in
blue. It's the boys in blue,
mate. It's the [ __ ] boys in blue.
Yep. Always the boys in
blue. When all when all when else all fails.
Yeah. Bad, is
it? But how did them two even start talking, Cactus?
Like how did them two even start
talking did it have something to do with
me? It's so mad to think that if there
was no me cat if there was no me cat to
share this might have been a very
peaceful community like LT would have
had the problems that he's had with
certain people. I've got a lot to blame
for a lot of the stuff that's gone on, Cactus, isn't it?
Yeah. That's kind of mad, isn't it? If
there was no me, it could be quite a peaceful
community. Who's the root cause for a
lot of this YouTube thing? Steven Howard.
Uh, you can't say that though, Cactus,
cuz LT's been to different places in
England and people have not shown up.
People have not shown
up, you know. So,
Do you want USA is tits, Stephen Howard?
I was like, you got nice boobs. She's
like, my ex said that as well. A bless
you. Bless you. You remember that um Diamond
Cactus? Yeah. If there was no me, this
community wouldn't have had half the
arguments that it's had in
it. But then the maddest thing about it
is like everyone has been affected but
me. But I've been affected in some ways,
but Monty man, you know, he basically
lost his life because of this community.
Um, LT's always got in madnesses over me
and it's all related to me. If you think about it, Cactus.
Yeah. You can bring whoever he wants, man. Everyone's
invited. Bring your friends.
USA Izzy pulled her Calvin Klein top up
and her boobies fell out.
Cactus. Yeah, she was wearing like a Calvin Klein
top and she pulled it up and then her
boobs come flying
out. She's so silly.
You're sick and twisted,
[ __ ] You're sick and twisted,
[ __ ] I'm sick and twisted for
you. That's what my friend said. You
should have said I'm sick and twisted for
you. No, she didn't. No.
No, you told me to text her when I get back
home. We kissed goodbye. She said, "Text
me when you get back home."
Cactus. It was special then, but it's over
now. Ah, good times,
man. Do you remember Peter Bennett
thought he found someone?
Cactus. Don't you always? Hey, don't you always. Yeah.
Yeah. And it's not because what she's
saying, cuz I've never had that with any
other woman where they just said that
and then just
disappeared. It's cuz she got what she
wanted, didn't it? The meal and
whatever. and she didn't want to be held
accountable accountable for her actions,
so she just played victim, you
know. Yeah, it's
strange. I don't care about the rumors
because I know it never happened and
even if it did happen, I wouldn't care.
Good. Glad you felt scared. So, I
wouldn't even care either way. I'm not
asked. Even though we know it's
[ __ ] but I don't care either way,
mate. And I got what I wanted. So, yeah. Either
way, I'm not I'm not buying any more of
them Stephen King it films anymore cuz
every time he seems to just keep coming
back. Cactus the clown gets killed but
yeah he keeps coming
back. I said you can't be coming back.
We defeated you in 1980.
The kids defeated
you. Yeah, she love scammed
me. Yeah, we defeated you in 1990, Mr.
Pennywise. I remember
it. The little kids, but somehow he
keeps coming back. So, what's the
[ __ ] point if he's just going to keep coming
back? Not sure, Steven Howard.
Yeah, I was laughing at all the Grand
Theft Autos. It shows a page where all
the Grand Theft Autos and then you got
six at the end and it it made me howl
for like 10 minutes cuz it looks so out
of place. Like they've not done a new
one for 13 years and then it's just
there at the end. It's so
random. That just made me laugh, man. I
don't know. It just made me
laugh. All the lovely little characters.
pork. Maybe uh maybe maybe eat a load of old
bail. Yeah, we was just talking about
USA Izzy's boobs.
Greavvesy, how they were quite delicious. Yeah.
Yeah. You're calling me
evil. You're calling me Yeah. [ __ ] trolls.
Yeah. I need to find a new
mama. Do you remember you're not my
mama? Yuck. Yuck.
Oh, barbecue in the San Andreas. San
Andreas. I love San Andreas. It's got
such a good story story line. I still
remember it. We're still trying to
complete it, but I remember it. The
policeman got something to do with
killing his mom in it. Big Smoke. I I
still remember it to this day. I still play
it. But um
um I I think it's got something to do
with Big Smoke killing his mom though.
And the policeman's behind a lot of
it. Yeah. I need them
nutrients. I need them
Yeah. Could you imagine how big her
boobs would get if she got pregnant? cactus.
Wow. Yeah, I know. It's something I
remember it briefly. It's a good story
line. I was saying to this woman earlier
in in the cinema again, she's like 50
odd. So, it wasn't anything like that.
We was like, they don't make things like
they used to. Horses, Grand Theft
Autos, that it clown. Do you remember
it? Oh, do you know the saying that was
making me laugh? Greasy. You'll like it
down here, son. You'll never have to grow
up. That's one of my favorite phrases.
Do you remember when he was pretending
to be the guy's dad that that died? He's
like, "You like it down here, son.
You'll never have to grow up." And then
he and then he turned back into the
clown. You'll like it down here, son. Do
you remember that one? Gy and then he
disappears. You like it down here? It's
It's quite It's quite
catchy. Yeah, that clown is [ __ ] up though. But
yeah, that clown's [ __ ]
bro. You'll like it down here,
son. What was your favorite GTA Cactus?
Greavves one was number four. I think mine's San
Andreas, you know, like we used
to. Is it belly? Yeah.
Yeah, hopefully I can get an Indian Izzy
tomorrow cuz I got to go to a club
where Indian people.
So yeah, I think Indian one
tomorrow. Yeah, it is. It is. I like the flying
cars. Liberty City is good as well.
You remember Blockbuster Cactus? Oh, [ __ ] legendary, bro. That's legendary. Um,
Blockbuster. It just reminds you of all of the
GTA's, but GTA 5 is good. Yeah.
Blockbuster word of days, man.
Blockbusters word of
days. Sat on the chair, eight years old.
Cactus, not a care in the world, not a
worry in the
world. Playing Homer Simpson, you know,
Goozy, not a care in the world. Young
Peter Belly, fetish Peter
Belly, not care in the world.
Yeah, I wish I could be a kid
again. Yeah, but Blockbuster was the
goat, bro. Blockbuster was the goat, you
know. Yep. with the sheep and the
um with a sheep and the lamb on it. No.
What is it? It was a sheep and they used
to do Wallace and
Grommet. Yep. I remember Walworth. They
had the best picker
mix. I wish I could be a Kiggy. I I felt
like I feel like I never I never grew up.
Grieves. Do you remember going all the
way to America to touch
you? Go on and touch
cactus. That's funny. But yeah, I wish I
could be a kid
again. Yeah. No beard, no nothing.
Uh feel like I never grew
up, you know. I can't even remember
much. Yeah. I I miss
WWE. I miss WWE. I miss Runescape.
Anyone here used to play
Runescape? Cuz if you haven't, I can't
explain the game to you. It's impossible
to explain it. But any Runescape
fans, that's how I met my friend Pepe
from Amsterdam. We met on Runescape
basically and he come to London. We met
up with some beers.
Yeah. Send me in, mate. I'll touch the
[ __ ] out of
her. Cactus. Send me in,
mate. Send me in, mate. I'll touch the
[ __ ] out of her.
That's what El Stewart said. Send me in,
mate. Yeah, I'd have to touch her again.
I don't think I'll be able to help
myself. Yeah, bro. That's the one. Well,
did you used to play
it? Did you used to play it? Yeah.
Oh, rude escape. What a
days. I remember have I remember I used
to bot it. If you've never done it, if
you don't know about the game, there's
no point in me explaining it cuz you won't understand
it. It's you can't It's a game that can't be
explained. You literally have to have
knowledge on it otherwise you won't understand it.
used to sit in I remember I used to No,
everyone's not played it, bro. Not
everyone's played it. No, they
haven't. So, do you remember the red
chins? Hunting red chins. I remember I
used to [ __ ] sit on the computer all
night. All night. Yep. All night. Yeah.
I used to used to sit all night and play that game.
Then I go to school in the
morning. Then I'd go to school in the
morning and somehow still do
it. Uh, bro, I used to just sleep on the couch. It
was I used to play it all night. All night,
bro. I'd have to say Runescape's better
than Grand for thought. That That is
legendary. That game. You will never
die. That's better than any GTA. It's
better than any game. I'm telling
you. So, do you remember like hunting
red chins? I used to bot it. Do you
remember botting? Yeah, I used to bot
it. I used to love botting on it and
then waking up and then the script still
running. Oh, bro.
Yeah. Do you remember?
I used to like doing the quests. Do you remember the quests? Monkey
Madness. Remember the quest Monkey
USA is got some big
t I'm not sure. I think I was just lazy.
Do you want USA is his tit? It's Steven Howard. Yeah.
What businesses do you think makes the most
money? I think food ones cuz you know
nightclubs. Yeah, they they will make
money but the thing with a
nightclub is in January, February
there's no business cuz no one goes out
cuz it will skin.
That's the thing. Nightclubs don't make
as much money as restaurants cuz
restaurants is all the time drinks.
People only start going into
places after like 10:00.
Yeah. Do you think the Virgin will ever
get laid, Steven Howard?
No. I said, "Do you think the Virgin
will get laid today?
No. Do you think the virgin will get laid ever?
Sorry. What? You reckon he'll die?
One, you reckon he'll die a virgin?
Yeah. If you don't find shovel car
attractive, you're a homosexual
apparently. Oh, that's a new one. Oh.
Yeah. Show call.