These people are [ __ ] weirdos, man.
Jeez. Back to [ __ ] 2022. Some
madness. What the
hell? You know, notice really in how
jealous people are in this community. I'
I've actually I've actually started to notice
that. Yeah. Do you know what it comes
down to in in
this? You know what it comes down to in
this community? It just comes jealousy.
Hate and jealousy in this community. You
know, I mean, it's what I was just
saying. Think I I have said that about
these people. Yeah. That they're, you
know, jealous, ain't got a life on
YouTube because it's the truth. Because
it literally is the truth. Like they
they have to bring family members up
because you own them. Like you have to
put family members up. They have to put
family members up because they know what
can they really do. They can't law you
cuz you ain't broke the law. They can't
come on your door. So the only thing
they can do is is bring family members
up because you actually destroy them
just by living a better life than them.
You know it it's it's it's actually insane, isn't
it? What we're saying. I'm coming off
this community today, bro. It's too [ __ ] weird.
This gives people excuses for this and
excuses for that and
there that people that have my [ __ ]
phone. You know what I'm saying, bro?
It's like you own them in it. Just just
just own it, bro. You know what I'm
saying? Like that's
it. That's why they do all of this
stuff. It's my last day, bro. It's just
weird. It's weird. I just had a phone. I
was on the phone with my sister and I
was saying to her, "Listen, here's the
thing. like you're lucky I'm I'm wanting
to come off of YouTube cuz I'm coming
off anyways. It's not because of you.
You know, at the end of the day, you
can't dictate to me what I can and can't
be on. If they want to put your pictures
up and be weirdos, that's up to them.
I'm my own man. I live under my roof. I
don't live with you. I'm not doing
anything wrong. I'm not in your yard
telling people to come in the door
talking about their kids. Do you know
what I'm saying? They've started it.
They're the ones that bring up family
members because I have a better life
than them. That's their problem, bro.
like you and I just said to her like,
you know, if we was making money from
this [ __ ] I'd be like, bye. I'm done
with you. Simple. I wouldn't care. If
you're, you know, it's not this and
that, I leave. No, no, no, no, no. If I
was, if I was making money on this, then
I'd stay. You know what I'm saying? Then
I would actually stay. But she just
wants to be a drama queen. And no, no,
no, no. But it's not even about that.
Why are these people even bringing
family members up? You know, they cry if
somebody brings up their family
members cuz they know that you own them,
bro. You know that you own them. It's
not even malicious. It's just the truth.
What have I said about What have I said
about these people? That wasn't That
wrong. What have I said about these
people that was that wasn't wrong?
That's slander. Nothing. You know what
I'm saying? Yeah. I'm leaving anyways,
bro. One second. I need to listen to
this voice note. It is getting super
super super weird, bro. Very very
strange. Like, no one even talks about
family. No one talks about family.
They're the ones that bring it up.
They're the ones that bring it up,
bro. It's mad, isn't it? Like, you own
them so bad. They're doing what they've
accused you of doing now, which is
crazy. It's crazy. I told you, bro. You
I was just saying this to my mom. Yeah.
You could have a You could You could be
a new person on here. Yeah. say 21, 22,
no history of saying anything to anyone.
No, no. They will target you just like
they used to do to Ant-Man and other
people. It's because it's jealousy. You
don't understand. These people are old.
They have nothing in life but YouTube.
Yeah. They're jealous of anyone with a
better life than them. Like, and they
will do what it takes to get someone
that's got a better life than them.
They're old. Think about it, bro. Yeah.
Let's just let's just say that
everything that they say about you is
the truth, which it isn't. Yeah. Guess
what? These people are old, you know?
How long have they been doing this [ __ ]
on YouTube now? You know, sat on YouTube
projecting every single [ __ ] day. You
know what I'm saying? And no one needs
to talk about their No one needs to talk
family. No, it doesn't matter what. No,
he didn't. No, no, no, no. I know why he
went to jail and it wasn't an
unthinkable thing, but he's just a
[ __ ] example. They target anyone with
a better life than them. Doesn't matter
whether you're innocent or you're
[ __ ] guilty. Do you understand this?
This is what I was trying to explain to
I'm doing normal harmless videos, wind
up videos. They're talking about family.
What the [ __ ] What the actual [ __ ]
Because you own them in every aspect.
They can't come on your door cuz you own
them. They just can't come on your door.
They can't get the police on you cuz
you've not broke no law. There's nothing
they really can do. So they bring up
family members. That's what I'm saying,
bro. [ __ ] them in it. You know what?
Yeah. I was kind of regretting all them
years ago, you know, talking about their
kids them years ago. I used to do about
I can see why now. [ __ ] them, bro.
They'll do the same thing if they had
half the chance. No one speaks about
kids. No one speaks about anything to do
with any family members, but they're the
ones that bring it up. So [ __ ] them, you
know? So absolutely [ __ ] them. We got
some [ __ ] [ __ ] here doing a
video of me
yesterday. The guy wears Primark socks.
The guy wears [ __ ] true religion. Who
can he talk about [ __ ] dress sense?
What the [ __ ] bro? It's attractive. Get
the [ __ ] over it. You know what I'm
saying? They're weirdos on here, bro.
And my sister's lucky for my sake that
I'm just leaving because I want to
leave. I'm insane. I'm leaving for ages.
I'm insane. I'm leaving for ages. But
mate, any kind of money I'd be making from here,
£500,£600, bye-bye. I'm taking the money
every month. Bye-bye. Cuz you shouldn't
be acting like this. But at the same
time, I'm coming off anyways cuz I don't
want to be on here. And it's just weird.
And you don't make no money from it. And
I've been saying this for ages, even
before today. You know, it's mad. They
know they can't do nothing to you, bro.
You think Do you think Listen, do you
think LJ can come to me like he did to
me? No. Even them three years ago, bro.
The guy shacked himself. Yeah. I was
standing in front of my mom. What can
they really do? Notice how they don't
bring up Timmy's family members cuz they
know that they could probably go there
and scare him. None of these people will
scare me. Yeah. No, they can't do
nothing to me. Do you understand? So
that's why they bring family up. You
know what I'm saying, bro? Like they
know not one of them can scare me. How
many of these people do you think live
in London, bro? A good few of them. A
good Let's be realistic about this.
Yeah, a good few of them that hate on
you probably live in London. Why don't
they come on your door? Cuz they know
they can't, bro. You know,
Yeah, bro. So that's it. Yeah, you
should have done this. You should have
done that. Bro, this place is weird. I'm
done. I'm [ __ ] done with this place,
bro. Let them have their shitty YouTube.
Look at it, man. Ant-Man. Just Just
think of Ant-Man as an example. Yeah.
He's come off this YouTube and he's been
Thailand four times in a [ __ ] year.
If that's not motivating, bro, I don't
know what motivating
is. You know, all they do is sit on
there every day hating. Is that what I
said? Is that me starting on them? Okay.
Yeah, I have started on them cuz that is
what they do. If that's your definition
of me starting on them, then yes, I have
started on them by telling them what
they do every day. Yeah. Because it is
what they do. Sat at home talking about
other people when they ain't got no
life. They do it all day, every day. And
what? Oh, don't arrest me for saying
that. [ __ ] hell. Do you know what I'm saying, bro?
Like, sat on. Look, look at it, bro.
Look, let me give you the prime example,
right? I went out on Thursday drinking.
Yeah. Went out by myself, met some new
friends, met some women, had some
drinks, enjoying myself. What were these
people doing? Sat on YouTube. Let's be
so real about this right now. Yeah. What
was these people doing? They were sat on
YouTube all by themsel hating. Yeah. You
know, I was drunk that day and I could
even I can still remember how many
people I blocked. You know what I'm
saying? I'm going out again today, bro.
So, and I'm done for two weeks. You know
what? I was going to I was going to do a
little gym video and give people
motivation, but [ __ ] them, bro. They're
going to have their shitty little
YouTube. Yeah. Same [ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
And anyone's watching, I suggest you do
the same and [ __ ] off to be honest with you. You
know, you know what I'm saying,
bro? One second. I just got sent another voice.
So yeah, I'm leaving, bro. It's too
weird. The whole like bring up family
and [ __ ] and oh, it's it's cringe, bro.
It's actually getting cringe. You know,
I only wanted some harmless banter, but
if they can't if they can't make it
harmless, then they can [ __ ] themselves.
But I'm leaving anyways. My sister's
lucky I'm leaving cuz I want to leave.
cuz I'm telling her right now, if I was
making money, I'm not going anywhere,
mate. So, but I'm coming off cuz I want
to come off because it's just too weird
what these people do. So, yeah. Don't
feel sorry for them, bro. Out of all the
times when you used to bring up their
kids years ago, cuz they're doing the
same thing when there's no other way
that they can get you. You destroy them,
bro. That's how you know they you
destroy them. No one speaks about
Timmy's family because they know they
can scare him. None of these people
scare me. They can never scare me. And
at the end of the day, there's some of
them that live in London and they still
can't scare me. So at the end of the
day, yeah, that's what it resorts to. If
it's not family, it's the boys in blue.
If it's not the boys in blue, it's
begging the black man to do something.
It's always the same with these people,
isn't it? Same dosses. And you know what
I actually noticed today when I was
actually in the bath? You actually start
becoming like these people. When you
associate with these weirdos on this
community, you actually
start becoming one of them. You know,
like I can't I can't explain it. You are
what you what you surround yourself
with. And these people are literally no
hopers. Like, and let me tell you
something. There's one thing they're
certainly jealous of is that you're
younger than them. And you can change
and they can't. So that's it, bro.
That's it. Even if you was exactly the
same as these people, you got age, they
don't even have that, you know? So
that's one thing that's already been proven.
since I'm one of the youngest people on
here was on here because I'm not going
I'm not going back. I'm not coming back
on here. But this bro after today I'm
going to have a little snooze go
out and that's it. Yeah. Anyways, back
to Thursday was meeting women made some
new friends. Never sat on YouTube. Sat
on YouTube all day every day hating. And
I noticed the younger you are and the
better you are, they hate on you more.
Have you noticed
that? Yeah, that's what it is. I've
noticed that. I've definitely definitely
noticed that because they've targeted me
more than anybody. It's because they
want to be you young, you
know, norm like don't have to [ __ ]
work and [ __ ] They they want to be you,
but because they can't be you, they'd
rather hate on
you. You know what I'm saying? So that's
what it is, bro. They're just old old no
hopers. That's what they are literally.
And you know what? Yeah. It's not about
them being on here every day. I should
have rephrased that. They're on here
every day. They can't take a day off of
YouTube. And it's what they do on here.
This it's what they actually do. It's
like they live to hate on YouTube.
That's their life to live to
hate. Hate to live. I'm saying that's
what they do,
bro. No one speaks about family members.
No one speaks about kids. And then they
still bring family up. No, I'm just done
with this community, mate. I was just
talking to my sister on the phone and I
said to her like, "Yeah, you're lucky
I'm not making money off this because I
would still be on here." But I I said to
her, I was leaving anyways. But it's
just the whole they they have to bring
family up when you know you when they
know that you own them. They've tried
the boys in blue. They've tried to beg
the black man to do everything. They
because it's always the black man. I've
noticed it's always the black the black
man they beg. They beg the black man.
That never works.
um tried money that never worked and
then when it all fails it's family
members. See, so this is why you know
years ago, right, I beat him to it. You
know, a part of me actually felt bad.
Oh, I shouldn't have. Yeah, they're just
putting pictures up on my sister and
that and then she's [ __ ] having a
tantrum. Being a bit of a drama
queen. Yeah, she's being a bit of a
drama queen. But um I just said to her
like, "You can watch my YouTube. I don't
mention their family. I don't mention
their kids. I just do harmless banter on
my channel and I just said basically
like I was coming off of this anyways.
I've been saying it for ages, so I'm
just going to come off of it. I can't be
bothered. It's weird. Anyways, mate,
it's probably a good thing to be
honest. You're not making money from it.
All you're seeing is just the same self
projectors. So now they're just not
going to get
content. They're they're just not going
to get content. I just can't be annoyed
with it now. They're just not going to
get content. So again, defeating the
object, like what you said,
Joe. Yeah, I told her like a picture is
a picture. I can't control what these
weirdos do. Like you know what they've
been doing for years. And at the end of
the day, I'm not under your roof. I live
by myself. And even if I was doing the
worst things, which I'm obviously not.
Everyone's got my channel. I'm under my
roof, not your roof. I don't need to
abide by your rules. If they want to put
your picture up and be weirdos, that's
on them, bro. Like, it's [ __ ] They're
not putting your [ __ ] But still, it's
weird. But, but at the same time, it's
still weird cuz why are they putting
pictures up of people's family when no
one's talking about their family? I
don't need to talk about their family. I
don't need to talk about their kids. I
told her like it's a picture is a
picture, but it is weird. I get it's
weird, but I just said to her like,
"You're a drama queen. Like, you're a
proper proper drama queen. You do
realize how much of a drama queen you actually are?
You know, I was telling my mom about
this as well, like no one spoke about
their kids. No one spoke about their
family. So, what's the excuse this time?
Because they can't do nothing
else. They can't come on your door cuz
they're scared. They can't call the old
bill cuz you ain't broke the law. What
realistically else can they do? They
can't beg the black man because the
black man men are not going to entertain
them, which is good. So, what what can
they do, bro? Nothing. So, they put
pictures up of [ __ ] people's [ __ ]
sisters. Why are they even doing that
anyways though? That's weird. Obviously,
it's harmless, but it's still weird. Why
are they doing all that weird [ __ ]
What? Cuz you got a better life than
them. Cuz you got more money than them.
Cuz you're better looking than them.
Come on, bro. It's harmless banter.
We're doing harmless banter. So, I'm not
taking it I'm not taking it a step
ahead. Why are
they? Truth hurts.
Maybe. It's got to be. Maybe the truth hurts. Got to
be. Yep. It's got to be the [ __ ]
truth hurts, mate. That's all it can
be. This weirdo [ __ ] It's just weird
anyways, mate. It's It's just It's just
weird. And there's no reason to even
stay on it either. I can't even say to
her, "Yeah, I'm going to You can't even
There's not even a reason to stay on it.
If you was making money or, you know, it
was like it benefited your life in a
major way, then I would obviously just
stay on it." And if she don't want to
talk to me again, that's up to her. I
don't mind, bro. It's not a
problem. I'm use as example, but there
isn't really no reason to be on here,
you know what I'm saying? So, best of
both worlds. She shuts up and you have a
better life. So, you
know, yeah, she stopped being drama
queen and you have a better life. So,
yeah, it's it works uh both ways. And
bear in mind, I'm literally I'm still
not over the hangover 100%.
Yeah, I went on the spirits and I was
[ __ ] bro. All day yesterday I was
[ __ ] Definitely sticking to beer
today. Definitely sticking to
beer. 100% I'm sticking to beer
today. And then I'm detoxing for two
weeks. I need to go to the gym before my
holiday. So, it's probably best I do
come off of it
now and call it. Saturdays just don't
feel the same without the Football Joe.
Saturdays just don't feel the same. without the
footy. No, it's not my mom or my other
sister. It's not my mom or my other
sister. No, it's not my mom. It's not my
mom. My mom knows about my channel. But
it'd be different if you was living
under their roof saying, "Oh, [ __ ] you.
Your whole family cover my door." And
then you had people coming on your door
and then people smashing your windows.
Then you're bringing trouble. I'm under
my roof and I'm not bring bringing
trouble to my door. Yet you're trying to
involve my household. That's what I'm
That's the bit I don't understand.
You're getting your [ __ ] involved with
my house when I don't even live with
you. That's the bit I don't understand.
And it's not it's it's my She's just a
drama queen. She's just a [ __ ] drama
queen. But, you know, I shouldn't even
be on here anyway. So, you know, it's a
win-win. She stops being a [ __ ] drama
queen. And I get a better life by coming
off here. So, you know, everyone's
happy. It's just a drama queen. I said
you I said you know I like you and that
you know I prefer you than my other
sisters. Some siblings just got better
but you really are a drama queen. Like
you really really
really are a drama queen. Like I've
never I've never met more of a drama
queen in my [ __ ]
life. Now I understand with the kids
[ __ ] Yeah. But no one's but it's still
but at the same time it's still weird
what they're doing. They shouldn't even
be bringing family up. Like, yeah, it's
harmless. But they still It's It's still
weird what they're doing, if that makes
sense. Why are they Why are they bringing family
up? Weird. No one's talking about their
family. I don't need to talk about any
of their family. So, that's why I just
mentioned Anita today. Because you own
them, bro. They've got to do all these
mad things. They'll do anything and
everything, but actually come at your
[ __ ] come at your
door. And you know, the reason I tell
people to come on my door is because
they hate every day. So, I just say if
you've got something to say, come and
say it to my face. That's that's what it
is. Cuz they want to hate on YouTube
every day. They know where I live, you
know? I just say it in a roundabout
way. It's safe to say they're just
generous of anyone that's got a better
life than them, man. It's got to be
that, bro. It literally has to be
that, you know? They It's got to be
that, you And I was trying to explain to
people as well, it doesn't matter who
you are, what your past is, they will go
for you. As soon as they see somebody
that's not fat, old like them, they will
go for them. You know, they will go for
anyone that's got a better life than
them, bro. It's been that way for years.
You can come, you could reverse time and
be a perfect soul on YouTube. You will
still get people that that that that do
[ __ ] that try to ruin your life. You
know what I'm saying?
Yeah. Talking about relationship. Why
don't you come out and meet me today
then? [ __ ] hell,
bro. Yeah. Them spirits are no good. Oh
my god. I'm [ __ ] dacking. Oh
man. But yeah, last try today
then. Done for two
weeks. Cuz even this like this is a
better life to them. You can go out and
drink what you when you want. I'm
meeting a friend later. They wish they
could have this life, this ongoing life.
You going out like look at went out
drinking, met some friends, met some
women, went to the cinema the next day.
I'm going out today. Supposed to go for
a meal yesterday. Never happened. This
is an ongoing life. Even though I'm not
rich. They wish they could have this
life, bro. These people on YouTube, they
wish they could. They wish they could
just have a normal, you know, I've I've
got a better life than a lot of people that are
27 in compared to like um
responsibilities and like the situation.
I'm not talking about women and that. I
mean, you're your own person. You can do
what you want when you want. It's a
pretty easygoing life. You know what I'm
saying? It's a
pretty pretty easygoing life to be
fair. And it's a very stable life as
well. You know what I'm saying? So you
know a lot of things you know in the
past few years.
So she was so cute. Joe, that tie woman
from Australia. She was so cute. Your little
face, the little
eyeballs. Oh, bless her
then. But yeah, I'm
Yeah, they brought Mont Bonty's family
up as well when when he come
on. I actually do kind of feel bad for
bringing Bonnie on here sometimes. I
think like I didn't but he could have
left at any time. I didn't know what
they were going to do, but like they
would have left at any time. Like
Yeah. Know what I'm saying?
But yeah, I was speaking to Natalie
yesterday. When I was saying when I was
drunk, it's like the reason I had a
problem with you is because of
uh it's cuz like you I've seen you talk
[ __ ] about me and she's like, "Oh, you
should try other cities like Manchester,
Birmingham." said, "Natalie, listen,
it's the same everywhere in England.
It's what it is. I expect it now." You
know, I I sent it I sent it Thursday. I
done so many approaches sober. All I got
was I've got a boyfriend is sober. And
then it got better when I started
drinking. But it's it's to be expected
anywhere now. You know, I I need to
practice what I preach. You know, I need
to remember this. Like this, it's more
than likely always going to be like it
here. But, you know, if you went out and
you tried, you can say I tried.
So, I just want to drink. Anyways, it's
never You need to expect it to happen.
Like, when I was walking back Yeah. to to KFC.
Yeah. Uh the other night, I was like,
"Oh, [ __ ] I just got two approaches. I
got a boyfriend." And I realized
something switched to I was like, "Yeah,
but you knew this was going to happen.
It's to be expected. You literally have
to expect this. How can you not expect
it? If you don't expect it, then you're
going to be disappointed, you know, and
it's been going on for years. So, I
mean, like, obviously, it's going to
happen, you silly
goose. Like, but at the same time, it is
[ __ ] up. So, it's a catch 22. Like it
is it is it is [ __ ] at the same time
because when I was walking to the
cinema yesterday uh on Thursday I was
like it is it is kind of mad how it's
hard to get a conversation out of
someone nowadays Joe it's not about a
relationship or sex it's like whatever
it is you want friend relationship
uh sex I don't know what people want you
you can barely get a conversation do you
know what they do you know what these
people remind me of in London they
remind me of do you know Star Wars the Drews
I think they're called drudes when
they're walking around like all NPCs.
Um, and there is some things I think
about that is [ __ ] up how like we
weren't warned as a child. No one told
us that. Like back when I was 19, 20, I
never got like, oh, there's no point
approaching women. They're just going to
pretend they got boyfriends. I was told
we were sold a dream. You know, it's
like even me and John, we were actually
sold a dream before we had the balls to
approach. We got told we thought that
like once we finally done it, it would
solve all our problems, Joe. Well, all
our dating problems rather, but it
never. So, we were It's some things are
still [ __ ] up though, how you're sold
a dream by people on the internet. And
but when you go out, they're like
[ __ ] Star Wars Dunes. I'm sure
they're called I'm sure they're druds.
Them [ __ ] robot things. Them white
robots. What are they, Drews? Sure they are.
Oh, they're drones. That's what they
are. No, no, no. One second. I don't think they
are. Yeah, they're drones. Like uh they're like
robots. I don't know what I'm going to
get today when I go out, but I got
nothing better to do. I'm going to go
meet a friend. So, listen to some good
music. I I I don't expect anything
today. It's going to be the same as it always
is. Yeah. Yeah. No, no, no. I I'm I'm
not saying that that's not what it is.
I'm not saying that's what it is, but
I'm and I do see it from that point of
view, but you need to see it as if
dating apps don't work and you can't
meet anyone through your friends, it's
the only option. That's that's where
you're at. So you've got to see it from
both point of views. They're scared.
That's your only way. So it's like it's
you need to see it from both point of
views. So there's there's both there's
there's both there's both u you need to
see it from both angles. You see you got
to see it as well. If you don't do this,
you wouldn't have been a virgin. You
wouldn't have met anyone. So this is the only thing
that will give you small successes. But
it's never going to be a big success,
Joe. Because do you know why? Because
it's been going on for years. Like when
me and Adman was talking about this the
other day, we was like I think the main
point is is how long it's been going on
for? [ __ ] years. Three, four
years. So at the end of the day, this
has been going on for years now. So
obviously, if it's not changed in years,
it's very unlikely that's going to
change now. Yeah, I know. So it's yeah
or whatever it
is. I've never met anyone through
friends. I've never met anyone through
dating apps. I never go on there again.
But yeah, you got to like it is what it is, isn't
it? Why do you think I didn't [ __ ] that
um Muslim girl off when she said she
just wanted to be friends? Because it's
hard enough to even make friends with a
woman nowadays. So I'd rather it than
nothing to be honest. Maybe people
change their mind and stuff. So I just
prefer it than just nothing.
So you know you Yeah. Yeah. I prefer
that than nothing to be honest.
Yeah. But at the same time, it still
shouldn't be this hard. Like you go to a
bar, club, the street, you know, you're
decent looking, you know. It shouldn't
be this hard. It shouldn't be this hard.
It should take longer and it should be
harder. But I mean, there comes a point
where it's like, you should have you
should have kind of met someone by now. It's not
normal. And when I've gone on dates,
I've made good impressions and stuff.
And you know, you do get women that are
out there just to waste people's time. I
don't know why they think that they
don't exist. They do exist. Case in
point, two months ago when I had that
foot injury, she obviously was wasting
my time on
purpose because it just just doesn't
make any sense why you'd meet someone.
It just it doesn't it doesn't make
sense. Like they are out there. These
people are out there. So
yeah, they are out there, bro. So I a
lot of approaches yesterday show. again.
Nothing mate until I started
drinking. I only got somewhere when I started drinking. So
So obviously I was in a club in it.
yeah, but it's there are there is stuck
up [ __ ] in this country, Joe. There
is too many stuck up. Like the only the
only people that replied to me yesterday
were these [ __ ] Australians.
It is that, but it's also there is too
many stuck up people in this country
that that you know, you walk around and
you see people that's got a head up their own ass. Yeah.
Yeah. It's impossible, bro. Like, cuz
you need to get a number. You need to
get a number that replies and then keep
replying and then meet you and then
stays with you. It's impossible, you
know. It might It's so hard. It might as
well just be impossible. But you have
got nothing better to do at the same
time. This Australian woman, she stopped
replying. Not the Thai one, the other
one was talking. She said, "Oh, oh, I
went back home." I said, "Oh, yeah.
Whereabouts like you living at?" Never
heard from her again. I'd hate to say
that. I didn't expect it, but I did
expect it. Happened with New Zealanders
as well. That's another thing that
happens because you need to get a
number. They need to reply.
I might just say they want to go out
later. The other ones go back to
Australia. They need to reply, then they
need to keep replying, then they need to
meet you, and then keep meeting you.
It's impossible, bro. It is actually
impossible. Like that's that's why I'm
going on a detox after today.
Um cuz it is it is impossible, bro. Like
you you know, you're going to come
across time wasters. You're going to
come across users. You know, it's
like, no, but this one lives in England.
This one lives in
England. Yeah, but you only get Yeah,
but you only get success with the
tourists because all the British are stuck
up. All the British are just stuck up.
So, your only kind of hope is with these
with somebody that lives here. You do
realize in central London, they're not
all tourists. They're not all tourists.
A lot of them, yeah, they're tourists,
but they live here. Well, not tourists,
then. They're from another country, but
they live here. Or some of them are from
England. Or some of them are American,
but they live here. They're not all
tourists that that that are going back
home. They're not all tourists that are
going back home,
bro. And if you only met British people,
you wouldn't even get a number. If there
were only English women, you would not
even get a number. They're the worst for
being stuck up. Damn it. Americans are the
worst. They're just stuck up.
Yeah, they shouldn't be stuck up though,
bro. Cuz I feel like it gives the city a
bad name. Like, do you think I can't go
to Middlesborough right now and be like,
I got more money than you. I'm basically
like like a millionaire here. But it's
weird why it changes the way they
are. Because it shouldn't make people
stuck up just because they've got more
buddies than people like but sometimes
Ant-Man was like, "Oh, like sometimes
you seem a bit snobby." Cuz with him,
yeah, I got a new phone and he said, "I
would have just got it secondhand and
paid £200." But I was like, "I like a
new phone because the battery I don't
like just know that someone's touched
the phone. I don't like knowing that
someone's like I will buy things
secondhand. I got a fridge that's
secondhand. A bigger fridge. I've got a
big fridge that's secondhand. Looks brand new.
Uh tables, chairs, but not a device. I
would never buy a device secondhand
because you don't know what people done
on it. They could have downloaded a
bunch of [ __ ] child
porn. [ __ ] child porn. Um or [ __ ]
madness on that phone. And the battery's
conked. The thing you got to think about
is is the battery. But
uh I just I would never get a secondhand
phone, you know? Even the phone I got
yesterday, it's not it's not anywhere
near the best
phone, you know? I'm just
like I'm nice to everyone, bro. I'm not
I don't think I'm better than people cuz
I'm from London. People in London think
they're better than people, but they're
really really not. And they give us a bad
name. They give us a really bad name.
I'm not similar to them at all. Then I
think that's a logical reason why you
wouldn't get a secondhand phone. I'd
never get a secondhand phone. And at the
end of the day, you know, if you're
earning good money, your lifestyle is
going to be better. You know, it's not
even materialistic. It's like if you're
earning good money, naturally your
lifestyle is going to be better.
You know, like say you're earning good
money, you live in somewhere like
London, what are you just going to just
start being a
slob? You know, of course your life is
going to change if you're brought up in
a city, you know, and you get money, but
my attitude don't
change. It's [ __ ] raining, bro. Oh,
you better stop raining, man. I'm going out later.
But I think that's the thing, you know,
people just are used to their own circumstances.
I fancy both teams to score, man. But
there's no football playing, no English
teams. I can make some money on the
football, bro. You watch when they start
again. Yeah, but then there's less
people. But London's good in so many
ways. The thing with the town is you'll
get a reputation, you know. Not London.
London's good, you know, good transport,
so many people. You can never get a
reputation, so many places to eat, so
much stuff to do. It's good to make
money here. Like, there's loads of pros in
London. It's just the [ __ ] women suck
and the people suck. Like, that's really
the only bad thing about it. Oh, and
phone snatches. I saw two people get
their phone snatched last week. Oh, boy.
Yep, they got their phone snatched. But London is
good. London is London is good, but it's
it's just that that ruins
it. Yeah, I was actually thinking of
going Blackpool today. Yeah. Fat chance
of that happening with this [ __ ]
rain. But London's good to make money.
That's the thing. Money is good in London.
So, I think I'd just always go back
home, you know, where I'm from. So,
yeah. I just like I do like London
though. It's like
even where I used to live
like even in Stratford. I prefer
Stratford than my mom's area. I get on
well more there than my mom's area. I
know people. It's more
fastpaced. It's more me. You know what I'm saying?
Like I didn't really get on well in my
mom's area. I just didn't like the neighbors
and having to wait around for things.
You know what I'm saying? I didn't like it.
Yeah. Well, they game's [ __ ] here anyways, bro.
Yo, I'm kind of getting hungry
now. I can't get a breakfast. I can't go
out in this [ __ ]
rain. Do you like my new uh large Do you
like my new phone, Joe?
What do you mean? You're almost live.
You are almost
live. What do you What do you
mean? Do I have my phone?
I know it's not the best, but I know
like I need this phone for something and
if I go around London, I know there's a
good chance of it getting snatched out
my hand. Not that I'm not prepared for it,
but I will be I'd be slightly conscious
of it. Whereas with this phone, I'm not
really going to be I'm still going to be
a bit conscious, but
like I don't know how they justify some
of their prices. Like that phone was
£400. [ __ ] that's [ __ ] expensive.
That's expensive, bro, for a [ __ ]
phone. But I didn't want a [ __ ] one and
I didn't want a really expensive one. I
wanted something in the middle. You know
when you get them 150 ones or 200 ones
and they just feel like [ __ ] in your
hand? Like you hold them in your hand
and they just feel like [ __ ] Like just so
cheap. But if I was materialistic, I
would have just bought another fold. But
I'm not paying that. And you don't
understand, Joe. you said, "Oh, yeah.
Doesn't matter how much money you get,
it's about justifying it." By the time
you've insured that phone, you're talking about
2.2K. And then also, what happens is a
new one's going to come out next year.
So, there's no way in hell you can
justify paying more than £1,000 for a
phone. No, I mean like the cold
approaches. If you cold approach in a
town, you're going to get known. Even in
somewhere like Newcastle, even like a
smaller city, you're going to get known.
Whereas, if you do it in London, no one
knows you. That's the good thing. Like,
you you wouldn't get a reputation for
doing it. See, where Antman lives, where
he used to live, cuz he's in Thailand
now, people would know him, you know,
and he he'd get banned from pubs. No one
knows me. Well, staff know me, you You
know, I'm friends with staff, but I mean
like generally I could go to the same
place every day doing approaches and no
one would know no one would know a
thing. They wouldn't expect it. They
wouldn't they wouldn't, you know, they
wouldn't know that I'm in the same place
doing it to different
people. But where Ant-Man lives, you
know, it's like he used to have to go
like Sheffield and that he used to have
to travel out like whereas in London
there's so many places.
Yeah. Yeah. But it's also the only it's
the only thing you can do at the same
time. It's not accepted, but it's the
only thing you can do. So
yeah. But yeah, but it's at the same
time it's the only thing you actually can
do really. Well, I'm going to go to some clubs later.
So, I'll go to some clubs later and see
what uh funny thing Joe is, um I saw two
women yesterday in the cinema by
themselves. You know who who you know
these little projecting
40year-olds that like to say, "Oh, you
do this alone. You do that alone." When
they're sat on YouTube alone all day of
their lives, every day of their lives.
You do realize that uh I saw two women
go to a cinema by themselves. Yeah. Yep. So, it's
like it's it's mad they talk about
alone, but they're the ones that are sat
on YouTube alone every day. They ain't
got a life. They're just projectors.
This is why I'm leaving, bro. There.
I'll show you what these people are. One
sec. Got one here,
actually. Wow, that Coke is still cold.
I've got a
can. No, they went bad themsel as in
individuals. One woman was by herself. I
was talking to her for about 15 minutes.
Yeah, she was older, like 40 odd. She
was like wearing glasses. She wasn't
dating material, but I know, you know,
we've got something in common. You know,
we both like horror films. She was
telling me when new horror films was
coming out. We just talking for 10 15
minutes. If only the younger generation
could be like that cuz we was there
before the adverts. So, we was just
talking and we saying how they don't
make them like they used to. And then
there was another woman that come by
herself and there was a woman with
another woman. So, yes, people do go to
the cinema by himself. It makes perfect
sense to go by
herself. I'm constantly by my by myself
going to the cinema. Yes, cuz I want to
go and watch the film. I don't want to
be with someone else, you know. I don't
want to go with another person. I want
to go by
myself because I want to watch the
film. You know what the [ __ ] Why do you
need something? But again, it's just
projecting because these people are
always by themselves. They're sat on
YouTube like [ __ ] man. You've seen Lord
[ __ ] Jay on Saturday. Yeah. Sat by
himself. All of this by yourself [ __ ]
mate. They need to look at their own
lives. They've been by themselves for
years on YouTube. They ain't got a
single friend to their name. They're talking about
themselves. Yeah, but when I show that
I'm with people, you just make excuses
and say I don't know
them. Bro, listen. Even when I show that
I'm with friends, you still say that I'm
not with friends. So, what's the point? You
know, so even when I show that I'm with
people, you say that I don't know them.
So, bro, it's just projection. Like I said,
anyways, this projector.
Yeah. [ __ ] It's heavy,
bro. Right. I'll show
you. This is what LJ's following
is. One sec.
There. A projector. I got a projector. Disable
projectors. That's them. That's
literally all you see on his channel.
You know what I'm
saying? I would class So I would class
him as being alone large ass. He doesn't
have mates. He doesn't have mates at
all, mate. I'm the only one on here
that's been seen with friends, women,
money, a life. Ah, [ __ ] off, bro.
Listen, that guy does not have no
friends. Not one single friend to his
name. That is that's why they say you
got no friends cuz they talk about
themselves. Again, these people are old.
They're old. [ __ ] disabled. Ain't got
a pot to piss in. They're just disabled,
bro. That's why they come in here cool
people skin. And this is how cold it is.
Yeah. This clan has been here overnight
and it's freezing. The the coke is still
cold like it's been in the fridge. Isn't
it supposed to be [ __ ]
summer? But these people don't have no
friends. They've got no money. You know
what I'm saying?
[ __ ] they're sat on YouTube every day
and got a life. Can't take one day off
YouTube. It's And it's what they do on
YouTube as well. It's not the fact that
they're just on YouTube. It's what they
do. It's so weird. That's why I don't go
on's channel anymore. It's so
weird. It's the same projectors, the
same talking, the same negativity that
they spout every day. You know what I'm
saying, bro? It's It's so weird. There's
no content on their channel
either. I think these people have been
bullied in life. That's the only thing
it could be, bro. Like, I think they've
actually been bullied in their life to
get like this. You know what I'm
saying? I was going to give him some
advice, you know, go to the gym. I'm
going I'm going to the gym on Monday.
So, but [ __ ] them, bro. I need to, bro.
I need to go to the gym, bro. Cuz soon
as I see my belly getting a tiny bit
big, the first thing that comes in my
mind is bomb. I don't know why, but
that's the first thing. I was like, this
is how this this guy
started getting older. You know, you
don't want to be like them. Obviously,
Lord J's ob beast, but you
know, you don't want to end up like
that. Yeah, but guess what, bro? Okay, I
can come off of YouTube for two weeks
and I can come back online and it would
still be the same people. It'd still be
the same people every
day, you know, same projecting people
every day, same repeating people every
day as Bonnie likes to call it. So, so
yeah, Bob is the first one that comes to
my mind, bro. I'm not even
joking. Can you hear that rain? You can
actually hear it. [ __ ] me.
Yep. I've lived the life, but I went
traveling all over the country. I went
abroad. Done it all in a year. They were
sat on YouTube, Joe. They were sat on
YouTube. They were sat on YouTube. Oh
yeah. Nothing would ever
change. You can come back in 9 years.
You can come back in nine Oh my god,
that rain is bad. [ __ ]
bro. You can come back in nine years.
It's It's still going to be the
same. But you know what? Yeah, but I
think Antman was right though, Joe. He
said they're just not interested in this
country. They're just not interested in
this country. That's funny, bro.
Yeah, that is funny, bro. Yeah,
obviously he's right, but you know, you
still just go and send it in
it. They're just not interested in this
country, the country of Great Britain.
That's [ __ ] funny, bro.
Yeah, they're NPCs.
So, this is uh bro. So, what do you
think's going to happen when I go out
approaching today? Richie, Rich, Rich,
Rich Richie, what do you think's going to happen?
Richie, you'll like it down here, son.
You'll never have to grow up. Yeah, I've
almost finished Grand Theft Auto San
Andreas. though. I love the story. The
story line is absolutely
ace. The story line is absolutely bonkers.
Absolutely [ __ ] bonkers. It is. It's
It's a lovely site.
Yep. I still remember the story line,
bro. Even from all them [ __ ] years
ago. Oh, you'll like it down here,
son. Too much, bro. You'll like it down here,
son. You'll like it down here, son.
You'll never have to grow
up. Oh, there's another horror film
coming next month, July. It's called uh
I know what you did last
summer. San Andreas is the best,
bro. I want to do some football bets,
bro. Doesn't feel the same. I'm done
with roulette. I'm done with slots and
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] I don't know,
man. I want to do some football
bets, but there's no football
playing. I think I won't get mad at it
anymore. I just want to do like an 80
pound [ __ ] I just want to do an 80
pound both teams to
score. You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
Oh my god,
bro. What is my life?
Eh. Hopefully people out today in the
clubs. No, I should be. Yeah, they've
got to [ __ ] be, mate. I'm going to
wear my Why I smell weed?
I smell weed,
bro. You smelling weed? I'm going to
wear um Ammani. I'm going to wear that
Ammani jumper with jeans and my new
trainers. Switch it up a little bit
since it is my last try today.
So, give it a whirl on
it. Give it a [ __ ] whirl.
He said he's going to be free after this
time. So, I'll wait for
him. It's Saturday as well, so the
trains will be 24 hours. So, we ain't
got to rush to get
back. It's going to be [ __ ] bonkers
today, can't we? It's going to be bonkers,
lad. We're going to be getting on it.
The de lad.
Why the [ __ ] is the weather like
this? Why is the weather like
this? Well, after today I'm gone, bro.
I'm deleting all my
videos. That's weird, bro. You got my Instagram,
Cory? Yeah, it's so weird.
Bless you if it's not your little thing
then. Oh, bless
you. Yeah, Instagram [ __ ] in it, bro.
But sure, you can have me on Snapchat
cuz I will be done with this today, bro.
I can't be dealing with my sister being
a drama queen. And you shouldn't even
just be on here anyways, bro. I mean,
you you you left for 9 months, isn't
it? Let the projectors project, you
know, for so long. Yeah. I was trying to
make money off of YouTube on my other
channel. The amount of money I used to
spend putting money into it and you
can't even make money on it, bro. You
can't even make money on YouTube
anymore. And [ __ ] me, bro. Like I I
tried so hard with all the content
videos, the traveling videos, and I
still didn't they still didn't offer me
partnership. I still wasn't nowhere near
eligible, which is [ __ ] man. I spent a
lot of money on that channel, you know.
That's why I didn't care when it was
gone. You know, I've still got the
videos, most of them. I wasn't making
money from it. So, [ __ ] it. In
it. Yeah. I've got another channel,
Cory. Well, I've got another YouTube
channel which I'll be sticking to one
that no one knows about. But in terms of
this community, it's it's just
weird. But you know what I was actually
thinking of doing? I think this is just
the craziest. I think this is just me I
think this is just me being crazy, bro.
But I was thinking of going to Belfast
and becoming a becoming the king, taking
over, you know, taking that crown, you
know, and we'll see. He'll be laughing
then. Just go there and take what's
mine. You know what I'm
saying? Just just becoming just becoming
the king. Just completely take over.
Just shut down the whole channel in it,
bro. That would shut down his whole
channel cuz he wouldn't be able to come on YouTube
again and I'd wear my crown. Yeah. I'd
have it I'd have it waiting for me. I
can completely take
over. You know what I'm saying?
completely and utterly just just shut
just put put each channel in shutdown.
Yeah. Yeah. Put your channel in complete
another [ __ ] shutdown,
matey. But it's [ __ ] mode. This
community [ __ ] mode for the grasses.
It's full of
self-reflectors. Yeah. It's not worth
being on here.
Somebody sent me a voice note. Yeah,
I'll take I'll take the crown, bro, and
I'll I'll take what's mine. Take what's
mine. But yeah, we're already beating
these people, bro. As soon as you come
off it, you're already beating these
people. You're younger than them. You're
better looking than them. You got more
money than them. You know, we're already
beating these people, man. We're already
people. You beat them just by
existing. You know, all they write is
just negative [ __ ] every [ __ ] day on
YouTube, man. Every single day on
YouTube. Writing [ __ ] negative
[ __ ] Every day.
Yeah. See if you go on L's. Yeah. Right now.
Yeah. The M can't even afford a bed.
You've got zero chance of mont skin and
he's anxiety. See, they just talk about
themselves, bro. Look, you could I'll
give an example right now for you. See,
do you see what I'm saying, bro? They
they just people that hate themselves.
They project. Exactly,
bro. That's what I'm saying, bro. They
talk about themselves for
years. They must not do their mental
health any good in it. Yeah. They talk
about themselves every day,
bro. Trying to tell me I can't afford a
bed when I have a I literally have a 500
bed. I literally have a 500
bed. Literally a£500 bed, bro. Like,
it's it's not even a joke. I don't have a bed.
Bro, but you see what I'm saying? It's
just the same pathetic spasticated
people every day, bro. It's not worth being on
it. Maybe it's a good thing in a way of
my sister being a drama queen because,
you know, I shouldn't even really be on
there to be
honest. They talk about themselves every
day. I'm surprised they don't get bored
like of talking about themselves every day. You
know, it must be hard, isn't it, being them?
It must be really hard being these
people. Is it? It must be really hard
being them. Think about what I'm doing
today. I'm going out for a drink. I'm having
fun. I'm having fun. You know what I'm
saying? I'm having fun. Fun in the sun.
I'm having fun. And then they're going
to just be [ __ ] sat on [ __ ]
YouTube. One second, bro. Someone's calling me.
Right, let me get my clothes out for
today then. Oh, this is going to be a long
day. This is going to be a long
one. But God loves a try, don't they?
God loves a try. And you know, do you
know the good thing about this approach
and [ __ ] is it gives me
exercise. Gives me the exercise I
need. You know what I'm
saying? But yeah, and I need to put my
some clothes out. Jeans, jumper,
trainers. Oh, [ __ ]
me. Yeah. And some
trainers. The new ones. I'm going to
wear the new ones today. I wore the VPs
yesterday, so Yeah, man.
They tried to call me a ma, bro. These
people are a ma. Tell them to show their
face and stop hiding behind a fake
account and you will see the definition of
mas. If these people Richie right literally
uh if these people literally bro
um these people really are the
bunters. These people are the bunters.
The real life
ones. Yeah. Proper bunters. Proper
proper proper bunters.
Isn't it mad how they tried to call me a
m yet I'm better looking than them and
I've been with more women than them? It
sounds so typical, isn't it? But it's
mad. They really talk about themselves.
Do they not realize they're just
affecting their own lives when they when they do
this? I'm starving, bro. I am actually starving.
Um, yeah, exactly,
bro. Yeah, I'm gone. I won't be on here
again anyways. So, see you in another lifetime. Bye.