[Music]
Get up there, buddy.
sir. Just waiting for my little man. Hey [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. How about again? [Music]
Hey, I got three numbers.
I've got three numbers. Three
numbers. Three numbers. Well, five. Five. Five.
Hey, that woman from Australia blocked
me. I'm going to write her a
poem. That woman from Australia, she
blocked me. I'm going to write her a
poem. I'm going to write her a poem. Yeah.
I'm going to ride a pirate pirate man. [Music]
I'm going to ride her. All right.
Hey, we knew a load of We knew loads of
times we'd be going here. We've been there.
Wherever. I never thought we'd be going Australia. Mate,
listen. You [ __ ] blocked me.
Who? What? He blocked me. You get fire. [Applause] [Music]
Wait for 10
minutes. kind of fun. [Music] [Applause] [Laughter] Wait. Dancing. It's okay.
Man, I got three numbers. I catch I got
three numbers, but I got five, but two
of them were fake. Yeah, that woman from
Australia blocked me. But I'm going to
I'm going to send her a poem. I got two
numbers. I'm going to send her a poem.
I'm going to send her a [ __ ] to wait for my
friend. Someone that tried to attack me
last year's in the same
pub. This is going to end bad though.
I'm going to write. Yeah,
bro. Yeah, bro. [Music]
Hey, someone tried attacking me last
year. I'll s a table and see him again.
B I think he's gone
though, mate. I'm going to write a
[ __ ] poem. I lost 20 pound of fish
and 20. 20 lost. Done. She join me to
it. Watch. Fish to me. I'm going to
write her a poem.
I'm going to write a [ __ ] choreograph
100% though. These boots will make you
fall in love, mate. Yeah,
brother. It's a
madness. I'm going to write a poem. I
got two numbers. You ain't leaving me
like that, mate. I got three real
numbers. Two fake ones. I'm going to
message this one from Australia. Australia. Yeah. [Music]
You [ __ ] worked. I was [ __ ] good.
I was talking to you for 15
minutes and you [ __ ] done me
over. You [ __ ] done a [ __ ] dirty
on the cat. You [ __ ] down the cat.
Yeah, I'm going Australia. [ __ ] this.
I'm [ __ ] going Australia, man. [ __ ]
this [ __ ] I'm good. I don't care. I
don't give [ __ ] [ __ ] this, mate.
Yeah. [ __ ] me over again. Time [ __ ]
dirty on me. Yeah. Time and time
again. Oh, [ __ ] that. I'm going. [ __ ]
this [ __ ] Yeah. I'm going, mate. I'm
[ __ ] going, mate.
Watch. I'm going to come there, mate.
I'm going to make you love me, bro. I'm
going to come to perm, Australia, and
I'm going to make you love me.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm going to come to
Australia and make you love me.
Yeah. I'm going to make you love me. [Music]
Yeah. Ready? Ready for clubbing? Yeah.
I need to go with my boy. Yeah. One sec.