Oh, [ __ ] me.
[ __ ] Turn off all the lights
there. Zippy, you never know when you're
falling towards the Zippy. Oh, [ __ ]
me. All I can say is absolutely [ __ ] me,
bro. Got a trace and a half,
mate. Oh, mate. [ __ ]
me. [ __ ] me. One second.
I got three numbers, bro. I can't
believe that tight Aussie blocked me.
I'm going to send her a poem, mate,
right now. Even if I need to pay
another£35 for the [ __ ] text. So be
it, mate. I don't
care. At the end of the day, bro, man's
got to do what
it is, bro.
Yeah, I'm [ __ ] pissed off, bro. I got
three numbers to be fair. I thought we
was going to get
five. Um, we got we got three.
So, I'm [ __ ] pissed off, bro. No way,
[ __ ] me, bro. If you got home all
right, [ __ ] me, Daz. No, I didn't pull,
bro. I got three numbers and was talking to people,
but all I got was like, I've got a
boyfriend. I've got a boyfriend. I've
Mate, you know that Australian, she
[ __ ] blocked me, bro. I was like, "No
way, bro. What the
fuck?" Me again, thinking I'd be Yeah.
So, [ __ ] hell, bro. Like, the madest
thing about it is you replied to my
message. You put a lover heart on my
message. You replied back, bro, and you
you [ __ ] blocked me. What the
[ __ ] I can't believe it, bro. This is
This is just crazy,
bro. This is just utterly insane,
mate. This is just [ __ ] madness, bro.
But yeah, I got like Yeah, it was the
same [ __ ] today. I got boyfriends. I got
boyfriends. But [ __ ] me, bro. What the
[ __ ] This is insane, bro.
I don't find none of it funny at all,
bro. I think it's actually mad, mate.
That's not even funny,
man. That's [ __ ] up, bro. I swear
these people are [ __ ] in their
head. It's like, what? So, you'll sit
there. Yeah. You talk to someone, you'll
love the message, you reply back, and
then you'll block someone. That's a
madness. Well, cuz I sent one message.
Watch. I'm I'mma guilt trip you right
now, mate. I'm going to write a [ __ ]
poem, man. I'm going to guilt trip the
[ __ ] out of you, man. You know what that
means? That's putting someone on a [ __ ] guilt
trip. I don't think any of it's funny,
mate. I think that's that's actually
[ __ ] up, bro. And you know, we're used
to laughing at everything, bro, but
that's not even funny, mate. I wish I
could even laugh at it. That's just
disgusting, bro. Not even joking.
It just don't make sense. You know, I I
messaged Anman. I told him about this
[ __ ] as well,
bro. Yeah. Well, that's me done for a
month. Anyways, I've done all I could
do. I can't believe that. When you be
Wouldn't you be pissed off, Dad? Yeah. I
was chatting up this little tie thing
from Australia on a on a Thursday.
Talking for about 20 minutes. Yeah.
Combo's flowing. Combo is flowing.
[ __ ] is flowing,
bro. Combo's flowing, bro. Yeah. Imagine this, bro.
Yeah. And then I'm writing back, "Hi, it
was nice meeting you last night and chat
with you. How's your day going?" He put
a love heart. Hey, it's good. Quite hung
over though. How about you? I wrote
same. I just come back from the cinema.
Nothing. I put Hey, I was thinking we
could meet up either tomorrow, Sunday
before you leave, before you go back to
Australia. You block me. What the [ __ ]
bro? What's the point of you giving me
your number and replying and putting
another hot, bro? What the
[ __ ] This is It's mad, bro. But I knew
after I lost 20 on Fishing Frenzy as well,
but thought I was kind of driven to do it.
Um, and it's not good,
bro. That's not even funny, bro. I'm
going to write her a message. Well, so
I'm going to guilt trip the [ __ ]
Watch. That's just [ __ ] piss. But I
told you after today, I won't expect
nothing and I'm giving up for a month
anyways. Like I probably spent a bit
more money today than I was actually
even supposed to. But yeah, it did kind
of upset me, bro. Like at the end of the
day, I know you're supposed to expect these
things. Bye-bye, Virgin.
Um, you know, you know, I spoke to some
French woman and you know, she she gave
me a number as well, but it's not the
point. But that that actually pissed me
off, bro. And that and that's the end.
And that's Oh
[ __ ] this 19year-old's been messaging
me. She's back on the
scene. Oh [ __ ] I didn't even realize
she was she calling
me. That Australian thing upset me, but
I'm not going to lie to
you. I like to a hell of a lot, bro. And
I've never liked a tie person
before. Just to have someone to [ __ ]
talk to and you [ __ ]
off. But why you can't come back? You
can't come back to my life. You [ __ ]
off for like two, three [ __ ] months.
What do you think? You're just going to
come back now and it's all going to be normal
tet. It's not normal. It'll never be normal, bro.
Yeah. Some madness. And I met some guy
that I wasn't expecting anything today,
bro. I don't even care about the I got a
boyfriend [ __ ] but
it's that pissed me off, bro. What the [ __ ] man?
Yeah, I said to my friend as well, I
just couldn't let it
lie. I just couldn't let it
lie. I'm saying no happens, bro. How do
you think people end up like
this all the
time? Oh, I see still stalking me, bro. Bye-bye,
Virgin. See you later, Virgin. Virgin boy. Bye-bye, Virgin. Oh,
what? Yeah, this 19year-old
come at the right time cuz I've given up
in this country. I got three numbers.
cuz I ain't messaged them yet. But I
just can't be bothered with it anymore,
bro. And then not to mention the people
that you got to deal with the [ __ ]
and that. It's like,
bro, use Antman, bro. Use Ant-Man as
motivation. That's crazy. Scary,
bro. I get it. You live in Australia
now. But don't you don't you think
there's a there's a way about things?
There's a way to do things
and it's just scary, bro. I'm not going to lie. It's very scary. Bye-bye,
Virgin. Oh man, what the
[ __ ] Oh, infield this.
So, got three numbers. I only got one on
the street as well. And I made, you know
what, to be honest, I made a new friend
today. We were sat there talking for
about 20 minutes. No, it must have been about 25
minutes. Um, but
yeah. Yeah. 19y old come back, but it's
not good enough, mate.
That pissed me off,
bro. Yeah. Bye-bye,
Virgin. Oh, [ __ ] bro. Oh, got this person here. Yeah.
Nah, you ain't got my new channel, mate.
You ain't got my new channel. That's [ __ ] You
know. Nah. Uploaded, mate. Listen, you
don't know my new channel. You said you
was going to find my new channel within
an hour and you ain't found it, mate.
You're just a fat loser that ain't got a
life. You're not married. You ain't got
no wife. You ain't got no kids. You're a
weirdo. That's all you are is a [ __ ]
Yeah, I can't believe this 19year-old's
come back. Well, 20 year old's come
back. She's kind of come back at the
right time. Brit
Bong. Anyways, bye-bye, loser. Yeah,
Brit, I've done a lot of approaches
today, man. I managed to get free numbers,
but yeah, I got a lot of I've got
boyfriends, but I that's the bit I was kind of
expecting. I was kind of expecting it.
You know what I'm saying?
But it's uh I wasn't
expecting this person to [ __ ] me over,
bro. No, it's got to be about4 because
obviously I'm I'm using an English
number. Yeah, I'm [ __ ] in my I'm actually Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, it's going to be about
three or4 pound, I'm guessing.
Oh, at least I got three numbers, I
guess. But it's not the point about
getting numbers, bro. Like, the thing
is, Brit Bong, obviously, I'm giving up
for a month. It's not about today,
but you you got to accept it. I got this
person messaging me, but it's always
going to be the same thing in this
country. Brick wrong forever and
always. It's always going to be the same
thing in this country, bro.
Bye-bye. Like, wrong. Like, all I saw
today, bro, was just a bunch of like
stuck up [ __ ] I hate using that word
[ __ ] bro. Like I don't even like it,
bro. It sounds very unccooped, but um
um I don't like using it, but it is what
is. She must have come back to London.
They always come
back. You've never had a what ride, LJ?
Listen. Yeah. You've never been to Asia,
LJ. You've never been to Asia
ever? You've never been to Asia? Cuz I
went out today, bro. That's the last
time I'm going out for a month. I got
this 19year-old up my [ __ ] ass again.
Well, I'll be 20 now anyways. But
yeah, let's stop talking about
yourself. Yeah. So am
I. Oh, listen. You never been to
Asia. How have you never been to
Asia? You never been to Asia, man. That's
crazy. No driving license. Never been to
Asia. Not well traveled. Because let's
face it, you've not really been anywhere
for your age. You've been basically
nowhere. What? America a few times.
Nothing. Not nothing. It's not [Music]
Um, you actually think it's [ __ ]
funny, mate. Anyways, I need to get I
need to write a love poem,
mate. Never thought I'd be doing this again,
LJ. Never ever thought I'd be [ __ ]
writing a love poem again.
I said this to my friend today. We was
drinking and getting [ __ ] We're going
to end up in prison, mate. We're going
to We're actually going to end up in
prison. And you hear a little smirk say
L. We're going to end up in some serious
[ __ ] here. Seriously.
Yeah. We're going to end up in some uh
the real serious [ __ ]
here. And then you got these people just
[ __ ] just smiling about it. LJ, it's not funny,
mate. It's not funny,
mate. Yeah, I almost had a fight today.
This guy was being a cocky [ __ ] RJ, and
I couldn't let it
lie. Couldn't let it lie, mate. I had to
go back to the smoking area. I couldn't
let it lie,
mate. I couldn't let it lie, bro.
But that Yeah. Well, this is 20 yards back.
Anyways, you come at the right time
because I'm [ __ ] done here for a
month anyways, bro. I've got these three
numbers. I'll text
them. You I told you, LJ, if somebody
breaks my heart again, it's just going
to stop talking about
itself. Um Yeah.
You know if my heart breaks again RJ
um it will stop bit wrong it will stop
completely if my heart gets broken again it will
stop it will stop completely
Hey, then that's the end of it, mate.
No, I didn't lie about nothing, mate. I
already told you I wrote to that
Morgan. I already told you I wrote to
that Morgan two weeks ago at 3:00 in the
morning. I told her about herself and
her dad and her boyfriend.
[ __ ] pair of [ __ ] mate. And you
know what? I won't as well. But it's not
to worry anyways, LJ. I found a new
love. I found a new love in Australia, LJ.
So, you know what I'm saying?
Yeah. I found the new I found. Yeah.
What do you think about J? I found a new
love. A [ __ ] new love. She's living
life. Yeah, she's living life. Skim with
ugly tattoos with an ugly boyfriend. I'd
rather have my life than have
hers. Anyways, see you later, fat boy.
Go lose some weight, fat
boy. Fat, ugly bone. Anyways, uh
yeah, the power couple
way the good old power
couple, whatever that [ __ ] means.
Yeah, that's all right, bro. I don't
mind who laughs, but they will never say
it to my face.
But guess what, bro? That's fine. I
don't mind. But they would never say it
to my face. Just like you would never
say anything to my face, so I don't
really give a
[ __ ] A Tim. [ __ ] Tim. That's why I'm
going. But she will never say anything
to my face. She's a
[ __ ] She's a [ __ ] [ __ ] That's
what she is. A [ __ ] [ __ ] That will
never say anything to anyone's
face. Oh man. talking about
yourself. Don't know how many times you
have to keep saying just talking about
yourself and you get blocked. You got
the talking about
yourself. So many self projectors.
Yeah. Yeah. Mate, if you book the
flights, I will send you the money,
mate. You book the flights, I'll send you the
money. I don't even know why I messaged
that Morgan and
[ __ ] the LJ. Them [ __ ] were laughing
at us. Yeah, listen.
Listen. Them [ __ ] were laughing at us.
That's what they were doing. They were laughing at
us and I just
[ __ ] I just [ __ ] snapped, man.
They were laughing at
us. Bye-bye, virgin
boy. Go get laid. Stop being a
virgin. Yeah, [ __ ] virgin. But yeah,
they were they were laughing at us,
LJ. Them [ __ ] were laughing at us.
But it doesn't matter. But I'm going to
Thailand anyways. I got this 20 year old
back. So I'm going to stay with her and go Thailand.
Um I'm going Thailand. So I'm going to
Thailand in [ __ ] 3 weeks. So I don't
give a [ __ ] mate. That's one place you've never
been. I'm done
for. It's a good thing cuz I can get
this [ __ ] to come out and keep sucking
my dick. So I don't give a
[ __ ] She's my only hope now. Anyway,
sir, I was going to go Australia, LJ,
and [ __ ] live with this
person, but it was all a
lie. Got sold a
dream. Sold a
dream. It's not nice though, is it LJ?
To be sold a
dream. I'm sure you can relate. I think
everyone in their life has been sold a dream.
Something else being sold a dream,
mate. Something has to be sold a dream,
mate. Maybe I'm just meant for this 20,
bro. Maybe that's telling you something, is
it? Yeah, maybe it is.
And the thing is, LJ, you laugh at it,
but a lot of people have committed suicide over
it. You remember that on rock and roll
this thing? A lot of people have
committed suicide over
it. Just a bit
drunk. Listen, Jamie, you need to get a
life. You fat
loser. You've been stalking me and LT
now for a very, very long time, mate.
You're just a fat loser. Stalker, you
ain't got a life.
Bro, so she's come at the right
time. I told you she'd come
back. The only one that's been rejected
is you by Britney, you [ __ ] virgin.
Bye-bye. You will see in four months,
bro. No one cares about Morgan. I don't
know why you keep putting it up. No one
cares about that little slapper.
You're obsessed with my sloppy seconds,
bro. Jesus Christ. You should know when
to leave things
alone. They were
saying that's what I'm saying to you,
RJ. There's a time to walk away in
life. And I don't think you know when that time
is. There's a time to walk away, Lord J.
Yeah, there's a time to walk away,
LJ. Yeah, you learn that you're alive, lad.
I'm done anyways. But
this version, I'm going to start
screenshotting that [ __ ] now, actually.
Yeah, I'm going to start screenshotting that [ __ ]
Sorry, I'm a bit high right now. I need
to stop screenshotting that
[ __ ] Yeah, one
sec. Only one that's been rejected is
you by Britney. You [ __ ]
burden. Wait, hold up.
You know, I you [ __ ] virgin. Oh,
but you used to say as well about
virgins and this person's a virgin. You
know all about virgins being the biggest
one yourself. See, my London, you see
see my London accent is quite strong. I
would say my London accent is quite uh
it's quite strong. Very strong indeed.
So yeah, you know all about virgins
obviously being the biggest one
yourself. You know, you know all the
telltale signs, don't you? Virgin
boy. [ __ ] virgin boy.
But we got another Australian here. Yeah.
Anyways, I'm about Hey, listen. Bit
bomb. Yeah, it's [ __ ] up, bro. Did you
go out today? Bit
bong trying to think. Yeah,
bro. I Dave's chicken and that, bro.
But it's the same old,
man. It's the same old here. But I'm not
complaining cuz I knew what it was going
to be like. This country will never
change. But obviously I've got this
person that's come back and that and it
doesn't make up for
it. It's not going to make up for it. It
is [ __ ] bro. Like you know the thing
is Brit B. Yeah. We got to laugh at it.
Not not laugh at it, but obviously we've
got to expect it. Yeah. Cuz it's England
and that is it.
But then at the same time it is kind of [ __ ] up by Virgin.
Um yeah block you virgin. Um obsess my
sloppy seconds as usual virgin. Um Brit
B. So like obviously you got to expecting that
but you find it mad like how you can't
even get a conversation out of people
nowadays. You can't speak to people.
people aren't really talking and that it's so
like it's mad, isn't it? It's like an
NPC world that we live
in. But at the same time, I don't really
want this 20-year-old back at the end of
the day. Like, if she were messaging me
and calling me,
but it's [ __ ] up. Like, I don't care a
bit wrong cuz obviously I expect it, but
at the same time, you do need a reality
check. Like obviously you can't help but
think about it sometimes if you can't
even get a conversation out of someone.
Do you really think you're going to get
a relationship out of
someone? It's bro I I obviously I was
drinking today just bit and I got it
about a million times. I've got a
boyfriend. I've got a boyfriend. I've
boyfriend. Bro, I got it loads today.
Bro, I'll tell Antman all about it. Oh
yeah, the 19year-old's come back by the
way. Cactus calling me and [ __ ]
messaging me. I didn't even realize till I come
back. But I kind of don't want to take
her back because, you know, you said you
was going to unblock me in a week. You
took months and now you're up my ass
again. It's not good, bro. Yeah, that
Aussie was bad, bro. That's [ __ ]
pissed me off,
bro. Anyways, I'm out of here in like
three weeks, so I don't give a [ __ ]
It is. It's to be expected.
But yeah, it's to be expected.
But it's scary, bro. It is scary,
man. It is scary though. Is it,
Cactus? It is scary, ain't it,
Cactus? Yeah, there was loads of I've
got boyfriends today, bro. Loads of them.
got three numbers.
But and then Australian one messages me
back. But I don't want that Australia. I
want the Filipino
Australian. I just I'm just going to go
to Australian. [ __ ] it, mate. Mate, you
know what I'm saying? Like maybe make
love. I was thinking that maybe if I go
there, we can maybe make
love. I don't understand it. Why speak
to somebody for 15 20
minutes? You've you've replied to the
message. You put a love heart. Okay, you
might have not seen each other again for
years. You live in [ __ ] Australia,
but what the [ __ ]
man? To then like block. It's [ __ ] insane,
mate. This will never change, bro. I'm writing a
poem. [ __ ] this. I'm writing a poem, mate.
See, we done this with English cactus.
We done this with American. We never
thought we'd be doing it with
Australian, bro. [ __ ]
this. What the [ __ ] I'm like right now,
bro. I'm stealing.
But then I see some guy that tried to
attack me like a year ago. It's just a
proper [ __ ] up
day. Enough of it, man. To be honest.
None of it's funny, mate. None of it's
funny. None of it at
all. But at least there'll still be a baby Peter
Cactus if I get with this 20-year-old,
19, 20 year old. It's got to be 20 now.
So, at least not not all was lost in it,
but it's not the point.
It's not the point, bro. It's It is
[ __ ] up. It is [ __ ]
up. You know what I'm saying?
Yeah. Yeah. I think I was literally just
[ __ ] I think I was created, bro. I
don't even think I've got parents. I
think I was actually created, bro. I'm
not even joking, you know?
I can't believe they've all got
boyfriends. No, I don't look nothing
like her. I don't look nothing like my family,
bro. No, I don't look nothing like my sister.
I don't know what pictures you've been
looking at. I don't look nothing like
any of them. Don't know why. It just
happens, doesn't it? Some people don't
look like their family, man. It just
happens. You know, I don't look like any
of them. And my other sister I don't even talk
to. Sometimes it's better that way, you
know. But I just stop talking to them. I
speak to one of my sister and my mom
obviously, but I don't speak to her.
It's going to have to be that, mate.
that. I wanted that [ __ ] Australian,
mate. I liked it when she was giving me attention.
Cactus, that's my
mama. Oh, it's another Australian
messaging me, but that's not my real mommy.
Cactus, you're not my real mama. I mean,
mama. You're not my
mama. Do you remember that? [ __ ] hell. Yeah.
I was drinking beer on the street and all
sorts. Yeah, Cactus is always the same.
I've got a boyfriend, bro. [ __ ]
hell. They're like NPCs.
It's like you take a brief.
Yeah. I'll come to Australia and make
you love me. Remember that one chapters?
I'll make you love me.
Yeah. I'll make you love me.
So you expect it like when you speak to
somebody for one minute or two minutes,
you expect it. Oh, they're drunk. Oh,
they just block you the next day. You
expect it. But not in this kind of
context. Like it depends on the context,
you see. See, it's very common. It's not
common when there's that context. You
know what I'm saying? It depends on the
context. I need to go to bed. I'm
Well, guess I talk about a 19year-old, I guess.
Yeah. She misses the money, mate. She
misses the [ __ ] money. That's what it
is. It's [ __ ] up. But
yeah, you know what I mean?
It's [ __ ] up,
bro. It's [ __ ]
up. I'm going to sleep, mate, cuz I'm
[ __ ] Well, I'm going to write this poem
and then go to
sleep. What I'm saying,
mate? Yeah. What could
happen? I don't want to impregnate your
heart. I just want [ __ ] Yeah. [Music]
Yeah, I'm out of here,
bro. They all got
boyfriends. They've all got
boyfriends. Oh, bro. He must have been
[ __ ] when he was sending that in it.
They've all got
boyfriends. Cactus. What do you actually
think the problem is? I think there's
just too many stuck up [ __ ] in this
country. I mean, that's the only thing it
can It sounds mad. Obviously, it sounds
bad for people that don't leave the
house or that, but that's
realistically the only thing it it it it
can it can be. Like, think of it, bro. I
don't know. Do you go London? Do you
ever go London? But I don't know if you do,
but there's just so many. It's like when
once you meet one, you meet them
all. You know, once you meet one woman
in London, mo, you know, for the most
part, you meet them all.
Once you meet one that says they've got
a boyfriend, you've probably met all of them. You
know, you know what I'm saying, bro? Like, they
all feel about what you look like, how
good-look you are. If people are stuck
up, they're stuck up. That's it. Right.
But I'm going to go sleep, bro. Need to
take in a lot today.
So my friend said, "Yeah, he got
blocked. He got blocked." Yeah, but you
don't understand. The context is
different. We were speaking for about 15
minutes. You reply back to my message.
You were telling me to come to Australia.
Look, [ __ ] come to [ __ ] Australia. What the
[ __ ] [ __ ] this [ __ ] up,
bro. I'm just going to go Thailand, get
with this 20-year-old, and call it a day,
mate. Cuz I've had enough of this,
bro. I've had enough of this [ __ ] I
probably spent a bit too much money today.
Anyways, more than I wanted to spend, but
yeah. So, my Antman said, "You tried
your best. That's it." And you know he said you
tried. That's what that man said.
So what about Sig Cactus? What about
Sig? Yeah. I was speaking to a guy
earlier in the pub. We speaking for
about half an hour. He's a good guy.
He's a good He's a good guy, bro. He's a
guy. He's a good guy, man. We speaking
for about half hour and it was just so
nice. I like generally just speaking to
somebody for London from London. We was having convos
and you know it was
good. Yeah. This guy bro that tried to
attack me last year. He walked into the
weather spoons. I was like oh [ __ ] Not
again. It is weird bro.
But anyways, I'm out of bit. I need to
sleep, man. Um,
yeah. Over and out. I'm going to write
this poem definitely.