Sorry, but yeah, I'm just doing
something. Yeah, it's Sunday again, man.
Chilling. I got three numbers. I ain't
even texted him yet, but Oh, man.
Yesterday was so bad, bro.
It was so bad. It was so [ __ ] bad. I
didn't really get much of a hangover
today cuz I only stuck to the beer. But
oh man, it was bad, bro. [ __ ]
sake. Why do Thursdays always seem to be
better than Sunday um
Saturdays? It's [ __ ] isn't it?
radio one still messaging back
but the the teacher still messaging back
but it's crazy man it seems I don't know
why Thursdays seem better than
Saturdays yeah I got it like
oh there was so many fake boyfriends yesterday
Cherry so many fake boyfriends [ __ ]
hell. I don't even know how people date
in this country nowadays,
ladies. Yeah, I need to get some pork
today. Pork chops. I had breakfast in
the Weber spoons. I don't even know how
people date in this country,
bro. Yeah, I got it a lot yesterday. I
wasn't wearing a tracksuit, but I
definitely got it a lot
yesterday. It's like you say a word,
they say they've got a boyfriend. That's
that's that simple. That's norm that's
always what happens. You say one word,
they say they've got a
boyfriend. Eight times out of 10, which was basically
yesterday. What do you mean did I send
it? Of course I sent it. You [ __ ]
[ __ ] Obviously I [ __ ]
did. It was the same [ __ ] [ __ ] What
the [ __ ] Of course I [ __ ] did.
Otherwise, I wouldn't be here [ __ ]
telling you about
it. Of course, I [ __ ] sent it. What the
[ __ ] I sent it hard and it's the same
[ __ ] I've got a boyfriend. I've got a
boyfriend. I sent it like wildfire,
bro. I even had men saying, "Oh, you're
good looking at that, bro." straight men
saying that to
me. What chance do people actually have
in this country? Well, not very much.
But these piggies come back in it.
So, yeah, I'll be in Thailand in in two
weeks. Well, 3 weeks. Just under three
weeks. So, I won't ever have to hear
that saying ever again. They're [ __ ]
just I don't I don't want even in the
[ __ ] in the in the shop. Even in the
um chicken shop like in in central
London when I was getting food and going
home. It's just a wild mate. Stay
wild. Never change. This country will never change.
Matey matey. But I'm gone in a couple of weeks anyways. Matey.
Matey. It's not been 3 weeks for ages.
No, it's not been three weeks for ages.
It started off as five weeks. And yes, I
am really going, man. It's not been no
five weeks for ages. But I'm not
mentioning people anymore like Lord Day
and that, bro. [ __ ] them. I'm I'm not
even doing any more of them immature
videos anymore cuz they're just weirdos,
man. And I don't want to be associated
with anyone on that
channel. So that's
it. Who's messaging
me? Yeah. Oh, yeah. I'm
going. You don't hear that there,
matey. You don't hear I've got a boyfriend then,
matey. Yeah, you get a lot in London,
mate. [ __ ] hell. It's all you ever
get. It doesn't matter where the people
are actually from as
well. You always get
it. Can't even get a conversation
without even hearing it. Even if even if
you wanted to just like I guess like
maybe make friends or
something, you would still get you would
always get I've got a boyfriend, bro. It
doesn't doesn't matter. But normally
it's not as bad as it's always bad. You
always hear it. But some days it's just
constant. Like sometimes it can be
Friday, sometimes it can be
Saturday, sometimes can be, you know
what I'm saying? There days where you
just nonstop hear it. Yeah.
I said it hard, bro. I've done fair
approaches. I've done a lot on the street as
well. Done a lot on the street,
too. Put 20 in the slots. I didn't win
anything. I didn't even spend that much
to be honest. The food was 16. The slot
was 20. That's almost 40. Then some
drinks. I think maybe 60. Maybe 6070 I spent. So, not
bad. Yeah, man. So, yeah, bro. That's
it. So, yeah, I've answered your question.
Anyways, I'm ignoring these self
projectors now. These little self-reflecting
weirdos. Yeah, they're weirdos, bro. I'm
blocking them on my channel, man.
Must be blue day. [Music] Yeah.
Yeah, Thursday's are way better anyways. What's up? Oh man. Oh [ __ ]
man. SP [ __ ] T on me, man. What the
[ __ ] My friend didn't get any numbers. Hey,
They're obsessed. Yeah, I know. They're
They're obsessed, bro. That's why I
can't be bothered with them anymore. I
can't be bothered with it, bro. I can't
be bothered with them, bro. They They
come right and
Yeah, we're pro
obsessed. They don't want to be me.
[ __ ] weirdos, man. Need a haircut at some point. Okay,
Um, they're all sad on here, but none of
them have got lives on this YouTube,
bro. None of these people have got lives
on here, bro. None of them.
Y none of them got
lives. I said to Figgy, do you want to come around
today? And obviously if they say yeah,
then I'm just going to have a bath, get
my tracksuit, and yeah, that's it, bro.
No, we'll see.
Do you like the up It
redeemed always find that you always come
down with a foot
ache. Yeah, these people have got no
life on this community,
bro. I think they're just fat, ugly
people that's been bullied their whole
life. Like what Monty man
said, these people actually get bullied
in real life. That's why they come on
here, bro. Yeah. skin ugly
projectors. It's getting boring now,
bro. That's getting boring now. You see
on my channel, bro, we switch up the
content. Whereas LJ is just for the
repeaters. They repeat the same [ __ ]
every day cuz they're disabled because
they don't understand you stuff. It gets
boring after a while, bro. The same
sayings over and over again. It gets
boring. You're [ __ ] disabled, mate.
They're [ __ ] disabled, mate. I said
this whole dating [ __ ] is going to make
me run away and never come back.
Run away and never come back.
Yeah. But why are they why do they bring
family members up when when you own
them? I noticed that. No, it doesn't
bother me. It's just weird. But why do
they do it when they cry? Yeah. If
anyone spoke spoke about their kids,
they they're the first ones to cry and
win no, but when you own them in every
way, all they can do is bring up family
members. It's it's funny really cuz it
shows how weird they are, is
it? [ __ ] absolute [ __ ] weirdos,
bro. Swear down,
man. Oh [ __ ]
man. They're weirdos, aren't they?
lot of fine numbers yesterday, but I
think some of them two of them are fake, but
definitely three of them are real.
So, you can't even approach a woman
nowadays without hearing I have a
boyfriend. Oh dear. How I was able to
make friends, I shall never
know. I shall never know. Maybe
Yeah. What's for dinner today? Not sure.
Anyways, I'll be back later.