Sorry about that, mate. Just just report done a
report. 181 contacts. [Music]
That's quite a lot. 181 [ __ ]
contests. Yeah. So, I done it, man. Takes a
while. Make sure my phone's not on silent. [Music]
Yeah, there we go. Reported again.
Yeah, that's what I love about these
phones when they're brand new. Yeah, the
batteries are so
good. went in there. Dick
man shows up to about 60%. They might
call me tomorrow or
something. So long to keep follow up these bloody
reports. [ __ ] hell. So boring, man.
So you know these people of jealous
virgins for somebody to even put themsel through
that or somebody to even put themsel through
that. You have to you have to really
wonder in it. You know you have to really wonder. One
sec. Let me do my WhatsApp on here.
Might as well,
mate. No, I don't want to do the
WhatsApp yet, actually, just in case.
What percent is
it? My eyesight is
[ __ ] Yeah, 50%. That's
enough. Don't need to be more than 50%, does it? flagship. [Music] Mush.
Hello. Is that Peter F? Yeah, that's me.
Hello, Peter. My name is P. I'm from Met
Police. I've got your report. Sorry for
disturbing you at this time. No, that's
fine. That's all right. I'll just email
you because Sorry for call you because
you're on the just emailed recently. Yeah.
I've reported it and I've keep following
it up and this person just keeps
harassing me every single day and
nothing is is is being done about it.
And I've got like a whole folder of what
he's done, what he keeps doing and he
won't stop. Like literally, he won't
leave me alone. And I send this to the
officers um when they come. I think it
was last week, a week and a half ago,
but nothing ever seems to get done. So,
you know, obviously is he?
No, it's somebody that I met 10 years
ago and obviously I I I suffer from like
panic attacks and crippling anxiety and
stuff and you know, I barely leave my
house because of this.
Yeah. Relationship. No. No.