I mean, and just like that, yeah, you
can be put into a
[ __ ] put into a bad mood, you know? It's crazy,
bro. Well, I did say about ages being
used as an excuse. Did say that, didn't
I? That's crazy, bro. Unrealistic
standards. I think that's the uh model
of the story to be
fair. It's a madness,
man. Yeah. You know what I [ __ ]
It's just annoying that is, bro. It's
like so just like
all the other people really in it. Yeah. What's up?
What the [ __ ] is that? Too young. messing up madness.
Bro, that's what these this is what I
don't understand with these women yet is
they'll say like, "Oh, well, I I don't
know why you can't find someone." No,
no, no, no, no. You're this, you're
that. And then their reason for not
getting with you is cuz they're 21 cuz
they're too young for you. [ __ ] hell,
bro. I didn't even need to step out the
house. Imagine that, Brie. I was talking
to this woman and she's like, I I sent
you on Instagram. She was like, "Oh,
well, you're lovely. I don't know why
nobody would want a relationship with
you." And then she said she's too young
for me. I was like, "Okay, well, I'm
expecting them to say 18 or 19, right?
21. You couldn't even make it up, bro.
You couldn't even make it up with
these." That just pissed me off, bro.
Like, I literally just went out for a
walk. I had to do something. That just
pissed me off. I'm not even going to
lie, bro. That just pissed me off.
Yeah. Just pisses you off.
It pisses me
off. All right. Yeah, I was going to
actually go on a full-on send, but I
can't be bothered
now. I don't know when I was going to do
it. Maybe today, tomorrow, next day,
Thursday. I can't be bothered now. My
mood's actually been put off because of
that because that's what you're going to
get when you actually go out.
When you actually go out doing it,
that's actually what you're gonna
get. You understand, Grezy? That's what
you're actually gonna get when you
actually do go out. Oh,
boy. When are you trying these dating apps anyways, Grezy?
Yeah. Either too old or too young for
you. I told you that word in my head. I
told you that.
I told you that actually happens,
bro. Oh yeah, that actually does happen,
Yeah, they've got unrealistic standards,
bro. That's what I said. It's not even
high standards. They're
unrealistic. I was just talking to this
woman on Reddit, Chico. Yeah. And she's
like, "Oh, well, I don't understand why
you can't find a relationship. You're
lovely." No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I said, "I assume that." And then she
was like, "Uh, yeah, I'm too young." I
said, "Why don't you go Why don't you
date with me? Why don't you date me
then?" Then she's like, "Oh, you're too
young for me. I'm I'm too young for
you." And I said, "Well, how old are
you?" She said,
"21." I laughed, bro. I'm not even Bro,
that was funny. Oh, bro. It's funny now,
but it wasn't funny, then. It pissed me
off, bro. Like it's actually stopped me
wanting to go out and do it now cuz
that's what you get when you go out
approach in real life that you're too
old for me, you're too young for me.
It's the same [ __ ] 20 [ __ ] one and
27. Nothing wrong with that.
Yeah. Always use that age as an
excuse. Nah, you don't need a decent
wingman. You need to leave this country.
That's what you need to do. You need to
go to Asia. I don't need a wingman. I'm
confident by myself. I can approach
anyone. I can talk to anyone. You don't
need a wingman. You need to go to
[ __ ] Asia. That's what you need to
do. What do you think, Greavesy? 21 and
27. There's nothing wrong with that. 2127.
Nah. Nah. Of course there
isn't. If they said 18, 19, I would have
been like, it's a bit too young. Yeah. But 21?
Nah. Nah, bro. I've been everywhere.
I've been all over the country. Women
are the same everywhere in these westernized
countries. I said to man, I want to stop
talking about it now cuz it's annoying,
bro. It's actually annoying, bro. It's
actually It's actually put me in a bad
mood. Like, I'm not even joking, bro.
That just actually put me in a bad mood.
I was actually in a good mood today. You
know, I'm not having this conversation,
Chico. Whoever you are, buddy. I'm not
having this conversation about wingmans
like that makes any difference. Well,
you're talking to someone that's tried everything.
Yeah. So, why is she saying that she's
too young for me when she's 21? And then
when I mentioned that, she didn't reply
again. Do they just love like taking the
piss out of people? Cuz it seems like to
me they just love take Well, to me,
that's what it seems like, but obviously
to most people can't do no wrong. So to
me it must seem like you are actually taking the
piss because if somebody said 18 19 I
would have been like oh they are
actually too young for you. So why are
you sat there
saying why are you sat there saying
how you can't believe no one's going to
date me? No when you're the same one
that's not going to date
me. You know what I'm saying? So,
uh, yeah. Like, you're Aren't you that
same woman then? Because you're saying
that you can't get with me because
you're 21. So, aren't you the same as
them women that keep doing this [ __ ]
So, yeah, that's pissed me off, bro.
That's actually annoyed
me. Like, I'm not going to go out
tomorrow or the next day. It's not much
better. If you go out in a group, you
get cop blockers. If you go out in a
group, it's not going to work because
you're gonna get caught. I'm not having
this conversation, bro. I'm not having
this conversation. Like, my channel is
is dedicated to dating. I'm not going to
have this boring, pointless conversation, you know? So,
yeah, I'm not going to have this
conversation again, bro. You're talking
to I basically come from dating. You
know what I'm saying? like it's I'm not
going to have this conversation, bro.
Like, whatever works best for you. Go
out and do
it. So, she can't get with me because
she's 21 and apparently that's too young
for her. This is why I don't even think
I'm going to bother going out for a
very, very long time now, bro. Because
it just puts you off cuz you know what
you're going to get. You know it. You
know exactly what you're going to get.
I'm too old for you. I'm too young for
you. I've got a boyfriend. I'm married.
I'm engaged. I'm sorry. I'm not looking
for anyone right now. I can't be dealing
with it, bro. I can't be dealing with
this [ __ ] I'm not doing it. [ __ ]
off. I was going to go out. I don't know
when, but I'm not doing it now for a
while, bro. [ __ ]
that. No, it's not dead in London, mate.
Everyone's People are always out in
London. Um, no. I didn't know what she
looked like, but it's not the point.
It's just annoying.
It's just annoying. And that man's like,
"Oh yeah, they use that as an excuse
because they're not interest." But no,
but no, that's not an excuse anymore,
you know, cuz I'm decent looking. When I
go out and I groom, I'm decent looking.
Yeah. I don't know about Ant-Man. At the
end of the [ __ ] day, bro, it's not an
excuse anymore. You know, someone not
being into you or not liking you. Nah,
bro. Not before not before first
date. You know, this is is I'm from
London PJ. You know, this London is a
lot more dead when it's winter. No, it's
not, bro. People go out all the time in
London, mate. I know. I've lived in
London my whole
life. Oh, here we go again. Nobody's is
obliged to like anyone. I think you're
missing the point,
Grezy. You You're actually missing the
point. You're missing the point, buddy.
The point is if you're decent and you're
good-look, you should be given a chance
because they moan that they can't find
nice men, etc., etc. I think you're
missing the point. what I'm trying to
make. Yeah, you're missing the point,
mate. I think you're missing the point
there. But at the end of the day,
um, at the end of the day, bro, like it
doesn't matter if it's winter or it's
raining, people still go out. It's
London. You know what I was saying, bro?
It's [ __ ] London. Like, people still
people still go out, mate.
who didn't who didn't want up to when
and Cony approached you. No, no, no. But
she's saying, "No, no, no, no, no, no,
no." But she is saying, "I don't know
why people won't date you. You're
lovely. Ret." And the next birth she's
saying she can't date me cuz she's too
young. It doesn't make any sense. You
know what I'm saying? Um, and this
wasn't form approach. I was talking to
this person online. So, you're just
being a hypocrite because you're saying
about how you can't understand why
nobody can will date me because I'm so
lovely and I look good, but then the
next minute you're saying that I'm too
young for you. So, so you're too young
for me. So, it doesn't make any
sense. But yeah, if I went out today
approaching, people would be out. Does
it make sense,
Greasy? Does it make sense to me? Does
it make sense to you?
It doesn't make sense to me. No, she
said, "No, no, no. This woman said to me
that I'm lovely. I don't know why you're
why you can't get a girlfriend. You
know, you seem lovely. Ret t." And I
said, "Okay, well, would you get in a
relationship with me?" She said that
she's too young for me. I asked, "How
old are you?" She said, "21." So, how
can you say that I'm lovely and you
can't understand why people don't give
me a chance if um
if you're doing exactly the same
thing? No, no, no. It's not the point.
It's it's it's real life. They do it in
real life as well. It's just the same.
So, yeah, she's just being nice. So,
what do they want then? what I was
saying to Antman because obviously well
he doesn't know the answers. So what do
you actually want? Because if you don't
want good-looking people because when I
groom and stuff I'm good-look, you know,
I'm not going to get into conversation
about my looks. What is it you're
actually complaining about them? Because
we hear about it that like, oh, you
can't get a good man T. But then when
people do approach you, you [ __ ] them
over. So I it's my job to ask, what is
it you actually want? I think I think
that's that's that's that's a fair
question. I think what it is with these
people, they want the perfect
man. That's what it is. They want the
perfect man and no one's perfect. That's
what I think it is with these people.
So that's what I generally generally
think it is. They they search for the
whole through the whole 20s to find this
perfect man that don't exist.
And then when they have kids in their
30s, they then settle down. They they
want this perfect man that don't exist.
That's what it is. That's what it took
me 27 to realize this. They want this
perfect man that don't exist.
So no, there's being fussy then there's
unrealistic. That's the difference.
There's being fussy and then there's
just being downright shallow and unrealistic.
So yeah, not to me it's not. It means to
me you've got unrealistic standards. Not
at all. There's a difference between
fussy and being picky as well. So, but
like I said, there's no point. You're
just going to defend women no matter
what I say. So pointless conversation
because you're always going to stick up
for women. So
pointless. I just wanted to let you know
that that person was just that they just
pissed me off today. And it just makes
you not even want to go out and try. It
just puts you in a bad mood. It put me
in a bad mood cuz it's like you're
reliving the same excuses. You're
hearing exactly the same excuses over
and over and over and over again. Even
when you're not going out, it's like
you're reliving it in your head. Do you
know what I'm
saying? Agrees. You don't have a bad
word to say about women. Bit like 95% of
the population to be fair. They ain't
got no bad words to say about women for
whatever reason, but they don't. They
like to stick up for women no matter
what they do.
So that's just the way society is and
would always be. I
guess nothing's going to change
there. Yeah, nothing's going to change there, mate. [Music]
M so it's not see and then they make the same excuses
bro. Yeah Stephen Albert we were going to do
uh we was going to do posters of um nons legs again. Yeah.
Yeah. Have you? Well you got a funny way
of showing it mate on this channel. I'll tell you
that. You know, they want the perfect
man but don't exist. That's what they
want. Thanks, social
media. I feel like getting drunk today,
but I can't cuz all the barbers are shut
and yeah, it's
raining. Pen and paper. Nope.
No, it's just on Reddit, bro. It's just
Reddit. It's the same excuses. So why am
I going to go out wasting my time and
wasting my money when I know it's just
going to be the same
old? It's going to be the same old, man.
You think people are not going to be out
today? Of course they
are. Of course there's going to be
people out today, bro. Nah, I'm all
right, bro. I'm staying in. That pissed
me off. I was actually in a good mood,
you know, as well today as well until I
was hearing the same excuses cuz I feel
like I'm reliving it again. And I
haven't even got out. I haven't even got
out and done any [ __ ] approaches for
I can't remember how long. But it
generally feels like you are actually
reliving it. The same excuses over and
over over again. You're too old for me.
You're too young for me.
Well, I just told you about that [ __ ]
with the unrealistic
standards. I was just talking to this
woman Narrow. Yeah. And she was like,
"Oh, you look good. I can't understand
why no woman would want a relationship
with you." Ret. And I said to her,
"Well, why don't you get in a
relationship with me? Do you know what
her excuse was? That she's too young for
me and she's 21." I was like, "Bro, this
week's canled." Like, just hearing that.
Yeah. I told Aman I need to go for a
walk, bro. It's pissing me off. So, no.
So, that's why I can't even bother. I
might have went out Saturday, maybe
tomorrow, maybe Saturday. But no, I
don't think I'll bother now for a few
weeks again cuz I'm reliving the same
excuses again. Even when you go out, you
hear the same [ __ ] and it does become very
boring. Very, very boring. Trust me,
after a while, it does.
getting a haircut in the [ __ ] cold to
hear the same old
[ __ ] Yeah. I don't actually know what.
And you know what I was saying to
Ant-Man? Yeah. He was like, "Oh, they're
just not into us or they don't like us."
But I said that doesn't wash anymore,
right? Because we're two different
people. I'm not ugly. Like I'm decent
looking when I grew, you know, smell
good, whatever you know you are. So it
it doesn't wash. Like if you were
somebody like Timmy Eldridge, Yeah. You
could understand why you're hearing all
these excuses in the world. You could
understand, you know, your place. I
would then think, okay, I know my place.
But when you're not nothing like that
and you're still getting these excuses
when people are also critiquing other
women for doing the same thing they're
doing, it don't make
sense, you know? It doesn't make [ __ ]
sense. There's literally nothing wrong
with you. And and and a lot of other
people that go out there and try. It's
just they want the perfect man that
don't exist. Like that's that's the the
conclusion I've I've I've come to,
bro. It's boring. It's [ __ ] boring,
man. Like, do you know before Christmas,
I think it was two weeks before
Christmas, I was speaking to this
40year-old. Oh, you're handsome, but I'm
too old for you. And she was 40 years of
[ __ ] age, and she had two [ __ ]
kids. You know, you think 27 and 40 is too
old. Yeah. And she's gone quiet now. But
it is it is just the same. Oh,
bro. I probably just chill in bed today,
bro. Um, that pissed me off. I'm not
going to lie to
you. Ah, some guys do the same thing. I
was actually married. I don't care what
other guys do, mate. I'm not into guys.
I just know enough women do it to me and
I'm not Timmy Eldridge.
So, what's the point of going out
wasting money, wasting time, getting
your hair done when it's just going to
be the same
old, you know? I don't even do
approaches so bad. Even though I can
approach anyone. I just don't even do it. Yeah.
So, you're going quiet now.
Anyways, so you're so what I don't
understand is you're saying that you
can't understand why women won't get in
a relationship with me, but you won't
get in a relationship with me because
you're too young and you're 21. So
you're using your age as an excuse, but
then you're wondering why women are
doing the same thing. You see, it
doesn't make any
sense. [ __ ] that Only Fans girl was
21, 22. It's a [ __ ] grown woman.
There's nothing wrong with that age, you
know? There's nothing. What's that? Six years.
Six. That I have so many uh problems. Uh
no, I've never considered that. You
little white knight. Go white knight
somewhere else. Don't have any problems,
but go white knight somewhere
else. Um what the actual reason
was. She says that I'm not even in England. [Music]
Um, she's a very particular and a very
picky person. She said that her her
standards are she said, "I feel like
most people would find my standards very [Laughter]
high." Yeah, I just told her now, bro.
Yeah, I've just asked her now. I said,
"What's the actual reason?" I've just
messaged her again. I said, "So, why
wouldn't you date me? Um, do you find me
ugly?" Because 21 and 27 is completely
fine. So, what is it, bro? What is
it? That's why there's no point even
going out, bro. This is what I'm trying
to say to you.
Yeah. Well, you're still a white knight.
So, got to do on another channel, I
guess. Yeah, it's crazy, bro.
It'd love to know as
well. But she's trying to have a go at
other women for doing the same thing.
Yeah, it's a madness,
bro. It is a madness. It is a madness,
lad. It just pisses me off, honestly,
bro. Just talking about it just pisses me
off. I was actually in a good mood today well. All
right. I actually was in a good mood
today. I see. Yeah, exactly. Exactly.
Exactly. And And more so it's like that
in London as well. So why why even put
yourself out there? Why even try? You
get to a certain age. It's like Ant-Man
says, he's like he doesn't care about it
anymore. It's like why even try? You
know, you know what their Especially in
London, someone like London, you know
what their type is. Unrealistic men that
will never like them. Like you said, 6'
millionaire, right? You are. So 6'5
millionaire. You're not a 6'5
millionaire. So why are you even going
to try? And that's that's the hard truth
of it, bro. And like people can call you
negative and te, but it's it's not it's
literally literally not. I have had
enough of it,
bro. So, yeah. Buses are leaving. You
don't want me here yet. You're watching
me, huh? Yeah, you don't want me on
here, but yet you're you're watching me.
How's that make any
sense? Don't be weak and give up. I've
traveled all over the country. I've
tried more than anybody in the world.
Nero, you can you can you can be my
witness for that one.
I'm going to give her some [ __ ] One second, bro.
just gave her some [ __ ] [ __ ]
bro. I don't even know where she's from.
She's not from England, but it's not the
point. She's not from England, but it's
not the point. I'm sick of it. I'm sick
of hearing it. You
know, giving up is the only solution,
bro. Going to
Asia. That's the only um only solution.
I need to renew my passport next week as well. Funny
enough, I need to renew my passport next week, lad. So
yeah, but you should be able to find
someone in this country, bro. With
somebody that looks like me, someone um
someone that's as confident as me, you
should be able to just find
someone. And you can't. And that just
goes to show how unrealistic their
standards actually are,
bro. That's how that's how unrealistic
their standards are in
men. Uh, not sure, bro. Good question, uh, Grievy. But
yeah, that that just pissed me off, bro.
They don't even live in England and that
pissed me off. You
know, it just sucks,
bro. Even then.
Yeah. They tell me I'm going to meet
someone, but I never
do. I never do,
bro. It's just the same old sad
song. How many stamps? Uh, four four
stamps. Well, four different
countries. That sucks, bro. It really
does suck. So, unless you're like 6'5
and you're a
millionaire, you you're best off not even
trying. That's crazy, isn't it? Unless
you're 6'5 millionaire, there's no point
you even trying, eh, in this
country. Yeah, that's crazy,
bro. And I don't look white as well,
which probably don't
help. One second.
And I probably don't look fully white,
which doesn't help either. See, they
want someone that's white. They want
somebody that's 6'5. Well, like white,
blonde hair, you know, blue eyes, you
6'5. Pretend you're a rich. I have I've
offered them money. They repeat myself
again. Um, I've offered them money as
you've seen them videos. It doesn't make
a difference. And the money that I've
offered them, they probably would have
thought that I was rich. It doesn't
work. I went around, they weren't last
Thursday, it was the Thursday before
that offering money and it doesn't
work. Offering them money and it doesn't
[ __ ] work. I've offered them money,
bro. The offering money doesn't work.
Nothing works in this
country unless you're um
6'5 6'5 millionaire who's got big following on
YouTube. You you don't have a you don't
have a chance in this country.
Sucks is it bro? But yeah.
Yep. Well approaching normally doesn't
work. So I mean what what do you do?
Nero, your skin m. Oh,
self-reflection. Um, oh, you got caught
me off guard. Sorry, Nero. You get a lot
of self projectors on this channel.
Lonely, fat, ugly, 40year-olds with no
money that like to project their life on other
people that like to reflect their life
on other people. They just get banned,
bro. Yeah, you're more than welcome
to. I just can't believe how hard it is
to get a woman. I actually can't believe
it. Like people in this community,
they'll say that they get women and it's
easy, but it [ __ ] isn't, mate. And
trust me, I would know of all people
like I've tried more than Ant-Man. I'm
confident and it still makes no
difference. So, I won't be going out for
a few weeks now because of that comment.
Bro, that pissed me off, bro. Like, who
the [ __ ] do they think they're entitled to?
Who do they actually think they're
entitled to about you're too young for
me cuz you're 21? Don't don't don't
don't [ __ ] love me
then. Yeah, if you accepted your
manta stuff's boring now, bro. I'm
better looking than everybody on this
community who's shown their face. So,
mate, at the end of the day, if I'm a
ma, what are
you? Like, stop calling yourself a m
every day. It will it will do better for
your for your mental health because I'm
a million times better than anybody on
this community that has shown their
face. So, you really must be the ma. You
know, it can't be good for your mental
health coming online every day calling yourself a
ma, you know, like it's no good for your mental
health. You know, you are the well and
truly ma. Aren't you the one that went
with that uh Craig Goodston?
deluded. I am below average. Yeah, you
keep telling yourself that, Fig Fires.
You're probably like a two out of 10.
You are probably like a two out of 10.
I'm below average. Do you think I care
about your opinion? Do you think you're
ever going to stop me showing my face?
I'm better looking than you will ever
be. Why don't you come on the panel now
and show us your face and I'll show my face. Come
on. Come on. Come on. Come on, bro. I'm
better looking than anybody on this
community that showing their face. So
when you're on here trying to call
people ma, do you know how stupid you
make yourself look? You make yourself
look so so so
stupid. I don't think you realize
that. And that's it, bro.
Like it's a
madness. I'm better looking than you.
I'm better looking than L. I'm better
looking than all of you. But you still
try to call me a m. Do you not sound a bit
thick? You know, like, do you not see
how thick you actually
sound? You You look stupid, bro. I'm a
million times better looking than you'll
ever be. You are, LJ. How about that?
Why don't you come in and show us your
face? You know, you're trying to call me
a manta, bro. I don't need to filter my
pictures. I'll show what I look like,
bro. I'm better looking than you will
ever be, bro.
Yeah, you people are them muners. That's
why you use mter every day because you
are them moners and that's why you call
people skint cuz you are skint
yourselves. See, the thing is you you
come on here, bro, and you say, "Oh, you
look ugly. You're never going to make me
insecure." Because the thing is, right,
we know what you people look like. Bomb.
Yeah. Hey, do you remember Bomb when he
was trying to say, "Oh, you're balded. You're
ugly." And then look what happened when he come
out. Look what happened when he come
out, bro. Big fat ugly [ __ ] with
no hair. You're all the same. You are
all the same kind of ugly. So I don't
And you're all the same kind of skin.
You really think that I can't go in my
pocket right now and show you money?
You really really think that I can't
come now and show you money? Of course I
can. But I'm not showing you
nothing. And that's what you need to understand,
lad. You know, I can make you hear the
money if you want, but you're not
getting shown nothing. You understand
that? You thick
fies. Yeah. Charlie, I was speaking to a
woman on Reddit.
Yeah. And uh you gonna laugh at this.
Jeff, she's like, "Oh, I can't
understand why you can't get a
relationship. You seem lovely t
um and uh she I was like, "Oh, well,
what would you get in a relationship
with me?" And you know what she said?
She was like, "Um, you're" She said to
me, "You're too young for me." I said,
"I'm too young for you. How old are
you?" And she said that uh
uh she said
um she said um
21. And it literally put me off wanting
to go out, bro. Because I'm reliving
them excuses. You know them excuses
where they say they're too old for you
when they're too young for you, right? I
feel like I'm reliving it again and I
don't want to go out because I know I'm
going to hear the same [ __ ] So I said,
"Oh, what's your problem? Is it because
I've got a 6'5 millionaire with blue
eyes cuz obviously they've got
unrealistic standards, right?
So, it doesn't, mate. I'm not going to
get into a conversation about my looks,
mate. I'm not the one that brought my looks
up. Yeah, it's never them. It's never
them. And the maddest thing is she con
uh what she done was mad as well because
she's basically doing exactly what she
was trying to find out what other women
were doing because she's saying, "Oh, I
can't believe you can't find someone.
You seem lovely." But this is the same
woman that are doing what these other
women are doing. She's trying to find
out why these women are doing what she's
herself. They must be taking a piss.
Surely to god they must be taking a
piss. But yeah, that's I'm not going out tomorrow or
Saturday. I would love to know what the
real reason is because I'm not
ugly and I don't care what anyone says
on YouTube. I'm not ugly and no one's
ever going to make me feel like I'm
ugly. So, you're not ugly? I mean, you
can talk normal. I mean, so what what's
what's going on, man? What's the
problem? Tell us the truth. Come
on. That's what I want to know. I want
to know the truth, the whole truth, and
nothing but the truth, bro. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Do you know
what somebody said to me um about a year
ago on Reddit? Do you know what they
said to me? They was like, "You should
go to a third world country. Women have
unrealistic expectations." And I think
they were right,
bro. I actually think they were really,
right. I think they were right, bro. I
remember the exact comment that I was
saying. You ain't even It doesn't No,
no, no, no, no, no, no. Well, well, why
are you using your age as an excuse
then? It's because you're down on your
eyes. Bye-bye now. Don't self-reflect on
another channel. I mean, yeah, but then
why use your age as an excuse
then? Okay, then you should have said
that. Why are you using your age as an
excuse? That's [ __ ] dodge,
bro. I The way I see it is I'm not leaving my
country. Now, I had a friend say to me
he'd rather die than go to Thailand
because when you do that, you're you're
you're admitting defeat. I mean Yeah. I
don't Yeah. I mean, you'll actually
admitted defeat when you go to
Asia cuz obviously why should a man have
to leave his own [ __ ]
country. I think we need to ban [ __ ]
social media. Do you know what I'm
saying? But they never said that though,
did they ti? They using their age as an
excuse. So, and they do it in real life
as well. They do do it in real life.
Definitely do it in real life.
Yeah. Whether they're too old for you or
too young for you, they say it's always
some excuse. It's always an
So, and I told her about it as
well, and she didn't reply because it's
the truth, though. It It is the truth. I
can't be bothered anymore, bro.
Yeah, seriously though, you look really
downy, mate. That's just a
self-reflection of your own ugly looks
because you're the one that keeps
talking about the way I look. You must
be jealous of my looks or something,
bro, cuz you keep going on about it. You must fancy me. Yep.
Exactly. Exactly. Exactly.
Exactly. That's it,
bro. It's crazy. Yep. That's exactly
what they would
say. That's exactly what they would say,
bro. They say, "No, if they if you were
the same age as them, they would say
that they've got a boyfriend or they're
not looking for
anyone." That's what they would
say. Yeah. You get it in clubs as well,
especially around Soho. Oh, you're
lovely. You're good-look, but I'm not
getting with you cuz you're too young
for me. You're too
old. No, I haven't.
And there's nothing wrong with the way
that you look either, despite what these
jealous trolls say on YouTube, but the
ones that are much uglier than you. Um,
there's literally nothing wrong with the
way that you look. Like, all all jokes
aside, yeah, like honestly, yeah, like I
said, if you were somebody like Timmy
Eldridge, I' I'd get it. I'd be like,
"Okay, yeah, this makes sense. This is
the cord I was dealt with in life. I I
get it." But when you don't look nothing
like Timmy Eldridge, you don't act
nothing like Timmy
Eldridge. You know what I'm saying?
You're one of a kind. You know what I'm saying, bro?
Like, it just doesn't make sense.
Doesn't make sense at all. Yeah.
Yeah, these westernized it's like what
Antman said. These westernized entitle
[ __ ] Autism. Uh Timmy's autism isn't
even that bad. You know, he's got things
that are worse than his actual autism.
His autism isn't even that bad, to be honest with you.
His autism isn't even that bad, Elad.
It's because you nearly 30. No job up
down the eyes, bro. It's not hard to work out.
Okay. Okay. This is funny, bro. So, how
much money do I have then? Ah, [ __ ]
sake. Um, what did I what did I expect
the response from the woman to be like?
Because I'm nearly 30, no job, have
eyes, it's not hard to work out.
Do you people not get bored of talking
about yourselves every day? Bro, you in
your 40s, you're skinny, you're ugly,
and you got no job. Go self-reflect on
another channel. Weirdo. Um, what did
you think the response from, um, this
woman would be? I thought the response
would be, um, well, I hardly know you.
Maybe if I got to know you, or something
other than using her age as a [ __ ]
excuse. Do you know what I mean,
Charlie? basically anything other than
using your [ __ ] age as a [ __ ]
excuse. But as I was saying before, I
was interrupted by that projector. Um, self-reflector.
Um, you know, and it's not just Timmy,
right, that that has autism, bro. It's
loads of people on here that's got
autism because why do they go on about
money every day? Like, we're talking
about dating. Yeah. and all of a sudden
they randomly come up and talk about money
like it's cuz they're skint themselves.
Yeah. Why do they always continuously bring up
money? I don't understand why they
continuously bring up money. I don't
understand. It's It's because they
haven't got any money. They're skin on
benefits, isn't it, Honey. So
yeah. Yeah, they're evil [ __ ] bro. So
yeah, that's what I would have thought
they would have said, something other
than them using their aids as an excuse.
So there's no point in me even going out
anymore. There's no point, bro. They
just killed the
vibe. They literally just killed the [ __ ] vibe, lad.
Yeah. Got six piece chicken as I always do.
I'm not showing you nothing. What? What?
What part of I'm not showing you
autistic little mongos that are obsessed
with money? Anything ever again. I'm
showing you nothing. Get that through
your head. And you can keep saying that
I'm skin all you want. I'll disagree
with you. Yep. I'm skin. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Yep. Yep. Yep. The skin is [ __ ] to life,
mate. Don't even have one piece. I'm not
showing you nothing. It's about time you
started showing me something for a
change. Isn't that right, Charlie? I'm
still yet to be shown 12 grand. Charlie,
I'm waiting for [ __ ] 12 grand. [ __ ]
50 [ __ ] quid. You know what I'm
saying? Yeah. When you show me 12 grand,
bro, you are overweight. No, I'm not
overweight. Projection. Your skin and you're
overweight. Nah, bro. It never is. No,
I'm not overweight. Try again. You're
overweight in your skin, though. Bye-bye
now. Like I said, I will be more than
happy to play the money game, Charlie.
Right. Let me Okay, let me take this
down. Right. I will be more than happy
to show you money when you play when you
show me 12 grand. Okay. I'm not going to
show you this, but I'm going to rub my
fingers around it. Yeah. So, you can hear You hear
that? That's the sound of money.
Yeah. It has a certain noise to it. If
you get notes together, you'll see it.
I'm not showing you nothing. Get that
through your head. I'm not playing your
little autistic little games. Oh, show
money. Oh, show money. Oh, show money.
Look, you can look. Look, you can There you go.
No, the Albanian was a The Albanian was
a a waitress. The Albanian was a Yeah. So,
yeah. Yep. It's newspaper, bro. Yeah,
that's what it
is. Yeah. I'm rubbing a Fiverr together.
Yeah. I'm not showing you no money. Get
that over your Get that through your
head. One, two.
Yep. Coming some Wonga
here. Well, go and [ __ ] get
it. 12K. Who would have that in their in
their pocket? Uh, shake my head. Well,
[ __ ] go and get it, mate, cuz that's
what you've got to [ __ ] show
me, mate. That's what you got to be
showing me, mate. Don't know where
you're going to get it from, but that's
what I'm wanting to be shown.
four. There we go. Actually, let's count
that. There we go.
Man, back in the oldest
it showing you nothing,
bro. Go your own money if you got so much.
Nah, I'm about showing you
nothing. Oh, that KFC hit hard,
bro. Get a job at
KFC. Well, it doesn't matter. I don't
know how you're going to get 12 grand,
but go back and get
it. Um, am I in good shape? I'm just
average and I used to go to the gym. It
made no difference.
It made absolutely no difference, lad. So
yeah, need to have a [ __ ] shower soon. [ __ ]
hell. The chicken fry. I imagine that ain't
it? Look like [ __ ] Timmy.
Yeah. Are you in good shape? Yeah. It
doesn't matter if you're if you're
ripped. Nothing's going to work in this
country unless you're [ __ ] 6'5
millionaire big YouTuber or something
like that. You're never going to find
anyone in this country. Women have got unrealistic
standards. That guy on Reddit was right
all the [ __ ] long. And I was trying
to lie to myself saying no. But nah,
they've got unrealistic standards. All
the same in the west.
Yeah, I need to have a shower in a bit,
right? Oh, [ __ ] me.
Yeah. How many do you think I would?
Come on. Ask if
if Bro, I'm not going to get into this
conversation. respectfully, bro. I'm not
going to block you. You're entitled to
your um own opinion. Of course you are.
I'm not getting into this conversation
with you, bro. I come from the dating
world. Grievy would tell you, you know,
what women say and what women do is two
different things. I'm not going to sit
here and have this conversation with
you, bro. It's boring as [ __ ] I know
these things, bro. I've gone out
approaching women. I know about life.
I'm not having this conversation. End the story.
Right. I'm not having this combo. It's
boring. It's boring as [ __ ] bro. I'm
not having this conversation. It's
ridiculous. It's stupid. You comment.
You're not going to get blocked. But I
won't be having this conversation. If
you're too ignorant to watch all of my
videos from my channel, that's that's
you, bro. You know, I'm I'm I'm a I'm a
content creator. So, you know. Oh,
yeah. There is no bro face facts. I
already know. I already know there's no
hope for me.
You know there's no hope for me, bro.
I'm not the one who's in the
aisle. Why do you think I don't really
go out much anymore doing it drinking? I
already know there's no hope for
me cuz the women's unrealistic
standards. I'm I wasn't born yesterday, man. You
know, you know how it is.
Stop calling me Peter, you weirdo. I don't gamble
anymore. Don't gamble anymore, bro. Only football
bets. Done with that.
Hey, you're still good as well.
could have put out that monster. Yeah,
you keep telling yourself that, bro. I'm
not playing that [ __ ] again. Unless I'm
drunk in a pub or something. No, I'm good,
bro. Don't mind staying bored, bro. It's
fine, bro. You know what I
mean? Just stay
bored. I'm not playing that [ __ ]
Life's depressing enough without losing money,
bro. It's depressing
enough. Um, I'm going to have a bath.
I'm going to have a bath. I'll just keep
quiet for a couple of days, I reckon.
Bro, no going out, no drinking, nothing,
bro. To get humidated some more. No, I'm
all right, bro. I'm good. It's depressing,
bro. Yeah, I said shower, but I'm going
to have a bath, I reckon.
What do you reckon would have happened
today if I went out approaching Steven
Howard? What do you reckon would have
happened today if I went out
approaching? That actually put me in a
bad mood, bro. To the point I just want
to kill myself, bro. I don't want to lie
to you, man.
made me feel suicidal.
That nothing here. [ __ ] it [ __ ]
life. See, I actually go out like if I
knew I had some sort of chance. Yeah.
These trolls don't get to me. They're
not even trolls. They're [ __ ]
spastics. It's that woman that pissed me off on
Reddit. No, it won't even these people on here,
bro. No, it's not even the people on
here, bro. These people don't put me in
a bad mood. These little
mongos, these little
self-reflectors. They don't get to meet
these little self projectors. It's just
that [ __ ] woman on Reddit pissed me
off. Makes you feel like killing
yourself, bro, when there's like no
hope. No matter what you do, how you
approach, nothing's ever going to
change. Nothing ever is ever going to
change. It's depressing, isn't
it? Make it better. Yeah.
Yeah, you are a ma. Stop calling yourself a
ma. Listen, Fig Fi, stop calling
yourself a ma. It's no good for your mental
health. It's no
good for your mental health.
calling yourself a manta big
f it's not nice man calling yourself a m you
know you know these people been saying
mter for like 2 three years and they're
the only munters that's that's the
funniest thing about it like they're so
stupid that they don't even know that
they're actually calling
themselves like what this community is
is just a bunch of 40year-old ugly fat
people that ain't got no life and what
they've basically done is they've
stumbled across a community that they
all sort of they have no place in
society cuz they they don't leave their
house and that. So they come on here and they just
self-reflect. Skin ma it's everything is
them. They only talk about
themselves. Like that's literally that
it's only themselves that they're actually talking
about. Like that's it. They don't know
anyone's lives. What money people have,
what money people don't have. They talk
like they know people, but they don't
know nothing. And amount of things that
they actually get wrong as well. It's
crazy. They're just [ __ ] ugly fat
people that ain't got a life. Like, you
know, these people on here, bro, I bet
you they don't even leave their gaff.
Like I bet you they don't even leave
their [ __ ] gaff. That's how bad it
is. They don't even leave their gaff. Yeah. Well,
So, Greavvesy, you're going to be
starting these dating apps soon, aren't
you, mate? April, you said, didn't
you? We're almost March. So, what's for
food later? I'm not going to eat later.
I had Gregs and then I had KFC. I won't
eat later. Maybe get some nuggets in the
early early hours.
Maybe, but I don't think
so. I kind of got off my food to be honest.
Yeah. No, no, no, no, no, no. Greedy,
come on. You're right. I'm wrong. Women
are not all evil. Come on. Come
on. Women are not all evil. Women are
perfect. Go these apps. Go in these
dating apps and show
us. Come on. Go these dating apps and show
on. These dating apps suck, lad. Okay.
Well, I didn't do any videos when I was
there. How about that
one? Huh? I didn't do any videos when I
was in America.
about that one. I was
there. Okay. I wasn't there,
bro. I wonder why USA is didn't ask use
her age as an excuse. I wonder why she
didn't use her age as an excuse.
I All right.
on Bumble, man. UK
asylum. Nah, I don't think so,
bro. The [ __ ] doesn't know my YouTube channel.
Hey, no bumbles are dating that.
Ad man's like the only thing you can do is come here which
is I don't think USA is he watches me
bro I kind of made her life a bit
hell made her change her number made
Charles up with her made her go to Please on
me. I mean, I'm a crazy [ __ ] man.
Yeah. No, I'm going to have a bath, bro.
And yeah, go from
there. Got to have a bath and go from
there. I need a bath,
mate. Anyways, I'm going, bro. I'll be
back maybe later.