Yeah,
man. Cooking a second meal again soon.
Cooking a second meal soon. Again. What's the
88? Why does it feel like it's the
ninth? Feels like it's the
ninth. We like for a little
bit. We back again later. I'm [ __ ]
knackering. Jesus Christ. Exercise and
warm me out. [Laughter]
Yeah, I'm [ __ ] nothing, man.
It makes me every time
now like those bastics on my channel may think
it [ __ ] my
Sorry. You're bad.
Oh, people got family members are
bad. They're banned,
buddy. Sorry, man.
Doesn't feel like a Monday today for some
reason. Doesn't feel like a Monday at
all. I told you when I say I'm going to
do something, I [ __ ] will do it. Oh,
[ __ ] I'm [ __ ] tired, man. I need
to cook the salmon at 5. Oh,
[ __ ] I'm actually tired, man. Going to
cook this s take this wash out. Cook
this salmon. Some ground water.
Ah, what was that?
Yeah, I'm tired,
bro. Had a nice bath. [Music]
Greasy. Oh my god.
I'll sleep like a baby
today. I will sleep like a [ __ ]
newborn baby, mate.
When is this film coming out next month?
What's the date? Oh [ __ ]
Yeah. Plus four.
Oh, it is the live today. Yeah. Why do I
think it was a knife? He's
alive. You'll still have around about 23. calculate this.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Why are you so [ __ ]
greasy? Told you
what? Told you. Agree with you matey.
you. Told you I'd do this [ __ ]
Mine. You know what? But I do find you drinking
today. These people try to follow me on Instagram
again. What's that [ __ ] from [ __ ]
California? Come running back, don't they? Huh?
a while back years
later. Who know that is definitely
Right. [ __ ] uh 8 hours behind aren't there?
That's actually weird. That is Why did
they do that?
tomorrow cuz tomorrow's Tuesday. So yeah,
tomorrow. Oh man.
Yeah, tomorrow got some
uh basically have a few things anyways to be
fair. I said to L, if you if you prove
that you booked the flights, I will give
you the money. But he can't do that cuz
he's full of [ __ ] mate. You ain't going
nowhere. He's anxiety. He want to know it.
See, I do actually kind of want to go
out Thursday now, but it will [ __ ] the whole thing
up. See, if I go Thursday, you can't
start the gym on Monday and then go out
Thursday. And I don't want to go out
Saturday either. So, we're pretty much
[ __ ] out of luck,
really. No, you can't really. for a few days.
Nah, cuz I wouldn't go out Saturday.
Saturdays are [ __ ] So
um guess I could go out Friday
maybe. Uh just knackered bro from the
gym. Gonna be eating my salmon soon.
Need to start my salmon at
5:00. So yeah, I'm still depressed over that Australian
Joe. I think there's something wrong
with me, mate. I get easily
attached if I just stood there. If I
just stayed there, you know what I mean?
Now I'll never know.
Jo, now I'll never
know. I mean, what the [ __ ] is wrong
with me getting attached, man? [ __ ] this
This [ __ ] is B. This [ __ ] is
bollocks every single time. So, I had a nice
bath and rest of my little muscles. They've exercised. So,
yeah, it's going to be fun, man. I'm so
tired. I'm [ __ ]
knackered. But it's all
right. Probably go again tomorrow to do
some situps and [ __ ]
Yeah, I can work my legs tomorrow. Be leg day
So, I'm just going to go out and have a
drink. I want to go out Thursday, but it
would just [ __ ] the whole gym thing up.
That's the thing. I just want to go out
for a drink. I know it's going to be the
same [ __ ] I know they're [ __ ] in this
country, Joe, but wanted to go for a
drink on Tuesday, Thursday,
sorry. But it would literally [ __ ] the
whole thing up. Obviously, if you done
it in two weeks, it's fine, you know.
But I mean, I could technically do
it. I used to do it. No, I never when I
used to go to the gym, I never used to
do the drink cuz the thing is when you
when when you do the drink and
[ __ ] when you do I'm stubborn Joe. I'm a
stubborn [ __ ] Like you know me though.
It you know me. You know me. I'm
stubborn mate. I can't let things lie in
it. You know you
know. But bro, I can't let it lie. You
know what I'm saying? I can't I can't
let things lie.
Uh yeah. Yeah, I was thinking about I
was straining at 3 4:00 in the morning.
Joe, I wish Mama F had me in the 1980s.
Then we wouldn't even be having this
conversation. We wouldn't even be where we are
now. We wouldn't even be where we are
now, mate. Having this
conversation. How many times do people
have to keep getting [ __ ]
over? [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, I'm in Thailand, bro, in three
weeks. But I can still go out for a
[ __ ] drink on
Thursday. What [ __ ] all to lose?
Spending 40, 50 quid. I know it's going
to be the same [ __ ] It's always the
same [ __ ] When I used to go gym, I
never used to go out drinking every
week, I don't
think. Maybe I did. Who knows?
I'm sure I
didn't. Sure. I didn't every
week. You can't do it. You can't. You
can. One second.
This is what you need to do, Joe, man.
You're you're very overweight. I can
tell by your videos when you're
like, and this is what
um most the people in this community
need so they can stop projecting every day on
YouTube. So they can stop projecting
every day on [ __ ] YouTube. I sleep
like a bubba today. I will sleep like a
bubba. But I felt depressed earlier.
It's cuz I my sleep was [ __ ] up
and just stuff that's happened. You
know, you think about stuff that's
happened and I felt like just getting
drunk because you don't even feel like a
Monday, but obviously I didn't.
So, which is obviously good, isn't it?
Yeah. Americans acting like a [ __ ]
Yeah. Know why this person's come back after two years?
Weird. I know exactly who they were straight
away. Are you telling me now you're in
London and you want to meet
up? What? You want to meet up? Yeah,
hopefully. What do you mean? I'll never
learn like with the I've got a boyfriend [ __ ]
Joe. Yeah, you're always going to get
that. You're always going to get I've got a boyfriend. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Man, you're always going to
go. I've got a
boyfriend. I summon soon. I'll show
Grezy it. Just fancied a bit of salmon today,
Joe. You know, sometimes you just fancy
a bit of
salmon. You know, life's pretty good
here in London. You know, you can make
some money. You can go out, spend 40, 50
pound, something to look forward to
every week. It's
not It's just a shame about [ __ ]
people breaking people's hearts and
[ __ ] It just ruins
everything, you know?
It's not a bad life here in London. It's
just the women are [ __ ] but you know,
we can still go out and drink and
that. No spirits
though. No spirits. [ __ ]
that. No spirits, matey.
I hate the feeling of being in love,
Joe. I hate being in love. You
know, you always think, "Oh, never happened again.
so what should we finish soon then? Take
that out. Uh,
summon. So what? You don't think I was
in love with that Australian Joe? I was.
She was Thai heritage and she done the
[ __ ] dirty on
me. She's done the dirty on me,
man. Now I'm going to have to get
nostalgia now every time I go back to that place.
Wow. But to be honest with you, it could be worse.
You remember that American from like
four years ago? And I never got their
contact details, man. I tried looking for them
everywhere. I couldn't find them. So, at
least it's not the one that got away.
That's That's the worst. That would be
the worst, I
think. No, I was in love,
Joe. I am in love. What's extreme about
anything that I do? and the
hats. You know what I'm saying? No. Why?
Why would you say I'm extreme, bro? How
am I extreme?
What do I do? That's
extreme. Yeah, she abandoned
me. But hopefully if I if I go to the
gym for 2 years and I grow some
dreadlocks, maybe she might accept
me, you know, get loads and loads of
money, build my YouTube channel up, get
dreadlocks. Then maybe she will love
me. How do I have a ban? No. The only
reason I had attachment issues with USA
Izzy is because that was literally
taking a baby away from its mama. That
was actually different.
That one was actually
different cuz you the thing is right,
you try to say that I've got attachment
issues, but at the end of the day,
right, at the end of the day, I've been
sold a dream here. If you if you look at
all of these cases, right, you will see
that I've actually been
sold I've been sold a dream every
time. Sold a [ __ ] dream every time.
So a [ __ ]
dream. It's not like you've not been
sold a [ __ ] dream. Every [ __ ]
time, [ __ ] You know what I'm
saying? Every time being sold a
dream. When When wasn't you sold a
[ __ ] dream? Every time this [ __ ]
happens. Come on. You know, every
Um, I'll be out of here soon anyways.
It's like what I said to Adman. You
know, one of these days I'm just going
to say [ __ ] the lawyer and run away and
never come back. He said he's already done that.
Yeah. I'll just say [ __ ] the lawyer and
never come back.
which is the best thing to be
honest. You know what I'm saying? You
don't like salmon? How do you not like
salmon? But I'll be back later anyways.
Yeah, I'm going to go and take this wash out