What? There we go. [ __ ] um
What a line this
time. You know what? I always get that
fan on even when it's not cold. Just the
sound of it, you know. It's
good. [ __ ] hell. Trying to rekindle old
contacts. Nothing, bro. Just back
tired. Done a lot of exercising today
and eating. So, I told you fresh start.
It's a fresh start, mate.
My sleep sleep schedule got [ __ ]
up. Yeah, I am tempted to go out
Thursday, but I don't think I'm going
to, bro. I'm going to stick to my guns.
Not because of money or not cuz of the gym. It's
just it's just the same old [ __ ] isn't
it? Like legit, bro.
It's not even about the
money. Where is that criminal record
thing? Where did I put
it? Yeah, I told you I was going to do
it, bro. You don't want to end up like Jamie
Thompson. That's how these people start,
lad. What do I do with that [ __ ] thing?
Never mind. Yeah, man. That's how these
people start. You see an
hour? Yeah, it was lush. It was [ __ ]
expensive as well. About [ __ ] 10 quid,
bro. 10 quid maybe? No, it was £957.
Where's my criminal record check
gone? Should be
here. Kebabs next week. No, I don't eat
kebabs. I don't see the hype on kebabs.
I don't really see the hype with them to
be honest. People go mad over kebabs.
But I was thinking about that Australian
thing again. Stephen
Howard. This is why, man. This is why
people need to give
up with [ __ ] dating in this country.
Where's that [ __ ] knuckle thing? Oh
[ __ ] This is here. [Applause]
Yeah, I'm getting ripped again,
bro. Yeah, I don't care, bro. He's
obsessed. He can keep talking about me. I don't
care. He's obsessed, mate.
Oh [ __ ] Where's that [ __ ] thing
at? Yeah, no one cares, bro. He's
[ __ ] um he's obsessed.
He needs to get to his gym, man. He's
obese. I got here then. I
don't I wouldn't put in
there. I don't have my criminal record
check, but I don't I can't find
him. Yeah. I don't care who he's talking
about, mate. He's a possessed weirdo.
He has to bring family members involved
cuz he gets owned a lot of it, mate. Yeah,
you were under the [ __ ] chair. That's how,
bro. Nah, I'm all good,
man. Well, you already know
why. The whole dating thing, ain't it? It's [ __ ]
madness. Obviously, I'm not I'm not I was
tired. You already know what the problem
is. You know what I'm saying? live.
Where the [ __ ] is that DBS gone, bro?
Trying to find my DBS chat and I can't
find the [ __ ]
anywhere. Yeah, but I'm not there to
approach. Yeah, I'm not there to
approach. I just Why would I approach them, love? Oh
[ __ ] Why would I approach
them? They're just going to say they've
got a boyfriend. Why would I [ __ ]
give I'm probably not even going to go
out this week to be honest with you.
Just pointless. Same [ __ ] every week. Grace, man. Bye-bye.
Everyone, no, I don't need to have a
bank to the toilets. If I wanted to
approach somebody, I would have done
it. [ __ ] I know where this DBS thing
is. I wanted
it under the chair. Where the [ __ ] has
gone? I have a wank in the toilet as
well. Where the [ __ ] has that DBS [ __ ]
gone? Swear down. It was
here. I don't know where it's gone.
Just messaging people, see if they want
to call out Thursday. But not looking good, [Music]
eh? Only over you, Monty. Only over
you. Where the [ __ ] has that
gone, Monty? Mate, some [ __ ] had that away.
Some [ __ ] has had that away,
mate. Nah, she's
not. Where was that DBS? That's going to annotate.
Some [ __ ] had that away, mate.
Maybe I put it in the bin. Hold on. I
only needed it for a job thing I pass.
So, got it
anyways. So, I don't really need it.
Maybe I chucked in a bit. Maybe. Yeah. Oh, probably.
Yeah. No, I'm not down, bro. I'm just
pissed off with the whole um dating
thing. I'm just pissed off with the
whole dating [ __ ]
It's actually mate like having to think
about it 3 4:00 in the morning sunrise
cuz obviously I couldn't go back to
sleep and all you see is the
sunrise. Yep. The [ __ ] sunrise,
eh? Well, at least we we should be able
to complete GTA San Andreas today. We're
on a 40 40 or 41st mission. So hope
you're well to uh agree that. Yep.
Wow. I'm so tired, man. All the working out and [ __ ] Yep.
Just another one to add to the [ __ ] collection.
AJ, I should be better tomorrow when
I've had a nice
sleep, when I've had a nice snooze.
Yeah, just going to work on my legs
tomorrow. Got nothing better to do, so I
might as well make the most of the membership.
Hey. Yeah. Now that's me going to the
gym. Told you I was I was doing this.
sat there eating his head
off. Oh, it's funny.
This is what this Jamie Thompson needs to do,
man. Instead of being on YouTube all day
every day with his fat ass, he needs to
start doing stuff like that today, ain't it, Steven
Howard? instead of coming on
YouTube. Yeah, [ __ ] proper fatty in
here. I told you these people that come
on here every day repeating and self
projecting, they're just [ __ ] fat
people that get bullied.
That's all they are, bro. Is just fat
people that's been bullied their whole
life. Told you this many times before,
bro. Fat people that's been bullied their whole
life. And you didn't call me back. No.
You already know why people are down,
bro. I just told you about that [ __ ]
thing in [ __ ] Australia. It's [ __ ]
depressing, bro. I was thinking about
that. That is
depressing. That is really, really,
really, really, really, really depressing, bro. minute. Greet
Steven come out
today. All right, let's see.
Back to getting no dates or anything,
eh? Back to the same old again. [Laughter]
Eh, literally, mate, I ain't got no
eyelashes. What the
[ __ ] It's a madness, isn't it?
No, the only time I'm going out this
week is if someone wants to meet
me. Otherwise, I'm not going
out. I'll be bothered, mate.
Why people like her do the things they do,
bro? I don't understand it, bro. It's
just proper [ __ ]
up. Is just so [ __ ] up, lad.
put on another walk today,
mate. If I had
um if I had a
um baby kangaroo, I'd be walking around
with a baby kangaroo. Yep. They
don't I can't believe she [ __ ] done
that. [ __ ] [ __ ] poem.
Yeah, I wrote I wrote a poem, bro. They
don't all live the other side of the
world. Oh, no one cares, bro. He doesn't
even know what gym I go to. So, good
luck. No one
cares. He doesn't even know what gym I
go to. And he will never know what gym I
go to. And no one cares.
He needs to join a gym and shop sitting
on his fat lonely ass all day instead of
trying to find out where people's gym
is. He will never know where my gym is.
And even if he does, he will never get
me kicked out. Take your weirdo [ __ ]
somewhere else. Bye. No one cares. Anyways,
so they don't all live in the other side of the
world. I've never had someone before
live in Australia that I liked.
I've been on a date with somebody from
Australia. I've kissed somebody once
from Australia, but never
before. Quite depressing, isn't it? It
was reminding me of the whole USA days
about two and a half years
ago. Some dark times and really really
dark dark times.
They were dark fans, bro. So
yeah, it's so [ __ ]
up. Lucky I have like people that can
just come around me and [ __ ] Otherwise,
I don't know where I'd be, bro.
Honestly. Know where I'd be, bro. For real.
Yeah, I want a baby kangaroo, man. Just
to like pet it and stuff. Yeah. Yeah. Right.
Hold on a minute. Right. So, this L
J I said to him I'd give him the flight,
the money for the flights once he's
proved he's booked
the Once he proved he books once he
proved that he books the
flights. Then he's pussied out again and
then he's trying to find out where
people go to the gym. He is a [ __ ]
man. I swear to God he is an absolute [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, he's a [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. Oh my
god. You know, you know that is as good
as grassing. That's as good as police
informing to be honest with you. Yeah, that is
literally as as good as police
informing. That's and and and that's it.
But yeah, I told you I was serious
greasy about this fresh start and
[ __ ] Yeah, I'm just waiting for my
friend. I'm going to call my friends and
play some GTA. Bro, this is [ __ ]
depressing, bro. What the
[ __ ] Like, think of it, Grezy. Yeah.
You know how you walk the dog like king?
You're just walking the
dog and you're just walking a [ __ ]
kangaroo. But yeah, just LJ is a [ __ ]
Yeah, just remember Steven Howard. He
can only go for disabled people. You can
never go for someone like me. And that's
been proven. That's been [ __ ] proven.
He is a [ __ ] [ __ ] I even offered
the money for the [ __ ] the the
planes. The plane. He doesn't even know
what [ __ ] gym I go to. Try again. And
he doesn't know which one I go to. Try
again. Shadow. But anyways. Yeah. So,
walking with a baby kangaroo.
walking with the baby kangaroo. Anyways,
Grezy, you're stand out as opposed to
walking with a [ __ ]
dog. Yeah, [ __ ] them, bro. I don't care
about them. They're all fat, ugly
people. It's what I was saying to you,
bro, like about the fresh start. That's
They're all sat at home [ __ ] fat,
ugly mongos. They ain't got a life. But
yeah, Grezy. So you'd be standing out
with a baby kangaroo. Could you imagine just
hopping just pop
pop? I'll [ __ ] go to the [ __ ] zoo
and [ __ ] steal one.
Yeah. I got Aussie shampoo as
well. That's the only thing I can be
reminded of now.
The only thing I can remind of you now
is the Aussie
shampoo with the little poo on it. I've
been using it for years, mate. [ __ ]
years. That is [ __ ] Never thought
Australia though. Never grooms in all my
life. Yeah. I thought like n
Australia. I thought these people only
are [ __ ] up in America.
I thought these people are [ __ ] up in
America, but not [ __ ] Australia. I
thought Australia had [ __ ] more more
about them than that to do to do things like
that. You know what I'm saying? Gre I
was only thinking maybe to go there to be able
to Grezy to be able to love you again.
Maybe touch you again. Maybe make love
again. to maybe make love again.
Easy. No, what happened was I woke up at
9. My friend cooked for me um at 8 and
then I just couldn't go back to sleep. I
don't know what happened. I don't know
if I fell back to sleep, but I woke up
at 2:00 3:00 in the
morning. I heard a bird singing. You
know that peaceful sound when you hear
the little bird
singing? But I tell you, the worst one,
Greavves, is the one that got away.
That's the worst. You remember that
American four years ago who I never got
their socials, didn't know their name,
couldn't find them anywhere. That's the
worst. I think that's the actual worst.
Cuz then you're thinking, you know, all
your life that someone's in a country
and never finding them, even if it is
state. Why don't this [ __ ]
anymore? Every time, bro, I need to stop
this [ __ ] You know, my friend said he
said, "You need to stop the
approaching." He said, "You need to
stop." And that like we was eating. He
said, "No, you need to
stop." He said, "You need to
Yeah. I think I'm depressed about it cuz
I my sleep got [ __ ]
up. So, I'm just like thinking about it
in it. Baby kangaroo.
Okay. Sad times, is it? Sad
times. Why do these people do this stuff
like Lord Jay? Why do they just let
people get on with their
lives? Because he's a fat, jealous
loser. That's why. He's a fat [ __ ]
jealous [ __ ] loser. I'm going to be
waking up in pain tomorrow. But I like
the pain of the
gym. No way I can end up like these
people again. Even if I've got to
[ __ ] go out. Even if I got to go to
gym three times a
week. I just can't get over Ant-Man
Grezy. Like he comes straight from
Thailand to my mom's. That's [ __ ]
mental health, is it? That's mental
health, isn't it?
Just want a baby kangaroo. Not not even
a koala. Just a baby
kanga. Just a baby kanga. Hop hop hop
hop hop hop hop hop
hop. And you know what I'm going to do?
And I said agreed. I said this to LT.
One of these days I'm just going to be
like, "Fuck the lot of you. I'm going to
run away and never come
back." [ __ ] the lot of you. And there'll
be no there'll be no more upload for me.
That'll be the last you see of me
again. That'll be the last you see of
me. Just run away and never come back. Yeah. Should
I [ __ ] this
mate? I run that be the last you see
me. How do you feel about that? That
would be the last you see me. Why do I
never come back,
mate? People have done it. Oh
man, now I'm going to have this problem
every time I go out. Now I'm going to get this
nostalgia. [ __ ] hell,
man. I've got to deal with the nostalgia
and now I've got to deal with the same
[ __ ] [ __ ] boring, mate. [ __ ]
boring. I might just make some money this
week. I might just make some money this
week. I don't
know. Cuz I can't be dealing with this anymore, you
know. How many how many heartstrings do
you reckon I have left? Where
you think I'm I'm on my It's on its last
legs. I think my my my heart is
literally on its last legs.
Cuz don't forget, bro, I don't drink. I
don't really drink much. You know, I'm
running alcoholic. Obviously, I never
have been. I felt like drinking today. It's
Monday. That's very unusual, bro. That's
not a good
sign, you know. So, it's not good, bro. It's not
good. All over the same website. You can
watch Scooby-Doo on
eh. And you know what? Um, Drezy, um,
Joe said, "I've got these abandoned issu
issues." Abandoned issues, attachment
issues. No, I don't. That was only one
time with my mommy from
America. YouTube. That was only one time with my
mama. That's cuz I wasn't getting nutrients. You
know, Joe said, "I've got attachment
issues and abandon
issues." Oh, I met somebody from
Australia last week and I and I got sold
dream. Greeny, I got sold a dream. It
was special then, but it's over
now. 15 minutes of
chatting. Good vibes. Message back. Love
the message. Block me. [ __ ]
off. What the
[ __ ] I thought I found a new
mama. No, but seriously, that was
different though, bro. That's that's
like nut that's nutrients and vitamins.
So, I can do with that now. I'm going to
the gym, bro. You know what I'm saying?
I could do with that now. I'm going to the
gym. I can do with that now. I'm going
to the gym, but I don't have it anymore.
So, I just have to have
milkshakes from the
cow. Yeah, it's [ __ ] up, bro. What
these women actually do. It's actually [ __ ] up,
bro. I just said you want to meet up
before you go back on Wednesday.
after they loved the message and reply
back. I was sending it to my fans. They
couldn't figure it out. They said,
"What?" They couldn't figure this [ __ ]
out. But because they couldn't figure it
out because they loved it and
replied. So, it's it's proper [ __ ] up.
We expect it when there's no context and
people don't reply. We just, "Oh,
there's another country we've met. All right.
Yep. Oh, but I wrote a poem. Yeah.
I'm not reading this [ __ ] anymore,
bro. You know, I wish I could just go to sleep and
just just wake up just go to sleep for a
year until GTA 5's out. And when GTA 5's
out, I can go play
it and then just get sucked into
something. No, I just wrote a poem,
bro, so I can get sucked into this game, bro.
I hope this don't go on for very long,
bro. I hate this [ __ ] I hate this
[ __ ] I really [ __ ]
do. Cuz I thought after USA that would
have been the end. Nah, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. Cuz what happens when
you realize you're better than
someone and their life is going to be downhill from now, you know that
You know, you can you can just find
something else. It happens with
everyone. Cuz it's fun, bro. Is
it? It's fun,
bro. I think you're right because you
might think they might reply to it, but
they don't have a heart. So, I mean, we
kind of expect it. I mean, we should
expect it, but it's just [ __ ] up. They
are just [ __ ] up. What they do is it
is really [ __ ] up.
a lot. What they do is just so [ __ ]
bro. It is [ __ ] up what these people
do, bro. But again, you should expect in
these Western countries,
so you had worse
happen. Oh well, I won't be out this
week anyways. [ __ ]
this. Not about the money. It's not
about the gym. It's about It's always
the same [ __ ] over and over
again. But I still want a baby kangaroo
though. You can tame it and bring it
up. They're so cute, mate. You can put a
stony on it.
Maybe I'll get tempted to go if I don't
go out this week, but I can't see happen,
mate. And there's this other Australian
as well. Listen, listen to this.
Yeah. So, obviously they live
here. So we're talking, they're
messaging back and
[ __ ] and I'm saying like, "Oh, I said,
"Did you have a good night? It was lots
of fun. Was out in Brixton then Soho." I
said, "Nice. I haven't been to Brixton
in ages." I was out with my friend in
Soho yesterday, too. Surprised we didn't
bump into each other. She wrote, "Haha,
that would have been crazy if we did. We
ended up back in wherever." I said,
"Haha, it would have been
Ace." Then I've messaged them back
saying, "Oh, do you want to do something
Thursday?" They've not
replied, but they haven't blocked me or
anything. They just haven't replied.
So yeah, it's
just I noticed that with New Zealanders as well.
Every every country, right, let me let
me explain this to you, right? Every
country is is is different. Every woman
from different countries is the same, if that makes
sense. Like every wherever they're from,
if they're from France, they're all the
same. If they're from Australia, they're
all the same. They're all the same in
their own way.
Like, they're all the same. Like,
depending on what country that they're
from. Yeah, maybe I'm the problem. Even
though that even though I've put
approaching videos up on my channel,
even though you've seen text messages,
even though you can't even say one word
a lot of the time without them saying
they've got a boyfriend. Yeah, bro. I'm
the problem, not them. Okay, bro. When
you actually have life experience and
you actually deal with westernized women
and you stop being a s, you will know
what the problem is. Then you would
really know what the problem is. So, no,
it's not maybe that the problem is me or
not them. It's literally them. When was
the last time you've gone out in London
and you've tried speaking to a woman?
Their attitude stinks. That's not even
the worst of it. That's how I know when
people say stuff like that. They ain't
got no life experience. They they can't
do. You know what I'm
saying? Why Why are you asking stupid questions?
Um, but listen, it's not about evil.
[ __ ] all of that [ __ ] I'll tell you how
they're all the same. Let Let me go in categories, right?
So, British, they're the worst. Stuck
up. They'll pretend they got boyfriends,
think they're better than you. That's a
no-go. French women, they'll be very,
very nice to you, give you their number,
then they'll [ __ ] with your head. They
will never say they've got a boyfriend.
I've never had it from a French person.
An American person will just be stuck up
and unenthusiastic. Australians will be
nice, give you their number, message
back, stop replying. They're all different
to depending on where they're from.
So, no, the problem is with them and
their unrealistic standards, unrealistic
expectations. I don't like to use the
word standards. So,
yeah, that's why I'm out of it anyways. So,
Damn them, bro. Of course, it's them.
I've done enough approaching videos to prove
it time and time and time and time and
again. And you can also prove it because
my conversation is decent. I look
decent, but you still hear that I've got
a boyfriend [ __ ] So, you must have
forgot about all the approaching videos
and all the messages. But I don't really
care who believes me, who don't believe
me, but I know what I need to do.
So, so yeah, I don't care, bro. Like,
people can think what they want in it. I
know what I've done. I know what I need
to do. So, that's it.
But yeah, that's how they're different
depending on where they're
from. Uh, maybe they Bro, I'm not going
over this again, bro. I'm not going over
this topic again. I've explained this
about a million times, bro. If you think
that, then good for you, bro. I'm not
It's not my problem anymore. I've
explained this a million times before
and I'm not explaining it again.
If you think that, then good for you,
bro. That's nice. It's not my problem
anymore. I've explained it to you. I've
explained it about a million
times. If you think that they've got a
boyfriend, then bro, think that it's not my problem
anymore. You know, I'm not here to
convince anyone or you know what I'm
saying. You know,
there's it just
doesn't I'm not explaining it anymore,
but I can explain to you how they don't,
but it doesn't matter what I
explain. You would just It would just go
in one ear and out the other. So, what's the point?
So they don't have a boyfriend
because they don't have a boyfriend
because 70 70% of men are
single and 90% of women say that they've
got boyfriends and women come from other
countries to work from countries like
New Zealand, but they claim they've got
a boyfriend even though they're living
here. Oh, this woman's saying she's free on Thursday.
Okay. Wow. Must have been a voice note.
Maybe someone will meet us first suppose
then if they don't [ __ ] us around. Um
boyfriend. Okay. Okay. So 70% of men.
Okay. On to the thing. People come from
Australia. People come from New Zealand
alone but they claim they've got
boyfriends. It doesn't make any sense.
People go clubbing to the early hours in
the morning but they're never with their boyfriends.
You see how none of it makes sense? I've
got sisters. Sisters have got kids and
they don't go out clubbing. Never when
maybe once every 6 months if that. They
don't go clubbing till early hours in
the morning without their boyfriends. So
just put two and two together, bro. It's
like, and there's people out there that
are feminists. There's people out there
that are feminists
um that don't even care about men, but
yet they all seem to have boyfriends. It
doesn't even make sense, bro. Like, but
I don't care anyways, bro. Whether they
do or not, I don't
care. Why does she ignore it? As soon as
I send a voice not, she's then saying that she's
free. It doesn't make any sense, bro.
You know, after this one, I'm so done,
bro. I swear to God, I've had enough of
this. And it's it's not even about the
what? No, cuz realistically, yeah. I
tell you what pissed me off. Yeah. With
this [ __ ] Australian. Yeah. Is that
bro? They live in Australia. We get they
live in Australia. But the point is you
should have just replied, "Oh, you're
busy. You're going back home." And they
just left it there. We could have just
allowed it. But they want to do the
ultra dramatic as always. You know what
I'm saying? So, it's just [ __ ] up,
bro. And it's
like it's just [ __ ] up, man. It's like
if you just go out and you get I've got
a boyfriend [ __ ] it's to be expected.
We know this [ __ ] But these [ __ ] up
things are happening,
bro. Yeah. Just had enough of it, mate. To be
honest, how they're wired like that. how
somebody can be decent looking and they
do it to people that are decent looking
and they don't care. That would never
cross our mind, anyone's mind. You know
what I'm saying? Like, but they they
just seem to
be anyone would think you're a [ __ ]
70year-old [ __ ] man.
But well, if this one meets
then, you know, that will be the fourth
fourth one this year, which is terrible
really. But it does, it wouldn't cross our
minds. But yeah, there's no way they
have boyfriends. No
way. [ __ ] like three out of 10 have
boyfriends. There's loads of women out
there, they don't care about men.
Loads of them are just like living their
lives. Like a lot of men are just living
their lives. They ain't got no [ __ ] I
remember I spoke before I told Antman
about this. It was I think it was months
ago and uh she was from New Zealand.
Um and she said, "Oh, she has a
boyfriend." Yet she yet she moved here for
work. Yet she moved here for
work, but she's got a boyfriend that
don't live here. Imagine
that. Imagine that. It's a madness,
isn't it, Greasy? You loved your
boyfriend so much you left to go to a to
the other side of the world. The
furthest you can go away, but your
boyfriend's in New Zealand. That's a
crazy relationship, ain't it?
Saturday, bro. It was [ __ ] draining,
bro. Oh my god. It's all you was getting
on Saturday. That's why I'm not going
out on Saturdays
again. It was It was constant, bro. We
was trying to have a normal conversation
with people that were from our area. Me
and my friend. I went out with my
friend, boyfriend, boyfriend, boyfriend.
I thought, "Fuck this, mate." I can only
imagine the amount of times that [ __ ]
Ant-Man got here that day.
God knows how many times he got it that day,
mate. Yeah, it does. It does get
draining. It does get
draining. It is boring, bro. It's [ __ ] boring,
mate. I personally think they're just
stuck up and they think they're better
than they actually are and they're
entitled. That's what my actual opinion is.
Yeah. So, she's saying she is free on
Thursday. What's they say?
Monday. Yep. Going to make some [ __ ]
gains. Well, I might get a kiss this year, eh?
But I've been [ __ ] with before from a
[ __ ] uh New
Zealander. They're kind of like French,
are they? Greasy. See, if you approach a
woman from France in England, in London,
they're not going to ignore you. They're
not going to tell you they got a
boyfriend. Nah, no, no. They like to
play the long game. They want to get in
your head. And they will reply back,
"Oh, yeah. Trust me, they're they're
very they're smarter than you think they
are. You think, "Oh, they're French."
Nah, they don't really understand
English, mate. They're the worst for
trolling. They're more like, you think
of a French person, they can't text
this, they can't text that, they can't
text this, they can't text
that. And then they, you know, they they
will type all of this madness, bro.
Like, remember the one with their little
dress with a little
dress? did have a kiss this year.
Uh, wait, I actually did. Yeah, someone from
Scotland. Yeah, I actually did actually.
I don't know what I'm talking about.
Yeah, I actually
have actually I have. Yeah, back in
February. And is there another
one? Yeah, I think one. Yeah, back in
January. Why does that Why would that
surprise you? I actually did have one
back in February actually. That's weird.
And that surprise I'm trying to think of
the other dates I've been on. Oh no,
obviously that 19year-old as well. Why
Why would that surprise you, bro? You
know, a lot of single people don't
kiss in in in 6 months. Why Why are you
laughing at that? A kiss doesn't mean
anything. But yeah, French women,
they're very like um
trolling and they're very clever as
well. Don't put it past them, mate. They
will just write a whole You would not
think it's a French person that's
writing it. And they've done it a few
times as well. About four
times. Yeah, there was one I was
speaking to. They're just take they're
just they're just piss takers, lad.
They're just piss
takers. But I can't hate them because it
is kind of funny at the same time. So
like I can't even like I don't know.
It's funny the way they do it. There was
one I [ __ ] done sober like right
outside the train station. Got the
number. But obviously it's a piss take.
They're taking a piss, but it's too funny to
hate. I want to dress up in my little
dress, you know? What the
[ __ ] It's bad, bro. That that that
year. Yeah, the trolling was getting so
bad. It was getting so
bad. Yeah, it doesn't matter. But yeah,
I have kissed two people this
year. That doesn't mean
anything. [ __ ] baby kangaroo.
Yeah. So, I just said we can meet where
where I said we're going to
meet. This is [ __ ] exhausting, mate.
You you actually think messaging people is exhausting,
Grezy? Nah, man. It's not even that. I
tell you what's [ __ ] exhausting. The [ __ ] whole approaching. Oh,
mate. That's what's [ __ ] draining, bro.
Let's just hope this person meets on
um that um thingy and then I never have
to do this [ __ ] ever again.
Yeah. Got some popcorn for later.
Let me go on thingy
channel every day. So I just went on
it. Baby kangaroo.
They're so cute, man. Yeah.
Oh, but I didn't feel anything in my
toodger. Do you remember that one? But I
watched that once, but I didn't feel
anything in my
dodger. I don't know where mommy fight
got me. I don't know where Laney got me.
She must have brought up the wrong
brought the wrong kid home in it. Yeah.
Yeah. Don't know where Laney got me.
I think I'm I think I'm nuts.
Seriously. No, you know what would
happen? What would happen is the
kangaroo would have the the the the baby
in its pouch. So obviously I'd have the
baby with the person from
Australia. Tie baby Peter would be in
the kangaroo's pouch. Bounce, bounce,
bounce, bounce, bounce.
So yeah, then that's what would happen,
man. Yeah, it would be in in a kangaroo
pouch as it got older.
Yeah. Having little T-bones in the barbecue. Steven
Howard having little
t-bones. Having little t-bones. Oh, the barbecue.
H. Well, this one just said they said
they're going to meet me on Thursday,
but we'll see.
Okay, they said Thursday they'll meet
me, but this one was from ages
ago. But in terms of Saturday and n sausage,
mate. Not a
sausage. I'm not going to make that.
um Muslim anymore. I'm not going to do anything until
she reaches out to
me. Nope. Nowhere near a fatty, mate. I
don't go for
fatties. No, I don't go that is lad. Uh, so
yeah. Was a pig. She's a [ __ ] pig.
Oh, I wish I could show you. I wish I
could show you this pie Australian, bro.
Yeah. I think Antman is funny.
I think that man is actually funny. Steven
Howard, do you not think? I think he's
funny. They all got
boyfriends. They got
boyfriends. [ __ ] funny, bro.
Hi, bro. Do you remember that teacher? I
was talking to them earlier again. I
said, "Let's let's meet up on um Thursday. My friend got
boyfriend. That's funny, bro. One second.
So, do you think if I didn't come on
this YouTube thing, YouTube would have
been a peaceful place, Steven
Howard? You think like it would have
been a peaceful uh peaceful
place? LT wouldn't have been arguing
with most people.
What do you
think? Am I behind a lot of it or am I
behind a lot of it?
remember. Ah, what are you doing,
mister? Wee wee.
Why do you need people like me? Samsung
I'll be back later, bro.