All right, captain. Oh,
[ __ ] Sleepy today.
Oh, Jesus Christ, mate. Put that [ __ ]
fan back on. I can't sleep without the
fan on. So, it gets quite expensive. Oh,
mate. Oh, I'm so tired. Body's
aching. Just a little snooze, mate. Just
Just a quick kick. And do you know why I
go live here when I'm just about to go
to sleep? Because of the repeaters make
me make me make me feel tired.
because they're so boring. So, they help me fall
asleep. The community is so boring. It
helps me fall asleep. I don't have to take any
pills, which is a good thing. Oh, in the little
nestles. Can't beat it. Can't beat it,
mate. Oh, [ __ ] me. Oh [ __ ]
man. Jesus Christ. My chest and my
bloody arms are [ __ ]
I'm just chilling, man. I just had a
breakfast. I'm [ __ ] I'm so tired.
I was speaking to somebody yesterday. We
were flirting a little bit. It never
come from a cold approach, but they live quite far
away. They live in England, but they
live quite far
away. Uh [ __ ] man. Someone says they'll
meet me Thursday, so we'll
see. We will see.
Hey, we will see.
Oh, I'm not saying, but they live in
England. And then obviously I'm not
going to go out this week, but I'm
trying to I'm trying to think of a plan.
I'm going to do three days next week
because I'm going in three weeks, but
I'm going to do three days next
week. But I'm trying to figure out how
I'm going to do
this cuz if I go out drinking
Thursday and I go out drinking Friday, I
can't go out drinking Saturday. So, I
was thinking maybe drinking Thursday,
doing it sober Friday, then drinking
again Saturday and get on the shots and
get on like the proper
like the proper spirits and then I'm done
forever and that'll be the last three
days and then I'm literally done
forever. But it's it's it's it's trying
to like figure out a plan, you know?
I was thinking beers
Thursday, sober Friday, and then spirits
Saturday. [ __ ] it. There's nothing on in
this anymore. So, but not this week cuz
obviously I'm going gym and that. So, I
can't do it this week.
So, I'm trying to think of a way around
it. I felt like I could do some
approaches today. In the morning, I went out
But I can't be bothered, mate, to be
honest. It's just the same [ __ ] in it,
Joe. Same [ __ ] Well, I'll be out of here soon anyways.
J out of here anyways, matey. I'll be Captain. So,
yeah, God loves to try, mate. And you
tried your best in this country, and
that's all that
matters. And after them three days we
would have definitely tried our best. So
after that I think yeah we done tried and
failed cuz Adman he's not even tried no
like 10% as much as me and he's he went
he's been four times so you don't really
have no excuse. That's why that's why I
done it. You know, you ain't got no
excuse not to
go. So, Oh, I'm
sleepy. I'm sleepy,
Joe. Oh, man. I need to eat at one.
Nah, you got Philippines and that. It's
not just Thailand. I'm going to go
Philippines as well where people are actually interested.
So go to a country where people are
actually interested. Hey Joe, that
sounds like a good
idea. Yeah, [ __ ] not interested in
this [ __ ] country. That's for [ __ ]
sure. They're not interested in this
country that Adban said. They
mate just chilling, man. I'm making from
the gym. I'm chilling. I need to eat at
1:00. Then I'm going to
sleep. Even though I should be sleeping
cuz I need to get into a schedule, but I
have to sleep. I'm tired. I need to eat
at set times otherwise someone comes in
the house and kills
me. I'm joking. But yeah. No. Um I'm
just chilling, man. I need to go gym
tomorrow. I think I go over I'm just
going to go three times a
week. Do a full body workout three times
a week. That's enough.
Yep. I've been saying that for a I've
been I've been telling people for ages,
man. I can't be bothered in this country
anymore. We still got chances for people
to prove me wrong. There's this person
I'm speaking to and there's someone
saying that they're going to meet me
Thursday. If this person don't meet me
Thursday, I won't be going out this
week. And to be honest, I probably won't
be going out next week either to be fair.
So, I probably won't even be going out
next week. I don't know when I'll be
out. Then I'll go in two weeks. Probably
the week after before I
go. No. Why would I be joking? I'm sick of this
country. Maybe next week. I might do.
Where are we now?
Actually, Tuesday. Yeah, I could do next
week. If you do this week, there's no
point of you going to the gym. It's not
enough. You could do next week though. Definitely.
I'm just going to do three days
straight. Send it, man. [ __ ] it. In
it cuz I cannot go if I want to. I don't
have to go. The flights were only
[ __ ] you know,
£500. So, I mean, if if I meet someone
here, then I can just scrap it off. I
have no hotels booked or
anything. So, if I can meet someone
before, then then obviously I'll
stay. No hotels are booked or nothing.
No, no, no, nothing's booked. just a
flight. So, I mean, if I can find
someone here, then obviously I'll stay,
but if not, then I'm I'm out of here. Addios. Addio [ __ ]
simple. But let's face it, you probably
will be going because if nothing's happening years,
then yeah, I am
going. Uh, go away. Uh, go away. Hey. Um, Lewisville
Slugger. Oh, this my eyesight's getting
getting worse. Lewisfield
Slugger. I'm not Monty Man or Timmy.
[ __ ] off. You're boring. Even Joe knows you're
boring. Like, you're boring, bro. There
there's no such thing as raw steak. Go
away, Louisville Slugger. Go on your 101
different accounts, you boring bastard.
You you know you get Do you know what?
I'm so nice, right? I'll tell you how
you give yourself away. You say man at
the end of every sentence. It's
obviously you. I can smell you from a
mile off, man. You know what I done
yesterday? You need to stop doing that.
Go to the gym or whatever it is instead
of coming on YouTube every day behind 101
accounts. You know what I'm saying? You
know, you are literally Louisville
Slugger. I can smell you a mile off. I
can smell you a mile off, mate. Like burnt
popcorn, you know. We It is literally
you. It is literally you. You're You're
the only person that does that in the
same style. You're low life, man. Get a
life. Get off of YouTube. I'm chilling
today, man. I'm [ __ ] with my workout
yesterday. Get a life. Get off of
YouTube. Isn't that right, Joe? Get off of YouTube.
get off of YouTube and get a life, man.
And yes, Joe, I am going. So
yeah, you need to get off of
YouTube. What the [ __ ] does raw steak
mean? I've never never never heard of raw
steak. Nope. I'm going tomorrow, man. I
said I'm going every other day. Well,
three times a week.
Oh well, I probably to be honest, I'll
probably go every other day because I've
got nothing better to do. I'm going
tomorrow. I go every other day. I could
have done legs today, but I never work
on legs, which is bad. I know, but never
have. So, think I'll do enough [ __ ]
walking. I'm going tomorrow every other
day. And then I'm going to be sending it
next week if this person don't meet me
Thursday. Three days in a row and then I
am done. I could just make the money
back in three days anyways. That's the
plan of attack anyways. send it three
days in a row and then I am literally
done. When I go I'm never I'm I'm I'm
I'm never trying again here when I come
back. That dictates it. When I look to
Max and everything, bro, like and that will be
me. That will be my notice.
So, but this person has has been
speaking to me. They've come out of
nowhere. So, they are real and stuff.
So, hopefully we can do something this
week. If I need to travel 4 hours, I'll
mate. I'd rather be
single. Yep. I'd rather be single. I
don't like any of the women on this
community. I would these women are
nothing to me on these on this community
because they're on
YouTube. I see better women every single
day of my life. I've been with better
women. So, that's why none of these
women on here bother
me. It's and that's how you know the
people that go on about them ain't got a
life. All of the numbers that I get or
people I meet, they're all better than [ __ ]
her. Uh she No, not stinky. Not stinky.
I just I just
wouldn't. No, I just wouldn't I wouldn't
get with any of the women on this
community. I could have got with her
before Monty, but the age gap was kind of weird.
I mean, even this Australian Joe, the
age gap is weird. She's I think she's
20, which in a way is too young for me.
I'm I'm going to be 28 this year. So, I
don't know what it was, man. It was just
maybe the like you said, attachment
issues, being sold a dream. I'm over it
now. Anyways, my friend had a bad
experience yesterday and we just got
over it together. So, he gave me some good advice. 22
She's 35, but she was 32 when I was 22.
And I thought it was a bit weird. I was
22 when she was 31. 32. That's too
That's too old, bro. When I'm 20 [ __ ]
two, that's too old when you're
22. I was a lot younger then, you know.
So, the age gap is weird. But yeah, even
20 is weird.
10 years isn't that much? Yes, it
[ __ ] is. That is weird, mate. The
most really you want to go, it's four
years, but obviously this person is 22,
so it's a bit No, you don't want to be
more than four years. I used to like it
when I used to meet people the exact
same age as me. I don't know. I just
thought it was good. But you don't want
to go more than four
years. 10 years is weird. It proper. It
is really weird. It's 25 and 35. That is weird,
mate. That is so [ __ ] weird. If you
don't see how that's not weird, then I
think it's proper weird
me. Proper weird. Someone in their 20s
dating someone in their 30s is a bit
strange. The oldest person I've been
with, I think it was Sig and she was
31. But we didn't date. We just [ __ ]
So we just had sex. So that was that was a bit
different. That was 26.
So trying to think how old No, I think
that is the oldest I've been
with. I've met some like 30 or 30 year
olds, but not 35, not 37. That's
even it's a bit I don't know. It's
strange. I just say to this one, what
you doing on Saturday? I can come up to
where you where you live. Got nothing to lose,
eh? The joys of having no
responsibilities, Joe, ain't it?
But after them three days, I am
legitimately done here. So there'll be
no more sending it. There'll be no I
mean I should have I should give up now
to be honest, but stubbing me is
stubborn me in it. So yeah, I've worked
out a plan and that's it. And
yeah, I'm using this phone. I can only
use uh WhatsApp on it.
Uh cuz my other phone I put my thing on
my other phone. So I just use this phone
to do the
approaching and then just message
everyone WhatsApp, Wi-Fi, WhatsApping it.
So I'm used to this phone.
yeah, I can make the money back anyways
that I spend. All right, mind.
Dating in this country. Hey Joe, dating
country. [ __ ] joke,
mate. Shouldn't be this hard. It should
not be this
hard. They asked me what the bar was
called. I told them what the bar was
called and where to meet and I did not
responded. Oh, you know that teacher,
she said that. I said, "Oh, let's meet
on Thursday." She said, "Um, today's
been hectic. Unfortunately, I've got
plans this Thursday. My mom's arriving from
Australia." So, then I sent a voice note
saying, "Okay, what about Friday or
Saturday?" Cuz I told him what I [ __ ]
do, you know?
So, yeah. [ __ ]
man. I never said I only stream once a
month. Yeah, that's where we're at anyways, man.
I'm done after them three days when I
when I decide to do it
again. But I don't know what I don't
know what raw steak means. There's no
such thing as raw steak because you can
eat steak however you want it. And my
steak wasn't even
bloody. So, I mean, that's [ __ ]
weird cuz um you can have steak however
you want it.
To be honest, the less it's done,
actually better it
tastes. What does raw steak mean? I'd
like somebody to explain that to me. I
know raw pork. I know raw
chicken. No such thing as raw beef.
Boxes eat steak raw. They actually eat it
raw. So, I'm going to eat um steak and chicken today. Yeah. Yeah.
I have to eat at
3:00. Around about that time. 1:00,
sorry. And then 6:00. Oh, sick. Oh,
matey. Oh, my belly my belly is going to
be so flat by the time I go out again. Oh.
But they are what I mean though. They're
here today, gone
tomorrow. These be archers. So
Better give it the end of the day to
reply. Wait, what's the day tomorrow?
It's Wednesday, isn't it? I'll wait
until tomorrow then because it's
Thursday. Oh, [ __ ] hell, man. This is
exhausted. Oh my
god. Anyone would think I'm a 70y old creepy man. You
know, but it is wrong that we were sold
a dream. You know, we should have never
been sold a dream. We should have been
told like they're not interested in this
country. Give up. Simple. Unless you
want to spend thousands and keep dealing
with time wasters, then you're best off
just leaving or just giving up to be
fair. I'm going to be confident again
when I try. Trust me, mate. I could have
sent it today if I wanted to, but I just
can't bother. But that's but you don't hear that.
So, and I think it's wrong to sell people a
dream cuz that's the reality is that
yeah, I've been with some people, but
the amount I've tried and the traveling
I've done, I've not really been with
that many people and I'm not a [ __ ]
ugly 70-y old man. So, it doesn't even
really make sense why. But
yeah. Oh, what do you mean? Who's the
mother to believe it? I was [ __ ] 19
years of [ __ ] age. They made out that
oh if you if you approach it will solve
your dating life. You know you'll meet
someone and no no no. We were we were
sold a dream to believe that once we
plucked up the courage to approach it
would work out. But all you get is I've
got a boyfriend. I've got a boyfriend.
We never we didn't know that
though. That's what I'm saying. We
didn't know that stuff until we actually
done it. Then obviously the trolling on
the dating apps was no good for the
mental health. Then we thought, okay,
well, if we actually go out and we start
speaking to people, we're actually going
to find someone.
But yeah, well, I'm not ugly. So if you
try and call me ugly, you're just self
projecting. So, cuz we all if you're if
you're going to try and talk about
looks. Yeah. Listen, we have seen you
people. We have seen what you people
look like. Yeah. The problem is me.
Well, my videos Well, my videos say the
problem is not me. So, again, I'm not
talking to people that don't leave the
house. I'm not getting into a debate
with people that's never approached
women ever in their life. I know it's
not. I'm leaving the country and that's
it. I'm not trying to I'm done with
trying to make people understand. It's
boring. What what do I get, Joe? A
comment on here trying to get a bunch of
40, 50y old
um people to understand. What do I gain?
Nothing. What What do I gain out of
sitting here and exp say I sat there and
I explained it for 2 hours to a bunch of
people that are in their 40s and 50s
that don't even leave the house. You're
literally just wasting your time, bro.
You might you might as well just go to
the gym for like 3 hours.
people that literally have no life
experience. It's It's literally
pointless. Proper proper proper
pointless. It's for
real. I was saying before I was
disturbed, Joe, if I speak to someone
tomorrow, I'm expecting not to speak to
them the next day. I think that's
realistic expectations. Yeah. I always
have it as I always think of it like
this. here today, gone
tomorrow. Like, say I'm speaking to
someone in the middle of the night, I'm
thinking, okay, well, the next day,
yeah, they might not reply or the next
day they might just go quiet or I don't
know, they just won't reply. I expect
that cuz it it will always suffer. That
happens. Too many stuck up [ __ ] in
this country. Yeah. So
yeah, so yeah, bro. Um, yeah.
So yeah, I expect it any I expect that [ __ ] anyways. So
yeah. No, I don't think about them. I'm
just telling you how like it is and
[ __ ] I don't need to think about it. I
know what I'm doing. I know the three
days I'm doing. So you know what I'm
saying? I don't need to think about it.
just [ __ ] up, bro. I'm over the
Australian thing now, but that's [ __ ]
up, bro. That is proper [ __ ] up. But
it's like what Adman said, they're
westernized. What did you
expect? We take the piss out of it, but
like they're all the same in the in
these westernized countries. For [ __ ]
sake, bro. The sooner you learn it, the better.
that reply fence reply and then they troll
you. Yeah, normally they reply and then
they troll you and then
[ __ ] then they just stop replying.
They never really block
you. Yeah, I think I've had it with four French
people. Why is that so weird?
Okay, I'm not here to make a bunch of
[ __ ] 40, 50 year olds that don't
leave the house
understand that literally have never
done a cold approach in their life. It's
[ __ ] pointless, mate. It's like me
trying to understand before I done it, you
know, because it seems that way. It
seems that oh you know if you approach
you know and they say they've got
boyfriends it seems that the problem is
you but really the problem is actually
them you know and that and that
literally what it is which is why I'm
leaving obviously the problem is [ __ ]
them you know clearly from the
approaching videos it shows that that
you know the problem is them and they're
not interested as much as they try to
sugarcoat and blame the man you know
they do it on Reddit all the time bro
[ __ ] of course the problem was [ __ ] dead.
This is why so many people complain
about the same thing. It's not one or
two people. It's multiple people
complaining about the same thing. Yeah,
they might react differently to it. I've
got friends, so many friends, and they
always complain about the same thing.
They say they've got boyfriends. I can't be
bothered. Like same, you know, different
people, same complaint.
So same video, same story, you know.
So if it was truly an an individual
problem, it would not be happening to
other people. It happens to other people as
well. So yeah.
Yeah. What's your opinion on it, Joe? Do
you think it's [ __ ] up how hard dating
is in this
country? I think it's just proper [ __ ]
up. I think it's really really [ __ ] up,
mate. Enough people don't [ __ ] talk
about it enough.
But I expect this person is maybe going to stop
replying. That's what usually happens.
It's always mind games. You would have
thought at like 27 years of age you
would have found somebody that doesn't
play [ __ ] mind games. It's always the
same. Mind games, mind games, mind
games, mind games, mind games.
And it's [ __ ] boring, man. You know what I'm
saying? [ __ ] people.
Eh, country people. Yeah.
got eat, bro.
[ __ ] I had someone say to me like,
"What's your diet like?" Cuz I thought
I'm going to gym. I was like, "Why are
people talking to me like I'm stupid?"
Like, "Yeah, bro. I'm going to the gym
and I'm eating McDonald's every day."
Like, is that what you actually think?
They told you like you're [ __ ]
stupid, bro. Like, I've not been to the
gym since I was like [ __ ] 15 years of
age. like I haven't made massive
gains. I hate people that speak to you
like they think you're stupid.
I'm just going to say to
this thingy, I'll just come next week.
This week, I want to try and meet
someone this week, you know, out of like
contacts that I've got and that I'm
going to try and meet someone this
week, but I won't be going out
approaching anyone. So,
yeah. Won't be doing that. Oh,
That's the thing. You get horny as well.
You know when you go to a gym, you start getting
horny. That's another thing. You start
getting horny when you go to a gym. [ __ ] hell,
bro. She [ __ ] proper audio, man.
be back later. Anyways, see