Yo. Yeah, I'm coming off here today anyways.
Yeah, this is getting weird again.
This bastard community, it's getting
weird and jealous again, but very weird. [Music]
It's getting proper proper weird again.
They're [ __ ] absolute like I know
we've said it before here. They're
actual low lives on here, bro. They're
actual low lives that live sad sad
existences. I swear to God, bro. And
Monty's not coming on my live streams
anymore anyways. He's going back to them
snaky ways. Oh, I don't like it, bro.
I don't like it. [ __ ] weirdos. Like
even even the other day when I was
drunk, God, their lives are so [ __ ]
these people, bro. I swear to God. He
ain't coming in again, though.
Monty just being a snake again. Oh, as
usual in in in little ways. He's being
the snake again.
Yeah, bro. He's a proper proper snake.
He is. Like, if you're intelligent
enough, you can actually see what he
actually does. But then if you let him
on and then you get a bunch of people
typing [ __ ] about like his kids, he will
start crying about it. This is what I'm
saying. And he will start crying about
it again and again and again and again
and again. So like I see what he does.
It's just every time. This is why I
don't join his panels. This is exactly
why I don't join his panels because it's
the same thing every time.
He will think the heat is off him. Yeah.
and then he finds it entertaining and I
have to leave again and then they will
go for him again. It's literally the
same scenario every time.
Like I was in these chat, right? I had
these bunch of [ __ ] [ __ ] kept
starting on me time and time again. I
said, "Meet me, meet me, meet me, meet
me, meet me." And then he's having a go
at me. I was like, "Why you having a go
at me? They brought trouble. I'm just
sat here chilling having a conversation."
Uh, no I didn't. Um, no I didn't.
Try again. No, I didn't. So, yeah.
Please have been called. That's good. I
didn't break no bell conditions. Good
for you. No one cares. You sad little
grass and little pathetic bastards.
No, I haven't. Try again, though. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Good for you. Yeah. You keep
telling yourself that.
You sidle bastards. Yeah. You keep
telling yourself that. No, I haven't.
You tell me. You You wish I did so you
could get the pizza bob cuz you're a sad
little bastard. You people ain't got no
lives. That's why you do all of this
because you fat ugly people ain't got no
life sat on YouTube every day. Yeah.
Oh, where's this thing gone now? It's
not letting me go on it. Why? Yeah.
You wish I broke my bell conditions. You
[ __ ] wish. I'm coming off this [ __ ]
anyways. It's weird, bro. It's just
really, really weird.
Said the same thing to Pride. Meet me,
won't meet me. Said the same thing to
the other one. Meet me, won't meet me.
They're just weirdos. They're just low
lives that just have to try to get
people nit because they're all jealous
of other people that's got a better life
than them. Simple. I ain't joining no
Monty Man's live again. I'm not coming
on here again. [ __ ] a lot of you.
Simple. After this live stream, I'm
done, bro. It's [ __ ] weird. And and
and and they try to target you as well
when you're drunk. They're low lives,
bro. Absolute low lives. They even try
to target you when you're [ __ ] drunk.
It's so weird.
So [ __ ] weird, bro.
God, they're weirdos.
Proper weirdos. I'm coming off, bro. I
need to go a gym tomorrow as well anyways.
Oh [ __ ] Why is that dog
sat on YouTube ain't got a life every day?
It's [ __ ] pathetic, bro. Weirdo.
Why is Why has that gone dark, though?
You get all the same spastics on there
again. [ __ ] red star. Red star. Red
star. I ain't got a life, man. They
ain't got a life. They're just fat, ugly
people that ain't got no life. That's
why they're sat on here every day. It's
fat, ugly people that ain't got no
[ __ ] life. Literally. And it's the
truth, bro. It is honestly the the gods.
The god's honest truth. Literally,
they've got no life. None whatsoever.
Same as that prime. Same as that [ __ ]
fish, man. They're all the [ __ ] same.
I'm joining your live stream. You want
me to come on your live stream? I'm on
your live stream. We're talking. I'm
getting these spastics that starting. So
I said, "Okay, they're starting it.
Let's finish it." And then Monty's
saying he's weird, bro.
Monty does this every time, bro. He He
does this literally every time. You
know, I don't even talk to him on it. He
does this literally every time.
Bye-bye, you fat ugly bongo. You're
another one. You fat ugly [ __ ]
Bye-bye. You should you should join the
gym as well, you fat ugly [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm just start ripping into these
people now cuz that's what they are,
bro. That literally is what they are.
That literally literally is what they are. No lie.
I got a date on Thursday, by the way. Cactus.
Yeah, I got a date on Thursday, Cactus. Yeah. pretty much.
These people need to get a life, bro.
And me going live is not like really
helping it. You know what I'm saying?
They they clearly have no life. Like you
should have just went on you it's
actually the fourth day but you should
have went on Monty's bro like they got
no life. Like you should have went on
Monty's when I was on there. They
literally have no life. I don't think
you went on there but they really have no life.
It's [ __ ] sad. really really
and truly have no life. I'm coming off
after today, bro.
Proper proper weirdos.
You see that thing I sent to USA Cactus?
Did you see it?
It's the same spastics every day.
Monty's the same snake. Same story, same people. Yeah.
Oh, I sent her a voice note cuz I
messaged her on a number and she didn't
um she has she has she actually has that
number. He actually has that number.
Yeah, she actually does have that number.
She actually does have that number. You
know, back on that number
cuz it was two ticks. It went to two
ticks whereas before it was one. So,
she's back on that number. She blocked
me straight away, mate.
Oh, I wanted to show you Australian Izzy as well.
But yeah, I'm just going to be done with
Monty as well, bro. Like, I'm done with this place.
Yeah, I want to show you, bro. This is
uh Australian, isn't he?
What I tell you about all that? Oh, yeah.
Good old Australian, is he? E. Bye-bye, fatty.
Bye-bye, Fatty. I'm going today. Bye-bye.
Yeah. Well, the next week, not the next
[ __ ] day. Look how Australian is he cactus.
life, you sad fat bastard. Nah. Nah, mate.
What happened? Do you reckon she turned
her Sim off that USA? Easy. And then
turned it back on. He must have turned
it off and then turned it back on.
Yes. She must have turned it off and
turned it back on.
When the coast was clear, it [ __ ] idiot. Yeah.
But no, she didn't.
Yeah, money can have a YouTube now anyways, bro.
He can deal with these spastics.
They come on here, they can't have a civilized conversation.
Yeah. And then uh
then they turn it back. Yeah. And then
[ __ ] you know what I'm saying?
They then start [ __ ] with people and
then they [ __ ] run away. What the
[ __ ] What the actual [ __ ] bro? Yeah.
Yeah. Like what the [ __ ] They can't
have a civilized conversation and then
they [ __ ] start [ __ ] Like, bro, it's
not a thing. I can go to Birmingham on
Saturday and [ __ ] that prime up. It's
not no problem, bro. It's not no
problem. The guy keeps still going on
about two years ago, bro. He's not about
anything. He's a keyboard warrior. Yeah.
Now I can actually talk about it now.
Yeah. Listen, you caught me off guard
two years ago. You caught me off guard,
you absolute [ __ ] Yeah. You was bigger
than me and you caught me off guard.
Yeah. I can come to Birmingham on
Saturday, not a problem.
and I will [ __ ] and and I'll literally
[ __ ] you out of your own city. And it
will actually be your own city. Like,
you're not about it. Same as that guy in
London. He's not about it.
You know, they start [ __ ] It's like
that Smokeoky Be. They start [ __ ] cuz it
sounds good. But guess what? They never
finish it. And it will always be the
same with these spastics.
Be the same with these [ __ ] low lines
on here, bro. Every time. Same as LJ
offered the flight, buddy. Same as LJ.
Same thing again. Back to repeating,
bro. Same as that smoky weed that lives in
plastics. Same self projectors.
Do you know what I'm saying?
You know, you need to grow up, mate.
You're in your 40s and you're on YouTube stalking.
Go up and get a [ __ ] life. You sad
fat ugly bastard.
Yeah, you sad fat harassing
stalking bastard. You ain't got a life. Yeah.
bastards on here, bro. S bastards.
I'm going to tell Monty to join my live stream actually. Yeah.
Now, I don't come on people's [ __ ] to
argue. I not argue with people that
don't want to finish [ __ ] That's why
there's no there's no point going on
these live stream because if someone
starts [ __ ] bro, but what do we do on
it? We block them, which is what it
should be on bodies. If someone starts
on [ __ ] if someone starts on someone,
you block them. He doesn't block anyone.
He lets them stop, but then when it
happens to him, he cries about it. He
cries about it. Huh?
He literally cries about it, bro.
The [ __ ] man. You can't have it both [ __ ] ways.
And that's it.
Yeah, you can have your shitty community
after today. Anyways, I'm done with it.
I'm telling Monty that as well. Same
thing as well. It's weird, bro. Too
weird. Too stalkerish for me. And that's it, bro.
Yep. Yep. Bye-bye, Fatty. Go make
another account, Fatty.
Bye-bye, Fatty. That's the fourth
account you got blocked now, Fatty.
You've got everything that I want, yet
you can't stop coming on my channel
projecting. Listen to what you're
saying. I've got You've got everything I
want. Yet you keep coming on my channel
stalking me. Yeah, bro. You have
everything that I want. Yeah, buddy. You
keep telling yourself that. That's why
you keep making fake accounts to get
blocked. Nothing screams that you've got
everything that I want than keep coming
on YouTube every day getting accounts
blocked. Yeah, bro. You hit the nail on
the head. Get a life, you weirdos.
[ __ ] hell, man. Absolute [ __ ] weirdos. Yeah.
Bye-bye. Fifth account now, Fatty. All right.
You have everything I want. That's why
you're stalking me every day. Sad
bastard. Get alive. Get off of YouTube. You're alive. Uh,
and they're so desperate to get people
nicked as well. They're proper losers.
They're such losers. Like everything
that they do on here, they're proper sad
little [ __ ] victims.
Shadows, man. You notice they'll come
here when I'm drunk as well. They're
such sad bastards.
really really really are so jealous.
I've never met such so many jealous
strangers in my life. Like it's [ __ ]
nuts, bro. Such jealous people. I never
know people to be jealous of people that
they don't even [ __ ] know, bro. It's [ __ ] weird. [Music]
Bastards ain't going to laugh but YouTube
ain't got no life but YouTube
believe him, bro. Swear to God. Yeah.
Such sad little bastards.
I'm coming off this [ __ ] bro. 100 million%.
Such weirdos, man.
So desperate to try and get people
nicked as well. They're such sados.
So, you know, they ain't got no life.
No life on YouTube every day. But
they've got everything that I want, but
they're on YouTube every day. Oh, yeah, man. Okay.
Lord J's becoming a weirdo again,
projecting his anxiety onto other
people. These spastics have been doing
this for years. They're literally never
ever going to stop. Literally, like
these [ __ ] retards
have literally been doing this for
years. These [ __ ] retards will never stop.
Like honestly, these retards on here
will never ever stop. They've been doing
it for [ __ ] years.
They're proper retards, man. Proper retards.
Project self projecting retards.
That's it now. Is it? Yeah. Piggies will
be on my door soon. You wish they'd be
Yeah. You wish they'll be on my door
soon, you little grass. You reckon?
Yeah. You wish in your wet dream, matey.
And that's what I'm saying. It's just
all weird [ __ ] with you on you people in
this community. It's all weirdo [ __ ]
You've been doing it for years, man.
I've just had an argument with three
people on that live stream. You're all
weirdos. Literally, man. You've got some
major problems, bro, from [ __ ]
childhood or some [ __ ] And you come on
here and you take out another people,
bro. You're all [ __ ] Yeah.
You're weirdos. You absolute weirdos.
And I'll say it to the police as well.
You all weirdos. You people in this
community are weirdos. Yeah.
And that's it.
Proper proper weirdos. And you never
stop as well. Not biting nails too much.
Nah, mate. You people never make me
anxious. You little You little pathetic
bully victim people. You don't you don't
make me anxious. Nah, not biting the
nails at all, mate. You people don't
scare me one little bit. You've been
doing the same [ __ ] [ __ ] for years.
You with you disabled people. So yeah.
Yeah. Sat on YouTube every day of your
lives. Nah, mate. Never mind over you
spasticated people. Anyways, go get a
life, you little weirdo.
See, that's what we do, bro. We don't
argue with people.
We don't argue with people
on our [ __ ] on our [ __ ] We don't
argue with these spastics. We kick them.
That's what we do. We don't argue with
them. We kick them.
know what I'm saying? Weirdos.
And be telling I'll be telling Monty the
same thing as well.
I'll be telling him the same thing. Yeah.
See, why my channel don't get out of hand?
My channel don't get out of hand. He let Spastics in.
He cries when Spastics, you know what
I'm saying, bro? So, like that's it.
But I mean, everyone on here's a snake
in it. So, [ __ ] weirdos.
Proper proper weirdos. They spend all
their life projecting and trying to get
people nicked. They're proper [ __ ] life losers.
Like proper proper proper life losers.
Dedicated obsessed losers.
Literally. They literally
proper losers, mate. Proper proper life losers. One Yeah. Oh yeah, literally thinking Yeah, man. Um, Anyway,
I'm gone, man.