Should should be working. I don't know
why it's gone back to [ __ ] dark
again, bro. [ __ ] me.
It is Sunday. So yeah, Monday definitely. Monday. Definitely
Monday for show.
Yeah, I don't really come on YouTube
anymore, mate. I've got a life on like
these people and it started like
creeping me out.
Yep. He's good. Yeah, man. It's just It
just started like really creeping me out
and [ __ ] So, I don't really come on
here anymore. I was waiting for Greasy
yesterday, but yeah, he didn't come on. Oh, man.
Yeah, bro. So, yeah, it just it just
it's so weird. It's it's it's so creepy.
I was telling my mom about this
yesterday as well. It actually gives me
the creeps this this um community. It's
so weird, man. It's [ __ ] [ __ ]
They're obsessed. They're weirdos. And
they never stop. They literally never
ever stop. They ain't They ain't got a
life, bro. This is why you don't see me
on here. All of it is just weird.
Uh just somebody I went on a date with
who I'm seeing again. She's actually
really nice to be fair.
You never realize how bad it was. Wow.
Wow. It's very bad.
You should realize how bad it is. It's
very bad. I thought the photo would
trigger someone. So that's why I just
thought I'd put it up there. And the
other thing is, and it's like Monty, I
told Monty as well, you can have your
creepy weird community cuz I said to
Monty, I was on your live stream. We was
talking normally and you have these
idiots that [ __ ] start, but then they
don't want to finish it. They want to
stop, but they don't want to finish it.
So what's the point, bro? It's creepy. It's weird.
And Ronnie is a snake as well because he
knows that they're going to start on you
but they're not going to meet you. So
he's allowing [ __ ] on his channel. So in
a way he is actually snaking cuz he's
allowing [ __ ] on his channel and
there's no [ __ ] on my channel. If
someone hates and someone projects,
they're blocked. Done.
They ain't [ __ ]
That's all she wrote, bro.
So but he lets them on. So what the [ __ ]
which is creepy. It is actually so
Like the way they bring family members involved and
they do anything to try and get people
nicked. It's so creepy. Literally, it
gives me the It's like a creepy old man
going near a school. I'm not even
joking. That's the only word you you you
can use for it. You know what I'm saying?
That's why you don't see me on here much
anymore. It's just I'm chilling today.
[ __ ] have a little live stream.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah. I was at my mom's the other day
and the I saw the neighbor.
He was chatting [ __ ] Just walked past
him. You know what I'm saying? And then
you got people on here,
you know, starting [ __ ] with people that
they don't even know. Yeah. I was at my
mom's for a few days. I was worried
about her. I thought she died. So, I had
to deal with a lot of [ __ ] going back
there, but I just ignored it to be honest.
I just ignored it. You know, I'm an
adult and at the end of the day, I know
there's consequences for your actions.
You know what I'm saying? How many times
I have to bite my tongue and not do anything?
Yeah. You You don't even know, bro.
It's like that prime, for example, when
I was last on One, Bob, there was a good
there was a good part of me that wanted
to go there and [ __ ] whip his ass.
But there's no point. There's no point
with him. There's no point with the
neighbor. There's no point with none of
them. There's literally no point.
You know what I'm saying, bro? Cuz the
way you got to see it with these people
is that if they're still starting [ __ ]
they've got nothing going on in their in
in their life, bro.
There's nothing going on in their life
if they're still doing this [ __ ] Crime,
neighbors, whatever. Well, neighbor, not
neighbors. So, they they've obviously
got nothing going on in their life really.
Yeah. The neighbor was saying stuff to
me. I just walked past him. I was like,
"Bro, you're still I was thinking in my
head, is this guy still salty from 8 months ago?"
I was like, "What the [ __ ] The guy is
still salty from 8 months ago." I was
like, "Bro, this this guy needs to get a hobby, bro."
And then I was walking there. I
shouldn't even be telling you this. And
there was this old woman and she broke
her neck to look at me, bro. Like, she
broke her neck to look at me, bro.
If looks could kill, I'd be a GTA
character killed on the [ __ ] floor in
my own blood, mate. That's all I'm
saying. But I just ignore these people,
me, I don't bother with these people.
What the [ __ ] is that? Chili gobas.
Oh [ __ ] I just I don't bother with it,
bro. Fighting and all that. It's no point.
See, I was thinking, yeah. Okay. You got
argue, you argue with these people on
YouTube, this prime. Okay. So, you go
there, you [ __ ] him up, and then what?
It never ends. It will never end.
They're all biased on here. They're
obsessed. They're clearly jealous of
something, whatever it is. So, there's
no point. That's why I just don't come
on here anymore unless I'm pissed. I
just to talk to Grezy.
All of it's creepy. All of it's weird.
So, that's how it is.
These people want to be me or something.
But yeah, I had a good date the other
day with that woman. She seemed really
nice. And she looked way better in
person. Oh my god. But
she's [ __ ] sexy, man.
Way better in person. Oh my god.
He's bolding hands and everything. It's good.
I feel ill today, man. I got three numbers yesterday.
I ain't text him yet.
detox. Two week detox now. I weren't
even in the mood yesterday going out,
but I wanted to keep my options open. But yeah,
we went on that date on Thursday. I
weren't even in a mood to be honest. I
just thought, "Oh yeah, they're just
going to be another time waster." No,
no, no, no, no, no, no. Like that's just
how I had it in my head to be You'd be
delusional not to
I done an approach. Oh, you're going to
laugh at this, right? I was on the
corner shop the other day
by the yard. Yeah. And there was this
woman in a little dress. She walked
past. I thought, "Oh, let me just go and
say I won't going to send it." I was
like, "My to my friend, I can't be
bothered." He said, "I'll just do it." I
done it. Yeah. Literally got her number
and guess what? She literally,
bro, there was people clapping on top of
the balcony, bro. They ain't seen
nothing like it before.
So, I'm just out here living life, bro. And then
you got people from LA a channel being
salty. You got neighbors being salty.
You know, it's ridiculous. But I can't be asked.
I got the gym. I got stuff to do. You
know, and then these people are so
obsessed every day. I don't know.
Dating still [ __ ] you know.
changing it is what it is. way.
But this is the problem you're going to
have as well when you start this dating
and [ __ ] because where people have
wasted your time so many times in the
past when you do find somebody that's
actually genuine. If you ever find
anyone that's actually genuine, you will
[ __ ] it up because you're just going to
assume, "Oh, they're just going to waste
my time again. Oh, this person just
wasting my time again because again,
you'd be delusional not to think that
what's the chances in this western
society, bro. You know what I'm saying?
I was talking to a few people about this
the other day.
Yeah, I got [ __ ] on Thursday, man.
Wine, [ __ ] rum, [ __ ] different
beers. And to be honest with you, didn't
really have much of a hangover. I just
slept it. I just slept it. I just slept
it off to be fair.
She is cute though. That person
we're going to meet again. Yeah. But
I think the only thing you can really do
in this country is
make money. Try
take it for what it is and leave. That's
all you really can do, bro. It's You
don't need to complain about this [ __ ] anymore.
You know what I'm saying? It will never
change. Like, yeah, obviously that's
what I just said.
She's sexy, bro. Oh my god. In real
life, she is like, bro, he is actually
I can say that cuz I'm the one that
[ __ ] approached her. So,
but yeah. Oh, [ __ ] up, bro.
So, yeah, I am.
I thought I just put it up there just to
trigger these people cuz they tried to
tell people that they can't get women.
They tried to tell people that they're
skin. They tried to tell people they're
this, they're that. But in reality,
they're only just talking about
themselves. We all know these people are
just talking about themselves. Like,
literally yesterday, Mom, you see me in
the bar? Oh, you're this. Oh, you're
that. Oh, you're this. Oh, you're that.
But here's the thing, bro. None of these
people's opinions matter to me one
little bit. [ __ ] a lot of them. You
know, you know what, right? You know
what I I'll do next time I'm drinking
and someone tries to insult my
appearance. I'll say, "Am I really?"
Yeah. Yeah. Why don't you come on
camera? I'll say to them, "Am I really?"
Right. And I'll say, "Okay, fair enough.
Your opinion doesn't mean nothing to me.
Why don't you come on camera?"
and that's where you'll always win.
Something a little cheeky line like that
would be enough to just to just end it. So, uh,
and I was waking up with these mood
swings when I was on Monty's. I was
like, "Bro, we got these two we got
these people that like starting starting
something that they can't finish, which
is a good thing really to be honest cuz
none of these people here are worth meeting.
No prime, no no one." You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, I thought my mom was dead. She
wasn't [ __ ] answering her phone and
[ __ ] She was sleeping. So, I just went
round to see her. I was like, "Mate, you
could have got me [ __ ] healed coming
here." You know what I'm saying?
Nah, it's just that area is like that.
They got nothing better to do. They
don't really venture out. So
obviously if someone does put their
hands on you and they try to violate
then yeah you fight back but other than
that I would just ignore it mate. I'm
I'm at that age in it. It's just weird drama.
you know. So,
and sometimes you'd have to stay around
there when your mom has to live there
and it's not, you know what I'm saying?
It's it's just not worth it, mate.
I want a peaceful life. You know what I mean?
I don't need to act the bad, man. I
don't need to do anyone to prove a
point. Point this, mate.
Oh yeah, this idiots. Yeah,
they are a few numbers.
Why do Saturdays always seem to be [ __ ]
But you go out on Saturdays and they
always seem so [ __ ]
when they're that's supposed to be the best day.
Ant man a bit of a taste of his own
medicine yesterday. I said, "Oh, you're
moaning. Oh, why are you insulting me?"
I was I'm not insulting you now. You
know how it feels, mate. when I used to
have to listen to your [ __ ] every
Saturday. I'm a guy doing it. And I
said, "Bro, listen. I've had more
success than you. Don't compare your
experiences to me. Yes, I deal with
[ __ ] Yes, I dealt with [ __ ] yesterday,
but bro, I'm nowhere near as damn bad as you.
Like, don't give it if you can't take
it, bro. Cuz then you just end up like
these people. I used to have to listen
to your [ __ ] every Saturday.
Every [ __ ] Saturday when you was
[ __ ] drunk. So, at the end of the day,
So, I can actually cuz cuz I can
actually say that I'm sick of hearing
it. Like I said, I've had more than you
and I've had women more women than you
and I've had more dates than you and
I've had more chance of being in
relationships than you. So, there is no us,
you know. There's there's you, you know,
just being a dick really. So, cuz I'm
sick of him just doing this [ __ ] every
[ __ ] month. Every every week. I was
sick of it. Every week, mate. You know
what I mean? Every [ __ ] week. I had
to listen to it, mate. [ __ ] annoying.
But he's a good guy, man.
Three times. Four times in a year.
quite good, man. It's quite impressive.
He would have done that if he stayed on
this [ __ ] community, would he? No. Sorry.
Yeah. No, you wouldn't
Well, those are rates that they're paying. Yeah. One second. Um,
Saturdays always seem to be the shittest.
I don't know why it is, but yeah,
always seems to be the shittiest.
I got whatever I went out Thursday after
that date, didn't I? So, and I got three
numbers. They all replied, "This is what
I'm saying, bro. It's it's
age difference maybe. I don't know what
it is." But
so, Saturdays you go out, there's loads
of people, but they all stuck up.
Thursday, you go out and then you get
less people, but
more opportunities. I don't know why.
It's It is weird. It is proper weird.
It is strange. It is strange.
Who knows about that?
This one could die, [ __ ]
Let it die. Let it die. Nope. Bye-bye. W Richie.
Yeah, to be fair, I'm not even hung
over. I stuck to beer. I think it's the
food that made me sick.
to be honest.
But we still have to deal with a lot of
[ __ ] in this country. But yeah,
don't know if that guy was messaging on
[ __ ] YouTube or [ __ ] what, mate? Who knows? Ah.
Oh, mate. I was I could go to the gym
today, but let's just do fresh start Monday
this time. We won't be drinking the same week.
I see these people replying to be honest.
They're [ __ ] English. So,
I just can't see it happening, mate. Yep.
We are basic. Still got four numbers.
This is today. Yeah.
Oh, that's somebody sent me uh a picture
of her two bed. I said, "Boy, is that
supposed to make me Dennis or
something?" I was actually thinking, "Is
that supposed to make me Dennis or something, mate?
Told you, mate. I told you.
I don't have a [ __ ]
Why you stick to be mate?
But to be fair, I kind of feel like a McDonald's.
My thing is [ __ ] up though, bro. God,
I need to get sorted tomorrow.
I don't want McDonald's because it comes cold.
McDonald's comes cold though, don't it?
They should get the nuggets. Maybe
let's just have a big day eating [ __ ]
and then uh obviously tomorrow we start again.
Yeah, sounds like a plan to me, mate.
Yeah, Greavves. I'm doing this live
stream dedicated to you and you're not even here. Greavves,
I'm ordering some chicken nuggets.
I don't want to
put some chicken nuggets.
Need to do this film for this job, but I
lost my DBS.
I've lost my [ __ ] DBS that's got my
[ __ ] criminal history on it, man.
I'm ordering some nuggets. Seconds.
Very bastard thing that don't come cold, is it?
YouTube ain't [ __ ] paying me this for this [ __ ]
Well, 24 for some [ __ ] nuggets.
Yeah, mate. Oh,
wait. Where is it, bro? Okay, ball.
One second. I'm trying to order this. Yay.
It's coming. Where are you, Greasy? 45 minutes.
That can't be right.
45 minutes for some [ __ ] nuggets.
Well, that's [ __ ] up as well. Hey, Greavvesy.
Hey. I was out boogieing the night away
last night. My little mates
with my little friends.
Yeah, I had this date on Thursday with
this woman in the picture. She's really
nice. She's really cute, too. Who was holding hands
and I was rubbing her little fingers
and uh her nails was painted pink. I
said, "Next time we meet, can you have
them violet, please?" Violet nails. B it.
Oh, it was so cute,
Grezy. So bloody cute. I had chicken and
pizza yesterday. Grilled chicken and pizza. A bless.
Let's go. Yeah. Sorry, Grezy, man. I
don't really come on here much anymore,
bro. It's the same people every day. You
You know it, bro. You know you know it
when I when I say this stuff, bro. Like,
and you know what, brother? It's not
It's not a community. It's just [ __ ]
weird. It's creepy. It's not a community, bro.
A community is where people talk about
things and religion and or they game.
They these people just self-project
every day. It's not even It's just
obsessed. It's weird. It's creepy. I
said it I sent it to my mom as well.
Yeah, cuz I went around the other day
cuz I thought she was dead. So, I went
down at six o'clock in the morning to
see if she was okay. Zy and I just said
to her like it's just it's just creepy.
It's actually a creepy community. Freakyified.
That's what it is. It actually gives me the creeps,
man. You might think I'm I'm joking, but
I'm actually not. I just come on here to
talk to you here.
Yeah, fresh start tomorrow. Back at the
gym tomorrow. Fresh start.
Don't have a hangover. So, yeah.
I don't have a hangover, Grezy, cuz I
just stuck to beer. But I've got a sore ass.
That sounded really wrong. I've got a
sore ass from the food I ate.
Yeah, mine's [ __ ] 46
minutes away. Bro, I really want this
Samson fold that's coming out next
month, but I can't I can't pay £2,000,
bro. That's ridiculous. Greavvesy.
I love Samson, you know. I'm a huge
Samson fan. I like all their little all
the little things that they that they
bring out. Yeah, I wasn't in the mood
yesterday to do these approaches, but I
just done him anyways. But I'm done for
two weeks now. I need a detox and a
break. But the thing is, Grezy, that
I do want the fold cuz I like Samson's
little products, but I don't know about
paying £2,000, mate. We're not [ __ ]
made of money here.
and I wouldn't get on a contract. So, I
just have to go without.
I just have to go without, mate. Cuz
there's no way I paid two grand for a
phone and I'm not getting a contract. So,
I'm pretty much screwed.
Yeah, I got the nuggets because the
burgers and chips always come cold. So,
the nuggets, they're eatable. You know
what I'm saying? When you order the
chips and a burger, it's [ __ ] cold. I
had Burger King last night, Grezy.
Yep. Add Burger King.
Definitely fresh start tomorrow, bro.
Sure is, Cactus.
Ain't I got a story for you, Cactus?
Haven't I got Haven't I got a story for
you? So, I was at the corner shop. Yeah.
What day was it? It was Wednesday. Yeah.
Yeah. I remember this. It was Wednesday.
And there was this little woman in a
dress, someone else. And I was like, I
might go and approach her.
I said, I can't be bothered. And then my
friend said, "Oh, you might as well." So
I followed her. Then I approached her.
Then we chatted. Then I got the number.
And then everybody was clapping. I made
a scene, Cactus. A big scene,
you know. But
I went out yesterday. It was still [ __ ]
Bro, it is still hard in this country,
bro. [ __ ] me. I was out yesterday
boogieing the night away. You [ __ ] missed it.
I don't know, bro. It's weird. Yeah, I
started on Ant-Man yesterday, ain't it?
He doesn't like it when someone gives it
back to him, does he? He's like, "Oh,
you're starting on me." I was like,
"Mate, I had to listen to your [ __ ]
every Saturday." I'm a gas doing it. I'm
a gas. Right, bro. No, you don't like it
when someone says it back to you. I said
to him, "Listen, there's no me and you,
mate." Yeah. Even though I have to deal
with these [ __ ] [ __ ] Even though
I have to deal with this [ __ ]
you're you're way down bad than me. You
ain't had nothing in years. I've had
more than you. I've been to cities with
you and and I and I pulled and I've had
chances to be in relationships and I
basically have been in a relationship.
So, there's no there's no [ __ ] me and
you. All right. you know.
Oh, some guy up the, you know, like a
balcony. There was a guy, there was, you
know, like a balcony flat. There was
some guy watching it. He was watching
the whole thing and he clapped.
Yeah, it was a [ __ ] madness.
It was a [ __ ] madness.
So, I just been out doing stuff. I don't
really come here anymore. It's so
freaky. Why can't everybody just plain
nice? That's what I don't understand.
I've been hitting the gym getting all
musculy and stuff.
Why don't man like him when you give it
back to him? Yeah. You want to know the
truth? I'll tell you the [ __ ] truth.
Other guys do it. You know what I'm
going to do one day? I'm so sick of
[ __ ] hearing it. I'm going to jump on
the [ __ ] Weather Spoons table and I'm
going to be like, "Other guys are doing
it. Other guys, how are you doing it?"
That's what I'm going to do, bro. He's
going to drive me to it one day. This
[ __ ] Yeah, this [ __ ] is going to drive
me to it one day. Yeah.
No, no, mate. He was loving it. He was
loving it, mate. When I got the number, Cactus.
Yeah. No, he was loving it, bro.
He was absolutely loving it.
I met some uh Kiwi lad yesterday,
Greavvesy. I was telling them about Alf
Stewart. They had a little mustache. You
know when they get they don't have
anything but a mustache. Greavvesy.
Well, Australians normally have that.
But these Kiwis had it. Oh, it's 25
minutes now. That 20 minutes was quite quick. So
yeah, they were they were proper Kiwi
lads. It reminded me of Mick Jonathan
Robinson Cactus who traveled to
Australia to try and uh tried to cover
his very dark but very devious past.
Cactus, he thought by [ __ ] off to
Australia, everyone would forget and he
wouldn't get caught. Nah, mate. Nah,
mate. We know what you done in England.
Isn't that right, Cactus? Every single
time it just reminds me of of of uh of them. Yeah,
they're proper Kiwi lads. We was having
a good chat. Oh, and guess who I was
with yesterday, Cactus? I was with the Indonesian fella.
And guess what? He's still [ __ ]
scared to approach.
He's still [ __ ] scared to
approach. I was with him yesterday.
Yeah, she's proper cute, man. She She
looks better in real life as well. We're
meeting again. She's proper cute, bro.
She's sexy, bro. She looks better in real life.
Cuz she's got a WhatsApp picture, but
she doesn't look as good in her WhatsApp
picture, but she is. She is cute, man.
I'm not even going to say where she's
from because you got stalkers on her and
that. But I just wanted to piss off a
certain person. Cactus, not mentioning
any names, but leave it at that. You
know, we're law abiding citizens here,
mate. But we'll leave it at that, then. Yeah. Yep.
She is proper cute, man.
Just holding hands and stuff, vaping.
That's how I got vape, cuz we vaping, you see.
Yeah. So, if I start dating this person,
look at USA Izzy, she's got a loser in
tattoos and look who I'll be with. And
even if it's not her, it will be someone else.
Well, [ __ ] loser, bro. [ __ ] off.
Know what I'm saying?
Yeah. I saw the neighbor, you know. I
went to my mom's. I saw the neighbor
cactus. It was very awkward.
It was very awkward indeed, bro. It was
so [ __ ] awkward.
People hate me around that area, bro.
I'm the new kid in town, bro. Wait,
we're not even inhaling it properly. I'm
They must think you're the new kid. Why
didn't they do anything? I can't be
bothered, bro. I literally can't be [ __ ] bothered.
You know me. I can't be [ __ ]
I can't be asked, man, with it all. I
just want a peaceful life. You know what I'm saying?
I just want a peaceful life. I don't
need to act no big man, bro.
You know what I'm saying? I just want a peaceful life
hopefully with this person. So, yeah.
But hopefully you don't [ __ ] up because
then we'll have to start it all over again.
And trust me, it's not funny. So, come
on, nuggets. Where the [ __ ] are you?
Did they say they were vegetarian? No, I
don't think they did.
No, they didn't.
Yeah, Greavves, I told you. I went to my
mom and somebody broke their neck to
look at me, bro.
I said, Mo, I don't think I'm going to
come to visit you anymore. This is really weird.
this old woman with a friendship, bro.
She was staring at me, bro.
I was like, "Bro, is this real life?"
Like, "Yeah, okay. We get it. We We
[ __ ] up a little bit." But this was
almost a year ago and they're still
salty. And I was only checking to see if
the old deer was still a [ __ ] live.
You know what I'm saying?
I'm never left alone, Cactus. Whenever I
go for a night out. Yeah. Last time I
went out on Thursday, I thought my mom
was [ __ ] dead. Then when I went out
yesterday and my [ __ ] card broke
broke and I got my sister messaging me
getting me involved with her problems.
Am I ever left the [ __ ] alone?
It's such a buzzkill,
you know? It's such a [ __ ] It's such
a buzz kill, mate. Maybe when I go out
again, I would actually be left in peace.
I'm never left alone, bro. never left alone.
You remember when the tenants used to
call me back cactus? What a buzz kill.
What a [ __ ] buzz kill. You know,
that's why I used to stop going out
because there's there's no point. I'd
make it into central London
and make it into central London, cactus,
and then I just get called back. What's
the [ __ ] point?
She is cute.
One sec. Where the [ __ ] is this?
Where [ __ ] are these [ __ ] Anyways,
Cers, I'm going to put a picture up.
I want to show you this Indonesian fella.
He says the girls are waiting for me.
So, why don't you do anything then?
This is me. I'm I'm going to cut my
other friend out. But yeah, this is me
and the Indonesian fella.
So, his English has improved, but he's
still very scared to approach,
which is a bit silly.
Right. Where are Oh, 6 minutes away. Oh
my god. I best get a [ __ ] t-shirt on. Grooy.
Jesus Christ. Oh, it's almost here. Oh, nuggets.
I've been having these nuggets since I
was a child. Since I was a fetish baby, remember? All right.
6 minutes away.
Oh, we're going to be making some gains tomorrow, bro.
Yeah, I'm about to put a t-shirt on. I
already feel like I I put on some
muscle. Look at my arms, bro. They're [ __ ] huge.
Look how big my arms are.
Doesn't take long for me, matey.
I reckon I could put three pounds of
muscle on uh in a month.
I can put three pounds on my to 100%.
Where are you stupid nuggets?
We're waiting for you. Come on.
[ __ ] cute, bro. interested. I have
Where is it? Where is it? Where is it? Gosh
darn it. Crazy.
Yeah, that's me and my little mate.
We're good pals. We've actually become
good friends. But apparently I don't
have no friends apparently.
That's just another form of projection.
It's coming, bro. It's coming.
We all know that LJ has no friends, man.
He talks about himself every day.
I want to try and make some babies with
this woman, bro.
What would they come out like if I had
babies with this woman? Cute.
What do you think, bro? You
I think Burger King's better than
McDonald's, but I think most people disagree, eh?
No, I think Burger What do you think,
Grezy? Burger King or McDonald's? I
think Burger King 100%.
Yeah, it's got to be Burger King in it.
But Burger King's not as popular as McDonald's.
I was having a discussion about this
yesterday over a burger. Me and this guy
were talking about this. He said it's
got to be McDonald's. But I think Burger
King's better, mate. But the nuggets,
McDonald's, 100%. Nothing can beat McDonald's nuggets.
Nothing. Like nothing. But the best is
KFC anyways, to be honest.
The best is KFC, I think.
Do you remember Grievy when you said God God um
God bless any woman that meets me, Greavvesy?
They don't know what they're in for.
Is that true, Greavvesy?
The women that meet me don't know what
they're in for. Is that true, Greavvesy? Oh man,
I was worrying like, are they going to
meet me or they not going to meet me?
What do you mean that's on them?
She's got a nice bum
holding hands walking around Leicester
Square. Greasy. What a lovely sight.
I was like, "Oh, I'm actually holding
hands with someone now. I'm sick of
seeing all of these couples holding
hands now. I'm being them for the day,
Grezy. I'm holding hands
with a young lady for a change.
How [ __ ] cute is that?
I'm one of them for the day. Come on.
Wait a minute. Come on, you [ __ ]
Yeah, I was waiting for you yesterday,
Grey. Bro, why was you taking so long?
I was saying, hey, boyfriend,
but you was [ __ ] you was gone, bro.
Did I get it yesterday? The boyfriend
[ __ ] 100%, bro.
I [ __ ] did that. Then I spoke to this
American just snobby up her own ass.
Didn't even know she was American.
But what what do you actually think it
is, Grezy? Like on honestly on on on a
level, I just think there's too many
stuck up [ __ ] in this country. I
think the person on Reddit was right,
though. Like stuck up [ __ ]
They said London is the problem with
London is it's very westernized and the
women think they're a lot better than
they actually are.
You need to try somewhere like Eastern Europe.
You say that's the problem with London.
Very very westernized. You know what that means?
But I love London though. At the same
time I do. It's just that they give us a bad name.
It is good London but they give us the
people just give us a bad name, bro.
They really give us a bad name.
They think that they're something that
they're not, bro. And it's and it's and
it's bad. Yeah. Okay. Dress better.
Yeah. You get more money. You do better.
But your attitude should never change.
You know what I'm saying?
But their attitude changes. They seem to
think they're better than everyone else.
You should know Greasy. You should you
should take a trip to Liverpool Street,
lad one day. jump on the train and you
you'll see stuck up everywhere, mate.
Hello, boss. Okay, the code is 638.
Thank you, boss.
That's my Mackis.
Could you imagine Ronald McDonald brought it?
That' be so cute.
Did you imagine Ronald McDonald bought it, lad?
[ __ ] hell. It' be so cute in there. Oh, what?
Yeah, he's real as well.
Yeah. Oh, the nuggets.
They're stone bloody cold. No, I'm
joking. They're nice and warm.
I remember always having this when I was a child.
Remember Grey years ago when they used
to do the um
when they used to do the dogs the dog
toys in McDonald's many many years ago. We're talking
maybe 13 14 years ago
when they used to do the crazy frog
toys. They used to do the [ __ ] dog
toys. Don't you remember?
Yeah, mate. That's what that those were
the days, mate. But yeah,
those were the absolute days, man. Crazy
frog. They done. What was the other one? Yeah.
You remember when they used to put toys
in the cereals? Squeezy.
Well, they used to put toys in the cereal.
Those were the days.
You might not remember it, Grezy. It
might be a bit past your time, but they
used to um put toys in the cereal. Yeah,
there used to be um ones called Big the Robinsons
and I really wanted a baby try and I
couldn't get it and I couldn't get it. Yeah.
I used to get my mom to check all them
to see what Yeah.
Oh, that's nice. But
no, I'm joking. McDonald's, the only
good thing about McDonald's is the
coconut nugget. But I wouldn't go in
to McDonald's to order it. I'm only
ordering it now cuz Oh, I need to go to
the butchers. I've got lamb for dinner today. Mhm.
But why is McDonald's so popular?
That's the million dollar question.
Because it's not even that nice. Yeah,
the nuggets are nice. you know, when
you're [ __ ] a bit hung over and that, but
all right, say you're drunk and then you
you go after you're drinking. But
I can't believe it's the most popular restaurant.
I just can't I just can't believe it.
Everybody on the