[ __ ] I'm exhausted.
Going to get KFC and some ice cream, I think.
Yeah, [ __ ] it, man. I'm so tired. I'm exhausted.
Tired, man. [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm going to get some B and J today.
None of them want offer.
is trying to get off there.
I really like the cookie though one. [ __ ]
I just try and [ __ ] walk somehow.
That' be a laugh. See? Yeah.
just depressed, mate. I'm going to go
KFC in a bit and get if I can even make
it there. I'm so tired. Yeah,
man. Show me his Tinder from the
Philippines. They're interested in these countries.
Oh, look how many messages he's getting.
Yeah, you don't get nothing here, mate.
No, you don't get anything here.
Wow, they're actually interested in the Philippines.
Not here, mate. I'll be living that life
in two weeks. Don't you worry about
that. I'll be living that life in two weeks.
I'm I'll be me. Not in [ __ ] in in
[ __ ] in England.
Not in [ __ ] England, mate. Not
hearing about [ __ ] boyfriends. [ __ ] that. actually interested.
I'm actually interested in that country. Yeah.
No, he's not been to Asia. He's got
crippling anxiety. He's got he's got a
fear of flying. He does.
I wonder how many pills he had to [ __ ] take.
No, not in the Philippines they don't.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Not in the
Philippines they don't.
And that could be the same amount of
women in this country if you wanted to
say that they just want your money. They
just want your money in this country as
well. Just more of it. Not in the
Philippines, they don't. Not in the
Philippines, they [ __ ] don't. And
also, we it don't even need to be a
third world country cuz even if you went
to Japan or China, you wouldn't have these problems.
or even if you went to South America,
you would have these problems. So
when you're saying they just want your
money, that's the same as the women here.
So what's what's the difference,
you know? But no, in Philippines, they
actually want relationships. He was
telling me all about this. And obviously
you got China and Japan, they're not
third world countries, I don't think. Uh,
sat here [ __ ] starving out my
stomach, man. I'm hungry.
You can send it, but I won't be there.
I'll be out of this country in two weeks. So, yeah.
Yeah, I'm not repeating it, bro. If you
don't listen to my [ __ ] then that's on you. It
£15 your name.
I'll be broke soon, mate. Don't worry about that.
Yeah, I'm not skin.
I'm not skin at all.
I get money in two days as well.
Well, this woman in New Zealand was
trying to make out that £650 skin.
[ __ ] hell, man. Have a word with yourself.
when he proves that he's booked it. Yeah.
[ __ ] me, bro.
Imagine that, bro. Jesus Christ.
These women really are entitled.
I [ __ ] hate them.
I really do hate them.
No, I'm not booking it for him. Well,
well, I could book it for him, actually.
Yeah, if he gives me his email. Yeah, I
could actually. Yeah. Yeah. Well, he's
never going to come for me. His anxiety
won't allow it, mate. He can only keep
going for disabled people like Timmy.
The guy's a [ __ ]
He ain't about that life. He's got
crippling anxiety. He's boring, mate.
He's been off and out many, many times.
He doesn't come out. And he actually
seems to think he's big as well. He's
just some fat diabetic
[ __ ] freak that's never had a fight
in his life. And he goes on like he's
just being hard, man. It's It's funny,
bro. It's actually entertaining.
You know what I'm saying? It's actually
entertaining. Like, he actually thinks
he's about that life, but he's really
not. Anyways, man, moving on. I'm not
talking about this weirdo.
But this dating [ __ ] Joe, really needs
to be avoided.
You know what makes me laugh though is
these women try to give you advice, but
they're the ones that have life on easy mode.
And then when they say that they have
problems with people, they're very, very
minor problems. Have you noticed that?
I hating me.
At least it won't be at least it won't
be rigged against me when I'm [ __ ]
finally in Asia. So,
I'm in [ __ ] Asia, that's for sure.
Good loving life, bro.
It's [ __ ] depressing, though. It really is.
I can't believe this woman actually
thinks that people should pay on the
first date. How entitled is that?
So yeah, if you pay on the first date,
they're going to meet you again. Oh my
god, this is just these people are so
delusional, man. It's unbelievable.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, my [ __ ] bones are aching, man.
Someone said, "What do you think you did
wrong?" I said, "I didn't. Women just go
on dates to pass time or use you usually."
That's what I replied back.
Hey, do you know what? Do you know what
somebody asked me? They said to me, "Do
you want kids?" I said, "Why? Why are
you asking me if I want kids when you
know that's not possible? But for your
information, I don't want kids. Then
they wrote around then you you have
written off half the female population over 24.
Then I turned around and said, um, oh,
really? They already ripped me off years
ago. They already wrote me off years
ago, so I guess we're evens.
I think that was a banger. Hey, what do
you think? I think that was a banger, isn't it? Uh,
I think I think that was a banger, isn't
it? They already they only wrote me off
years ago. So, guess we're even in it.
That's true. To be fair, brave. Why am I
brave? Trust me, we have be we have we
have much better things to pass the
time. Oh, really? What? Then go out and use someone.
Well, you [ __ ] don't. You've got
better things to do than the past of
time. Oh, really? Is that why you give
your numbers and troll people?
Yeah. Is that why a lot of you women sit
there when you troll people via
WhatsApp? Yeah. You keep telling yourself that.
So, I don't know if some why people ask
me if I want kids when I don't want
kids. that even if I wanted kids, unless
you go to Thailand, that wouldn't
happen. So what what's the point of the question? Definitely not Oh yeah.
Where do I go?
So yeah, they do go on dates to waste people's time.
So yeah, they are trying to establish if
you are serious about a relationship,
most women will want kids. So that's
true. That's not true.
Cuz when you approach women, they
pretend they got boyfriends. So what
you're saying is not true.
Yeah, it's just somebody I went on a date with. Ah,
I'm not always right about everything.
I'm not always right. I'm just right
about these women and these dates. So, yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. That was just a date I went on.
Well, at least I get to got to hold
hands and stuff and and and smoke off
the same vape, but that's about all I have. Yeah. So, yeah.
Yeah, we were smoking the same vape.
We were smoking the same vape.
Yeah, cuz I bought a vape, but we was
vaping the same vape and holding hands.
She was from Italy.
I've never been on a date with somebody
from Italy before, but I've had bad
experiences with them. They're proper [ __ ]
French, Italian, German,
Polish. They're all [ __ ] All of them are [ __ ]
Yeah, they're the worst.
Italian. There's another country I'm missing,
but Italy is one of the worst ones.
They're one of the worst. I I know this
before cuz I've
I've dealt with a a lot of them.
They're proper devious [ __ ] So, yeah.
Yeah. So, I've got the vape here.
Well, I'm not answering them questions.
Stop being weird on my channel. But yeah,
stop asking. Stop asking weird stuff. Yeah.
Stop being weird.
A good feeling of [ __ ] weirdo, bro. Yeah.
Yes, we know she's good-looking, bro.
Stop being a s. We've already been over this. [ __ ] hell.
And stop asking me weird questions. I'm
not answer I'm not answering it. We
understand, bro. She good looking. Not
being a s.
[ __ ] sake. You want
I didn't pay for all of it, but yeah,
I'm not I don't want to talk about
anymore anyways. And I don't wor the t-shirt. So yeah,
anyways, moving on, bro. Moving on. I'm
not talking about it no more. weird, bro.
It's better than that virgin can get in
it. See, you know what's so bad, though?
Is this little virgin tries to say that
I'm ugly. Yeah. All of the women I've
had, whether I [ __ ] them, the ones I
didn't [ __ ] the ones I kissed, the ones
I didn't kiss, the ones I done stuff
with, the ones I didn't do stuff with,
they've always been better than than his ugly misses.
He's ugly the wolf. But I'm the ugly one.
They've all been better than anything
that he's ever had. Have Have you
noticed that? Have you noticed that's a
correlation? That is. So, I'm the ugly
one, right? Apparently. So, this virgin
says with his rat face, with his rodent,
spasticated face, yet all of the women
that I have been with, one second, I'm
multitasking here, have all been better
than what he's with.
That's strange, isn't it? for someone
that's ugly like me. Talking about your
[ __ ] self, mate.
Oh, one second, bro. He's talking about the tunnel.
Yeah, it is jealousy, bro. But one thing
I love about this [ __ ] is like when I
meet these new people is that they these
people will never find them.
Obviously these cuz the first thing I
think of is that virgin
is cuz like obviously he would never be
able to find them because he doesn't
know them. So it will eat him alive the
fact that he doesn't know any of these
people and he obviously can't find them.
So obviously with the USA Izzy one I I
just I just doxed the [ __ ] and you can
see how obsessed he gets over her.
He's so obsessed.
So you can see like the kind of stuff
that happens when people know who who
they are. Obviously when they don't know
them, they can't contact them. So they
have nothing on you. So that's the thing
that's good, you know.
Yeah. So obviously they can't contact
them because they don't know who they are.
They don't know who they are. You see? So
that's the thing you got. That's the
problem you got with it.
But he's been doing this. He's been
doing this for years, Joe. You know, bro.
He's been doing this for years, bro. Sorry.
for [ __ ] years.
Literally years, mate. Like years, mate.
Before I even had sideburns.
It's all the fact it's all cuz he hates
the fact that he's a virgin. And mate,
you can keep going on about girlfriend.
Mate, no. Again, he's a [ __ ] virgin.
Trust me, he's a [ __ ] virgin. I
already told you about that please
thing, bro. How much time it takes up,
how you have to do it every week. I
swear I ain't I ain't followed it up,
bro, for [ __ ] ages.
Like, I need to follow up again at some
point. But you get my point, [ __ ] You understand? So yeah,
it's weird. But it does it does it does
make me think of it though
cuz the women seem to get better and
better every time. Have you noticed Joe?
They You seem to level up and up and up
and up and up and up and up. If you
stayed in this convers if you stayed in
this country, who would it be next time? Yeah.
Actually, it's my vape. I bought it.
Anyways, I'm not talking about it anymore.
I'm not talking about this no more, man.
Nothing goes wrong in the dates. They're
just time wasters.
I tell you, uh, do you want do you want
do you want to know how you know you're
wasting your time in this country?
I approached this woman from Pakistan
about it's got no three week two weeks
ago. Three weeks ago
simply I'll tell you a story. Yeah. And
then we met again on uh I think it was Sunday.
We was walking for 5 hours. Went to
Nando which I paid for. Just talking
about life. No weirdness. No trying to
kiss. No trying to do nothing. Just
walking man. My legs were [ __ ] by the
time I come back. Then they said, "Oh
yeah, we should meet again." No, no,
you'll be a good friend. I can't date
you cuz you're not Muslim. So I was,
"Oh, okay." Except the friend zone. And
then when I tried to like message them
again, they never replied. And that's
how you know you're just wasting your
time meeting these people.
So yeah, I'm going to have KFC.
So yeah, Cidy, I told you basically what happened. Yeah,
I tried to meet her again. I said, "Oh,
I tried saying to her Greavves, "Yo, I'm
not really experienced with this dating
thing. I had bad experiences and [ __ ]
but I think we shouldn't meet again at
that." But she weren't having none of
it. She replied back, but she weren't
having none of it. That also goes to
show that you wasn't you're not the
problem cuz you didn't even do anything wrong. But
nah, mate, I'm going KFC getting some
ice cream. I'll probably be in bed all
day to be fair. Yeah.
Poor life. Eh, I've had Subway for ages.
Why do these women go on dates to waste
time? Anyways, let's talk about this, Grezy.
Why do they go on dates when they're not even interested? Yeah. Huh?
No, seriously. Why? Why do they do it?
Um, to try to meet her friends.
I know it to try to meet her friends. If
I could stay with friends with her, then
I could have tried with her little mate.
Screamsy. turtle baits
and yeah that's why obviously Yep. Exactly.
Yeah, man. This a funny one. It is sad though
cuz they were sexy. Feels sexy, bro.
S of it.
I mean, USA Izzy went out for a free
meal ticket, but at least I had her [ __ ] body. Yeah.
Bye-bye. Stop talking about yourself.
Stop talking about yourself. Everything
that you've just wrote, everything that
you wrote, it just goes, it just goes
about yourself and you're in your 40s.
Go self-reflect on another channel, you [ __ ]
I can tell these people about
themselves, mate, in a perfect way. I
mean, USA Easy is a proper [ __ ] but I
mean, at least I got something for the
money I spent. At least she made you pay
for the meal and give you a body,
but she's an evil, nasty bastard at the same time.
No, this one wasn't making me pay for
stuff. I just wanted to because I
thought they were sexy in it and I
thought I might as well in it to try and make
a good impression. They they were happy
to buy their own stuff, but I just said
I I'll pay for it. Basically, I spent
£100 in a [ __ ] ball. What the [ __ ]
Maybe I did get a feel. Maybe I never 25
and I'm 27.
Somebody said, "Why don't you eat women
out, Grezy?" I said, "Because they're smelly."
Cuz their vaginas are smelly.
Greasy. Because they are smelly. That's why.
Are you going to be alone forever? We're
all going to be alone together. Me,
Grezy, Cherry. But at least we got
Stitch and Scooby-Doo. Eh,
[ __ ] off. I'm not eating out your smelly bitty.
I'm not eating out your [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] that. Yeah.
Hey, Stitch. I'm sick of these women
wasting my time.
Look, look who it is. It's Stitch Grezy.
Look, it's little Stitch. Yeah, [ __ ] [ __ ] Yep.
Stitch. Why do you think women go on dates?
Surgeon legs could never get a date like
that. He could never get a date like
that, mate. [ __ ] no, mate.
[ __ ] no. Uh, that's why he targets the
[ __ ] vulnerable boat.
Really stitch. So what? They're not
going to give you the puni.
What the [ __ ] do you have to do to get
somebody interested in this [ __ ]
country, Stitch? What have you got to do
to get someone interested in this country? Eh
What should I eat today? Grievous. I'm
thinking KFC and Ben & Jerry's.
What are you thinking?
I just want to have a day break today. A
day in bed.
Baby, I'm not eating. No cut out. Are you mad?
USA is he wanted me to eat out. No way.
Yeah, I'm going to get KFC and better Jerry's.
Yep. Remember, Grezy, I felt something
in my Todd.
I felt something in my to Grezy. Uh,
so what do you think will happen if I go
out approaching on Saturday in the bars and clubs?
one at a 100.
mate. More like one in a [ __ ] million.
Yeah, you might get that one in a 100
chance. It's not It's not one in a 100.
It's about one in a million.
No, it's not one in 50. It's not one in
50. It's not one in 50 at all
because I'm trying to think about how
many people No, it's not one in 50.
No, no, it's not one 50. When I go out,
I must do about 25 30 approaches, I'm guessing. So,
no, it's not one in 50. And it's got
it's gotten harder as well. It's about
one in a million. That's about one in a
It's not one in 50. And it's not one in 100.
I don't think I've kissed I might have
kissed two people this whole year. Well,
I know there was somebody from Scotland,
but no, it's not it's not one in 50.
It's not one in 100 either. about one in
probably realistically it's probably
about one in 10,000 [Music]
You had I've had 50 to 100 dates since.
Bro, are you a [ __ ]
It wasn't 3 years ago. It was two years
ago. I've had 50 to 100 dates since.
Bro, you [ __ ]
I've never had 50 dates in my whole
life. What the [ __ ] are you talking
about? 50 dates since two years ago.
You're a [ __ ] I've had literally four
dates this whole year. And we are in
we are in June.
We are in June. So January, February,
February, March, April, May, June.
That's 6 months of almost going out every week.
So, uh, yeah. Think it's about one in a
million. And then the dates that don't
go anywhere. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. It's impossible.
It's almost impossible in this country. Yeah.
Start all over again.
Well, then you don't hear from me again.
Is it? It is what it is. Yeah.
Yep. Not this week. Last week.