Oh, sorry, man. I was too tired yesterday. Yeah,
I just did my little weekly um check,
you know, just to see if it's the same people.
You know what I mean? Always doing it
just to see if it's safe. But you know I
I can take a day of YouTube see but
these people can't they have
their life maybe
it's their food and life It's gorgeous
today. It's lacking. Yeah.
Yeah. Just checking to see if it's the
same people every day.
You know, mate, you're still on YouTube. No budget.
Still on YouTube, are you
[ __ ] woke up the whole neighborhood?
I mean, I've just come on to see if it's
the same people. Obviously, I wasn't on
YouTube for 3 days. I' been busy. Some
people got a life, you know. I didn't
know you was still in YouTube,
you know. Yeah.
Didn't know you were still on YouTube, mate.
I don't cover much anymore.
It's the same [ __ ] every day. They people
I thought we see.
I just put a watch on.
Just put a nice wash on.
Go in. Put the clothes out on the line.
Have a shower. Come back. Lovely day.
What was your uncle? Oh,
I got some bad things to say about,
you know, I love It's saying that this
is such a um thick and twisted community
because I'd love to say everything but I
can't get too many glasses on here and
[ __ ] you know, and that's why I don't
like I don't share my life on here anymore glasses
dirty little grass like them little
keyboard warriors that don't show their
family faces. That's why they ruin it
because I can't share everything. Son,
anybody need glasses? Uh,
I can share that little thing. You know,
it's a shame though because otherwise
people can say where they're going, when
and stuff. Probably even give their
[ __ ] address to be honest. But on
this place, the little jealous grasses. So um
I left my [ __ ] keys at the escort's
house the other day all the way in
[ __ ] Wembley. I ain't stopped the
past couple of days, man. But good. Told
you I would be out this this week. I
will be going out Wednesday. My friends,
so I get Wednesday. It's going to be a
nice day. We'll go out drinking.
I do have
I told you I stick to my guns and when I
say something I mean it bro
I'd love to share more things but
fortunately I can't
these escorts are going [ __ ] bad mate
Let me see if he wants to come around today.
That Muslim woman randomly messaged me.
It's so weird.
I know she's a troll.
He's been [ __ ] stable
[ __ ] mentally [ __ ] unstable. [ __ ] parents
if you ask me. Yeah,
I was where I met my mommy yesterday.
Cactus Joe. Was it Cactus? Cactus Jack.
I was wearing my mama. Our bless
these jealous glasses. What do you think?
These little jees.
It's a shame though cuz we could have
like good combos and stuff.
Good workout today. My arms are getting
big as well, but
slack on the gym.
I don't know how people can be on the
YouTube every day.
You're not going to get this color arm
by [ __ ] staying in like you [ __ ]
Are you [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] paratants if you ask me? [ __ ] paradox.
I need a shower, but there's no point be
showering before going to the gym. So yeah, you might see
[ __ ] is such a [ __ ] I to call her a
[ __ ] 20y old. She's such a
Who the [ __ ] do these people [ __ ]
think they are?
I hate her, bro. I'm going to I think
I'm actually going to block her, bro.
You can't stand it, bro. I'm doing these
things to get away from these westernized [ __ ]
and I'm having to [ __ ] deal with
them. What the [ __ ]
I'm doing things to get away from these
[ __ ] westernized guns. I can't stand
them. And [ __ ] look what you just turned into.
I [ __ ] can't stand him. She's turning
into a [ __ ]
You wouldn't like She wasn't like this last year
now. She's just a proper [ __ ]
I'm so autistic, bro. One second. Hold
up. Let me Let me end this live stream.
Yeah, I just told her about herself, you know. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye now. Sorry I don't talk to [ __ ] So,
okay. Listen, stop calling me. Bro, I
swear if you call me mate one more time.
I'm not sure, bro. I'm going to go this
bitch's door. I swear she's winding me
up. I swear to God.
talk to him and [ __ ] off and stop
[ __ ] messaging me before I come on
your [ __ ] mommy's door. You're
winding me up now, bro. I swear to God.
Stop texting me and [ __ ] off. You know
what I'm saying? Cuz I'm going to come
on your [ __ ] door if you don't leave
me alone, bro.
that would have most in this [ __ ] Yeah.
where I'm going to go this bitch's door.
She winds me up again.
Going to give her one chance. If she
messages me again, I'm going to come on
your mom's door, bro. [ __ ] winding me up.
This [ __ ] 19year-old is pissing me off.
I'm going to write now. I said, "Listen,
by the way, it's Pday. You unblock me.
If you unblock me
and message me one more time, I will cly
be going on your mom's door. I will personally
your mom's door now. Leave me alone.
Stupid [ __ ] Yeah, I just texted her
that. I said, "If she doesn't if she
does this whole thing again, I'm
blocking. Block it." And basically one
more time, I'm going to go on her mom's
I don't give a [ __ ] bro. I was out all
day yesterday. I don't give a [ __ ] So,
you better hope you got brothers on and
and [ __ ] bro. You're winding me the
[ __ ] up. Leave me the [ __ ] alone.
[ __ ] can't stand this [ __ ] bro. I
swear to God.
I hate her. I actually hate her. And you
know what? She was actually all right.
That's a year ago. Now, she's just a
complete Leave me alone and stop [ __ ]
messaging me, bro. You want to talk
about me, talk about you, bro. You're
the one with mental issues. You're the
one that's blocking and unblocking
people and they don't even like you,
bro. What the [ __ ] man? People trying
to get on with their life and you're
doing all this [ __ ] madness and when
someone tells you something you don't
like, oh, you you run away again. [ __ ] off, man.
[ __ ] had a good day yesterday as
well. You know what I'm saying?
You don't have money. That's your
problem, bro. If you find your voice,
that's your problem, bro. It's not my
problem. Go to the [ __ ] work that
other people [ __ ] do. Leave leave the [ __ ] alone.
Trying to get all smart on WhatsApp,
bro. I told her about herself. What the
[ __ ] I'm not your ATM, bro. You know
what I mean? [ __ ] off.
For start, it all starts at a young age.
Well, no, sorry. They're okay at a young
age. 18, 19. They're a bit more like I
wouldn't like to use the word gull
gullible, but they're more sort of not
even that necessarily naive as well, but
they don't know as much. And when they
start getting to like 20, they just turn
into all the same [ __ ] I have to see
[ __ ] all the time. I'm in London every
day. I have to see [ __ ] everywhere. All
the time. Same dick ass.
What the [ __ ] I told her if you unblock
me and you message me again, I'm going
on your mom's door, bro. I don't care.
Leave me alone, bro. Start your [ __ ]
again with me on your phone and see what
happens. I'll come your [ __ ] door,
bro. I swear.
She's a strange. I was like, you're a
bum, bro. You don't even work. How do
you have no money? You don't even
[ __ ] work. It doesn't matter if you
work. You ain't got money, bro.
You're a broadcast [ __ ] and you're
messaging my phone. [ __ ] off, bro.
Hello, mate. Chill out. I'm not your mate, bro. Yeah.
When they can't get what they want, they
start [ __ ] doing madness. You've
already called the police. Call the
police on [ __ ] what, man?
Yeah. You can call the police as much as
you want, bro. Yeah. Tell the police. I
said, "If you don't leave me alone, I'm
going to come on your door." Yeah. If
you don't leave me alone, I'm going to
come on your door. Simple.
You know what I'm saying?
If you do not leave me alone, I will be
coming on your door. Leave me alone.
Yeah. I didn't say that. What the [ __ ]
man? You know,
the only one that's autistic is you. The
only one that's a broke ass [ __ ] is
you. No one else. You know,
good bro. [ __ ] off, man. You weirdo.
Stop messaging me, you [ __ ] creepy [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah.
Well, because people won't send you money.
Because people won't send you money.
No, bro. [ __ ] off.
[ __ ] [ __ ] man.
All the same. Gave up with it because
they're all the [ __ ] same. Whether
they're the same now or they turn the
same, they're all the same.
Look at them. What the [ __ ]
We met a lot met a lot of pickage
yesterday as well, bro.
Why is it these guys like these these
like Jack the L kind of ethics guys
always try and give it when they're with
other people, but they never give it
when they're by themselves. When they're
by themselves, they're [ __ ] bro.
They're all weak [ __ ] anyways, but
they when they're by themselves, they
say nada. But then when they're with
other people, they try to get all brave
and had a drink. [ __ ] off, mate. With
your four other [ __ ] behind you.
You know what I mean?
You're talking to five other people.
That's good then. So, stop messaging me.
You're speaking to five other people. If
you're talking to five other people,
then stop messaging me. Simple. Good for you.
So yeah, man. [ __ ] leave me the [ __ ] alone.
Who the [ __ ] do they think they are?
Man, are you mad? [ __ ] [ __ ]
Speaking to five other people. That's
good for you. So, leave me alone. Like,
I don't need you. I don't want you. And
you're [ __ ] messaging me. [ __ ] off,
You know what I'm saying?
Not stupid idiot.
It's a shame. It
see the same [ __ ] everywhere, same
women everywhere with the same attitude
everywhere. It's boring, mate. I don't
think I don't even talk to people
anymore. It's boring. Same people, same
attitude, same NPCs.
And know I'm going to I'm going to bring
this topic up now. Yeah. Again, cuz this
kind of pissed me off today. People say
that all women aren't the same. Never
ever met anyone that weren't want to
come. Literally like sat here saying it
right now. I've never met a good one in
27 years. That speaks volume, man. With
that age range, you know.
Yeah. Well, I have, but they're in their
50s. I mean, does that really count? Not
really. But no, I agree with this [ __ ]
They literally are all literally are all
the same and I don't even care about it
anymore because I don't care, bro. Like,
I'm leaving soon. So, and I don't really
care about that [ __ ] But they they are
literally all the same. Generally are.
And if they're not, it's because they're
18 and they're going to turn the same.
That's the only reason they're not.
They're just [ __ ] Complete [ __ ] [ __ ]