Oh [ __ ]
What a [ __ ] day I've had.
Oh, nice and cozy now.
Oh, [ __ ] me.
What a [ __ ] day I've had.
Have you ever said that?
Have you ever said that before? Like coming home.
What a [ __ ] day, man.
I've said it a lot, bro.
Yeah, I had it, mate. Now I'm tired. I'm sleepy now.
So, you didn't answer me earlier. Why
did um why did my mommy leave me?
You didn't answer me, bro.
You didn't answer me.
I'm [ __ ] busy, mate.
I need to get a haircut.
Yeah, I went to the gym. My muscle was
real nice and hard, which is a good thing.
You already found your Yeah. So, who who
is my mama? Huh?
Who is my mama? here
taking a baby away from his mother. That's mad.
I don't know why I come up with these things. Yeah. Yuck. Yuck.
That's not my mama. Yeah.
The football should be starting soon, is it?
The football should be starting soon. Eh,
it starts in uh August. Yeah, apparently. So,
oh, I feel like if I go to sleep, I'm
not going to wake up. I'm that tired.
I'm so tired, man.
I've done a lot the past couple of days, Gy. Yeah,
I had one up there. favorite saying
mine. Now I'll never know.
No, I'll never know. Yeah.
You know, like we used to, Isabella.
Like we used to
do you like Laney Grezy name Grooy.
Yeah. Sorry you couldn't meet my dad,
but unfortunately my dad's dead, so you
know Laney has to do. Yeah, man.
Laney's good, man. I like Laney.
Now the red's turning brown. Yes,
kind of. Well, tomorrow should be fully brown.
I'm I'm such a pork lover, aren't I?
I'm such a pork lover.
Yeah, this other one does the same
thing. Blocks, unblocks, blocks,
uh, cactus. They're all the [ __ ] same, mate.
They're all the [ __ ] same, lad.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Blocks, unblocks, messages. Oh, bro. I
hate it, man. I really do.
Yeah, they've got mad world. Yeah.
Do you think USA is he had mental illness? Definitely
they are all the same. They definitely
Virgin boy says they're not, but that's
cuz he has no experience obviously
because he's still a virgin. But no,
they definitely are all the same.
No, they definitely are all the same. Definitely.
Definitely they are.
Just like that. USA is he done? That's
mental health as well.
How can you sleep with somebody and then
start making up [ __ ] afterwards?
Practice is mad, isn't it? I know.
I am bro.
I wrote that USA Izzy [ __ ] as well.
Yeah, but she wouldn't give [ __ ] to me
though, would she? Now, she knew she
couldn't [ __ ] with me. So then what do
they do, mate? They play the victim and
then go to the boys in blue. It's always
the same with these [ __ ] And I've
had enough. And I'm not having it. Greavvesy. Yeah.
Yep, that's the one who she was lying.
Do you remember when I was messaging all her friends?
Do you remember that? When I was
messaging all her friends.
It's funny, bro. Yeah, it's funny, man. My finger.
Yeah, it's funny, bro.
I told you I left my [ __ ] keys in
[ __ ] Wembley, man.
Yeah, I was going to call him the other
day, you know, see what the scar was.
But the madest thing with him is he used
to moan about women ghosting, but then
he would do the same thing cuz he
literally done the same thing to me.
That was so weird, bro.
That was really weird. Albanian.
You remember the Albanian, bro?
You remember the good old roulette days?
They weren't good days, bro. They
weren't good days.
Fancy a fishing frenzy session. Boss,
I don't really gamble anymore, man.
Who would you say the worst gambler is?
I'd say definitely Timmy in it.
I was lying in bed, man. I feel a bit
[ __ ] depressed and [ __ ] man.
I was tempted to like play some roulette
and [ __ ] I don't know why.
even out of drinking.
But I'm not doing it. But just happen
sometimes, doesn't it? Yeah.
I don't really I don't really no more, buddy. Remember,
it's just gambling.
It's just gambling. You win some, you lose some.
I stopped because of my mom really the
stress and my mom didn't like it and stuff, so
I just gave up.
What do you think happens when we die?
Where do you think we go when we die?
I think it's just I think it's like just
before we were born.
I keep going past the place I met my mama. Cactus.
The bike keeps taking me to the place I
met my mama. It's [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] weird, bro.
Other guys do it. Yeah, I'm going to I'm
going to I'm going to jump on the table.
Yeah, other guys do it. That's why so
many people going to Thailand now. He
was telling me today people from France, America, Australia.
Yeah. Cuz no one wants to deal with
westernized women, bro.
Nope. They never at all.
I have other ways to make money, but
maybe I'm a shoplifter like Antman.
Yeah, maybe have a shot if they're like that bad.
Nope. Wrong again.
I'm wrong again, buddy.
I'd never say what I do, but you're
wrong there. I can tell you that for sure.
Tell you, bro. But too many too many glasses.
Too many glasses sadly.
But if it was a normal community, I
could tell you and I could even put some
videos up my but too many glasses, bro.
Yeah, I took some videos, bro.
I don't like people know my business in
that way, which I think is fair enough and agreed.
How do you think people get snitched on?
How do you think a lot of drug dealers
get caught? I mean, like I'm using as a
figure of speech or stuff happens
because some people get robbed. It's
because they say too much.
It's because they say too much. Look how
people get robbed and [ __ ] Yeah.
I was going to see Lady today, but I
couldn't be bothered.
I don't want Laney to die. If Laney
dies, then I'm [ __ ]
But hopefully she won't die for like
another 20 years.
25 years maybe.
Imagine that. Both your parents dead.
That's pretty depressing, isn't it?
Yeah, it's pretty depressing, bro.
But some people are um in it. So, yeah.
Rage. Actually, it was actually above
average rage. You don't know how many
hours I've done. So, try again. Bro,
you're sat on YouTube on £300 a month.
Bro, please stop it. You're on YouTube
on £300 a month. And also, you don't
know how many hours I work, [ __ ]
and you don't even know what the minimum
minimum wage is. So, yeah. Try again,
buddy. Bro, it could it could be worse,
bro. I could be you on £300 a month.
Yeah, you asking. Yeah, you asking.
Yeah, you asking, mate. That's why you
talk about people being skinned. You're
an 86k a month. Yeah, maybe in your wet
dreams, bro. Yeah, in your dreams. 86
grand a year doesn't even sound
believable. Shut up, man. You're on
benefits. Shut up, bro. Listen, just
stop it, bro. It's getting boring.
Coming on YouTube, starting [ __ ] you
can't finish, and then losing and then
running away. You're not on no 86 grand
a year. Stop talking about yourself. You
asking. Anyways, bye-bye now. No
repeating on my channel.
There's no point entertaining these
people. Greasy, bro. They've been doing
it for years. They just be a 40year-old
[ __ ] virgin. They ain't got a life,
bro. They're just on [ __ ]
They're just um They're just little
sad little lowlight little virgins on benefits.
There's no point [ __ ] even
entertaining them. Like really, bro, there's no point. Oh,
and you do realize that there's such
thing as a side hustle and then there's
a main job. There's two different
things. It's like selling weed. Say you
sold weed and you made450 a day
that adds up to with all the other money
that you get.
There's a difference between a main job.
Yeah. Bye-bye. You're boring now.
Yeah. And I don't deliver food either.
You don't know what I do. Try again.
Yeah. Uh try again, buddy. You don't
know what I do. and you're not on 86
grand a year because um you probably
don't even live in London. So yeah, and
there's such thing as a main job,
[ __ ] And then there's a side
hustle, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
Just like if somebody wants to sell
weed, but okay. But well, guess what?
We're not on YouTube sat on YouTube all
day skin like you on YouTube cuz that's
why you're hating because if you was
really on 86 grand a year and you have
all these things in life, you wouldn't
be on YouTube hating.
It's the truth, isn't it? This bitter
little 40-year-old virgins ain't got a
life at YouTube. It's been proven many,
many times. No, I haven't called her.
Sat on YouTube skin anxiety ridden ain't
got a life. Sad 40year-olds.
Have you noticed they're all in their
40s as well?
I can make 150 in a day.
Bye-bye, [ __ ] No, it's not. You
don't know what I do. Keep guessing. You
will never know. [ __ ] hell. You made
three accounts, you little low life.
Don't get laid, man. You little bit virgin.
Making accounts to get blocked. But
you're talking about my life. Hey,
listen people. Yeah, this guy's trying
to talk about my life. Yeah.
He's trying to talk about my life, yet
he's just made three accounts to get
blocked. He's made three accounts just
to get blocked, but his life is better
than mine. Yeah. Yeah.
That guy is not 86 grand a year, bro.
Trust me. Three grand a month. Yeah. Say
you get three grand a month. That's more
than probably most people. But this guy
who probably don't live in London is
claiming that he gets all 86 grand a
year in his dreams, mate. I think when
he gets his benefit payment, he gets the
NS mixed up. He gets the NS mixed up.
And you're not going to see no videos
because I don't put I don't put that
[ __ ] on this channel. You know how many
videos I've made the past three. Um,
yeah, I'm almost at the end the past
three days. I'm not putting on this
channel. Too many glasses.
Too many glasses, bro. Yeah, I still
upload on the other channel. I'm not
putting I'm not putting it on this
channel. I don't put anything on this
channel. I just go live on this channel.
So, you won't be seeing no videos and no
nothing. So, yeah.
To be honest with you, I just use this
community as therapy to be fair. Yeah.
Yeah. It's actually it's actually all
right. You know, man, I you know, I
actually use this YouTube for therapy.
Um Yes, I am going. I'm just not putting
videos up. Just like I was cycling
around London two days ago, right? Did I
record that and put it on YouTube? Well,
I recorded it, but did I put it on the
channel? No. I'm not showing you grasses. Nada,
read between the lines, bro.
So, anyways, moving on now. We're not
getting into this [ __ ] like this whole
Boston thing again. So, we're not we're
not talking about this now. If you don't
think I'm going, that's on you, bro. I
know where I'm going. I know what I'm
doing. Simple. Get [ __ ] If you don't
believe it, bro, that's your problem.
Yeah. I made videos yesterday, the day
before that. I'm not putting them up.
Doesn't mean it never happened. Nah,
I'm almost at the end. I'm on the 85th minute.
Anyways, I'm not talking about this no more, bro. Boring.
But yeah, to answer your question, I'm
on 85th mission.
Most of them are easy, but some of them
are quite difficult.
So, these little retards tell you to get
a job, even though they don't have a job themselves.
Nope. Cuz I don't need to show you
little retards anything.
Yep. I'm lying. Okay, bro. Anyways, so
these little retards, right, on YouTube
that on benefits, Joe, right, these
little sad 40year-olds, they tell people
to get a job and then when they think
that you've got a job, it's, "Oh, we
don't believe you." Or, "Oh, you earn
minimum wage." Like, when are these
retards actually going to wake up and
sort their [ __ ] lives out? They've been
doing it for [ __ ] years. Do you know
when something's been going on for
years? Yeah. With these little [ __ ]
spastics on this YouTube, you know, like
years is a long time. They're [ __ ]
proper retards, aren't they? Like
they're proper proper proper retards.
Like they really really are.
It's quite sad to be honest.
Proper retards, man.
That's how those man.
Yeah, the flying ones are
I tell you one that I couldn't get past
yet. My friend had to do it was
um trying to get the guy to land in a [ __ ] truck.
Couldn't do it to save my [ __ ] life,
bro. He kept dying.
But the helicopter one was hard as well,
but I I managed to do it the first time.
You remember the helicopter one where
you've got to get the bandit.
The bandit one, that was a [ __ ] man. And um
most of them are easy, but some of them
are hard, bro. The bandit one was quite hard.
Yeah. Well, what? Okay. Okay. Okay.
Okay. Why don't you people start proving
stuff then? You're only as good as what
you can prove. Okay. Why don't you
people start proving stuff then? Why
don't you people start proving that
you're not overweight, you're not fat,
so you're not overweight, you're not
ugly, and you aren't skin. Okay, why
don't you start proving stuff? You
haters, right, that sit on YouTube all
day self-proing. Why don't you start
proving stuff? The same question goes
back to you. You're only as good as what
you can prove. Yeah, prove me wrong. Why
don't you all come in the Streamyard
right now and show me that you're not
fat, ugly in your 40s and skin. Prove
it. Prove me wrong and you can't do it.
And that's where I always win.
Yep. That one. You know, it was hard to
get No, no, no. It was hard to get him
to land in it.
So, I'm talking generally, bro. You know,
you know what I mean?
Yeah. Anyways, you're banned anyways,
bro. See you later, man. I forgot to ban you earlier. Yeah, man.
These people are [ __ ] [ __ ] man.
They're [ __ ] retards.
So they tell you to get a job. Then when
they think that they've got a job, then
when they think that you've got a job,
they say that you're earning [ __ ]
minimum wage. Also, there's a difference
between a main job and a side hustle,
you [ __ ] [ __ ]
Do you understand?
They're they're like two different things. Like [ __ ] [ __ ] much.
And I actually made a decent amount of
money in three days actually. And I
barely even tried. So this is London,
bro. Not where you [ __ ] live. But yeah.
How much does security get? I don't
think they get that. I don't even think
security get that that much. They get
They get like £13.
They get £13 an hour, I think.
I think they get £13 an hour.
Yeah, they get like £13 an hour security,
which isn't good. Which isn't that good.
Imagine that doing security £13 an hour.
I'm sure it's £13 an hour. Yeah, man.
Yeah. It's weird, is it?
Nah, it's [ __ ] money. It's like £13 an
hour and I wouldn't want to keep seeing
all these women that I can't get.
So, actually, yeah, man.
Yeah, man. Stop talking about yourself.
Yeah, bro. Stop talking about yourself.
I'm having to ban you, bro, for your own
mental health cuz you're talking about
yourself. You sad 40year-old with no
life and no money. Yeah, stop talking
about yourself. Go get banned on the
fifth account, you sad little projector.
But anyways, um there's two reasons.
Because of um
the pay [ __ ] and obviously the the women
and that. So yeah, when Joe says life's
better working, he's talking [ __ ] bro.
Yeah. So that's how much you'd get about
£13 an hour.
With what I do, I can get more than
them. I could actually get more than
them if I really tried. I put the hours in. Yeah,
I could have done 150 yesterday, but it
would have been hard, mate.
It got to the point where I was so tired
I I literally had to stop. So, but yeah.
Yeah, man. Well, I'm just saving a bit
of money and then I'm just going to
never work again. That's my whole That's
my whole um
that's my whole plan because working is [ __ ] bro.
Ignore Joe. He doesn't know what he's
talking about, mate. working is
it just makes your problems worse cuz
all you do is think about [ __ ] women
and [ __ ] So,
but obviously I need extra money cuz I'm
doing stuff. So, I'm I'm
only going to be doing it until I have
enough money. Then I'm never going to
just to get a little comfortable amount
and then I'm just going to learn to live
with what I have because
I'm not [ __ ] worth it, bro. [ __ ] that. Yeah.
Unless you've got your own business,
it's all [ __ ]
I'm doing manual work. He says I'm doing
manual work, bro. You don't know what I'm doing.
All of it is [ __ ] Unless you've got
your own business, bro. Um, it's shy.
And I mean, most people do manual work
anyways, do they not? Yeah, man.
You get my point anyways, dude.
Yeah, bro. I had to deal with these
[ __ ] [ __ ] yesterday. Well, it
wasn't anyone's word, but he was trying
to chat [ __ ] cuz I was riding on the
pavement. And I'm saying like, you're
not going to act big if you was by
yourself. You're only acting big cuz
you're in a group. Typical [ __ ]
That's what they tend to do. These Jack
the lad kind of guys. They like to start
[ __ ] when they're in a group because they're cowards.
Yeah. They like to try and start [ __ ]
when they're in a group. [ __ ] off, you
You get so many [ __ ] in this
country, bro. I can't wait to leave next
week, man. I really can't.
So many [ __ ] Yeah.
So many [ __ ] in this country, man.
Don't know if you notice that.
No, they weren't Irish, bro. They were from England.
Why do these people come on YouTube and
talk about themselves every day though?
I wonder what USA Izzy does for money. Joe,
she probably sells her ass on the street.
She probably sells her ass on the street, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. She probably sells a
Yeah. She avoids me on Facebook, man.
She ain't about that life, man. She's
not about that life.
Yeah, she ain't about that life, man. Nit
about a light, man. No. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye. [ __ ] Don't make another
account to get blocked. Bye-bye now.
No, I think she's still under the same
number cuz when I messaged it on my um
when I got a new phone, it come up.
Then she blocked me straight away. I
hate her, bro. I actually hate her, man.
If I ever see her, I'm going to [ __ ]
slap her across her face.
I will [ __ ] slap her across her face, bro.
I'll have to [ __ ] slap her, buddy.
Do you remember Scott? Um, Cactus.
Do you remember Scott? It's been two years.
Well, she called. Yeah.
Yeah. No way, Jose.
She needs to pay for what she done to Petina Cactus.
Yeah, she needs to pay. Mhm.
[ __ ] [ __ ] man.
Remember when LT was messaging us?
But yeah, working [ __ ] mate.
But I don't think the people in here
actually do work.
She's [ __ ] dead, bro.
Dude, actually [ __ ] man.
She doesn't even look good. I don't know
what the [ __ ] I was thinking when I
approached that, man. What the [ __ ] Imagine, bro.
Could you imagine Asia?
Can you live off a grand a month,
Cactus? I remember when Virgin Boy used
to say, "A grand a month's decent."
A grand a month is decent.
A quiet station.
A grind above is decent for not working. Remember cactus.
A grind above.
Ah, [ __ ] grind them up. F.
I'm skin, bro.
Yep. I'm skin, bro.
When are these people ever going to stop
talking about themselves cactus?
I feel bad for them like coming online
talking about themselves,
calling themselves skin. I feel bad for them.
Their disability gets them confused with
themselves and other people. Yeah.
One had big boobies. Cactus.
a very young age because of it.
Is that funny that Ant-Man makes money from shoplifting? Yeah.
It's too risky though, man.
And if you get caught, you've had it in it. Cactus
[ __ ] shoplifting, man. [ __ ] that.
I can't believe Adman's got like 50
convictions. No, I think it's 20
something. That's the madness, bro.
Imagine going that many times.
Imagine going to court that many times,
bro. [ __ ] that.
That's madness, bro.
There's blood in there.
I need to get my [ __ ] um
keys, bro. I got to go all the way to
[ __ ] Wembley, mate. [ __ ] that for a
game of soldiers.
Cactus. [ __ ] that for a game of soldiers.
But yeah, that guy don't get seven grand
a month. He's a He's a fantasist as well
as a [ __ ]
Not Not even many people in London get
seven grand a month. Not even qualified
people get seven grand a month.
Even most qualified people don't even
get seven grand a month. So
he doesn't get no [ __ ] seven grand a
month. He's full of [ __ ] mate. Complete fantasies. Yeah.
Why do people need to lie on here? I
don't get it. there.
Do you remember the solicitor cactus? Yeah.
Calling in sick because of your bad experiences.
And obviously if you have depression or
something, right? Um
obviously working can make it worse though.
Just somebody I met on a date.
Just another [ __ ] really in a cactus.
Just another one to add to the [ __ ] collection.
Isn't that right, Trip Rage? Just
another one to add to the [ __ ] collection. Yeah.
Yeah, man. I made 90 quid yesterday.
Triple H. Doing some work.
Done some work, bro. grafted for 90 quid.
[ __ ] hard, bro.
Just another one to add to the [ __ ] collection.
These experiences are so depressing, bro.
Can't stay on here, bro. Too many grasses, unfortunately.
But these experiences are really bad, bro.
I think about him all the time, Catus. Actually, yeah.
Do you want my opinion, Triple H?
They're all [ __ ]
I love it, bro. Yeah. [Music]
Oh, you're the link. I've got to listen
to your silly little Jordy accent.
I've got to listen to your silly little northeast accent.
I've given up on life as well, bro. Yeah,
I basically give it up as well, man. What?
Yeah. All right, [ __ ] Yeah, lad.
Oh, your best friend is Fraser.
What's going on with Aunt, man?
Nothing, man. He's in Thailand.
Is he still there? Yeah, he's moved
there now. He's not coming back. Has he
moved over there? Yeah. Is that mad? No.
Some madness, lad. So, what have you
been grafting? What have you been doing
graphing wise? Why have you been up
late? That's what I'm saying, man.
There's too many grasses on here, buddy.
Yeah, but like you don't say like where
you work for like what did you do? Just
a bit of like laboring or something.
Yeah, pretty much.
So, what did you do? Did you gamble 90 quid?
Oh, I don't gamble that much anymore,
bro. What the [ __ ] I don't know. Maybe
like once a month maximum.
Oh, yeah. I don't really I don't really
bother with it much anymore. Me. I don't
know about you.
Um, no. When did I last gamble?
When did I last gamble? Let's teach Bean
your special body. I think I gambled them.
Wait, I think
Did I fly?
No, I never did. No, I thought I never I
don't think I've gone before three weeks
ago. I lost gamble, lad. Did you lose?
Yeah. What? How much? How much? 150.
What the roulette? What was it on?
Club. Oh, in club. Yeah. Yeah, it was
one of um in the machine and like a 500
quid jackpot in the club and
150 lad on a game called Lucky Gems I
think. And cops. Yeah, I lost 250 on net
like two weeks ago.
It's a net only one minute. It's
pointless playing them. Huh? Pointless
gambling. There's only one winner. Yeah, it's us.
We never win, lad. It's [ __ ] man.
Is it? That Tim Eldridge have all turned
on Eldridge, haven't they? That um
I don't even watch him anymore, bro. Be
real. I was being into throwing stand on
him again. I think I just think they're all [ __ ]
Yeah. What do you What do you think? So,
how long how Yeah. How long did you
[ __ ] like What time did you start
working? What time did you finish?
I don't like 7 hours.
Cash is better than [ __ ] all in it, lad.
Yeah. It's anything's better than
nothing, is it, bro? That's it, mate.
That's it. These people like these
people, these people ask, these people
ask is it they don't work. Majority of
the money don't work. They just they
just claim off the um the [ __ ] Nash
or whatever it's called.
Are you still doing the same job? Yeah,
man. So, how much are you racking in a
week? Well, the odds vary. Huh?
What did you say? Can you hear me? Yeah.
Oh, yeah. Um, don't know. I just It
varies. I was I used to get 800 cuz a
week that didn't 640 and 700s and that
just so depends how many hours. What's
the most you got a week? Uh, how much
about 1100 quid on it? 1100.
Really? Honestly, didn't I? You must
have been [ __ ] though. Is it? Well,
you working outside jobs over the long
bar, mate. Yeah, but you must have been
You must have been You must have been
really tired, it I was tired, right? But
I woke up with a notification, 1100
quid, didn't I? Yeah. The best week I've
had, 1100 bar. But how much do you
normally get that normally? Now it
varies, but what's what's the most common?
What is this?
Not really, mate. Between like between
five and a half and seven. No, because I
don't put the hours in now. I only work
like I only put four hours in on a
[ __ ] on a Friday. I only work like I
only work um about 30 hours a week or
something like 31 hours a week away.
Yeah, it's not bad then is it? [ __ ]
good money really for what it is. Like
yeah, it's all right. There's a lot of
dead end jobs out there. But working
[ __ ] in it. You have to admit it is a
[ __ ] Yeah, but you got to work to
[ __ ] you've got to work to um
or you die or you die in it. No, you
don't die, lad.
Yeah, but you will die because how can
you eat then?
You can't eat. No, but you
No burgers. Didn't they used to call me
on the Remember when he had that burger
on the floor page? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Do
you remember is Isabelle Eldridge?
Yeah. I ref that one. Yeah. You had a
girlfriend called Izzy. So they all made
an account, right? They all made fake
accounts. No, that was my girlfriend,
bro. What the [ __ ]
No, she wasn't my girlfriend, mate. You [ __ ] mad.
I've already Hey, Triple H. I already
found mine, mama. [Laughter]
Yeah, these people these people mock me.
This account always this account always
comes in and mocks me, man.
Really? Yeah. He just copies my sayings. I think
Go on. I was going to approach this um
this woman in the shopping mall. Yeah.
But I didn't and I let her walk past. So
I guess I'll never know now. It
just called approaches. He struggles to
get women's son don't you? I guess I
guess I'll never know.
Grey now I'll never know.
Do you get it though? Triple H. Do you
get it? Yeah. Yeah. Cuz Yeah, I know
what you mean. Like
so you doing a bit more graph then? A
bit more like cash and hand work then as
well or not. No. Are you doing a bit of
cash and hand work still? Just if and
when I can be [ __ ] to be honest. Yeah.
No, that's it, lad. Why does that keep
[ __ ] muting and going? Cuz how could
you keep the screen on like No, I'll
never know. So, Triple H, do you get um
Are you into like [ __ ] and [ __ ]
I've just had one. Really? Having a nap?
Have you? Have you actually? All right.
Having a Yeah.
I've got a girlfriend. Yeah. But that
doesn't mean like you have it all the
time just cuz you have a girlfriend.
Like there's some people that don't do
it. There's some people that don't do
it. You know what I mean? I know. I
always get it. Me, mate.
When the mornings and that. No, not
really on the morning, but
quite frequently, lad. Like it wakes you
up and that. Huh? Yeah. Yeah. That sees
Mark's bad on the drink, isn't he? What
do you say? Bad on the drink. He's Yeah,
I think he's got a problem seasideing it.
I don't know. I don't watch him. I I I
have a quick check of um
I have a quick check on him, Mark. like
he um he normally post him on I have
like 5 minutes to scroll through. What's
going on? Yeah, I don't I don't watch
him, bro. But the alcohol is getting to
him. I think lad
he's got a problem in it. Ah, he's a
he's got eyes. He's got an alcohol
problem, but I don't mind actually.
You got a problem in it? No.
Want to go I might have a couple but no
one got a problem. Do you remember Money Mike? I Huh?
Hey, you know what? I'm going to start
calling you now. I'm going to start
calling you captain. Who? Captain.
Why? Cuz it's a funny word, isn't it? Captain,
some guy knocked on my door. He said,
"You're right, Captain." [Laughter]
It's weird though. Have you had any more
trouble to your mom's door? No, I don't.
I don't live there. Oh, no. You don't know then?
No, I don't live there. Me, man. What do
you think of the king of Belfast?
I think he's a [ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
What do you think?
You remember when he came my door before
and that Dan Alitical whatever he's
called messaging me said J got defeated
by the gate. Yeah, they're [ __ ] idiots.
That was a good comment though.
Well, imagine imagine getting killed
over YouTube and at your funeral they'll
say it's over YouTube. Imagine that.
Had some madness, lad. It happens. It
does happen, isn't it? [Music]
Whatever happens, lots of people bully
other people and all on the same website
you can watch Scooby-Doo on. Insane, bro.
Yeah. So, you're still in the Northeast?
You're never going to leave, are you?
No, I'm planning on moving to um Spain
when I win the lottery, lad.
Spain? Why Spain? I don't know. I love
living in Spain, me. Yeah.
Yeah. Would you like Spain? Do
you know my girlfriend's called? Hello?
Yeah. What? Isabelle Paris. Paris comment. No.
See her name is Paris. Yeah. Greavves.
I've seen Grey's comment. Someone got
killed the other week live on YouTube in
America. It's a mad It's funny, isn't
it? It's not funny, mate. It's Yeah, but
how could you get killed over YouTube?
Yeah. What? Someone shot How could you
get killed over YouTube? Someone shot
the self live on Tik Tok as well, apparently.
Yeah, that that app causes that app
causes trouble, don't it? So, you still
haven't for that long legs?
I'm not talking about it, bro.
I I don't think I've got one now. I
haven't even subscribed these [ __ ]
black [ __ ] likes.
Talking about it, bro. It's weird. It's
weird, isn't it? Do you know what the
Sean lad used to do when he used Pete
Pete used to get women and Sean used to
try and message him and that weird?
Yeah, it's weird, bro.
So, why don't you go on holiday and that ever?
I do. We I don't know. We haven't been
in a while, have we? We've just been in
the caravan holiday. We've just been on
a caravan holder to be fair though two weeks ago.
Are you going to go Are you going to go
abroad again? We'll do. Yeah, eventually. But
going to try and get some cash there,
lad. Yeah, it's expensive. It's
expensive, isn't it? Yeah, you got spend
money and you've got your [ __ ] then
your pay. It's good few grand. You need
to go Australia, boy.
You what, lad? I said you need to go
Australia. Oh, too far away now. Yeah,
but you like it there.
You never have to grow up.
You like it there, Triple H. I'm telling
you, bro. Huh?
You never have to grow up.
It's [ __ ] I'd like to work in
Australia. Like, to be honest, huh? I'd
like to work in Australia. Yeah, you get
you don't get much. There's not much
taxes, so you earn some good money. I
know that's it. Like I know I know
that's you don't pay much tax. Yeah, but
it's not that far.
It's 24 hours, lad. Yeah, but
I don't think I got another 24 hours on
a plane, may Huh? Don't think I could do
24 hours on a plane.
You never know until you try.
I it l Yeah. You never know until you
give it a go.
So, have you been on any dates and um
many recent dates like Yeah, I ain't
been going out, man. Drinking to be
fair. I can't be I can't be bothered
with it anymore. I was um I went on the
drink for a full week. Meaning up
really I went on a uh a full like drank
every day for a full week.
And then I lost me job and then I got me
my job back. Really?
I just stick to the beer now. I don't go
on spirits. I just stick to the beer.
I drink star prime, mate. I don't mind
Guinness as well, but I don't really
Yeah, I love I love Guinness. Yeah, I
love Guinness, but what I'm saying is I
can't drink spirits because the
hangovers are too bad the next day.
Yeah, my girlfriend drinks gin and he's
roughing that the next day.
Yeah, bro. is
I could come to the northeast and we
could have a tea party. You could come
over the northeast. I'll meet up with
you, lad. No, you said that last time,
but you didn't come out three times. I
won't go off, man.
I come three times. You didn't come out.
Go. Can I go meet Peter? See, mate, I
went there three times. You didn't come
out. I know, but you you put stuff on
first YouTube and that. [ __ ] Well, I'm
not getting put on YouTube. No, no, no,
no, no, no. You told me to come. I came
and you didn't come out. Oh, no. Lad.
And you tried saying you was in hospital
and [ __ ] man. You're a [ __ ] house, bro.
You're just like Kobe Dan. You're a [ __ ]
house, bro. Yeah, but who's dick rock
hard? Huh? Who's dick rock hard? So, why
didn't you come out anyways?
Well, bro, why didn't you come out? I
don't know. Just you you have that phone
out. [ __ ] up, mate. Huh? You have that
phone out all the time, bro. The excuses
you made were laughable.
They were laughable. Didn't be didn't
buy no [ __ ] come all the way to
London done his lot in the bookies and
then he went out to go home. Yeah. Did
you hear about that? Is this lad job
right Albino mighty called? He went
changing the subject cuz he knows he's
in the wrong.
He went to I'm trying to change the
subject because you know he got house he
went to he went to [ __ ]
he went from Birmingham to London mate
got off the train went the bookies
and got the fo I'm sorry never had the
devil that's a madness it
did you used to watch my travel videos
did I I like no videos I actually mostly
like the co videos mate what what what
what travel ones did you like
do you like the Scotland ones. Yeah,
they were all right, actually. Did you
ever meet my Mr. Jane?
No, he didn't come out. Why didn't he?
He was all right, actually. Mr. J. Yeah,
but he was weird, isn't it? Do you
remember when he said he wanted to spank
me and that? He's weird, isn't it?
Oh, yeah. It was weird, lad. You
remember? You remember, is it?
I said that you and Mr. GD to meet up in
it. Those were the good those were the
easy days with Qu Goodson, is it?
Good on there. I've not seen him about
for ages. Me, man. I think he's [ __ ]
up a he [Music]
remember when you said yeah you used to
lose you used to lose your money in the
bookies and then you'd have to do the
walk of fame
no wor really it's the worst feel in the
world yeah it's horrible
[ __ ] hell bro got paid on the Friday
two hours later done me lot in the
[ __ ] Mark table made me like [ __ ]
depressed that's mad broing vile
horrible I don't do it now like going
bookies now What did your parents used
to say though or your mom whatever
he like and uh and then one day he just
said he lent me some money actually and
then if I do it again I won't get no
help no one gra another bar I turn me
life around lad
the gambling no good for anyone I don't
even I walk past the betting shop and I
don't doesn't entertain me you know the
worst the worst is Timmy man he's the
worst bro yeah Timmy's wild is hem is a wild gambler
Yeah. Do you remember Toaster?
Toaster. Do you know what I watched
every now and again? The Birmingham meet
up. Really? Do you know when they all
met in Birmingham? Toasty and all that.
Well, you're you're in it too deep in it.
I No, I'm not in I'm hardly on me, mate.
All right, Captain.
Why did the Huh?
Why did the fella say that?
Captain Kh. Captain Khan in it. You
remember when you had that fight with
Remember when you had that fight with Dave Tiger?
He's a [ __ ] man. Is he? That was a
madness that like that was a good that
you know. Yeah. Tiger, aren't you, lad?
Yeah. You won the fight. Yeah. You're
always Yeah. You're You're always
thinking where the next drink's coming
from. Is it? No. Are you sure?
No. I drink every weekend, mate. Yeah. I
I I ain't drunk. I didn't drink lot. I
ain't drunk for like two weeks, mate.
I'm having me woman this weekend. Nice.
Hi. Day at night is it? Yeah. Where you
going, man? Um probably like um probably
in Italian somewhere maybe.
Yeah. Nice, man.
Yeah, you should come to London. There's
loads of um good restaurants here.
I will end up going to London in the
end. Like you'll like it. You'll like it
down. You'll like it down here, son.
Dick Rockard fighting on the Mattress.
Yeah, that was a madness that was Trip
H. You'll like it down here, son.
You you like it down here, Sunny Jim?
You from down south, lad? I've been
London. Have you been to London? Have
you? Yeah. Any good?
I've never actually been London to be
honest. Been limp.
I've been everywhere, man. You not been
Liverpool? I have. Have you? Yeah, once.
Yeah, I know you've been to Manchester.
I watch you video and Yeah, I've been
Manchester like 10 times. I've only been
Liverpool once. Liverpool's mint, man.
I'm I want to go Manchester. I don't
want to go. Yeah, but it's quite it's
quite dodgy. Liverpool's quite dodge in
it. It was mad through there. Like it
was off at You know what I mean by
dodge? Dodgy like dodgy.
How do you know what I meant?
The only thing with London Yeah. It's
always it's always chocker. I know what
that means. Troer means ram die.
A lot of people there block.
Why' you ask me if I know what it means,
lad? cuz you might not know what it
meant in it. I don't know, mate. What's
big? He went to Leicester one time and
he got his balls rolled in.
I've never been to Leicester.
I thought you were going to fill that.
Are you filling the Arsenal marking?
Like, does he was he chilled out of it
now? Mate, he doesn't show up. He does
all of this stuff on YouTube for attention, bro.
Yeah, I just ignore him, bro. Everyone,
he does it with L. Do you remember LT?
I know. I've not seen London Taylor
about actually. I don't mind him. I
think he's all right Taylor mate. It's
funny though, isn't it? He's all right.
Taylor, you know, he could have killed.
Yeah, but he could have Yeah, but if I
was in that day, he could have killed me
in it. Yeah, he wouldn't have killed
you. Obviously would. He took your bike
off you, didn't he? It wasn't my No, it
was my bike. It was my bike. My bike.
No. No, bro. There's been some madnesses
on this YouTube like Yeah, but who's
behind a lot of it, do you think? Are
you I don't know, man. Are you on that
Tik Tok? Nah, bro.
Nah, bro. How much you normally spend on
a date night?
A lot of money, huh? A lot of money. How
much do I spend on it? Maybe 200. 400.
How much? 400. 400.
400 lad. 400.
Really? Yeah. We go on the drink like we
go like go down the like we go like in
the main part and that expensive but we
get flat out lad.
You have you don't have a kid do you? All right.
Do you do you actually or is you just lying?
Yeah. Yeah, we don't. We do, mate. Oh, I
thought you was lying, bro. Is it? Why?
I don't know, bro.
Nice two, bro. You have two kids? No,
he's two old, I said. Oh, I thought you
said you had two. You don't have a baby Peter?
Yeah, I have one with you, bro.
With his? Yeah, about that.
Have a baby Peter with Isabelle, lad.
Nah, she's ugly, man.
He's been mad enough. I want I want to
[ __ ] that Jane, bro. Oh, you want to
learn? She's going to make you food
before, weren't you? Yeah. I want her to
give me a [ __ ] Then I can send it to
Mark. He's not with Is he? Yeah.
Oh, let's do it together. Why you doing
that? Yeah. You need
I'm a girl. Hi, bro. You know my friend.
Yeah. You know how I always use the word
[ __ ] Yeah. All right, lad. So, he went
to work. He went to work, bro. And he
said to his supervisor, "Thank you, cunt."
And then and he was like, "What did you
say?" He was like, "Um, he was like,
"Yeah, it was it was slip of the
tongue." It was like a zip of the tongue
in it. And he almost got hiding. Right,
Peter? Jump into
jump into uh box. I'll jump in. We'll
jump in, lad. All right. You first.
Hello. Yeah, I said you first, man.
Yeah. All right, a minute. Right in a
minute. See you, [ __ ]
Thank you, [ __ ]
Thank you, [ __ ] Imagine that. Yeah.
Imagine going to work here and saying to
your supervisor, "Thank you, cunt." Bro, imagine
Thank you, [ __ ]
No, I just can't be bothe.
So, he spends £400 on a date. That's a
madness, bro. On date night. 400 quid.
[ __ ] you now, bro.
The most I ever spent was seven. But um but um
I booked a hotel. So Yeah.
I'm [ __ ] tired, bro. Oh. Thank you.
where I'm going. Yeah.