Just a little welfare check. I might
start then Monday to be fair.
Check. I might start every Monday.
See if it's the same people in Ind.
No, I think I should do it every month. Oh,
nothing better to do. Yeah.
And then have a good old piss up.
Just have a good oldfashioned piss up.
like a black man. Yeah.
[ __ ] I think that's what we should do. And then [ __ ] ducking [ __ ] knuck.
Nothing else to do Monday. Make it out
of it. Get some food then [ __ ] Wednesday.
Send it, bro. Smash them hard, man.
[ __ ] stomach. Huh? Yeah, man.
Oh, there's a stretch, man.
My muscles are getting big. My body is
getting big. My skin is getting tired.
My pockets getting filled. Well, what
more can you like?
You know, when you wear white socks, the
tan comes out more. You know
the time comes out more.
So yeah, time comes out more backside.
But it's literally Monday. There's
nothing else to do. Well, thank
I probably get some sun lotion as well.
It's why milk and [ __ ] My [ __ ]
shit's expired, bro. Yeah. That money today.
It just takes a day to
Yeah. Okay. Let me see it.
Uncle that money boy. Yeah.
So I think going to be the last day.
Maybe again Sunday. Maybe
I'll do it today.
Go gym tomorrow
Wednesday and then go from there again. Oh,
and it goes to show that you can never
have someone telling you what to do.
This doesn't know what he's talking
about. [ __ ] you feel good when you
work. Do your [ __ ] mate. Do your [ __ ] [ __ ] sh
any kind of job, security job, and do it.
No job's good, man. No job's good.
Act driver can do it.
It's [ __ ] bro. You might sit on
benefits your whole life,
you know. You get hobbies.
On benefits your whole life and get some hobbies, man.
I think that's good, you know. Benefits.
and get some hobbies or something.
You know, I could have someone telling
me what to do like
being told what to do.
depend on an innocent one.
Yeah. Yeah. It depends. Obviously, if
you got kids and stuff, it's different.
But I've never ever wanted kids. Like
even from younger, I never ever wanted kids.
I just never and I think you know like
from a young from a very young age
because of it if you want kids but yeah
I'll be grafting today grievously I need
to make some more money
to be honest it's not a bad job so yeah
tomorrow I'll be at the gym or when did
I be at the gym I'll make as much today
and then I'm done [ __ ] hell
you know I'm partly doing this cuz I
want to get the Samson fold And yeah,
even though I get money and I have like
I want to make sure I have more than
enough money so I can get this stamp and fold
when it gets released then
I might end it with like a Chinese restaurant afterwards.
Yeah. And man says that's the only thing
he can't live without, women.
Yeah, pretty much. You can't
Well, you can't live without thinking
about them. Yeah,
that's just the way it is, is it? Man,
for ages. Are you proud of me, Greg? I'm
not drunk for a while.
Look at me, bro. I'm looking good,
aren't I, Grezy? I'm looking quite cool.
You can tell by the detox. I might look
a bit tired from all the work, but
things are good, is it? thinks I'm looking pretty pretty cool.
Yeah, I think I'm look I'm looking pretty cool.
I like it. Do you think I'm looking pretty cool?
Is it from the beard? I think I'm
looking pretty all right.
Yeah, man. I think so. I'm looking nice
and nice and pump. Ready to get the
night on Wednesday. Easy. Uh, what a lovely site.
I think I'm going to have to get on the
spirits this week, man. I think I'm
going to have to get on the spirits.
That means I can't do nothing for like 3
days. Well, probably for like 2, three
I look rest, but I don't feel rest. [ __ ] hell.
[ __ ] nothing, mate.
I want to show you these videos about
enemy like cycling around and [ __ ] bro.
Don't like putting anything on this channel, bro.
I just don't like putting anything on
this channel, guys. as you can probably understand,
you know, but
and the thing is, you know, when people
work and stuff, I have to deal with the
stress from work.
But I don't know, Greg, it's I don't
know what I'm going to do about this
fold, man. It's either like you pay you
pay it on rent um you pay it on contract
and then you got to pay £200 a month.
It's only for a year or you buy outright
for like two grand. I don't really want
to spend two grand on the [ __ ] phone.
So it's sort of like
what do you do man? It's one of them
like what do you do?
I It's only £200 a month for a year, is
it? [ __ ] it up.
Depends how much you love your phones in it. So,
or you can buy outright, but it's a lot
of [ __ ] money in it.
Depends how much it is, man. Like, I can
earn money and [ __ ] now. Maybe if it was
like 1.5 1.6 I could buy it but not I
can't justify two grand
literally can't justify it.
I think I'll just get on [ __ ] um contracts.
Oh but the problem is free as sim free
as [ __ ] man. The provider free is [ __ ] [ __ ]
The provider is actually [ __ ] Free
provider was [ __ ] man. Oh man.
Yeah. What are you about anyways?
Like central London. You can't get signal. So
I think I just have to do the 200 pound a month. Yeah.
So you don't need to worry too much
about these things, do you green? If
they're not on the ground a month,
we're not on the ground a month like a
certain virgin. See, I'm not insecure to
show my to show my face to show my body.
These people are
I've actually been slacking on the gym
even though I went yesterday. Like I'm
slacking a lot, man. Should have went a
few more times, but Right,
man. I need to get a haircut though.
Definitely needs to get a haircut.
Now, if anyone wants to start a fight
with me, Grezy, I can knock him out with one punch.
Greasy. Anyone wants to start a fight
with Peter Belly? One punch.
We get a few long ones. Sorry to make it quick. Oh, I knocked a bit.
My ass is still hurting a bit.
[ __ ] hell, man.
I'm going to eat at the end of the day.
I'm going to go to a restaurant and eat.
Let's try this restaurant
about 11 10 11 [ __ ]
I wanted to see lady today but not
I don't have to have nothing better to
do on Monday. It's [ __ ] Monday, you know.
I really wanted to do it on Sunday, but
I couldn't do it on Sunday, man.
I was I was too [ __ ]
I didn't do it. I wanted to do it Sunday
as much today as I did [ __ ]
I'm sorry. Uh Saturday my
Oh [ __ ] man.
I need to get some key card as well. Oh,
I can give you there are so many grasses
on there green. I can give you some sort of examples
of things like funny things that happen
like you laugh your ass off but too many grasses
going have this coke uh ch have a
breakfast this morning.