I'm just waiting for.
Yeah, I'm waiting for maneuy.
Greasy, greasy, greasy. Greasy. for
going to come on YouTube but show off something
I do it on the grand
um but uh yeah
ties with the GTA 6 the grand six I told
you I was serious about it now you Hey, come on.
coming to speaky.
That's what I like coming on here much people. So easy.
That's it. It g
it like [ __ ] body band. [ __ ] that, bro.
I tell you what, I'm [ __ ] starving.
We need to have some [ __ ] breakfast. Barbecue today.
I need to do an approaching session
again, man. It's been about two [ __ ]
weeks. What the [ __ ]
Don't think I can do it anymore, mate.
I'm not [ __ ] exhausted.
Oh, it's a hot man sportsman. Yeah,
I could have went out so bothered.
Literally can't be [ __ ] A really, bro. So tired.
We can't sit on our [ __ ] scrawny
virgin asses all [ __ ] day like a
certain person. Again, not mentioning
any names. Don't mention names, mate.
Biden citizen. I want to sit on our
[ __ ] lanky ass in all [ __ ] old
virgin lives. I'm saying yeah. Yeah.
I wanted to show Greasy what I bought.
I'll show you Greasy.
Let me try and count this. How many
[ __ ] video I got on here? One sec.
Six, seven days.
Oh, it's not 23. What the [ __ ] One,
two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
Three approaches on that channel.
A lot of approaches
don't be bothered to do anymore to be honest. Oh [ __ ]
hell of the [ __ ]
should have been
told. We're getting ready for GTA 6
early, mate. We're getting ready for GTA 6 early.
That's if the [ __ ] TV doesn't pack up by then.
Yeah, I was having a little show
yesterday. Let me just treat myself to a
nice TV. You know, why not? Nothing
wrong with a nice TV, you know. I just
thought I bought buy myself a nice TV from Arus,
as I like to call it.
Now, I just need to get a PS5 and
she say 6 when it comes out. So, I
wouldn't got an Xbox.
[ __ ] me baby, bro.
About £500. It was about £500.
[ __ ] brackets. Jesus Christ.
And you're telling me you can live off a
[ __ ] grand a month? Yeah. You You're
having a [ __ ] R with me, mate. You're
having a [ __ ] ranking boy by
[ __ ] grand a [ __ ] month.
That's [ __ ] poverty living, mate.
[ __ ] poverty poverty living mate.
That's not enough for Peter Benny's lifestyle, mate.
Could work. Could go right. Can't be [ __ ] So,
I literally can't be asked. Oh, bro.
Be out Thursday. Definitely be out
Something gave me my money yet. Why?
Sorry about that, mate. Ant.
Come on, greeny.
Where are you?
So that little trip cost me probably
over 500 quid honestly
£1,000 a month like a certain virgin
boy. Like even though it is a bit
expensive, it would do, you know,
still need to get a dog. Still need to
get th So we're nowhere near we're
nowhere near there yet.
[ __ ] dogs like 1,00 [ __ ] 200 quid.
That's what happens from a [ __ ] having
you know you know what having a dog is
actually like now
I want a dog I need a PS5 the detects
and the fold that would be a lovely site
that would literally be a lovely site
you can't do on a grand
take you to save up on the a month. And
you might think I'm I'm taking a piss
here or I'm starting problems here, but
but I'm not. Not decent.
[ __ ] yesterday, mate. [ __ ] hell.
Not decent. It's [ __ ] [ __ ]
Show your [ __ ] matey. Yeah,
I'm [ __ ] starving.
Yeah, we're getting slowly but surely
ready for GTA 6.
Only took him 14 [ __ ] years. [ __ ] it up.
Only took them 14 [ __ ] years, mate. years.
I don't know. 14 years. Well, there's a murderous
Yeah, I was hearing about the Lisa thing
with um Monty. I was I was watching it.
[ __ ] It's [ __ ] up, is it?
That is [ __ ] up, man. That's why I
never date anyone from YouTube. I never
meet anyone from YouTube.
I never meet a [ __ ] anyone from woman
from YouTube. He's [ __ ] bad.
Meet him up on YouTube now. Little MTS.
Yeah, I don't even meet him up on
YouTube now, buddies. They're all [ __ ] empty
talking to [ __ ] Star Wars, bro. [ __ ] that. Yeah.
Must be [ __ ] pissed out of his [ __ ] head.
Must be pissed out of his [ __ ] head.
completely missed what I've said.
Some serious growth today.
I really can't be [ __ ]
Really can't be harsh, man.
Did I leave? I never said I'm leaving. I
said I come on here now and then to see
if it's the same people in me.
I never said I left. I come on if and
when I [ __ ] want. Leave. It's the
same old people. And it is always the same people.
I'll be satisfied when I go live and not
one person comes in. Yeah.
And not one person comes in and I'll be
like, "Yeah, they got a life. I'm the skin one."
Yeah. But it would never happen. That's
the whole point of a welfare check. You see? So
that people going to come. People cuz
they're all in Monty's. That's why
that's because they're all in Monty's
Monty's live. If if there's no if there
if there's no one on my live stream,
it's cuz someone else is live all the time, bro.
[ __ ] me, bro.
Yeah, I bought a telly yesterday.
Lost me an arm and a [ __ ] leg. But
we're getting ready for GTA 5.
We are getting ready for GTA 6. Why do I
keep saying five? I mean six. [ __ ]
sake. I keep getting it mixed up, bro.
It's GTA 6, not five, it's six.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Yeah, GTA 6.
Yo, really enough? You haven't gambled
for a while. I fancy to go on the flops
and I don't gamble anymore.
I don't even gamble anymore, bro.
I don't gamble anymore. I don't approach
women anymore. Those are things I don't
do anymore. Good.
It's a good life, man. [Music]
But yeah, it's cuz Monty's live and
there's drama on his channel. These
people will never get off YouTube. It's
their life, man. It's all they have.
They will never they'll never come off
YouTube, man. Maybe 20 years down the line
and I'll still be on YouTube. It's all
they have, mate. That's all they have. YouTube. [ __ ] never.
It's who they [ __ ] have. the out.
They can't get off it. Even for one day,
they can't get off it.
They're skind virgins.
Skind little middle-aged virgins.
It's because little virgins. Oh.
I can't even get off of it. Oh, really?
Can't get off.
Can't get off of it. I mean,
there must be the skin ones in it.
There must be Oh, bro. I want to show
you why I got grievy.
One second, mate.
Yeah, I'm going to go Griggs in a bit. All
right, here we go. Greasy, if this is
not getting ready for GTA 6, bro, early
I literally don't know what is. Yeah, man.
I got this yesterday, bro.
Yep. It's set up. I actually got an
Xbox, but I need to still buy some
things for it. Yeah,
easy. I went for a little stroll
yesterday, man. I thought, you know
what? Why not buy a uh news held packed up?
Do you know what I mean, Grezy?
My other one packed up, so I thought,
let me um spend some dollar now. I've
been working hard and [ __ ] So,
but it's not over yet, Grezy. I've got a TV.
I need to get the PS5, but we don't need
to get that for a long time cuz GTA 6
out. I need to get a French heat like
King and I need to get the Samson fold.
So, I'm still knowing it finished. And
then that's what you will call a lovely site.
And I'm going to try to breed the dog.
And then I'm just going to keep all the
puppies, have them on the bed whilst
playing GTA 6. Yeah,
whilst playing GTA 6.
Yeah, bro. I had to buy the bracket as
well. [ __ ] hell. It was quite
expensive, Grezy. But, you know, we're
not £1,000 a month for me, Grezy. So, we
don't need to worry that much.
I do like today, but that means going
and I can't be bothered.
I'm still waiting for actually pay as well. Yeah, it's good.
[ __ ] I spent about500 on everything
yesterday. [ __ ] hell, man. Yeah,
ladies to be honest.
I went to ladies story there.
Yeah. What I'm saying? The one that my
mom was that packed up.
The one that up
my mom was that packed up. Yeah. They're
trying to say it was a 50 in. But that's
a 55 in. And that's [ __ ] massive.
That's huge. There's no way that was a
50 in. Even though I only buy the TVs
from Argos, it can't be a 50 in because
that's a 55 one and that looks 10 times [ __ ] bigger.
Maybe it's cuz it's a new model and
[ __ ] But yeah,
you know, I don't think it's 4K now,
but it's big enough that it's big. It's
big enough in terms of um
all of that stuff doesn't matter, bro.
It doesn't make a difference when you
use the console. You know that whether
it's 4K, whether it's not 4K, the
console graphics are the console graphics.
Is it a 4K?
Yeah, it is a 4K. Yeah. What the [ __ ]
Wait, so that just went down? This 4K?
Yeah. Wait, what the [ __ ] So, that went
down £50 since yesterday. [ __ ] [ __ ]
That £450 yesterday. I've just looked now
and it's gone down to [ __ ] 400 quid.
Oh, no it isn't. I'm looking at the
wrong one. Sorry. Yeah, it is 4K. Yeah,
I just looked on it. Yeah, it is.
I was thinking the QLED one is £150
more. Should I get that one? But I
thought a TV is a TV in it.
Um, and you know once you're playing GTA
then it's a graphic the graphic the
console graphics are the console
graphics. It doesn't matter what is.
Yeah, it's 4K. Yeah, that's good for a price.
But obviously you get See, my whole
thing is with that £150 I can have a day out
rather than spending it more on TV. So
that one doesn't even look that good.
The other one that's more expensive.
Yeah. So I don't understand how they're
trying to say that one was 50 in when it
looked a lot smaller. And my mom's 55 in
is more than enough it. Yeah. Grezy need
a little Frenchie. The little console
the little puppies. I'd never leave the room. Greavvesy.
Yeah. I saw a Frenchy yesterday. £1,200.
[ __ ] hell, man. There's one [ __ ]
bootify out here.
1200 pound greasy.
1200 [ __ ] quid with little puppy. Oh,
but they're so cute. Little fries in it.
They're so cute.
Yeah. So, Grey, would I be able to fund
this lifestyle on a grand? You need you
need to ask me would I be able to fund
this lifestyle at £1,000 a month.
Do you think I'd be able to
100 grand a month? A man
be a bit uh shocking, wouldn't it? Yeah.
Nah, I don't think so.
Yeah, I think to the grafting today, but
I can't be bothered going to the city
and [ __ ] doing mad hours, bro. I can't bo
I think I should make some money for
Thursday cuz I'm going to go out Thursday.
I'm going to go out Thursday and then
graft Saturday, Sunday cuz I like to
drink during the week and not the weekend.
I think that's a good routine, is it?
You drink on the Thursday
and then you graft on the Saturday,
Sunday. You don't have to, but you know
it's you have extra money in it. So yeah. Yeah. [Music]
I don't like drinking on the weekends.
Too many [ __ ] Music. Too many [ __ ] about
if that makes sense. Too many. Oh.
Oh, I tell you what I had yesterday,
Grezy. I had two bacon and cheese wraps
and they were absolutely beautiful. They
were, you know, Gregs, but you know how
they're normally like cold.
You know how they're normally cold? I
don't like them when they're cold. So,
what I do is um
um I have to wait 20 minutes for them to
make him fresh bacon and cheese wraps.
Oh, they're the [ __ ] dogs, mate.
I had two of them. I gobbled them all up.
I'm [ __ ] hungry now though. I have
the barbecue today as well, Grey. Oh
[ __ ] The barbecue today as well.
We don't want this life to end, Grezy.
We don't want this ongoing life to end.
But if we get put back to a grand a month,
it's going to end. You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, having a nice barbecue today.
Video's coming later
burgers the [ __ ] lot, mate.
I can't be wrong. I need a break.
I need a [ __ ] break, mate. You know,
I ain't stopped.
I ain't [ __ ] stuck, mate. Yeah.
for it. So
simple as that.
Is that right?
I'd love to tell you why I do that and
be able to have some nice conversations
and stuff cuz some of the funny stories
come with working
but too many shitty little on debating whe
too many jealous people on here bro
that's got a light so it's it's the
shame is it merely
I need to sit Now, there's no rest for
me, matey. No rest for me, matey.
Anyways, I'm going I'll be back later.
I'm going to be showing you the barbecue over there.