Oh
no. All right. 6 hours. Cool.
There we go.
Yeah, I've been feeling better for ages.
I just went to get some food. Yeah, I've
been feeling better for ages,
mate. I love how these people think like
me losing 200 pound yet affects me. But
it gave me mood swings, but it doesn't
affect me financially, bro. [ __ ] Like,
oh god, bro. If only these people
knew. If only these little mongos knew.
But they don't know. They'll
never They're [ __ ] retards,
bro. I was just on John West's live
like, "Bro, [ __ ] me. These people have
got no clue, man. It's
funny." Oh man, bro. [ __ ] it up.
Yep. No more gambling for
me. No more gambling. Oh my god. [ __ ]
me. No more, bro. No
more. Trying to go out tomorrow. Send
it. Got to be a send it kind of day
tomorrow just cuz there's nothing else do.
Yeah. Yeah. That
It's not a lot to me, mate. Not a lot to
me. It's not a lot of money to [Music]
me. It's not a lot to me, mate. How much
money do you get a month,
Owen? And then you'll think why it's a lot.
How much money do you get a
month? Why stop at £280? Cuz I was
stupid to even gamble in the first
place. Nah, I'm good, bro. My gambling days are
done. I'm going to go back to the gym or
something. 1,500 a week in your
dreams. Yeah, you get 1,500 a week in
your [ __ ] dreams,
then I don't think so.
I don't think so,
buddy. You don't get $50 a week, do
that. No, you don't do that.
We'll be getting some numbers tomorrow,
bro. Don't you watch that,
[ __ ] Don't you watch that,
[ __ ] Well, at least it's only
280 for a month, isn't it?
Yeah, it's not a lot to lose. If that's
only for like a
month, right? If that's if that's only
for like a month. Yeah.
Then I mean that's not bad,
bro. That's not bad, bro. If it's just
for a month, you know what I'm saying?
No, for a month. It's not
bad. If you lost 280 every month, not
really, bro. I got this passport sorted.
I'm going to go out tomorrow. Send
it. Yeah, I was really confident last week sending
it 4K a month. Lucky
you. Lucky you then. Is
it? No, no, no, no.
And you a lucky f
then stony. Huh?
What are you talking about? Oh, yeah, it
did. The first time Oh, yeah. Yeah. The
first time I bought a Stony, I literally
I can't remember. I think I won some money or
something. Treating myself to um some
Vapor Maxes and a and a bright blue uh
Stone Island jumper. And they put me in
the van saying, "Oh, uh, yeah, we, uh,
we had some burgaries and we need to
check if like the phone's yours and all
of this [ __ ] bro." I was like, "What the fuck?"
Yeah, it was a madness,
bro. That's the first time I bought a
Stony the first day of me wearing it. I
think it's the day I met Morgan,
actually. I think it was the day I met Morgan. Maybe. Don't
know. Yeah, I got four of them, bro. I
got four of them.
Yeah, four of them. Hello, PJ.
I did you watch Did you watch my video?
Yes. You're still being trolled by
Fishing Frenzy. I can see. No, it Do you
know the thing is with gambling, Timmy?
You win some, you lose some. It's just
gambling. Yeah, but you keep playing the
same game, Fishing Frenzy. I've stopped
playing that game, PJ. It's a trolling
game. But Timmy, you win some, you lose
some. It's just gambling.
I I'm up fucking700 pound this week.
Well, over the two weeks, PJ, but I'm
going to I'm going to uh Blackpool the
West Millions tomorrow if you want to
meet me. It's not in the West Midlands.
It's in Lanasher.
It's the same. It's It's the North It's
Northwest. It's Lancasher. You're
trolling me. You know it's Lancasher. I
can tell you. No, I don't know. How
would I know it's Lancasher?
Well, you do now cuz I've just told you.
No, but you're lying. It's in the West
Midlands. Oh, just Google it. It's
Lancaster. You're trolling me. Are you
sure? Yes. I'm absolutely 100% positive
that Blackpool's in Lancaster. So, why
do I think it was the West Midlands
then? Because that's just you, PJ. Well,
Stoke on Trent is the West Midlands. No,
Stoke on Trent is Staffordshire.
Yeah, but it's near the West Midlands.
But it's Staffordshire. It's like one
stop away, isn't it? Right. Can I
explain how the West Midlands and East
Migllins work? Yes. The West Midlands is
Birmingham, Manchester, Liverpool, and
Blackpool. No, you are completely
completely wrong. Do you know what the
West Miglands is? Herfordshire,
Worersha, Staffordshire, and the West
Miglands, East Migllands, um, Leicester, Nottinghamshire, Darbisha,
Staffordshire. I'd say it's more West Miglands.
Edinburgh is the West Midlands.
Edinburgh's in bloody Scotland. Yeah,
but West Midlands is a big county.
I know, but in that county, PJ, there
it's like you look at America, right?
There's certain states. Now, look at the
West Midlands as the same. Right, you've
got Hey, Timmy. I kissed I kissed a
Scottish woman last week. Oh, did you?
Did you get a hard on? Yeah, and I
touched her boobies. [ __ ] LPJ. You
and women, mate, you need to [ __ ] do
you know I wouldn't broadcast that
everywhere. [ __ ] hell. Huh? I
wouldn't broadcast that everywhere, PJ.
Yeah, but it's it was a lovely site to me.
You are desperate, ain't you? I was
playing the deluxe roulette in the
arcade to me. It had 80 quid off me. So
today I'm down 280 [ __ ] quid. Where
the money from, PJ? Cuz even I [ __ ]
ain't got this sort of money to lose
every time. Um, how do I have this kind
of money? I've got my money. Do you pay
any bills, if you don't mind me asking?
That's none of your business. I have So,
you don't So, you're just giving the
answer away. No, you don't pay any
bills. Okay. How much money do you get a
month? PJ, I tell you how much I get a
month. And I'm being dead serious.
Everybody thinks I'm all on fully
benefits. I'm actually selfmp employed
as well, which I ain't going to go into,
right? Okay. Well, how much do you get a
month? Do you want to know how much I
seriously get a week? Yeah, about £500 a
week. There you go, man. That's good
though. How much I had to pay bills, PJ,
out of that £500 a week? How much? 300.
So, I only get left with about two
disposable per week. Some weeks I'm not
even that. No, I've got money coming out
my ass to me. So, you obviously don't
pay any [ __ ] bills or you just don't
want to pay your bills and you're trying
to end up with a bankruptcy like Kayie.
I'm an Uber driver back in the day. I'm
I'm an Uber driver.
You're an Uber driver. You don't even
know how to drive a bike, let alone
[ __ ] a car. Hey, Timmy. This guy on
YouTube before he was saying that he got
40 used to get 40 grand a month. That's
mad, isn't it, mate? There's people on
YouTube like stop and stepping that get
over 60 grand plus a month. PJ. Oh my
god. Yeah, but the thing is stop and
step. No, but the thing is Timmy, I show
losses. Stop and step doesn't do you not
get it. Oh, stop and step it's all a
[ __ ] com that is mate. I watch I
watch his recent video. Yeah, where he
was in London King's Cross. There's no
way the first£100 he put in, he got to
270. It's bollocks, mate. He's pamp six
grand up on fault. He's got a load of
[ __ ] Jimmy, watch my videos. Mine's
Mine's real money, too. And they're
losses. They're real on my channel. I
know. I don't really upload gambling
[ __ ] anymore, PJ. I can't be as I put it
on for a few hours and I take it off.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. But PJ
Wipe, what I'm saying is what I'm saying
is PJ White, at the end of the day,
right, you are being trolled by the same
game, Fishing Frenzy. Do you know what I
do? If I say this is real talk, right,
if I'm 200 pound in one game or sorry,
in on the I don't play the 500s, I only
play the hundreds, right? Because I fath
out the programs a bit, right? So what I
do PJ is I'll try£10 in each game.
Right. Yeah. Now if I do get involved in
one and it's not coming in, what I do is
I change the game. I I go into another
game. I sometimes jack pot that game off
a tenner. Then I go back into that game,
chase out the feature. Time you gambled.
Pardon? When was the last time you
gambled? Yesterday. How much did you
lose? I was at 40 quid. Yeah. But but
but I did spend 70 quid yesterday cuz I
my pubc I got for free in my chip shop.
But I did go home last night and I did
buy some sniffs. So that cost you could
Timmy could you live off a grand a
month? [ __ ] hell. PJ in this check
climate. No, I've just said that. No. No
either. PJ said that. But P but PJ this
is the real reality of it. If you had to
start paying bills, right? your water,
your TV. Well, not I don't pay TV
license. It's a bunch of nonsies. I tell
them to [ __ ] off and they then they
knock the door. But but I don't I don't
pay Timmy. There's no money in the The
thing is there's no money in the
gambling industry anymore. The industry
is [ __ ] PJ, right? PJ, you need to
There was I argued with Timmy, I argued
with one of the bookie workers today.
Yeah. And he said, "I'll come outside
with a pole in that." I said, "Come on
then." I swear to God, Timmy, it it
turned into a madness, bro. Yeah. Should
have should have went live and done it,
PJ. Yeah. I told him, "Come and hit me
with it." And I said, "Go on." I gave
him my address. I said, "After work, why
don't you come in my door then?" He was a Muslim.
Yeah. I said, "Why don't you come to my
address after work then?" Huh? And he
say I'm racist. No, I said he's Musl.
Yeah, but you are racist though. But
that I generally don't like him. PJ,
I've got a good reason not to like him.
PJ, I don't PJ, this is what you don't
understand, right? I don't mind the ones
who come over here and like the British
people associate with the British people
like don't criticize the you know the
western western race the democracy how
England should be right what annoys me
is the ones that come over here want to
take our laws you know change our laws
put severe law you get two years because
you throw a bit of bacon at a moss but
if you piss on a church you get a
[ __ ] smack on the wrist yeah you read
about the bacon yeah you I've read that
was a few years ago But no, it's wrong.
It's wrong. What? If you throw bacon at
a mosque, then you should get the same
prison sentence for pissing on a church.
It's not just a church. It's the same. If
you're Timmy, I'm Muslim.
No. Yeah, you are Muslim, ain't you?
[ __ ] me. Don't tell me you're a [ __ ]
nons. What's one of them on 91y olds?
But you do talk a bit nons PJ. You know
they found Monty's new address. Yes, I
know PJ. We've already [ __ ] and we
found his new Tik Tok. So where does he
live? Lester. He lives at 39 Lime
Street. Where is it? Lester. Lester.
Yeah. Wow. Jaden found it in it. Yep.
Jaden and [ __ ] Westy did mostly
Jaden. Westy and Jaden were Well, I say
Weston and JD did it together. Westy
found it first, but he weren't sure
that. But Jaden put the clues together
and found it.
Yeah. So technically they're both team
effort. I'll just call it a team effort.
But um but the thing is
PJ this is why you get trolled and I'm
going to explain why you get trolled is
because you have come on here in the
past right and you've done some shitty
things to women and stuff like I mean
what I mean and they deserve it as well.
No no no PJ they don't
deserve I've never I've never gone for
an innocent person like PJ. You're
telling me why what you done to that
woman on X was acceptable. What do I do?
Well, you said you were going to rape
her and kill her and burn her. I didn't.
No, I never. That's what it's all over
ex. No, I said I wanted to go out and
hurt a woman. That's what I said to her.
I didn't say I was going to do anything to her.
Right. So, she's put on X that you
threatened to [ __ ] harass her,
[ __ ] threaten to burn her alive and
all this and all that. I didn't say
that, bro. No, I didn't say that. But
PJ, can I ask you a question? Why why on
earth makes you feel the app to speak to
a random woman on social media who you
don't know and say you want they deserve
to get hurt? I don't know, but I was
probably pissed off. But PJ, when you
behave like that, you're going to get I
mean, you are very lucky. Let's be
honest. You are extremely lucky because
other people for what you've done would
have been in prison by now. Oh, they
Yeah, but no one's ever come at the door
either to me. Is that good, PJ? Loads of
people have come to your [ __ ] door.
No, but not recently. No, no, no, but
not off that ex. No, because no one
knows where you [ __ ] live now because you've moved.
Is that funny? Well, no. Yeah, people
used to Yeah, but people used to come at
your door, PJ. I've had people at my
door. I've had it worse than you. But
the difference Yeah, but not over
YouTube. Yes, I have. But the difference
No, because the reason is PJ, I've
scared them off. That's why the
difference, PJ. I've gone out with, you
know, [ __ ] chainsaws and baseball
bats. Don't forget, PJ, where I lived in
Neverco, I had a lot of friends, right?
I knew a lot of people. Don't forget, I
was brought up in Shirley, right? My,
you know, I'm not going to go too much
into it, but a family relative of mine
knew every hard bastard in Shirley. You
would never, Timmy, you would never go
to Blackpool. You would never move to
Blackpool, would it? Why would I want to
move to Blackpool? It's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
hole. You would You would gamble every
day if you lived there. You would be
too. I lived in [ __ ] I lived in
[ __ ] Western Super May. It doesn't
matter where I live. Western Super Mar
[ __ ] you know the seaside. I will
gamble wherever I go PJ. There's no
escape from it. Yeah, but Blackpool's
the worst of it. No, Blackpool would do
me [ __ ] good cuz there's old school
stuff there. I know the [ __ ] empties
and I know how to [ __ ] get the
[ __ ] lighters to [ __ ] open the
[ __ ] machines. Yeah, but you'd be in
Cole Island every day. No, I wouldn't
be. I bit the old school arcade [ __ ]
trying to [ __ ] rob the machines. Rob
mobing the machine. Yeah, but Timmy, you
I know one place you've never been and
that is Middlesbrough. You've never been
there. Uh, you're very wrong, PJ. I had
a family relative who lived in
Middlesborough. I went there [ __ ] I
used to go there about five, seven times
a year. It's a That is a [ __ ] hole. That
is I'll tell you one thing now. The
family relative who I knew who's died
sadly, God bless her soul, right?
um basically had a massive house in
Middlesborough, a threebedroom story
house. Right. How did you How did you
get to Middlesbrough then on the train?
No. The M1.
Yeah, but it's far, isn't it? Padam.
It's far though, isn't it?
Middlesbrough's got some nice parts, PJ.
It's not all the [ __ ] Yeah. You know
what's so mad to me? Yeah. I was walking
down two of the streets and it was
poverty. Listen. Listen. It was um house
after every other house was boarded up.
All of the businesses. Yeah. Was [ __ ]
bust. And then when I walk like 15
minutes up the road, bro, you come into
this estate and all new houses,
everything. Bro, the thing is, PJ, the
whole [ __ ] world's falling apart.
Let's be honest. Co's killed off the
local business, the local supplies.
Middlesbrough is the Middlesborough is
the West Midlands. No, it's not the
[ __ ] West Midlands. It's [ __ ] not
Mercy side. Yorkshire. It's not. Yeah,
it's T-side. It's T No, it's No,
Newcastle's Yeah, it's T-side. It's
T-side. Same [ __ ]
Is it T-side? [ __ ] me. You've got me at
it now. Uh, yeah, but it's the same
[ __ ] Yeah, it's T-side. I think I I
need to check it up. I think it's T-side.
So, where Timmy, where's one place
you've never been then in England that
you want to go? You want to know?
Yeah. Do you want to know the truth?
There's one place in England I've never
been. Yeah. That I really like to go.
Good question. I think I've been
everywhere. Um I've been Hampshire. I've
been Portsmouth. I've been all around
there. I've been Barkshire. I've been
Bratnull. I've been I've been um
Trobridge. I've been devises.
Oh, I've been to Reading. Yeah, it's a
[ __ ] I don't mind reading. It's
average. I've been worse places. PJ, you
haven't been Sheffield. Yes, I have been to Sheffield.
Yeah, it's a small place, isn't it? I've
been to Wam. I've been to [ __ ] I've
been to [ __ ] um what's it called?
Leadeds. I've been to [ __ ] um Doncaster.
Yeah, that's the Yorkshire.
Yeah. So, anyway, PJ, I've been nice
now. Now it's time to get to the Jeremy
Kyle bit. So, why do you feel the need
to do what you do, harassing women?
Funny. Is it cuz no woman wants you?
Yeah, I'm I'm a virgin like you. Yes.
Yes. I knew you was a virgin, PJ.
Everybody on YouTube knows that. Timmy,
how can you call me a virgin when
there's a video of me getting a [ __ ]
Yes, but that's not actually having sex,
PJ. I have no sex, it still means I'm a
virgin. So, even even though I've been
in bed with women and had [ __ ] that
that means I'm a virgin. Yeah. Yes. You
have to put the dick right at the vagina
to make sure you're not a virgin. Oh.
So, so what do you reckon she done after
sucking my dick? Well, I don't think she
shagged you. I think you got too excited
and you couldn't get a [ __ ] hard on.
Yeah. When did you last kiss a woman to me? Yesterday.
Where was she from? I don't know. I just
kissed her and I just went. [Laughter]
PJ, come on. I was a little bit drunk
yesterday, PJ. So, I don't remember
everything. Don't forget PJ. I'm an old
Timmy, do you want to come to London
tomorrow and meet me? No. PJ, we can go
we can go in the pool. PJ, why would I
want to go to London? It's a [ __ ] hole.
Just to have some drinks with me and pay
[ __ ] £15 a point.
Well, we could pre- drink. It's not 15.
It's like £7 90. You go to [ __ ] Diddilly
Street tonight. It's fucking£15 plus.
Yeah, they're not Guinness. PJ, I went
to [ __ ] I was in London the other day
and I was in London Marabo and I went to
the bar right next to that and it was £1150 a
point. No word of a lie. Well, come
tomorrow. Come and meet me. Come and
meet me tomorrow. But it's short notice,
PJ. I can't. Yeah, it's only an hour and
a half away. Come on, bro. I'm scared to
be around you, PJ. Cuz that many people
hate you. I'd only get shot in the
middle of the [ __ ] high street of
London. Oh, don't be silly, Timmy. Come
and come and meet. Nah, there's a
manhunt after you, PJ. We all want you dead.
Timmy, what's better, Leeds or Birmingham? You
dead. No. What's What's better, Timmy? What's better? You dead.