I'm starving, man. I'm going to have
this BBQ in a minute. Oh, man. [ __ ] starving.
Honly day for me today, buddy.
[ __ ] starving. I am mate.
My pleasure, G. I went back to it.
Oh, [ __ ] hell. Not bad. Not good. Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro. I'm starving,
bro. I'm having this barbecue soon, bro.
I'm [ __ ] hungry, lad.
Hope you like the TV, mate.
Hope you like the TV. A certain virgin
could afford that. Could he cut this?
Nah, mate. Not on a grand a month. Not
on a grand a month. I actually done an
approach today at the mall. Actually,
when I went to the butchers,
I don't even need to tell you what she
said cuz you've probably already guessed. Yeah. Boyfriend Yep.
I bought a new TV just for GT. I bought
a TV just for GTA 5 and GTA 6. Boyfriend.
Yeah, I done an approach today, bro.
Grievously at the mall. I didn't even
plan to. I ain't done it for a while,
bro. Cuz I can't be asked with it, man.
Look at me. I was looking sexy as [ __ ]
Nice tan. Looking sexy.
I'm a bit tired now. Same old boyfriend [ __ ]
You can't even get a conversation.
I went up and spoke to her and then when
I asked her, "Oh, what's your name?" as
like a greet. Oh, I got a boyfriend. Wow.
It's a madness, bro.
But I'm going to do it.
I'm looking forward to this barbecue.
Grezy, I am [ __ ] starving, bro. [ __ ] really.
Yep. Can't be friends. It makes it makes
you laugh when people on Reddit say,
"Oh, why don't you get some female
friends? Why don't you make some friends with women?
They really have no clue in it.
It's laughable. They have no life experience
at all, bro. You know what I mean?
Doing a barbecue video.
might do it just for you, man.
Yeah. I can't even be bothered going out
anymore. Me, bro.
Lying that way. I can't even be [ __ ]
It's the same [ __ ] is it?
I'm getting too old for it, man.
It's just the same old [ __ ] is it, Gy? Yeah. Uh,
I'm going in a minute cuz I need to
light this barbecue up. I'm [ __ ]
dying of starvation here. I had KFC
earlier. Well, I had a burger from KFC
I'm really hungry, bro.
[ __ ] hungry as [ __ ] [Music]
got my friends.
I look a good sexy idea as well, but
[ __ ] it up.
Still waiting for my little pavement. We
still waiting for my little payment. How
cute is that?
Spending the dollar on TVs and GTA.
Had to buy a new [ __ ] GTA game as
well cuz I couldn't log into my account.
I'm gone. All