Get up Yes, sir.
[ __ ] guess who I better end up today, bro.
Yeah, she is. Stop being a suck.
I thought I'd go on a Wednesday session.
Stop being a s job. You get know you. Okay.
Yeah. Don't be a s get you nowhere in
life, buddy. Don't get you nowhere.
Won't even get you laid, mate. Don't
even get you laid.
[ __ ] won't even get you [ __ ] laid, son.
We need a chat, bro. Honestly, we need
we need a real chat here.
What you doing to backis,
mate? They're not even trolls. They're
just spastics. You stop calling them
trolls, buddy. They're just self
projected little spastics. They ain't
got a life on YouTube. Trolls ain't
them, bro. Trolls are not them. They
ain't trolls, brother. They're little
spackers. They got no life. No anxiety with them.
Little bit. Little bit, mate. Little
bit. Oh, mate. Hey, listen. What a
[ __ ] day I've had. That I can
actually I can actually say that, bro. Yeah, bro.
They're not even trolls. They're [ __ ]
losers, bro. But seriously, we need we
need a serious chat here.
So, I woke up today. Yeah.
And I went to the gym. So, I woke up at
7 o'clock in the morning
and I thought, you know what, after the
gym session, I always get I always get a
um a milkshake after I go to the gym.
And um I went to the gym, got a
milkshake, I done three approaches in
the morning, mate, somebody gave me the
dirtiest look ever. One ignored me and
one said she had a [ __ ] boyfriend.
Bear in mind, I'm in shape now. I work.
I got my [ __ ] together. don't live with
my mom. And you know what? Yeah, I done
a video on this thinking like this is
actually a [ __ ] madness. Like all of
the excuses these people have been using
over the years. You live with your mom,
you don't work, you're this, you're
that, you this, you're that. And mate,
you can't even get a [ __ ]
conversation out of someone nowadays,
let alone a [ __ ] friendship, let
alone a girlfriend. Like literally, bro,
that's the first thing that literally
come to my to my head. Yeah. So, I
thought, "Oh, [ __ ] What do I do?" So, I
went out. I tried to I I went out to
went to make some money. I literally
couldn't even think straight, bro. It
ruined my whole day. It literally ruined
my whole [ __ ] day. That's how bad
this country is. I can't wait to leave.
Couple of days, bro. I'm out of here.
And I can't wait. It's going to be lush
cuz this country is backwards, bro.
I'm surprised I didn't get [ __ ] run
over today. To be honest with you, man.
This country is backwards. You can't get
nothing in this country. It's [ __ ] All
of it's backwards. The women, the
government, the [ __ ] everything.
UK is [ __ ] Yeah, you are skin. Stop
talking about yourself. Bye-bye now.
Yeah, you are skin. Go get some money
skin. Yeah, that's what I'm talking about yourself.
It's all [ __ ]
Oh no, I've actually got some money here
to be honest. Yeah, I got some bomb
change here actually. There you go, mate.
There you go. That was for an escort,
but I could be [ __ ]
That was for an escort, but yeah, like I
said, I could be [ __ ] So, didn't even
get one. Yeah. So, talk about yourself
for a living, man.
It will shorten your lifespan. Trust me,
it will shorten your [ __ ] lifespan.
Don't talk about yourself for a [ __ ]
living. Oh, where's my car gone, man? [ __ ]
What's popping, Stephen? Well, what a
[ __ ] day I've had. Let me just start
by saying to you, yeah, what a [ __ ]
day I've had.
Like, that's that's literally how I'm
starting it. Yeah. I woke up today
just ordered some McDonald's. I'm
waiting for some McDonald's. Yeah, I
went out to I woke up today. I thought I
need to go to the gym. Not been
get out of the house. I'm not try again,
buddy. So, talk about yourself. Anyways,
I woke up today. I went to a gym cuz I
haven't been for two days.
I let I wanted to do some approaches.
So, I done these approaches near the
gym. Not in the gym, but near the gym,
cuz I didn't see anyone in the gym,
mate. The first person gave me the
dirtiest look ever.
Then the second person ignored me. And
the first per and the third person said
they had a [ __ ] boyfriend. I'm
thinking, [ __ ] bro. Like, it wasn't
pissing me off at this point. It was
like [ __ ] Like, you can't even get a
conversation out of someone. Like, you
literally can't even get a conversation
out of someone. Yeah. Let alone a
friendship. Let alone a [ __ ]
relationship. like [ __ ] what all of
these people on [ __ ] Reddit tell you.
You can't get [ __ ] anything. Um, I
didn't let it bother me that much
because obviously I just saw it as
ignorance. Yeah. So, I went to work.
Well, I tried to go to [ __ ] work and
it was stuck in my head all [ __ ] day.
I'm surprised I didn't get run over and
then all I was getting the same [ __ ] and
it was doing my [ __ ] heading, bro.
I'm surprised I didn't get run over.
Then I done another approach after the
[ __ ] job. Nothing. Then I went out
with my friends. I got three numbers. It
is [ __ ] bro. I swear now. I can't
wait. Four days and counting and I'm out
of here, bro. It's no longer my problem.
And the only maddest thing is it didn't
even piss me off at at the in the
morning. It was more of a like, oh [ __ ]
Like, [ __ ] Like, all of these all of
this [ __ ] that people say is [ __ ]
cuz I work. I'm not fat. I've got a
decent body now. But [ __ ] me, bro. I've
got a decent body now. I'm not fat. I
don't live with my mom. I work. So, it's
all it it it gave me a sense of reality
that this is real life. What you hear on
the internet is not real life. Any
advice that you get on the internet is
not real life. This is real life. This
is here and now. NPCs that can't even
have a conversation. So that
[ __ ] tells me if you can't even
have a conversation with someone, how
would you even get a relationship with
someone? It's like Star Wars [ __ ]
droids. You know what I'm saying? It's a
madness, bro. It's [ __ ] up. Yeah. It
almost ruined my whole day, bro.
Yeah, it literally almost ruined my
whole day. I'm not even joking. And I
went to the barbers, had a haircut, done
some approaches. It's [ __ ] up, bro.
It's so [ __ ] up. I can't wait to go,
bro. Three days on camera, I'm out of here.
Yeah, it's not normal, bro. This is not normal.
It's [ __ ] up. And I was thinking, what
the [ __ ] I've got a decent body.
I [ __ ] work. I don't live with my
[ __ ] mom and I'm still getting these
[ __ ] Star Wars [ __ ] droids.
So yeah, you you got no chance in this
in this country, bro. Like and I drunk
friends. I drunk today. Yeah, cuz I I
was going out with my friend. So yeah,
it's [ __ ] bro. You can't get in this
country. It's a It's a crying shame,
bro. Like you can't even get a
conversation out of someone. That's
[ __ ] worrying, bro.
No, I'm not going to Spain. Why I go to
Spain? It's for the [ __ ] English
people, bro. You mad.
But yeah, bro, it is [ __ ] It is
actually [ __ ] cuz like I've got a
decent body now. I earn money now. I'm
like a normal person now. And what the
[ __ ] bro? You can't even get a
conversation out of someone. [ __ ]
It's actually very worrying, bro. It's
not even funny. It's actually [ __ ]
So, you can't even like the thing is
stupid now. You can't even get a
conversation out of someone nowadays.
The only thing they ever say is they
have a boyfriend. That's literally if
you get a conversation out of someone,
that's the only thing they ever say.
It's [ __ ] mad. You can't go to work
like that, bro. You can't work like
that. You can't go to work and earn
money like that.
It's really bad, bro. No. No. No. No,
no, bro. It's really, really bad.
Like, I almost not was able to work
today because of it. It's that that that
that that that bad. But this is real
life. This is what I'm trying to say.
This is real life. You understand? Not
Reddit, not [ __ ] mongos on the internet.
You understand? It's real life, bro.
It's very real.
I had to go to the other side of London
the other day to get a [ __ ] escort
cuz these escorts around here said, "Oh,
you can't come in my mouth." Bro, if I
can't come in your mouth, I don't want
no [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] cuz I
might as well wank myself. If you can't
come in someone's mouth, you might as
well just masturbate, bro. This country
is so [ __ ] It's all backwards.
I was looking good today as well, but I
go to the gym now and everything.
It's bad, bro. It's actually bad. Like,
I actually work. I actually [ __ ] go
to a gym. Like, I actually do normal
things. I don't gamble no more. And you
you can't even get a conversation out of
someone. It's worrying, bro.
I got free numbers today. But bro, it is
bad trying to get trying to get anything
in this country is impossible, bro.
Like, you've heard it from the you've
heard it from the horse's mouth.
I'm going out again tomorrow.
Send it again. I'm working uh Saturday
and Sunday and I'm gone, bro. Simple.
It's really bad, lad.
No, bro. I don't come on YouTube
anymore. I don't watch the [ __ ] I
actually look good today as well, bro.
Look. Got my hair done, everything. [ __ ]
As a [ __ ] man. Yeah, man. All good.
Well, you go to you go to Philippines
for that, actually.
Where's my McDonald's? Uh uh. Where's my
Mackey's? Oh, it's 4 minutes away.
I'm surprised I didn't get run over
today, bro. I'm not even joking.
I was able to go out and make money
today. I shall never know.
But this is what I'm saying. This is
this is what I'm trying to say to you,
bro. It's like this is not normal.
I I go to the gym. I don't [ __ ] about
YouTube number. And you still get these
NPC women that can't [ __ ] socialize.
It's [ __ ] bro. it
and I'm going to send it tomorrow and
then that's it. I can't do it before
working, bro. You can't work with a head
like that. You can't. You can't, bro.
You know, not when you have to focus on
[ __ ] It doesn't matter what I'm doing,
bro. I'm never going to tell anyone what
I'm doing. They're all snitches on here.
And my body's looking good now as well.
You can't get nothing in this country,
bro. I'm telling you. Unless you've got
a million subscribers on YouTube, you
can't get nothing.
It's bad, bro. It's [ __ ] Like, I done
three approaches today after I finished
the gym. I went to McDonald's. I got a
milkshake, which I do every single time
I come out the gym, bro. I tried talking
to three [ __ ] people.
Yeah, it was that bad, bro. Yeah. And
then I done one
and you can't do nothing about it.
Um, what was the other one of them?
One, did I?
I think I done another one. You can't do
nothing in this country. You can't even
get escorts that will [ __ ] let you
come in their mouth. I had to travel 30
miles the other day to go to an escort I
already knew cuz that's the only one
that would let me come in the mouth. I
want a [ __ ] [ __ ] not to
masturbate myself. If I wanted to come
on you, I would masturbate my [ __ ]
self. It is [ __ ] Right. Six. One sec.
We're getting McDonald's. One second.
Two seconds, bro.
Oh yeah, I forgot to tell you as well.
Yeah, I met an American today. Guess
what her name was? Steven Hwood. Guess
I'm actually decent looking as well,
bro. I look after myself now. Go to the
gym. I'm actually a decent looking guy.
You still can't get nothing in this
country, mate. Right. Listen. Anyways, I
met an American today.
You never guess what her name was. Yeah.
Give you a little clue. Oh, mate. Right.
Her name is Morgan.
Yep. That's what her name was. McDonald's.
[ __ ] moving, man. [ __ ] moving.
What the [ __ ] bro?
[ __ ] country, man.
Not bad, bro. It's got haunted.
But listen, bro, listen. What?
No, it wasn't Chinese. It was someone else.
I also lost my keys there as well. I had
to go all the way.
I had to go all the way to [ __ ]
Wembley just to get my dick stopped. How
mad is that, bro?
It's not about sex, bro. It's not even about sex.
It's anything you want. Friendship,
relationship. You can't even get a
conversation out of someone. It's
worrying, bro. Very, very worrying.
I might do a video on this tomorrow.
This is [ __ ] up, bro. Crazy, bro. But
this country will never change. It will
never ever ever ever change.
Like it's something in their
personality, something there's something
wrong with them, bro. I'm telling you. Um,
this country is impossible today, bro.
Bro, it go start now. Like,
you can't get nothing, bro.
Yeah, but I'm pumping the muscles and
everything, bro. You already know. You
can't get nothing in this country, bro.
You can't get [ __ ] all literally.
Why do you think And's been to Thailand
so many times
and it will start affecting your work.
It will start affecting everything. And
this I knew this would happen as well. I
knew this would happen even before I
started doing this.
You know this will happen. It will
affect your whole mood, your whole work and everything. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm burnt because I've been in the
sun three days straight, bro. Tomorrow, tomorrow, bro.
But yeah, bro,
mood swings and everything. It's bad,
bro. It's really bad. People don't understand, bro.
And you get people on Reddit. Yeah.
telling you that you need to work, bro.
You can't [ __ ] work when you're like
that. You don't understand. You can't
work when you have to deal with these
[ __ ] stuck up [ __ ] Like, they
don't understand, bro. Like, it's
impossible trying to explain this [ __ ] to people, you know?
Like, yeah, you could say it's my fault
for doing it, bro. I didn't expect them
to be [ __ ] ignorant or [ __ ] free
[ __ ] This country will never ever ever change
this [ __ ] bro. Look at me. I'm normal
looking. Yeah, I'm I'm building a decent
body slowly but surely.
You can't get nothing. Nothing, bro. I
go to the gym four times a week. I work,
but ass off. Still get nothing.
Still get nothing, bro.
So, it tells you all you need to know.
Real life is not the internet.
And the mad thing is, yeah, you're not
fat. You're not ugly.
You ain't got [ __ ] face. This [ __ ]
meant blood. Know what I mean? Crazy, bro.
It's [ __ ] [ __ ] crazy, man.
You should have seen what I was wearing today, bro.
Can't even get a relationship. [ __ ]
hell. Let alone a let alone [ __ ]
Right. No, no, no. Let let me rephrase that.
You can't even get a friendship, let
alone a relationship with all them.
You know what I'm saying?
That's the difference. [ __ ] the sex. We
don't care about sex. We're talking
about actual relationships.
I want to do a video about this, bro. No MPCs
and nothing else to say about them.
Boyfriend. Boyfriend. Boyfriend. [ __ ] off.
Nah, it's [ __ ] annoying, bro.
I go to the gym four times a week. I
earn money. Yeah. Don't gamble. Don't
live from above. Try again, man. So,
like, this is what I'm saying. It's so
bad how hard it is to even date in this
country. What the [ __ ] bro?
It's weird, isn't it?
It's so hard, bro, trying to date in this country.
so so [ __ ] hard. It's it's it's a joke.
It's [ __ ] depressing.
I tell you that. It's [ __ ] depressing, mate.
This is one of the reasons I bought the TV,
so I can game before I go Thailand.
Cuz it will never change. Never ever
ever change. never change. Your only
hope is Yeah. is that Yeah.
is that you use escorts or you go to
Thailand. That's Well, even escorts are
not an option anymore unless you find
the right one.
I can give you a [ __ ]
but you can't come in my mouth, which is
not a [ __ ] That is not a [ __ ] Yeah. A [ __ ]
is not where you finish yourself or get finished.
Yeah, this country is it's just
backwards, man. It really really It's
really bad, man.
And I know if LT was watching this, he'd
be so proud of me because I go to the
gym now. I hit the gym.
Do you understand what I'm saying
though, Slim? It's [ __ ] up, man. It's
you can't get anything with a woman in
this country. You can't even get a conversation.
Like not even a single conversation.
They're just not interested in this
country. It's like you laugh at it,
right? We laugh at it cuz we think, "Oh,
it's funny." But it's the truth. It is
honestly the the the the truth.
Otherwise, I wouldn't say the [ __ ] you know? Yeah.
Send it to
make money for two days. Yeah.
It's really bad, Stephen. Man, it's
really, really bad.
This is my first drink in two weeks.
First drink in two weeks.
I went to see Laney um the other day,
Stephen. I like Laney. She's good, man. She's good.
Yeah, I like N. She's good. We had some
good conversations, you know.
Yeah, I had some conversation with N the
other day, man. She's good, man. N is a good one.
Yeah, man. I was having some
I don't know if it was working or what
it was but I was thinking about my I was
actually thinking about my dead dad and
I don't ever think about any dead person
and I started like the past couple of
days I was thinking about my dad and how
did he actually die cuz we don't still
don't know how he died and no I was
getting into like deep depression you
know and this is what I don't know
whether it's the working or the women or
cuz I'm not sleeping properly, but it
just started [ __ ] my [ __ ] head
even though my mom actually brought me
up by herself like it's I was getting
some really um dark thoughts, you know.
So, I went to Laney and we had a little
chat and stuff and yeah, Lane is good, man.
And neighbors don't start anymore. So,
when that stopped, that stopped, you
know. So yeah,
I don't know why it had me thinking,
man. You know,
even though my mom brought me up and stuff like
it just had me thinking, you know,
sometimes it can take 15 years, whatever. But
I just said, don't ever expect me to go
to another funeral again cuz I'm not
doing it. So, doesn't matter who [ __ ]
dies, I'm not going to another one. Simple.
I don't like funerals. I feel wars. I'm
never going to any of that. Yeah,
you're good, man. You're good.
I said to her, "We need to go for a meal again."
I said to her, "Man, we need to go for a
steak meal again." You know,
just to say sorry for this whole YouTube [ __ ] And
I kind of feel sorry for bringing some
trouble in your door and stuff. Anda,
you know what I'm saying? see that we're
just being a good [ __ ] um just being
a good son, you know,
being a good son.
I'm not going to any funeral ever again.
No, [ __ ] that, bro. I'm not doing it.
and that's the thing you got to
understand the same with your mommy. You
know, your mom's not going to live forever.
I remember the other day. Yeah. About a week ago,
she wasn't picking up her phone. I hope
she ain't dead. Then I have no parents
left then. And um
so she wasn't answering her phone. She
was last seen at 2:00 p.m. I was like,
"What the [ __ ] is going on, man? I'm
drinking you're not picking up your
phone." So I went to her like 6:00 in
the morning. I said, "I'm coming to your
yard, man. Like what the fuck?" So yeah,
after the afternoon, you know, it's not fair, man. Yeah.
And you know what? Yeah.
That women's [ __ ] today.
I felt like going and gambling. I don't
gamble anymore. Yeah.
I was in LT's area. [ __ ] I felt
like gambling. I swear to God, I was
about to gamble, bro. I was about to go
into William Hill and play Frankie, but
I never done it. All for the women.
That's the control has over you. You
understand? Like the whole [ __ ] with him. Like,
but I never done it. I was in L's area.
I was doing something. I was like, "Fuck
this. I'm just going to gamble." I never done it.
People don't understand the severity of
this, bro. They really don't with these
women's system. They really, really don't.
You need to go to work with a clear
head. If you ain't got a clear head, you
can't work. Simple. Done.
[ __ ] bad, bro.
It's really bad, though.
And for the past five days, right?
You know, I couldn't even approach. I
was mentally and physically exhausted, bro.
Nah, man. Nah, bro. I was mentally and
physically exhausted. I couldn't even
approach. I approached the first time
day before yesterday. I've got a
boyfriend. First approach. Second. Done.
[ __ ] three approaches in the [ __ ]
morning. Can't even have [ __ ]
conversation out of them. No NPCs.
[ __ ] NPC. [ __ ] women.
[ __ ] [ __ ] Nah.
Nah, it's not funny, bro. You laugh at
it, but it's really, really not funny
cuz it ruined my whole day. Well,
actually, half of my day cuz I couldn't
even work properly. So, it's not funny.
These nuggets are lost. It ain't even funny, bro. NPCs
pure Reddit. I don't go on Reddit, mate.
I don't go on Reddit at all. I've not
been on Reddit for [ __ ] ages.
And you know what, Steven? It's all got
worse. You know what I mean?
Escorts are worse. That [ __ ]
19year-old is a [ __ ] A complete [ __ ]
Like, it just gets worse and worse and
worse and worse and worse. It just gets
bad to worse. So, yeah.
She's a [ __ ] She's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
man. That 19year-old's a [ __ ]
She's a [ __ ] right [ __ ] She is. You
remember her? Um,
long story, bro. Long story. But I need
to go sleep in a bit. But I'm going to
do a video about this tomorrow though,
about this this [ __ ] because this needs
to be addressed.
And I feel like I'm in a position now to
address it. I work. I go to the gym. I
don't live with my mom. So, I mean, what
better person to say it, lad. Never mind.
I can't believe I met another Morgan
today. Steven Howard.
I just wish these women were different,
but they're all the same.
They're all the same.
Do you understand, Super? They're all
the same. I don't care about sex. Bro,
I don't give a [ __ ] if somebody made me
wait too much for sex. I don't give a
[ __ ] I don't have a wank, man.
It's just [ __ ] It's just women every single time.
They're just all NPCs.
You can't even connect with them.
They're all the same. They're literally
all the same. Bro, my my elbow is itchy as [ __ ]
They're all the same, bro. I swear to
God, they're all the [ __ ] same. So, yeah.
I think now, yeah, it is actually
impossible to find someone
back two, three years ago. Yeah, you
could have went on dates. You could have
found someone maybe. But
yeah, they've all got boyfriends, Nick,
or they ignore you. I went out the gym
today. I approached somebody.
Um, she just gave me a dirty look. The
second person ignored me. And the third
person said she had a boyfriend.
Yep. They're all the same, bro. They're
NPCs. And I was saying to Ant-Man, I was
like, "Motherfucker, you can't even get
a conversation out of them. Let alone a
[ __ ] friendship, let alone a [ __ ]
relationship. [ __ ] me." Yeah. You got
more chance of winning the lottery, bro.
Nowadays, yeah, it's impossible, bro.
Two days ago. Yeah. It wasn't in the
gym. It was on the street. It was in the
mall. It wasn't in the gym. I'm never
approaching the gym ever, bro.
To be fair, yeah, Stephen, listen.
I've already gave up.
The only reason I went out drinking
today is cuz my fe
for two weeks.
Why thought I get a bird? Cuz they're
all stuck up [ __ ] That's why, brother.
Cuz they're all stuck up NBC [ __ ]
They're addicted to [ __ ] social
media. That's why.
Nah, don't let it get me down, bro. I
couldn't even work today because of it.
How about don't let it get you down. I
could barely [ __ ] work today because
of it. I'm surprised I didn't [ __ ]
smash myself in front of a [ __ ] car.
I couldn't even focus because of it.
about don't let it get you down. Well,
it's [ __ ] well did for almost half a
day. It's [ __ ] It's annoying. It's
[ __ ] annoying. It's [ __ ] And I
don't even use [ __ ] Reddit anymore.
I don't even use Reddit anymore, bro.
Yeah, you can't help, bro. I'm helping
myself by leaving this country
respectfully, bro. I'm I am I am helping
myself and I'm leaving this country just
like Ant-Man did has and he ain't never
coming back, bro. I'm helping myself.
I'm leaving. You know, it's about time,
bro. It's [ __ ] madness.
So, yeah, that's that's it, Stephen
Howard. And it's definitely got harder
the past 2, three years.
No, what I'm saying is I'm surprised I
didn't [ __ ] smash into a car cuz I
couldn't focus cuz it was in my head all day.
Get a boyfriend. It's [ __ ] annoying,
man. It's [ __ ] [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] annoying. Like, I know we
laugh at it. Yeah,
but it ain't funny. It's [ __ ] annoy.
It's Why it's so [ __ ] annoying,
you know? It's [ __ ] [ __ ] You
ain't got no [ __ ] boyfriend.
But half of these women are [ __ ]
feminists, bro. They hate men.
You know what I'm saying, stupid?
Because listen. Yeah. Half of these
women are feminists. Yeah. They hate
men. They're not in relationships.
Yeah. Look at all these men that
struggle. 90%. But yet they've all got
boyfriends. [ __ ] off.
It's so boring now, bro. Change of
record. I don't drink anymore, bro.
First time in two weeks.
First time in two weeks, bro. I don't
drink no more. I don't even try anymore,
bro. I don't care. Just work. Play GTA. That's it.
Yeah. They're either lesbians or they
hate bed or what something.
Yeah, maybe in the dreams, Ross. Yeah,
bro. You get a sh in your dreams, but
that's about it, bro.
Yeah, it used to be the word for me, bro. And
you got to work and think about it as well.
I was cycling today. Yeah.
in Nester swear right in central London.
This [ __ ] guy's kid. Yeah.
He's like, "Oh,
you should be cycling." I said, "Yes, I
should be. It's not a [ __ ] pavement."
Yeah, it's a [ __ ] park. Furthermore,
you should watch your [ __ ] kid. He
almost ran into a [ __ ] fountain. He
almost He almost ran in my [ __ ] bike.
Yeah. Yeah, he almost ran into my
[ __ ] bike. He almost ran into my
[ __ ] bike. Yeah, if it was a problem
with me cycling in the park, why didn't
you tell me that before your kid almost
[ __ ] ran into me? Yeah, [ __ ]
That's why I said to him, you're full of
[ __ ] as well. That's the other
thing when you go out in the sea, you
got to deal with [ __ ] You know
what I'm saying? Um,
nah, bro. You definitely got Yeah, you
do have We don't have women problems.
You definitely got women problems, bro.
None of you on here get women, bro.
Yeah, you are a virgin. Anyways, you're
bad, buddy. You are a little virgin.
[ __ ] off, bro. You should be watching
your kid. It's nothing to do with where I'm riding.
Yeah, [ __ ] I got to do with [ __ ]
as well. That's another thing. Every
time you got you go work, you got to
deal with these [ __ ] [ __ ] I
hate him, bro. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Proper proper [ __ ] This whole
country is backwards. It's pretty [ __ ]
None of that stuff happens in Thailand,
bro. Telling you. Um,
it's full of [ __ ] this country,
bro. I'm not even talking about women. I
mean, they're just [ __ ]
You open the door for some [ __ ] [ __ ]
No, I wouldn't. That's the answer. They
don't even [ __ ]
don't even say thank you. What the [ __ ]
But yeah, this woman [ __ ] needs to stop, though.
Yeah, you are virgin. Stop talking about yourself.
I know how many times I have to tell
these people, "Stop talking about every day." But yeah,
I like Laney, man. Lane is a legend.
Lane is a [ __ ] legend, man.
But you can't get anyone in this country.
You can't get a woman in this country.
Nah. Not even as a friend.
Not even a [ __ ] friend, mate.
It's It's a shame, bro. Bye-bye.
It's a sad sad sad life, bro. It really really is.
Why is it so hard this country, Bobby?
Tik Tok, Instagram, maybe.
It's a shame you can't get a woman in
your own country.
your own [ __ ] country, bro.
Sad, sad, sad. It really, really is,
bro. It's sad, sad, sad. You know what?
This country makes me depressed. I'm not even joking.
It's like it's so so sad, bro.
This country actually makes me depressed.
That's why I'm getting into gaming
again, bro. When I come back,
it's a shame, bro.
Can't even get a woman as a friend. And
not even not or a relationship. It's so bad, bro.
[ __ ] up, man. Yeah, man.
Some air, man.
And I fight.
Hey, this is stupid. They call me skin up.
They call me Skimp, bro.
Yeah, I can fight if I need to.
Yeah, they call me Skip, bro.
They must be talking about themselves. Oh man,
they must be talking about themselves.
They really must be talking about
themselves every day.
Stephen Alwards, you see these people on
here, they don't bother me. They're just self-reflectors.
They don't bother me, mate.
They literally don't bother me at all.
They just talk about themselves for a
living. That's why we don't pay them no mind, lad.
No, I'm talking about the haters, man.
Roll on Thailand. Roll on Thailand.
Oh, mate. I can't wait, man.
I can't wait. Finally be out of here.
I can't go sleep straight away, man.
We take some McDonald's.
But yeah, you can't find anyone here, bro.
Yeah, I stopped approaching for like a
week, bro. I couldn't do it for like a
week. I was that mentally and physically
exhausted because of it. I couldn't do
it. I literally couldn't do it.
Uh, but I didn't think I was ever going
to be able to do it again. But
there's a point there where you need to
think like, bro, this country ain't
going to work, bro. You know,
um, and then you need to leave it, bro.
Like, you need to allow it, bro. Which
I've already done. This is why I work
now. But like, obviously my friend
wanted to go out, so he really wanted to
go out. So, I thought, [ __ ] it, we'll go
out Wednesday. But you really need to
leave the You need to allow this
country, bro. Really? Like, it's never changing, bro.
Never changing, bro. Never changing.
It's [ __ ] up. It's [ __ ] up, bro.
It's sad, man. It really is sad. The
fact that you can't even get a
conversation out of someone nowadays is
is really worrying,
you know. That is really worrying. And
it tells you a lot as well is that like
if it's really hard to get a
conversation out of someone
and then all they say they got boyfriends even
the only thing they say is they got
boyfriends if they ever do say anything.
It's boring man.
It's so boring. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm just having a little rest now.
Yeah, talking about yourself, mate. No
talking about yourself on my channel, mate.
That's like me promoting suicide.
Yeah, you're talking about yourself, man.
And then obviously you can't even get an
escort nowadays as well
cuz you can't come in their mouth. Apparently,
you can get a [ __ ] Steven Howard,
but you can't come in their mouth.
Yeah, but that's not really a [ __ ]
is it? If you can't come in someone's mouth. Yeah,
it's got really bad, bro. It's all of
it's gone really, really, really bad.
I'll be out here soon. Anyways,
there is point cuz everyone pays for it.
Everybody pays for sex. Everybody does.
Dates, drinks, time. Everybody pays for
it. You know what? Yeah. It makes me
laugh when you get these guys that say,
"Oh, we don't pay for it. We don't pay
for sex. I never pay for sex." But then
they [ __ ] buy drinks and food and
[ __ ] which they're paying before they
get their punani. You know, I've never
understood that. And you know what? I
get it. Some people don't want to pay.
Some people some it it's more an
opinion. Yeah. Some people do it, some
people don't do it. And there's no right
or wrong answer. It's an opinion. But
everybody pays for sex. That is a fact,
mate. Like I I can count in one in one
hand the amount of times I've not paid for it.
But I don't even pay for sex. I'd never
pay for set. I just get [ __ ] I don't [ __ ]
Bro, listen. You You've got blocked on
about seven accounts, you fat loser. Get
blocked on your seven, you [ __ ]
loser. Bye-bye, loser. So, yeah.
yeah, it's [ __ ] up this country, bro.
It's [ __ ] up. It really is [ __ ] up.
It's quite worrying.
No, bro. It's quite worrying, bro. Really is
at train station. Uh Steven Howard completely sober.
It's 12 hours.
[ __ ] [ __ ] is [ __ ] Morgan, man.
I don't give a [ __ ] about sex, man.
I just care about [ __ ] Bye-bye.
It is it's it is sad. It is it's
actually [ __ ] Like I'm actually
trying to like raise awareness
and you got these people there trying to
take the piss. But yeah,
but it it just shows that this is real
life. This is not Reddit. It's not
YouTube. This is real life.
Real life is women pretend they got
boyfriends and they're ignorant.
Not real life is, oh, women care about
confidence. Women care about this. Women
care about that. That's not real life.
This is real life. 7 8:00 in the morning
is real life. You understand?
So, it goes to show like, oh, that's
what it is. They don't care about this [ __ ]
bro. [ __ ] what are we in 19 [ __ ]
80 or some [ __ ]
Bye-bye, mate. Your hand don't count.
You know what I'm saying?
I've got a decent body,
decent looks, got a job, don't live with
my mom, and you you know, you still get
the same [ __ ]
You still get the same [ __ ]
It's madness, isn't it?
It's crazy, bro. It don't even seem real.
Seems like some sort of sick joke.
Bye-bye. Stop talking about yourself.
Stop talking about yourself, man. It's boring.
Nah, it's not funny. It's [ __ ] annoying.
Nah, it's really not funny, mate. It's
[ __ ] annoying. I don't even like it
when it happens to other people.
Nah, it's not funny, bro. It's annoying.
I can't even watch it when it happens to
other people. It's It's not funny, bro. It's annoying.
Nah, nah. No, no. Even when it doesn't
happen to me. I hate it. I hate watching
it. It's annoying.
I hate hearing it. I hate listen hearing
it happen to other people. It's so boring.
I don't even find it funny. I think it's
annoying as [ __ ] It's boring.
I don't even know how you can laugh it.
It's annoying, bro.
90% of men in this country struggle. Yeah. Simple.
Everyone gets it. I've got a boyfriend.
I've got a boyfriend. It is [ __ ]
boring, mate. So boring. It's not funny.
I don't know how you could laugh at it.
Hopefully I ain't got a big hangover
tomorrow, man. [ __ ] hell. I only
drunk beer. I only drunk beer.
Steven Howard on Saturday earn80 £86.
I'm getting too old for this [ __ ] bro.
I grafted, bro. I'm getting too old for this [ __ ]
Yep. And I'm not telling you what I do.
None of your business.
been making I made some money today as well.
Yep. Oh, [ __ ] bro. But like
you can't work with all of this [ __ ]
going on with these women and stuff. But
Antman said that it wouldn't let it
wouldn't bother him and he can work on
No, no, no. But bro, it does bother you.
It does bother you cuz it's depressing.
It's depressing, bro.
Really, really depressing.
Like I know we laugh at it, but it's
depressing. I said to my mom as well,
I'm going to go Willie Hill today and
gamble. I didn't do it, but I felt like
I was driven to do it, but I didn't do
it. I don't gamble anymore. I told you this,
but I was so tempted.
You know, these women drive me to it.
They're [ __ ] so ignorant. Oh my god. So yeah,
I'm so [ __ ] man.
Why is it so hard to get a [ __ ] woman
in your own country?
What the [ __ ]
I'm gonna do a video about this tomorrow.
Like for real, for real I am, bro.
Do you like my TV, Steven Howard?
£450 it cost me.
Yeah. Yeah, I said to my mom yesterday,
I can't work. I can't work. I can't even think straight
cuz of this whole women [ __ ] and the
whole attitude. I can't even I can't
even g I can't even think straight. Like,
I don't know how I didn't get killed
today. I'm I'm surprised
you ain't seen my TV. I'll show you,
man. I bought a TV, man. £450.
Where is it?
Oh, never mind. I bought a 55 in TV.
It's quite big, man. It's actually quite
big. It's nice TV, bro. So yeah,
it sounds I'll show you it. One sec.
What's up, bro?
There you go. That is pretty good to be fair.
Load, load, load.
There you go.
Let's play GTA 6.
No, it's It's a 55 in. It's [ __ ] huge, man.
[ __ ] 32 in. Are you [ __ ] mad, bro?
It's [ __ ] massive.
You mad, bro.
What are you doing to my [ __ ] ass
mate? It is nowhere near [ __ ] 32. The
TV is [ __ ] massive. I thought I buy a
TV cuz my one I'm broke and I'm want to
get ready for GTA 6.
Bro, you already know, man.
What else but Samson, bro? What else but Samson?
Yeah, get a chip fire stick. [ __ ] that,
bro. They're like 70 quid.
Do you remember USA? Is he Steven Howard? Uh,
do you remember
that cute Howard? Oh.
Nah, not me, mate. I don't like her. I
only like her boobs.
I I only like her boobs. Oh [ __ ] Yeah. But
yeah. Hey, I'm going to sleep, bro. I'll
be back tomorrow.