It's [ __ ] pinching it down
[ __ ] again, brother.
It down, man. There's a
We got some arches to be getting.
It's [ __ ] raining. What the [ __ ] as [ __ ] Jesus. [ __ ] hell. There is
still being [ __ ] from yesterday but
ain't going to let that stop me.
I am not going to let that stop me one little bit. Yeah, man.
That's the last day. Oh, today's the
last day, man. So, made counting it. [ __ ] hell. Yeah, man.
Straight to the bar. I just start
drinking straight, man.
Stop drinking the beer, I think. Yeah, man.
Sorry about that. Stop [ __ ] talk about
I was going to do 11 hours tomorrow. Oh [ __ ]
Let me send it really hard [Music] on 60%. Oh man, is massive. Hey, Grezy.
I got three numbers yesterday and I
never replied yet.
Bro, I was in such a bad mood yesterday,
bro. I almost couldn't do the work cuz
of these stuck up women. And on 3:00 in
the morning yesterday after the gym
session, bro, and I thought, "Fuck it. I
didn't even plan to work." Then went to
work and [ __ ] it [ __ ] it just ruined
my whole mind for like two two hours.
Uh, so I'm going out today drinking some
beer. I was out yesterday. I'll do a
live stream for you, Grezy Buddy. her boyfriend.
I'm still I'm disbelie I'm still in
disbelief, Grezy. How [ __ ] up this
country actually is.
How if you can't even get a conversation
out of a woman, how are you expecting
friendship? How are you expecting relationships?
I I don't I'm still in disbelief, bro. Like, really?
Yeah. I mean, Grezy is [ __ ] is it?
I've never heard that before, like you
can have a blowj job, but you can't
finish in someone's mouth. I've never
heard of that. Have you?
until I until I went to these escorts.
So, I've never heard of that.
Never ever heard of it, mate.
I heard of people that don't give
[ __ ] but I've never had someone
say, "Oh, yeah." I I've had people say
they don't swallow. They spit instead of
swallow. But I've never had someone
like straight up just say like they
don't. That just doesn't make sense,
bro. Let me drink some more water. I'm [ __ ]
That's [ __ ] bro.
That's it. Actually, they must be taking a piss.
Didn't come in, but they must be taking a piss, you know.
No, it's not about speaking to random
people or not. It's the whole
It's the whole thing of it. It's the
whole thing of it. It's [ __ ] up. It's
not about whether you speak to random
people or not. It's just all [ __ ] up.
The whole thing is [ __ ] up. You know,
there's only three things you could be
looking for. Friendship, relationship,
or sex. You are not going to be able to
get any of them three if you can't get a
conversation out of someone. It's just
[ __ ] up. Doesn't bother me either. I
got the TV. I got the GTA. That's one of
the reasons I bought that [ __ ] and
started working to get away from away
from this [ __ ] Do you know what I mean, Grezy?
Get away from these westernized women.
up. I said I was going to go out today
and work for two days straight. So, I'm
going to go out again. So,
yeah, it's [ __ ] up, man.
Okay, I feel [ __ ] today, but I'm still
doing it. I don't give a [ __ ]
I don't give a [ __ ] I'm still doing it, mate.
I done it yesterday. I got five numbers,
but two of them were fake, so I got
three numbers. Yeah, I hammered it yesterday, bro.
I done a train station. My friend
thought I was [ __ ] mad.
Yeah. Oh, I had a pizza as well. So,
just had a pizza, drinking some water,
then I'm going to go out [ __ ] send
it. I'm probably just going to do them
drunk today. I can't be bothered to do
them. So, we're on the street. It puts
me in a bad mood. So, probably just do
these ones drunk.
Go back to the old nestles. smash these
hours in tomorrow and Saturday and then
by Sunday I should be in a nice little
nestles playing GTA 5 GZ. Yeah.
Oh, my washing machine's packed up as
well. Yeah. [ __ ]
[ __ ] packed up, mate.
You know what that means? Grezy packed up.
Yeah, not funny, bro.
I met somebody yesterday from America,
Grezy, and they had the same name as USA, Izzy. Yeah,
they had the same [ __ ] as uh
they had the same name as um USA. What the [ __ ]
I can't even be bothered to go out
today, bro. But I'm going to do anyways
cuz I said I was going to do it. Yep.
Never changes in this country will never change.
That's just the way it is. Yep.
It's [ __ ] in it, man.
Trying to date anywhere but Asia. It's
[ __ ] in it.
Hopefully one of them numbers get back.
What the [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. You better you better stay tuned,
Grezy, cuz you're going to hear
you're going to be doing a lot of it tomorrow, bro. boyfriend.
You're going to hear a lot of it, [ __ ]
Don't you worry about that. You're going
to hear they got boyfriend friends. I
know you love that. Is it? Yeah.
I don't know how you can love it. It's [ __ ] boring.
Well, I don't know how you actually love
that. It's so boring, bro.
Boring as [ __ ] Yeah.
It's not even funny. It bors me, bro.
I said to man, what do you think? He
said, "Same [ __ ] it [ __ ] mate."
Yeah, I'll probably do some on the
street to be honest and then maybe just
go straight to the ball.
[ __ ] hell, mate.
I'm all kitted up. Greasy.
All kitted up. Got a nice tracksuit. Got
a nice yellow bag. You need a yellow bag
with you. And yeah, I'll give it a whirl.
Give it a try. Really?
Give it a little try. Give it a little.
[ __ ] me, mate.
Let's add some more to the Let's add
some more to the [ __ ] collection.
Yeah, let's add some more to the [ __ ] [ __ ] collection.
Is that right? Music.
Let's add some more to the [ __ ] collection.
I would have done more than one day a
week, but I was I wasn't by myself yesterday, so
I want to add some more to the [ __ ] collection. It's I thought
and only beer do that to I didn't know
only be could do that to me you know
I didn't know like only be could do that to you really boyfriend.
And all of the numbers I got yesterday,
one was at the train station. Imagine that.
I think right, they're just not
interested in this country cuz of
[ __ ] Tik Tok and people making money
on Tik Tok and
and and and and being independent. I
swear to God, they're just not
interested in this country. Bro, my
question briefly is why do people on the
internet lie? They say once you have
your [ __ ] together, once you don't live
with your mom, once you work, everything
falls into place. No one tells you that.
Oh, they're just not interested in this
country or 99%. Like, no one ever told
me. I don't know if they ever told you
that. They made it seem like, oh, once
you finally speak to women,
everything would change. Like, it's it's
mad how you're lied to your whole life
by these by these people, you know, on
on the internet, bro.
So this Indonesian guy said he wants to meet tonight.
Okay, that's me. [ __ ] it.
If you [ __ ] show me up, [ __ ] I
[ __ ] get you. You understand, [ __ ]
That's what, son?
Yeah, [ __ ] it. Let's have some lols,
mate. Let's meet him. He wants to meet
up. So, [ __ ] it. I said, come with me
today then. You know, simple.
I wanted to do it by myself, but he's
off, so we'll do it together. Well, he
won't be doing it.
You [ __ ] show me up though, Grezy.
I'll [ __ ] do you.
If I can do you, mate,
like a certain person's stepdad done him
right in the throat, mate.
The dog. Yeah, I'm not [ __ ] about.
Don't [ __ ] show me up, mate.
You better not [ __ ] show me up, man.
I'm not [ __ ]
the Indonesian fella. I might go live
with him. Do you remember the Indonesian? [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, I said meet me at
me. Anyways, after today I'll be like
I'm a [ __ ] warrior groovy. Yeah. Oh, mate. [ __ ] me.
Why did it come up? Yeah. Burn.
And it doesn't help. I've got a [ __ ] assache.
I've got a [ __ ] assache. Crazy.
Have you ever had an assache? sake.
It just misses me.
Couldn't have been lady that fast, could it?
I said if I do two and you don't do it,
if I do [ __ ] three, [ __ ] you
don't do it, I'm going to literally cop block you.
I'm going to tell them you're [ __ ]
nons or something.
I'm so cheeky. Grezy.
Oh, sake. Must be nice.
Who the [ __ ]
is sexy? Yes.
You got no chance in this in this country.
Got no chance in this country.
That best be off soon.
Waste of time today, honestly.
What else could you be doing?
I don't I can do tomorrow, but I'll be too [ __ ]
I go out today, which I'm going out
today. I don't think I'll be able to do tomorrow, man.
As in like be so so fast.
Sit down, mate. I can sit down. I need a
[ __ ] sit down. Can
I'm going now. Yeah, I'm actually I'm
ending it and I'm going. So, stay tuned, Greasy.
I'll see you later, bro. I'm going to
come back later.
And I'm going to be like, boyfriend
talking about yourself.
Stop talking about yourself on my channel, buddy.
It's no good for your mental health, but
it's not nice to describe yourself on my
channel, man. My channel is not for you
little 40-year-old projectors.
This is a channel to basically, it's
like a therapy channel, really.
Um, yeah. Stop projecting your [ __ ] life
on my channel, buddy. You thought you
old mess. Um, what happened? Well, would
you like to know what happened?
I went to I went to the gym yesterday
and I've actually got a job and I've
actually got more money than you ever
have. So, you're talking about yourself
again. Anyways, um,
bye-bye. You're talking about yourself.
But um anyways um Joe uh so basically
was rally interrupted there. I went to
the gym yesterday and caught up with you
for a couple of days and then I done
some approaches which I didn't even plan
to do any approaches that specific
moment but I had to go out and meet some
friends. So um I done three approaches.
One ignore one gave me a dirty look, one
ignored me and then the other one then
she had a boyfriend and I was like oh
like it didn't bother me that much at
first. So I was like, "Oh shit." Like,
you can't even get a conversation out of
someone, let alone a friendship, let
alone a relationship, let alone a family
if that's whatever one it is you want.
And it's like, "Oh, this is this is
crazy." And I and I took a step back
think like, you go gym, you work, you
don't live with your mom, even though I
go and visit her sometimes, and you're
still dealing with this [ __ ] which is
deep down I knew that was going to
happen, but like people said, "Oh,
you're negative." No, no, no, no, no,
no. And it's not negative. It's facts
because I'm living it. So then I I
thought, "Oh, let me just go to do this
job now." I didn't even plan to go yesterday.
Then I went to try to start this [ __ ]
job and it was just winding me up for 2
hours, bro. I literally was going to go
and gamble. I didn't gamble. There was a
William I was in LC's area. Yeah. I was
just about to gamble. It was winding me
the [ __ ] up. I swear to God I was going
to go in that William Hill and Gamble
and just do a U-turn and go straight
back home. You know, it ruined almost
the whole day, but I was able to like
get a couple of hours in and then just
went back, got my haircut and then met
with some of these um friends of mine.
So, it's it is really really really bad
that with the whole escort thing as
well. It's bad bad bad. This country is
very sad. It's a depressing it's a
depressing place to be.
It is a depressing place to be cuz I
mean if you can't even get a
conversation out of someone
then I don't think you could even find a
a woman's friend to be honest with you.
They're all NPCs
literally like they're literally NPCs.
Like not [ __ ] no slags, no hoes, none
of that slagging. They're just NPCs,
nonplay characters. And then uh
and then like I've got decent body now.
I've been going through the gym. Well,
decent. Yes, I'm building my body up.
I'm just about to go out and meet a
friend. Well, she's coming in a couple
of hours. Look, man. Looking good. Work
don't even my mom. So, I mean, at the
end of the day, though, it was just all
[ __ ] wasn't it? At the end of the
day, in terms of like getting women, and
then the [ __ ] escort, I still can't
get over the escort thing the other day.
We can give you a [ __ ] but you can't
finish in our mouth. I generally think
they're taking a piss in it. like
they've got to be trolled in it. I've
never had I can't get over this. Sorry
for repeating myself, but I've never had
a woman say, "Yeah, I'll give you a
[ __ ] but you just can't come in my
mouth." I've had people say they don't
swallow it. But I've never had someone
ever say that. Um, yeah, you you you I
could give you a [ __ ] but you can't
cover my mouth. Like, it's either you
suck dick or you don't.
It's a [ __ ] madness, bro. This
country is [ __ ] I'm telling you.
It's really, really, really bad. Uh,
I don't know. Probably tell the security
and probably argue with you. I mean, it is England.
I mean, there's a security there, but I
mean, I've never heard of that. And I
had to travel to the other side of
London to see an escort that I've been
seeing for a couple of months. It's
really, really, really bad, bro. This
country is really bad. I got three
numbers yesterday. None of them's
replied back so far. I got an American
called Morgan. Got one at the train
station in front of everyone. It's so
bad. But even after the work yesterday,
I approached someone. This this ain't
changing, bro. This is one of the
reasons I bought this TV to start like
gaming and that, getting into something.
This is not good, bro. Like, this is
really, really, really not good. It's so
It's so different to what you hear on the internet.
It's so different. Like people never
tell you this [ __ ]
I'm going out today, but I already know
what I'm going to get. It's going to be
the same old.
But um I said I was going to go out
today anyways. So, and I'm working two
days straight. So, I should make some
money. Hopefully get like 300 hopefully.
And that's it. 55 in. Yep.
I know what I'm going to get today. It's
going to be the same [ __ ]
But I've got nothing better to do. So
that's my TV. No. Yeah.
Hopefully make 300 in two or three days.
But yeah, this will never ever change,
Joe. It's not even like it's luck
anymore. It's not even luck. It's just
impossible. Like two years ago, yeah,
you could kind of say, "Oh, yeah, it's
luck." Yeah. But now it is actually
impossible. Like it got so bad I
couldn't even do it for 4 days. I was so
mentally and physically exhausted I
couldn't even do it for 4 days.
I didn't think I'd ever be able to do it
again. It's bad, man. People People make
it seem like dating is so easy and it
ain't [ __ ] easy. Not for most people anyways.
Social media has a lot to answer for.
Especially Tik Tok.
Especially Tik Tok and um Instagram.
It's never changing. You can't even be
positive about it cuz it's been going on
for [ __ ] years. And now by the looks
of it, you can't even use escorts. Cuz I
thought before the only option was is
escorts in Asia. You either go to Asia
or you get escorts. That's the only way.
That's literally the only That's the
only thing I could actually think of.
And it and it plays with your mind as
well. And it [ __ ] up. And it [ __ ] you
up when you're trying to work.
I knew that would have happened before I
even started working. I knew this was
going to happen. You know, it's going to
play on your mind and [ __ ] with your
head. I knew it. I knew it. I knew it.
I knew exactly. I said this a couple of
months ago. This is what's going to
happen as well. I said it. I did say it.
You know, I did [ __ ] say it. It's bad,
you know. And the escorts, [ __ ] it. What the [ __ ]
Even they've got attitude. The
20-year-olds got attitude. These other
women are NPCs.
Nope. And even if I met any women from
work, they would still say they got
boyfriends. Why would it matter if I met
somebody on the street, bar, club,
library, or work? It would still be the
same. They're still NPCs.
They'll still reject you. Doesn't matter
how Doesn't matter how you meet them.
Doesn't matter what you look like.
Doesn't matter how you meet them.
Doesn't matter what you say. They're
just not interested in this country.
Exactly what Antman said. don't like he was right
like that like now talking like people
trying now obviously there's people in
relationships from ages ago or might
have got lucky and met through a [ __ ]
friend but now as in trying as a single
person they are not interested in this
country it's end it's end of story
there's there's no gym this none there's
none of it simp plain and simple simple
as that so that's it which is mad when
you're above average looking and you
work and you by yourself. But hey,
that's just the way it works, isn't it?
I can understand if you look like
somebody like uh from Timmy Aldridge,
then you know your place. You know that
like you got [ __ ] genetics, you're
overweight, you look [ __ ] then you
could kind of be like, "Oh, well, I kind
of know what I'm getting myself in for
here." But when you actually look decent
and you got [ __ ] money and you you're
still getting the same [ __ ] you're
thinking, "What the fuck?" So
you look like Timmy Aldridge or even
that money Mike then it would be
understandable. You would know your
place. You know that you're playing with
fire. You're playing with at your own
risk. But you don't look like any of
them people. There's nothing wrong with
you or 90% of the other people that
struggle. You know, they're just not
interested in this country. And at the
end of the day, you can sit here all day
explaining it to people, explaining it
to people, but they're never going to
understand until they go outside and
they speak to them theirelves. And then
there's no point trying to sit here and
explain it over and over and over again
cuz real life experiences contradict
their advice contradicts your life
experiences. Put it that way. So that's it.
But I know tomorrow I can go and be
like, "Oh, I just worked and shit." So I
won't um I know I tried and [ __ ] so
and I'll be doing it drunk as well. Obviously,
but it will never change, mate. It will
never ever ever change. I basically gave
up to be honest. It's just cuz my
friends wanted to go out yesterday.
But it is very very sad. Very very very
It's the world we live in. Eh,
it's just the world we live in, you know.
Just ignore us. Ignore us. Stuck up
women. It will always be the same in
this country. It will never change. Never Potter.
Never Harry Potter. You can't even get a
conversation out of someone. Their minds
must be [ __ ] due to uh
it's next Wednesday. Yeah.
Um their minds must be [ __ ] due to
social media, is it? They must be And I
think this is where the looks come from.
They're thinking, "Oh, why is this
person approaching me?" because they're
so addicted to Tik Tok and because
they're so addicted to Instagram, they
don't know how to socialize, which is
also good when you do it drunk because
then they can socialize a bit more
better because they're drunk. That's
another reason why it's better when
they're drunk because they can actually
socialize better. And a lot of them,
they're just so nervous. They're just bye-bye [ __ ]
Um yeah, bye-bye you little forey fat
[ __ ] diabetic. Um little anxiety with
him [ __ ] Um, so what I was saying is uh yeah
um I think it's um they don't even have
you know why I exchange my money when I
bring when I bring in my bank card bro
why would I exchange money? What the [ __ ]
What the [ __ ] bro?
I'm using my [ __ ] Revolute card.
What? Anyways, who the [ __ ] transfers
money? What the [ __ ] There's literally
a bank account that there's no fees when
you use it abroad. Anyways,
um what I was saying is their minds must
be so [ __ ] due to social media like
Tik Tok and Instagram, they don't think
it's normal somebody just going up to
them and speaking to them.
You know what I'm saying?
No, obviously you can pay by card, bro.
You're going Thailand. How many tourists
go to [ __ ] Thailand? What the [ __ ]
But this is just what I need to be
honest, mate. You This is no life in
England, bro. It's no life for anyone.
Like, we laugh about it. We joke about
it, but this is no life for anybody in this country.
Like, all all jokes aside, bro, like I'm
surprised I didn't [ __ ] crash
yesterday, bro. I was so out of it
because of these bad experiences. These
stuck up [ __ ] What the [ __ ] bro?
How the [ __ ] are you supposed to work
when you got that in your mind? Are you mad?
And it just gets worse and worse and
worse and worse and worse and worse and
worse and worse. So,
but I've got my TV. I'll make some money
tomorrow anyways. And I'm out anyways.
But Laney better look after the [ __ ]
TV good whilst I'm [ __ ] gone. I'm not
Bro, listen. Like it's really no life in
this country. There really is no life in
this country. It's bad, bro. Really, really bad.
And like I said, if you look like Timmy
Aldridge or someone like that, then
okay, it makes sense.
Then we understand, you know what the
[ __ ] We know where we are, bro. We
know. We know our place in society, bro.
Or even if you look like L J. So
maybe they only take cash. Yeah, maybe
they do bank transfer.
But if I could just use the escorts, I
would just stay here. But you can't use escorts anymore.
I had to travel [ __ ] past Wembley
[ __ ] the other day just to get with
an escort. Like that in itself is
[ __ ] Imagine that you've been working
all day, you just come back and you
literally had to travel out of London.
That was literally out of London I had
to go to. It's not good, bro. It's
really, really, really, really not good.
You know what I'm saying? These women,
it's just excuses, man. Like, oh, you
only want people for sex, bro. I would
legitimately wait one month before
having sex. It's not about sex. You
can't even get anything from them.
Friendship, relationship, nothing. It
doesn't literally nothing.
I [ __ ] date their [ __ ] father. And
it's definitely got harder. The past two
years, I've noticed it's definitely
gotten harder. It definitely has.
Always. England's always been [ __ ] you
know? But in the past two years, there's
definitely been some mad changes, bro.
You know what I'm saying? Cuz you're not
getting chances like you used to now, you know? So
it's either escorts or Asia is the only
way from where I'm in.
So but they offer a service for money
and I don't know why people use them.
Maybe they're busy, maybe they prefer
escorts. Mine was because I was busy and
I didn't want to deal with the whole
dating [ __ ] anymore. Well, regardless of
why you're using them, they are offering
a service for money. It's like selling a
washing machine. It's like selling a
washing machine and somebody coming to
buy the washing machine and be like,
"Nah, I don't like your skin color, so
you can't buy my washing machine." It
doesn't make sense. Do you know what I'm saying?
They're allowed to not give [ __ ] if
they don't want to give [ __ ] and
they just want to get [ __ ] And yeah,
I mean, still bit weird though cuz
you're offering a service for money, but
then you then say that you It's just It
don't make sense.
None of it does. None of it makes sense.
What the [ __ ] It's come. What the [ __ ]
Why are they scared of K?
All right. And it's that it was that
much of a turnoff that I traveled 60
miles round trip. I'd rather do that
rather than [ __ ] finish myself.
Yeah. Stop talking about yourself.
Um Yeah. So, like I'd rather do that
round trip than [ __ ] What is a
[ __ ] where you can't finish? That's
just masturbating yourself.
That's basically you just masturbating yourself,
isn't it? That's you masturbating yourself, really.
Whereabouts in Thailand am I going?
Never you mind where I'm going, bro? The [ __ ]
Are you trying to call police or
something? I'm gone Wednesday anyways,
mate. I It will be your problem when I
leave. I can't believe I can't believe
Ant-Man has been four times and I've
dealt with way more [ __ ] than he has.
Way more [ __ ] than he has and ever will
in this country. Like more than anyone.
Literally, I've probably met more women
than anyone in the world.
Sounds delusional, but it sure feels
that way. Cuz who would have actually
approached people more than me?
I can't imagine it, bro. I really can't imagine it.
Unless they're [ __ ] serial
approaches, so they're just all NPCs.
They're just NPCs, nonplay characters.
That's that's that's the only slagging
you could actually give.
But yeah, it's the ignorance. I can't
deal with the ignorance. I can deal with
when I'm drunk, but which is why I'll be
drunk today, but like normally I can't
deal with that [ __ ] bro. It's [ __ ] boring, man.
boyfriend [ __ ] is boring.
Boring. And you know what's going to be
so mad is when they get to their 30s.
Yeah, this is a [ __ ] up thing, Joe.
When they get to their 30s
or, you know, mid30s, they're going to
be like, "Oh, I can't find someone.
Where's all the good guys gone?"
Literally happens every time in their in
their 30s or 40s. Yeah, man.
There's literally no point even going
out today to be honest. But going to
meet this Indonesian fella
and you get the [ __ ] on it. Yeah.
[ __ ] hell. I'm [ __ ]
Oh my god, my eyes. I was only drinking
beer yesterday as well.
I'm tired, man.
But ain't a problem in it.
But yeah, it just never changed in this country.
What are we going to do? Get numbers.
They don't reply. You know
this in this this Indonesian guy I was
trying to say, "Oh, you're negative.
That's why you fail." I was like, "You
fail. That's why you're negative." Other
way around, buddy. Because the other way
around wouldn't make any sense. Cuz I
tried to put it I I always say this.
Yeah. When people try to blame the
mindset thing and all of these excuses
like people living with their money and
all of this, I said, "Okay, so let's go
by your logic." Yeah. You just wake up
one day negative for no reason. So you
wake up, right, and you think, "Oh,
[ __ ] I'm going to be negative every day
for no reason, no prior experiences, but
you just want to waste energy being
negative." Well, I don't even think a
psychopath would do that. No, no, no.
What would make actual sense is you get negative experiences
and then um
that's where the mindset comes from
because it's obvious. That's the only
thing that makes sense.
How you man? You good? Good, bro.
So, I was just talking to that guy about
something. I didn't want to I didn't
want people knowing our business, but yeah,
just the guy gave the guy a word of advice.
Yeah, I just gave him a word of advice.
Can't even be [ __ ] go out today, bro.
[ __ ] hell. Um, anyways, I'm going to
charge this phone and I'm going to
leave. Enough rambling. Yeah, going to
charge this phone. I'm going to leave.
See you. I'll be live later in the club maybe. Yeah.