Just waiting for good old
Grezy. Good old Greasy.
Yay. Yeah, man. M.
Yeah. Yeah, bro. [ __ ] hell. To be
honest with you, I can't be bothe, bro. It's too
cold. Yeah, [ __ ] that,
bro. Can't be bothered, man.
It's [ __ ] cold. Nah,
I can't be bothered, bro. Waste of
[ __ ] money in
it. Literally, guys.
But this person is a me and us in two
weeks. Hey, we'll see.
Bro, I I'd rather just wait for Ant-Man
to be fair. [ __ ] [Music] it. No. Yeah. Passport's
£88. Uh 88 pound Yes. [Music] I sugar. Yeah,
basically. What the
[ __ ] One second.
Need to make a few of these accounts to be fair. Good
morning. Let me see. Brian Baxter. Brian
Baxter. Yeah, man.
Yeah, I can't be bother going out
tomorrow. I can't be annoyed, bro. I'd
rather just get a [ __ ] passport
sorted to be honest. Can't be sending
it, bro. It's [ __ ]
long and I can't be bothered dealing
with people tomorrow.
feel like um you get to a certain point
yet you get to a certain age and you
think [ __ ] it I want to do other things you
know [ __ ] this women [ __ ] is boring
bro [ __ ] hell every [ __ ]
week does does get boring bro it does
boring it does get if it was like I was
saying to thingy if it was the summer
it'd be a different story man I'd be out
every [ __ ] I'd be two, three times a
[ __ ] you know, week. You know,
summer's different, bro. Like,
but not a [ __ ] Yeah. You know what I'm
saying? A winner, bro.
[ __ ] Four thumbs up on that video. Yay. Back up, bro. Yeah.
What's popping, bro? [ __ ] all, man. Just
chilling. Had a beef
chain. But I was going to go out
tomorrow, sending it, but I can't be
bothered. But I'm just going to get my passport
sorted. And then that's it. Ant-Man's
coming back on the 19th, so I'll meet
him. I'll go for a drink on the 19th, I
think. I can't be bothered going out,
bro. Swear down. It's boring. It's cold.
It's the same
[ __ ] We've done this
like a million times with this the these
women, bro. And it's just it just it
gets boring, bro. You get to a certain
point in your life that you think, I
want to do other things, but this
approaching [ __ ] and it's just boring
and man, it's boring. We've had women,
they they're the same. They're all the
same. It's boring as [ __ ] Like, we
might as well just do other things.
Isn't that right, Greasy Boss? I got to
pay £88 for a [ __ ] passport
tomorrow and get my hair done and that.
I'll get my hair done and that but I'm
just not going to go out sending it. I
can't be [ __ ]
bro. I can't be
asked. Could go Blackpool
tomorrow. Literally could go Blackpool tomorrow,
bro. Actually could
go. But would that be okay with you, Greasy Boss?
Greasy, would that be okay with you,
boss? Um, yeah. No drinking.
So, why do I have so many stalkers? Hey,
Greasy. Why do I have so many stalkers, bro?
Uh-huh. I want summer. I wish it was
summer, bro. H I'll be out three times a
[ __ ] week, bro. I wish it was
summer. No [ __ ] bro. I actually
do. We got a film coming out in March,
but it's not until like the 27th of
March. Yeah, I might not drink for a month,
lad. Yeah, but I don't go mad though.
Yeah, but the thing is, Grevy, I don't
go mad. They're just little repeaters.
But the thing is, Grezy, they don't make
me go mad cuz guess what, Greavvesy?
Who's the one that's better looking than
them? Me. Who's the one that gets more
money than them? Me. So, if you actually
think about it, bro, they they don't No,
no, no, no, no. You got to understand
with these little weirdos, even if you
don't react to them, they will still do
what they do. So, it's not for reaction
that they do it for. Because even if you
don't react to them, they will still do
it. That's the difference. You see, and
that's how you know it's because they're
jealous and they do what they do because
they're jealous. They don't do it to get
you mad. They don't do do it for
reaction. They do it because they want
to be you. Because they're jealous of
you. Because even if you don't react,
they still do it. Even if you don't
watch their channel, they still do it.
So what what's the excuse that time
then? Do you know what I'm saying, bro?
Like [ __ ] hell.
But yeah, I could go out send it tomorrow,
but I can't be bothered, bro. I am just
going to chill, bro. Just wait for this
horror film to come out. Yeah, I'm going
to go Well, I'm going to not drink until
the 19th till Ant-Man comes back, then
we'll go out
together. Yeah, really slagging me off. Good for
him. You know what I'm saying? But, uh,
drinking in the winter is not the one, bro.
Bless you, Grezy, and your little £750 a month. Bless
you. Bless you. If you're on £750 a month, bless
you. Bless you in life,
Greavves. I can't get myself in a proper relationship,
lad. I can't get myself in a proper
relationship at my age, bro. Sorry.
Nah, bro. [ __ ] I don't care, bro, about
this woman [ __ ] women [ __ ] anymore,
lad. I don't care about this women [ __ ]
anymore, bro. It's actually boring, bro.
swear. We're doing some serious
traveling this year,
lad. Bless you,
Grezy. You're still better off than some
people, bro. My friend in Liverpool gets
£400 a month.
See, I'd rather I'd rather a way to make
money. Like, I'd rather go out tomorrow
and [ __ ] make money than do approaches and
[ __ ] do other things. I'd rather do
other things, you
know? I'd rather do other things,
but you know, then then this approaching
and drinking. I'm kind of going I want I
want to go on a detox, lad.
I want to occupy my time, but I can't be
bothered with women, bro, for a while.
It's boring as [ __ ] They're just boring
as [ __ ] And they're just predictable
and just they're not even worth it, bro.
I swear to
God, they literally aren't, bro. My sex
drive has gone down.
I used to get when I was
21. That's what I used to get when I was 21,
lad. But all all jokes aside, now the
gambling [ __ ] is is over,
bro. That Uber thing, if you could
actually make good money from it, but
you can't, man.
ways to occupy Peter Belly's time. You
know, I want to stay away from the
alcohol for a bit and the woman for the bit. [ __ ]
Um, yeah, I would tell you more things
about my life, Grezy, but I
don't I don't want these people knowing
anything about my life. Like, in that
way, you know what I'm saying?
Like, [ __ ] lost 300 pound today. I
got it back though.
So, it's [ __ ] almost 300 quid. [ __ ]
sake. How mad is that on stupid
machines? Madness, bro.
So, you know, you're never going to work,
Grezy. Are you never going to work?
Nah, you're never going to work. Never
How much do you get a month? Harry fraud. Yeah.
I can't be bothered with [ __ ] I can't
be bothered with women at the moment,
bro. I swear to
God. I can't be bothered with him at the
moment, bro. I can't be bothered with
drinking either, man. It's [ __ ]
wrong. Shame about I can't believe I
lost fucking£300 today,
bro. I would tell you how much I'm on,
but nah, too many jealous people in this community.
So keep it to keep that to myself,
bro. But it is [ __ ] though.
Like this passport
thing. Yeah, Gregy gets a lot of
money. No, no,
no. I'm on the same as G. How much does
get, bro? As tempted as
that. Yeah, you keep you keep thinking
that, Harry, bro. You keep thinking
that. I'm not going to tell you how much I get,
bro. Sorry, there's too many grasses on
this community. I'm not telling you
nothing. But yeah, we we'll say I get
1,500 a month. I'm trying to get back to
16 and code
benefits. How much do you get, Steven
Howard? No, no, I can't. No, no, no. The
thing is I can't work because, you know,
at the same time I want to work because
I'm bored, but at the same time I'm so
used to not working and living that life
without working. when you're
self-employed or when you've when you've
got big money and you don't need to
work, you will see what I mean. Like
you're your own man. You can do whatever
you want when you want to do
it. But it is, you know what I'm saying?
Like which is good in a way. You're used
to like life, you know,
so not having to [ __ ] do anything.
I get I get £1,100 a month, mate. That's
how much I get. I get £1,100 a
month. Yeah, I get £1,100 a month,
man. You keep telling yourself that,
Harry. Have you seen my
videos? And I've not worked for years.
Look at my videos, bro. And I've not
worked for years.
Bro, you really don't know how much I
get. I'm not saying how much I get. As
tempted as I'm to tell you, I'm not
telling you how much I get. Sorry, bro. Too many
glasses. Trust me, I'm not telling no one
nothing. But just know I'm living that
life, boy. Yo, and there's holidays to come.
Trust. I spend my money on [ __ ] women
and drinking. That's why this month I'm
I'm saving, bro. I'm actually saving.
Yeah, I lost 280, but you know, that was
that's the start of the month. I ain't
done it for a
month. Doesn't matter how I get money,
bro. It's none of your business. I'm not
I'm not saying my life on
here. Yeah, I've got no TV. Yeah,
congratulations, bro. I don't care about TV. Anyways,
um I don't watch TV and no one I knows
has a TV either. So
yeah, 280 is
massive. Is it really? I don't think it
is. And if you was earning a grand in 4
days, you wouldn't think it is
either. I get money on
[ __ ] I I spend money on [ __ ]
gambling, drinking, and women, but I am
definitely cutting down. I'm I need to
get a hobby, bro. I swear to God. I
actually need to start
saving. That's why I'm not going out
tomorrow. I need to get this passport
sorted. And I I'm not drinking tomorrow
either. I'm not going to drink for a little while, man. Believe
that cuz it's pointless, man. It's It's
not fun if you do it every week. Every
once in a while is okay.
Who doesn't own a
TV? Ah, bye-bye
now. Yeah. See, I would tell Greavesy my
life, but I think Greavvesy would
grass you get 1k a month.
Steven mate, who's going to pay for my
little stonies? If I'm on a grand a
month, Grevy, who's going to pay for my
little stonies, lad? Our baby Peter's
our future baby Peter
Stony. And who's going to pay for the Reese
clothes? I'd be
[ __ ] in it.
Yeah, you would be [ __ ] mate. I would
[ __ ] Well, no, cuz I'm basically
going to be living off a grand a month
because I won't be going out drinking or
trying to get women for a while anyways
cuz it's boring, bro. It It does get boring.
It does get boring, bro.
Trust. So, how much can you save a month
out of 750
grezy? But, you know, I spent a lot of
money last month on [ __ ] women.
Yeah, US. I don't think of USA anymore.
Steven Howard. Yay.
I tried to save a couple of grand a month
working. It never ends up working, mate.
Hopefully I can save about 1,600 pound
this month if I'm lucky. Yeah,
hopefully. If I'm lucky, bro. Yeah.
She's a [ __ ]
[ __ ] That's what she is. She's a
spacker. You're going to need to pack
in, bro. You're not going to be able to afford
it. You're not going to be able to
afford it, man. On
[ __ ] on a
like Yeah. You're not going to be able
to save if you're doing that.
Yeah. Do you remember when the rat face
was trying to show his bum chain? Steven
Howard when the little rat face was
trying to show a grand off. Oh, it's so
embarrassing, isn't it?
Oh, it's so embarrassing. Rat face
thinking that he's got money. Oh boy, I
feel sorry for that little
rodent. Bless the little rodent in
life thinking that he's got money. Oh, bless
him. It also It's also what you actually
have as well, not how much money you have.
Wow. Yeah, man. Beat me. Beat me. Beat
me at it, bro. Beat me at it. I'd love
I'd love you to beat me at
it. So, who who's going to pay for the
Stone Islands? Steven Howard, if I'm on
a grind a month, who's going to pay for
the little stone islands and the little
Reese clothes and the little nights out
trying to get for trying to get women?
That's what I say to Laney. I say to
her, "Who's going to pay for all of
this? The Stonies, the Nights Out, the
Baby Grows, if baby Peter ever comes, a
grand a month just won't do it." You know, the
Stonies. Ah, what a lovely site.
Remember them Stonies, bro? Oh, bless
you. You know what I'm saying? Who's
going to [ __ ] Who's going to be
paying for that,
bro? Might be a [ __ ] grand a
month. You're on a You're on a grand a month,
Shell. You're on a grand a month, mate.
Stop fronting, you little
virgin. You can't even afford a passport.
The rodent face can't even afford to go abroad. [ __ ]
[ __ ] Nah, mate. It's got to be Stone
Island, Greavves. It's got to be Stone
Island. But the problem with Shill is
his funds won't allow it. His funds
won't stretch that
far. Do you understand? His funds
literally won't go that
far because he's on a grand a month. So
he can't afford Stone Island. You
understand? Cuz he he he's living in
poverty, mate. To to put it to put it
politely, he's living below the barrel.
It's why he can't afford Stone. See,
I've got Stony. I got Stony gear. I bought it.
You know, I bought it,
mate. I I bought it with with some money, you
know. Se can't can't get women like me,
can he? Steven Howard, like that
Scottish, like all these other women and stuff.
Uh cuz he's a
[ __ ] He gets it for being a
[ __ ] Yeah, he gets it for being a
lad. Yeah. Who's going to pay for the
stone island gear,
bro? Oh, you can easily take it.
Nah. Who gets the most money? Me. I didn't say
that. I'm not saying how much I get a
month. Sorry, bro. You get too many
grasses on here. Jealous
grasses. If it was a If it was a
community that wasn't full of jealousy
and [ __ ] and and grasses, bro, I'd tell
you my whole life
story, you know?
But yeah, can't be doing that,
Dad. But I would say me, look on my videos,
bro. Yeah, I remember I used to get 700
pound when I was like 21 when I used to
be Izzy and I used to find it very hard
to live off.
very hard to live
off. I used to find it very hard to live off, bro.
Um I just found it very hard to live off [Music]
um 700 a month when I was 2021.
It used to be like, "Do you get 320
pip?" Um, Grezy, £320 pip,
right? Yeah. I got a [ __ ] advanced
payment out and I [ __ ] blew it on the
[ __ ] machine. 300
quid. [ __ ] hell, bro. It's [ __ ]
hard trying to get that as
well. It was hard trying to get that
money as well, bro. [ __ ]
sake. But we live and we learn, eh?
It'll be all right
tomorrow. I don't know. It just makes
you feel guilty,
bro. It just makes you feel
guilty. Even though it's not a lot of
money to me at that, but still bad in
it. So, Greasy, you get 320 pip, right? Yeah.
I'd love to tell you how much I get.
Greasy, do you want me to tell you how much I
get? Do you want me to tell you how much
I actually get,
bro? I think you would get jealous if I told you.
But I used to get £700 a month month
when I was
21. Nope. Over
3K. Over 3K. I shouldn't even be saying
that, but yeah. There you go.
Over three grand delayed. Try
again, mate. Who's going to pay for all
of these women to satisfy Peter B's
[ __ ] needs if I was earning any less than
that? No, just my own money. Well, I
tell a lie. I have
likeund I'll calculate 50. Five, six, seven,
eight. Five, six. Hold on. I'll tell you
how much my bills are. Probably about £150 in
bills when I get like 3.3. So, don't do
it. That's why it's very hard to stay
in. That's why it's very hard to stay
in. But I need to save money cuz I want
to go on holidays, bro, this year.
So, it's quite a good amount, isn't it?
But no, it's without the housing
costs. Who else are going to pay for
these [ __ ] stonies? You know what I'm saying, bro? Yeah.
Yeah. It's quite a bit, is it? Uh,
Grezy, it's quite a bit, eh?
I don't think I could I couldn't imagine
going back to
700. I I have lived on 700 before when I
was I told you 2021 it was hard, bro. I
always used to run out of
money. I always used to Well, I I've
I've lived off like £300 a month, bro.
I've lived off like 300 pound a month. Nope.
Nope. Told you Peter Benny gets money,
mate. Just cuz I don't show these little
mongos that are on the [ __ ] ground a
month doesn't mean nothing. You know
what I'm saying? So
yeah, but the thing is Grezy, that's
what I'm trying to say. Like when I used
to get £700, I used to run out of
money. But then at the same time, I used
to live off £300.
Yeah. I mean, I could probably do it now
cuz I don't really care about women
anymore and I don't I'm not really going
to go out as much cuz they're boring.
They're the same old. When you've had
women, it doesn't you I've had enough
women. But if you're actually trying to
get women, you're on a grand a month.
You're limited to what you can do, you
know? You can't go out as
much, you know. But if you're if you
don't care or you're at the stage that
you don't care and you just have
different hobbies, then yeah, you can
live off a grand a month, bro. You
know, it just wouldn't be as
good. Think of it, bro.
I get, okay, I'll give you an example. I
get a payment
of £600 tomorrow, £40 haircut, 890
passport. I've got to put some money in
the gas and electric. That's almost spoken
for. So there you go,
bro. Depends on the months and the
outgoings, I guess.
But that rice share trying to say that
he gets 2,900 a month. No, he doesn't.
No, he does not. There is no
benefit that pays 2,900
no. He just chat [ __ ] Trust me. He y
Bro, why is he bragging anyways? Bro,
he's trying to claim that he gets 3k a
month. He gets 3k a month, but what does
he do with it? He sits in all day, bro.
He's agrophobic. He sits in that [ __ ]
apartment in Glasgow and he does
nothing, mate. So why is he even
bragging? Yeah, he doesn't get that much
anyways. I get more than him and he
doesn't even get that
much cuz there's no benefit that pays
that, you know.
Doesn't matter how I get money, but I'm
saying, you know, he does not get no 2.9K.
Simple. I'm not [ __ ] telling my
[ __ ] business, bro. I've got my
[ __ ] Wiz, but it ain't it a it ain't
obviously all benefits. How can benefits
pay [ __ ] three grand in
Glasgow? Trust me, he's chatting
[ __ ] you know? He is chatting [ __ ]
bro. And for somebody that's on three
grand a month, man, you should be
ashamed of yourself. If you really are
on that amount of money,
then bro, you're sat indoors all [ __ ]
day. You know what I'm saying? You don't
get no 2,900. No [ __ ] way does he,
bro. He doesn't. He doesn't, lad.
Bro, it doesn't matter, bro. I I get
money. It doesn't matter. I get money.
Simple. Believe it. Don't believe it.
I'm I'm not going to say my life story.
But since you was all saying how much
you get, I told you how much I get. But simple,
bro. Just believe what I'm saying, bro. Yeah.
But that rice does not get 2.9K a
month. It's like that. Sean, I get way
more money than him. I've got way more
money than him. I don't need to go to an
ATM and do and play the money game with
these people again. You know why? Cuz I
already beat him. I already beat these
people and I show them six grand. Steven
Howard, when I show these people six
grand, I had already beaten them. So I
don't need to beat them again until they
show me 12. They can call people skin
all they want, bro. We no different. You
know, we just put [ __ ] 300 on the
pound of the [ __ ] machine today for sake.
Yeah. And that's it,
lad. But yeah, 750.
So, how many times could you go out in
London if you was on a grind a month?
Once if you're lucky, mate. I remember
in the summer I spent 700 pound in one
day. When I met when I met that
19year-old, the first time I met her, I
spent about 800
quid. Hotels, drinking, gambling, even
though I won. [ __ ] knows what it went
on, bro. But it went
uh uh stop repeating yourself. Why do I
only have £25 at Christmas? Uh probably
cuz I gambled all my money.
Duh. Oh, but I don't have so much money.
I'm skinn apparently. So yeah, I spent
£800 the first time I met
her. 800 [ __ ] quid, bro.
pound. Oh, [ __ ]
hell. That's a madness, isn't
it? So, yeah, you could go out once in
London a month,
but Well, I just answered your
question. I have more I have more money
than that ratfaced rodent [ __ ] would
ever have, mate.
Before talking about people's [ __ ]
noses, why don't you fix your [ __ ]
ugly rat face? You rat face little
bastard. Know what I'm saying? And that's facts,
lad. That is [Music]
facts. But yeah, I did actually spend £800 one
day. That's the thing in London. I've
most I've spent on drinking is about
250. That was just drinking.
So yeah, if you get a grand a month, you
basically be [ __ ]
Really? Yeah, I'd be [ __ ]
bro. I'd have to not go out for like a
month. Well, which is what I'm doing
anyways. I'm saving money anyway, so I'm
basically living off that now.
Yeah, he did. But I've got them all
saved. I've got them all saved, lad.
I've got them all [ __ ] saved,
bro. But I will do the post. I just
can't be bothered at the minute. It's
not cuz of police because they wouldn't
even arrest me this time anyways. I
don't give a [ __ ] about the police. I'll
show the police channel. Mate, if the
police come on my door, firstly, I'll
tell them to [ __ ] off and come back with
a warrant. Second of all, if they get
the warrant or ended up in the
house, hold on a minute. Right. So
you're going to come on my
door living at my mom's. I don't live
with my mom anymore. So you're going to come on
my going to let this rodentfaced sura
rap bastard keep making videos of me
every day. community post on [ __ ]
off cuz the police but I'm not asked about the
police you know to you know look what
happened today in the bookies with that
[ __ ] guy I weren't going to let him
intimidate way mate no [ __ ]
way don't care what [ __ ] weapon he
has so I don't care about the police lad
I don't give a [ __ ] you know. Little
bastard. Yeah, he's so ugly. How he
talks about the way I look, he's he is
[ __ ] so ugly. He's an ugly rat.
I think that's what um makes him
like get over help helps him deal with
the fact that he's ugly is that he talks
about my nose. [ __ ] hell. What a
[ __ ] kid would
say. Think of it, bro. He's still
obsessed with my sloppy seconds, but I'm the ugly
one. Well, obviously wasn't ugly to them
to get them, lad.
Uh cuz we just had a
disagreement. Uh I met him in a pub.
Yeah. He was from Glasgow. I think of
him sometimes when I watch like Scottish
videos cuz I lost contact. And I said,
"Oh, I'm going to send it, lads. I'm
going to I'm going to approach this
woman here." It was in the Weather
Spoons. And they said, "Oh, go on." And
then I done it. And I said, "Oh, just
another one that pretends they've got
boyfriends." And I was like, "How do you
know they're pretending?" I mean,
because they say it all the time. It's
so weird how like in
a maybe they do. I was like, "Well, they
don't because they're in a pub
and they don't have boyfriends cuz they their boyfriends
um they would be with their boyfriends."
And I was at a stage where I was just
sick of hearing it, just sick to death
of hearing it. And then he was just
being weird. and I got his number and I
messaged him and he said, "Oh, you you
need help." And [ __ ] This was like last
year. I wonder what happened to him. My
phone got stolen. So,
um, obviously I lost his number and that.
So, his name was Tam from Glasgow. He
had a mad accent,
bro. [ __ ] Glasgow.
[ __ ] horrible accent. That isn't it?
Yeah. I'm not having this conversation,
bro. I'm not having this conversation.
Whether they pretend they do, whe they
don't pretend they do. Listen, I know
they pretend to. They pretend to. I'm
sick of hearing it. I'm gonna stop
hearing it. Simple. I'm not having this
conversation. It's boring as [ __ ] It is
boring as [ __ ] They don't have
boyfriends. Probably about four out of
10 of these women actually have
boyfriends. I'm not having this
conversation. End the story.
Simple. Was he another great man? No, he
was just a he just turned out to be just
weird, bro. His friend was all right.
But yeah, I wonder what happened to him.
Anyways, [ __ ] good
guy. It's is the point of this combo,
bro. Like, where do women say they've
got a boyfriend? Literally three to four
of them actually do. It's obvious. It's
common sense, you know?
They're just they're just [ __ ] in this
country. I'm not dealing with them
anymore, bro. I can't be bothered
dealing with them. I go out to drink cuz
I want to drink.
Simple. Yeah. They don't have Yeah.
Women that go clubbing until early hours
in the morning don't have boyfriends.
No, they don't. Yeah, I'm telling you
they don't. Yeah. End
of. I'm right and you're wrong. Simple.
They don't have a
boyfriend. Their boyfriend don't
exist. Isn't that right,
Grezy? And I don't really care if they
do or they don't. It's annoying hearing
it. [ __ ] hell. And I have a choice to
not hear it. And I'm not hearing it anymore. Simple.
Why do you think I'm not going to go out
tomorrow? Because I can't be bothered
listening to it. It's boring as [ __ ]
It's cold as well. It's boring as [ __ ]
bro. I remember this
account. That's my lack of life
experience. I have more life experience
than you will ever have. Boy better
believe. Boy better know. Yeah. I have
more life experience than you will ever
have. Trust me, I will ever have. If you
actually think these women in nightclubs
actually have boyfriends, you're a [ __ ]
idiot, you know? Okay, maybe two out of
10, dude. But that's about it. Maybe two
out of 10 actually have boyfriends.
Three out of 10 actually have boyfriends.
Yeah, they're they're [ __ ] in this
country, bro. End of Yeah. And that's it.
Yeah. Um I'm not incapable of a
long-term relationship. Uh, Greavvesy,
I've actually tried being in a long-term
relationship with that woman from
Manchester, and she's the one that was
incapable of being in a relationship
because they don't even give you a
chance. So, actually, they're the ones that are
incapable. Oh, that's enough of that big
nose. Oh, shut up, you little rodent
face, you little rat. You want to grind
them up, you little rat. Go suck your disabled dad's
dick. Listen, Sean, you look like a
[ __ ] rat. Go and sort your ugly rat
face out. You [ __ ] ugly rat [ __ ] Go
give your rat face a wobble and get
plastic surgery, you ugly [ __ ] And
whilst you're at it, go and sort your
ugly fat girlfriend out as well, you
little virgin. Bye-bye
now. Um, I have more life experience
than me, had a job, and I have met a
woman over for se uh actually several
times, mate. I'd rather have a big nose
than be a big [ __ ] ugly looking rat
like you. At least the nose is [ __ ]
fixable, you know? You [ __ ] ratfaced
ugly bastard. You can't grow a beard.
Your face looks like someone's thrown
acid on it. Your face looks like someone
has has actually thrown acid on your
face. That's how ugly you actually are.
Like, I know you ignore this [ __ ] when I
say it. You are very ugly. You are very,
very ugly. Like you you can call me what
you want, but at the end of the day,
you're the ones that's obsessed with my
sloppy seconds. And I got these sloppy
seconds because of my looks, but you
call me ugly. But that doesn't make
sense. How can I be ugly when you're
obsessed with the women that I've been
with? Um, and yeah. And Henry, do you
know why I've never had a job? I
actually have had a job, but do you know
why I've not had a job in years? Because
I'm successful and I don't need to be
someone's [ __ ] When you got a brain,
you don't need to work for someone, you
know. It's called having a brain, you know, basically.
Yeah. Bro, you look like a [ __ ]
rat. You are [ __ ] stinger, mate.
Uh meeting a girl a few times
isn't skin little manta. Sean I I I get
more money than you.
Sh. What are you talking
about? And doing one day mate. Did you
hear what I just said? I said I don't
need to have a job. I'm
successful. Successful people don't need
jobs. Sean, why are you showing your
housing benefit off? You're embarrassing
yourself. Sh, you're supposed to be
showing us 12 grand. But you ain't got
12 grand, you little ratfaced bastard on
a grand a month. You
know, mate, even if I lost everything,
mate, I will always have more than you
would ever have, mate. Go make another
account, you little virgin.
Yeah, it's life [ __ ] Even if you have a woman, bro,
like they're boring, bro. Like when you
when you had enough of them. Yeah. Like
you've you've been with enough of them
and you've been with enough of them.
You've been with enough of them. [ __ ]
like it gets boring, bro. And when they
just they're just all the same as well,
bro. Like, I can't be bothered dealing
with them. Like, it's they're [ __ ]
boring as [ __ ] You know what I'm saying, bro?
Yeah, life's money where we got [ __ ]
mate. But it's more depressing if you gamble, lad.
Like, there's things you can do. Like,
I'm, bro, I've got to rely on these
horror films to come out. My life's
boring unless these horror films come
out. Like I love these horror films, but
they're not always in the
cinema. Like, yeah, life is [ __ ] bro.
But it doesn't mean that you should
waste money gambling just because life's
[ __ ] you know? Like, it is
[ __ ] And I'm in a very lucky position
as well. And it's and it's still kind of
boring. Even if you had a woman, it's
[ __ ] boring. They're just [ __ ]
[ __ ] as well. Not even when you get them. [ __ ] devious.
Devious that just play
games. I'm very good at
cooking. The only thing you can really
do is just
like travel or something. I don't know,
bro. It's [ __ ]
Life is [ __ ]
bro. Yeah, but I'm waiting for this
horror film to come out. I'm looking
forward to it, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. You are the virgin. You are
the little virgin, mate. You've never
stuck your autistic dick up nothing. You little ratfaced
virgin. You are skin and you are a
virgin. The only thing you've ever had
Well, actually you No, actually you're
not a virgin because you've had your
dad's dick. So actually you're not a
virgin, but the only thing you've ever
had is daddy's dick. You've never been
with a woman. You never stuck your dick
up a woman. That's why you're obsessed
with Izzy. That's why you're obsessed
with Morgan. Cuz you're still a virgin.
And to be honest with you, you are the
one that's the gay lord. You are the one
that's a closeted homosexual. People
used to um used to um tease you about
being gay. And that's where the trend
come from with Cheryl Cole. Oh, if you
don't like Cheryl Cole, you're gay.
Yeah. That's cuz you are a little gay
little virgin that's never been with a
woman. That's the only reason you made
them comments because you are the
virgin. You are the gay boy. Gaylord who
sucks his disabled dad's dick. You
little virgin. Mate, I don't know how
you can come on here after your your
your mom's boyfriend had you up against
the wall screaming like a little [ __ ]
I don't understand how you can
literally like, mate, you've got a
disabled girlfriend that can't even
talk. Yeah, good for you. You're still
obsessed with my sloppy seconds. No one
cares. But I don't understand how you
literally got grabbed up against the
wall. You literally got slapped the [ __ ]
out of by Philillip Campbell of Leads
and you're going to come on here in your
little bedsit on £1,000 a month. £1,000
pittance a month that you get and try to call
me. Oh mate, I've had love more times
than you. And you know what? She will
never know what it's like for her
boyfriend to make love to her because
he's got erectile dysfunction. She Yeah.
And you know what's Do you know what's
so funny is she will never be able to be
loved by you because you've got erectile
dysfunction. You can't get it up. You
can't get it up. You can't get that
disabled dick up. You showed me the
X-ray before of your disabled dick
that's never been up. Nothing. You
remember? You showed the X-ray, mate.
You showed the X-ray of that [ __ ]
disabled autistic dowy dick virgin
that's never been up nothing. That
[ __ ] disabled dick has not been up no
woman. Mate, listen. You know, you know
when when I first met you. Yeah. And I
told you that I I slept with these
escorts. I think it was a few the first
time I met you and I was like, why is he
denying it? Why is he denying it? And it
makes sense. It's cuz you are the
virgin. It made sense all along like not
not back then. Now I figured it up. I
was like why did he even deny this deny
that it's because he was one himself and
and that's and that's and now I actually
understand it is that you are the Virgin
the Kent Virgin notoutheast Virgin
southeast London. You're from Kent.
You're not from
southeast you're from Kent. It's a
completely different place. Yeah, people
from London don't sound like you, Virgin
boy. Yeah, they don't sound nothing like
you. People from London, they are
nothing like you or your n's dad. Even
Cudden is not
London. Yeah. I used to say all the
time, I've been with this escort, I've
been with that escort. And he used to
say, no you haven't. No, you haven't. I
was like, I [ __ ] have, Virgin boy.
And then I had to get my mom to like
It's all because he's a little virgin.
He's a little downy virgin with a
disabled dick and a disabled dad. That's
why he was doing this for all of these
years. This was before I met Izzy. This
was before I met any of these, bro. This
was back when I was like
17. Yeah. And that's what it is. It's
because he is a virgin. It makes sense
now. It does make sense. It's because
he's a little erectile dysfunction ugly
little virgin that can only play prey on
the vulnerable. And you know what you
need to say to your girlfriend Sarah?
She'll never know what's she will never
know what it's like for her boyfriend
for her boyfriend to um make love to
her because he's got erectile
dysfunction. That's what you should say
to your disabled girlfriend. Anyways, go
make another account, Virgin Boy.
That's it, bro.
Yeah. Yeah, man. See, all these women I
meet, Stephen Howard, I have them on
WhatsApp. I have them on uh WhatsApp,
lad, cuz I don't want this virgin
finding out any woman
that I speak
to. You understand how it is, right? Yeah.
Ow. And that's how it
is. Very angry. You lost all your
pennies all this time. You're stuck in
20 P spins, mate. I will always have
more money than you. I get more money
than you. Why don't you tell us how much
money you get a month? Why don't you
join the game? How much money do you get
month? I'm going to do some posters of
you, Sean. I'm I'm coming with
posters. I'm coming with posters,
mate. Yeah, I'm coming out with the posters, mate.
posters. Then you're going to be doomed.
I'm not going to tell you where I put
all of them as well.
I'm going to do posters of your show and
you're going to get your your ass
whipped, you know. You're going to get
your ass whipped,
mate. Yeah. And then you tried making up
a story that your mom called the police
on you 22 times. Nah, she didn't, mate.
Nah. Nah, she didn't, mate. Nah, you got
[ __ ] up by your mom's
boyfriend. By your mom's boyfriend. He
had you up against the wall, Shan. He
had you up against the wall, you little
[ __ ] I had an argument today with a
guy in the bookies. He's got his P. I
said, "Go and hit me with it then, big
man. Hit me with it then, big man. I'm
not no [ __ ] Sean. Some little [ __ ]
Kent virgin. A virgin from Kent." That's
what I was actually thinking. And stop
saying that [ __ ] little India area that
you live in is [ __ ] I is London. That
little [ __ ] hole that you live in that
little virgin area is is not London. Why
do you keep saying it's London when it's
not? Yeah, I did. I [ __ ] did, mate.
Yeah, and I gave him my address as well.
So, why don't you come after work, big
man, away from the cameras? Yeah. But
anyways, Sean, [ __ ] all that. Why do you
keep saying that little Orington [ __ ]
little virgin area that you live in is
is London. It's not London. London
doesn't have villages. You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, I'm an S6 boy, bro. Yeah, I'm an S6 boy.
Yeah, I'm a London I'm an Essex boy even
though I was born in London. Yeah. Okay. S6
boy. [ __ ] idiot, bro. [Music]
sleep in a bit, bro. Quiet.
I'm going to sleep, bro. See you.