Hey bro, how we doing man?
Approach boyfriend. [ __ ]
got the be.
Yeah, man. Just on another approach.
It's got was on it.
This is insane, bro. What the [ __ ]
Generally, don't even think they look at you.
Coming tomorrow, man. Push for time
today, but I'll do a video tomorrow. This
This is [ __ ] up. It's like it's the
only word they know is I have a woman.
Like, how about just a normal
conversation and a friendship? Ah, no
chance for these NPCs, man.
No [ __ ] chance for these NPCs. These non-playing characters.
No chance for these non-playing characters.
[ __ ] hell. [ __ ] way, man. It seems
to be the same people you see as well. Same people,
same attitude. Like, by the same people,
I mean the same attitude pretty much.
It's [ __ ] annoying. Oh, bro.
I'm gone on Wednesday anyways. I ain't
got none. I just went and done an
approach. Literally didn't even look at
me. Sorry, I've got a boyfriend.
I'll show you her right now if you want. Oh, [ __ ]
Right over there.
Not this one. The second one. Not the
first one. The second one. I've got a
boyfriend. Oh man. How are you going to
get friendships, bro? How are you that
you can't even get a conversation out of
someone, let alone a friendship, let
alone a relationship? Like, I'm going to
I'm going to mate, my new video is going
to have a banging title. I'm telling
you, it's going to have a banging title.
You can't even get a conversation out of
someone, bro. What the [ __ ] I don't
[ __ ] like fall on the street as well.
It's so bad, bro. It's really bad.
It's really hard in this country, but
I'm telling you, I swear to God, it is 62%.
Yeah, I just done one over there, bro.
The bag and left the drink and
everything. I've got a boyfriend. That's
the only word they know. Like, they
can't even have a conversation or give
like normal feedback or just anything.
It's the only word they literally know.
Like, it's madness.
It's literally all they ever say. Like
we joke about it, but it is the same old
[ __ ] Like, it's not even to do. It's
not even luck anymore. It's boring.
Like, it's not even luck. It actually is
so boring, bro. And it takes a lot to bugs.
It's [ __ ] up, man. It's [ __ ] up,
It's the only word they actually know,
bro. People need to get some life experience, man.
Or like Reddit and [ __ ] They need to
get some life experience. That's what
they need, man.
You can't get nothing in this country,
bro. I was going to do a video earlier,
but I couldn't be [ __ ] man.
I went to Gregs, but I'll do one tomorrow.
You can't get nothing, mate, in this
country. mothers before getting nothing.
I've done about three approaches. Oh, anyone else?
Hey, they're all NPCs, bro. I'm telling you.
Too many stuck up [ __ ] in this
country. I think the person on video was right by
you know even when I get a number today
cuz I am going to get a number.
It's just going to be the same [ __ ]
It ain't even funny. It's [ __ ] boring, bro.
Don't go below 60, man.
And you got [ __ ]
Joe saying it's luck. It's nothing to do with luck.
It's literally borderline impossible, bro.
It's not even anything to do with luck
anymore. Maybe 3 years ago it was, but not anymore.
Boring as [ __ ]
Anyone here? No.
No. There's no one here, man. People
going to start coming down.
It's [ __ ] dead. [ __ ] finally leave.
Looking straight forward to the last time.
This will never change.
It will never change. Right.
I'm going be back later.