[ __ ] hell, bro.
It's so bad, is it?
[ __ ] fed up.
Oh, [ __ ] hell. One number on one Facebook.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Oh, mate. I'm [ __ ]
I'm actually [ __ ]
Oh, mate. Oh, what a [ __ ] day I've had.
There's a charger, bro. Charge. Sh [ __ ]
Oh, you're not. I'm [ __ ]
Yeah, man. [ __ ] hell, bro. Yeah.
Roll on Wednesday, mate. Roll on [ __ ] Wednesday.
What a [ __ ] day I have had, Grezy.
What a [ __ ] day I've had.
I'm not even trolling when I'm [ __ ]
saying it as well, bro. It was so bad.
It was so bad, bro. Like,
I went out, bro.
I swear that I got I got a boyfriend
about 15 times in a row, which is quite
unusual cuz like usually you get it, but
not that many times. I got one Facebook
and one number.
Sad, sad, sad. It's a sad country we
live in, bro. I got it about, bro. I got
it. [ __ ] it. I got it constantly, bro.
Like, I'm not even joking. There was
this one woman, right? You know what she
told me? She gave me a number and she's
like, "Oh, yeah. I might be breaking up
with my boyfriend on Saturday." Um, she
said to me about how,
"Yeah, I don't think you're good-looking
enough." I said, "You need to leave him.
If anyone said that to me, bro, I'm
leaving him." Like all someone has to do
is give me attitude and I'm leaving him,
bro. Like what the [ __ ] You let
somebody say that to you and stay with
them? Are you [ __ ] mad? You think
someone could ever disrespect me like
that and I'll still be with him? No way,
bro. That's that is that's emotional abuse.
Um, and yeah, Grievy, I can't wait until
Wednesday. I can leave this behind me,
bro. You know, this country is You're
going to laugh at this one, Grezy, as
well. I bet this woman, she was 44. She
has one child, right? Which is normal.
Single mom, whatever. 44. How old I told
her I was? I told her I was 30 and she
said I was too young for her.
Uh, no. I just Fishing Frenzy. I put 20
on Fishing Frenzy, lad.
Yep. I'm still going, bro. 100%. 1
million% of my I'm still going, mate.
This ain't no life in England. You're
existing in this country. You ain't
living. That's it.
So yeah, 44 a 30-year-old is too young
for a 44 year old apparently.
Interesting. You learn something new
every day. And yeah, man. It was
constant. It was I've got a boyfriend
constantly. It was constant, mate. But
I'm surprised I even got a number to be
honest and a Facebook. Sad, sad, sad.
Um, it's really sad. It's a depressing
life in this country. I need to go off
tomorrow for like 11 hours as well.
Uh I don't know what I'm going to go
for. Um 2 weeks. I'm going for 2 weeks.
It's really sad. This country is bad, bro.
We'll be out of here soon. Anyways,
Mr. B, it's impossible in this country,
lad. You can't get women in this
country, bro. There was an Indian. She
was like a 10 out of 10. I swear to God,
bro. She's with four guys and four other
women and she said, "Oh, I got a
boyfriend, mate." They said it bare
times, bro, today. I got it loads of times.
Yeah, I got loads of times. I had one
that was speaking to me and apparently
she doesn't give her number out. So,
it's all right, bro. We got it all made,
bro. We got the Xbox. We got the TV.
We're going to Thailand. We're ready for
GTA 6. And I'm done in this country,
bro. I don't give a [ __ ] Even when I
come back, I'm done with it. It's boring now.
It's always the same. Oh, I've got a
boyfriend by people that are brainwashed
by [ __ ] Instagram and Tik Tok. It's
so It's so [ __ ] annoying, bro.
Oh my god.
You see this many pound I lost? Yeah. I
calmed down after like 5 10 minutes.
Didn't bother me. See, I didn't care.
After 10 minutes, I don't really care.
But this women [ __ ] is not normal, bro.
It ain't normal.
It's really not normal, bro.
It will never change ever.
Never. Ever. Ever. Ever. I think there's
too many stuck up [ __ ] in this
country. Oh, I met a gay guy today.
Greasy. Yeah. I met a gay guy. Yeah.
Yeah. He's from Nottingham. Uh typical e.
That's how you know you're [ __ ]
bored, bro. Yeah.
Can't wait until Wednesday. Get me out
of here, mate. Get me [ __ ] out of here. Yeah, man.
Yeah, it's hard, bro.
Looking forward to nice sleep, making
some money tomorrow and then
out of error.
So life for any young person grey.
What a [ __ ] day I've had.
Yeah, I'm still going 100%. No excuses, bro.
This ain't a life, mate, for anyone.
here in England.
The women are terrible. The people are
terrible. Like, it's not even just
women. It's it's it's everything. Like,
the people given us a bad [ __ ] name.
God knows how many times they've gave us
a bad name. They gave London as a bad
name. I don't even want to associate
with these people, bro. You know what I
mean? What the [ __ ]
It's not funny, bro. It's [ __ ]
annoying, bro. They're all NPCs.
Like, I don't understand how these
people can just slag off women. Yeah.
Saying they're hoes and this and that.
That's all along, bro. They're not any
of that stuff. They're just non-playing characters. Just NPCs.
You know what I mean, Grezy? They're
just non-playing characters. What the [ __ ]
Yeah, all NPCs.
Stuck up people.
So many stuck up people in this [ __ ]
country. More so London as well.
Do you want my opinion, Grezy? Uh.
Uh-huh. They're old. [ __ ]
Love it, mate. Love it. Grezy. [ __ ]
love it, mate.
boyfriend. [ __ ] off, mate. I'm sleeping now.
I would, you know, when somebody says to
me, yeah, like, oh, it's an excuse. It's
a nice excuse. I get it. But the thing
that I don't understand is why they
giving excuses, bro. You don't look like
Timmy Elders. You're not [ __ ] ugly.
You're not fat and ugly. That's the whole problem.
You're not any of these things. So,
like, they shouldn't be saying they have
boyfriends and [ __ ] Like, cuz
you ain't, you know what I mean? All
right, that's the thing, bro.
It's impossible this country, bro.
It's sad, bro. I don't know how I
managed to ever get laid.
Bear in mind, these were things like years ago,
but now it's gotten worse.
It's going so much worse. So, so much
I had an American today said she had a
boyfriend. I was like, "You got a boyfriend?"
Really? Wow. So, you left your boyfriend
all the way in America? Brave woman you
are, isn't it? That's some madness,
And then the other one was trying to
take the piss as well. Like, people
really don't understand, bro. Until they
put themselves in this situation, they
will never ever understand.
Bit like YouTube like so.
They're just westernized [ __ ]
That's that's what they are.
Loads of [ __ ] in London though.
Loads of [ __ ] All sort of genders.
They think, "Oh, cuz we got more money
than you. We're better than you, mate."
You know, every single person I meet
you, I tell them, "I've been to
Middlesbr, bro, mate.
povertyridden area. Every other house is
boarded up. Complete [ __ ] Oh, guess
what? I never thought I was better than no one.
People treated me like I was better than
them, but I never thought I was better
than no one, bro. Mad.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] up, bro.
This a sad country.
And I specifically said to the woman as
well to see what she would say, "I'm not
looking for fun. I'm looking for for um dating."
Which is what I actually said to them.
And they still weren't interested. Even
though they were 44 years of age and
apparently a 30-year-old is too young
for them. This country stinks, bro. I'm
not even joking. It's [ __ ] up, man. Yeah.
Yeah. I got I got a boyfriend [ __ ]
today. Like [ __ ] me, bro. 10 times in a
row at least. I don't even know how I
got a number.