Oh, [ __ ] hell, mate.
Just checked to see if it's the same
people at your job. You know, little uh
little uh what's it called? Welfare
check. That's it.
Cuz I'm fat today. Yeah.
Don't really come on here much anymore.
Same repeating people.
That's why you don't really see me on
here. Some people actually have a life
that these people need to get to life.
Yeah, for real. Yeah.
Obviously, I don't go on other people's
channels anymore. So, see if anyone
comes on here
and if someone does come on here, just
see if it's the same people.
Same people every day on YouTube.
Oh, [ __ ] hell.
I'm so tired.
I'm going tomorrow. I haven't been yet.
I'm going tomorrow, matey.
But before I do, I just wanted to see if
it's the same people YouTube. You're the
same person on YouTube. Hey, one minute,
[ __ ] You told me. One second.
Hold on. You told me that about how I
can't get off of YouTube.
Yeah. And you're banned by [ __ ]
Just if you actually go back, you I've
already answered that. You told me that
I can't come off of YouTube, yet you
can't take a day off of YouTube cuz I
was off of YouTube for over a week since
I just answered your question. Yet, I
was live for 2 minutes and you're on
YouTube, mate. Practice what you preach.
You people will never get off of
YouTube. It's your life. Your life is
YouTube. Literally YouTube. You can't
even take a [ __ ] day off of YouTube.
[ __ ] pathetic. And you you come on
here every day talking about other
people, man. Get a grip. And I'm going
tomorrow to answer your question again.
Yeah, there you go, man.
Like I only knew like when I was younger
to be honest with you, bro. Like about
you people projecting like I don't need
to get into like my life details on what
I do, what I don't do, what I don't do.
I would, but there's too many snitches
on here so I don't too many jealous
grasses. I mean, nothing to really be
jealous of. But I mean, these people are
jealous of anyone that's got a life. Cuz
let's face it, bro, they just sit on
YouTube, maybe they're their fat ass,
ain't got a life in their 40s, self
projecting. So, I mean, they'd be
jealous of anyone really, bro, to be honest.
So, yeah. Yeah, that's never going to
happen, mate. That's never going to happen. So,
anyways, how come you people still on
YouTube anyways? Can't get off it. Oh [ __ ]
Why can't you people go off for YouTube?
Oh, [ __ ] today. I'm literally exhausted.
I can't even [ __ ] get out of bed. So,
I thought I'd just talk to some of these mongos
cuz there's not any genuine people on here anymore.
You know, this is [ __ ] community. It's
not even a community.
You know, I've actually got to do a
video. I've been meaning to do a video,
but I just ain't had the time to do it.
I've just been so busy
about people in London and [ __ ] and
[ __ ] like that, but I just ain't got
around to doing it to be honest.
I haven't even had time to even [ __ ]
go out anymore drinking. I don't really
care. I'm [ __ ] off to Why would I to
be honest? I don't really care about it
anymore. I'm not asked.
My whole thing was make money, leave
this country. I'm above it now.
Above it anymore, bro. Really? No.
So [ __ ] tired.
So tired, bro.
It's not even a joke. So yeah,
that's it really.
But yeah, it was going to do it was
going to be like a video about people in London
just complete [ __ ]
I know I deal with them three times a
week, mate. So I'd [ __ ] know [ __ ]
complete [ __ ] But it probably be a [ __ ]
just [ __ ] dick. Yeah.
So anyways, how come you people are
still on YouTube?
Ain't got a life? It's been It's been
nice the past couple of days. I've got a
tan. Even though my skin's kind of like
peeling, but I've got a nice time. Went
for I said I did go for a drink Monday
with someone. Uh, why are you people
still on YouTube?
Self-reflecting away. Self-reflecting
your life away. Oh, bro, that's a
banger. Projecting your life away.
Yeah, projecting your life away. That's
literally what you people do. Project
your life away cuz you're talking about
yourselves. Your little bongo sounds
every day on YouTube.
Literally, man. Do you know what? I was
so tired yesterday. I was actually I was
actually high. I was just laughing at everything.
That's called hard work. That is
something that you people should do.
Hard work. Instead of telling other
people they ain't got a job, why don't
you [ __ ] get a job your [ __ ]
selves? You [ __ ] lazy b idol
[ __ ] that don't know the meaning of
[ __ ] work. Because let me tell you
something now. Yeah. If any of these
people in this community actually
worked, they would have time to come on
here every day self-reflective. Believe
that, bro. Believe that. You know,
they're just 40year-old losers on
benefits that [ __ ] talk about their
fuckingelves every day. Uh I'm I'm I'm
This woman was like, "Yesterday, are you
high?" I said, "No, I'm just high on
life. I'm so tired.
I'm so tired." You thought I was drunk.
I was like, "No, I'm not drunk. I'm just
high on life." You know?
Yeah. Just high on life, man. [ __ ] hell.
Oh man, that's so funny. You are.
See, this is what happens, mate. When
you don't get proper sleep, it starts it
starts affecting your your mental
health, you know. It starts affecting
your mental health, matey. That's what it does. Yeah. Yeah, man.
You thought I died, bro? Why would you
think I died? It's just It's just having
a life. Something that these people need
to get. Nah,
you won't be seeing me again for another
2 3 weeks cuz I'm off tomorrow. And when
I'm back, even then, I still won't be on
YouTube. Nah, it's called having a life, man.
and seeing what and it's called actually
uh having a life and actually working.
You see something that these people
don't do. These people don't do.
Yeah, I have to keep saying that.
Something that these people don't
[ __ ] do. Just sit on their fat asses
every day self-reflecting. Yep. Tomorrow.
And I've been busy the past few days,
past [ __ ] two weeks really. But yeah,
I had a lot of stuff. I haven't even had
time to do anything. So yeah,
haven't been out drinking. Don't I don't
need to do that [ __ ] anymore. I'm
[ __ ] off tomorrow. So why would I care?
I'm so tired, bro.
So so so so tired. [ __ ]
That's why I'm resting today for to uh
wanted to try and make some money today.
But unfortunately, I'm too tired and I
have to deal with [ __ ] So many
You don't need to know what what part
I'm visiting. You don't need to know that.
But just know that the country is Thailand.
You don't need to know that. I've seen
you on Large A channel as well. Nice try
though, buddy. You need to wake up
pretty early to fool me.
You're not going to know. And you're
giving off Lewisville Slugger vibes,
which actually I saw last week on Monty
Man's Lewis Phil Slugger. Get alive, you
little [ __ ] That's another thing. Yeah,
Lewis Phil Slugger. Yeah, bro. You're
asking. You're asking because you want
to start calling up [ __ ] hotels and
trying to get people [ __ ] lit. Come
on, man. Use your brain cells. Like,
even if you're you are only asking, you
know what's going to happen if someone
says exactly where they're going. This
has been going on for years now, bro.
Like, come on, man. You know what will
happen if I if I say where.
You know what happens? You know the
score. You know the drill with these
little [ __ ] bongos.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And guess what? These
sados will call every single one of them.
Yeah. You know how many hotel rooms
there were in Newcastle? A lot of hotel rooms. So, but yeah.
So, yeah. No one's died or anything. I
just can't be bothered with this [ __ ]
anymore. It's [ __ ] boring.
It's [ __ ] boring. It's only cuz I've
had a day off today and I'm really
really tired. I thought let me just come on here
cuz I got nothing else to do today.
Bit like these people
these people's lives every [ __ ] day
really in it. Nothing to do. Come on YouTube self-relect.
But they self-relect, don't they? Yeah,
that's what makes me laugh. If these
people are actually working, right, they
wouldn't have the time to come on here
doing what they do every day.
They wouldn't. They [ __ ] would not,
bro. Their mind would be so [ __ ] from
work. Yeah, we all know. But listen, you
you know, we we you people are retards.
You don't know anything. The only thing
you people know what to do is to come on
YouTube and self-reflect behind the
keyboard every day. Like you, we are
spastics. That's we is the [ __ ] crew
that can't live without YouTube. Look at
this, bro. I was off of YouTube for over
a week. I guarantee you are going law
days right now and it's the same
spastics every single day on YouTube. We
the spastics don't know anything but
your own [ __ ] lives. Oh yeah, you bully
me so much, bro. You keep telling
yourself that. Yeah. Yeah, bro. You
bully me so much. Yeah, bro. Calm down.
You bully me. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Bro, any
bullying that you think you do on the
internet, you have been bullied. Every
time you try to leave your house, you
get bullied. You get bullied in real
life. Sad little bastard. Now go. And
here's what how I'm going to leave this
now. You know where I live. So if you if
you got anything to say, you can come
and say it to my face. Bye-bye now.
Simple, bro. That's how you deal with
these little mongos, these little 40-year-old virgins. Simple, bro.
I don't uh This is why I don't really
come on here anymore cuz it's just the
same atmosphere, the same repeating
people, same spastics
that can't get off of YouTube. I know
I've said that about 10 times, but it's
the truth. They can't come off of It's
like, think about it like this. Yeah.
They don't make money from this YouTube.
They've got no content on their channel,
yet somehow they're on YouTube all day,
every day. Why would somebody with this
job, with all this money, be on YouTube
all day, every day? It's because they've
got [ __ ] all. YouTube is their life.
They're they're Mr. Lone. They're Mr.
Lonely. Do you not understand? These
people are Mr. Lonely. They ain't got no
life, bro. They The only thing that they
have is talking to each other on YouTube every day.
It's like I got an email from LT. I need
to speak to you ASAP. Bro, sorry I
wasn't ignoring you. I was busy. But
bro, you don't need to talk to me
because I don't care about this place.
It's the same with Jane. She was
emailing me. I don't care about this
place, bro. No one needs to speak to me
about this [ __ ] community. We've
already wasted [ __ ] enough years on
this [ __ ] with these retards. You
know what I'm saying? Like, [ __ ] hell.
We've already wasted enough years.
All these [ __ ] retards, bro. There's
nothing to [ __ ] talk about. You know
what I mean?
[ __ ] retards. They are.
That's what they are, bro.
Little self-reflecting little bully
victims. That's what they are.
self reflection bully victims
that get bullied in real life. They're
sados, bro. Real real sados.
Yeah, man. They bounce off of other
people's life. Like they just sit around
all day. Yeah. Waiting for people to spill information.
So then Nathan was saying, "Oh, that
you know what I'm saying?"
But to summarize, they're basically just
40 year olds that are just 40-year-old
losers that have failed in life.
No one on here is my age anymore. No,
nah man. You are the spastics. No, no,
no. You are the spastics. You, LJ, all
of the people on on his channel. No, no,
no. You are the real spastics and you
can't come off of YouTube. You're so
spasticated and you can't even come off
of YouTube for one day. You're so
spasticated that you throw the same
insults every day. But no, no, to be
honest with you, you're not actually
spasticated for that because you're just
talking about yourselves. So really, you
don't really have anything off to go by.
Sorry, I take that back. Because when
you talk about skin, no job, you're just
talking about you're just talking about
yourselves. So actually, it's not even
like a low IQ thing cuz you're just self
you're just self projected really, you
know? Like, bro, listen, listen, listen.
That's all right, but you can never go
at us in real life. That's the
difference. You can go at me online, but
you can't go at me in real life. So,
there's no point. There's no point if
you can only hide behind the keyboard.
Like, no, no, no. Let me tell you what's
weird is is is LJ and his followers. You
people are the weirdos. You sit on
YouTube all day repeating yourselves.
That's what you call spastics. You're
all in your 40s. Yeah. All sat on
YouTube repeating yourselves every day.
That's what you call spasticated. If you
go in the urban dictionary, go to a
library right now, right? Yeah. But the
thing is, you people don't bully no one.
You you are the 40year-old bully
victims. Like that's that's the truth of
it though is you are the ones that get
bullied. That's why you are the
40year-old losers that repeat yourself
every day on YouTube because you get
bullied every day. Like you people don't
even leave your house due to the
bullying. And you want to say that you
because you repeat yourself on YouTube
every day, you bully people. No, you
people have always been bullied. That's
why the the word bullying is stuck in
your head because it's what you've
experienced. And again, you're 40 year
olds on YouTube. And you want to talk
about spastics. 40y olds that can't get
off of YouTube. Ask your mom. Ask any
[ __ ] adult. Yeah. Do you think it's
normal that a bunch of old men on
YouTube that can't get off of it is
normal or is it spasticated? Like I will
ask anybody, bro. I'm high on life. The
[ __ ] [ __ ] 40year-old on YouTube.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I Okay, bro. Okay.
Yeah. Yeah. Bro, you're boring now.
Listen, stop. Stop deflecting. You
people of 40year-old spastics on YouTube
every day that can't get off of it. Look
closer to home, bro. This is your life.
Listen, listen, listen, listen, bro.
This YouTube is your life. It's all you
have. I've already proven it. I've
already proven it that I can come off of
YouTube. Yeah. And you know what I've
seen? I've seen you 40-year-old spastics
that can't get off of YouTube that ain't
got a life. I'm saying what I've seen.
You spastics every day on YouTube that
can't get off of it. I've seen it. I've
seen it every day in the past. You
little lowife skin losers that can't get
off of YouTube because you don't have
anything. Am I lying? No. Am I lying?
No. And I'm not going to get into that L
thing anymore cuz it's not going to
work. I've explained it millions and
millions and millions times again. And
that's another thing you people do in
this community. You're stuck in the past
because you're repeating spastics.
Yeah. But no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no. Listen, listen. You people
are not bullies. Listen, listen, listen.
I will give you my address right now and
you can come and bully me. Okay, bro.
Bullies. You want to know the definition
of bullying, right? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I
will give you my address and I will give
you every chance to come and bully me to
my face. 40year-old [ __ ] I will tell
you about your mom. Okay. Listen,
listen. I'll show you how much of a
bully you are. You suck your mom. Your
dad's a [ __ ] nons and you know where
I live. Are you going to come and do
anything to me? I will stay in this
house all day. I've [ __ ] told you
about your mom. She's a smelly [ __ ] with
a smelly fanny. Your dad's a [ __ ]
nons and I'm telling you to come on my
door and I will wait on this door. Your
mom has got a smelly fanny and your
dad's a nons. Are you going to come on
my door and bully me? The answer is no.
Exactly. Everybody knows where I live
and you're banned. And this is exactly
why I don't come here no more because
it's the same spasticated brain dead
[ __ ] people. Everybody knows where I
live in London. Everybody knows. I've
been doxed about a million times. So if
you're not going to back up your talk,
bro, stop being like them [ __ ]
cyclists in London, bro. Please stop
being like these cyclists in London. I
just said that your dad's a nod and your
mom's got a smelly fat fanny.
You know what I'm saying? Yep. You're
talking about yourself again. Again.
Stop talking about yourself, bro. Like I
said, if you've got anything to say, you
have my address. I'm telling you to come
on my address. I'm inviting you to come
round. So, I mean, bro, stop being like
them cyclists in London.
They're [ __ ] retards, man. They're
such bully victims. Like, think of it.
Yeah. They have to sit on YouTube all
day in their 40s repeating themselves
because they get bullied that much. They
can't even leave their house without
getting bullied. These people are the
true bully victims. They're losers.
They've been bullied their whole life.
That's why they come on YouTube trying
to bully other people cuz they are the
real bully victims.
They're proper spastics. I've just told
him about his mom and his dad and they
know where I live and they're not doing
nothing. It's embarrassing, bro.
Seriously, stop being like them cyclists
in London. Stop starting something that
you can't finish.
Stop starting something that you can't finish.
You know, it's it's embarrassing.
You know, I was having this conversation
the other day with these [ __ ] with
someone about these [ __ ] cyclists in [ __ ] London.
Yeah. Stop starting something you can't finish.
It's embarrassing. That's a real real
real real embarrassment. It's starting
something that you can't finish. It's so embarrassing.
It's like the whole Morgan thing. I
started it what a month ago and trust
me, I would have damn well finished it
if they reply back. It's embarrassing, bro.
I don't understand why people do that.
Start stuff they can't finish. It's so embarrassing.
You know where I live, buddy. You
already know where I live. Bye-bye.
Look, he just made another account to
get blocked again. Loser. 40-year-old
loser. I told you, bro. I told you what
these people are about. 40year-old self-proing
skin losers. I told you, bro. I told you
what they're about.
I told you [ __ ] what they're about,
bro. 40year-old losers. Just like the
bomb. They've got nothing in their life
for YouTube. I've been told you, bro.
[ __ ] absolute bully victims in real
life. Absolute bully victims. This is
why I don't come on here anymore, bro.
Oh, I'm going up there tomorrow. It's
going to be so fun. These people really
are the true bully victims. They've been
bullied their whole life. That's why I
have to come. I'm high on life again. I
need to tell this woman I'm high on life again.
cuz she said, "Are you high?" I said,
"Nah, man. It's just lack of sleep and
shit." I feel sorry for these people,
bro. I really do feel so sorry for these people.
I really, really do feel sorry for these people.
Their lives are their lives are [ __ ] finished, bro.
Their lives are over. Awesome.
Bye-bye. Up front now. No live. You
ain't going to lie to YouTube. Anyway,
we're going to keep We're going to
ignore these spastics now. Anyways, I
think we've g them enough time.
You claim that you're in North London.
That's a bit strange, is it? Because uh
didn't you have my address for like how
many years? And what? You lived in North
London and you never ever came to
Stratford. Well, you just gave yourself
away there, didn't you? Get alive. Get over YouTube.
Stop bullying yourself. Stop making
accounts to get blocked. It's
embarrassing now, man.
It's really, really embarrassing now.
I smoke about this guy's dad and his
[ __ ] mom. Stop starting something
that you can't finish.
It's embarrassing, bro.
Stop being a London cyclist. Stop being
a dickheading people in London.
Why is that all [ __ ] Yeah, man.
Yeah, these people claim that they work
and these people don't [ __ ] work.
These people don't know the meaning of
[ __ ] work. They just sit online all day self-reflective.
That's all they do. These people don't work, man.
They're just sad bastards.
I don't get that, bro.
Three accounts to get blocked. [ __ ] hell.
What a sad bastard.
make a cup of [ __ ] in a minute, I think.
So, anyways, you didn't answer my
question, man. Why can't you people get
off of YouTube? Oh, [ __ ]
Uh, it's like bullying a kid. But the
difference is you people don't bully no
one. You never have and you never will.
You bully yourselves. You embarrass
yourselves on YouTube every day. Just
like when somebody goes on a chat. Yeah.
And you all self project them. Nah, bro.
People bully yourselves. You embarrass
yourselves. Really? just come on YouTube
every day embarrassing yourselves
like the little spastics that you are.
Hate to say it, but it's truth, man.
And none of you's work either. None of
you's [ __ ] work. Not any of you. So, yeah.
I'm [ __ ] knocking, man.
Yeah, I want to make a proper cut now as
well. Second thing Yeah, man. Oh, brother. [Applause]
You sure got know about Morgan obsessed virgin boy? Bye-bye.
You're not getting my attention.
Mother, you're still obsessed with my
sloppy seconds, little lad.
You're still obsessed with my sloppy
seconds. That can only be virgin boy. No
one else cuz there's only one person
that's obsess obsessed with my sloppy
seconds, you know, due to him still
being the biggest virgin going. So, it's
got to be those virgin bike. He now and
now mentions Morgan
the all of all of this um but the virgin
which we not mentioned any names. Sorry
Timmy I've uh this lack of sleep has
been uh been um [ __ ] with my mental
health a little bit you know. I've been
very very tired
you know. Sorry about that buddy. I've
been working really hard lately Timmy.
So uh yeah. Oh, that that looks like
virgin boy. Morgan winning in life. Oh,
that's definitely virgin boy. That's
definitely virgin boy. Want to be London Virgin boy.
Does it sound like I'm talking about you, Timmy?
[ __ ] hell. Now I'm off tomorrow, mate.
I've just been so busy, Daz, with
[ __ ] work and [ __ ] I haven't I don't
really come here anymore. It's boring
and [ __ ] So,
um I'm off tomorrow, bro. Saturday.
Three people already asked me that
question. I've got it all packed. I'm gone, bro.
And to be honest, I haven't really
really been going out, bro. Like
drinking and [ __ ] Can't be [ __ ] I'm just exhausted.
[ __ ] exhausted, bro.
Yeah, man. Very exhausted. I haven't
even had time to go to the [ __ ] gym,
to be honest.
Only like half a day where I'm not doing anything.
Yeah. Do you know what, Daz? Yeah. So
many [ __ ] in London, bro. Like, cuz
obviously like where I go to work and I
have to deal with these, bro. There's so
many [ __ ] in London. It's not even
There's so many [ __ ] I've met more
[ __ ] than I've actually seen my own
dick. There's so many [ __ ] It's
It's all It's everything, bro. It's not
even just the [ __ ] women. It's not
even just the women. It's it's it's
everything. Obviously, the women the
women are a big part of it about why
this country is [ __ ] up, but it's not
that. It's it's many different things, bro.
Like, it's just the people. But I don't
know if you've ever been to London.
But you know what? And this is how you
know. Yeah. And guys, I'll tell you a
story. Yeah. Uh so two weeks ago, bro, I
was bored. Yeah. So I was just cycling
around and I wasn't anywhere near
hitting anyone. and I wasn't near anyone
like causing an injury. And then this
[ __ ] woman was like, "Oh, you're
supposed to be there." I said, "I'll go
where I want. Thank you very much. It's
none of your business." And then she
started like swearing. And she was with
another guy like I said, "Come back and
say to my face. I'll par the bike." I
said, "Stop walking away. Yeah, you
started something. Now finish it." This
is what they do in London. They like to
n people's business because I get it.
No, but I get it. I understand. Yeah.
you know, people have bad days and
whatever or whatever the reason they
want to act like that. I mean, we all
have anger problems, but finish it.
Don't walk away. Like, don't run away.
This is what I don't understand. Don't
start something and then run away.
It's stupid, bro. Like, what's the
what's the point of starting something
you can't finish? It's boring, bro.
Um, and then but then the thing is is
that when you come across these Chinese
people, you never get these problems.
They're so nice, bro. They're so [ __ ]
nice. Like this is the thing and I've
experienced it a lot. And that's how you
know it is this country, bro. Cuz you've
not even left this country. And as soon
as you start dealing with Asian people,
Chinese people, they're the nicest
people you ever meet. And then you get
these stinking people in this country
want to [ __ ] get involved with
people's business, but then want to
[ __ ] walk away. Don't walk away.
You know what I'm saying? What's the
point of walking away? Just little
things like that is just
they're just the whole attitude.
You know what I'm saying, bro? People
have bad days. You know, people piss
people off, but [ __ ] don't don't it's
none of your business where I'm riding.
You know what I'm saying? You know,
this country annoys me, bro. It's one of
the reasons I don't go out in it
anymore, like drinking. I don't I I went
out Monday with my sister and that's
about it, bro. Just for a few drinks,
not not to approach or anything. I can't
be annoyed with it anymore, bro. I'm
busy with so many other things. So,
not asked with it. I hate it, bro. I
hate all of it. I hate everything about
this country. It's why I'm getting away
from it. I'm going tomorrow.
You know what's so [ __ ] up about this
country, Joe? Yeah, I'm going tomorrow.
Yeah, I said I was going Wednesday, but
I'm actually going tomorrow. Trust me,
on my mom's life, I'm going tomorrow.
Of course, I said I was going to go
[ __ ] Wednesday. Yeah, to fool you.
But I'm actually going tomorrow, 100%.
I've not even been drinking in this
country. I've not been approaching
anyone. All I've been doing is work flat out.
Extra money to get out of this [ __ ]
country. No one can [ __ ] tell me
nothing. Now this country is stinking,
bro. I hate this country, bro. I [ __ ]
hate this country.
I'm going tomorrow. Watch. 100%, bro.
Yeah. I can't stand the the the
the people in this country, bro. They
like to start stuff they can't finish. Yeah.
He's like, he's two skin up. Talking
about yourself again.
You're still obsessed with uh still
obsessed with Morgan. You're still
obsessed with my copy seconds. Wow. Bro,
do you know what happened the other day,
Joe? Yeah. I was cycling
and u this stupid [ __ ] woman. I'll give
you two examples. Yeah. Of what's [ __ ]
up with this country.
She said she said, "Bro, stop asking me
stupid questions. I'm going tomorrow.
believe it or don't believe it. And you
know when I could understand if you're
almost knocking somebody over or whatever,
you know, or maybe knocking their child
over and she's like, "Oh, well, you
should be there." I said, "I'll go where
I want." I just looked at her. I said,
"I'll go where I want. Who are you? PC
[ __ ] prod or something." And then she
starts running up her mouth. Bear in
mind, she was with another guy. I said,
"Why don't you come back and say it to
my face and stop walking away?" I
literally parked up the bike. I said,
"If you got something to say, come
back." What's the [ __ ] point, bro?
Why do they start stuff they can't
finish in this stupid country? They have
a bad day. Yes, everyone has a bad day
and we like to start things, you know?
Some people have anger problems or some
people that people can only take so
much. I get it and I get like starting
because I've wanted to do it, but I will
finish what I start. Don't walk away
like a little [ __ ] You've got a guy
next to you. You You've started. Yeah.
You wanted to try and get me in a bad
mood. Now I'm in a bad mood. Come back.
You know, [ __ ] [ __ ] And then
I was trying to lift this bike up of a
ramp that broke. Right. You're never
going to believe this, bro. I'm going tomorrow.
Yeah. You're never going to believe
this. There was this There was this
Chinese couple. Yeah. I was trying to I
was trying to push the bike up the
[ __ ] um some broke a broken plastic
thing and it was a nightmare. They
literally stood on it, helped me, and
then they said, "Take care." And I was
like, "Bro, if this I'm already getting
a taste for what Asian people actually
like. They're so nice." And then you get
people in here, they're [ __ ]
[ __ ] And then you get people in
[ __ ] London and they're completing
[ __ ] [ __ ] that start [ __ ] they
can't finish. [ __ ] losers.
Like, bro, Chinese people are the most
nicest people you'll ever meet. They're
either very nice or they just keep
themselves to themselves. They don't
bother anyone. But then you get [ __ ]
[ __ ] in this country, [ __ ] women
and men that have had a bad day. They
like to try and start on people, then
run away like a little [ __ ] What the
So many [ __ ] in London
that need a harsh reality check, bro.
Damn. [ __ ] I would have threw that bike
in that [ __ ] jaw, bro. I'm not even
joking. Yeah. Don't start [ __ ] you can't
finish. Don't Don't Don't worry about
where I'm cycling. I'm not almost coming
into you. I'm not crashing you. Don't
worry. You're not the law. Don't worry
about what I'm doing. You know what I'm saying?
They're all nice. Anyone from Asia is
nice. Anywhere from Asia is nice. And I
can give you many, many more examples.
You don't get these problems with Asian people
or anyone from a third world country.
It's just these Londoners are [ __ ]
I hate them, bro. They give us a bad
name. They really give us a bad name.
They start because they've had a bad day
or their life [ __ ] but then they don't
want to finish it. They want to put you
in a bad mood and then run away. What the [ __ ]
So many [ __ ] in this country, bro.
It's like NPC [ __ ] in in in
at this point, bro. It's just embarrassing.
They're [ __ ] absolute [ __ ] I
don't even go out anymore, bro. I don't
even drink anymore, bro. I can't be
annoyed with it.
It's boring as [ __ ]
I've even I I haven't even had times to
[ __ ] I haven't even had time to check my messages.
And then a Chinese couple, I'll take
care. Imagine people in England was that nice. Wow.
Why would I become a Muslim when I don't
believe in their religion and I eat
pork? Stop asking stupid questions, bro.
But yeah, I hate England. Like, you get the
odd one. That's all right. But nah,
they're proper [ __ ] in this country.
proper proper [ __ ]
But yeah, LT, bro, there's nothing to
talk about, bro. Um, you know, doing
this [ __ ] for years. I mean, I had Jane
Jane was emailing me. Why are these
people emailing me? I'm not on here
anymore. I'm only on here today cuz I've
got a day off and I'm [ __ ]
Yeah, because they're not proper
Muslims. Yeah, because they're Muslim by
name, but they're not actual Muslims. If
a Muslim does what a Muslim is not
supposed to do, they're not a Muslim.
That's the whole point. They're not a Muslim.
And no, lots of um Muslims don't lots of
most Muslims don't eat pork. If they
they might gamble, they might drink, but
they don't touch pork.
But yeah, that's because they're not
Muslims. They're Muslim by name.
That's the difference.
These people that are English but
Pakistan heritage and they're not
Muslim. I know Muslim. I have Muslim
friends and mate, they do not touch
pork. They do not touch alcohol. They do
not eat stuff that's not halal. They're
very very strict about it, mate. Trust
me, they're not Muslims. The people that
you're talking about are not Muslims.
So, no, I wouldn't um
wouldn't convert to answer your question. No. But yeah,
but yeah, that's why sometimes I can't
be bothered to go out and make money cuz
I have to deal with [ __ ] and [ __ ]
It's horrible, bro. Horrible.
But I still do anyways. So yeah,
it's a good thing to be honest because
you don't have time to think about these
[ __ ] women anymore. I don't even care
about them anymore either way.
But just it's boring, bro. It's so
boring. I don't even have time to think
about it anymore. It's a good thing, really, man.
I even I even had I haven't even had a I
haven't even had time to moan about it.
I haven't even had time to do a video
about it, which I was meaning to, but I
just don't have time,
you know? When do I get time to [ __ ]
But I do want to do a video still about
this whole thing when I get back about
the whole dating thing and like what
people are like and [ __ ] It's It's a
really depressing country.
It really is a depressing depressing
country to be in.
And the fact that like people give their
number and then reply then stop
replying. It's just so weird how like
you can't get any kind of relation in
this country. It's [ __ ] up. It's all But yeah.
Yeah, boy. It's good. Yeah, man.
You must be depressed. Jo ain't working every day.
But these people on here don't work. N
there's no way they work because if they
worked, they wouldn't have time to do
what they do every day on here. And I'm
I'm living proof of it. There's
something not right with what they're
saying, bro. There's something not right
with what they're saying. They're saying
that they work and they have money, but
then they're on here every day hating.
It's not looking right, bro. It's not looking right.
You know, so there's there's something
not right there, bro. Cuz they're
claiming that they work and they earn
all this money, but then on the other
hand, they're on YouTube. Maybe they
hated. It's not looking right, bro. Bye-bye, Virgin.
Um, yeah, I'm [ __ ] I'm [ __ ] I'm
tired as [ __ ] Joe, bro. I've been
[ __ ] [ __ ] working my ass off, but
I'm tired, bro. I'm tired. I wanted to
make some money today. I could have made
some good money today, but I'm too
tired. But there's even there there's
tomorrow to be honest. But it's a good
thing to be honest because,
you know, you can say you've made your
own money. I've made my own money and um
and I don't care about the women
anymore. I don't care about any [ __ ]
like that anymore, bro, cuz I don't have
time for it.
But it is tiring. It is tiring,
you know. It is [ __ ] tiring. Um,
but I'm going to have to reduce the
days, I think, because Yeah,
I haven't even had time to go to the
[ __ ] gym because of it,
you know? So, cuz I was building up like
a good body, but I've just been so Yeah.
[ __ ] basically. So,
but it's good, you know. It is good. Yeah. [ __ ]
I don't know what I'm going to eat today. Yeah.
But these people on here don't work.
These people that hate on here, they
don't work, bro. Trust me, they don't work. Yeah.
Imagine virgin boy trying to work Joe.
It [ __ ] kill him, mate. It would
[ __ ] kill him. It would kill that virgin.
One day of work would one day of work
would actually kill that virgin. If I
told you what I've done in the past two
weeks, bro, you wouldn't even believe
it, mate. So, there'd be no point even
saying it. So that that would actually
kill that virgin.
[ __ ] kill him.
I'm telling you it would [ __ ] virgin. Oh
no, I generally would, bro.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
I'm going to try and start making money
from the football maybe
um on in August.
kind of. I can clear £100 in a day if I
do enough hours. I can clear like 100 in
a day, but I'll be fat by the end of the day. So, bro,
yeah, maybe 110 maybe, but yeah. Yeah, bro. So, yeah.
Yeah, but it's enough. It's enough, bro. It's enough.
So, most I mean, most jobs are not even
paying that in a day. I mean, unless
you've got a trade. I mean, a bartender
is not getting [ __ ] £100 a day in
London. Wait, let me calculate the
hours. No, no, no, no, no. So,
so bro, bartenders are not getting £300
a day. [ __ ] people working in
restaurants or a normal job that's not a
trade is not getting £200 a day, bro. So,
yeah. And obviously, you're not paying
rent as well. So,
that's the whole point of it.
So, I mean, yeah. So, that's it.
It's on top of other money that you're
getting is the whole point of doing it.
No point trying to explain it, bro. You
can't live solely on a [ __ ] £100 a
day. No, but I mean most jobs in London
are not paying1 150 pound a day.
Like [ __ ] on it. Probably not even
construction to be honest. So, so yeah,
that's good, bro. Hey, Mom.
Now, how much are you supposed to be
[ __ ] earning a day? What? £500.
Get real, grunt, buddy.
Yeah, it depends on the day, depends how
busy it is.
I mean, if you even if you even if you
done a couple of hours Yeah. and you
done like 3 4 days a week, that's like a
night out in it. [Music]
So that's like it's like a night out in it.
Guess it pays for like a night out,
but not really cuz if you done two days,
say you done two days, you get like one
180 200 that's like a night out. So it
depends how you look at it really.
That's what or like a day out or
whatever you whatever it is it Yeah.
No, you don't get taxed.
You don't get taxed, buddy.
Think 3K You think 3K a month is a lot?
You think 3K a month is a lot, bro? Come on, man.
It's not before tax cuz I've not got taxed.
I didn't get taxed. I've been paid about
six times and I've not been taxed. So,
I didn't get taxed.
Oh yeah, I haven't been taxed
and I've been paid about five, six times. So, but anyways,
that's it, bro. So, yeah, man. Um, but yeah,
could you imagine being a [ __ ]
bartender, bro? [ __ ] that.
Absolutely [ __ ] that. Could you imagine
being a [ __ ] bartender?
Could you imagine that, bro? [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] that, bro.
absolutely [ __ ] up, man.
There's no ways to make money now.
There's no ways to really make money
now. There's no money in the gambling industry.
Like, there's no money. There's no ways
to make money now.
What I can see anyways. But yeah,
no, not really. Even if you got an SIA
badge, they still need to give you
shifts. That cost 3005, sorry, £500.
Then you got to get given shifts and you
might not be given shifts and no. So
there's no way really nowadays to make
money. Not like they used to be.
Not like they used to be. No,
not at all. At all.
Not at all at all. Yeah,
but at least we'll never be skin that
virgin with a rat face. Oh, that's the main thing.
Have you ever heard of um separate account, matey?
Yeah. You ever heard of it? You ever
heard of it, matey?
Yeah. It's hard nowadays, bro.
But it doesn't matter how much you earn.
Something's better than nothing, is it?
Uh, something's better than nothing.
We're just talking about [ __ ] working. Really?
No. Yeah, we're sending it tomorrow.
We're leaving this country. Well, I'm
Oh, Joe. Boring. Listen, bro. I don't
suffer with anxiety, so you saying this
stuff to me is not going to bother me
one little bit. I know you're less of a
troll than most of these people, but
bro, you're saying this to the wrong
person because I don't have anxiety like
LJ and these people. So, you're saying
it you're saying all this stuff to the wrong person.
You You're saying it to the wrong
person, bro. Like, seriously. Like,
you're not going to put any kind of
fear, any kind of anxiety into me. Like, bro, seriously.
And I'm going to Thailand.
That's where I'm going. Yeah.
Well, put it this way, Joe. If you have
no bills, Yeah. and you have 1.3K for
the month. Say you paid all your bills
and everything and you have 1.3K left
for the month. Do you think that's a lot?
Yeah, bro. I'm going to go to prison.
Yeah, bro. Yeah. Yeah.
Put it that way, right? Say someone gets
paid. Yeah. There you go, bro. So that's basically,
bro, I would love to tell you
everything, but there's too many grasses
on here, and I don't want people know my
business. It's as simple as that. I just
don't want people knowing my business.
It's simple as that.
No, I'm not on big money, bro. I wish I
was on big money. If I was on big money,
I wouldn't have to be [ __ ] working
[ __ ] three times a [ __ ] week. But
I plan to give up. I do plan to give up.
I'm just going to try to earn some money
and then get used to the living off that
money cuz yeah I don't even though it's
a good it's good it's good it has its
pros as well but I can never do anything
like security and that [ __ ] that no way
am I doing that
but with security it's easier in a way
cuz all you got to do is stand
with other jobs you need to be focused 24/7
and you just can't do every day. So, like,
but yeah, it'll be I'd love to tell you
like loads of things, bro.
Nope. I'm not doing that either.
Nope. It's not even that, bro. It's not
even that. And even if it was that, I
wouldn't tell you anyways. But no, I
swear my mom's life it's not even that. So,
nope. It's not even that though.
Um, but yeah,
it's not even that.
And I wouldn't even tell you what it was
because there's too many glasses on this community.
So, but you I swear my mom's life it's
not that. I can swear my mom's life is
not security. Don't think I say little
things so you get the clues that you
think it is, but it's not, you know.
It's like these little spastics. Say
right now I just told you, "Oh, I've got
an SIA SI SIA badge and I do security."
All of these people that's been telling
you to get a job for years that don't
have a job themselves, what are they
going to turn around and do? They're
going to report you to get your license revoked. So,
nah, bro. It's not not even close.
Maybe if you get it right, I'll actually
tell you, but it's not. So, try again.
And tax don't come out every month.
You are riding, bro. I said I rode on a
bike two weeks ago. Yeah. I rode around
London. Yeah. Once. That's what I done.
Yeah. I done it once. Yeah,
but it's not that. So, try again. Yeah, man. [Music]
It's really really not that. And it's
not security either. So, yeah, bro.
All right. Do you remember Joe? 1K a
month is decent. That's a decent amount
of money. 1K a month. You remember that,
Joe? Do you remember that, Joe? You
remember that? 1K a month is decent.
It's decent amount of money. It's decent
for doing [ __ ] all.
It's decent for doing [ __ ] all.
Ah, it's decent, mate. No, decent money
a month is maybe like for a single person average
maybe one point
maybe 1.6 1.8
I think if you got 1.6 1.8 and all your
bills are paid I think. Yeah.
Yeah. 1.6 1.8
after all your bills paid. I think.
Yeah, that's that's like an a that's
that's that's decent. Yeah,
after all your bills are paid though.
So, you might think, Joe, oh yeah, if
you get £10 an hour, it's [ __ ] But you
don't understand if somebody can work
and pay all their bills and they have
all the rest of the money to themselves.
You don't understand it because you only
see it from your point of view. You see,
oh 100 pound a day is nothing. Or if you
got there were some days I made £80,
some days I made £90. Oh, that's
nothing. But if it pays if three of them
paid all of your bills and you'd have to
fork out of your own money, it does make
sense if somebody was doing it 2 days a
week, but you just see it as, oh, well,
it's less than what most people get. So,
you don't see it the way
other people see it or I see it. though.
You know, if I could [ __ ] make 90 100
pound today, I'd be laughing, bro. So,
the whole point of certain things or or
extra income, it's not as a main income.
That's the that's the whole point of it.
It's not as a main income. You can't do
them things as a main income. You understand? So yeah,
even £10 an hour is good really if it's
just extra income.
Shame it wasn't easy. It
got £60 I forgot to put in the bank. Yeah.
Why is it for a certain someone bro?
Yeah, but say book stop I wanted to do
go to America. Yeah.
Example, I could do it I could do it like probably
3K a month. You could do it in one month
without doing probably like two and a
half months maybe.
Maybe two and two and a half months.
Yeah, probably two and a half months.
Yeah, you could probably do it about
America. You could probably do like two
and a half months.
I'd love to tell you everything, bro,
but I just can't.
We can share each other's lives, but you
can't on this community, bro. Too many
grasses, giving too many people ammo.
If you knew everything, it would make sense.
But you don't know any you don't know
anything. That's why it doesn't make
sense to you, you know, because you
don't know anything about like the
situation. So, yeah.
So, it wouldn't make sense to you.
Yeah, that's good, bro. But that's your
main income. But what I'm trying to say
to you is that's that's good, but that's
your main income.
So, that's your main income. You see,
that's the difference.
When somebody gets £10 an hour, it's not
their main income. It's like when
someone sells weed, it's not their main income.
There's something called a side hustle
and there's something called a side side hustle. Yeah,
you might see it as, oh yeah, this that
and the other, this, that, and the
other. I calculated it yesterday
how much I earn in just them few days.
is I calculated it up and it was about £350
that I never had. That I never had
and my bills don't even come to that. So
that's money I never had. So
trust me, it does make sense. It might
not make sense to you, but it does to me.
But yeah, it's better than nothing.
Anyways, you're not going to believe
this. Anyways, you know my one of my
friends. Yeah, I know loads and loads of
people. When he first come here, you
don't know how much he was working for
an hour, do you? I actually said to him
a few times, "No, you're lying. You're
chatting [ __ ] in it." I was like,
"You're chatting [ __ ] in it. You're
chatting proper shit." He's like, "No,
no, mate." He was being paid £1 an hour.
Yep. He was being paid1 pound a [ __ ]
hour for working in a [ __ ] shop.
I actually thought he was chatting [ __ ]
When he first said that to me, I'm not
going to lie. I thought he was chatting wank.
Yeah, he was being paid £1 an hour, bro.
What the [ __ ] Anyways, £350 that you never had.
It's It's extra money, is it? But
say like I stayed in this country,
right? Say you stay in this country,
right? Say for example, you stay in this
country when you come back. Yeah. And
then you do you work two days a week and
you made let's just say in 2 days you
made 150 or you made 180 or you made
200. That's enough to go out drinking with.
So it does it does make sense.
Even though it doesn't get paid as much
as what you're getting paid,
like what you're getting paid, like it's
it does make sense, but it makes a lot of sense. Yeah,
just low unfortunately, but
yeah, he got paid£1 an hour. Yep.
I need to pay the gym and then I need to
pay my phone bill and I don't want that
coming out of my own money. You understand? So
I don't want that [ __ ] coming out of my
own money and also you can and also you
can save with it as well because think
of it like this. Yeah. Say you was
working and you was getting 5060 pound
you was getting 50 60 pound a day and
you worked every other day. You could
easily save so much money in a month.
Doesn't matter how much money you were earning.
You could save a lot of money in a month.
A lot of money in a month.
You know, even if you was earning 50, 60
a day, you have days out and do other
things with it. That's what you'd have
to be doing if you were saving to go on
holiday. You'd have to be doing that.
You either do that or you [ __ ] rent
or you rent houses is the only way. So yeah,
no other way, buddy. AR
a grand a month is decent, but is it
really decent though, Joe? Nah.
Nah, it's not decent, bro. It's [ __ ]
That is proper [ __ ] money, bro.
Everything I do is legal.
Nope. Everything I do is legal. Everything.
There's not one bit of criminality,
mate. If it mate, if I was doing
criminality, I wouldn't be so [ __ ]
Yeah. For [ __ ] 3 4 days. If If I was
doing criminality, mate.
Nothing I do is illegal. Not one single
thing I do is illegal. I [ __ ] wish it was. But yeah,
but it doesn't matter if it's a few
hours or loads of hours. It's extra money, bro. So So
yeah, but look at all them barber shops.
They don't declare tax.
They don't declare tax. So,
you won't go to prison. Don't be [ __ ] stupid.
Yeah, maybe that's not a bit Maybe
that's a bit of a [ __ ] but it's not
exactly illegal. You know what I'm
saying? You You're not even It's not
like you're earning millions and
millions and you're not [ __ ]
declaring [ __ ] tax.
Know what I'm saying? So,
but other than that, yeah.
Okay. Say, okay. Say you got say you got
£1,000 a month. Yeah. And you done
something that that got you £10 an hour.
You could easily go to America in two
months. Easily. Two two and a half
Yeah. Probably two two and a half month.
Yeah, but you're not going to go to
prison, you [ __ ] idiot. Maybe the
maybe the maximum thing is prison. Yeah,
bro. It's just like this whole malicious
communication thing. You can go to
prison for 2 years, but I'm not going to
go to prison. This the solicitor already
said you're not going to go to prison.
Judge already said you're not going to
go to prison. Yeah, technically you can
go to prison, but [ __ ] hell.
But you get um thingy, don't you?
You get [ __ ] um
you get tax rebates, don't you?
Well, of course you won't be going
prison because you're not even going to
be going to court in three and a half
years. I mean, stupid thing. That's why
you won't even be going prison. Yeah. Oh, [ __ ] Yeah, man.
I'm surprised YouTube never paid me for
the amount of videos I used to do and
the amount of money I used to spend. How
YouTube never [ __ ] paid me, you know?
I'm surprised they ain't never paid me
any money, bro. There was this guy on
YouTube. He was making 40k a month from
YouTube. And I'm thinking, how can you
make my my my content was way better, bro?
The smaller channels are always bit
better than the bigger channels.
I was riding on the bicycle two weeks
ago, Joe, and it kept taking me to where
I met uh Morgan. It kept taking me to
the same location. It's like it's trying
to haunt me, trying to mock me. It
didn't let me monetize it. It said I wasn't eligible.
It said I wasn't [ __ ] eligible. So,
yeah, it said I wasn't [ __ ] eligible,
bro. Which doesn't make sense cuz I had
so many banging videos on that channel.
But that's the whole point. I should
have been eligible. That's the whole
point is I should have been eligible to
be able to apply,
but apparently I wasn't. So [ __ ] [Music] Yeah, man.
I don't know how I didn't get [ __ ] If
it was like 10 years ago doing this, I
think YouTube would have paid me.
How can you make 40k a month on YouTube,
Joe? That's ridiculous.
40k a month. [ __ ] hell.
Yep. I needed it was said it said I
needed 10 million short views. Back 10
years ago, there was no such thing as
shorts. Therefore, I would have made
decent money like 10 years ago.
Yep. You need 10 million. And I think
Oh, was that like
something like 30k? Yeah, that's what
the That's what it was. It was the um
short um thing you needed like 30 I
think it was snow. No, no, maybe it was
like it was it was in the millions basically.
So it's impossible to even get sp uh to
get um sponsor from YouTube nowadays. So
I couldn't make money on YouTube even
though I put a lot of money in the
channel. So yeah, there is no real way
to make money nowadays really
unless you sublet a house. something
cuz you can't just live off benefit. You
can, but you it'd be very hard to save.
It'd be very very very hard to save just
on um just on benefits and [ __ ] in it.
No real way to make money nowadays delayed.
How's living off £750 a month?
It's more to survive, but you can't. No,
no, no. You can live, but it's
you wouldn't be able to save.
Whereas if you got 60 pound a day or 40
a day or 50 a day, you can save.
Yeah, but if you come off of benefits
and you work, you're not better off
unless you've got a trade.
So that's not even going to work unless
you [ __ ] sublet. So
it's not because even if you work,
you're still not going to be much better
off unless you unless you've got a
trade. You're not going to be much
better off. You're not going to be much
better off cuz then you're going to have
to pay rent and then you you're going to
have to [ __ ] pay this and pay that
and then you're going to pay a car. Like
you're not going to you're not going to
be much better off. That's the difference.
Cuz most people I know work and they
have no money.
I mean, I don't have loads and loads and
loads of money nowadays, but I have
enough. I've got savings.
So, but like
it seems that you're better off than these people.
So, I'm saying
Yeah. I don't want I don't Yeah.
Yeah. We usually get 750 a month. Yeah,
I'd love to say so much on the agree
with you, but you have too many grasses.
Like, I like you and Joe and stuff, but
there's too many grasses on here.
There's just too many grasses,
grasses, but I'd love to say things
on a normal community. You could on a
new a normal community, you could say
where you're going, when you're going.
Not on this [ __ ] spasticated
community. Nah, no chance.
No chance, mate.
I got £60 here. I need to I supposed to
put this in the savings, but
can't do that.
And man owes me money as well.
But you can see how tired I am, bro.
Look [ __ ] exhausted.
He's put this in the savings.
Nice bit of saving.
Oh, did you uh you must have won your
claim. Hey, Grezy,
you must have won your claim, Dad.
Did you win your claim, Dad?
Yeah, I'm just happy gaming now, Grezy,
with the little characters. I've been
playing GTA a lot recently. Well, when I
had time. But yeah, man, the little
characters in it.
But what's getting annoying recently is
people keep saying, "Oh, borrow. Can I
borrow money? Can I borrow money?" And
it's getting really, really annoying.
But Ant-Man needs to give me money back
today. Yeah, I had to lend someone money
the other day. It's like you're working
just to [ __ ] lend [ __ ] money and
then happen to get your money back. It's
annoying, bro. Not doing it again. It's
so annoying, bro. Even though I've got
the money, I hate [ __ ] lending it,
bro. Cuz it's trying to get the money
back. It's [ __ ] annoying, bro. So annoying.
Hate it, bro. Ain't it greasy?
It's [ __ ] annoying, bro.
Oh, lovely little characters. You know
who's a lovely character?
Um, Nico from GTA 4. Rez
So, basically, Joe, if I didn't work
them a couple of days in this one
account, I'd have nothing. I'd have
nothing in it. Obviously, I've still got
savings in my other one, but I'd have
nothing. So, does it make sense to you now?
Does it make sense to you now?
Does it make sense now to you?
Then I'd have to [ __ ] dip into
savings and [ __ ] which I'm not doing that. So,
so yeah, it does make sense even though
it might not make sense to you. Yeah,
I messaged some women yesterday on WhatsApp.
Then they're still the same piss takers.
Same same old. Oh,
same old bro.
Same old it greasy.
Same old. Same old. mode.
I even I haven't even had time to go to
a gym, Gregy. Really, bro?
Yeah, agree with you. Why can't these
people come off of YouTube anyways, bro?
I was off of YouTube for [ __ ] I think
it was over a week, lad.
But these people can't seem to come off of YouTube.
It's strange, isn't it? They can't seem
to come off of YouTube.
It's as if it's all they have.
And it's not a community because they
don't do anything but self-reflect. So,
it's not even a community. Do you know
what an actual community is? This is not
a community, bro.
Yeah. It's not a drug. I think it's
spasticated me. I don't really come on
much anymore, bro. I'm away tomorrow
anyways, but I'm I don't really come on
it much anymore. I think it's [ __ ] spasticated.
I don't know how you can find a drug.
It's [ __ ] weird.
It's so weird, bro.
No, I think it's a weird me.
Someone owes me more money.
What do you think, Greavves? A grand a
month. That's decent money. A grand a
month for doing nothing is decent money, Greavesy.
What do you think to that?
It's decent money. Grand a month.
[ __ ] yeah, man.
Station money, mate. Stent money.
Is it [ __ ]
Is it [ __ ] decent money, mate?
It's [ __ ] money.
Cry the box. Cry the bomb. Never. Yeah. tomorrow.
So greasy like
do you ever plan to work or what?
Do you plan to or uh
What month is the end of summer? Huh?
Oh my god. Is this red star still
stalking me? You are a loser. [ __ ]
hell, bro. What a fat loser. I literally
just went on this [ __ ] Red Star
channel. Bear in mind, I never go on
this little bully victim's channel. I
just went on it for the lows and he's still stalking.
What a [ __ ] loser, bro. He's such a loser.
Yeah, I already done mine this morning.
Oh, bro, this guy is such a [ __ ] loser.
Do you know what? Yeah. In all of my
life, yeah, I have never come across
such a keyboard coward loser in my whole
life. A little [ __ ] that's only got
energy behind the keyboard. Just jealous of retards.
He is such a loser. Like, I say that
like, go, he sits online all day waiting
for content. He's such Bro, this is why
I don't come on here anymore. It's too
weird for me.
I don't know why I just type the name.
Yeah. and never ever go there. He is
such a loser. Just like that [ __ ]
virgin. They're such losers, bro.
I gave them my address today as well and
I'm still waiting. Bro, apparently one
guy claims to live in North London. This
community, this community is full of [ __ ] bro.
This community is well and truly full of
[ __ ] And that's why I don't come on
here no more, bro. Like I said, I'm only
coming on here today cuz I'm just
resting up. I'm tired. But yep, I'm away
tomorrow and I won't be back for
probably like a month this time.
It's so weird. It's creepy, man. It
gives me the creeps.
It actually gives me the creeps, bro.
It's really creepy.
It is so [ __ ] creepy.
So, so creepy.
They sit there all day on YouTube, bro.
They've got to be fat, diabetic, and
housebound. They've got to be, bro. Fat,
diabetic, and housebound.
They're [ __ ] losers, bro. Such losers.
Been going on for years. I don't know
how they can still do this year in year
out. year in year out year in year out
and not get bored of it. Bro, I think
they're severely autistic.
They've got to be they've got to got to
be severely autistic to do this right
month in month out, day in day out, year
in year out.
They really have got to be autistic.
They've got to be, bro. Autistic
children. I'm telling you, bro. They've
got to be.
It's like LT, he he emailed me saying,
"Oh, we need Oh, I need to speak to you
ASAP." I just didn't reply to it
because, bro, there's nothing to talk
about this bastic place.
There's nothing to talk about about this
[ __ ] place, you know? You got [ __ ]
Dane emailing me like, "Bro, I'm not
doing this year in year out, year in
year out, year in year out." you know,
with these self projecting creepy spastics.
You know what I'm saying?
It's so they can sit there all day and
they've got to be jealous of something.
These people have got to be jealous of
something in life, you know, and we
should start talking about it, lad.
No one will ever leave here, bro. I
didn't come on YouTube for over a week.
Why wouldn't I leave here?
And even if I didn't leave here, right,
I was I was off of YouTube for over a
week. Something that these people can
never do. They can't take one day off of
YouTube. [ __ ] the leaving part. They
can't even take one day off of it.
I'm not [ __ ] addicted to YouTube,
bro. Speak Speak for your [ __ ] self.
Addicted. I'm not [ __ ] addicted to
[ __ ] YouTube. People that ain't got a
life or addicted to YouTube. No, no.
People that ain't got a life or addicted
I'm not [ __ ] addicted to this [ __ ]
I'm [ __ ] going away tomorrow and I
won't be back for [ __ ] a month. I was
already off for [ __ ] over a week. I'm
not [ __ ] addicted to this [ __ ]
I'd come on today cuz I was severely
bred and I've got nothing to do.
So, I'm not [ __ ] addicted to this
[ __ ] place, bro. I think it's [ __ ]
boring and weird. I think it's creepy. Creepy, disabled, [ __ ] repetitive.
Like, I don't I'm not addicted to this
[ __ ] bro. You mad?
I literally have nothing to do today.
Nothing. Like, literally [ __ ] all to do today.
Say that. I could have just But I'm
going away tomorrow. So,
I'm gone, bro. And I won't be back for a month. So,
you could have fun.
But I don't understand how they can be
addicted cuz it's just it's boring. I
see Monty Man's deleting his channel.
It's weird. It's super super super
Like I told you, I've not been on that
Red Star channel for months. I just
typed it now and he's still stalking.
He's still obsessed. This is what I mean
with these jealous fat people, bro. They
never stop. Even if they don't get Even
if you did not react to these people,
they would still do it. They would still
do it. That's how you know they're
jealous and disabled because people
normally do stuff for a reaction. You're
a [ __ ] [ __ ] I'm going to do this.
I'm going to do that. But with these
retards, it's backwards because even if
they don't get a reaction or say they
didn't get a reaction for a year, they
would still do it. They they would still
do it. That's how disabled and jealous
they are. Like, bro, Jesus Christ could
come down from Earth and promise these
people that no one's watching your
channel, no one's reacting to you for 5
years, right? And they would still do
what they do because they're disabled.
Like I used to go on Timmy's right and
like [ __ ] with him because he used to
react funny in it every time. But these
people now I'm off tomorrow bro. I'm off tomorrow.
I just been busy with [ __ ] Uh
um yeah. So
yeah, bro. And this and and they still
do it, bro. It's [ __ ] weird.
They're [ __ ] weird.
I don't know how the [ __ ] these people
can be jealous of people that they don't
even know or be obsessed with people
that they don't even know and they've
been doing it for years. They've got
autism or something.
I like that, bro. Like, but it's just
pointless talking about the same [ __ ]
with these people. It's the same old argument, bro.
Let me guess. [ __ ] Smokey Be said
something whilst he's hiding in Milton
Kings. We're done with it, bro.
You know, it's it's [ __ ] boring as
So, I don't know how people get addicted
to to this community. It's just like
that red shot. I'll give you an example.
Another stalker. He's been doing this
for years and years and years and years
and years, but he will never meet
anyone. He will never say anything to
anyone's face. He would just
continuously bully himself on YouTube,
embarrass himself on YouTube, but he
will never say anything to anyone's face.
So, it's like this is a prime example of
embarrassment. Like, I don't even say
yeah, that these people get bullied.
They just embarrass themselves. I guess
some people have picked up on it as
well. You know,
people know where I live. Like, if
they've got something to say to if
they've got if they've got anything to
say, come and say to my face. That's
They know where I live. You know what
I'm saying? So, it's like, "What? What?
What the [ __ ] Stop being a London cyclist."
I just say to them, "Stop being a London
cyclist. Starting something you can't
finish." Simple. Yeah. Tim's still on YouTube. Yep.
But they're all on YouTube. They ain't
got a life. I was off of YouTube for
over a week while I was busy with stuff.
These people ain't got a life, bro.
They'll never leave YouTube.
Leave YouTube lad. It's all they have.
Trying to think what should what I
should eat today.
It's weird, Slim Lad. It's weird
that they're still on YouTube doing what
they do. It's just so creepy.
Creeps me out, bro.
years and years and years and years and
years they've been doing this. You know,
that's why I made a new channel, bro.
That's why I made a new channel where
they can't find me, lad.
You know what I'm saying? Where they
can't find me.
I got some good content on my other
channel, but to be fair, I've not
uploaded on it to be fair.
It's just boring. It's autistic. It's
repetitive. It's creepy. Like, you know,
but it's [ __ ]
They literally live to stalk men on the
internet. How creepy is that?
Like they don't they don't
psychologically [ __ ] with my head, but
they they creep me out. I mean, I I can
I I can I can give I can say that for
nothing that they creep me out.
I can say that they creep me out, bro.
But that's about all they do is creep me
out. They're just so creepy.
There's such like it you know all of
this right is all to do with right it's
all to do with the bullying that they've
received all throughout their whole life
and they project it on YouTube like this
red star just just Jamie Thompson but
the thing is with Jamie Thompson is
Jamie Thompson He shows himself. But you
can imagine this is what they all look
like. Fat, ugly, double chinned, no
woman, no money, no friends. And it
explains why they're on a community like
this. You understand, bro? It explains,
look at what this community attracts,
bro. Losers. It attracts nothing but
losers. Yeah. You might get the odd
person that comes and has a normal chat.
You might get maybe 10% of people on
here that are normal. But if you notice
the kind of people that it attracts are
losers that are on here every day.
Doesn't that tell you everything you
need to know? Bro,
think of this stuff for example. He has
to Yeah. Stop talking about yourself,
Virgin. You see, that's an example. You
got to understand with these ugly
people, right? Look at this red star
right on YouTube, right? on YouTube
every single day repeating himself from
the time he wakes up to the time he goes
bed. He's living his worst life in his mom's basement.
I don't know how it all started, bro.
With [ __ ] gambling, is it?
They're just jealous of anyone that's
better looking than them, that's got a
better life than them, bro. That's how
it starts. It starts with jealousy. Fat,
ugly, 40-year-old losers. It starts tells
you how it starts. These people are fat
and ugly. They've got no money. They've
got no life. So they take out on the
world. And well, they don't take out on
the world cuz they ain't got they've got
no balls to take out the world. They
come on YouTube and they hate on anyone
that's got a better life than them. And
they call them everything that they are.
Jobless, skint, ugly, everything that
applies to their own life. That is their
reality. That's how it starts, bro. And
they know that they're so old now they
can't even change it.
They sit on YouTube all day repeating
like the sad fat loser [ __ ] that they are. Just sad
creeps. That's all they are. It's
creeps. There's no there's nothing else, bro.
Just sad sad sad sad creeps, bro.
Yeah, look, you can see that Jamie
Thompson still stalking me. You see what
I'm saying? Sad, jealous little creeps.
So, they have done they they have they have um
they have um successfully done one
thing. Um they've creeped me out.
They've they've literally creeped me
out. That's what they've done. But bullying
really bullying people, mate. I will
give them my address any time, a million
times, and not one person will pull up.
And if this [ __ ] keeps making fake
accounts, I'm just going to keep
reporting them to the police again. Bro,
this jealousy towards me needs to stop.
Bro, remember, bro, I'm skinn. I'm this.
I'm that. Yeah, bro. Listen. I'm
skinned. I'm this. I'm that. So then
maybe you should leave somebody alone
that you that's that's less than you.
But they know you're better looking than
them. You got more money than them. And
it kills them. It's just like that
Ronald Pump said, you're better looking
than them. You got more money than them.
Remember that. And it's true. It's the
truth. I'm accepting it. And I've
accepted that stuff that comes with
being better looking than them, having
more money than them. But [ __ ] hell,
son. Give me a break. Leave me alone.
It's not my fault I got more money than
you and I'm better looking than you. Cuz
let's think of it, right? If it's really
not that, let's let's let's go back to
the start. Why would these people come
online every day stalking another man
that they don't know? Let's let's really
look into the science of this, right?
I'm sure there's normal people on this
channel. Why would somebody come on
YouTube every day stalking another man?
It's jealousy. The only thing it can
come to is the J word. Jealousy. What
else can can the arrows point to? What
else can the archery arrows really
really point to? If God gives you one
life, yeah, you've got one life and
you're supposed to live your one life.
What would you do in your one life?
Would you sit on here stalking people
every day? No. Why would you sit on
YouTube stalking people every day?
It's jealousy. The only thing it can it
can point to is jealousy. I'm Unless I'm
Unless I'm lying, bro. Unless I'm wrong,
somebody can tell me what else it is.
You know, cuz think of it. These people
do not bully no one. They don't affect
no one. They bully themselves. But their
whole intentions is to come on here and
try to bully someone. What? Somebody
with all that money? Somebody that's got
all this good looks would want to come
on YouTube, I quote, bullying people
that they don't know. It's not looking
right. It's not looking right. Why the
[ __ ] would someone with all this with
all these looks, all this money, God has
given them one life to to live their own
life, but they're coming on YouTube
stalking men. jealousy. There's nothing
else it can be. Just like that lanky
virgin. The string aer pissed virgin on
a grand a month. The stringer pissed
virgin on a grand a month. [ __ ] face
with no teeth. Right. As an example,
claims they've got a girlfriend. Claims
they have sex. Why they on YouTube
stalking me every day?
There's nothing else. It could literally
be, bro. There's literally nothing. Or
or it could be they want to [ __ ] you.
It's either that they're jealous or they
want to [ __ ] you.
They're either jealous of you or they
want to [ __ ] you or there's both because there's literally
nothing else. But then I could say it
can't even be that because even people
that you're in love with. I mean I've
not done [ __ ] like that to them. So I
mean like or or well liked maybe, you
know. So God has remember God God has
given these people one life, you know,
and they're choosing to waste it on
YouTube. Maybe they stalking people. So,
I mean, it doesn't look good, does it, bro?
You have to think logically about why
these people do what they do, you know?
And then when they start something they
can't finish, stop being a London
cyclist. That's all I say to them. Stop
being somebody in London that can start
something that they can't finish. It's
boring, bro. It's boring.
The whole self projection [ __ ] is
boring. The whole me going live [ __ ] and
you saying [ __ ] is boring. You know, if
you got something to say, you've got my
address. Come and say it to my face. If
you're not, then you're blocked. It's boring.
You want to hate, come and hate in real
life, you know? Simple. Don't do it
behind your little keyboard. It's boring, bro.
Think of it, bro. Yeah. Look at that
bomb. Yeah. We never ever thought he was
going to dox himself. We never ever
thought this guy was ever going to dox
himself. And he would constantly go on
about people's looks and constantly go
on about people's faces. You're this,
you're that, you're this, you're that,
you're this, you're that. And then look
what happened when he finally got doxed.
Big fat ugly [ __ ] with no hair.
Yeah. So God can only imagine what Red
Star looks like. He probably looks worse
than [ __ ] Jamie [ __ ] Thompson. But
I mean to be fair to Jamie Thompson, at
least he actually shows his face. But
it's a prime example of what most of
these people will look like. They will
look like him.
You know what I'm saying?
They will look like him. And that's why
I made another channel. But that's why I
I don't put content on this channel when
I just go live on it talking to the 10%
of people because it's just hate, weird
creepiness, and jealousy on this
community. That's why you don't catch me
on here, bro. It's weird.
Look, look, look, bro. Yeah. I give you
an example. Look, I just went on Jamie
Jamie Thompson's channel. It's the same
people that are saying stuff behind an account.
It's been going on for years.
It's literally been going on for years.
[ __ ] off, you [ __ ] virgin.
It's been going on for years. You
understand, bro? It has literally been
going on for years. Why do you think I
literally ignored all the [ __ ] emails, you know?
isticated people behind an account that
will never say anything to anyone's
face. And like I said, bro, if I'm
wrong, you got my address. Simple.
You're this, you're that, you're this,
you're that. Like, bro, how many times
have we been hearing this for years?
You're this, you're that, you're this,
you're that. And all of these people
behind these accounts are 40y old spastics.
Imagine that, bro. Like, you're this,
you're that, you're this, you're that,
you're this, you're that. Yet all these
people are of 40year-old spastics that
only know about their own shitkin life.
Come on, bro. Like, how many more years
is it going to go on for? We should all
talk about this, bro. How many years is
this going to keep going on for?
Smokey B, another keyboard warrior
hiding in Milton Kees. Like, we can go
over these people one by one by one by
one, but it's boring, bro. You know
what, Jamie Thompson channel, I can tell
you how many times I've been to their
area and not one of them came out.
You know, I can tell you where I went to
someone's country and they didn't come
out. Yeah, you would like to hear about
that, would you?
They can they can do this year in year
out. You I'm giving some I'm giving
these people a platform to talk about to
talk about this. I'm actually giving
them a platform. You know,
it's like this all night spaz type type.
But he never said nothing when I was in
his country two times. So at the end of
the day, it's laughable. These little
keyboard warriors are something to laugh
at. Creepy, I must say. They are creepy.
They creep me out. I already admitted
they creep me out, but they're just
something to laugh at. Really
embarrassing themselves on YouTube.
Cuz I give you an example, [ __ ]
If somebody come to my country two times
and I didn't so much as say a word to
them, I would just probably just leave
YouTube to be honest. But again, these
people have no shame. But there's no
point in saying that they've got no
shame because they don't care that
they've got no shame.
They don't care that they've got no shame.
And is this little virgin? Okay, I need
to start doing screenshots again. Actually,
one second. I just start doing
screenshots of this virgin again.
fit that in every week, bro. Not a
problem. I've been trying to go to a
gym, bro, but I've not really had much
time to be honest.
Every time this virgin comes in on an
account, I'm going to start screenshotting again.
Yeah, I'm going to start screenshot this
virgin. But no, I haven't really had
time to be honest. I'm probably going to
go today actually.
I should be able to fit in today
actually. Yeah. Um I'm a bit [ __ ] but
I should be able to fit in. Yeah, I'm
actually going to go today actually.
Yeah. I haven't been for a little while,
man. I haven't really had the time.
But yeah, today I'll go actually. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm going to go today, bro.
Where's my socks? Actually, I'm going to
go in a minute, I think. I thought I
lose all my [ __ ] games, bro. I'm
talking about these [ __ ] people on
YouTube again, bro. What?
Yeah, I just haven't had any time to
myself really. So, yeah,
get a nice steak today as well. It may be.
Yeah, get a nice steak today. wall
steak and a steak. Yeah.
And a nice steak. Oh,
these people. I just can't believe them,
bro. They're unbelievable, man.
They're still being [ __ ] retards on
YouTube every [ __ ] day. It's a madness.
You would have thought these people grow
up and get a life.
Yeah, I have one more pumpkin before
[ __ ] up out of here. Yeah, man.
I supposed to make a video and I've not
even had time to,
but these people have got all the time
in the world to sit on YouTube and stalk
people. [ __ ] madness, isn't it?
But it's [ __ ] madness, isn't it, man?
They can sit on YouTube all day stalking
people year in year out, bro.
But remember, bro, these people are the
ones with a better life.
Remember, bro, these are the ones with
the better life.
[ __ ] what life, bro? YouTube.
They ain't got no life, mate.
They ain't got no life for [ __ ] YouTube, bro.
I'll be live later anyways.
LT can come on if you want knows my channel.
This whole [ __ ] with these [ __ ]
weirdos on this community, bro. We need
to stop rapping. It's boring now, bro.
Yeah. It's so weird. It's like every
time you go live, you get stalked. It's weird.
Stop talking about yourself.
Don't self-reflect on another channel.
Um, but anyways, I'm going now. So,
yeah, I'll be back later
and then you won't see me again for a
month. So, you better be on tonight
or see if people are stuck on YouTube.
Can't get off it. One sec. Iceland.