Yo yo,
this place is getting weird again.
And it's not even been 3 hours.
Do you know what it's like yet? It's
like walking into a [ __ ] dungeon,
bro, that you can't get out of whenever
you're on this spasticated place.
But let's see if this little [ __ ] old
shows where he is today, bro. This guy
is pissing me off, bro.
Swear to God. I was speaking about in
the gym that as well. Yeah. Oh, is he
just going to be another one that can
start something that they can't finish?
Just like most of these little retards
on this community. These little stalky little retards. Yeah.
They never ever stop, do they? These
people, they never ever ever ever stop.
[ __ ] what, bro? What is wrong with
these people? Like honestly, yeah. What
is actually wrong with these people?
What the [ __ ] is wrong with these retards?
Well, it's self-explanatory. They're
they're [ __ ] [ __ ] They're not
[ __ ] normal people. But what the
[ __ ] Seriously, bro. Like, just wait
until this little [ __ ] does a video. I'm
free all day today, bro. Got two phones,
got a power battery,
and that's going to be the same. The
same is going to go to all of these
people now. Anyone that wants to run
their mouth today. Yeah. I'm going to
let them come in the hangouts and I'm
going to make them show me where they
are. If they don't, they get kicked. Simple, bro.
I'm [ __ ] off tomorrow anyway. So,
it's not it's not a problem. You know,
stop being a London cyclist. That's my
new meme now, bro. You want to come
online, you want to bother people every
single You want to harass people every
day cuz that's what you do. You harass
people. You don't bully when you bully
yourselves. You harass people. You
annoying little twists. Yeah, but you
you don't want to back your talk up.
You know, you know what? You claim you
don't know where I live. Everyone knows
where I live. But [ __ ] all that knowing
where people live because all you people
do is accept police to people's [ __ ]
door. Show where you are. Join the
hangouts and show where you are.
Smokey me all the bro. I'm dead serious,
I'm full of energy today.
So you just want to come on the internet
and stalk people and bother people every
day but you don't actually want to do
anything bro what is your life what is
your life bro
I'm saying yeah I'm about bro again but
you can come and say to my face come
back it doesn't bother me bro yes I'm
this I'm that I'm this I'm that yes okay
come and say to my face that's the only
time you're going to be took seriously
it doesn't bother me what you write
about yourself on the internet. If
you're if you're if you're referring to
me and you're calling me it, come and
say it to my face. And if you're not
saying it to my face, you're talking
about yourself because look, your name
is before the comment that you've wrote.
So, you're talking about yourself. If
you're not talking about yourself, I'm
more than happy to meet you anywhere
today. Join the hangout. Show me where
you are. I will come anywhere you are
today. I'm free.
That's it, bro. And if you're not going
to do that, then shut up. Simple. I
might go put a link there if I'm going
to say that.
Cuz you got to understand, bro. It's
getting really boring now. Really, really embarrassing.
You've been doing this for [ __ ]
years, man. You know, we know it's the
same four or five people. Yeah. Doing
this year in year out. Year in year out.
Okay. So, you're calling it now. Join
the hangouts. Let's arrange this beat up
and you can say it to my face. But
you're not going to do that. You're just
going to be a [ __ ] on YouTube every
day projecting your life away.
Yeah, I've got the best [ __ ] sayings.
you people really need to sort your life out, mate.
Bye-bye, fat fats. So,
bye-bye. Go to the pub, Jamie. You don't
need to go to the pub. You need to
[ __ ] lose weight, you fat [ __ ] If I
looked like you, mate, let me let me
tell you something. If I looked like
you, the last thing I'd be doing is
coming on [ __ ] YouTube. If if if I
was the size of you, the last thing I'd
be doing is coming on YouTube. You're an
embarrassment, mate. You know what I'm saying? Like
you think he he is a mug. He's always
been a mug. I come on here today minding
my own business. This [ __ ] wants to come
on here and bother me. So, I've asked
him to show me where he is. Simple. And
I will meet him today and slap the [ __ ]
out of him. You know what I'm saying?
Vi, let me let me just check if that's
the real. Yeah, probably not.
Okay. Not the real belly, so no point
giving you any um advice. But yeah,
either way, bro, like you're not the
real belly. You're not the real belly.
But I just don't get this [ __ ] bro.
It's why I don't come on here anymore.
You little [ __ ] [ __ ] ruined my
[ __ ] mood when I was in the gym as
well. You know, why I don't come on here
anymore, bro. It's why I do not come on here anymore.
It's so weird. It's so weird, bro. Like,
weird is, to be honest, is an
understatement. They're [ __ ] weirdos,
bro. I swear down they're weirdos. They're [ __ ] Hello. Who's this? Huh? Damn, [ __ ]
Yeah. See what I mean, bro? It's full of
spastics. This community is full of
spastics, bro. Full of life spastics.
Full of spastics, bro. Full of [ __ ] spastics.
And about the whole working thing, I was
I was obviously [ __ ] trolling you.
You think I need to ever [ __ ] work?
But again, it's the same example of what
I done with Pat Muster before. Oh, I'm
working in Foot Locker. Oh, I'm working
in Foot Locker. I'm working in Foot
Locker. Do you really think I've ever
worked in Foot Locker?
Do you really really think that I'd be
working a [ __ ] minimum wage job when
I get enough money? And furthermore,
man, even if I was working like what my
friend said, for one pound an hour. Say
I was working for one pound an hour,
bro. Yeah. Let's say, let's just say
right now I'm working for one pound an
hour. Well, guess what, mate? You people
are sat on YouTube every single day, not
even making£1 an hour, self projecting
your life away. So, bro, who's the one
that's more [ __ ] These people.
Like, you would tell any of these people
anything, bro. Really? Come on, bro. I
tell these people what I want them to
know. Why do you think they get
everything wrong? They're [ __ ]
spastics. That's literally what they
are. They never ever will ever stop as
well, bro. Which is one of the reasons I
made a new channel, even though I've
been slacking on it, bro. I haven't
really uploaded much on it. It's because
they literally never stop, bro.
Like, they never ever ever stop. It's [ __ ] weird.
Like it's so weird. They've got to be
[ __ ] [ __ ] Like I don't even like
use that word, but they they got to be [ __ ] bro.
So, I've been on that Red Star channel
for ages. I went on it once and he's
still stalking. Like, what? What, bro?
What is wrong with them? They're
obviously autistic. Yeah, but what else is it?
Cuz it's [ __ ] weird. They [ __ ]
bother people every [ __ ] day. Yeah.
Where is this? Where is this Milton Ke
wanker? Well, after today, bro, you need
to remove the smoke from your name cuz
you're not on no smoke. You never have
been and you never will be. You never
have been on any smoke and you never
[ __ ] will be. Yeah. I literally said
I will travel to you today. I'm serious.
[ __ ] 40 minutes an hour. It's not a
problem, man. What the [ __ ] No, this is
the reason why I stopped going on
buddies. Cuz I'd go on buddies. They
start, they can't finish. They start,
but they can't finish.
Start on people, but they can't finish
it. What's the [ __ ] point, bro? I
don't understand what they're trying to gain
other than just harassing people every
single [ __ ] day. Harassing people
every [ __ ] day of their life. They
live to harass. It might not seem weird
to you, but it's [ __ ] weird
to [ __ ] me
really think I would have to work with
amount of money I'm on. And furthermore,
even if I [ __ ] was, like,
what are they doing on YouTube every day
harassing people? Like, come on, bro.
What are these little retards doing on
YouTube every day harassing people?
They do nothing. They don't go to the
gym. They don't go to work.
They do nothing. They do nothing but
hate. That's their life. That's what
they live for.
It's so weird, bro. And there's nothing
else to do but to leave, bro. That's
literally it. There's no getting the
police involved. There's no They're
never going to stop. They've already
shown that they're never going to stop
these [ __ ] retards.
They will never ever ever ever ever ever
ever ever stop. I don't even think
they'd stop even when you're dead.
There's something that you have that
they're jealous of. I don't know what it
is. Better looks, maybe more money,
maybe easier lifestyle. There's
something not right there, bro. There's
something seriously not right there.
There's something that doesn't add to
the last piece of the puzzle,
you know? But they'll never stop. Even
when you're dead, they'd probably never
stop. They're [ __ ] weirdos. Weirdos.
And it's not like they they have a
channel. Yeah. Like an archive channel
where they put any bit of content on
there. Like they put everything for my
channel on there. It's so weird. It's so
[ __ ] weird, bro.
These people really give me the creeps.
Hey, give me the creeps, bro.
Give this guy some more time.
Just these weirdos, bro. These weirdos
starting stuff they can't finish. Like London cyclists.
Bro, these people are ultra weird, bro,
in this community, bro. And the the
older I get, the more I realize it.
Like I went on that Red Star channel and
that Jamie Thompson channel today and
I've not been on their channel in
months. Bro, I haven't been on YouTube
for over a week and as soon as I go on
their channel, they're still stalking
me. Bro, are they gay or something?
Like, are they actually gay? Are they a
batty boy or something?
What the [ __ ]
There's something not right with these
people, bro. They're [ __ ] mongos.
And then they're trying to say that I
work a minimum wage job. Bro, I don't
even work. I just told you a [ __ ]
story just the same as [ __ ] I told
Pat Mer that I work in Foot Locker. You
really think I need to work with the
amount of money that I'm on? And also,
even if I did [ __ ] work, which I
don't, and I was earning minimum wage,
what are you earning, bro? You're sat on
YouTube earning nothing. You're sat on
YouTube earning [ __ ] all. So, it's like,
what the [ __ ] You got these people out
of London. They think they know about
people's lives, but they don't know
about people's lives.
They're [ __ ] mongos, bro. But let
that smoky be show me where he is today.
I will slap him up, bro. This guy has
been bothering people for years.
That's why I don't come on here anymore.
This is why I don't come on here anymore, bro.
Cuz they start [ __ ] They can't finish.
They [ __ ] ruin people's [ __ ]
moods. And then they all run away like
the little retards they are, bro.
They're made for each other. Yeah. The
people in this community are made for each other.
They are literally made for each other,
bro. All of them.
You got the Lanky Virgin still giving it
the big and I'm thinking, bro, you're
still doing this. You're literally still
doing this. I was off of YouTube for
[ __ ] 10 days, bro. And they're still
doing this. They're still They've been
doing it for years, bro.
But when you come back from doing some
mad [ __ ] and then they're still doing
it, I'm thinking, bro,
these people are proper disabled. Like
there's there's nothing else to say.
They're just proper they're just
properly disabled in it. That's it.
You know what I'm saying, bro? All
right, let's see what job they're doing.
You know what on YouTube? I mean, they
stalking, but they're skinned. They're
all skinned, bro. You don't understand.
They're all skinned. They're life's
losers. I'm going on holiday tomorrow.
They're going to be on YouTube. You know,
this community is a waste of time. It's
a waste of people's time. It's a waste
of people's energy.
It's just a waste of everything, bro. Do you understand?
Yeah. You have to laugh at them, bro.
You have to laugh at them.
[ __ ] idiots, bro. They're proper
proper idiots, bro. They're proper
They're just spasticated, bro. I don't
know what I'm going to eat today.
Chinese maybe. I don't know. [ __ ] knows.
I can't believe they're still doing it
though after the year. Steven Howard,
it's like the Virgin,
you know? I don't even go to the police
anymore cuz I can't be bothered, bro.
I'd rather just live my life. They're
the ones that are still on YouTube
obsessed every day clearly. So that's
why I can't even be bothered with the
police anymore, bro.
cuz you're living your life and they're
still obsessed. So, they're the ones
that are losing every single time they
come on YouTube and they come obsessed,
right? You are owning them, bro. You
don't need no police involved. Like,
[ __ ] nothing's going to happen
anyways. Like, they're they're showing
what they're about every time they're
obsessed with you. You understand?
I don't know. It's just some [ __ ] fat
weirdo that keeps stalking me.
some fat weirdo that keeps stalking me.
And as you can see,
they also start [ __ ] they can't finish.
So what's the [ __ ] point of it, bro?
Stop being a London cyclist.
Yeah, bro. Whatever.
Yeah, I'm a [ __ ] I'm a big [ __ ] bro.
compensate to my face. Simple.
It's all weird. It's so weird, bro. All
of this is so weird. Like, you don't understand.
They're just self- projecting 40year-old
spastics. And I'll say it to any one of
their faces. Any one of these people's
faces, I am prepared to say it to today.
Starting with Smokey B. Show you in
Milton Kees. We'll arrange a time cuz
bro, I can go in Milton Kees right now.
It's not a problem. But we know the
excuse is going to be, "Oh, well that's
not a set time or a set date, so it
doesn't count." Like, you know what
these retards will do? They do it all
the time, bro. Bomb's done it. [ __ ]
they all do it. Like, I'm live now.
Yeah. Anyone that that's got a problem,
anyone that's going to run their mouth,
I'm going to tell you, okay, you're
talking about yourself. Unless you're
going to come and say it to my face, or
I'm going to come and say to you, for
you to say it to my face, rather. [ __ ] off. Simple.
How long are they going to keep being retards for?
[ __ ] annoying retards for, bro? Like,
think of it.
I have LT email me. I've got [ __ ]
Jane email me. I don't I didn't respond,
dude. I can't be annoyed with it. You
know what I'm saying? Same people, same
story, same spastics. I never meet anyone.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
That's why I can't be asked.
Uh, he was here earlier.
They're [ __ ] proper retards.
Just self-reflecting little failures,
bro. That's what they are, you know?
just like trying to say I've got a
minimum wage job, bro. I don't even
work. I was chatting [ __ ] to them. And
bro, even if you're working a minimum
wage, imagine this, Stephen. How would
you Yeah. Would you rather work a
minimum wage job or be a [ __ ] on
YouTube every day like these people
being spasticated, got no money? Think
about it, bro. I don't even work
anyways. Well, I tell these people what
I want because when you lie to these
people, it gets them going. It gets them
talking about stuff.
Like, bro, think of it, bro. They're [ __ ]
They actually [ __ ] these people in this
community, bro. I swear down. Yeah.
Yeah. I kept going to uh USA Izzy's
location two weeks ago. Steven Howard.
See, even that, bro, I started that with
her and I'd finish it. Just like a month
and a half ago, I wrote on her Facebook,
I started it and I'll finish it. Simple.
And they live in a [ __ ] other country.
So, if you're going to start something, finish it.
Yeah. I'll tell you the story again. the
cyclist two weeks ago when I wanted to
ride a bike for the day. [ __ ] tried
saying, "Oh, you can't go there." I
said, "I will go where I want." Yeah.
Then she started running her mouth and
then I parked the bike and I told her to
come back. Yeah.
I told her to come back and say what
she's got to say to my face and don't
walk off. She was with a man. They both
walked away. What's the point? It
reminds me like this. It reminds me of this community,
you know, whatever reason people do it.
Bad day, [ __ ] life. I don't know why
people start, bro, in real life or they
do it on YouTube, but finish it. But
finish it, [ __ ] That's what I'm
saying, bro. Like, so that's why I say
to them, stop being a London cyclist.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I don't have problems with with any of
them. I just don't understand why they
start stuff they can't finish. It's a
bit like this community. I don't know
why. Like when I've been walking around,
I see these cyclists just go mad at each
other, but they don't finish it. They
then cycle off. What's the point? You're
in a bad mood. You now put someone else
in a bad mood and now you're walking away.
What the [ __ ] It's It's stupid, bro.
Like, back up your talk. Simple. I don't
get it. If you're not going to do it,
what's the point?
You know this Smokey Bee, he's been
running his mouth for years and years
and years. The other day he's been doing
it years and years and years and I don't
ride. It was two weeks ago. Years and
years and years he's been running his
[ __ ] mouth. So I've asked him to show
me where he is. And look, he's gone
silent. So what's the point, bro? You
know what I mean? Same spastics, bro.
You know, when I come back from
Thailand, I'm not coming on this [ __ ]
ever again, bro. I'm just going to do a
whole complete Ant-Man.
No, I wasn't riding on a
I was riding over a bridge. It was two
weeks ago. I was riding over a [ __ ]
bridge. And it weren't any of her
business anyways where the [ __ ] I was
riding. She's not the [ __ ] police.
She's not the police. She never almost
got hit. Mind your own [ __ ] business.
You're not authority. You're not the police. Simple.
So I in my thing I'm thinking who the
[ __ ] are you? You're just another
[ __ ] pedestrian. Don't tell me where
I where I need to go. It's not being
rude. It's you're being rude by getting
involved in someone's business. That's
got nothing to do with you. You know
about you should be there. I'll say I'll
go where I want. I tell you exactly
where I went. I said I will go where I want.
That's what I said.
And I parked the bike when she started
running her mouth. I'd like to I I
parked it on this and I told her and her
man to come back. Simple
cuz it's [ __ ] pathetic, bro. No one's
almost rode into you mind your own [ __ ] business,
you know? I tell you what I can't stand.
Yeah. Is Londoners f firstly it's these people people
from London, bro. I can't stand them.
You will never understand it even if I
explained it to you, bro. Like, they
need to learn to mind their own [ __ ] business. Yeah.
Why do they start stuff they can't
finish? Like, I was going to do a video
on this the other day, but I was just I
had time to do stuff. I've been busy. I
can't sit on YouTube all day. Why do
they start stuff they can't finish?
Then you meet Chinese people and they're
the nicest people you ever meet.
They go out their way to help you even
if they don't speak [ __ ] English.
That tells a mad story, bro. And we're
not even in Asia yet. So, what the [ __ ]
I hate [ __ ] Londoners, bro. I can't
stand it, bro.
No, you you don't like when I mean
Londoners, I mean like
they're just [ __ ] This country is
full of just too many [ __ ] bro.
It's simple, isn't it?
I hate him, bro. Like, serious seriously hate him.
Yeah, but it's because she's putting me
in a bad mood. Okay, I'm in a bad mood
now. Now what?
You know what I'm saying?
And there was a cyclist I seen the other
day. I was walking, bro. It was like a
month ago. He went into this guy saying
saying, "I'll [ __ ] smash you in your
face, bro. If he said that to me, that
bite would be going through his [ __ ]
jaw." You know, they they
overexaggerate. I've seen it with my own
eyes. Yeah. You people are nowhere near
hitting them and they still find an
excuse to stop
and get involved in people's business. They're [ __ ]
You know, that's the only thing I I used
to dread. It happened in the Weather
Spoons the other day. This woman tried
mocking me and I said, "Yeah, yeah, with
with with a guy." I said, "Yeah." What
are you walking away for?
Typical London [ __ ] Smart [ __ ]
but run away like a little [ __ ] What's
the point? Just [ __ ] get a boxing bag
and just punch the [ __ ] boxing bag,
bro. There's no point starting on
someone when you can't finish it and you
run away is stupid.
It's so like get a box. Like I get No,
no. I get the whole people being pissed
off because I'm pissed off sometimes. I
wouldn't take out on a random person,
but I guess some people have got
different tempers. But even still, I can
understand why people would do it if
they're pissed off. But then finish it
then. Whether that's verbally or
whether that's verbally or [ __ ]
or if it turns physical, it turn at the
end of the day, you started it. So, it's
like starting a book but not finishing
it. It's pointless. You can't start a
book and not finish it and then mark and
then sell the book. It doesn't make sense.
But they're proper proper [ __ ]
here. Like you you meet Chinese people,
bro. They're so nice. They'll go out
their way to help people. Oh bro, I can
give you a million and one examples. But
these people in this country, they are
just sucks [ __ ] like to the max.
Yeah. They love to get involved with
people's business. And then when you
tell them about themselves, they run away.
It's like remember that time that
O'Neals was in security. Oh, he's doing
his job. I said, did did anyone ask you?
Are you involved in the conversation?
Uh, did anybody ask you, Nosy?
Uh, who asked you about what the bounce
is doing, [ __ ]
And then there was one another time when
I was on a payment two week. I was I
only went for a bike ride for a day and
then this guy started and I just laughed
at him. I was like, "Bro, you're
starting when you're with four guys.
It's embarrassing." Another thing they
like to do, [ __ ] They like to
start on people and they're in groups. It's embarrassing.
It's like It's just embarrassing, bro.
Yeah. I had um I had to put something up
a ramp and it was kind of broken. these
this Chinese couple come in and helped
out. They stood on it and they helped me
and they said, "Oh, take care." I was
like, "How lovely are they to just help
like someone to help someone and then
say take care?" Like that's they were so
nice. I assume they were a couple. I
mean, [ __ ] man. I wish every imagine
English people were like this and less of [ __ ]
And you know, the thing is they're not
even hard. They're not even strong,
these people here. They just start [ __ ]
but they can't finish it. They're all mouth.
They're all [ __ ] bro. Like what?
There was another thing I was saying.
Oh, yeah. There was something I was lost
like two weeks ago as well. I was trying
to find directions and I asked about
five people. Weren't weren't trying to
help me. Weren't bothered to help. And
then one guy like he generally didn't
know. It's not like they generally
didn't know and they were polite. They
were just being [ __ ] And then I
said, "Oh, I hope I don't get robbed
here, mate. I hope I don't get [ __ ]
stabbed here, mate. You don't watch.
They don't even like, if you don't know,
you don't know, but there's there's just
a way of saying things. They're just
they are just [ __ ]
Like, they just give this city such a bad name.
Chinese people are just so cool, man.
They're either very nice or they just
keep themselves to themselves. like a
lot of people just want to do, you know?
They're [ __ ] absolute [ __ ] bro.
So many [ __ ] about
There was this one guy, bro, the other
the one over there like 3 weeks ago. I
was with my friend. Yeah. He started a
conversation with me. Yeah.
Then um and it's like why should we have
to put up with this [ __ ] Yeah. This guy okay.
So where you from? He said somewhere.
Oh well I had to clunch my fist jar and
had to walk back in the bar. I wanted to
[ __ ] him up. You don't understand. Like
somewhere. Like who do you think you are
[ __ ] And my friend was like oh
leave it. Leave it. Leave it. Leave it.
Leave it. Uh, I've had to do that a few
times with like American people, not
like over and over and over again, but a
few times. And then I just had to ignore
it because what's going to happen is
they're the kind of people that when you
[ __ ] them up, they're going to run to
the police again. Start something that
they can't finish.
Maybe a black person would fight back,
but not these white people. Nah, they're
[ __ ] These white people in London,
they're complete [ __ ] They're all
mouth, mate. Do you remember the [ __ ] men? somewhere.
I just looked at him, bro. I swear down,
bro. Like, I was like, "What the fuck?"
And you started a conversation with me,
[ __ ] [ __ ] I would have to smash
his teeth down his throat, boy. But the
thing is that's going to happen is
they're going to run to the police.
Now, if it was a black person, I would
trust. Yeah. They're not going to run to
the police. But you got to understand
the types of people. You got to
understand types of people and you need
to analyze kind types of obviously if
they put their hands on you then yeah
like or or something then yeah you know
b them whatever but you need to analyze
the kind of people that
um that you're dealing with. It's like
my mom's neighbor. I just allow him
because you know like my mom lives
there. It's going to cause her problems.
You know I go there a couple of times a
week. It's best just to just leave it
again. Unless they put your unless they
put hands on you or like they really try
to bore you off then obviously it's a different story.
But that's why I just I'll just leave it in it.
But you got to analyze
the kind of people. You know what I'm
saying? But obviously if they put their
hands on you, they b you off then smack
him in the face. Like it's it's different. Yeah.
But yeah, them uh and it is a London
thing as well cuz no one else does it.
They like to get involved with people's
business. They like to try to take the
piss out of people. And then when you
give them what for, they walk away. So
it's like you're ruining my mood cuz
you've had a [ __ ] day at work or your
life is [ __ ] My life's not [ __ ]
perfect. Could you imagine? I went I
went to Liverpool Street. Yeah. Could
you imagine I went out to Liverpool
Street right now and I started on a load
of people and I just ran away. Think of
it. Think of it. Put the shoe on the
other foot. Yeah. Say like my life is
not [ __ ] perfect,
you know? But so well does that mean I
can go to central London and start [ __ ]
starting people and run away? Imagine
the shoe was on the other foot, bro.
It's embarrassing, bro.
Yeah, she told me to meet her the other
day, but I didn't. This country is
It's a depressing country, bro. Like,
past few weeks, I've not even been
approaching. I ain't been drinking. I
can't be bothered. Yeah. Every Yeah. But
I'm just using as I mean, the people
that start in London has have probably
got a better life than most people, but
they for some reason they like starting
things they can't finish.
And I don't know why there's so many
[ __ ] in London. Like they don't
understand that they're very very
privileged. And then the maddest thing
is you speak to somebody
in um in a third world country and
they're the nicest people you ever meet.
So it's like they don't realize how
privileged they are and they're still
[ __ ] [ __ ] everywhere in this
in this [ __ ] city. And I don't know
why, bro. You know,
they don't try to help people who's
lost. They try to start on random people
that they don't even know, then run away, you know,
cuz one day, bro, I'll just end up
hurting one of these people, bro. I
swear to God,
it's always the white people as well
from London. [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] proper [ __ ] You know,
they think they're better than everyone
and they're [ __ ] not better than no mate. You understand?
Yeah. Must do, bro. Must do.
It's a weird It's weird, bro.
But yeah, I ain't really been
approaching. I ain't done anything, bro.
Ain't really had time for the gym to be
honest. I went today. Well, I tried to
go today and I was there for like 30
minutes, but it was too packed. So
other things to think about, bro. Nope.
All I know is the bike kept taking me
there two weeks ago. I just went out two
weeks ago on the bike and I made up a
story that I was working. Obviously, I
don't [ __ ] work. I don't need to
[ __ ] work, but I just told these
people just to see what they would do.
Just like the Foot Locker thing.
But it kept taking me there. So
I just going to random places. Yeah.
There will never be no updates, bro.
She's a [ __ ]
She started something that she can't finish. Simple.
You know what I'm saying? But yeah,
but like I would ever tell any of these
people I work and why would I even need
to work anyways?
If someone gets 3k a month, why the [ __ ]
would they need to work?
But it's a shame though. It is a shame
because on a normal community, right? Do
you ever remember like travel vloggers,
like normal communities, you could tell
people where you're going, when you're
going, what time you're going, what
you're making. Like, you could tell
everything and there'd be no glasses.
There'd be no no one on this community.
It's like you can't even have proper
conversations because there's too many
jealous glasses. But you can't even have
proper conversations because you'll say
stuff and then somebody will be like,
"Oh, well that doesn't make any that
doesn't make any sense. That logically
doesn't make any sense." You can't go in
depth because of the grasses. So it's
like you can only tell like 20% of a story.
And I think I can practice what I
preach. Bro, the only thing the only
time I started something I can't finish
was with my mom's neighbor. And that was
for my mom's sake cuz she lives there.
That's the only time I've started
something I can't finish. I started
something on that USA Izzy about a month
and a half ago and I would have finished
it, mate, by the time that week was up.
Trust me. So what excuse do these people
have? They live in the same country,
bro. Like what the [ __ ]
I would have started it and I would have
finished it, bro.
Had the money there and then. Have the
money there and then. It's not a problem.
Stop it, bro. It's embarrassing.
I would have slapped up that [ __ ]
damn as well. Cheeky little [ __ ] talking
about how he's going to [ __ ] cut
people's dicks off and everything. Madness, bro.
But that's like that's the only time.
But I can't do anything cuz my mom it so Yeah,
it's a shame though, is it?
Yeah, these people's annoying me.
I was sacked. Never had a delivery job.
Like I said, I tell you what I want you
to know. Deliver, bro. Why would I have
a delivery job when I get [ __ ] three
grand a month? You stupid idiot. It's
like when I used to tell Pat Must I work
in Foot Locker. Yeah, you asking
forever. Stop talking about yourself.
Yep, you're talking about yourself
again, mate. Like I said, buddy, when
you've got the balls to come and say it
to my face,
I'm here. You can join the hangouts and
I will meet you today. If you're not
going to do that, bye-bye. Simple. Like,
bro, be a keyboard warrior all you want. Yeah. So,
you're never going to say anything to
anyone's face. You asking. Stop talking
about yourself. Never had a delivery job
in my life, mate. I've not worked for
years. Yeah. Just like I worked in Foot
Locker in it. Yeah. Yeah. Like I work in
Foot Locker in it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Bro, like I work in Foot Locker in it.
Yeah. Like I'm working, bro. It
These people really are [ __ ] aren't
they, bro? They really are [ __ ]
They're just self-reflectors, isn't it?
They tell people to work and then when
they think people work, i.e. put locker,
i.e. anything, then they try to grasp on
people. So, which which one is it?
So that just goes to show that they're
just talking about themselves. You know,
when they say that people are skinned,
they got no job, they're just talking
about their own lives.
They're just literally talking about
their own lives. Because as soon as they
think people are working,
even though I've worked for like 10
years, when they think that people are
working, they try to grasp. So like,
which one is it? You can't play two
sides of a coin here.
None of these people work on here
because if these people worked on here,
bro, they wouldn't have the time to do
what they do. They would not have the
time to do what they do, bro. Believe
that. The only way that they would um be
able to um
do it is if they were like if they owned
like a restaurant maybe. But trust me,
bro, none of these people on here work.
Believe that, bro. Believe that. Cuz
when if any of these people try to say
they work, yeah, ask them how do you
work? What do you do for work? How do
you have the time, bro? You don't
understand that when you work, cuz I
worked 10 years ago, you have stress
that comes with a job and you wouldn't
have time to be on there projecting. You
wouldn't have time to be on here doing
what these people do.
With that Joe, I can kind of believe he
works cuz he's not on it all day every
day. There's possibilities, brother. I'm
telling you these people, they do not
work. I'm telling you, they don't work,
bro. Believe me, they do not work. Trust
me, they don't. They're just 40 year old
Mongaloids that ain't got nothing better
to do than to self-reflect their [ __ ]
lives onto others every day. So,
yeah, I got a phone number at the train
station the other day.
with these women anymore.
I've got money. I know what I can do. I
know what I can provide in a
relationship, bro. It's their loss. They
don't want it. It's their loss. You
know, I've got enough phone numbers. I
don't need to try again. I'm leaving
this country tomorrow. I I don't need
I've got nothing left to prove. What
have you got left to prove?
You put No, she didn't block me. You put
what you've got on the table. They don't
want to accept it. That's their loss,
bro. Simple. I don't I'm not asked.
I had my friend complaining about it
earlier today. I said, "You either leave
or get used to it. It's how many times
are we going to keep going over the same
thing, bro? It's so that's I know what I
have." And yeah, if that's not good
enough, I don't care. [ __ ] them. Their
loss, not mine. So,
cuz it gets to a point like how long are
you going to keep doing this and how
long are you going to keep going over
this? I have a boyfriend. All like, bro,
like we get it. Like, what have you got
left to prove? Nothing.
And when you come out of the gym and you
can barely get a conversation out of
someone, it tells you all you need to know.
So it's like you got nothing left to prove,
you know, at 27. So the weather's hot, man.
The weather's hot.
Really hot. Yeah.
But when I come back, I won't be on it
no more, bro. So, if you want a new
channel, you got to email me cuz this is
I've already got a time, bro.
Cuz this is getting weird, bro. Really
[ __ ] weird. I got a tan, but I had a
tan. Oh, no. It's a time, but it's
getting less and less now.
Getting less and less. Yeah, bro.
It's all good.
So yeah, man.
So yeah, you can't have proper
conversations on here where you can't tell.
What's going on with this [ __ ] smoky
be as well?
[ __ ] [ __ ] ears.
Look, Lar Spoons all by himself. I'm
here all by myself cuz I'm tired today.
I do. Look at that, bro.
Is the smoky be on days? One second.
Somebody go on channel. Remember
that USA is he Steven Howard?
She is a [ __ ] in it. Proper [ __ ]
She's another one, man. She was big. She
was really big until she met her match.
Really big until she met her match.
Five example. It
keeps taking me to places. I can show
you exactly where I was, bro. Let me
turn up my other phone if you want. Kept
taking me there, bro. This was two weeks
ago. I only wrote it two weeks ago.
Show you this.
Why stop? Like, why do all of that, bro?
Like, if you ain't going to back up your
talk. I don't get it, bro.
You're a [ __ ] idiot.
I'll show you exactly on my other phone.
This phone was £400. One second.
He got wellbellied. Peterbellied.
Where is it, man? somewhere.
Look at that view, man.
Look at that view, bro. [Music]
That's beautiful. That view, mate.
I'll show you, bro. Look.
So, I met the [ __ ]
just behind that
Get a job, you bomb. Same to you. Get a
job, you you are a bomb. Yeah, but like
I said, smorg wasn't saying any of this
[ __ ] to me when I was in Newcastle.
So whatever you say, whatever you say,
bro, it's pointless because man's been
to Newcastle three times and uh yeah,
look, can you see it?
This was two weeks ago, bro. I was cycling around.
You see behind that eye. It's a beautiful view.
Anyway, smoking the tide. You get a job.
Yeah. Why don't you get a job?
Yeah, it's a good meeting place, buddy.
telling me to get a job when you don't
have a job yourself.
Why do you do this, bro?
You tell people to get a job, but you
don't even have a job yourself. It's embarrassing, bro.
It's embarrassing, isn't it? Steen Alwood.
They don't have a job themselves and
then when they think that you've got a
job, they try to make you lose your job.
But yeah, that was two weeks ago, bro.
Good view, is it? Good view.
I also got another view where there was
a load of old bill
saying there. Look at look at look at that bro.
That is what you call a load of old bill. [ __ ] me.
Our road got [ __ ] closed off. But yeah,
it is boring, bro. They need to get a job themselves.
They don't have a job, bro. None of
these people have a job. Trust me, bro.
None of these people ever work
a [ __ ] day in their life, mate.
Not even a day in their life. Could
you imagine a virgin working Steven? Yeah.
Could you imagine, bro? The virgin at work.
you imagine the virgin?
[ __ ] kill him, mate. [ __ ] kill him.
You would kill that virgin, mate. A day's work.
But say that he might actually be able
to lose his virginity. If he actually
got a job, he might be able to earn more
money and and then being able to lose his virginity
and stop being such a virgin.
Oh, USA is the Oh.
USA is is such a [ __ ] in it.
And the thing is, she's not living her
best life cuz what? What? You got a
partner with a and a job that she has to
go to every day. That's not really
living your best life, is it really?
Why? That's why he's still a [ __ ]
virgin. I keep saying this to you, bro.
He's still a [ __ ] virgin.
He's still a [ __ ] virgin, mate.
These people are [ __ ] weird, lad.
What makes you say that?
Well, yeah, cuz the normal Izzy was my
fault. That was my kind. That was my
fault to be fair.
No, she's worse as in like
the way she is.
She was a [ __ ] as well. She deserved
everything. She got the family
messaging. Like she deserved everything,
bro. What he means is worse as in like
she done worse.
Yeah. Cuz with Izzy. Yeah.
Cuz with Izzy. Yeah. you you brought it
on yourself cuz you brought someone on
YouTube that was 18, you got trolled to
[ __ ] So like
you kind of brought that on yourself in
a way like at least 75% of it. But with
this whole uh
with this whole American one, she
started it, bro. She started it and
there was no YouTube. There was no
YouTube. There was no nothing. And she
started it. So yeah, she's way worse.
Couldn't back up her [ __ ] talk
either. Like I'm scared of anyone she
knows. Are you mad, bro? Please.
Yeah, I hate her, bro. With a patch. I
hate that [ __ ]
You don't know, bro. I hate that [ __ ] Really, bro? Yeah.
These people are [ __ ] bro. Yeah,
but I don't think I'll try again here
even when I come back. To be fair, I
can't be bothered with it, bro. The
whole women [ __ ] anymore. It's [ __ ]
boring as [ __ ]
I don't even think about it anymore.
It's so boring, bro.
They're all NPCs. They're all non-playing characters.
They're literally non-playing
characters. You try to speak to someone,
they've got no conversation in them.
Then um and the only conversation they
have is I've got a boyfriend. So, I
mean, it's just boring, isn't it? They
bore me, bro. They really, really bore
me. It's so boring as well. [ __ ]
I just hiccuped there.
It's so boring, bro.
I hate it, bro. Me.
I gave up with it. I still got some. Yeah,
it just goes to show Stephen that like
you never meet someone when you least
expect it or and what really raised red
flags for me Yeah. is when I come out
the gym and I can barely get a
conversation out of someone. I was like, "Oh [ __ ]
That's [ __ ] up, bro." Like, if you
can't even get a conversation out of someone,
it's not looking good, is it, bro?
You have to match it up with what people say.
It's like, so what? You're all of a
sudden going to find a relationship or a friendship
when you can barely even get a
conversation at someone.
Like that's that's not normal, bro. So
then it's not like they had a
conversation and they were genuinely in
relationships or they generally weren't
interested. They generally didn't really
even say anything.
No, it wasn't from the gym. It was It
was around the mall. It was It was on a
street. It's It's just when I come out
of the gym. I didn't even plan to do it.
I just thought, "Oh, let me do a
couple." It was It was a Wednesday, then
I went out on Wednesday drinking.
No, it was just around the shopping center.
I was like, "Oh, [ __ ] Yeah, this is
this is impossible, man."
And then other things were like, "Oh,
well, you're not fat and ugly like Timmy
and all of these people." So then it's
like, yeah, you need to kind of leave
this country now, bro. You have nothing
left to prove.
You You have nothing left to prove, bro.
What the [ __ ]
One one ignored me, one, another one
ignored me, and then another one said I
had a boyfriend.
So it's like,
that's weird, bro. You know what I mean? Yeah,
there's just too many stuck up women in this country.
That's um and that's what I put down to
and I just gave up, bro. I don't really
care anymore. I don't care. It doesn't
bother me. I've got other things to
think about, bro.
Yeah, it is the worst.
And you know they don't have boyfriends
because think of how many men are
single. So many men are single. It's
like what my friend said. He's like,
"Oh, it's like one in five men are in a relationship.
There's more women on earth than men,
but yet they've all got boyfriends.
It's like it's pointless, bro.
They all have attitude problems and
um shit." So
yeah, bro, it doesn't bother me anymore.
I've had enough experiences with them as
well, bro. I don't really care
if they want to fit their bed and people
leave them to it, bro. It's don't care
anymore, man. You know,
you know what I mean?
It's always going to be the same. Just
stuck up women addicted to Tik Tok. It's
never going to change. But
I got I got some numbers that Wednesday, but
none replied. It's got worse. It's
definitely got worse. It gets worse
every year, bro.
Um so there's just no point, bro. Just
leave him to it. It
unless you've got a million subscribers on YouTube
or some famous Tik Tocker, you got no
chance in this country. Simple as.
I've accepted it now, bro. I don't care
about it. Like, I've got my mind on
other things. So,
but you that that's the first thing you
need to do. You need to give up hope cuz
there is no hope. You know, this has
been going on for years now. You know,
you went you went out in the gym the
other day, you couldn't even get a
conversation out someone.
Like, bro, come on. It's time to like
wake up and smell the coffee. Do you
want to still be doing this at 35
saying, "Oh, I told you so. I told you
so." Like, what kind of life is that,
bro? You know what I mean?
You have enough numbers. The way I saw
it yesterday is I've got enough numbers.
I can fit some time in.
Let me offer these people out for the
next two weeks. You've got enough
numbers on your phone. Germany have got
enough numbers on your phone. You know, it's like
taking women [ __ ] up. Weird. Like
Yeah. Yeah, I am looking forward to
that. But I'm just saying I've got to
come back. I've still got to come back
in two weeks.
I'm not going with a train there.
Obviously not. You [ __ ] ill.
No, I can't be bothered with it, bro.
It's not my problem anymore. Which is
why I'm leaving the country. It's not my problem.
This whole thing is not my problem anymore.
It's your problem or whoever's problem
that chooses to stay in this country.
It's not my problem anymore.
It's your problem. It's not my problem anymore.
Don't even approach anybody even about.
I can't be asked
taking women. But what what made me
laugh is no one on Reddit ever told me
this, Steven Howard. No one on the
internet ever told me this that oh
you're going to come across piss taking
women or women that pretend they've got
boyfriends. Like I never heard it.
It's a bit [ __ ] that you lied to your
whole life in it. I know I've said this
many times, but like do you not find it
a bit cunny having lied to you your whole life?
It's a bit strange, isn't it?
It is a bit strange. Do you think
stick the [ __ ] test on them tonight?
I'm not going out today, bro. Even if I
weren't going away tomorrow, I'm still
not going out today. Why would I waste
my money going out, bro? What the [ __ ]
Is it all of a sudden going to change,
bro? You need to get real about it. If
something was going to happen, it would
have happened by now. It's been years.
It's been going on for years. Nothing's
all of a sudden going to change.
Things don't take long to change.
You know what I'm saying? Like that long ago,
you know, even when you don't approach
like even when I've been cycling, even
when I cycled around that two weeks ago,
never did I see a woman that did look
stuck up. Same attitude, same NPC ways.
And I didn't even speak to them. They're
all the same. They they're they're all
they're all NPCs. They're non-playing characters.
Like they've been they've been
brainwashed by Tik Tok. They've been
brainwashed by Instagram.
It's pointless even trying to speak to someone now.
So like they're all they're all the same.
There was somebody the other day that
come out the house. Oh. And I was like,
"Oh, they said I said, "Are you
American? Are you from are you
American?" No. Are you Irish? Said,
"No." I'm Dutch. I said, "Oh, I've been
to Amsterdam." And I was trying to start
a conversation and you could tell they
didn't really want to talk. This was the
other day as I won't even hitting on
them, but just cuz I've been there. You
just can't even get a conversation out
of them, let alone a relationship, let
alone [ __ ] a friendship.
That's also something to add in in in in um
in the video. That is concerning. Very concerning, bro.
Well, it's not concerning. It's just the
same [ __ ] I'm saying, but you get me.
No, bro. Never mind.
It's like this French one. I'm not
actually in the UK. Well, you are in the
UK cuz you live in the UK, you know.
How are you not in the UK when you live
in the UK? That doesn't even make sense.
But why does the virgin get so bitter
about me meeting women as well? for like
the little virgin. Why does he get so
bitter about it?
Such a virgin.
And he tries to like bait people so then
he can run to the police. He's such a
loser, bro. He's such a [ __ ] loser.
He's like he chats [ __ ] then tries to
bait people to try to get the police
involved. He's a loser.
You're a proper proper loser, bro.
It's cuz you don't have a life. He's a
[ __ ] virgin. It's like he panics.
Yeah. Every woman I speak to, he's like,
"Oh, I hope they're not interested. He's
such a little virgin."
But he don't have a life. That's the
whole point. He don't have a life. He's
a [ __ ] virgin.
Think of it, bro. He's nothing but a
[ __ ] little bit of urgent.
They're all weird. They're all weird.
They're all [ __ ] weird, bro. I was
off of YouTube for [ __ ] 10 days.
He's a proper virgin, bro.
How is that French woman not in the UK
when she lives in the UK? She told me
exactly where she lives.
Oh yeah, he's a proper proper virgin.
That's why I used to call him one
because he's he's the king of virgins.
He is literally the king of all virgins.
Like he should have a crown. Yeah. on
his head to cover up that receding hairline
and uh be called literally the king of
virgins cuz he's the biggest one going.
That's why he knows all the telltale
signs cuz he's the biggest one himself.
You understand? You pick somebody that's
got a [ __ ] girlfriend that proves
that they've had sex.
No, it does not.
He's the biggest one going. That's why
he always used to he he never used to
believe the stories that I used to tell
him. I said, "Yeah, I [ __ ] an escort.
It woke up the whole house. Then I
[ __ ] another escort." Like I've been
active from 17. And he used to make up
stories. Oh, they ask you for ID. I
said, "No, they don't. Escorts never ask
people for ID." And no they don't. I
know because I've used them. And any
story I would tell him, he he would
literally not believe it. And I think at
one point, I think I had to get my mom.
I think it was my mom. It was my mom, I
think it was. And it was all because
he's the virgin. Like I didn't I didn't
know it from from years ago cuz I was
young, but I was like 17, 18.
Used to go to the Pizza Hut, used to go
to the Burger King. And I think I had my
mom on the phone once and she had to
literally tell him that yeah like he
woke us up with the escort
all because he's a virgin himself and
he's going to die one you know sometimes
bro listen I actually sometimes when I'm
on the street it does cross my mind like
he's going to die a virgin like I
wouldn't wish that on anyone I wouldn't
wish I'm being 31 and still being a
[ __ ] virgin know what I'm saying that.
Yeah, he's he he's a proper proper
proper virgin. But it might not be where
he's not had it's it might not just be
where he's not had that opportunity to
have sex. There could be something where
it don't go in like a medical problem
cuz I had a friend that his dick wasn't
working properly. Had to go hospital
with him. As gay as that sounds, it was
a specific hospital and he wanted me to
accompany him obviously look at his
dick. It could be as simple as maybe
erectile dysfunction. Maybe maybe it
don't work properly. You know, there's
something where it don't go in. You know
what I'm saying? But it could be various
various different things. But he's
definitely definitely a virgin.
Definitely a virgin. 100% complete
Complete [ __ ] virgin, son.
Yeah, I couldn't imagine being a virgin
at that age, bro. I literally couldn't imagine it.
That's sad, bro. It
technically had sex when I was 17.
I could imagine being 31 and a virgin,
bro. That's [ __ ] up.
At least once. At least have it once. I mean,
what's for dinner today?
That smoky be is a [ __ ] Oh,
making a cup of [ __ ] in a minute.
And I was thinking of like
cuz I've saved a bit of money.
Somebody's number I'll be like, "Oh,
let's go to a steak restaurant. See what
their response will be.
And if nothing happens, bro, when I come
back, I'm not trying with anyone again.
They could [ __ ] themselves. If they want
to think that they're better than me and
whatever, then let them, bro. I don't
care. Like, what what have I got left to
prove in this country, bro? Nothing.
Simple. Been there, worn the t-shirt.
Like I just said to you, bro, what are
you proving? What What you going to keep
trying until you're 35?
Yeah. If you want to go out for a drink
and try then yeah, you know that's not
really trying cuz you're just drinking
anyways. But I mean like in terms of
like going out your way to find someone
like what are you trying to prove here, bro?
Other than I told you so. You know it's
the same old. You know it's the same
[ __ ] You know it's never going to change.
It will never change in this country
ever. So what the [ __ ] bro? Don't be a
I told you so. You know what I mean? Sorry, buddy.
You still there, Steven Howard? Yeah.
I can't believe that USA Izzy
didn't even apologize
cuz my whole thing was making the rumor
is true. You know, that was my whole
point is to try and make the rumors true.
And I don't know why her dad is so mad
at me. Like it's it's what needs to
happen. you know, somebody that makes up
lies about someone and [ __ ] and and not
even it weren't even the lies. It was
the whole of what they done. It weren't
even just the silly little lies. That's
like my Well, it's not mine though. It's
pretty [ __ ] up, but it weren't the
main part. Like, what what the [ __ ] did
he expect? Now, if we're actually going
back on it, what did he actually expect?
It's not like they left it on good terms
and they didn't mock you and then you
just all of a sudden didn't accept it.
Like they were [ __ ] with you from the
start. So I don't know what he actually expected.
Like even if it if it was just lies then
it would have been a different story.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] up. But it's all of
what they actually done. So I don't
understand what why he was so surprised
when I told him that what he's been
doing. It's not a case of like stuff
being normal or not being normal, but
it's like you wanted to mock someone's kindness.
So, what I don't understand what they were expecting
or you just used to like are you used to
[ __ ] people over and somebody not
standing up for themselves?
Cuz it seems that that's the way it is.
It seems very much that's the way it is.
You know what I'm saying? Like,
do you feel sorry for that [ __ ] I
don't feel sorry for that [ __ ] at all, bro.
But even 3 years later, if I ever see
that [ __ ] bro, I will tell her about
her to her face, bro. 3 years later, I'd
still do it.
I would, bro. I might not beat the [ __ ]
up, but I tell her about myself to her
face. But if I saw Izzy, I'll just walk
past her, be like, "Fuck you." But this
one, I would actually I'll tell her
about herself to her face, bro. Even
sometimes now when I'm bored, like I'll
go like when I'm really really bored,
I'll go and find ways. I just contact
the [ __ ] saying, "Yeah, what you say
now, you little bitch."
Like or say something or like try to
arrange me going over there, but they
won't have any of it.
They won't have any of it.
But yeah, her dad was mad at me for contacting him.
I don't understand what what he actually expected,
you know, like what the [ __ ]
[ __ ] it, bro.
I don't think they've ever ever had
something like that happen before.
They're so used to just [ __ ] with
people. But they got what they deserved,
you know? They got what they deserved.
Really, I I don't feel bad. I don't feel
like I done anything wrong. Me,
I don't feel like I did anything wrong
with that one. I feel like, yeah, I
might have went over the top, but like
no, I don't think I done anything wrong.
I think they deserved it
to be honest.
And if they lived here, it would have
been a lot worse. Trust me.
Cuz I would have went to where they like
if if they lived here, bro, I would have
went to where they worked. Trust me. I
would have went on their door. I would
have went to where they worked. I would
everything, bro. Trust me.
You'll be You'll beat your match one
day, mate. You'll beat your match one day.
I will be if I Well, I don't do anything
wrong, but if I was to continuously [ __ ]
with people, I'd beat my match.
You know, you'll beat your match one
day, mate. Trust me.
She's nasty, bro.
I can't believe I bought that [ __ ] a
[ __ ] steak. Steven Howard, [ __ ] me.
I can't believe I bought
[ __ ] steak. What the [ __ ] bro?
You don't think that's crazy, bro?
[ __ ] hell, bro.
[ __ ] these [ __ ] Ladies good.
The dog's good as well.
Yeah, I I speak to my sister, my other
sister. My sister and my mom, but I just
don't speak to my other sister.
Yeah, I just don't really, you know,
don't like each other. So, my other
sister, I was out with her the other day
drinking my I just don't talk to my other sister.
But that's all right. You know, you're
not always going to get up with all of
all of your siblings. Um
because I just don't like we just I just
don't like her. Simple. So don't be
scared to it.
Think she's very selfish. But yeah, my mother's cool. Yeah. Um
yeah, I don't like the other one. It's been cool.
I need to get into it. But yeah. Yeah.
The buy the money back from who? That
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
No, it was about the money, bro. I
didn't Why would I care about money? I
had a lot of money, you know.
So, how do you make money nowadays,
Stephen? Now, when we was thinking about
it, we were talking about this earlier.
How do you make money? I don't think you
can, is it? You can't make money on
YouTube because it's impossible to get
part the ship now. Almost.
I don't think you can. There's no money
in the gambling industry.
Now, you can't make money nowadays, bro.
Not nowadays. The land. [Laughter]
You can't get cash and eye jobs.
They're like almost impossible to get
now. Cash in a hand job, mate. It's hard
enough getting a normal [ __ ] job, let
alone a cash in hand job.
No, you can't get you can't get them anymore.
You can't get them anymore, matey.
You can't. And there's nobody in the
gambling industry anymore. It's kind of
dried up the money, is it?
No, you can't make money nowadays, bro.
Maybe you could stop it, but that's about it.
But then you need to get a house and
there's no ways to make money nowadays. 80, bro.
I told these people I was making money
working and I just started to [ __ ] with them.
Then they tried to pass in. But yeah,
I thought we would actually tell these
people that I work idiot. Yeah, right.
Glasses in it. Data.
Bit [ __ ] in it, Steven Howard.
It's [ __ ] mate.
Well, at least we're not skin like
Virgin, is it? He's skinning
skin flint, lad.
He's skinn than a [ __ ] skin flint.
And a [ __ ] skin flint, lad.
Skinner than a [ __ ] skin flint.
Skint and a [ __ ] skin.
Isn't he cherry cherry tree bened by a
skint and a fing skin?
Oh, you're making me hungry now. I might
get very hardy today. He's skinting skin.
I used to I used to beat him at the
money game. I used to be like, "Where's
your [ __ ] money? I want to see the
color of your money." You used to hate
that in it. You remember the 50 pounds
of that? I still have money, but I don't
go casino anymore, so I don't have cash.
But remember, she used to like that.
He used to hate that in it.
You can just tell he used to beat up.
You could just tell we used to beat up
Sarah in it. I want to see the power of
you ever. You ain't got You used to hate
it, man. It used to hate it, mate. Your mother Your mother,
he's committed suicide, mate. That's
where your mother's gone. Yeah.
Oh my god.
That's where your mother's gone. By
catching the high job could not get
it, right? Oh
yeah, she's left you mate. She lives in America.
See, he said I've got anxiety this be. I
literally said I was going to come to
build Ke today.
I said I was going to go to Bill Ke today.
I said I was going to go with Kings.
I look he's right away.
What a [ __ ] idiot. Run his mouth on
YouTube, but a little [ __ ] in real
life. Just like most of them. See these
plastics on there? They really do.
They really belong together.
The spastics of this community, they
really really belong together. it.
The only good thing USA Izzy had was big boobies,
but they were all fat anyways. So,
but I hate that [ __ ] bro. For real. I
hate them, bro. I hate women. They're kind of
Yep. Stop talking about yourself. It's
not nice to call yourself a loser.
Bye-bye. Bye-bye, self-reflector.
Like I said, bro, if you've got anything
to say, you can come and say to my face.
Other than that, cheerio.
I don't know what I should eat. Maybe a macadox.
But then you just get hungry after, so it's pointless.
I don't know what I'm going to eat, bro.
I'm [ __ ] tired. I'm [ __ ] hungry, bro.
I'm trying to think what I could eat.
I'm so hungry, but I don't know what I fancy. Who's this?
No, I don't fancy KFC.
Maybe a botti.
I don't know. I fancy, bro. By baby. Yep. Tomorrow.
Show plane ticket. Show plane ticket.
How about you suck my dick and I'll show
you the plane ticket. You didn't even
smell a plane properly, you [ __ ]
Yeah, show plane ticket so you can try
and stop me boarding a plane tomorrow.
Yeah, bro. Keep dreaming.
You spelled plane. You spelled plane wrong.
Yeah, I've just been busy the past
couple of weeks, Alex. Man, I don't
bother with the approaching other women
anymore, bro. It's I can't be annoyed
with it, bro.
I'm not saying, bro. I'm not saying
early. I'm not saying when too many
grasses on here.
These people think I'm working and
they're trying to grasp me up for
working and they don't even know that I
was just chatting [ __ ] to them the whole
time. They're [ __ ] proper retards. I
hate this community, bro. I swear if I
ever catch one of these people in this
community, they're going to get they're
going to get good hiding, bro.
Look at Smokey Be shut his mouth now.
What's the point, bro? Come on.
If I ever catch one of these people
here. Yeah, I need to get a good [ __ ] hiding.
A good [ __ ] good old hiding, bro. I swear down.
Just any one of them, bro. I hate them,
you know. I actually hate them. The more
I come on here, the more like I actually
hate these people. You don't understand?
They start [ __ ] They put people in a
bad mood and then they run off [ __ ]
start [ __ ] all the [ __ ] time.
What's the point?
Do they bully me? No, they they bully themselves.
No, they're just [ __ ] They're just
creepy. They creep me out. Bully me, but
none of these people can ever bully me.
I will meet any one of these people from this community. Bye-bye.
These people bully themselves, mate.
They creep me out. They're creepy.
But now these people don't bully no one
because the thing is, right, they have
my address. I've offered one guy out today
and he has literally not responded back
and he has wrote comment after comment
after comment after comment after
comment. I said I will meet him today
and he's gone quiet. So, no, these
people don't bully no one. They bully
themselves. They embarrass the No, no,
they don't bully themselves. They
embarrass themselves on YouTube every
day. That's what they do. They embarrass
themselves. They're [ __ ] disabled,
bro. That's what they do. They embarrass
themselves on YouTube. They're [ __ ]
disabled. If they really bullied people,
people wouldn't be coming back on here.
People would either kick a bully's ass
or they would stop coming on something.
You're calling me out. One second. Hold
on. Hold on. You're calling me out.
Okay, I'll put the link up.
You're calling me out, [ __ ] Boy.
Okay, let me put the link out.
Calling me out, bro. You are not calling
me out. One second. What?
You don't bully people. You just show
yourselves up every day on YouTube.
Like I'm here. I have said, bro, for the
past [ __ ] god knows how many hours,
one of you people join the hangouts and
I'll meet any of you today and you will run away.
So it's like, who are you really
bullying but yourselves? Yeah, you come
online. Yeah, you write stuff behind the
keyboard. You've been doing that for
years, but you're never ever going to
say anything to anyone's face. You're
never going to come on anyone's door.
You're never going to meet anyone
It's just people every [ __ ] every day
calling out my lies. How am I lying, bro?
You people really are spasticated. Like
there's there's no point even like
explaining anything to you people.
But no, you people don't bully no one.
You bully yourselves and you embarrass
yourselves. How can you bully somebody
behind the keyboard?
Think about that. Doesn't even make any
sense. You bully somebody behind the keyboard.
But you're living your worst life. So
how could you be bullying anyone when
you're living your worst life? Sat on
YouTube, no no money, can't leave your
house. Do not think that you're the one
who's actually being bullied by life.
Think about it, bro. You come online,
you write a few mean things to somebody
that's living life whilst you're scared
to leave your house. You got no money,
you got no friends, and you got no life.
Who's the one that's really being
bullied by life? You are. No one else.
You don't bully no one, bro. Yeah. Really?
Is that true, bro? Okay,
that's nice, bro. Why don't you come on camera?
Self projecting. You're already bored. Another self-reflector.
So my hairline goes further
than your recliner, bro. But do you know
the difference is you're already bored.
So I mean,
yeah. I mean, it doesn't really make any
sense cuz you're just self projecting
again because you're already bored.
What have I told you about self? Listen,
bro. Let me let me tell you something
though. Let me sit up a second. Oh,
[ __ ] Back's a bit [ __ ] Let me say
something to you very clearly. No matter
what you say about my appearance, you're
never going to make me insecure. You're
never going to make me stop showing my
face. You're never going to make me
think, "Oh, are these people on YouTube
right?" No. Because you're just talking
about yourself. So, it doesn't I don't
know how many times I have to say this.
Think about it, bro. I show my face, you
can't. That says a lot. That says a
[ __ ] lot that I can show my face, but you can't.
So, you're talking about yourself. Yeah,
it's true about yourself. You're bored.
You're fat. You're ugly. Yeah, it is
true about yourself.
Stop it. You're going to make me high
again, bro. I won't be able to stop
laughing. It is true. Yes. About
yourself. You're talking about yourself, brother. Listen.
And you know what I think it is with
these people? I think their disability
gets you confused with them. That's what
it is. They because of their disability,
they get theirelves confused with you. I
think it's part of their disability. I
was actually thinking about this two
weeks ago, lad. I'm overweight. Not
overweight. Bro, again, you're talking
about yourself. Okay, bro. [ __ ] all this
[ __ ] I'm being very rude here. One second.
Right. There's the Hold on.
Join the Join the Hangouts.
Join the Hangouts and put your camera on, mister. on.
I know, right? Turkish barber. Oh,
really? Nice, man. Anyways, uh join the
hangouts and put your camera on. We will
see who the real fat ugly bastard is.
Come on. Come on. Don't be a little pussycat.
We will see one big fat ugly
[ __ ] Where'd you put that
camera on? Come on. You're not camera
shy, are you? I've gone high again. Come
on, you big ugly [ __ ] What are
you waiting for? Stop hide behind your
little keyboard. You gay boy.
Gay boy. Gay boy. Stop running away. Gay
boy. Nah. Handsome. You're not handsome,
bro. You're a big ugly [ __ ] You
can't even come on camera. You're camera
shy. You big ugly [ __ ]
You big fat ugly baldy baldy can't join.
The baldy [ __ ] can't join you.
It was self-reflector
again. Don't start something you can't
finish. It makes you look stupid. You
baldy [ __ ] Cuz you know what
would happen, bro? If someone if I went
on if I went on a on a community, right,
and I was talking about someone and they
put their camera on, I wouldn't hide
like a little [ __ ] like you. Yeah. Bye-bye now.
Bye-bye now. He's a big ugly
[ __ ] bro. Listen,
I'll start. Yeah. Oops. One second.
I'll put my camera on. I'm not bored.
So, let me wipe this a sec. So, I can
show you the difference, bro.
Sorry, you can't see properly. Right. I
can show you me, bro. I go to the gym.
They're my arms. I've been slacking a
bit lately. Here's my hair. I've got a
bit of a cold.
This is me. I'm not bored. I'm not
Got a lot of stress going on and [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm sure I went to the gym today, but
that's my arms, not fat. This is my
body. What are you waiting for, bro?
Whatever you say about my appearance,
it's not going to bother me. It's not
going to make me start wearing a hat and
think, "Oh, even though I wear a hat now
to keep the the sun off my face, bro,
you're not going to make anyone insecure
cuz you're just talking about yourself."
Look, I even put it back for you if you
want, bro. Look, I'm showing my face.
You can't show your face
for a reason, bro.
You can't show your face for a [ __ ]
re z I can show my little cute face.
See, I I even blinked as well.
So, what the [ __ ] bro? Stop starting
stuff you can't finish. [ __ ]
embarrassing. It's so embarrassing.
Comment on the internet starting
something that you can't finish.
You come on here, you call me all of
these nasty names, right? I'm on camera.
Yeah. With my little cap,
but none of you can join.
None of you can join.
Why? Why can't any of you join? Why not?
No red store. No Smokey Me. No. No one.
Cuz they're all fat ugly bastards.
DJ, why don't anyone of these other
these other people join?
Cuz they're all fat ugly bastards.
B. Hey, look. I can even do a little
hairstyle for you if you want.
Look at that gorgeous face. It's so cute.
Oh, see, look. I can even do a funny
hairstyle for you if you want. Nope. I
got nothing wrong there.
Like, come on, bro. You're supposed to
be bullying me here. I'm showing my
face. You don't make me insecure. I even
done a funny hairstyle for you. But
you're the one that can't even join the hangouts.
So, it doesn't really make a lot of
sense, does it? Yeah, bro.
See the thing is bro what you got to
understand is these people in this
community can say anything behind the
keyboard but they can never join they
can never show their face and that's
when you always become the winner think
about it bro if I if I was on a community yeah
starting on someone for their looks say
there was like a load of people yeah and
I was saying you're this you're that
and then they put the camera on And then
they put the link up and they said, "Why
don't you join?" Then I would join. Then
I would join. If you don't join, it's
cuz you're an ugly bastard. If you're
giving someone [ __ ] lad. Uh, I'm insecure,
bro. You're talking about yourself. The
link is up. Join. Jeez. Sorry, but this
guy isn't. You are down. You are down.
Syndrome. Stop talking about yourself. I'm insecure.
Okay. Join the hangouts and show your face.
I'm insecure again. Your disability has
got you mixed up with me again, buddy.
You're talking about yourself. You're a
loner. You're in your 40s.
You are fat. You are ugly. You can't
join. You are talking about yourself
again. Your autism has got you confused
with me and you, bro. Join a hangout and
cut your camera on. Simple.
I'm going to ban you now cuz you've
injected enough today. So, it's like,
what the [ __ ] is the point, bro?
Why do they start on people that they
don't know and then they can't even put
their camera on? I'm insecure. Never
have I ever been insecure. And only you ugly [ __ ]
would ever make me insecure.
Ever. Are you [ __ ] mad, bro? You
think you ugly bastards could ever make
me insecure? Are you mad?
I'll be gone after today. Anyways, bro,
I won't be back for a month. Even though
I'll be back here in 2 weeks. It's too
weird for me, bro. It's like it's never
going to change.
It's always going to be the same self-p
projecting miserable lowife people. Never changes.
The weather never changes.
having a dowy attack. Oh, bro.
You see what I mean with this Lord J?
He's gambling, bro. This is all these
people do. They're [ __ ] gamblers, man.
That's their life, bro. Gamblers.
Do you like the hat on or do you like
the hat off? I think they both look cool
to be fair.
These people are proper retards, bro. They are.
Proper retards, lad.
Yeah, it's just the same old, bro. Your
skin. Your skin. Yeah, we've heard all
this before, bro. So, I'm just back on
the channel again. Your skin. Your skin.
So crazy, bro. It's just the same [ __ ]
on it, is it? So, back on this channel now.
All they do is themselves.
Whoa, bro. It's so sad.
All of these little 40year-old losers.
All these little 40year-old [ __ ] losers
all coming together. It's so sad, man.
Their lives are like the piss, bro.
Red, bro. Their lives like the [ __ ] piss.
They're all [ __ ] [ __ ] isn't it, bro? Really?
They really are spasticated bastards, bro.
Oh, sorry about that, man. Just making
up a cup of tea.
Yeah, man. So many self-reflectors on
this community. It's unbelievable cuts off.
Yeah, man. Sorry, I need to um keep this
the off my head. Yeah, there we go.
These people talk about themselves every
single day, man.
Actually, I think I might be in a chair
here. It's the only place I can get a signal.
I don't understand it, man. Oops. You
don't get Smokey Be showing his face. Don't get
self-reflective showing their face.
They must be real [ __ ] ugly bastards,
man. Oh, [ __ ]
There we go. Nice in the shade.
Nice in the shade, bro. It's nice, is it?
I was making some serious gains, bro.
I just don't have time to keep going to
the gym. But don't worry, I'll never be
fat like these people. Never.
Thank you, mate. Means a lot.
Yeah, I'll never be like these mongos,
bro. Never be like these mongos.
Like my little hate.
I like Nico in GTA 4, bro. I like Nico
in GTA 4.
I like Nico GTA 4, bro.
He's cute in it. Ste um I'm trying to
figure out what to eat today. Grezy,
but I can't have McDonald's cuz I don't
feel you very much. So, it won't be a McDonald's. No.
Yeah, tomorrow. Sorry about that, man. I
was making a cup of can.
Making a cup of
Yeah, my clothes are on the line. Look,
that pink t-shirt is mine. Yeah, that
Yeah. So, where's Smokey Be gone? He's
been writing all of this [ __ ]
Then when I've offered to go to Milton
Kings, he shut his mouth. Keyboard warrior.
Why? I don't come on here much anymore.
I don't come on here much anymore with
these little sp these little spastics.
Griezy, I like you, bro. You know,
you're you're a pretty good [ __ ] and
Steven Howard, but bro, it gets so weird
so fast. This community gets so weird so
Really, it gets really, really weird,
bro. Really, really weird.
They're London cyclists.
They start [ __ ] they can't finish. Yeah.
I'm just saying, Greavves. I'm like, you
know, I don't care about these [ __ ]
anymore, bro. I'm just going to Thailand
to go on holiday. I don't give a [ __ ]
You know, when I come back, I won't even
be trying unless I'm like blackout
drunk. I don't care about them anymore, bro.
The way I see it, Grezy, is I've got a
lot to offer. And if people don't want
it, bro, [ __ ] them in it. You know, I'm
not [ __ ] begging people. Are you
[ __ ] mad? They can [ __ ] themselves,
bro. You wouldn't even want anything in
this day and age, to be honest.
I'd rather just stick with the little
characters. They would never leave me greasy.
The little characters will never leave
me, will they?
Nah, I can't be bothered, bro. [ __ ] that.
Don't be [ __ ] brother. No,
I don't know why James made me greasy. I
think she wants my little Willy Wonka.
[ __ ] off. Stop getting me involved with YouTube.
This is why I don't like come This is
why I don't like getting involved with
this [ __ ] bro. Because I just get too involved.
I was seriously thinking of going Mil
and Keen. I'm still going to go if he
shows me where he is. If he shows me, I
am going there today. Like, there's no
doubt about it. I was thinking of just
going straight from the gym and just
going there. Grezy, bro, these people
give me mood swings. You know what I mean?
I want to just seriously just [ __ ] one
of them up, bro. You don't understand. Yeah.
Yeah. They're [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. I
swear now, bro. It [ __ ] with your mood as well.
These people [ __ ] with your mood as well, bro.
It's why I don't come on here anymore,
bro. It's why I don't bother.
There's just no point in any of it.
They're just London cyclists. Isn't that right, music?
a quart still.
It's a Spider-Man mug, actually.
Yep. You like that, Grezy?
Grezy, do you like that? It's a Spider-Man mug.
I like Grezy. Yeah, I just care about
the little characters now. Greavves.
I was watching some GTA 4 ones. Um, uh,
some clips from GTA 4 and then how the
guy goes flying. He gets knocked down
and he goes flying.
Do you see it with Nico? He keeps going
flying, bro. What the [ __ ]
But it's a weird community g um gre cuz
you can't say what you want to say on
here because there's so many grasses.
So you'd be telling somebody a story and
then the story doesn't make sense
because the story doesn't make sense
because you can't tell the full story
because of these little grasses. Do you understand Greavvesy?
Yeah. That's why bro this is that's what
I'm saying. You know
it's not a normal community. It's It's
spasticated, right? It's really spasticated.
You know what I mean?
So many weird stalkers on here.
So many weird stalkers on here. You like
my little hair, Grezy? It's quite It's
kind of cute, isn't it?
I can make you laugh, Grezy.
Huh? Grezy, I was on the phone to this
woman yesterday. She keeps calling me.
She won't leave me the [ __ ] alone. And
she was like, "Are you drunk?" No, I was
just so tired yesterday. I couldn't stop laughing.
I was so tired yesterday, bro. I
literally couldn't stop laughing.
I couldn't stop [ __ ] laughing, bro. I
was I felt high, bro. Or like something.
She said, "You are."
I said you're a gun.
I said creepsy.
Creepsy. I said it's a good way of
calling you a can.
It's a good way of calling you a calling
you a c. Crazy. Yeah.
Calling you a [ __ ] Yeah, man.
Still don't know what to eat today.
Got me today. Greasy. I don't know what to eat.
I don't want to take I don't want um I
don't want um an Indian because
might just get a berry, I think.
I know what I'm having, bro. [ __ ] knows.
Nah, I'm not cooking today. I can't be [ __ ]
I can't be [ __ ] to cookie.
No, I can't be bothered.
Timmy, you're not holiday.
You're not on holiday, Timothy. Stop talking rubbish.
You're not on holiday.
You like that green tea?
I don't know what I'm going to eat today, bro.
You're not on holiday, Timothy.
Don't talk rubbish.
Don't forget I know all your little lies
and stuff. I might just go to your
chicken shop, Grezy.
I might just go to the chicken shop.
Is that cute?
Sorry, Timmy. We don't have virgins on
our channel. Bye-bye. You can have a timeout.
You can have a little time out.
How do you like that one, Grezy? You can
have a little break for 5 minutes. We
don't have virgin, bro.
We don't have the you know what virgin
and we don't have you.
Oh, I don't want to see that ugly face
again. Please don't make another YouTube
channel. I don't want to see that ugly
face. That ugly face.
You're going to make me vomit, mate.
Oh, that face is so ugly, bro. I think
these people are lying to themselves,
bro. You know when they try to call me
ugly, bro? I think they're actually
lying to themselves. I think it's part
of their disability, bro.
I sure am, boss. I sure am. Yeah.
Do you remember Greavvesy? Peter Benny
can't get attached anymore because he's
already found his mama.
Oh my god. All the fish and chip stops
here, Greavves, your halal. So whenever
I have Savoy, they put chicken in it. Yuck. Yuck.
Chicken sablo. Yuck. I want a pork one.
I want a piggy one. Funny enough, I went
to Griggs today and I got two sausage rolls. Yep.
I don't want a chicken savoy. I want a
pork one. Who the [ __ ] wants a chicken
savoy? Yuck. Yuck.
No, to be fair, it is [ __ ] disgusting, bro.
I just wanted a nice little satellite, you know.
So cute in there.
I'm going to message my mama
to say I found she a savoy
I want a satellite, but I can't find any
ones here that are not Hello. I might
have to go to the beach.
I'm going to go all the way to the beach
today. Um, greasy just to get a sabot.
That make some good content, is it? Imagine
that, bro. Going all the way to the
beach. You can't get them here, bro.
Most of the stuff here. So, they won't
sell it. Maybe the beach. Maybe.
Yeah. Obviously, we have that problem
over here. Grezy, you don't have that
problem. But yeah, we have a lot of that.
So, obviously, they can't sell um pork.
So, their sausage pork.
I might have to pop to the beach. Easy
with the little
How about What about that? No. Oh, hello.
Hello. You're not going to find a a
kebab shop around there. That's not
allowed, mate. Unless you go to a
Chinese one, but that that means me
walking a couple of miles, which I don't
particularly want to do.
I fancy a little subloid today.
I want a chicken one. I want a pork one. 200.
Two. One sec.
No, you can't cuz all places around
here. So, I can't get a nice pork
sausage. I want a nice little sabai.
Only place you're going to get that is a
Chinese fish shop. And I know one of
them. Or you go to the beach. But that
means going all the way to the beach,
Grezy. That's a bit of a travel.
Imagine going all the way to the beach
to get a little satellite. A, that's so cute. Was
this steak nasty? Nasty.
Yeah, most of the fish and chip shops
places here fish and chip shop places
here here are halal. So, we can't have
it. One second. My calling me.
Yes, you can get pork but not in a fish
and chip shop because most of fish and
chip shops are halal. So yeah, you can
get pork pork chops from the supermarket
or Gregs. Yeah, you can get pork but
just not in a fish and chip shops
because they're halal
because most of them are run by like
Muslim people. So they're they're halal.
only there's only one place I have in
mind. I want a savai sausage,
but savoy is supposed to be pork. And
obviously our places don't sell pork. So
they they replace the pork for chicken,
which is disgusting really. Can't make a
chicken savoite. So you can get pork,
but you're not in fish chip shops.
You can't make something pork, chicken,
and chicken pork. It doesn't make sense.
Sabo are supposed to be pork sausages.
Yeah, I was tasting. I was like, "This
tastes weird, man." It was really grimy. So,
yeah, I didn't like it, bro.
Maybe I'll just have fish and chips.
Maybe I'll just have fish and chips. I
don't know, bro.
Yeah. [ __ ] knows.
Yeah, they do. Turkish people because
they sell kebabs with them. So yeah. Yep.
Muslim. Yeah, they do.
The Smokey be is a [ __ ] y'all.
He is a [ __ ]
No, they don't. It's It's It's Turkish
people that do. Yep.
Um I don't know what to eat today.
There's got to be a berry in it. Got to
be a biryani and two pieces of chicken. I think
it's got to be that, mate. It can't be
nah the house. It's got to be that, bro. Think
then I need to get a bottle of coke.
Then I'm going to come back. Oh yeah.
Yeah. It's got to be um it's going to
have to be that, bro.
No, it's not all parts of London. It's
just some parts
and the part that I'm in. Yeah. [Music]
Imagine USA Izzy watching my live stream
now. Ah, look how far I've come. It's
quite cute, ain't it?
No, I'm not getting Indian, bro. Too expensive.
I need to save, buddy. I need to save.
I'm gone tomorrow, matey.
I could get an Indian. Maybe I will get
to be fair. Maybe I will just get an
Indian, to be honest.
Uh, yeah, I'll just get an Indian. [ __ ] it.
Yeah, I'll get an Indian, bro.
Can't be able to cook today.
I need to do some stuff tomorrow.
Grievesy, imagine USA watching my live
stream now. Grievy, remember I said I'll
meet you. I'll meet you and I'll say it
to your face in front of your silly
boyfriend that's got tattoos on his
arms. I don't have tattoos on my arms,
but I'll give you one big punch.
This is how it went with the cyclist.
I was on the little road and I done a
left because I I couldn't be bothered
going all the way around. And this
stupid fat woman was like, "Oh, you
should be there." And I said, "I'll go
where I [ __ ] want." I literally said
that she was with a guy. I said, "I'll
go where I [ __ ] want." Not the not
with the U, with with the A. Grieves.
It was the A. Then she started running
up her mouth. Obviously to move this
table here. I was on this was like two
weeks ago. I was on a little bicycle.
Then I parked the bike. I said, "Do you
[ __ ] what? Come on then. Say to my
face. Don't walk away. You and that guy
that you're with. Come on. Come on. Come
on. That's what I [ __ ] thought.
[ __ ] Ozy man. [ __ ] little [ __ ]
You have a guy as well. [ __ ] Yeah. Look.
No, I just cycled around cuz I was
bored. Just wanted to go to some hot spots.
Nah, bro. Not even.
You I'm a skin Afghan. That's nice, bro.
Yep. Yep. Yep. See, it doesn't bother
you, bro. Listen, listen, listen. I'm
not um I'm not going to ban you. I'm not
going to ban you. Yeah. But what I am
going to say is that's nice, bro. But
I'm not going to block you. That's good,
bro. But when you can say it to my face,
come back to me. Yeah, nice, bro. When
when you can come and say to my face,
I'll take you seriously. Until then,
we're carrying on with the story. So,
basically, Goozy, that's what happened.
Actions speak louder than words. No one
cares what you can write behind a
keyboard. Bro, listen.
Say it to my face.
Ah, okay. Bro, listen.
I'll come to you today if you show me
where you are. I'm going to put the link up. One second. Uh,
right. I'm going to put the link up,
man. Cuz you're being a keyboard warrior again
like keyboard warriors.
this uh feeling. Hold on. So,
oh [ __ ] we can't get Wi-Fi properly
here. One second.
I'm going to put you right.
It's all [ __ ] bro. What is wrong with
this [ __ ] punting internet? One second.
Right. One second. Wait for the link.
Right. Come on. Join and show us where
you are. Come on.
Join and show us where you are.
Otherwise, I'm not listening. Come on.
Come on. You've started on me. You
started on me for no reason. You pester
with the script. You're a big man behind the keyboard.
Show me where you are and I'll come to
you today. I will literally come to you
right now. I'm free today, man. I
anywhere before I go away tomorrow. So,
this I've got like a point to prove here
with my little legs. Yep. I'm this. I'm
that. I'm this. I'm that. I'm this and
that. But I'll give you the chance to
say it to my face.
But you're just going to roll go like
bro all of this whole you're this you're
that you're this this self projection
it's boring now bro [Music]
will not say it to anyone's face like
I'm not even telling you to come on my
door I don't want anyone coming on my
door cuz you're just filled up with
scooters I'm asking you to show me where
you are join the hangouts and I will meet you
and you can say to my fan every [ __ ]
day you're you're breaching the peace
here we was having a nice convers
conversation. You're yappy yappy yappy
yappy yappy yappy yappy yap yap yap yap
yap yap. But you're not willing to show
anyone where you are. So stop starting
something you can't finish. It's
annoying, bro. It's not annoying.
It just makes you look like Look, and
now you're nowhere to be seen. What's
the [ __ ] point of it all, man? It's
You're nothing but a London cyclist.
You're waiting for me, bro. You're not
waiting for me. I just put a link up.
You're in the hangouts.
Oh, here you are.
Bye, you little [ __ ] You suck your
mom, you [ __ ] man. Hello.
Suck your mom, you [ __ ]
Yeah. Go suck your mom, you little
[ __ ] Don't tell me who you are, you
[ __ ] bro. Yeah. Yeah. Why do you suck
your mom? Suck your whole mom. Yeah.
Yeah. Say to my face, [ __ ] bro. You're
[ __ ] dead. I'm too busy sucking your
mom. I'm too busy sucking your mom. You
bro, you and Sean.
Suck your mother,
bro. Listen, you're still talking. Come
and meet me. I'm sucking yours. I can't
suck my mom when I'm sucking yours. I'm
sucking your mom up. What I do? Yeah,
come now then. Come now. Come now. What
I do, bro? What should I do, bro? Okay,
come now then, bro. I'm waiting for you.
What are you going to do, bro? You're
going to do nothing. Think you're
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. Stop yapping and come
and meet me. Suck your mother.
You're not about nothing. Go and suck
your mom. You go and suck your mom, you
little [ __ ] Yeah, bro. Look,
I told the guy to come, bro, like about
10 times now he's left, bro. Or is that
all you can say is suck your mom. Suck
your mom. Suck your mom, bro. I'm asking
this guy to meet me and all he's doing
is making empty threats. He's a [ __ ]
bro. You're a pussio.
Like, it's so annoying, bro. Why do you
come on here? Like, yeah, you sound a
bit scary. You don't scare me, bro. I'll
meet you anywhere you want. Like, you
don't scare me. I'm telling you to come.
I'm trying to meet this guy. And all he
keeps saying is suck your mom. Suck your
mom. Suck your mom. You might sound
scary. You don't scare me one little
bit, brother. Not one little bit. Trying
to [ __ ] beat you here, son. You won't
beat me. Yeah, I'm a [ __ ] Oh, come and
say it to my face. Say it to my face.
Say it to my face. What? Bro, what you
going to do? You're not going to do
nothing, bro. Shut up. I've tried to
meet you about a million times,
bro. Listen, you don't scare me. Stop
saying just watch stuff. No, no, no, no,
no. Stop your [ __ ] and come.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
You are [ __ ] You're just like these
people, bro. You're all mouth. You're
just No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What's what's going to happen to me?
What's what's going to happen to me,
bro? People know where I am. Every week
I go to this what? I used to go to the
same pubs, the same places. Bro, what
are you going to do? You're not going to
do nothing. Shut up. Yeah,
that's it, bro. Stop running up your
mouth on the internet if you ain't going
to do nothing. Oh, watch. Oh, watch. You
know, people used to say that when they
were like 10, bro. Stop chatting and
come and do something, you [ __ ]
idiot. Well, I can't be bothered with
this community anymore. It's full of little weasels.
You know what I'm saying, bro? It's full
of little weasels.
You're You're just a little weasel, bro.
That's what you are. Like a weasel.
You're a weasel, bro.
You know what I'm saying? Like, you're
coming on your mom. Oh, [ __ ] Your mom.
But you're not saying nothing to
anyone's face, bro. Allow it. You're embarrassing.
at watch. Bro, what are you going to do?
What the [ __ ] are you going to do to anyone, bro?
One second, bro.
I need to send this thingy to someone.
You see what I mean? They they disturb
the peace. It's like breach of the
peace. What these people do, Grievy? You
understand? They start [ __ ] with people,
but then they can't finish it. He's not
Yeah. He sounded Bro, show me you're
about it then. Show me you're about it.
What? Because he talks a bit like this,
bro. So, come on, bro.
That makes him sound like about it, bro.
He doesn't If he's about it, he would
stop talking and he would come and do
something or he would at least try and eat me.
Yeah. Oh, bro.
Anyone can sound like that, but he ain't doing nothing.
You know what I'm saying?
He's just a keyboard warrior. It seems
like they're everywhere now, bro. It
seems like they're everywhere. Listen,
bro. Show me where you're at and I will
come and meet you about watch what you
will do to me. You're not coming
anywhere, bro. Yeah. Tell me where you
are and I will come to you. Simple.
Yeah. Tell me where you are and I'll
come. You're not coming anywhere, bro.
Simple. You're not coming anywhere.
Yeah. And you're going to use the
excuse. Oh, you're too far. Where are
you, bro? Where were you? Where were
Yeah, that's the real question. Where
were you? Yeah, you're not about
nothing, bro. You're on YouTube. You're
a keyboard. Shut up, man. You're not
about that life.
Watch. Watch. Watch. Think about it,
bro. How long have you been watching me?
You knew where I am. You knew where I
am. You knew where I was. Yeah. And you
ain't done nothing. Yeah. In North
London. Where in North London? Where in
What are you going to do, bro? You're
not going to do nothing to no one, bro.
Shut up, man. You're the same as that
Smokey Be. You're a pair of [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying, bro? Yeah.
Come [ __ ] One second. One sec.
I need to write this thing to someone here.
You're an idiot, bro.
Talking about deliveroo, bro. Who does deliver?
Not me, bro. And another thing is you
don't even work. You bum, bro. You don't
even work, bro. What the [ __ ] are you
all about? You're talk You're trying to
hate on a job that I don't even do, bro.
I've not had to work for 10 years, but
guess what? You don't even work, bro.
You probably sell crack to [ __ ] kids.
You probably sell [ __ ] crack to
[ __ ] kids, bro.
That's your job, bro.
You're You're an absolute [ __ ] idiot,
bro. No one's scared of you, bro. No
one's scared of you one little bit. No one's
little bit, bro. Really embarrassed. You're
this. You're that. You're this. You're
that. You're this. You're that. [ __ ]
off, bro. [ __ ] right off, bro. Yeah.
Come to Plasto.
Okay, bro. Come to Plaster. I'm waiting.
Yeah. Why don't you come to Plaster? I'm
waiting for you. Yeah. You want to know
where I'm at? Come to Pl. I'm there. Simple.
You don't know about that life, bro.
Watch what I do to you, bro. Listen,
stop saying watch and come through. I've
just told you where to go. Yeah. Come to
Plasto and I'll meet you with Plasto. Simple.
Talking about kids. Talking about kids,
bro. Shut the [ __ ] up, bro. Listen.
Listen. Come to Plasto. Yeah. Come to
Plasto and I'll talk about kids to your
face. Yeah. Simple. I'll talk about kids
to your face. How's about that one?
Idiot, bro. No, I'm walking from this
one. I'm not scared of this little
[ __ ] Oh, you think I'm scared of this
little [ __ ] Are you mad? He ain't
about nothing. I told him to come to
Plasto. You're not going to embarrass no
one, bro. Shut up. Well, he sounds about
it. This [ __ ] [ __ ] ain't about
it. Tell him to come to Plato right now.
Yeah, this little [ __ ] neat [ __ ]
is going to embarrass me. Are you mad,
bro? Please stop it, man.
You're going to embarrass me. Come
through, you little [ __ ] Simple. Yeah,
you're about it. Come to Plowro then.
Why don't you want to leave your ends?
Simple. [ __ ] off. Shook of you. Shook of
you. Of you. I'm literally telling you
to come. How can I be shook of you?
Well, watch what I do to you. Shut up,
man. You little keyboarder. [ __ ] off,
man. Little [ __ ]
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You notice I notice
how you won't leave your area though in
it. I notice how you won't leave your
area though it [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah. Watch what I do to you. You keep
talking but you're not doing it. Yeah.
You keep saying that but you're not
coming. So I mean you keep saying but
you're not coming in it. So shut the
[ __ ] up, bro.
Yeah. Go sell your [ __ ] crap to [ __ ] kids.
Yeah. Simple, bro. Go sell [ __ ] crap
to kids like you probably [ __ ] do.
sending crap to [ __ ] kids probably.
Yeah, you're this, you're that. You
won't leave your ends, bro. You're hard
in your ends. Remember that. Remember,
you're not leaving anywhere, bro. Cuz
I've just told you where to go about 10
times. I've just told you where to go
about 10 times. You're not about it,
bro. Shut up, bro. This whole This whole
bad man [ __ ] doesn't scare me, bro.
Bro, what do you mean give you the
location? You go to class, bro. Train
station or by the train station and I
will meet you. Simple. That's it. And I
[ __ ] [ __ ] Well, listen. Listen.
These people don't understand what
people Prime never scared me. Prime
caught me off guard. Get it right,
[ __ ] Yeah, he caught me off guard
about a million years ago. Stop getting
excited, bro. Stop getting [ __ ]
excited. But guess what? You don't scare
me. Anyways, go to Plasto.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. So, you're
not coming to Plasto then, [ __ ]
Simple. You're a [ __ ] boy, man. [ __ ]
off. You're a [ __ ] boy, bro.
Yeah, he's my new daddy. Yeah. Yeah. I'm
I'm your new daddy. Yeah, I'm your new
Yeah. Yeah. Come now, then. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Come now. Come now.
Like you scare me, bro. Are you mad? You
think you scare me, bro? You don't scare
me one little bit, bro. Not one little
bit. I will say what I want now. Who the
[ __ ] do you think you are, bro? You're
no one, bro. You're a [ __ ] Simple.
Plain and simple. You're a [ __ ]
You're a [ __ ] bro.
[ __ ] idiot. You scare me about walk
away from this one. You scare me, bro.
That mirror scares me more than you
would ever scare me, bro. You don't scare me.
You'll never leave your M's either. Even
if you do really, you're going to smash
my phone. You're going to do nothing.
Shut up. You're not going to do
anything. Shut up, bro. The bad man [ __ ]
needs to stop. You're not going to smash
anyone's phone. Shut up. How many times
have you seen where I am and you ain't
done nothing? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Whatever, bro. Yeah. Come back when you
can take it to my face. You're a
keyboard warrior. Shut up, man. Yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. I'll see you in
Plaster, bro. Yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. I'll see
you in Plaster, bro. I'll see you in
Plasto. I'll see you in Plasto, bro.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. You're just being a
10year-old now, bro. You're just being a
10year-old now, bro. It's boring now.
Oh, you're boring, bro. You're throwing
out 10-year-old insults. Oh, boring, bro. Boring.
You're boring, bro. You're boring, bro.
Stop the keyboard warrior [ __ ] bro. It
doesn't It doesn't scare me, bro. I'm
not like from these I'm not like these
little idiots from [ __ ] town and
that, bro. You don't scare me one little
bit. So, stop it, bro. Just allow it.
Stop embarrassing yourself. Get off of
YouTube. Simple. That's it. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm a nerd. I'm a nerd.
And you're calling me a nons? Are you
[ __ ] mad? Are you [ __ ] mad? Let me
Let me tell you something. Yeah. Let me
tell you one thing. I don't give a [ __ ]
about any of these people in this
community. I hate them. I hate every
single one of them. LJ Prime, all of
them people that you mentioned, I hate
them, bro. You think I care what I've
said to them in the past? I hate them.
[ __ ] them, bro. And [ __ ] their family. I
don't give a [ __ ] Do you think I give a
[ __ ] about any of them? Do you think I
give a [ __ ] about what I've said about
their family? I can't stand them, bro.
If they were dying of of um what's the
word? If they were burning alive, I
would I wouldn't piss on them. Yeah. Do
you understand? And you're calling me a
nons, bro. There's there's actual nonses
on this community. Yeah, there's actual
nonses on this community. Have you Have
you gone for them? Not like, bro, I'm
not scared of you. Like, come past now.
Like, you don't bother me one little bit
because so far all you've done is been a
keyboard warrior. I've told you where to
come. You do not bother me one little
bit. And I'll keep saying it. I'm
telling you to come, but I'ming you.
You're trying to call people a nons when
there's about three or four different
people in this community that are really
nons. Have I ever seen you? Have I ever
seen you go for any of them? So don't
[ __ ] come on here yet trying to act
like a bad man trying to intimidate. You
don't not intimidate me, bro. Yeah.
Simple. [ __ ] off, bro. Stop typing and come.
Typing and come, bro. You're boring.
You're [ __ ] boring, bro. You're
[ __ ] boring. Simple. Boring, bro.
Boring. Go sell crap to kids or some
[ __ ] Yeah. I'm petrified, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm so scared, bro. There's
beer out my chest. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
But if you was really about something,
you would have already you already done
something. Yeah. You're going to get the
train as we speak. Yeah. Yeah. Of course
you are, bro. You're boring now, bro.
Yeah. You're boring now, bro. You're
proper boring now, bro.
You going to smash people's phones out
their hand? You're not going to do
nothing. Shut up. Watch, watch, watch,
watch, watch. Shut up, bro. It's boring now, man.
Yeah. You're that guy from [ __ ] um
Yeah. You're that guy. You're that guy
from [ __ ] what's it called? Monties,
isn't it? Bro, just allow it, man. It's
embarrassing. Please, just stop it.
You keep on from [ __ ] embarrassing
yourself, bro. It's so embarrassing.
Stop it, bro. It's embarrassing.
It's embarrassing, bro. It's embarrassing. Yeah,
you're a keyboard, bro. You're boring. Bye-bye