Get up there.
Right. So, we got £40 to flip into
something. So, I'm going to do 20 pound
on Fishing Frenzy and I'm going to do 20
pound on the roulette.
See? Yeah. We'll see.
And we will see a delay. It's
there. How many people sub to this
channel? Quite a
few. Yeah, definitely quite a few first
Guinness. That's the first one,
bro. Can't be a good old Guinness in a
good old Guinness class. Well, actually,
I don't even think that is actually a
good to be
fair. I got my passport uh photo sorted.
It's like 20 pound on Frankie and then
20 on [ __ ]
I don't know which one to
start. I'm going to start with
Frankie. Think I'm
starting. Yeah. And then we'll go.
We got do these [ __ ]
approaches. What is it?
I'm planning a trip. Well, I got a
passport. Well, it'll be sorted by next week.
Wow. All them notifications there.
So, we've got 40 spins to get a
bonus. I'm going to start on the
roulette. I think let's start on the
roulette. I feel like that's going to be
slower. Let me go on the roulette. Start
on the roulette and then we'll
[ __ ] featuring a spin ball. It would
be featuring a [ __ ] spin ball, would it, man?
Fernandez left 16 now.
Um, this is where it [ __ ] up cuz you
can only do 20p
minimum on the actual numbers. So this
is where it [ __ ] you
out. What's the chance you're going to hear anything like be
nice? Well, you got 20
shots. That would be lovely, mate. That
that 20 will be nice.
The [ __ ] is
that? Come on. Stop. 11 on.
Can't even get a [ __ ] spin, bro. What the [ __ ] Come on. Come
on. [ __ ] seven. You dirty [ __ ] [ __ ]
number. It's 20 pound. Oh, it's always
[ __ ] seven, bro. I feel like getting
this glass and smashing on the [ __ ] machine,
but it's [ __ ] annoying as [ __ ]
man. God, it's so [ __ ] hunting damn annoying, you
know. I just put 20 pound. I'm putting
another 20 pound in.
Yeah, we're getting on it today, but
we're sending it. I saw this pass which
is out. You
Yep. You win some, you lose some.
You win some, you lose some. That's the
spirit. So it's there. But my spoons if they
different, but we won't get into that
because we're not allowed our different opinions.
Going to put us in a stinking bad mood.
But you know watch bonus
bonus. You are a
[ __ ] Come on. Ah.
Oh, that's good. Is it? That's a lion.
Okay. Come on. Bonus. Come
on. Bonus. Got to give us a [ __ ]
bonus, mate. Come on. Bonus. annoying.
No, I'm just playing. I don't need to
make money for an escort, man. I can get
an escore anytime I want. I just want to
get a [ __ ] bonus on this game.
I've only put 40. I'm only 40 in. I'm
not put anymore in bonus. Uh for you.
I am, bro. I've only put I'm only I've
only put 40
in done my passport photo. [ __ ] it. Come on.
It's not having it, is
it? It's not having it today.
Bye-bye, Peter Griffin. Take it all,
mate. I'll have more money than you would ever
have. No m I've got more money than you
will ever have. JB
Thompson, Peter Griffin. No. No. No.
Yeah, 50p a spin. It's a 100 pound
jackpot, [ __ ] boy. Yeah, it's a£100
jackpot, you [ __ ]
spacker. So, yeah, it is 50p a spin when
it's£100 jackpot, you go.
I would do. I'm tempted,
but it's just gambling. You win some,
you lose some. So they
sayians are a bit different to that.
Hey, gambling. Win some, you lose
some. I've been hearing that since
probably like November
now, you know.
You win some, you lose some. It's just
gambling. That's what I've been told by
like workers and other people and stuff.
Yeah, I don't agree with that. Cuz if it
was if it was just
gambling. No, I'm not showing you little
grass is nothing, mate. I will see to it
in my own time after this beer. I'm not
showing you little grasses
nothing. I'm not showing you little
grasses nothing. So you can get the
police involved. [ __ ] out of here, man.
You little dirty stinky little grasses. This
guy, you win some, you lose some. But
that one cost I think I've heard that if
I got a penny for every single time I
heard that excuse, I I'd be a
millionaire. I actually would be rich.
I'm not even joking. I would actually be rich, bro.
For every single time I heard that
excuse with this red gambling, I'd be rich.
Yeah. So, yeah. Anyway, Jamie Thompson,
I've got more money than you. I'm better
looking than you. I'll always have more money than
you. So, what's lost me losing 40, mate?
I don't care. I get over three grand a
month. Do you think I give a [ __ ] about
losing 300 quid? You know what I'm
saying, bro? Get your facts right.
[ __ ] Peter Griffin with a double
chin. You know what I'm saying? [ __ ] Peter
Griffin. [ __ ] Peter [ __ ]
Griffin. You are one ugly bastard. [ __ ] Damn
them. You win some, you lose some. So they
say. So they say. I love that bit. So
That's all they ever say is that it's
just gambling. And it happens, mate. But
it doesn't happen because it doesn't
happen 12, 13 times in a
row. It's not gambling. Stop saying it's
gambling. It's not gambling. It's
something more than that, you know? It's
got to be something more than that.
Yeah. No, it's not rigged, mate. It's
just gambling. So they say. I always
have to I always have to add that bit at
the end. So they say, because that's
literally all they ever blame is
gambling. But if it was gambling, you would literally
win. Bye-bye, Peter Griffin. You don't
have no wife, Peter Griffin. That's why
you're on YouTube every single day
stalking me. No, I didn't get
breakfast. I got
KFC. That's why you keep stalking me. Is
it Peter Griffin? Peter Griffin of
YouTube? Mate, if I was as ugly as that,
bro. Yeah, I'd kill myself. Look at me.
Yeah. Wait, let me go back. I want these
little weirdos know where I am cuz you
know they like calling places up, mate.
If I look like Peter
Griffin. [ __ ] hell, bro. That's some
madness. No, I lost 40 quid. I had a
budget of 40, but it's just gambling.
You win some, you lose some. So they say
they say. He sure doesn't say
anything. Okay, he doesn't say anything.
Yeah. So, yeah. Yeah. If I look like you
peed with him, that's when I would
really, really, really, really, really
Yeah. You're happily married. That's why
you're sat on YouTube every day stalking me.
Yeah. Um, there you go. Look, I got
hair. I don't have a double chin like
you, you ugly [ __ ]
Making sure there's nothing in the
background so these little grasses can't
call up anything.
But remember, it it doesn't it doesn't
wind me up, bro. Just got my hair done
as well. It doesn't wind me up because
it's just gambling. You don't
understand. How can I get how can I not
getting a trim? I already got a trim,
bro. Stop being a [ __ ] As you can
see, I've already got a trim. Stop being
a spacker. Look at my beard. Look at my
hair. It's just gambling, so they say.
So they say, Buzz. So they say, but
yeah, I don't think so,
bro. It's going to be a long one, man.
It's going to be a long one. But that's
all that's the good thing about all of
this [ __ ] man. That's the good thing
about when Oh, there we go. Open up a
little bit. Uh when money is no object,
right? All my passport photos done as
well. Bye-bye, Peter Griffin. Look at
me, bro. Look at my looks. Yeah, my
hair. And then look at this ugly [ __ ]
Look at him on screen, bro. Look,
compare us two. Compare us together,
bro. Look at me. And then look at that
ugly [ __ ] God. And then look at the
rat face from Wington. Look at that
Orington rat face
bastard. It's going to be a lot.
We had shopping, bro. Got some passport pictures done,
too. Yep. That's where he pot from. I'm hung
over. Um, you can't get a woman. That's
why you stalk me on YouTube every day.
That's how I can explain it because
you're sat on YouTube every day stalking
me. Because you can't get a
woman. There you
go. Got a nice trim, bro. Well, if you'd
even call it a trim.
You win some, you lose some, you know,
man. So they
say, good thing money is no object,
eh? Otherwise, uh, it's lucky we're not
on um the virgin's income, the virgin's
income, a grand a month, a poxy grand a
month. Then we'd be in trouble, you
know. Then we'd be in big, big trouble.
Nah, maybe like 40 minutes. Sick fad,
ain't it? Nah, about 40 minutes. So, I'm
sending it all night, bro. But I'm going
to go home, drink some more, and then go out. One
sec. But you can't get it. That's why I
use No, we just lost 40 quid.
Yeah, I'm done with it now anyways, bro.
So, after today, I won't be going out
for a little while anyways cuz obviously
the passport uh I won't have my passport
cuz I need to redo it. Got these photos
here. So, we got to give it one
last. Yeah. Peter Griffin, get off of
YouTube and stop talking Peter
belly. Listen, Peter
Griffin. Peter Griffin.
Why you making polite noises? Bye-bye.
Now, who skip Miles? I'm skinn. Nah,
mate. Never skip me, mate. Never skip
me. No, never skip me,
lad. I'm an odd.
Bye-bye. Look at me, bro. Compared to
that rat face in Orington, and that's
all you can talk about is my nose. Oh, wow.
I said should have kept me on. That's funny. But
Yeah, you're looking at yourself, Peter
Griffin. You're looking at yourself,
Peter Griffin. Peter Griffin, you're the
one that has to sit on YouTube every day
with your fat double chin face. You ugly
overweight bastard stalking me. You're
looking at yourself in the mirror.
That's what you're looking at. You're
looking at yourself. Peter Griffin. Look
at your face. Peter Griffin. Peter
Griffin. You're not married. Peter
Griffin. If you was married, you
wouldn't be on YouTube every day
stalking me. You ain't You're not
married. You ain't got no money. You're
a fat Peter Griffin looking bully
victim. You're looking at yourself. You
need to stop looking at yourself, Peter
Griffin. You little
stalker. You're not married. You ain't
got no money. You don't go to no Vegas.
Shut the [ __ ] up. Oh my
god. Do I rank today? Stop asking stupid
questions about that. Stop asking stupid questions.
[ __ ] it. Bye-bye. How many times have
you got? You keep getting blocked, man. You s
bastard, mate. The day I'm as ugly as
you and Rap face is the day I start
thinking, "Ra, this is my life." You
know what I'm saying? Yeah. But
yeah, there you go, Dad. I'll be sending
it today. How many numbers we predicting delay? A
lot of goodness of it.
There we go, bro.
Nah, not yet, mate. It's too early. I'm
just having a few here then.
Yeah. If anyone catches my fancy, you're
not going to see it, Bob.
It's a sick fade, ain't it? It's a sick
bro. Yeah, it's a sick fade
out. Look at that, bro. Sick, isn't it?
Yeah. How the [ __ ] does that ugly
rat? No, I'm not put no more in, bro.
I'm done. I'm done with it. I'm done.
Done. Done. Done. Done with it, bro.
Today's the final day going out as well
cuz I need to do my passport tomorrow.
So, I'm going to send it as much today and
then obviously after
today go to Yeah, I'm done for like a month, bro.
Done. How many numbers we
predicting? How many numbers we
today? How's homelessness? Well, no, I'm
not homeless. He doesn't want to
entertain. Yeah, the spackers. You know
what I'm saying, bro? The spackers. Exactly.
You already know,
bro. I wouldn't know how it's treating
me cuz I'm homeless. You don't know
nothing about my life. Yeah,
bro. I'm thinking we will get four or five numbers
there. What do you think? Four or
five? I'll say four or five.
But I might do the series again. Um, I
might, you know what? I might do one
more thing tomorrow. Um, Palms and M
cheese. I might do Wherever Peter
Belly's legs take him. We're ignoring
these weirdos now. Anyways, um, wherever
Peter Belly's little legs take him. So,
it'll be like this.
It'll be like this. Yeah.
So, I woke up this morning and my little
legs I don't know where my little legs
are going to take me and then I'll just
like go where my little legs take me. Be
anywhere, mate. It's going to be A4,
bro. It's going to be
A4. I might start that series, you
know. I might actually start that
series. What do you think? I think it'll
be cool. I like that. Yeah. Wherever
Peter Benny's little legs taken. No.
That's sick of it. I'm in I'm large and
charge. I just lost 40 pound on the
machine. But you win some, you lose
some, Grezy. You win some, you lose
some. Isn't that right? It's just
gambling, so they say. But wherever
Peter Belly's little legs take
him. Yeah, bro.
You already know, mate. And and women
was put on this earth to satisfy Peter
Billy's needs as well. Don't forget
about that. They were put on this earth
to satisfy my
needs. I got to do this fast tomorrow. Madness.
What? Find Sam, mate. You'll be knocking
on about a million [ __ ]
doors. What? Knock on a million doors to
find good old Tam. Nah, bro.
Yeah. See, I would I would see the thing
and shoes. I would ask Sean to come with
me, but he's on a grand a month and a
grand a month ain't going to cut it,
mate. Because these these trips are
going to cost maybe 7800 pound. You know
what I'm saying, bro?
So, a grand a month, Shell. A grand a
month, Shell. It's not going to do it.
You know what I'm saying? Like, I'm not
I'm not trying to take the piss, mate.
to be nasty or anything or or even sort
of like the big I am, you know? But a
grand a month, shell is not going to cut
it. Not grand the month. A grand a month
ain't going to do it, mate. Sorry. Get
up. The grand
sh You want to grind a month?
Sh is on 750 a month. Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] my legs,
bro. You know what though? It is
actually a pointless community to go on
because it's just the same repeaters every
day. That's actually true to be fair.
Jamie Thompson stalks me. Peter Griffin.
I've got a Peter Griffin looking that
stalks me there. [ __ ] hell,
bro. Can I get another goodness? Please,
man. I want to go back to that betting
shop now. I want to go back to that
betting shop, mate. Give that [ __ ] what
for? Give that little [ __ ] what for, mate. I'm
saying, but I'm scared if I do it like
people going to start looking and that.
Yeah, of course they will stop looking, bro. The
[ __ ] I might do it owner cunning and
then send it to
Grezy. I'm not going to put it on this
grassy community, but I'll send it to
Grezy. Okay with you,
boss. Grezy, is that okay with you, boss?
Bad thing about Guinness is you got to
wait a couple minutes for them to
probably [ __ ] behind
me. Is that okay with you, boss? Me
going in a betting shop to own this
[ __ ] [ __ ] I'll tell him to [ __ ]
come out now with your stupid [ __ ] Like
I told him yesterday, you know, stupid
little [ __ ] [ __ ] mate. Yeah, I'll
I'll do the [ __ ] windows
in. I'll do the windows in, mate.
It's gambling. Win some, you lose some.
We're greasy. You win some, you lose
some. It's gambling. That's what I
always think of when when I lose.
Gambling. You win some, you lose some.
We're getting some [ __ ] today.
But no, we
are. Cheers, man.
is have to be careful. I don't need some
mongos now where I drink,
bro. Good old
Guinness. That's £10 in drink now. Okay with you,
boss. Oh, look at this. Oh, that's
not what we got. Hit up a few of the Irish pubs
today. Hit up a few of the Irish clubs. Hey,
Grezy. We're getting some today, man. [Music]
Yeah, at least it was only £40 today. So
that's 320 in two days. I mean, if we
could just leave it at
that, then obviously it's all right in
it. You need to stop, bro. It'll kill you. That
will well your mind, not your [ __ ]
finances. You know what I'm
saying? You know how it One second. Yeah. Well, budget Yeah,
there are people so hateful on this
community. Like you read some of the
comments. Yeah, they're so hateful. I
don't know why they're so hateful. Their
lives must be really [ __ ] Yeah. For
them to come on YouTube every day hating
on people that they don't even know.
Yeah. Their lives must be really
shine. Really, bro.
Like they call people skint, but they
don't even know you. They don't know what you
have. It's crazy, isn't it?
Like, they don't know you. They don't
know what you have. It's madness,
lad. They talk about themselves. That's what they
do. I mean, their lives are [ __ ] bro.
That's why they have to sit on YouTube
every day hating on
people. I'm probably just going to be on
it all night. To be fair, I'm probably
just going to go home just have a few,
go back, get changed, and just go, bro. [Laughter]
Y I want. my second
one. You know what? I might just I might
as well just go to a [ __ ] you
know I send
it like ch that chase.
They look all right. Where
they don't mind if I do, eh? Don't mind
if I [ __ ] do.
You're too old. I told you, Timmy. You
should You should have come today, bro.
You should have come to London. I told
you we could have went for a good
oldfashioned piss up. I might go black
ball tomorrow. I might go to the I'll be
in the West Midlands tomorrow. I'll be
in Blackpool tomorrow. I'll be in the
West Midlands. Blackpool
Timmy. Yeah. On the
pier. You want me to down this
pine? Yeah, I
was. I can down this pine if you want
to. Okay. Down this pine in. Oh, it's
good. It will stand in
it. You can't see nothing. Let me down the pine
in. Um I I don't know if I should do it.
I end up being sick. I'll do it. I'll do
Okay. One, two, three, four, five.
What? I'll go green for a
second. Got it. Yes.
Oh, my legs. Oh.
B leg. Double leg.
Oh, what's that? The second
one. [ __ ] it.
Give me a
minute. I had to lean on just one
Oh, there you
go. You all right, Timmy?
Timmy, wrong one. Timmy, how you doing?
I'll be in the West Mill
tomorrow. You're coming to Birmingham to
bar. Yeah, I'm going to
Blackpool. Blackpool's not West Mland.
It's Lancaster. Stop 12. No, it's West
Midlands. I'll be there tomorrow.
I'll be there tomorrow. It's not West Midlands.
It [ __ ] is. It isn't. It's Lancer. It
[ __ ] is, mate. It [ __ ] hurts. It's
L. It's L. I just I just lost 40 on the
machines, Timmy. Pard, I just lost 40
pound on the machines. Well, for [ __ ]
sake. Stop gambling, PJ. But Timmy, it's
just gambling. You win some, you lose
some. Right. Yeah. I'm not being funny.
You've got to stop playing that fishing
frenzy, mate. It's pulling your I was
playing the roulette to me. Oh, the pub.
Look, I was I was playing the bar
roulette. Oh, [ __ ] hell. Not that bar
piece of [ __ ] It was It was in the pub
to me. I don't play that bar roulette in
the pub. It's [ __ ] terrible. I know
the one you I just I just down I just
down the Guinness bag. [ __ ] hell. Can
you Are you going to do a pub crawl channel?
Yeah. Not in this area though in central
London. Why not? Why don't you do 16
pubs and that' be great content? I will,
but not just not this area. Look, I have
to sacrifice my liver to do pub craw
calls. Yeah, but Timmy, well, you're
going to meet me in Blackpool
tomorrow. I'm not going to Blackpool.
[ __ ] me. I've got plans, PJ. I can't go
150 mile bowl at the country.
You can if you want to, Timmy. I can't,
PJ. I'm seeing my mom tomorrow. No, I
never done Bulls in. But PJ, all right,
Timmy. All right. You're not going to
come to Blackpool and meet me.
Okay. I'm just making sure you don't see
the pub. So, you get these little grasses on
here. Yeah, we're on it today. Triple H.
I'm going to be on it all night until
8:00 in the [ __ ] morning. You can you
watch. I ain't done balls in. Trip. How
can I do balls in? Can I get good,
please? Yeah. Thank you, bro. How can I
How can I do my balls in, bro? I get
over three grand a month. How am I doing
my balls in?
How can I do my balls in, bro? That
doesn't even make sense. Yeah, I lost
300 lb in the past two days. So what,
bro? You know what I'm
saying? Oh, we getting some [ __ ] today,
bro. One second, Timmy, man.
No, I don't do that [ __ ] mate. That's
for you. That's for you people up north.
I don't do that, bro. You
crazy. Yeah. It flips into a a tablet.
It goes like this and it goes like that.
Yeah. Very expensive. Yeah.
1.7. What you iPhone? Most people are
iPhone to be fair. Yeah. I've not had an
iPhone since I was 14.
Yeah. Literally. Thank you. Anyways, cheers.
Are you correct?
Think I've already [ __ ] mate. This is
only the beginning.
See, triple eight, let me explain
something to you, mate. Yeah, let me
explain something to you,
brother. The reason Okay, let me explain
something to you. The reason Triple
H Sean can't go out as much and do as
much traveling as me is because he's on
a grind a month.
Trip understand it's he's on a grand a
month. So someone that's on a grind a
month. They don't have as much money
as as Peter Belly. You know, I might just go
tomorrow, wherever my little legs take
me to the break. I might just I will
just wake up tomorrow and I'll be like,
wherever my little legs take me. Could
be Scotland. It could be Blackpool.
Could be [ __ ] Australia. But I need
to renew my passport, you know. It could
be anywhere. Triple H, you know, but
shill on a grand a month. I mean, yeah.
Okay. Can save. Be a bit hard though, is it, mate?
you a grand a month is
laughable. I will go out today and I'll
probably spend I'm hoping I don't spend
much. I'm probably going to spend that 300
quid, mate. You You understand? I'll
probably be spending about [ __ ] 300
quid, mate. You know what I'm saying?
Probably about 300 on the [ __ ] piss. That's expensive,
Timmy. It's [ __ ] London. Why don't
you come to Joint Rich and then we can
have a drink and I can beat you up when
I'm pissed. Jimmy, I want to meet you in
Blackpool the West Midlands. I don't I
can't get to Blackpool. I'm meeting my
mom. Why don't you come to Birmingham
Sunday? We'll have a few points and I'll
beat you up. Cuz I want to meet you in Blackpool.
I just told you I'm seeing my mom
tomorrow. It's a [ __ ] It's It's I
want to meet you in Blackpool cuz that's
the West Midlands to be. It's my mom's
[ __ ] birthday tomorrow. I've got to
see my mom tomorrow. All right, Trip.
Tell him that he needs to meet me in
Blackpool in Westminster. I can't when
it's my mom's birthday. It's
disrespectful. She's 63. Timmy, in all
due respect, yeah, I want to meet you,
but the last time I met you, you were
slapping the back of your head. Don't
worry about that, PJ. Worry about me
slapping your back of your head when I'm
pissed. Timmy, you couldn't even beat me
two on one. You tried kicking me. I I dodged your
kick. Timmy Timmy, it's a laugh. Timmy,
you left PJ. Can you Can you show us any
women around the park? You left you left
your friend to get beat up. Uh to be
fair, if I wouldn't have pulled you off
Tiger, you would have you would have
actually beat Tiger. I got to get Yeah,
I was dodging your kicks, Timothy. No,
you [ __ ] I will give you that. You
got Tiger on the
floor, mate. I Bro, I walked up the car.
Yeah, you tried kicking me. I walked up
the car and I held your leg. Remember?
Yeah, but you did. I did. Not hard. It
was only a little [ __ ] Timmy. Why?
Why was you You're the one that started
it. Why was you walking up the road
letting your friend deal with your beef?
You left. You [ __ ] was walking up the
[ __ ] road. It wasn't It wasn't my
fault. You [ __ ] said to Tiger, you
was a [ __ ] Tiger pro wrong. I have
never argued with Tiger ever.
Ever. You said come to London to Tiger
and like Tiger went to London. No, I
said to you come to London. So, you did
say to Tiger, you did. You You've got a
short memory. trying to get other people
to battles, bro. Yeah. Now, you
could cause your [ __ ] bluffs. Do you
know what, Timmy? You're you're you're a
[ __ ] I used to defend you. Yeah. Back
in the day, I used to [ __ ] defend you
and you throw it in my [ __ ] How can I
defend you, PJ? You talk about kids all
the time. No, no, no, no. I I defended
you from Pat Mustard. No. Yes, but PJ, I
can't defend you when you're talking
about kids and asking attacking women.
How am I supposed to No, no, no. But you
How the [ __ ] am I supposed to defend
that? Use some initiative, you know? Oh,
yeah. PJ is a great lad. He wants to
rape women and [ __ ] nons. How am I
supposed to defend that, PJ? Use some
initiative, you know. No, no, no, no.
You You stabbed me in the back before
that, Timmy, bro. So, how did I stab you
in the back? Because you It's like, bro,
you stab cuz you you back chat, bro. Is
it? You I've defended you. Is it? I
can't defend you, PJ. And we've had this
many conversations. When you say you're
going to acid attack women and bake
women. Oh, John. PJ, don't you realize
PJ that Timmy's a [ __ ] [ __ ] He's
a pedo. Yeah, he is. Yeah,
you're Tim. And so, are you PJ? You
[ __ ] packing nons. PJ, you're packing
nons as well.
You I'm a
Well, first of all, I'm Well, first of
all, I'm not Muslim. So, you you do look
Muslim. Yeah, it's cuz the beard, don't
it? Yeah, you look like Bin Laden. No,
not anymore. I got a trimbo as well. Look.
Anyway, John West, how you doing, my lad?
So, Timmy, yes, we need to quit
gambling, man. I I've done all right
with gambling. So, are we going to meet
up on Sunday and I can beat you up? I
would show you that machine that I was
just on, but that guy's on it. It's
[ __ ] up. Are we talking about a meet
up so I can beat you up? Okay. Hey, meet
me in Liverpool, the West Midlands. For
[ __ ] sake, it's Mercy side. No, it's
not. I'm kicking you, Jimmy. I'm I'm
kicking you. Just Just stop it. Triple
H, I'm trying to meet Timmy in Blackpool
in the West Midlands, and he keeps
saying that it's not in the West
Midlands when it is in the West Midlands
cuz I've traveled. I know these things,
bro. I know these things, bro. No, it's
it's definitely the West
Midlands. Look, I'm wearing track boys.
Obviously, I'm gonna get changed later.
Gonna be on it. I pulled some I pulled
some Scottish women last week. Uh,
Triple H. [ __ ] hell, bro. It may It
makes me want to actually go back to
Scotland. I might I might actually do
Blackpool in Glasgow, bro. I might
actually do Blackpool in
Glasgow. I'm not even joking. Tomorrow,
I might actually do
it. What did Tom Wood say? He said
there's no point arguing with Timmy
because it's like arguing with Timmy is
like is like playing chess board with a
pigeon. It will [ __ ] all over it and and
act like it would anyways. That's funny, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. They're never going to find it,
bro. They're never going to find it.
They can keep hunting, but they're never
going to find it, mate. Damn.
But this gambling needs to stop Mac.
This gambling needs to stop
trips. Yeah, they're [ __ ] sados,
bro. We getting some [ __ ] today.
You don't know what pub I'm in. What pub have I
in? Let me try to see. I don't think
there's anything that says You don't
know what pub I'm in. Yeah, I lost 40
quid on it. I lost 40 on the [ __ ]
blueprints. I lost 40 quid. put on pis.
PJ PJ, can you go around the puff? Can
you put your camera on and go? Yo, go
on. I get over three grand a month. Get
in there. What's that on being a
[ __ ] Nah, man. Pier's got his way.
Stunn. You really think I'd lose 300
pound if I couldn't afford it? Come on.
Come on, bro. You don't get three grand
on B. I do. Yes, I do. Jimmy, see, how
do you get three grand? Because Pit pays
out high weight three 737. Don't you
worry about that. But I do. I would lie.
I would lie to you. Why you lying? Why
you lying? Timmy, why you lying, Timmy?
I can't live off a grand a month.
Listen, Timmy, how much do you think I'm
going to spend today drinking? Honestly,
about 600 quid on your credit card. No,
bro. Listen, I don't know. Maybe it's
not 300, but I'm going to spend a good
couple hundred quid today. Is that on
your credit card?
Nah, Peter. Timmy, not at all. You're
not on three grand a month. You got a
credit card and I know a month. I know
your credit rating, Peter. Timmy, why
would I lie, bro? I can even name the
credit card you're using. Timmy, listen
to me, bro. Yeah. Do you think I can I
can afford Stone Island and and drinking
if I was on a grand a month? Be honest
with you. Hey, you let's be honest. You
won the clothes when you won that five
grand. No, but how did how did Okay.
Okay, Timmy, if you go on my channel,
how was I able to afford all of that and
to gamble that amount of money? Think
about it. Grand a month because you
because I can answer that question. You
were n grand and you spent most of it on
clothes. Okay. Really? Timmy, we saw you
have six grand in cash at one stage, PJ.
Okay, Timmy, do you want me to withdraw?
Do you want me to withdraw you 9 on the
pound right now? Do what you want. It's
your credit card. It's my It's not my
credit card, but mate, I can't get a
credit card. My credit is [ __ ] If you
want to [ __ ] pay all that, please. Oh
my god, bro. It's not. Timmy, I wouldn't
lie to you, bro. So, you're telling me
you get three grand a month off the
Yeah, over three grand a month. Yes, I
do. Do you think I was bored yesterday,
Timmy? It's called doing other things
but not benefits, idiot. Who said it's
all on benefits? So, you're working cash
in hand. It doesn't matter what I'm
doing. I never said it's on benefits. I
never said it was all on benefits. But
you just you've just admitted you're
subleting again. Nope. I'm not doing
that either. So, you know what I'm
trying to say? There's ways in London.
There's ways in London to make money to
me. There's ways in London, boss. Don't
tell me you're [ __ ] selling yourself.
No. No. I never I never I just said it
wasn't all benefits. That's what I said.
No, I'm [ __ ] not. I don't even have
that house anymore. So So you're lying.
Okay, I'm lying then. Okay. Okay, we'll go.
Yep. I'm a skin. Yeah. Anyway, I think
you've had a little win on the football
and you've lost most of it. Yep. I've
had a little I've had a little win on
the football. Yeah. Good. Good lad.
Honestly pays a long way. So anyway, can
you please put on your camera because we
want to see the birds in the pub. I
guarantee you I can get you a girlfriend
in that pub.
Listen, Grezy. Griezy, one second. Let
me kick Timmy. Do you think I'm lying
about getting over three grand a month?
Grezy, no, I'm [ __ ] not, bro. I can
get cash out right
now. I can get you out a ground right
now. It's not a
problem. Bum bum
bum. Yeah. just like, "Bro, I never
Yeah, you know how it
Yeah. Yeah, I'm lying, bro. Okay. Yeah,
I'm lying. I'm lying, bro. I'm skin."
Yeah. Okay. I'm lying. Okay. Well, I'm
lying in it.
This is a sad song, bro. It makes me
think of a certain person. They used to
bang the sound at O'Neal's, mate. They
used to bang the sound at
O'Neills. This is a sad song,
bro. They used to bang this out in the
hills, bro. That water streak. [Laughter]
Yeah, I'm not playing. Thank you. I
already put 20 quid in it. I'm not doing
anymore, bro. [ __ ] no. I'm not doing no
more. I put 20 quid in it, bro. I've
already put 20 pound in
it. I've already put 20 pound in it,
bro. I'm not doing it. I'm not doing it no more.
Yeah. I remember that time every time I
used to drink greasy. Yeah. It used to
[ __ ] me up, bro. Every time I used to drink. Yeah.
And I used to meet people like it
doesn't matter who they were. I used to
just go on about that [ __ ] USA Izzy
every [ __ ] time, bro. It used to go
on for like two years. Literally like
two [ __ ] years,
bro. Two [ __ ] years, bro. Imagine
that. Two years of [ __ ] torment and
then it finally went away after two
[ __ ] years. That's a [ __ ] madness, bro.
Imagine that. Two years, bro.
You're just trying to find out the pub
that I'm going in. Timmy, you're not
going to find out where I am. Okay,
Timmy. [ __ ] sake,
bro. Okay, Timmy, if I show you £1,000
right now, you're going to you have to
show me. You have to show me two grand. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm dead, bro. I swear
down. You have to, bro. I can easily do
it. I can easily do it,
bro. Easily do it, bro. Easily do it.
Yeah. Timmy, you don't know about people
what they have, what they don't have.
It's like what? It's like people are
here. I I I don't need to play the money
game though because I've already won. I
sold six grand in cash. [ __ ] [Music]
hell. I shouldn't even be showing money,
but I feel like pissing these [ __ ] off,
Grezy. I actually feel like pissing
these [ __ ] off. Like, you know what I'm
saying, bro? I feel like pissing these
[ __ ] off, bro. Like, it's immature, but
at the same time, it's immature. I'm not
I'm not showing money, bro. I'm not showing money.
This is my drink in like 1
million. I said I never had seven grand.
grand. Want me to piss these [ __ ]
off? Do you want me to Do you want me to
piss these [ __ ] off?
Greasy, I'll go to the ATM right now and
piss these [ __ ] off if that's what you want.
Yeah, I lost all my pip. Grezy, just say
the word, man, and I'll go to the
ATM. Go on at Listen, one second. Timmy's on
it. No, I will do it if you
want, mate. You don't want to pay the
[ __ ] money game with me, bro. Trust
me, you're not going to win.
Oh, you sure
So you're saying that you want me to do
it? So you want me to do it? Loosier. Okay. All
right. I can't be bothered, bro. I fully
fully can't be bothered. And that's
Timmy. Okay. Right. Okay. Timmy,
will you show me? Right. I've got to go
to the bank, PJ, but I can show you
£415 and I'll go to the bank and take another five
out. Noimmy PJ I'm I've got I'm about 50
quid under a grand
so I want to play the money game but I
get paid again mind you Monday above a
healthy amount. So I'm as long as I
don't do my bollocks in I'm in the room.
So if you go to the ATM PJ I'll show you
my 415 quid. Yeah to prove to you. You
show me you show me your 515 and I'll
get a grand out. Okay that's fine.
That's a good deal. I'm up for that.
Ready, PJ? Ready.
Ready. There. I can count it out if I
have to. Do you really want me to count
it out? Count it out and I'll go to the gym. 20 40 60 80 100 120
140 160 I don't know why I'm doing this
180 cuz it's all there [ __ ] 220 no
two sorry two 240 cuz it's 220 there
okay I'll go to the ATM now okay I
believe you believe
I'm coming back. Okay. Go see that. Can
we see the ballots on the ATM, please?
I'm coming back. I'm coming back. We
want to see the balance of the ATM.
Okay. We believe you. We believe. I'm coming back.
This is [ __ ]
seeds. I just want him to go around
around the pub so I can get him kicked
out. I'll make him do it. Trust
me. Yeah. I pretend there's a bird
interesting dress. I get to look around
the pub and then be [ __ ] getting thrown out.
I can't [ __ ] believe the seats on this
plunker. This is [ __ ] funny. This is
lush. It's good to see you triggered,
Baz. It's a good job I'm doing my job
correctly. And you can't show anybody
cuz you're [ __ ] skids. I can count
mine out. You can't count yours out
because you got about what 1,600 to your
name and you can't put it in your bank
cuz they'll [ __ ] take all your money
off them because you owe them lots of
money. Good to see you [ __ ] rattled.
Yeah, the slug hasn't been salted. You
could keep dreaming it for the next 50
years cuz I came to Liverpool and you
never met me. So I [ __ ] own you.
You're in my
pocket. Sorry Baz, the slug hasn't been
salted because you didn't come to Liverpool. I
win. What the [ __ ] is he doing? Is he
having a [ __ ] [ __ ] or what? What the [Music]
I can't stop
laughing. I have never come across such
a big crap like PJ my [ __ ] life.
[ __ ] scenes on
it. Going out on YouTube live drinking by himself. It's [ __ ]
lush. Do you know what? That's not a bad
idea. Good thinking, Batman. Right
there. I'll try not to get out the
stream if I can. Right there. If If I
press the C, I'm on the phone. You see?
Wait there. I've got a plaid. Is that Timmy? Timmy. [Music] Hello.
Okay. [ __ ] Hear me? over grand
here. I see your
money over a grand here,
mate. Turn out for you. 1 2 3 4
5 100 1 2 3 4 5 2
4 1 2 3 4 5
6 1 2 Three.
Seven. One. 2 3 4 5 6 7
8. No. Me. 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 1 2 3 4 5,000
80 There you
go. Done deal. Rob me, bro. You
mad. There you go. I just thought I'd
get some bomb chains out for you. Come
on, Roden face. Let's see your money if
you still got it. Come on, Roden boy.
Come on, you little virgin. Come on.
Give it a whirl. It all virgin. I love
winding these [ __ ] up when I'm
drunk. I love winding them up, mate. You
have no idea. There you go. Smack bank.
Grand peanuts. Let's see your money.
Come on. Me. I've already showed my
money. I've got to go to the bank to get
more out. I just counted it. It's over
grand. I just I've just counted you 450.
What more do you want for me blood? I
can't be asked to go to the bank until I've
shipped. Come on. Come on. I got I
[ __ ] own PJ. I'll wait till I go out
and I'll show you the APM and I'll
[ __ ] upload it for you.
I just got help.
No. Yeah. So, you've heard me buy 50
quid. I've got 950. So, you got 50 quid
more than me. By the time you spend your
day, right? By the time you spend your
[ __ ] day, right, let's be open about
this. By the time you [ __ ] spend your
day, Yeah. Timmy, I get more money today.
Well, you you've been paid today. I'll
take it then. Uh, Timmy, what did I tell
you? Yeah, you said I get a grand a
month. I just showed you over a grand.
How much did I lose yesterday? 200 280.
I roulette after. Oh,
yeah. I told you. This is why you
shouldn't talk about This is why you
shouldn't talk about people that you
don't know. You see what I'm saying?
Yeah, I know what you're saying. The
truth though, Timmy. It's true. Yeah,
it's true. It is true. Am I lying? Am I
lying? No. No, you showed money.
Huh? You showed money. Anyway, PJ,
where's that little [ __ ] Orington
virgin? That little rat face. One
second. I know. One second. Where's the
skinny little rat face with no teeth?
The [ __ ] ugly [ __ ] with a fat ugly
girlfriend. Where was he now with his
[ __ ] little uh with his shitty
[ __ ] what's it called?
Um with his shitty
uh with his shitty little uh housing
benefit. Where is he? Where's that
little rat face on a grand a month? I've
just shown over a grand. There you go.
I've just shown over a grand to that
[ __ ] virgin with a rat face. the ugly
skin rat. And I'll say whilst I'm
showing money, where the [ __ ] is he?
Where is this little rat face? [ __ ]
[ __ ] Bro, don't talk about
people that you don't [ __ ] know.
Doesn't do you no favors,
lad. You've been shown money countless
[ __ ] times. Yeah. And I'm not showing
no money ever again. Yeah, that's
enough. You don't need to get four grand
out. Four grand.
Look, I can bite it. Let's see your
money. Come on. Exactly, bro. You ain't
got nothing. You ain't got no money.
I've got [ __ ] car this around now.
Yeah. [ __ ] me, bro.
Yeah. Where's the skin rat
anyways? I need to keep it moving to, bro.
Yeah, look, I'm I'm in I'm in a pub here
with a [ __ ]
Yeah, imagine that. You can lose so much
money on these machines. I'm not
doing You can lose like so much, bro.
It's crazy, is it?
Yeah, it's my credit card, bro. Do you
even believe what you're [ __ ] You don't
saying. Credit card. I wish it was a
[ __ ] credit card,
mate. I wish it was a credit card, lad.
I actually wish it
was. I want to rub it in your face. Somebody
name. Yeah, it's a credit card.
Anyone who's watching this, [ __ ] rat
face. Rat face little virgin. There you
go. Some peanuts that I just got from
the ATM. There you go. I just got from the [ __ ]
ATM. There you go. People are probably
looking at Oh, I have to [ __ ] Look at
this. Look at this rat face. You can
sort your rat face out with that, buddy.
Come on. You rat face. Oh, come on, bro.
One, two, three, four,
five. There you go, man.
Why? Stop talking about Timmy,
bro. What about that rat face? Um.
Uh uh. How? One, two, three, four,
five. One, two, three. One, two,
three. Hey, hold on a minute,
bro. Hold on a minute. One second. How
are you? Yeah. What about that rat face?
The rat face little virgin in Kent.
People trying to say he's got [ __ ]
money and that he ain't got no [ __ ]
money. The [ __ ]
virgin. That [ __ ] virgin ain't got no
[ __ ] money, mate. He ain't got a pot
to piss him. [ __ ]
virgin. Isn't that something, brother?
Yeah. Isn't that something for you?
E. No friends, no nothing. This is just
to show Timmy that you shouldn't talk
about people that you don't [ __ ] know.
Yeah, that should be a lesson to you and
you people on here. Don't talk about
people that you don't [ __ ] know, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. I think it's a good,
bro. Let me count. Let me see if I got
that right. Timmy, I want to see some of
your money. I want to see the rat face's
money. One, two, three, four, five. One,
four. I think I [ __ ] lost 20, you [ __ ] Yeah.
Hey, you're right. I was just showing
you skin people money
again. Yeah. No one can show me nothing
as usual. Nothing changes in 6
months. Come on, Timmy,
man. Come on,
Timmy. Show us some money, bro. Come
on. Yo, just showing him some money. for
showing him some bum change that [ __ ]
out my ass and you can't show me
nothing. Yep. YouTube never changes. A
YouTube never changes. Hey, calculate
that, bro. The losses on what I've just
shown you. You should actually calculate it, you know. Yeah.
One, two, three, four, five.
There you go. Done.
It's mad how none of these people can
show me any
money. It's mad how none of these people
can ever show me any money though. Is it
m [ __ ] hell? Cuz they ain't got no
money cuz it's
skin. Cuz it's skin. Yeah. Rat face
doesn't owe no
one. At the minute I'm winning at the
money game and no one can show me
nothing. Nah, that rat face loser don't
know no one, mate.
[ __ ] [ __ ] rat face. Ugly [ __ ]
That disabled autistic rat looking
bastard. You [ __ ] don't know no one. bad.
Yeah, Timmy got beat at the money game again. So,
yeah. We're going to be getting on it today.
I need to go in a bit
delay cuz it's going to be a long one.
Yeah, benefit day. Yeah, it's benefit
day. Okay, bro. You keep telling
yourself that, buddy. Benefit day.
Yeah. I didn't know benefits pay that
much. I actually didn't know benefits paid much.
You learn something new every day, don't
you? I can't believe I just got over a
grand now just to show these [ __ ] bongos. [ __ ]
hell. I'm not playing fishing. You can [ __ ] wild,
mate. I won't put any more money in that [ __ ]
I'm not in a Weather
Spoons. I'm not in a Weather Spoons.
Crack on, mate. Yeah, we'll put you will
be put out. It's not a Weather Spoons.
So, you're wrong there. Where I'm at is
not a Weather Spoons. Congrats. It's not
a Weather Spoons. You want to come in,
do you? Yeah, man.
I'll be out today, de lad, and I'll be
out sending a care. Whatever,
mate. I'm out on a session, mate. I just
had to show these people over a
grand. Yeah, you're always on your own, you little
loser. I'm going to be out sending it today,
bro. I just had to show these [ __ ] over
a grand. No one can show me
nothing. [ __ ] it now. It's a badness, isn't
it? We lost 40 on the machine. No more,
bro. No more.
What's happening, mate? You all right,
bro? Well, there's the cashier, lad. How
much is it? Seven and a half. Yeah, bro.
I've showed these people six grand
before and they didn't show me nothing,
bro. My slug showing 100 quid,
lad. Make a [ __ ] millionaire. [ __ ]
mong grand. I just showed over a grand.
I know. See me showing 400 on that. Yeah. [ __ ]
Yeah. He said he's going to show me the
rest tomorrow later. We'll see in it.
Oh, he's showing nothing. He ain't
showing nothing, bro. No way. Is he?
[ __ ] no. Is
he going outside yet?
Yeah, bro. I'm just going to have a few
drinks and just go hit the city in it.
Going in the pool in it. [ __ ] it. What
you smashing on the Guinness, lad? On
the Guinness, bro.
Yeah. Can't beat a good old Guinness, man. You
know, I can't believe I had to get money
out for this. I [ __ ] feel stupid,
bro. I swear. still there. Yeah.
Nope. Think he's gone. My phone's going to die.
Can I show a job or a girlfriend? I've
shown many, many women. Many, many, many
women. And you can't show me nothing.
Just like you can't show me no money. I
just I just whacked out over £1,000 and
you still can't show me nothing. Yeah.
I've shown many, many girlfriends and
many, many, many women. Can you show
anything, you little keyboard warrior?
No, you can't. Bye-bye now, [ __ ] spacker.
Go on, bro. Yeah.
Easy. I need to go in a bit,
lad. Oh, so that's the next thing. So,
first thing is money and then the second
thing is it's a girlfriend. Oh, come on.
Stop being [ __ ]
stupid. Doesn't even make sense what you're
saying. I discovered we'll ask him to
head back get changed and then [ __ ] send him
send the copers are on the way. Good for
them. No one cares. You don't know where
I am and I'm not in a weather spoon. So crack on,
mate. You don't know where I am, so
that's literally impossible. And I'm not
in a Weather Spoon. So congratulations, bro.
Yeah. Crack on,
mate. Take ages to his phone as
well, bro. You don't put one bit of
anxiety in me. Not one bit.
Bye-bye. My life is so empty. Stop talking about
yourself. [ __ ] said the same thing. Uh,
well, I'm telling I'm telling you. Well,
I'm telling you. I'm not [ __ ] I'm me.
So there's a [Music] difference.
Relax. I'm going to finish this. I'm [ __ ] open.
Whoa. Can't believe it's quart 1
already. It's time
to wait to start and it's quart
1. Absolutely. You know what I mean?
Good for you.
Anyways, it's kind of peaceful though to be fair.
D. I love it.
They actually let you withdraw that much. Well,
Oh man, I am fast. Oh, [ __ ]
steal. I have to go out do these
approaches by my [ __ ] self. You
can. I don't need no one, bro. I don't
wait on no one, bro. Byebye,
[ __ ] These people are proper [ __ ]
bongos on this community, bro. Swear to
God. Yeah. Yes, bro.
I'm not put in
there. What is
this? Right. I'm out of here. I'll be
back later or
tomorrow. Who knows? One or two. May or
tomorrow. I can't believe I played the
money game with these people again. Even
though I beat him many, many times. [ __ ]
me. Right. I am [ __ ] out of here,
mate. See you tomorrow
or the next day.
No. Well, see Tuesday or tomorrow. Over
and out. I am [ __ ] out of here. So, I will AV