Yep. Weekly welfare check
as you do. Checking to see if it's the same people.
So then obviously we can say who's the
ones that have a life and who's the ones
that don't have a life. I was able to
take one day off from [ __ ] YouTube.
Well, almost a week really cuz a bit of
weight. So I'm back. No man, I've got to
always start the live streams like that,
you know. Always got to always got to
start the live streams like that. [ __ ] hell.
You know what? Yeah, I think I need to
find a [ __ ] therapist to start
ranting ranting to because that's what I
use this whole [ __ ] platform for. I
don't argue with these little low lives.
I don't get involved with these little
low lives. Yeah, it was good. I was
already there when I was on YouTube last
time. I just didn't let any of you know.
Back to this depressing [ __ ] hole.
Back to this depressing dump of a
country. You know, it's [ __ ] mate. I
hate England. You know what? Yeah, I'll
wait until some more people [ __ ]
join. But we're going to get into this
now. Yeah. When more people join, we're
back to this [ __ ] old [ __ ] old slow
annoying country. You know, this country
annoys me like a bug. You know why was I
on YouTube? I was on YouTube for one
day, bro. You on YouTube every day? Cuz
you can't get off it. Cuz you ain't got
a life. You're on YouTube every day. Why
you on YouTube every day? Get off. Get a life.
Yeah, get off of YouTube.
You can't take um one day off of
YouTube, bro. That's concerning, bro.
Yeah. I can tell you people ain't got
real lives and you ain't got no real
real [ __ ] going on. Yeah.
Yeah. This this, you know, when you're
back in this country, you just realize how
how depressing it is. It is so
depressing. You know what? You know the
maddest thing about this country? It's
actually the people in it. You know, if
there was no people in this country and
and and the weather wasn't um as
bipolar, it would actually be an all
right country to be honest. If there was
no people in it because the people are
just [ __ ] [ __ ] I hate them. Um
this country wouldn't even be too bad,
you know, if it wasn't for the people,
the women, um the [ __ ] on the
bikes. It would it would actually be an
all right country. Um yeah, it was good.
Yeah. Back to this [ __ ] now. I was I was
already there last week. I just didn't
anyone on YouTube though. But yeah, this
country, bro, when you know when you
come back to this country, you just
realize how depressing it actually is.
Like it could actually make you cry.
It's so so so so depressing,
you know? Like it really really is. It's
an annoying aggravating country. Like,
you know, when I was on the train today,
I was saying, "I hate this country. It's
full of entitled dickheads." I was
saying it out loud, bro. I was saying it
out loud and I was waiting for somebody
to say something to me. I want to smash
their [ __ ] face and
Yeah. Disent disinterested women. Yeah.
In this country.
Yeah, man. New people need to really get
some like real life problems, bro. Yeah.
Yep. disinterested women. You mean
that's all this country has to offer and
[ __ ] people. Um I knew that from
working as well. So
do you know what Yeah. was was was
putting me off with this whole country.
Uh the working it was the people. It
weren't customers. It wasn't trains or
being tired or being it's the actual
people in this country. Um
yeah, good for you, bro.
Yeah, like it it was the actual people
that started depressing me. It realized
how much I actually hate people. See,
before I never had no opinion on it. I
just thought, "Oh yeah, where you go to
clubs, people are drunk. Some people
just act like dickheads." But no, there
are some proper proper [ __ ] in this
country. I hate all of them, bro. I I
was waiting so much, bro. The last time
I went out, I was waiting for someone to
start. I was going to smash that bike
over their head. I'm not even joking. I
hate this country.
I hate this country with a I hate
everyone in this country, bro. I'm not
even joking. Asia all the way, bro. Asia
all the way. They got the right idea,
bro. I [ __ ] hate England. [ __ ] hate it.
And there there's this guy right on
Instagram. He says, "People always moan
about England, but it's really not that
bad. It's really not that bad, bro. If I
was to list everything that's wrong with
this country, right, then you think I've
got a long list. But to be fair, it's
mostly the people to be honest, you know, you know. So
yeah. And the thing is with this
country, it never changes, which is why
I left cuz I realized like
how many years are you going to keep
putting up with this [ __ ] How long are
you going to keep putting up with this
[ __ ] Day in [ __ ] day out. You know
what I'm saying? You can't even [ __ ]
go to [ __ ] work without a [ __ ]
[ __ ] You know what I'm saying? Day
in [ __ ] day out. Do you know what I'm
saying? Like [ __ ] these [ __ ] in
this country. Do you know what I'm
saying, bro? Like, bro, they're [ __ ]
normal [ __ ] pedestrians, bro. You
want to [ __ ] stand day in [ __ ] day
out with these [ __ ] [ __ ] Like
you don't know how much I said it on the
train s and I said it out loud bro and I
would have smacked anyone up that went
towards me. They get you like it, bro. I
never had no opinion before. I had no
opinion ever before on people in this
country except the women you know but
that weren't just England. That was
America as well. It was it weren't I had
an opinion on people that went to the
clubs. I never had no opinions on on
people until I until I started until I
started doing this thing, you know. I
had no opinions cuz I didn't really have
experience with them. But they are
proper proper proper proper [ __ ]
And you know what I felt like doing
today, bro? I felt like starting on
people cuz I had a bad day. You know
what these people in London do? Yeah.
What these people in London do? Yeah.
They like to start on people cuz they've
had a bad day. I was going to start
today, but I weren't going to run away
like these people do. I was going to
start and I would have [ __ ] finished
it. That's the difference. like which is
it sounds like you're the range. Yeah.
When you say that, but that's what they
do. That's what these these [ __ ]
do, you know? And I and I have to say it
with a capital D. Like you're just doing
what half the population is is sort of
doing. Do you know what I'm saying, bro?
Like they actually do that.
This country has gone to the shambles,
bro. But I've been meaning to do a video
on this and I've done videos. I've just
not uploaded them. But it's bad. It is
really, really, really, really bad. You
know, they're entitled, you know, and
you know what it is? I tell you what it
is. Did you watch that 24 hours in
police custody the other day where that
guy got um 10 years and seven 10 years
and 7 months? There's no um what's the
word? There's no thingy in this country.
There's no um
what's the word? There's no um
there's no um what's the word? There's
no what's the word I'm looking for? There's no
Oh, what's that [ __ ] word I'm looking for, mate?
Um there's no um
deterrent in this country. That's why
everyone's entitled [ __ ] you know.
I I got stopped for going past the red
light. Um was it a couple of weeks ago?
Police pulled me up. They said, "Oh,
like you know, you went past the red
light." No, no, no, no, no, no, no. I
said, "Yeah, I was in a rush." They
said, "You know, we can give you a £50
fine." That in itself, there's no
punishment in this country. It's why
they're all [ __ ] It's why they're
all entitled [ __ ]
And I say to them, every [ __ ] in there,
they're [ __ ] all [ __ ] That's
why there's no [ __ ] you know, you
rape someone, you're out in [ __ ] 5
years. What the [ __ ] I couldn't believe
that that joke. That's why they're all
[ __ ] in this country. That's why
they're all [ __ ]
You know, places like Thailand, places
like Asia, they don't tolerate no
[ __ ] You break the law, you're
[ __ ] Simple. That's what needs to
happen. You know, this country is it's
it's if you remove all the people, right?
You remove all the people, right? This
country wouldn't be bad. You know what
I'm saying? If you removed everyone in
this country, the country wouldn't be
bad. or or only Chinese people or or
Asian people or like Chinese people are
cool like Asian people are cool but like
you you remove any westernized person
this country is is good bro it it is
it's it's the people it is the system as well
think of that bro what's a 50 fine if
they were giving you to give you a 50
[ __ ] fine there's no there's no
punishment in this country this why
they're all [ __ ] they're so
entitled that they think they can make random comments
to people that they don't even know.
That's how entitled they are. Like, try
to put yourself in their in in your
brain, in their brain, bro. Just think
it's not a normal thing to do.
It's bad, bro. It's a depressing
depressing depressing awful country.
It's an awful awful country. Not to
mention how many times they they they
[ __ ] block the [ __ ] roads off.
It's It's all mad, bro. It's all [ __ ] mad.
But yeah, you can't you can't even get a
conversation out of someone nowadays.
It's it's it's not But it wasn't even
that. It was cuz I'd already given up
with the dating thing. It was the whole people.
You know, next time I ain't [ __ ]
coming back. [ __ ] this. You know what I'm saying?
You know, we've got all problems and and
and and and the women [ __ ] is like 10
15% of it, but it's still there at the
end. I've got a million and one problems
I need to deal with at the moment. I
don't know how I've not [ __ ] done
myself in to be honest with you. I think
at the end of the day, some anyone else
would have done themselves in, they
would have they would have killed
themselves. Like um they would have
either killed themselves or they would
have had a mental breakdown. I'm sure of
it. I'm sure of it, bro. You know,
they would have killed themselves.
I I think bro like this amount of stress
is only normal for two people not one
per and then obviously the whole [ __ ]
you've been out there for three years
bro spending that amount of money and
you're still dealing with this after 3
years [ __ ] hell that is just like
even though that's like 15% of the
problems it's still a problem you know
what I'm saying it's still right at the
end it's just like a middle finger to
you know what I'm saying
Nah, not Jay Willow. I hate this country, bro.
You know, I started um work Jay Willow.
Yeah, I don't mind saying this to you,
bro. Cuz of like, you know, you seem to
be one of the only normal people in
here. I wasn't lying about Thailand. And
you know what? I actually got sick of
going in. And it wasn't because I was
tired. It wasn't because it's long cuz
obviously I needed I needed the money.
Um it was the people. There is so and
yes, I did go to Thailand. Um, if you
don't believe me, don't believe me.
That's up to you, bro. I'm not going to
sit here and argue with you, you know?
I'm talking about real life [ __ ] here.
This country needs to [ __ ] change. If
you don't believe me, don't believe me,
bro. I don't lose no sleep. I've never
met you in my life, bro. Like, I've
never ever ever met you in my life, bro.
Like, if you don't believe me, that's on
you, bro. I'm not going to sit here and
argue with you. It was good, bro. But do
you know what's even more depressing,
Ghost? I'm back in this [ __ ] hole, bro.
You know the maddest thing, bro? I was
thinking you're another one who's come
here a few times, bro. This country is a
sad sad sad country to be in, bro. You
know, you know the worst thing is when
you come back. That's the worst thing. Um,
yeah, it was really good, but it's the coming back.
And you know, the thing is, nope.
Bangkok. And do you know the maddest
thing is? Do you know Ghost? You know, I
was doing this whole uh work thing. Yeah.
And do you know like it do you know what
it done bro? It made me start hating
people which I never had like an opinion
on it ever before cuz I didn't really
know like how many people worked. I'd
only deal with these stuckup [ __ ] in
this country but I didn't mainly in
clubs. I didn't really know what people
were like. But bro, it made me really
start hating people. Really did. And I
and I was looking up like the the job um
description and it seemed like it's like
a very common thing.
Um, there was there is [ __ ] there,
bro. Don't know about you, but I I was
in such a bad mood today, bro. I felt
like doing what they done, like just
starting on a random person, just going
to Liverpool Street and being a [ __ ]
[ __ ] like they are, you know? And
like I I've just decided with the with
this whole work thing and this whole
something else, I really hate people.
Like I was saying to my mom earlier that
I just want to be like Richard Branson.
I want to make enough money and then
just go live in an island. live on an
island. I would love that, bro, with a
little dog. Be away from people. Um
Um Yeah, I got a key ring.
Bye-bye, you [ __ ] But yeah, I I
really do hate this country. Uh ghosting, bro.
I've got so much stress at the minute,
bro. Like, I'm surprised I'm not dead.
I'm surprised I've not [ __ ] killed
myself to be honest. Like so much
stress. If I told you, bro, oh bro, you
wouldn't even believe me. But obviously
I'm not telling people what what happens
on here. But bro, it's really, really,
really bad. And you know what Scal Spiel
told me before?
Do you know what he told me? Yeah.
Everyone pulls in Thailand, bro.
It's just a thing. Do you know what a a
guy called Scal told me before? He said
there's only up. No, with me I'm down.
I'm [ __ ] Literally, I am screwed.
Like, I'm completely [ __ ] Not going
to get into it or anything, but yeah,
I'm basically [ __ ] Not with police or
anything, but yeah, there's only one
way, bro, and that's down. There's no up
now, bro. I'm completely [ __ ] I'm
just waiting around to die now, bro.
Good luck anyone that could take this
amount of stress, eh? Uh, no. I done
videos, but I put it on my other
channel. Yeah, I put videos on my other
channel, bro. But yeah, it's um a lot a
lot a lot a lot a lot a lot of stress,
bro. And there's only one way now, and
that's down, bro. There's no up, there's down.
I'm not going to get into everything,
but it's just
Yeah, I'm going to have to leave this
country again. It's between leaving this
country or suicide,
right? That's that's how it gets, bro.
Yeah. I've done videos on my other channel. Yeah,
it's really bad. Like really really
really bad. Like if I could share like
10% I think most of you people would
have had a mental breakdown.
Like it's really really bad and it never
changes. And it's not even about women
even though that's like maybe 15% of it
in this country. It's about 10 15% but
it's still that bit at the end like oh 3
years and you still ain't found anyone
in this country. And then you still have
people telling you that you're going to
meet someone and no. It's the whole
thing of like like we accept it. We know
what it is, but we need to acknowledge
the fact that it's not normal. Like you
wouldn't be normal if you if you didn't
acknowledge the fact that um
that it's not normal. Obviously, it's
not normal, bro. Like that's it. So
So I'm basically [ __ ] bro. I'm just Yeah.
I basically do myself in. I think if I
didn't have my mom, I think I probably
would do myself in. Not that I need my
mom, but like you don't really want to
be burying a child. So, cuz they're not
blips. See, little blips are things that
um talking about yourself. Um little
blips are um I just told you I got women
over there, bro. I just said that about
10 times, but we're not there now. We're
here. We're back in England. We're back
in this [ __ ] hole.
So, as I was saying, ghosting, it got to
a point where it was hard even going to
work because of the people in this country.
I hated public transport cuz I hate
people now. Like, yeah.
So, it's really, really bad. Like, I'd
be here all day if I told you
everything, bro. And it got to a point
where the last time I went, I was going
to run somebody over with a bike, bro.
If someone started on me, it was I think
it was a Sunday was the last time I done
it. I would have rammed them over that
bike, bro. I'm not even joking. I was
like, I'm waiting for someone today to
start. I'm waiting for some [ __ ] in
London to start, bro. And I'm going to
[ __ ] chase them with this bike. I
swear to God. And that's not normal,
bro. Like, they That's how much I was
losing my temper with them, bro. I was
just doing this [ __ ] uh Uber Eats thing.
Yeah, I was just doing this Uber Eats
thing. But funny enough, the customers
were all nice. None of them were rude.
No Chinese person was rude. They were
all sound, but it was the people that I
was sharing the road with. Um,
and I was like, listen, I get your
point. We all have bad days. I'm [ __ ]
now. Yeah, we all have bad days. We all
have things going on in our lives, but
that does not make you feel the need to
be entitled to start [ __ ] going on
the [ __ ] street to people that you
don't know, right? Having an attitude
and then running away. Do you
understand? You're not superior, bro.
You understand? Like, everyone's got big
problems in their life, bro. Massive
problems. I think 65% of people on
anti-depressants and what? So, we can
just go around on the street being a
[ __ ] [ __ ] to every Tom Dick and
Aari because, oh, poor me. Like, you
know what I'm saying, bro? Bro, I could
tell you some mad stories.
It's crazy, bro. It's no life in this
country. It's really really no life,
bro. Like, no, I won't be fine tomorrow
because it's not a bad day because
there's other things going on. I'm not
going to tell you, bro. I'm not going to
tell you. It's other things and I'm not
going to get into it. I'm [ __ ] pretty
much. So, this this will never ever ever
ever ever ever change, bro.
Did I spend bucks over there? Uh about
one and a half.
But yeah, I'm I was earlier I was really
thinking of suicide, bro. Like I'm I'm
not even joking.
Really, really, really thinking of it.
The country that I'm in with these
[ __ ] the whole the women [ __ ] was
all the way at the end. It's not a life
for anyone, bro. It's no life for
anyone. Like, we laugh at it, but it
really ain't no life. It ain't no life
for anyone, bro.
It really ain't. I can't stand the
people in this country, bro. I don't
know where you people live.
It's like that woman. But I was thinking
about that like the other day I told
you. Yeah, it was hot. She's like, "Oh,
don't." So, uh, you're not supposed to
be there. I said, "I'll go where I
want." I said, [ __ ] starts running up
her mouth. Had to hawk up that bite,
bro. She's with another guy. I said,
"What are you saying? Come back now.
Come back here and start running up your
mouth." Does that sound like a normal
thing to deal with when somebody is is
is is at work, bro? Like, do you
understand? It's not it's not a normal
way of living, you understand, bro?
Like, it's it's it's not normal, bro.
These people and they done it. It's
happened a few times like in in in the
past. Like, they're they're pedestrians
on the street, bro. They're pedestrians
on the street. It ain't normal. You understand? So, yeah.
Yeah, it makes you feel better. Stop
talking. Hey, listen. This channel ain't
for you spasticating repeaters. We're
talking about normal life and [ __ ] in
this country. We're not talking about
you um you you repeaters and yeah, bro.
And I had to deal with other people and
I've just realized I really hate people
except from Chinese people and stuff.
But um yeah, I can't Yeah. And that's
the worst thing ghosting because I've
come back to this this depressing [ __ ]
country. Hey Grevy, you know what I said
to my mom today as well? I said to her,
I like Grezy talking about yourself.
Bye-bye. Stop self-reflecting. Anyways,
this this channel wait for you
40-year-old losers to self-reflect. We
we we done that years ago, bro. Anyways,
stop self-reflecting, you sad bastard
that ain't got a life. Anyways, Grezy, I
said to my mom um that if I had all the
money in the world, I would literally go
to an island like Richard Branson with a
French bulldog and I would just live my
life in peace.
You know, the the guy that owns Virgin
Medi has his own island. Cuz I've come
to think how much I really hate people
in this country. If I was if I was
living in Asia, it' be a different
story. I hate people, bro. I hate them,
you know? I really really hate people in
this country, lad.
Um, it's they're entitled [ __ ] stupid
[ __ ] [ __ ] Like I was sending a
voice note today. Yeah. To someone on
the train, right? And there was
obviously people on the train looking.
They weren't saying nothing to me, mate.
You think any of them were going to say
anything to me? I'll tell you to your
face. You're a westernized [ __ ] You
need to sort it out, bro. I hate it,
bro. I hate England. like, "Bro, you
really really don't know." Rezy, that's
what stopped me wanting to like do this
whole um Uber thing. Well, I don't do it
anymore. It was actually the people. It
weren't the job. It wasn't the trade. Uh
I the work. It was It weren't the
customers. It was the actual people on
the street, these London [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] Um, and it got
to a point where I had to like take a
few days off and calm down because
um, if if anyone started that day, I
would have ran them over the bike, bro.
It's not even a joke. I'll give you an
example. One woman did say something on
that day. She was like, "You're a bad cyclist."
Um, okay. I said, "You so are you." I
mean, why are they saying stuff to
people that they don't know? Like, this
is people on the street. Like obviously
I understand road rage happens when you
almost bump into somebody or they almost
bump into you or you smash up their car.
These are random people on the street,
bro. Yeah, I took free food. I took free
um free delivery foods. Yeah, they were
[ __ ] lovely. But the person got their
money back. But we're talking about the
people, bro. It's really really a
depress It's really a depressing country
to be in.
And I look back on like and I was
watching this guy. Yeah. and he went to
Manchester, right? Um, and he said it
was his first time in Manchester. Um,
and it's mad cuz it got me back to
thinking like, [ __ ] he's been
Manchester, obviously he's been abroad
as well, of course, but it's so weird
for him to say like this is my first
time in Manchester and he's like 2 years
older than me and it's like I've been to
Manchester 10 times and like when I used
to go out trying for 3 years, spending
that money and I have nothing to show
for it. I think that as well is about
20% of it as well along with the other
problems. It just gets worse and worse
and worse. You know what I'm saying? The
only way is down. And I I shouldn't take
other people's food. Imagine that
happened to me. Well, I don't need to
imagine it, bro. Um actually, I took it
for a certain reason because the road
got blocked off. That's another thing.
The road start um kept getting blocked
off. I wouldn't need to imagine if it
was me because if it was me, I would
just get somebody else to deliver the
food. They don't lose the food. they get
their money back or they get fresh food
from another driver and I cancelled it
because they blocked the whole [ __ ]
road which is why I had to cancel it,
not because I wanted to cancel it. They
blocked the whole road off and Oh yeah.
And I had I had a funny conversation
with the police as well. I said, "Um,
can you let me go? I need to deliver um
I need to deliver um I need to deliver a
um you I need to deliver um some food."
And obviously the gay part was I was
like I like he said oh you can't get
through. I said I need to deliver this
customer's food. And he says oh can you
walk to them? I looked at him I was like
bro are you okay about can I walk to
them? I said no it's 16 minutes away.
They've ordered food. They want their
food. And he's like oh can can they
come? I was like bro is this guy taking
a piss? Like there's no there's no way
they people can be that stupid. Like I
actually thought I walked away like bro
there's no this guy's taking a piss on
it. Like is he really asking that? Like
imagine imagine the shoe was on the
other foot. Yeah. And then he would not
let I said I need to deliver this food
to a customer and they weren't having
none of it at all at all. And then then
I tried another road. It was blocked and
that's how I ate the food. So I didn't
eat it because I wanted just to eat
their food. I physically couldn't take
it to them because once they block a
main road it blocks about four
locations. So, I had to go all the way
back home cuz I couldn't work. So, yeah.
And I was like, uh, and then you get
stupid people. Um, I I had something the
other day when I was trying to sell
someone something and they were like,
oh, what was it? He was like, um, he was
like, oh, uh, uh, is it new? I was like,
brother, did you not read what I've just
put or are you just being intentionally
stupid? Bear in mind, I'm already sick
of people as it is due to this job. I
was like, bro, are you intentionally
being stupid? like, "Please tell me
you're intentionally being stupid or
you're just trying to wind me up." And
then he says, "Oh, you seem to got anger
problems messaging people around for
your ego." I said, "Bro, is that really
what you think? Is that really really
what you think?" And furthermore, right,
if I was doing that, guess what? I'd be
doing everything that you're doing. So,
you need to practice what you preach,
bro. You are the same people that go on
the road starting on people that you
don't know for no [ __ ] reason. And
another thing we need to put uh we need
to say as well is starting things they
can't finish. Um which is what they like
to do in London. They like to make
little sly sarcastic comments and then
when they're told to come back they soon
[ __ ] their [ __ ] pants. No one would
think that these are normal people that
you don't even [ __ ] know.
So yeah, I just made my decision that I
actually hate people. Firstly, it was
women because they're all just stuck up
and entitled and they're all the same.
But it wasn't people in general until I
started this and then realized like,
bro, they really are stupid, aren't
they? Like, you've got the police asking
a stupid question. So, yeah.
So, I'm thinking if I went out, if I
went out starting on people for no
reason, that's literally what you people
do yourself cuz I've experienced it.
Seven days of me working on this job,
right? Like I said about the woman as
well. Yeah. Don't uh you're not supposed
to be there. I said, "I will go where I
want." You're not a police officer.
Don't tell me where I need to go. I
didn't even say in a rude way. I just
said, "I'll go where I want."
N you're [ __ ] this. You're off. I
said, "You [ __ ] what?" I parked the
[ __ ] bike and she [ __ ] ran off
with this guy. Yeah, she was with this
guy. I said, "Come back and say that to
my [ __ ] face." Yeah, I'm not in a
[ __ ] I'm not in the best mood, but
guess what, bro? I don't go around
starting on random people. It's like who
the [ __ ] do they think they are bro? You
know what I mean?
What I should have said was you need to
mind your own [ __ ] business. So if
you can imagine where it is you are
where you are. Think of it in London.
And then it got to the point like I said
Grey hated sharing public transport with
them. All the Chinese people were fine.
All the customers were fine. That's the
funniest thing about it. Grezy. All the
customers were fine. They'd help you.
They were so nice, bro. like um you know
what I'm saying? Like why did I start? Um um
Maybe because I needed extra money.
Pretty self-explanatory question. And I was bored.
I mean that's pretty self-explanatory, right?
So, that's basically,
no, it's not a dead job. It's actually a
really good job. You can work when you
want. You don't have anyone telling you
what to do. Um, you're self-employed,
grievy, which was the best thing. Like,
you could do it when you want, cycling
around, no one telling you what to do.
It was it was it was beneficial in a lot
of ways. Like, I'll never do a job
that's not self-employed. Never.
Um, so but that's my experience as
somebody trying to work, you know, like
this is the [ __ ] you got to deal with.
And the police kept um blocking off the
roads as well. Um,
nah nah. If you don't earn enough, it
was not a dead job, bro. But again, it's
a job. It's a job. I'm telling you
experiences of what happens when you
work in this job. Yeah, I'm saying that.
So, yeah, was something better than
nothing. But it's not the point, bro.
The people and their attitude is [ __ ]
disgusting in this country. Like, I'm
not even joking, mate. It's really,
really, really, really bad. It made me
start really hating people. And I never
had an opinion on on it before, bro. So,
yeah. No, you can earn and still be on
benefits. You need to earn a certain amount.
But anyways, bro. Um, like that's me
just giving you experience. Obviously,
when I do it again or I work again, I'm
never going to I don't do it anymore.
But when I do do something again, I will
never tell you what it is. Obviously,
cuz grass is on here, but people sort of
figured it out and I didn't want to tell
anyone until I stopped. So, I will never
ever obviously tell anyone ever again.
But again, that's it's the point still
standing, bro. It's really bad.
I I just figured I just hate people.
So like it's that's it, bro. But yeah,
Ghosting, it weren't no customers. It
weren't no Chinese people. They were all
nice. All of them were nice. Like even
when like you had to go all the way to
the top, they'd come down. They were
really, really nice people, bro. Really,
really, really, really nice people. Um
cuz most of them were Chinese. So, and
it's like, bro, you ain't even been to
Thailand yet. I was thinking at that
point, and you're already seeing the
difference, bro. It's this country, bro.
I'm telling you. I'm telling you it is.
So yeah, I don't gamble anymore. So
you can get it weekly or you can get it
the same day.
But it was something to do and it was
something to help me basically accept
the fact that I'm completely screwed. So
but yeah, I'm not doing that again. So
yeah, if it weren't for my mumbler, I'd
kill myself. I ain't going to lie to you.
I'm not going to lie to you, bro. I'm
all serious on this channel. I know
makeup stuff. The fact that you tried in
all of them years,
um, you know, you all that money you
went through and you're still having the
same conversation. It wasn't for my mom,
bro. I'd kill myself if I didn't plan to
live in another live in another country.
Um, it's really, really, really, really bad.
So yeah, I'm not going to tell you all
the problems, but um if any of you had
these problems, you'd kill yourself. Um
well, you wouldn't you'd probably have a
nervous breakdown or you'd give up your
life or you'd be [ __ ] You might not
necessarily kill yourself, but you
wouldn't be able to do it. So
yeah. So it's bad, bro. I ain't even had
time for myself for so long. I haven't
gone out for a drink. So
So yeah, man.
But anyways, I just told you something I
did that I don't no longer do. And when
I do do something again, I'll never tell
anyone because too many grers.
But that women thing is is very concerning.
Obviously, like I said, it's like, bro,
you look decent looking. There's nothing
wrong with you. Yeah. You got enough
numbers on your phone. Somebody should
be interested. It's not normal. It's not
normal, bro. Do you understand, bro? It
ain't normal. You know, where I hadn't
approached for like 3 weeks, I had some
numbers on my phone. Yeah. I thought,
"Oh, let me hit them up again. Let me
hit them up again." I contact them, see
what they're saying. I was like, "Let me
ask I I invited one I met at the train
station. I said, "Oh, do you want to go
to a steakhouse because it's only money
I haven't had?" And just see what they'd
say cuz I I had already had their
number. And then they turned around and
said, "Oh, it was nice meet um hi,
that's very kind of you.
Um but I'm flying out and I won't have
time. It was great meeting you though."
And I'm thinking, "Huh?"
Like I didn't even reply. I'm thinking,
"So, bro, you can't even be One second,
bro. You can't even be decent looking
and invite somebody out to a 250 meal
and they're still not interested. What
the [ __ ] bro?" And obviously, I
messaged like a couple of other numbers,
but I had I'd already had them from like
the Wednesday and the Thursday like
weeks ago, bro. They're not recent. It's
not normal. It's really, really, really,
really, really not normal, bro. And then
you've got people saying, "Oh, like you
don't give up hope. No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. You know, you'll find
someone." Bro, this has been going on for years,
for [ __ ] years. And when I heard
about that guy going to Manchester, you
know, and he's only been once, and then
I'm thinking, bro, I used to do that all
the time. Go Manchester, get the same
old [ __ ] Go Liverpool, get the same old
[ __ ] Bro, Scotland get the same old
It ain't [ __ ] right, bro.
No, they don't ghost. It's all different things. So,
yeah, it was good, bro. But now it's
even [ __ ] that I have to come back to
this country. But I'm back in this
country now. So,
so yeah, I'm [ __ ] Completely screwed. So, yeah.
But yeah, it's not normal ghosting, bro.
A decent say put put in your shoe, bro.
If a decent looking person or an average
looking woman hit you up and say, "Oh,
do you want to go for some lobster? Oh,
do you want to go for some steak?" You'd
be at least interested to give them a
try, wouldn't you? If you were single,
like, you need to put the shoe on the
other foot. It ain't normal, bro. It
ain't normal. And even though it's 15%
of the problems, it's still a big
problem. It's not like, yeah, you look
like Timmy Eldridge. I'd get it, bro.
Like, you're fat, you're ugly, you you
you're not, bro. Like, you got a decent
body. You look normal. Normal to decent.
I've got into captain recently. It's not
normal. It ain't [ __ ] normal, bro. I
flew directly, but it cost a bit more
money. So, you understand, bro? It's not
like you look like one of these people.
You understand? So it's it's like a kick
in the tooth and then you've got to deal
with the people and [ __ ]
So yeah, like the only way
Yes, you can fly direct. And I'm not
talking about it anymore, bro. If you
want to keep being obsessed about it,
you keep being obsessed about it. So
anyways, ghosting, that's basically what
it is, bro. It's It's not normal, bro.
like I completely just give up with
life. I gave up with the whole dating
thing when I done the Uber before I went
Thailand, but I'd already I had already
given up with them. It was a different
kind of stress. Now I just have to sit
around now, accept the fact I'm
completely [ __ ] and there's nothing I
can do about it unless I want to leave
the country again. Do you know how
annoying that is? Do you know how
[ __ ] annoying that is? Having to sit
around in your own [ __ ] and sweat and
there's nothing you can do. It's a
frustrating life, bro.
It really, really, really, really,
really, really, really is. 3 years of
nothing. Oh, I called that USA Izzy. Oh,
[ __ ] I forgot to tell you. Yeah, I
called that USA um the other day and she
picked up. I said, "What you saying now,
you little [ __ ] Why didn't you accept
my offer when I said I was going to come
to your country last month and a half?
You [ __ ] mug." Didn't say nothing.
soon shut her mouth. Didn't know who I
was. And it's it's all like previous
experiences, the whole 3 years, all of
the other things going on. It just adds
up and adds up and adds up. What's 15 +
15? 30. What's 15 * [ __ ] four, bro?
60. It all adds up. All of it adds up.
You understand, bro? I've already been,
bro. I've already been.
But yeah, I could understand it if you
was like fat and ugly. Then I could
understand like you're fat, you're ugly.
Like I can understand it, bro. I
understand that. I don't care what
people look like. But in this day and
age, it's very
uh it's very shallow.
I'm surprised I've not had a mental
breakdown. I'm really surprised. I'm so
surprised. Really, this this this life,
bro. It's just uh I've got videos
uploaded on my other channel.
It's really bad ghosting. Like, it
really is. I I even wish I was joking,
bro, but I'm not.
And then you realize all the people in
this country are [ __ ] as well.
I love to know where the entitlement
comes from. It It's because there's no
discipline in this country. That's what
it is, bro. It's because there's no
discipline in this country. Why do you
think, right, every time you you you
meet a Chinese person, they're all nice.
All nice and they mind their own
business. Because, bro, they've been
brought up better. This country, bro, it's like,
uh, because I just went there cuz I
liked it there, bro.
So, like, out of all of the customers I
dealt with, Yeah. throughout this whole
eight days of Uber, seven, eight days.
Never met a bad person, bro.
Never met a bad person, bro. They were
all so nice, bro. Every single one,
restaurants, customers, they never had a
problem with them.
Never had a problem with them. Even
Eastern European, you don't get problems
with them. They're just, they don't
start on people. It's just these
[ __ ] in England. I want to give one
of them a good hard lesson, bro. I want
a woman like that woman. She's so lucky
she didn't get rude to me that day. The
last day on it like, "Oh, you're a bad
She said it like this. You're a bad
cyclist." I said, "So are you. Thank you
very much." I was waiting for her to get
rude, bro. Like the last time I was
waiting for any man or any woman to get
rude. You I would have chased them down,
bro, in front of that bully band.
So it's like, think about like this,
bro. We get the dating thing. Don't you
not think it's abnormal, right?
That when a normal person is working,
bro. Yeah. You can't even work without
dealing with it. Do you not understand,
Grevy, how it's not normal? Like, we all
heard about people owing people stuff
and all of these excuses to stop to uh
for women [ __ ] behavior. But the thing
is is that you can't even work without
dealing with this
because these people seem to think the
world revolves around them. Oh, poor me.
I'm having a bad day. Let me be a
[ __ ] and start something I can't
finish. Oh, [ __ ] losers. This country
is full of [ __ ] losers.
You know what I'm saying?
I can't believe what that police officer said.
I can't I can't believe you he actually
asked that question.
You done a protest. You've blocked the
whole road again. You know,
and got a job, bro. I've been doing this
Uber for weeks. What are you talking
about, you idiot?
I was doing Uber for [ __ ] weeks.
Yeah, I did.
But the amount of numbers and traveling
and trying I've done I you should be
with someone. You should have a handful of experiences
like you should be rolling it in bro
with the way that you look. It's not
normal. It's not a normal way of life.
Obviously that's not the main problem
that we're dealing with now but it's a
problem bro. It is a big problem you know.
Yeah I did. I just answer that. Oh.
Oh, these batteries almost out. [ __ ]
Why do you think this country is full of [ __ ] anyways?
Obviously, I had to go to work because
if I didn't go to work, Grezy, how could
I um fund for little Franklin's
membership? I wouldn't be able to fund Franklin's membership.
£15 a month.
But I did have to take a break for a
little bit because of a [ __ ] I need a
fan. It's hot in here, man.
Yeah, I'm playing Franklin right now actually.
But I do hate this country. I hate the
people. I hate the women. I hate the
waiting around for things.
Oh, mate. Yeah, I call that USA Izzy up.
Greasy. I told her she she said hello. I
told her to go suck her mom.
Why is this run out of batteries, bro? I don't understand.
Uh, could be cuz I'm overweight and
disabled, bro. Uh, bro, I think you've
got yourself mixed up with me. I'm not
disabled or overweight. I think you
could be mistaken me with yourself.
Classic projector, bro. Please, can you
just for one day, just just one day?
Like, I know it's hard because you
people have nothing else in your lives
but coming on YouTube every day, but
just for one day. Okay, I know one day
is hard for you. Just for 12 hours. Can
you just try not to project once and
have a normal conversation?
Yeah, I done it on an ebike. Just just
for 12 hours. I know a day is too hard
for you. I know none of you can take a
day off of YouTube, but just for one
day, you know,
you know, just just for one day, bro.
That was a little bit hot. Half actually, bro.
Yeah, it makes no sense. It makes no
sense that I was doing Uber on a bike.
Okay, explain to me how that makes no sense,
right? So, okay, I didn't do Uber Eats
on a bike because it makes no sense,
bro. It is amazing. And then you come
back to this country full of [ __ ]
and then it's worse when you've been out
and then you come back cuz you know what you're missing.
And they don't all just want money as
well, bro. Like you can go to the
Philippines as well, which I've not been
to, and they actually want genuine
relationships. Here, you just get piss
takers, [ __ ] [ __ ] just
Oh, bro. I just don't even want to be
around people. I don't even want to talk
about it anymore.
Do you know what my friend said? Yeah.
Do you know what my friend said? Well,
one of these people I go out with, uh,
Greavvesy, he's like, "Oh, we should go
out." I was like, "Bro, the last thing
that is on my mind is going out. Do you
not realize I'm fucked?"
You know what I'm saying? I've got so
many things to deal with and you're
talking about [ __ ] going out, like
going out and drinking, mate. I haven't
even had time to go to the [ __ ] gym.
And I said, "Can you stop asking me to
go out when you're scared to speak to
people?" He said, "Oh, I just want to go
out and have fun and it's not all about
women, but you keep complaining about
women." No, no, no, no, no, no, no. And
you can't even [ __ ] approach. So,
[ __ ] off, mate. I don't even have the
time to go to the [ __ ] gym now
[ __ ] days, you know? And yes, I would go back.
Why don't I want to talk about it, bro?
Because we're not like Lord Jay. Oh, I'm
going to Vegas. Shitty Vegas that I've
been to six times and then says it every
day because of his anxiety.
But yeah, this country never changes.
There's one number I got. She said that
she's in Greece for 2 months and she's
going to meet me
um when she comes back, which is not
going to happen. So yeah, I actually
felt like going outside today and just
punching someone up, which is again, it
seems like it's um what's the word? It
seems like you're deranged, but you're
not deranged cuz it's all of these
people doing it as well. I mean, they're
[ __ ] saying stuff on the street and
everything now. So, I mean, practice
what you preach, mate. And when I said
that to that guy, um, who I was trying
to sell something to, he never said
anything off that. I said, cuz you know
I'm right. You can't call anyone
frustrated or got a temp or a temper.
Do you know what I'm saying? When
[ __ ] you are, you do the same [ __ ]
You do the same thing. That's how
[ __ ] deranged you are.
What was my favorite thing? the food,
the weather, the people. It's not like
this [ __ ] country.
You know what? I'm I was thinking back
on this the other day. Um Grezy
surprised how I never ever ended up like
doing someone in like the amount of
times I used to go out drinking and had
to deal with [ __ ] I'm very very
very surprised like I never ever end up
hurting someone really badly
cuz I think you would or anyone else would have.
Now, people don't give me credit, bro.
Like, you you you get people that say,
"Oh, you're impatient, mate." I've only
just started losing my patience three
and a half years later.
It will happen one day, bro. I
definitely reckon if I continue doing
that Uber, somebody would have been on
in an ambulance. Somebody would have
been in an ambulance. I'm not even
joking, bro. Like, you laugh at it, but
it's not funny at all. It's not funny at all, bro.
Yeah, I'll record it, bro. [ __ ] run
him over the bike and record it.
One even tried giving me a dirty look,
bro. And I just gave him a dirty look
back and I as if to say, "Don't you even
think about fight to start on me, you
cunt." You know what I'm saying, bro?
Yeah. You don't bother me. Oh, well,
you've had a bad day. Oh, what has
happened, bro? The wife has cheated on
you. Oh, did did the child keep you up?
Oh, poor me. The world revolves around
me. I'm a big Londoner and the world
revolves around me. Oh,
I'm going through a bit I'm going
through a bit of depression right now.
Oh, damn. The world revolves around me.
Oh, poor me. That's literally what it's
like, bro. They That's literally what
they're like, you know? I'd actually
love to meet people that actually don't
have any problems.
I didn't see any, bro. I didn't see any
and I didn't order food, so I'm not
sure. But they generally feel like the
world revolves around them.
And I always say to people, I'm from
London, but I'm not a [ __ ] And I
and I explain to them that like, oh, I'm
from London, but I'm not [ __ ] like
these people. And I say in front of
their face, I say, I've been to
Middlesborough. I've been to poverty
ridden areas and I've never thought I
was better than anyone. But these
[ __ ] do, they think the world
revolves around them because they've had
a bad day. Okay, you've had a bad day
and and your point is I've had a bad
week. I'm [ __ ] The only way up for me
is down. I'm completely [ __ ] now.
I would trade positions with anyone
right now. But you don't see me going
out starting on people, random people on
the street as well, cuz that's [ __ ]
[ __ ] And what's even more [ __ ]
is they can't finish it. [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah. Again,
there's no discipline in this country.
This is why people do that.
Like I said, you watch the new 24 hours
in peace custody. This guy raped about
four women and he got 10 years and 7
months. He'll be out in 5 years.
The police stopped me going over a red
light. Oh, you shouldn't do that. You
know, you can get a 50 fine. This is why
people take the piss. They they because
they there's no discipline in this country.
You know what I mean?
There's no discipline, so they
so they take the piss out of the the
system. So like that's that's what it
is. Um Greasy.
[ __ ] 10 years. 10 years. I mean, I
hate women. They're [ __ ] But [ __ ]
10 years. [ __ ] hell, bro. You be out in five.
And then and then the police is stopping
me saying, "Oh, you went over the the
red light. I was in a rush." He said,
"You know, you can get a £50 fine. Do
you think a £50 fine is enough to deter
anyone from doing anything?
You know what I'm saying?
This this this country, bro,
you know, I would I wouldn't mind if it
was just the women, but it's actually
the people. It's the people and the
women." But a lot of the the times it is
women as well though. Like I'm thinking
Grezy I wouldn't even do that. Stop like
making comments to random people on the
street. Like I'm not even bro I wouldn't
even be I wouldn't say brave enough to
do it. I just wouldn't like
they're [ __ ] who it just like who
thinks of these things, bro. You know
what I mean?
You know what I'm saying? But they'll be
the first one to play [ __ ] victim
when you [ __ ] tell them about
themselves though. You know what I mean?
And you know what I mean, Grezy? Like I
was saying to you earlier, bro, maybe
you didn't hear it. It's not like it's a
manager that needs the work done and
he's in a bad mood because some people
have bad days or you dealt with a shitty
customer cuz he had a bad day. It's
random people on the street and there's
no reason to be acting like that.
There's literally no reason. You understand, bro?
Well, it's definitely run out of
batteries. They're not It's not normal,
bro. They're not customers or managers
like, bro, like them things happen, but
this that's not normal, bro. That ain't
you know? And don't forget about the guy
guys in groups that act big and hard.
You get these white guys in groups.
Yeah. They've had a drink and they start
acting the big man when they're in a
group. [ __ ] [ __ ]
I still tell them about themselves even
when they're in a group. I just say,
"Yeah, come back when you're not in a
group, mate, and see how big you are." I
hate this country, bro. I swear down. I
was so close today, bro, to going out
and doing someone in, bro. Like, not not
not straight away doing someone in, but
just starting being a [ __ ] and looking for trouble.
And to think people actually turned you
like that as well, it's mad. They never
told me that on Reddit. Jesus. I was
going to start something like in the
middle of Liverpool Street.
What's the worst thing about London? Uh
um the people. What the [ __ ]
This is [ __ ] Uh the people and the
women. The people. The women.
The phone snatching. You get your phone
rolled very quickly. And just people's
attitude. The people and the women. If
there were no people, it'd be all right.
And if the weather was a bit better,
then England would be perfect.
Um, but yeah, the phone snatching is a
big problem. That's the only thing you
need to worry about when you go to
London, bro, is you're going to get your
uh you're going to get your phone
snatched. You're not going to get
stabbed, but you'll get your phone
snapped if you're not careful. Um, so
and they keep blocking off the [ __ ]
roads, which doesn't allow people to work. So,
yeah. Snobby girls with egos. They all
think they're better than everyone.
Yeah. But you know the badest thing,
Grezy, is is like I was saying to you,
bro, no one ever told me this. Like if
you approach women, you're going to get
I've got a boyfriend. You're going to
deal with [ __ ] when you try and go
and work for a living. No one ever told
me this on the internet. So I feel like
5% of it is I was lied to my whole life.
Um it's it's a really really bad place
to to live.
Trust me, if it wasn't for Laney, I'd kill myself.
Yeah, they think they're better than
everyone in London and they're not.
They're just [ __ ] And I say to
their face like all the time, you're
nothing but a [ __ ] Like, I do, bro.
Like, I hate these people in London. I
hate the women. I hate the people. I
hate the cyclists. I hate all of them.
Hate all of them, bro. Trust me, you don't understand.
I hate the whole dating [ __ ] in this
country. It's not normal for somebody to
not look like Timmy and Stalker prime
someone. I hate everything about this
country. I hate everything. I did. I
told that woman about herself. I said,
"Stop walking away. If you got something
to say, come back." I parked the bike.
Yeah, I did, bro. I did tell them about themsel.
Everyone that made a little slight comment
and then they just rode off. Might have
been like three people or something. So,
and trust me, them bikes are [ __ ]
heavy, mate. So, if somebody runs you
over with that bike, you ain't getting
up, bro. You are not getting up. Cuz
when the when the when the battery runs
out grievy, mate, you can't even cycle
it. It's that heavy.
What I would have done, honestly, if
someone started on me that day, the last
day I done it, what I would have done is
I would have done a U-turn. I would have
chased them with their bike and I would
have grabbed them by their [ __ ]
[ __ ] ear. I would have got them off
that bike and I would have pushed the
bike over them, bro. I'm not even
joking. Yeah, I'm not even joking. And
there's no way they're faster than that
bicycle. You know, I even said to Laney
as well, like, I'm going to run somebody
over with my bicycle.
I'm going to run someone over with my
bicycle today. Someone pisses me off.
Yeah, [ __ ] [ __ ] Right.
[ __ ] lick them over that back. I swear down
it wasn't good money, but it was better than nothing.
But this Jamie guys still stalking me.
You know, this is why I don't really
come on here much anymore. Um, Grezy,
but I only come here for like a ranting session.
I don't get involved with any of the
drama because um it's just [ __ ]
The people just never ever stop. They
don't know when to leave people alone.
I'm just not involved with any of this
um [ __ ] on here anymore, bro.
I have to do that another day, bro.
Yeah, I was going to ride them over with
my big bicycle, Grezy. With my big bicycle.
Change my lifestyle?
What do you mean change my lifestyle?
You need to leave this country again.
That's what you need to do.
And it is this it is this country as
well cuz you you never have any of these
problems with Asian people.
I told you about that story. I was
struggling to put the bike up the ramp.
These two Chinese people come over. They
help me and they said take care. And
another thing is right um it was I was
trying to find some flats. The map was
sending me I was like 2 minutes away. I
was in the the the place. I asked a few
people, "Do you know where this house
is?" It was something. It was like the
name of the apartment. No, we don't
know, mate. Don't know, mate. I was
like, mate, I'm lucky I don't get robbed
over here or I don't get stabbed over
here because no one's going to be
helping me, you know. And even you can
tell some of them generally did know.
they generally generally did know
because of um and but even if they
didn't know it's the it's their whole
attitude whereas a Chinese person would
go out their way to help you even if
they didn't even understand English.
Nah, it's actually right to be honest.
I've actually got some videos I'll show
you actually. What's it bro? Oh yeah.
A food delivery ain't on, bro. You're self-employed.
You're self-employed, which is a good thing. [Music] Um,
one second, please, bro.
Right. I've got some videos. Yeah, I
want to put up. I'll just let you see. Oh [ __ ] Something's here.
One second, bro.
Now, this is a job I got which was
paying quite [ __ ] good.
Can you see it? £14. Can you see that?
Oh, it's backwards, isn't it?
That was £14 that job was paying, but it
was quite a way and the thing was almost
run out of battery.
Wait, can you see it properly or is it
going or is it dodge?
One second, bro.
It's the other way around, is it? Can
you see it or no?
I got one for Grezy. Stay tuned, lad.
Yes, you do. Stop calling yourself a M.
Stop self projecting. You don't. Yes,
you do. Keep the whole 40. What they pay
you? They pay you. No, they've already
take the cut. So, when you do it, they
pay you that and they pay you a tip. No.
Yes, they do pay you it. They pay you
the full amount.
Now, you're going to laugh at this. Look
at these views, bro. [ __ ] me.
I don't do it anymore so I can tell people.
One sec. Oh, here we go. Greasy, you ready?
Oh, yeah. Here we go. Here we go. That's literally
so many piggies.
So many piggies.
I just want to show you this is where I
met my box.
Look at the views.
That's where my mommy
went behind that bridge. Funny enough,
right? Went away on that bridge. Yeah. Good time.
My mommy had just got off of it.
My mama bridge.
Not bridge. It's an eye. The [ __ ] am I
talking about? I think the location is
in last Saturday. Last Saturday.
Yeah, good things.
I just wanted to show you.
I never Oh,
yeah. I just never ever just uploaded
them, but I've done videos of it.
Look at that view, man. Here you go. That view.
There you go.
Made 100 pound. It was [ __ ] long,
bro. You don't know the amount of area that was
It's probably somewhere that
look at that. But didn't um LJ say I
couldn't do that? Hold on a minute.
Didn't LJ say I couldn't do that?
He's a projector, bro. He's a [ __ ]
projector. All remember he said I
couldn't do that?
He said to me, bro, he said he said I
can't deliver to people's houses.
Yeah, he's a projector.
He's a self projector, bro. The only one that's scratched.
Oh, here's one. Here's one. Here's one.
The delivery here. But today it seems
like I'm doing North London. Done all
South London the past two days. Do you
know what I was thinking? Yeah. So,
guys, it's a good one.
Something else. And it just reminded me
of LT. I was like, what if I'm
delivering food to L? And that was his
name all along.
Why is there so many hills and bloody
computes and houses and angels? I
thought imagine it was London Taylor cuz
it was his area, isn't it? This is North
London, but I'm going to have to go back
to central London now. Else I'm not
going to get any uh
I'm not going to get
It's cute. Is it Grezy?
That's the thing. It sends you out and
then when you're out, you have to go
back into central London.
That's why I don't stay into central
London, but I wasn't getting an order. So,
back to central we go.
I thought I could deliver.
Oh, that self projector, bro. Got another one.
One second. I should have one here. One sec.
Here we go.
Okay. So, I know I forgot to record it
last time, but here is where I had this
one night stand back in there and castle.
Yeah, it kept sending me there. It was
trying to haunt me.
Just reminiscing, you know, bicycles here.
Loads of apartments.
I used to hate the apartments, but I
used to hate him. But sometimes it take
you 10 minutes to find one. Yeah, man.
That was a nice one. Yeah.
Some more on this main phone, too. Yeah,
it was good, bro. It was good.
Show video of Thailand. Nah, mate.
That's on my main channel. Bye-bye.
Yeah, Greasy, bro. Do you want me to put
the um videos up on the main
little videos? Do you like the way I met
my mama? They kept taking me to that location, bro.
Yeah. I called that [ __ ] the other day.
I said, "Go suck your mom."
I told her to go suck her mother. Yeah,
I used to come back some days as black as suit.
Yeah, I done a lot of different areas,
bro. I done Angel. I done Hammersmith. I
done Camden. I done Elephant and Castle.
I done Waterloop. I done Cora. Oh, mate.
I've done a whole of [ __ ] London,
bro. Must have been that week.
Yeah, it's cute, isn't it? The little
bicycle. I was going to run somebody
over with the bicycle. music
With the bicycle. Yeah,
I'm going to run him over with my big bicycle.
Hey, that bicycle is not to be [ __ ] with, bro.
That bicycle will [ __ ] KO you, bro.
It will you
Why does it do that? You silly little sausage.
Oh, do you like that, Grimzy? Silly little sausage. Yeah,
nice little bicycle. Keeping people's bellies full.
You just show and wake up. Stop talking about yourself.
Oh [ __ ] One second. Somebody just messaged me.
Yeah, but all all all jokes aside, yeah,
we are actually [ __ ] now. Like we've
had our laughs and stuff, greasy, but we
are actually [ __ ] I've not drunk in
about a month.
Don't feel better for it. I've not drunk
in about a month. I ain't gone out in
Obviously, I already in the country for
two weeks before that. Don't know when I
have time for myself again, mate.
I have so much stress, bro. I just
I'm going to knock
cuz Scalport used to always tell me
there's only up for now. But I'm telling
you, bro, there's only down for now.
There's only down.
Believe that, bro. See, like if if the
police took your phone or something or
you got your phone stolen and it's a
blip. You know, two weeks, 3 weeks,
you'll be fine again.
But in some situations,
as they say in America, you're damn bad
and you're [ __ ] There's no being
positive. Like, if there weren't any
grasses on here, um I'd tell everyone
everything. You know what I'm saying?
But yeah, know you're [ __ ] pretty
much. And also, you can't keep positive
because you've been doing this for three
years with this women's stuff as well,
which is another again, it's only 15% of
it. You've been up and down the country.
You used to go out three times a week.
You shouldn't be in this position, bro.
You shouldn't be dealing with this [ __ ]
alone. You should be dealing with this
[ __ ] with someone, but you're still
dealing with this problem. And people
are still telling you that you're going
to meet someone in in how long then? How
long? This the next time someone says
this to me, oh, you're going to meet
someone. How many more years? Because
this has been going on for over three
years. Let's just say for argument sake
over three years. So I'm going to sit
there and say how long left now? Cuz
we're we're basically almost finished
our prime now, you know, in a couple of
years, you know? So like how how long
now? How long left? When we're 50, when
we're 60 or like how long? Like
ask yourself the question, bro.
Going to be in financial difficulty soon as well.
So you got all of that problem, all of
that on top of the whole women thing and
the whole shitty people thing. It's depressing.
It really really is depressing, bro.
You know, I wish I could actually laugh
at it, bro. It'd be funny, but I can't
even laugh at it.
I will be out drinking tomorrow and
showing money. No, I won't. Hold on.
What's this? I'll be out tomorrow
showing money. Why would I be showing
you money? I don't show you little
Mongo's money anymore. I'm not involved
in your weird stupid drama, bro. Like,
you already pissed me off last week to
the point where I done that video to
that Smokeoky Bee who like all it is
with these people and Grezy is they just
want a reaction because their lives are
[ __ ] They're not willing to meet
anyone. They're not willing to say
anything to anyone's face. All they're
trying to do is gather information and
just annoy people. Like, that's all they
are. I'm not throwing no [ __ ] money,
bro. Are you mad? [ __ ]
Yeah, it's UC day, bro. I could go into
my savings right now and withdraw a load of money.
What does that mean? You've been shown
money a million times. The [ __ ]
And it's not really Yeah.
To go out right now and show more money
than that. Why does it bother people?
People show money, bro. I've showed
thousands and thousands and thousands.
And it got me thinking as well, like I
keep saying, bro, when I used to go out
and have all that money like spent,
disposable money to spend, just seeing those
um the the bars, the clubs, and how you
did not meet anyone in them years. Sad,
sad, sad, sad, sad.
Bye-bye. Go self-reflecting on another
channel. Like I said, information and
trying to wind people up. You're not
getting my attention. Go away. Um yeah.
Yeah. So, all is all you people do on
here is is talk about money every day.
And the maddest thing is none of them
have got money. I'm not talking about
you grievy. I don't know what you have.
You don't seem to bother people on here.
But they all go on about money and none
of them have money. They just call each
other what they are themselves.
So yeah, but since we're talking about
the money, it was making me think, was
it yesterday? It was yesterday as well.
I I was sat I was sat by the door here
by the front door and I'm thinking [ __ ]
just that guy when he said that this is
my first time in Manchester.
Um and then he's like 3 years older than
me and I've been like I've been
Manchester 10 times. I only ever went to
these places for one reason. Well, I did
like to travel as well, which I don't
take back the bad the the traveling. You
know, the traveling was good. The good
experiences were good, but at the same
time, you have to be human and think
like realistically, you should have met
someone by now with amount of people
that you used to approach and stuff. You
should not be in this situation.
Even though the times were good, like
the traveling times and whatever, like
we had loads and loads of money spent,
it's good. No one's saying it's not
good, but you really should have met
someone because you cried more than
anyone in the world. And I don't think
anyone's ever going to understand that.
So, cuz they they don't understand.
So, there's no point even trying to make
them understand because they they don't
understand. You understand?
4 years. We had free money. You had all
the time in the world. What do you think
we done when we had free time and free
money? What do you do when you've got
free time and free money?
So, you do a lot of things. You know
what I'm saying? So,
but that's again that's not the main
thing. That's just 15% of it,
which is how people get a mental
breakdown because things become too much
for people, I assume.
And then have to deal with people.
Oh yeah, bro. One second.
but I don't know what could even go me
up with the Uber thing because I'm not
doing anything illegal. You can earn a
certain amount of money every week.
You know, you're allowed to earn a
certain amount. So, I don't even do it
anymore. If I still done it, I wouldn't
be telling anyone. It's just cuz I don't
do it anymore.
And that's what any of you people need
to do. You don't tell anyone anything on
here. Don't forget these people are
people in their late 30s, 40s, they
ain't got a life. You know, same people
every day projecting. This is literally
their life. So they will do anything to
try to ruin other people's lives. You know,
people wouldn't like to be in my
position right now, mate.
But you don't see me [ __ ] taking out
other people, do you?
like they're just sad little losers that
just want to ruin other people's lives
cuz they're that's why I don't get
involved with this [ __ ] no more, bro.
With these sad people on here, I don't
entertain them. I just come on talk
about life and the reality and
just how we're completely [ __ ] basically and so yeah
not for me but I was I was dead if I
didn't have I'd probably kill myself. I
ain't talking about I'm not like I'm not
trying to make people feel sorry for me and no. Oh man. So Yeah, bro.
No, I'm not lucky. I'd rather die, bro.
I'd rather drop dead.
Know what I'm saying? Bro, it's only
down from now. Don't believe Scout Phil,
bro. He's a [ __ ] man.
You know what I'm saying? But but yeah,
nothing's going to change. Like,
you know what I mean?
Like like nothing's going to change. The
women thing is not going to change in
this country before we leave again,
Grezy, cuz it's been going on for 3 years.
Um, and all of the other things where
people just make life so difficult.
Nothing's ever ever ever ever going to change. Yeah. [Music]
Yeah. But they're not they're not all of
it. It's not that's not the whole
problem though, is it? It's like 15 20%
of it. I'd say it's about 15 20%. No
more than 20%.
But anyone would feel the same to be
honest. Any like I said, bro, anyone
would have just killed someone by now or
killed himself. You know what I'm saying, bro?
It's like what Eminem said, how can you
think positive when all you see is negative?
Don't judge someone unless you walk with
their shoe. Like that's it, bro. So,
it's sad, bro.
No one cares. I just I stated about 10
times, I'm not interested in the weirdos
on this community, this weird drama, and
you trying to get my attention. I'm not
a part of what you weirdos do. Did I
understand? Like, Cory, I'm not
interested in these weirdos. Like, I
come on here once a once a week maximum
because they're weird. They never leave
people alone. They never stop. These
people will never ever ever stop.
You know what I'm saying, bro? They have
like some sort of jealousy, obsession. I
don't know what they have. They will
never ever ever stop. Never stop, bro.
This is another thing. They've been
doing this for years as well. They're
just [ __ ] fat, ugly people that ain't
They're just low lives. Just just just
put it bluntly. They're low lives in it.
You know what I'm saying? Like, you know
what I'm saying, bro? So, they're not
even worth entertaining. like they they
they they pissed me off last week, bro.
Um that Friday and I asked this guy to
show me where he was numerous times and
I would have met him. But there's no
point. They're all [ __ ] houses, bro.
Like no matter how much these people try
to wind you up, just think of it.
They're never going to meet anyone.
They're sat on their [ __ ] keyboard
all day running up their [ __ ] mouths
cuz their lives are [ __ ] They know
where people have lived for years. They
ain't done nothing. Just ignore them.
They can't take one day off of YouTube.
So, it doesn't look good, does it?
That's weird. How can you not take one
day off of you? One day off of YouTube.
I only use I only use this for like
therapy sessions kind of.
So, yeah, I'm [ __ ]
Yeah, it's all the same. It's the same
people every day.
Yeah, it's the same spastics every day, lad.
I need to find ways to make more money.
I need to find I'm [ __ ] bro. And I've
got all of that stuff on top of it. I
don't know how I done it for them three, four years.
But I'm just waiting to die to be honest.
There's no going up from now, bro. Ain't
no going up.
There's no going up.
Trust me, bro.
It is sad. It's depressing, bro.
Like I said, I'm very surprised I've not
had a mental breakdown.
Very, very surprised. You might think
it's funny, bro, but it's not funny, brother.
But what is really going on in these
people's lives where they have to start
on random people on the street. That's
why I started calling these people on
YouTube London cyclists. I said, "Stop
being a London cyclist.
Stop being a London cyclist.
Stop being a London cyclist."
That's what I say to them. You want me
to do a little video, Greavves? I'm
going to do a video at some point, bro,
talking about this country when I'm
ready. But I'm going to go to the field
and you're going to see the scenery and
I'm going to do a little video. Would
you look forward to that, boss?
Would you look forward to that?
Would you look forward to that, boss?
I do think that's what actually happens.
I think people I don't think it's one
thing or two things or three things. I think it's
I think it's multiple things that add up
that people just can't take them while
they have a mental breakdown. I don't
think it's one or two things. I think
it's numerous things. Yeah. It would
just be a video about this country. I
post on this channel and my main
channel. Well, my main channel no one knows about.
I'm talking about the escorts, the whole
people, the whole like the whole
people's attitude and [ __ ] Like
I done about 10 videos on it, but I just
didn't upload any to be honest. Like
what I said something. So yeah,
cuz it got to a point where it's like I
just just I just like when I go out now
in this country, it's just to go out for
a drink and enjoy myself, but I'm going
to be struggling to even do that now. So
do you think if I went out again,
Greasy, and I got a boyfriend, I'd start
boning and complaining about it? Nah,
cuz you expect it now, is it? It's
nothing to complain about. It's been
going on for years, mate. It's a broken record.
It's a broken record. It's not even
anything to complain about. It's just
how it will always be in this country. You know
how they expect people to work and deal
with all of this as well is insane. Richie,
do you want my opinion, Cory?
You like You like the little police
story, didn't you, Grezy? Where I was
looking at him like, "What the fuck?"
Do you want my opinion, Cory?
They're all [ __ ]
That's what they are. Yeah.
Yeah. Cuz I couldn't believe what he was
asking. He said, "Oh, you walked to
them. What? 16 minutes away? Did you
like me on my little bicycle, Grezy?
My little bicycle. My little bicycle.
It's cute, isn't it? My little bicycle.
But like I said, I only tell these
people cuz I don't do it anymore. And
obviously I didn't earn over the about.
But when I when I get into something
proper, I'm not telling anyone anything
cuz they're fit for information. Then
they will start grassing cuz they can't
get you no other way cuz they're
cowards. Like I was just like done it a
few times, not doing it again. So yeah.
Yeah. Greed. He's like, "Oh, can't the
customer meet you?" I said, "Well, no,
cuz they're 60 minutes away." What the
[ __ ] You know, the [ __ ] roads were chocker.
The roads were chocker block.
The roads were chocker block. I'm going
to upload a video on my channel. Yeah.
So you can see the video properly. The
roads were [ __ ] cha. Yeah,
it was cho block.
The roads were [ __ ] cha block.
I was trying to I went back to find my
mama Grezy, but she was nowhere to be seen.
He was nowhere to be seen. Yeah. Oh,
that for my mama.
I don't need to do anything. C.
Okay with you, K.
I play with you c. I agree with you.
What do you think about the one of my
friends? Yeah. That went to work and
called you supervisor come by accident.
I was dead mate. And his supervisor said
what did you say?
I was thinking about that. I was dead.
He said what did you cuz he just said it
cuz he's so used to me saying it in it. He said
and he was like what? He's like, "And
the supervisor said, "What? What did she tell me?
I'm going to get him in trouble with
it." Yeah. And he's like, "Oh, it was
just a slip of the tongue." And he said,
"You don't you need to watch watch your tongue."
Thank you, D. [Laughter]
Do you ever do you ever read Rainbow?
You used to say it, bro. Imagine that,
Burger. Imagine that at work. I just was
just imagining it because it's You can't
even say it's just the funnel because
you don't call someone a [ __ ] You know
what I'm saying?
You don't just call someone a [ __ ]
Anyways, I'll be back later. Maybe
I'm going to put some videos up.