Yeah, bro.
I had to speak to somebody. body. Body.
Yeah, you have to laugh at it, bro. You
have to laugh at some of this [ __ ]
Really got to laugh at it, bro. It
You know what? You just seeing that
guy's face here and you just laughing in it. Yeah,
we are [ __ ] up.
[ __ ] hell. Is this Virgin still at
this? This is why I have to stop for a
little bit, bro. Oh, [ __ ]
This is why I have to stop for a little bit, bro.
If they can do this like continuously, bro,
how they can do this continuously coming
on and annoying people every day,
they must live really sad lives, bro.
Really sad lives. I was talking to
someone about to end the live stream. Um,
they're mentally and phys they're
mentally obsessed, isn't it?
They sent a letter, bro. I'm not talking
about it anymore. One sec.
But it is a shitty situation, won't it? Yeah.
Got someone coming around in a bit. Get
some money for that as well. So, yeah.
Right. All of it's worse. No, no, no. I
tell you what's worse. Do you know you
know the worst thing is that you've
traveled around this country, right,
time and time and time again and you
still don't have anyone. Plus the whole
money side of it as well. It's [ __ ]
up, bro. And this whole you should be
with this bro. You should be with this
USA is he you should be with this [ __ ] right now.
I could tell you so many so many so many
bad stories, bro.
So many so many bad stories, bro.
It's [ __ ] up, bro.
But you wouldn't be spending £400 anyways
cuz you kind of calm that lifestyle
down, you know. But yeah, still [ __ ]
yeah, but you know, you wouldn't
but it just made you thinking in four
years, three or four years, you know,
you should have found someone by now.
You need to leave this country again,
bro. That's you know what the only thing
you you you can do is what Antman's
done. Like think of thinking of it now,
bro. This is the only thing you can do.
You go to Thailand and you teach
English. Like generally that's the only
solution. Now you're [ __ ] here. You're
[ __ ] here with money. And to be honest
with you, even if you have even if you
still get loads of money, you're still
going to be in the same position. You
don't have nothing left to prove. It's
the only way out now, man. So, if you're,
you know, like you can't book one way
tickets and stuff, but
but yeah, no one made me lose anything.
That skint virgin, that Orton [ __ ]
virgin rat face might have been
reporting, but they've got no they've
got no they were on to me before this
whole YouTube going live. That [ __ ]
creepy little virgin lanky [ __ ] didn't
[ __ ] cause anything. But yeah. Yeah.
No, you won't be skin. No, you won't be
You really won't be skinned, but you
you're just not going to. It's just
another problem that you didn't need.
But yeah, you are going, but yeah,
you're going backwards. That's exactly
what you're doing.
You won't be skinned. You'll never be
skinned like that, Virgin, as well.
You won't be skinned. you'll just be um
you're not going to struggle
financially, but it's just a thing that
we didn't need.
Look, I got banned on Reddit again.
But generally, that is like your only solution now.
You was losing your last.
Yeah, the day is horrible, bro. I didn't
have problems with him.
women as well. No, I have a big problem.
And the only most annoying thing is the
amount I've tried in this country too.
The amount I've obviously tried in this
country and you've been not rewarded for
it or anything. It's like,
yeah, it's [ __ ] up.
I don't have anyone to support me
either. Like a partner. See, my sister's
got like a partner and [ __ ] I don't
really have anyone. So,
yeah, you're very strong for going
through all of that and not having a
mental breakdown. See, some people have
mental breakdowns just from moving house. Um,
you know what I mean? So,
yeah, at least you'll never be skin like
that virgin. But the only reason I said
about Uber Eats is cuz I don't do it
anymore. Uh, Nicola, otherwise I would
have told anyone. Obviously, I don't
tell my business. Too many grasses on
here. But when I do ever get into
something again, then
obviously I will be telling people. So,
uh, I won't be telling people. Sorry. My
bad. Lose my [ __ ] mind, is it?
I'm losing my [ __ ] mind there, bro.
Yeah, I don't have anything.
Oh, this woman from America messaged me.
Why is he messaging me? What the [ __ ]
Well, that was USA. Is he then the [ __ ]
This is going to be the comeback where
somebody finally meets me and actually
gives me money.
And I said to this transgender woman, I
said, "Um, we're [ __ ] Like, I'd
rather I'd rather um trade places with
you now." You said that you've got a lot
going on. Try being in my shoes. Yeah.
No, I know you're not joking. I know
you're not joking. I know you're not
Maybe she's in London.
Yeah, there's no way to make money anymore. Yeah.
It is sad, isn't it?
I'm surprised I wasn't able to make
money from YouTube, but even that would
have come to an end. You know, there was
people making 40 3040,000 a month on
YouTube. They're not making that anymore, you know.
But that virgin is still obsessed with
me. This is one of the reasons I don't
come on here anymore, Nicolola, is
because of the obsession and the
weirdness. I come on here once like in a
blue moon. But
I bet a lady would hate to be me now. E Yeah. Uh, bro.
Why is she message me? That is weird.
I remember this person from America as well.
How about USA? Is he um apologizes now?
Nah, that never happened, isn't it?
That would never happen.
Let me try this. Yeah.
See, the um the Uber Eats was good, bro,
cuz you could spend you can make money.
You can make back what you spent.
You can make back what you spent, if
that makes sense.
So, when you spend money, you can make
it back. Does that make sense?
Um money. Yeah. you can make back what
you basically spent. So,
it was something better than nothing.
You know what I mean?
But I don't know why that virgin thinks
he's got money when he literally has no
money. He's actually skinned as [ __ ]
But I got money. I can show you money, bro. But
there's no point showing these people
money cuz they never show you nothing.
Do I mean Nicolo?
Know what I mean?
Didn't want to come.
You know what I mean? But
see, imagine it was your only income.
then you would literally be [ __ ]
Like you would literally be fat. It
wouldn't even be a joke. Like say you
got £300 a month. Obviously a fat £1,100
a month ain't good, but you still have
savings. Imagine you had no savings and
you was on £300 a month and say that was
like your only income. You'd be [ __ ] bro.
You would be [ __ ]
I don't know how these people can do
this for years. Like Red Star and all
that. How these losers can do this for
years. You know what I mean, Nicolola?
How these losers can sit on YouTube for
years doing this?
It's mad to me.
They're [ __ ] losers.
They're actually [ __ ] losers, and it proper losers.
They are proper losers.
Losers, losers, losers, losers, losers. No. Yep.
But you'll meet someone, so to say.
So they say,
but you'll meet someone. So they say,
so they say. Yeah.
That's what they say, bro.
M I think everyone's taking a piss. Cuz
it's not like you've lost some of your
income. You've lost most of your income.
That's the [ __ ] up thing about it is
you've actually lost
you've actually lost most of your income. [Music]
Know what I'm saying? You've not lost
most of your you've not lost like £500
or like£600. You've lost most of it. So
it doesn't affect them.
Let me check my emails.
The [ __ ] is the phone?
No, I won't get a proper job. Are you
mad? [ __ ] that.
I'll just have to live off what I get. Simple
proper job. Are you mad after dealing
with people? You're [ __ ] mad if you
think I'll ever work again. I will never
Having to deal with [ __ ] stupid
You mad? That Uber thing was enough and
it made me really start hating people.
Could you imagine being told what to do?
I'm lucky I didn't break. One of them
people are lucky I didn't run him over
that day. Like I told you that day I'd
work. Yeah. Well, it will be good luck.
That's basically what you're living off.
Once you pay your rent, you're basically
living off 1k a month. So, I don't know
what you're talking about. By the time
you've paid your outgoings, you're
basically living off a grand a month.
So, yeah, it won't be good luck, bro,
cuz I'll find other ways to make money.
So, I hate people. The Uber made me hate
people. I never hated people before. I
only hated women. I didn't hate people. But now
I hate I hate women. Sorry. I hate
people. And that was just Uber.
Yeah, but what are you left with?
But what are you left with though every
month? That's the million dollar
question. What are you left with?
You're talking about you, bro.
You can live off one 1.1 1.2K a month.
Like, stop being a fantasist. Please
You don't even live in London. So, yeah.
Anyways, I'm not comparing how much you
get, how much I get. The thing is, bro,
I hate people. So, why would I want to
work when I hate people?
You know, like it really made me start
hating people the job. I didn't hate the
work. I didn't hate the customers. I
just hated the people I share the road
with. No, no, no.
I'll always rise. No, I won't, mate. I'm [ __ ]
I won't rise nothing, man. I'm [ __ ]
I'm on the same money as that skin
virgin now. I don't know why people
think he's got money. He's got no money.
Every time I play the money game with
that [ __ ] nons, he's always ran away.
Yeah, but he he acts like he's got money
and he literally has nothing. I think he
took out his whole housing benefit once.
Yeah, he goes on like he's got money and
he's literally got nothing.
Trying to say that he showed 14 grand
before. [ __ ] hell.
for messaging me.
You do not get 4K a month off the rent.
Stop talking [ __ ]
No, you don't. Maybe between you both.
Maybe between you both, but not one.
You do not get 4K a month off the rent
or just one income, bro. Stop talking [ __ ]
No, I'm not loaded, mate.
Me [ __ ] loaded. Are you mad?
I just got from savings.
Yeah. So, you're left with two grand basically.
Trust me, you would live on 1.1k a month
if you had no rent.
Stop being a fantasist.
I'm going to have to live with it.
But yeah, I won't be on here again after
today, bro, because it's okay for the
first day and then it just gets weird.
You know, Virgin Boys obsession, Red
Star. It becomes very weird and
obsessive and I don't like to waste
attention on these sad low lives. So
yeah, it was only I come on today cuz
yeah, just thought I'd just Yeah,
I use this as like therapy sessions.
But guess what, bro? No matter what I
said today, I'll never be like red
stolen virgin boy. Nothing to live for.
No money. Yeah, I might get less money
now. But yeah,
I live in a bedit, mate. I live in a
five- bedroomedroom house. What the [ __ ]
are you talking about? I've never lived
on in a bedit in my life. I'll never be
like them sados. I'll never be like a
[ __ ] 40 eold on [ __ ] £300 a month
that I'm going after today, bro, for a
week, two weeks. I can't I don't The
whole thing This is pointless. I use
this for therapy sessions, bro. I don't
get involved with a weird drama. These
people start, you argue, they um you try
to meet them, then they don't meet you.
What's the point of it all, bro? They're
[ __ ] low lives. Well, I'm not going
to sit here and argue with low lives.
Right, that's it.
It's just the whole thing is just weird
to me. This whole community is weird.
But I come on to speak to the decent
people like Grezy and So yeah,
I would rather be dead to be honest.
But I don't care if I die. Listen, bro.
I keep telling you I wouldn't care if I
now you know I've got you know
I've traveled a little bit and I live my life so
it's only down from now anyways so I
wouldn't really care if I for example
died bro so yeah
I don't want people to feel sorry for me either
no I got Xbox and I've got a new TV as well
which come with me. It's going to be
very stressful to move all of that. But um
we'll do it somehow. Yeah.
Anyways, moving on.
I'm not going to talk about this no more. So, yeah.
No, no, no, no. the 29th.
Call that month.
Yeah, bro. Timothy.
I can't stand the people on here. You
don't see me on it, mother.
You don't see me on here, bro.
Yeah, like my only thing that was really
stopping me doing myself in and [ __ ] was
probably the house and the income to be fair.
And now that's gone. Well, it's going to
be gone. So
yeah, I can't think of a way out to be honest.
It took me ages to sleep yesterday, bro. Hello, Grezy. So yeah,
no racist on my channel, bro.
Yeah, it's not cool.
It's not cool, bro. So yeah,
don't know, man. I'll find somewhere.
I mean, it was going to end anyways, you
know. I still got savings, but the whole
point of it is you should have met
someone by now.
You know, you did do well. You did
travel and stuff, but like
it's more of a case of like you should
um you should be in a relationship now.
You should be dealing with this with someone else.
Nah, I won't do that to lady.
I just leave her alone. Old people want peace.
I wouldn't want to do that. So,
I don't want to be a burden. You know
what I mean?
Maybe maybe I'll just [ __ ] the bounces
up and go prison. Maybe
you might as well be in prison at this
point. You got nothing to lose.
It's holidays blues that I've lost
basically 80% of my income. And I'm
losing my house. Yeah. Yeah. That's
holiday blues, bro.
That's not anything else.
Holiday blues. No.
Yeah. So, like anyways, what was I
saying is in them years, you should have
met someone and anyone you go to, you're
just going to be um
basically like a burden and [ __ ] So,
So really I can't think of a worse
position to be in bro
you call I can't bro
I've got money and it doesn't matter if
you if you stack money because savings
go it doesn't matter if you stacked
money you didn't stack money savings are
always going to go and I've already got
money and I wasn't stupid cuz again I'll
repeat myself I was making money on the Uber
So yeah, I did stack money. I've got
stacked money. But that doesn't mean
anything because any money is going to go. So
it doesn't matter. Even if you had 10
grand, 10 grand's going to go. If the
money ain't coming in, the money ain't
coming in. Which was the whole point of the Uber, obviously.
But it is what it is, bro.
It is what it is.
You think if you stacked money, what
what the money is going to last forever. So,
I did see it coming, which is why I was
prepared for it.
It's all right. Anyways, it's not a problem. Uh,
it doesn't work like that, Henry. It
does not work like that. I'm not going
to get into it anyways. I've said what I
needed to do. I've said what I needed to
say. And it does not work like that. You
can't just find somewhere, right? Put a
deposit and then they stop paying your
rent. It's not as easy as that. You know
how things work in London. So yeah,
they use bat in Thailand. Yeah.
Oh, has he? That's good for him, bro.
Yeah, that's good for him. One's already sold anyways.
Yeah, that's good for him, bro.
Good for that little virgin. No one cares.
was already told. Probably that [ __ ]
No, I didn't get as much money back
then. I didn't get as much money back
to be honest.
Oh yeah, they're bad. Cuz I can't take
it with me. Yeah, I'm selling it cuz I
can't take it with me.
I'm not I'm not selling my stuff. I'm
selling my washing machine because I
can't take it with me. I'm not sending
my TV or my Xbox. I'm sending my washing
machine because I can't take it with me.
And obviously the boxing bag I can't
take with me. And the fridge. I'm going
to get a fridge. I've got everything
somewhere else. I'm not selling my TV or
my Xbox. No way. That's mine, bro. So yeah,
it's cuz I can't take it with me. But
the TV and Xbox is mine, bro.
Saying that, but I can't take the thing
with me. So, we're only sending things I
literally can't take with me. So,
get money for that. That virgin's still
obsessed. And this is exactly why I
don't come on here anymore.
Yeah, I'm moving, bro. Yeah, bro. I just
Yeah, I'm getting kicked. Oh, I didn't
tell you, Ghosting.
Yeah, I lost the [ __ ] house and Uber
account and [ __ ] so I'm basically
[ __ ] So, I have to sell the stuff I
can't take with me, basically.
Yeah, bro. So, basically the whole story
is is basically lost the house, lost the
income in the house, and then lost the
eBay account. So, I'm basically [ __ ]
Like, I've got like £1,100 a month now. So,
basically, suicide seems the only way
out to be honest. Delayed.
Yeah. Which obviously explains what I'm
saying, but it did. So,
So yeah, bro.
Nope. They're not taking on any new riders.
They're not taking on any new riders, so no.
Well, there is no other way, bro.
There is no other way. Unless this
person that's just messaged me is going
to take me under their wing and take me
to America and give me money.
No, they're not taking on drivers, bro.
No, I wasn't on No, I was on like £700 a month.
I was on like £700 a month. I didn't have savings.
[ __ ] virgin. This is why I don't come
on here anymore ghosting lad. Like when
you don't see me on here for a week, two
weeks, 3 weeks, it's the jealousy and
the stalking. I I can't deal with it,
bro. It's too weird for me. It creeps me
out. It's why you don't This why you do
not see me on here anymore. And they
never stop. And the thing is, ghosting,
they never leave you alone. They never
ever ever ever stop. And it's like a
place where you're getting involved with
weird drama. And it's so weird. Like
this is why you don't see me on here no
more. The last time I was on here, I
lost my [ __ ] temper and I was [ __ ]
calling people out. Like it's just
weirdness and jealousy on here. It's
weird. And they've been doing it for
years. This whole jealousy towards me.
And that's why I just leave. That's why
I can't be bothered with it. It's why
you don't see me on here.
Anyways, I'm coming back, bro. No, I
don't gamble anymore. One second. I'm
coming back, bro. I just need to do
something. Give me about 10 minutes, lad.
10 minutes. Give me about 10 minutes, bro.
One second, bro. I'll come back. I just
need to do something.
Yeah. One second. I'll come back on in a
bit, bro. I'm just doing something. One sec.