Yo yo your um
messages to be
better start answering your [ __ ]
message is 50. Oh, [ __ ]
>> Yeah, sorry. I had to talk something out
there. One second. Is this virgin still
stalking me? Let me go. Let me Let me see.
There's going to be more stuff for the
police. Get the [ __ ] in there.
Let me see.
Virgin's not really saying that much cuz
he knows better. [ __ ] virgin.
I was about to say, mate,
calls for the [ __ ] police report, matey.
That calls for another police report, matey.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I had to sell that [ __ ] Some [ __ ] was
trying to give me 150 for my telly. I
was like, "No way. That's not for sale,
mate. We're not all skin like the Orington virgin."
Let me go on my mail. Um
he's done that one with that person. What's that? Let's
leave it around
pretty much [ __ ] evens, bro. Is it?
Yeah. [ __ ] hell, bro.
Got these little weirdo stalkers
messaging me. They got nothing better to do.
rest of the night. Oh. Remember
the Lo number for various different
reasons. just being a [ __ ] [ __ ] mate.
Um, that's why
don't count them dates too be no
these people on YouTube really are.
Oh, I'm completely [ __ ] That's what's
happening. I'm completely completely [ __ ]
Oh, I don't even know where to stop, bro.
Talking about yourselves as well. So,
yeah, waiting for you, Joe. So, to cut a
long story short, basically lost the
house, going to lose the income from the
house. Still got money and savings and
stuff. Someone just bought something and
my Uber account got banned. So yeah,
I'll be living on a whooping 1.1,000 a
month now. Yay. I just had to sell some
last things like the wash machine cuz
I'm moving and stuff. So yeah, basically
suicides on the cards cuz I ain't giving
off that [ __ ] money. And yeah, I had a
long story with the Uber thing as well.
And bro, there's so much to discuss and
like it's madness. But um
yeah, bro. very um
very uh yeah
no more mate. But I still got savings,
bro. You people don't even get 1k a month.
Um like I'm not talking about you. I'm
talking about you people on like £300 a month, bro.
Um, the reason it didn't work out is cuz of um
is because of uh
this Pakistan girl messaged me. So, hey,
how are you doing? I'm Sam down bad.
That's what in in America they start
calling people down bad, bro. That's
what you call yourself. You call
yourself [ __ ] down bad. Basically, um
cuz they kept um blocking um the roads
off. cuz they kept blocking the roads
I couldn't deliver the food.
Um, I'm sorry I'm disappearing without
telling you. I'm struggling as well.
There's a few problems. Sorry, bro.
Doesn't matter how many savings I've
got, but I've got savings.
Doesn't matter how much I've got, but
I've got enough. But anyways, Joe. So,
uh, they kept blocking off the roads.
Um, they kept blocking off the road, so
I had to cancel some of the deliveries.
They blocked the whole road and they
done it more than once. So I couldn't
deliver the food in central London. So
then I got a strike. Then I got another
strike and they closed the account down.
You never guess though what Joe one of
uh the police officer I said, "Oh, I
need to deliver food to the customer. I
need to deliver food to the customer."
And he's like, "You can't get through
the road. You always you always uh you
can't get through the road." And I said, "Um
um you can't get through the road." And
he says, I said, "I need to deliver food
to the customer." And he's like, "Oh,
well, can't you walk there?" And I
looked at him. I was like, "Are you
taking a piss?" But I gave him like a
look. I was like, "Bro, are you all
right?" I feel like some people are just
being stupid intentionally. Then he's
like, "Oh, can the customer meet you?" I
said, "Well, consider they ordered
food." No, they can't. Um, but I tell
you what the job did do. It was good
job. Good, flexible job. They made me
really start hating people. Um, not the
customers, like the road rage. Um, it
really made me start really hating
people. A hate for them that I never had
before, cuz I didn't really deal with a
lot of people. I only dealt with women.
I never dealt with like public. And it
made me really, really, really start
hating people. Um, I went in one Sunday.
Yeah, I think it was the last time I
done it. Um, I went Sunday and um,
basically what happened was um, I said
if anyone pisses me off today, I'm just
going to run them over with this bike.
Like, I'm literally going to run them
over with this [ __ ] bike, bro. I'm
not even joking. So, it started
affecting your mental health because you
realize what people actually like in
this country making sly comments. Um,
yeah, I've had these women message me now. Um,
too late now. You know what I'm saying,
bro? But yeah. Yeah. It really made me start um
started hating people. It really made me
start hating people,
but I didn't really care about the
house. I did care about the house. No,
no, no. Let me put it this way. I cared
about the house, but I didn't like the
responsibility that came with the house.
I didn't like the responsibility that um
came with the house. Um
it was really bad, you know, like um so
I'd rather just do the Uber and just
earn 150 a week, 200 a week is enough
for me. I've done the whole going out
spending hundreds. It never got you
anywhere. You know what I'm saying? With
these women and stuff. I was happy with
that. Having no responsibilities, making
a bit of extra money, but now that's
[ __ ] I'm basically [ __ ] now. So
yeah, it's actually suicide.
So, um, yeah, it's either that or
suicide, bro. Like, [ __ ] I'm the only
thing I could do now is just go to
Thailand and do what Antman's done
doing, cuz it was depressing enough in
this country when you didn't even need
to worry about money. Now you got to
worry about money. Think of it now, bro.
Nah, this is not a hurdle. This is I'm
completely [ __ ] This is not a hurdle.
I am completely [ __ ] And then with
the Uber thing, it got to a point where
I couldn't go to the gym. Um because I
didn't have time for the gym. But now I
have all the time in the world world now
cuz I'm not working. But the house was
all right cuz I saw it coming. I saw it
coming. I prepared myself. I was
working. It was all right losing that.
It wasn't all right losing the house,
but it was I had something else to do.
Now I have nothing to fall back on. So
I'm [ __ ] basically. So you're not
[ __ ] You still have over a grand to
live live on a month and you got
savings. But um I don't think people
understand the severity of it. It's not
a hurdle. Like I'm [ __ ]
I'm literally [ __ ] So like there's no
hurdles. Like you're [ __ ] You just
have to get used to living off that
money that you get. Simple.
Um there's no way around it, you know?
So that's it. No point stressing over
it. It is what it is. I was telling my
mom and my sister and they didn't really
seem to understand the severity of it.
They're like, "Oh, don't panic." And I
was like, "Mate, I've lost a house. Two
forms of income and you're telling me to not panic?"
Just imagine it was your only income.
You who would have really been [ __ ] then?
Um, you would have really, really been [ __ ] then. So,
but the Uber thing was all right. I
didn't mind making £80,50 a day or
whatever it was. I had nothing better to do. So, but
yeah, cuz all the high life always comes
to an end. Like even with the Uber, I
was going to live a high high life, but
I would have lived just a normal life.
The whole plan was to work and then
spend the money on the night out cuz I
just wanted to go out and drink. I ain't
drunk for a month. and gambled for ages,
bro. You wouldn't even believe it.
I could understand if I was [ __ ]
because of gambling, then I'd say, "Oh,
it's your fault." But you're not. You're
not [ __ ] from gambling. You're [ __ ]
because of this this [ __ ] shitty situation. But
then I lose the independency as well.
So, you lose a lot of [ __ ] with it,
mate. It's 1.1K without rent. It's
without rent. It's a It's without any outgoings.
Again, you're thinking of your income
and your outgoings. When I mean 1.1K,
that's all mine.
So, it's enough to eat and live on.
Again, you're thinking of it from paying
rent. People on benefits don't pay rent.
I don't know how many times I have to
say this, but well, it is what it is
anyways. What can you do?
>> What what it is, bro.
>> I was already a normal working person in
society. But yeah, it really made me
start hating people. Anyways, Joe, you
like you you'd ride on a bike and you'd
get these women making sly comments or
these people um um writing sly comments
and stuff like you'll get these people
writing, you know, saying sly comments
and bro it really does affect you because
there's no discipline in this country
which is why they're [ __ ]
So yeah. Yeah, it's enough to live on.
But but that's that's the problem I was
dealing with with the Uber. It made me
really it start it made me start hating
people. Like it made me start hating public transport, you know.
Bro, listen. I'm talking no rent. I have no outgoings. Yeah.
So, when I'm talking about £1,100 a
month, there's no rent. There's no
nothing obviously because I won't be
able to afford to pay it. So,
no, you just have that all to yourself.
So, you just don't go out for a month.
I'm not going out for a month anyways. I
need to move. So, one month you'll be
kind of back to normal. Hopefully, you
would have found something by then. So,
they make slight comments like, um, oh,
sorry, bro. She was like, yeah, um,
she was like, oh, um, you can't be
there. I said, I'll go where I want. And
then she started running her mouth. I
parked the bike. I said, "Come back and
say that to my face." I said, "Come back
and say that to my face. See what
happens to you." Part the bike and everything. So, um, yeah.
So, yeah, they don't know how to mind
their own [ __ ] business in London.
But yeah, it's not fair.
And it's not like it's a hurdle either.
It's not like it's it's a hurdle.
And I think the worst part is is no one
gives a [ __ ] They don't care. They
think, "Oh, it's just a hurdle. This is
not a hurdle, mate. This is not a
hurdle." You know how how often do
people move house? Think of this. People
probably move house like every 10 years.
It's not a hurdle, mate. It ain't a hurdle.
You're You are basically basically [ __ ] Um,
when Joe went, I was just going to tell
Joe something, but he left anyways.
So, yeah, I wouldn't be able to pay
rent. Wouldn't be able to my mom rent
anything. I'll only have like the gym,
which I've already paid for, and phone
bill, which I've already paid for. So, yeah.
I'll just be back to normal life. But I
was back to normal life. I was [ __ ]
working. So, you know what I mean?
no. And I don't want her to, to be honest.
It's not her problem.
It's not her problem, bro. No, I'll find
some. I'm going to find some anyways. So, like,
nope. And if I was going to do anything
like that, I would never tell anyone. I
don't tell people my business until it's
over. The only time I tell people my
business is when it's over, bro. Because Yeah.
I was getting some deep conversations
about it today with people.
So yeah, um
I won't be going out for a month
anyways. I'll just hit the gym and then
just go out next month or something
unless someone wants to meet me.
But I don't really have
I don't want to go into my savings, you
know what I mean? So,
no, we're not talking about that stuff anyways.
The old bill can't do anything. It's a civil matter.
But yeah, bro, like say I get a job next
week. Uh, Harry. Um. Oh, yeah. Harry,
keep getting you confused with J. I
wouldn't tell anyone.
I'd never tell anyone. No, never tell anyone, bro.
I only tell people cuz like it was over
and [ __ ] So, I wouldn't have told
anyone. If I still had the Uber Eats,
what I was going to do is I was going to
come back in like a couple of weeks and
it would have fizzled out.
Anyways, we're not talking about that
grass and [ __ ] bro. We don't want it on my channel. Um, so yeah.
So yeah, bro,
I love piggies too much.
But um yeah, like I would have just
waited and obviously the idea would have
fizzled out. You know what I mean, Jay?
Um Harry, it would have just fizzled
out. The whole thing would have just
fizzled out. Does that make sense? So
nobody would have known anything. Um
obviously, but obviously cuz they buy my account. So yeah,
you know, with the U, like I keep
saying, with the Uber thing ain't bad,
bro, because you could have still made
like 1.5, 1.8. You know, you don't need
to keep living the high life. You've
been there, done it, worn the t-shirt.
You just need to save more and think
about getting back out of this country.
You know, you weren't miss you're not
missing. You've done it, been there,
worn the t-shirt. You had savings. It
weren't bad. But you can't even do that.
I just have to hit the gym now. I've
already paid for it. So, at least I've
got that in it.
I don't want a job, bro. I don't want to
be someone's [ __ ] That's the whole
point. I don't want to be someone's [ __ ]
Now, he doesn't do it anymore. And if
all fails here, then you need to go to
Thailand and do what he's doing. That's
literally the only thing you can do now.
I'm sorry to be a repeater, but that's
like the only thing you can actually do now.
So, yeah, you'd have to go there. All
you need is a oneway ticket. You pay 1
120 for the course. You know what I mean? So, yeah.
Don't stay in this frustrating [ __ ]
country, you know? It's no life for
anyone, bro. This this depressing
country with the [ __ ] in it.
[ __ ] that can't mind their own business.
You know what I'm saying? [Music]
Working ain't a life, mate. Working is
[ __ ] Being someone's [ __ ] is [ __ ] And
you don't spend more than 1K a month. So
stop stop trying to
mate. Listen, you earn nothing. You go
to work and you be a [ __ ] and you're
left with 2K at the end of it. What What
is your life, bro? Think about it. Most
your life you're going to look back and
you worked. You know what I mean? What a
[ __ ] life is that working.
That's a [ __ ] life working, mate. At
least in 2 months you'll basically have
two grand. If you save for now, just the
money you get, you have like two grand.
Beats [ __ ] working and being someone's [ __ ]
And that was a good thing with [ __ ]
Uber is that you could do it when you
wanted. No one could tell you anything.
And you were just basically a cyclist.
You know what I mean?
Don't worry about me, mate. I'll get by
one way or another.
But then at the same time, I did like
doing something greasy,
you know? I didn't like being lazy like
these people. I did like kind of going
to work, but I didn't go every day cuz
some days you couldn't do the next day.
You would be too [ __ ]
Yeah. Good for you, bro. I can go on
holiday when I want and I don't want a car.
So, we're all in different parts of our life.
So, I stopped the Uber cuz they banned my account.
So, what are you going to do for extra
money, Greasy? You'll be [ __ ] now, is it?
Yeah, you'll be [ __ ] now, Greasy, won't you?
You'll be [ __ ] in terms of extra
money, won't you?
You know, you'll be [ __ ] now.
But what are you going to do for extra
money? You're [ __ ] Everyone's [ __ ]
I think there's no point trying to look
for ways. You either go to Thailand and
do what he's doing. Um
or you you basically just have to be on
benefits. There's nothing else.
You say 4 500 a month.
Yeah. I won't be going out for a month
anyways unless one of these women want
to meet obviously.
See that Italian one still replies back
and the other one's still nice. I don't
know why that USA Izzy was such a [ __ ]
I don't know why she was such a [ __ ] but
yeah. See, the plan was you do Uber two
times a week and it pays for your night
out. That was the whole point of it.
That was literally the whole point of
it. You know, we didn't need loads and
loads and loads of [ __ ] money. You
know what I mean?
But it is bad.
It's all right.
Oh, it's a long story, bro.
So, how long did you say, Greavves, it
would take you to save up to go to America?
If you don't Uber, you could probably do
it about 2 months without it. Probably 6
months, as an example.
Well, not really. You just do food
shopping and you just don't go out.
Nothing else you can do, is it?
Firstly, I'm not homeless. And secondly,
I've got savings. Does anybody on this
community have savings? No, they don't. So,
and yes, I slagged Virgin Boy by for
being on a grand a month. And guess
what? I'm still technically on a more
than a grand a month. Actually, I'm
technically on more than a grand a month
for a couple of months, actually.
Yeah, actually, I actually am.
actually am, you know. Yeah, I actually
am, you know,
but I was glad to do them things in 3
years. It was fun.
But again, the only bad thing was is
obviously you didn't meet anyone, which
you should have met someone. You should
have met the love of your life. You know
what I'm saying? You should have met the
[ __ ] love of your life. I should have.
That's the only disappointing thing.
Doesn't matter where I'm getting these
savings. Mind your own business. So yeah.
Yeah. Simple as that, bro.
No, I won't be. Yeah, but I'll have
somewhere to go. That's the difference. So,
it don't matter, bro.
I love somewhere, bro. Don't worry. So,
that's why I'm selling out the washing
machine. I'm not selling my TV. [ __ ]
guy tried to offer me 150 for my TV. I
said, "No way, bro.
It would have made sense to sell the TV
and then just get another one next month
when I'm sorted. But no, I'm not selling
my TV or my Xbox. The washing machine. I
had to sell the boxing bag. I have to
sell cuz I can't take it with me and
some other things. But I'm not selling
my [ __ ] TV, bro.
I won't have anything now. But Franklin,
it's all right, bro. Just go to the gym
for a month and just don't go out for a month.
You should have £1,600 in one account. So um yeah,
can't believe I heard you say Izzy's
voice again. It was so nice. Hello.
Yeah, don't waste your time, Greasy,
trying to think of ways to um It'll be
back to the pork chop days, eh? It will
be back to the pork chop days. E, Zippy.
Yeah, it'll be back to the [ __ ] pork
chop [ __ ] days.
You know them uh pork chop days where
you [ __ ] where you [ __ ] skin. No,
I'm joking, bro. It will never get that
bad. It will never be that bad, bro.
I'll never be that damn bad, believe you me.
But it's just a bit [ __ ] obviously
losing the thing and it
No, no, no.
So yeah, you just adjust any money you
get, you just adjust to it.
But I didn't expect I think the whole
thing that annoyed me was the Uber thing
more because the two Cuz the TV because
the TV you expect it to go like the TV
you expect on the TV the house you
expect but you don't expect when you're
actually working for them to actually
ban your account. It won't go quick in
London bro. I don't have no outgoings
except the gym and I've already paid it. So
yeah I won't be able to eat out every
day. I'll just adjust. You just adjust.
Yeah. And the thing is no one cares. No one understands.
No one cares. No one understands.
So I think that's the worst thing. But
yeah, I won't eat out every day. But you
just get used to it, don't you, bro? You
just adjust. You're on more money than
you was before. So I'll just adjust,
bro. I'll just hit the gym hard and I'll
adjust to it, bro. Don't worry.
No problem. I got the gym as well, so
it's all right, bro.
It's not a problem, bro. I just hit the gym hard.
Month is nothing. So,
there we go.
It is bad, isn't it? It's bad to be down bad.
It's bad to be down bad. E
do hate being down bad. No, I'm not
going to be homeless.
I won't be homeless, bro. Yeah.
No, it won't be a good chunk of money,
mate. You can eat very cheaply. And
don't worry about me, bro. Don't worry
about me. You're working. You've got all
this money. Don't worry about me.
You won't b You won't pay for your food
daily. You'll do a weekly food shop,
obviously. But anyways, don't you worry
about me, bro.
Worry about your own life. You've got
all this money. You got a nice job, nice
car. You don't need to worry about me, bro.
Worry about your um worry about your own
life, mister. I have everything. You
don't need to worry about me, bro.
No, you won't be that you won't be that
damn bad, bro.
I was stable to do it, you idiot. And
the whole point is I'm not going to do
any other jobs cuz working is [ __ ]
Working is [ __ ] So it's not going to be
a chunk of my money cuz I've already paid it.
But I have a fridge somewhere else. I'll
just do a I'll just do a weekly food shop, bro.
I'll just adjust for the month. It's all
right, bro. Trust me, I'll be all right.
Yeah, I don't have much life experience.
Okay, bro. You keep telling yourself
that. I live by myself. I've traveled by
myself. Yeah, bro. I don't have no life experience.
Somebody with the name of Henry on
YouTube told me I don't have no life experience. But
do you know what? The women [ __ ] wasn't
bothering me when I was working. I
didn't give a [ __ ] about them. I still
don't give a [ __ ] about them.
Yeah. So, you just learn to adjust squeezy.
It's not There's nothing else you can do.
So, and I paid for the gym. I got that
for a whole month. So,
you know what I'm saying, bro? What it is.
So, yeah. But yeah, I ain't got no life
experience coming from you
or a month. So if you save that in a
month, that's like 1,500. Yeah.
Yeah. It will just be that way in it. I
won't be depressed cuz obviously I've
got the gym.
Hopefully some things I've applied for replies back.
You don't want to be down bad.
Remember that down bad, Greezy.
But if the worst comes to worse and I
can't live with it, then I'm just going
to have to do what Ant-Man's doing
cuz we know it worked for him, so it has
to work for me.
I remember an ad man applied for Moss.
Yeah. She said, "I really want you, but
you don't want me." She suck my dick good, bro.
Well, I'm not really [ __ ] I'm just
going to not get as much money. So, I'm
actually not really [ __ ] But,
bro, they closed my account because I
had to cancel some deliveries. I order
them because they block the road.
Yeah, that one that said I really want
you. She sucked my dick.
Yeah, I've got no bill. I've got two
bills that amount to like 40 quid.
Yeah, it amounts to like 40 quid. A few bills. So,
but yeah, you're going to have to do
what he does.
You got nothing to lose. cuz he was
saying to me like if you're truly like
suicidal and [ __ ] that's a way out like
you know it works.
So he said that obviously
you have to do that you know it works
I can't remember bro
okay Henry bro whatever you say buddy
bro you don't know about London you
don't live in London how are you telling
me about my city you don't even have any
money you're just a fake account what
the [ __ ] would you know about London you
don't have no money you don't know about London
So, what the [ __ ] would you know
anyways? And I can't remember, bro. She
just stuck my dick in there. Anyway,
that's all I remember. Um,
stop being a fantasist. You remember
when Bob like these people are so far
from life experiences, they have no
idea. Like, do you remember when Bomb
used to say, "Oh, I spend two grand on
the night out. I spend two grand on a
night out." Oh, you don't [ __ ] spend
100 grand. You fantasist. Shut the [ __ ]
up. And then you had somebody earlier
say £250. No, you [ __ ] do not, mate.
You know what? I only spent £250 once on
a night out without gambling.
They're such fantasists that they've got
no life experience cuz they don't even
leave the house. You remember the the
lies bomb used to come out with?
Who grounded a night out? [ __ ] off,
mate. The most I ever spent was £700.
I did spend £700 on um before. [ __ ]
hell, I don't think I even had that much
money then at all. Um yeah,
I done it two times. Yeah.
I'm surprised that Italian messes back all normally.
Yeah, that I wonder what that USA is problem was
cuz that is not normal, bro. Even if you
legitimately done something wrong, that
is not normal.
Must had mental problems.
must have had [ __ ] mental problems.
But I'm all right, Grebies. I've got my
TV. I've got my Xbox. Got my two phones.
So, it's just going to be the gym and
Franklin now, ain't it? It's just going
to be the gym in Franklin. So, yeah. Um,
so yeah, man.
You can kiss goodbye to them barbecues,
lad. You can absolutely abs fuckingutely
kiss goodbye to him, bro. You greasy,
you better kiss goodbye to him.
Yeah, you can kiss goodbye to them barbecues, mate.
But to be honest, you had a good three
years. Restaurants, escorts, traveling.
You had it. You had you had your peak
life easy, which no one else did.
But then it's still, but then at the
same time, it's [ __ ] up. You still
never met anyone as well. So that that
is [ __ ] up. We know what it's like
here, but it is [ __ ] up. You should
have easily had relationships with
amount of [ __ ] I used to do. But
like you should have at least had
um some [ __ ]
I'm probably going to eat some pork
chops tomorrow to be honest. But yeah,
you should have had like
relationships and stuff or even more one night stands.
I never used to do them every week and I
could do them every week. I could still
do them every week if I wanted to.
I could sure do want to.
And don't forget we got the football
starting soon. So start making the money
on the football. But yeah, but yeah,
pretty [ __ ] eh? I know some guy. He
gets £300 a month and he's he's depressed.
But like I keep saying, it's not about
the house. It's about the fact that
there's no other way to make money. What
do you think? You were just going to
have the house forever. Nah, bro. We expected that.
You know, we expected that, mate. But we
It's [ __ ] up that there's no other way
to really make money. That's the
ultimate [ __ ] up thing.
Well, legal ways anyways. There's
There's illegal ways, but there's no
legal ways, which they're
which is what they try to prevent, which
is weird to be honest.
I just have to become a shoplifter, man.
Obviously, bro. What the [ __ ] Obviously.
Yeah, obviously. Where the [ __ ] Oh my.
It's pretty [ __ ] All right. Well,
that's the that that is annoying. And I
said to my mom, "Do you think it's more
like depression or frustration,
but it's probably frustrating to be honest.
There'll be no way to change your
financial situation now."
Obviously, there'll be no way to change
your financial situation now. So, Obviously,
that's the that's the problem, is it?
>> [ __ ] hell, bro.
Is that what they do now with the facial recognition?
Yeah, he used to shoplift all the time,
right? Used to make some good money shoplifting.
You're down bad now.
You're [ __ ] down bad.
You're down bad.
[ __ ] I'm [ __ ] bad, bro. Oh, [ __ ] Nah,
you probably adjust to her in like two weeks.
You adjust to it, bro. Easy.
No, I used to get like 700 lb when I was
like think but I remember I was always skint
like nons legs when I used to meet Izzy
and that but that was different bro. But
I did you do you adjust to it
but you need to not put pressure on
yourself at the same time. There's no
point in trying to put pressure on yourself
cuz of there's no other ways to make
money. So there's no point trying to
think of other ways.
We was kind of like eating in and we was
actually eating in anyways, wasn't we?
We actually eating food in anyways.
But yeah, you don't need to think of
other ways. There is no other way.
Unless you shoplift, I'll sell shell your ass.
You remember when nods legs were showing
these little [ __ ] bub chains? Bro, I
can go into my savings right now and
show a load of money. I will never show
these people anything ever again.
There's no point. They never show you anything. any money.
But it is what it is, bro.
Yeah. The woman was like, "What's going
on? I'll just have to sell about the
Uber and it