Yeah, man. Let's talk about these low
lives on the YouTuber.
the car girl from the YouTuber Don't. Yeah, bro.
myself a nice cl
I need I need a [ __ ] gym tomorrow bro
that red store big fat ugly [ __ ]
ain't got a life Yeah, man. of YouTube
getting [ __ ] up. Oh, [ __ ]
I love how these people sit on benefits
all day and they try to call other people.
They call other people skin, but there's
some benefits all day.
I think I was kind of exaggerating to be honest earlier
to be honest with Hello. Oh, [ __ ]
Come out too long.
[ __ ] it up.
Where that sugar is? Need that sugar bait.
the island basket on YouTube.
I won't be doing it again, bro.
I won't be doing it again with these little weasels.
They literally live.
They literally live to obsess
live to obsess over people's lives.
It's a madness, bro.
ain't got nothing in my but you
know I don't understand I want this
community from Timmy why is there so
many spastics on this community
but so many spastics
to be honest.
I'm so obsessed with other people's lives. So weird.
They're so obsessed with other people's lives. creepy community.
I mean, the whole thing is like creepy.
This whole community is creepy.
They call people skin, but they're the
ones that start on YouTube every day.
They can't get off it.
They talk about what
I think these people would love to be
young again, but they're not. They're
fat and ugly. They're like I think
they're like London cyclists, but just on YouTube.
But they are cyclists, but they're just on YouTube. Yeah.
London Spy on YouTube.
What building is more?
Too many weirdos ain't got a lot. Yeah. God is
I got things to do. So
yeah, bro thing is how you call me, bro.
Listen. Yeah, you got to think about this, bro.
It all just come a bit of a shock to me, bro. Like, bro,
got designer clothes. I still got more
money than these people. Nice new TV,
Xbox. These people for nothing.
Think about nothing in their lives. That's why
they want you to bro. [ __ ]
It felt weird. But you just adjust. You
adjust to any money you get, bro.
You adjust to any money you get.
Trust me, bro.
No, I don't speak to him. Cuz think of it, Cory.
Did you watch that video? I owned all of
them, bro. Think of it, bro. They've got
all this money. Yeah. Everyone's skimp,
but they're sat on YouTube every day.
You know what I mean?
I'm not going out for a month anyways. So yeah,
I don't know, bro. I don't watch Saga.
Yeah, they're [ __ ] weirdos, bro. It's
the truth. They're sados. Bad pricks.
And like I said, Richie, I'm never I
only told these people these things
because I had already done them.
The guy said, "I'm scared for selling a
a fridge and a washing machine. It's
called moving house." So when somebody
moves house, they can't take things with them.
I was even thinking of selling the TV in
the Xbox cuz I can't take it with me.
But I'm not I'm not selling none of that.
But I was thinking because obviously
when I was moving and stuff, but no, I
had to sell some things because I
couldn't I couldn't um take it with me. So So
yeah, bro. Got a brand new telly, got an
Xbox. So I'm all good, bro.
I stopped going out for 6 weeks before,
didn't I? So I can't go out cuz I've got
things to do.
So, just hit the gym, get a good body,
and then [ __ ] Yeah. Yeah, bro.
Yeah, just go to gym. Save some money,
bro. It's It is what it is.
I'm going gym. Um
cuz I'm not going out for a month. Like
I said, I've got some feelings to sort out.
Not cuz I'm scared. Obviously, I can go
out whenever I want. But yeah,
you know. So, yeah. But they're so in a
people's lives. Like, trust me, when I
get a job again, no one's knowing
anything. They only knew cuz I told them
because I lost it. So,
but you can just tell, bro. They're just
basement dwellers. like that red store,
that smoky bean. They're just basement
dwellers. They're just sad, fat, ugly
people that wish they were young again.
They wish they were young like us. So yeah,
it'll be good, bro. It'll be good in the end.
Tim has never seen a gym in his life.
Never, bro. Never.
It's a shock at first, but you just
adjust the money that you get it. camera
stuff more than these people.
Little Jay's never seen the gym in his
life either. Fat [ __ ]
again. He's got all this money, but he's
sat on YouTube every day.
Doesn't add up, does it?
Doesn't add up for these people. They
got all this money, but they can't get off YouTube.
It makes you wonder, doesn't it? All
this money, all this life, but they're
on YouTube every day.
You know, if I ever see Timmy again, I
think I'm going to slap him up for
getting me on this community.
Or should I slap my sister's boyfriend
up? Cuz he's the one that got me into
gambling, which I don't gamble anymore, but
he's the one that got me into gambling. But um
and obviously with the gambling I found
this channel. So yeah,
yeah, I'll do some gaming streams. Yeah,
go gym hard in it. Just go to the gym
hardcore, bro. It
save up a bit money for more money for a
month. They'll start going out again.
Hope the good.
Oh, [ __ ] me.
How the rapping going, Cory? How's the
rapping going, bro?
How's the rapping going?
Yeah, so easy to own the freaks.
Yeah, I'm sitting my washing machine and
my fridge cuz I'm moving house.
Yo, at the end of the day, call me.
Like, I can actually get out a load of
[ __ ] bro. Money. But there's no point
with these little weirdos cuz they they
just self-reflect. So there's no point.
They just self-reflect their own lives.
But there's no there's no point even
like arguing with them and [ __ ]
Yeah. Nice, bro.
These freaks are so easy to own.
This guy's got a whole channel dedicated
to me cuz I live in his head. Imagine
that. Sat on YouTube stalking. That's
what Pat Mustard used to do, bro.
It wouldn't surprise me if that account
is Pat Mustard. You know that? Sit
online stalking men all day. Imagine
that. Imagine who's actually behind that account.
And the thing is, bro, is they try to
call you ugly. They try to make you
insecure, but they're the ones that
don't show their face.
>> They're the ones that don't show their faces.
Um, that red store account, bro.
All he's got in his life is stalk him. I
must have used to do that as well.
Yeah, you know that, bro. If they're if
they're doing this every day, stalking
you and [ __ ] you just know that you owe
them. You just know that they're jealous
of you, bro. Cuz they wouldn't do it if they wasn't.
I I should be a psych um psychologist. I
know these things.
Think of it, bro.
Think of it. That virgin in Kent, the
Orington virgin, right?
I know I'm better than him. I know I've
got more money than him. I'm better
looking than him. I've got a better life
than him. I've had a better life than
him. So, what do I do, bro? I don't
waste my time. I don't stalk the virgin.
I don't make videos. That's the right way around.
You know, that's the right way around, bro.
So, people that do that, they either
want to [ __ ] you, be you, or there's
something that they're jealous of.
There's nothing else it can come to.
Think of it, bro. A life in it.
You know what I'm saying, bro? So,
yeah. You sell a [ __ ] washing machine
and you sell a fridge when you move
house, you [ __ ]
I didn't even buy that fridge anyway. So,
I got somebody for the washing machine.
Think someone's going to buy the fridge
as well. But
yeah, someone's got to buy the fridge as
well, I take it. So yeah.
Yeah, I hate these people.
My mom jokes about like sometimes mom
tells me about these people in this
community and she doesn't understand if
I ever find one of them or find where
one of one of them lives I will kick the
[ __ ] out of them bro I will kick the
[ __ ] out of them whether it's red star
smokey be I don't think she understands
like how much I hate them
I was begging LJ like pay for half my
flights I pay for half your flights I
will [ __ ] you up bro I'll kidnap you
I'll put you in the back of a [ __ ]
boot it's not a
But I said to him, "Stick to um bullying
retards cuz that's all you can do." Oh,
I come to your house. I come to your
house. Bro, you come to my house about
100 years ago and guess what? You done
nothing. You had several chances to kick
the door in my face and you done nothing.
Like realistically, you done nothing and
you had the chance to do something.
Like you need to understand, bro. Yeah,
this is 100 years ago. It's time for a
new update. You got all of these people
that you speak to. Some of them must
live in London. Come again.
It's not like you done anything and I
ran away from you. Just nothing
happened. You had a chance to do
something. You didn't do anything.
You know, that's it. You know, time for
round two now. Stop living in the past.
You know what I'm saying? But you'll
never come again because you know you'd
get [ __ ] up.
I hate that LJ, bro. I hate all of them
on here except like Grezy and a few other people.
I hate them, bro. I really do hate them.
I don't think you understand this. Why
I'm not on here. I hate them, bro. If I
ever find out where one of them are, I
will [ __ ] them up, bro. I'm joking.
I really do hate him, bro.
And if that go was on here, I started
here again. He come on my door when I
was 21. Well, I wasn't even in. Huh? I
remember that time. That go
when I was 21, bro.
Wow. Congratulations. You know what I mean?
Yeah, hopefully he is.
it's a madness, isn't it? That red,
that red star will never meet me, bro.
That redstone will never meet me ever.
He will never meet me, bro. He will
never meet me.
What do you think of me doing the Uber thing?
He kept taking me to USA Izzy's um place.
What do you think of that, Cory?
I'm a mad [ __ ] You know, LJ is just
jealous that he can't do it. His anxiety
won't allow it. His weight won't allow it. Yeah. Oh, Krie,
there's a good thing about the job
though, Richie. The good thing about the
job is you're self-employed and you can
do when you want. That's the only good
thing about it. I [ __ ] my hand up on the bike.
But I don't mind it me. I mean, you can
you can earn £200, go on a night out,
save. It's it's not bad, you know?
It's a self-employed job. That's the
That's the good thing about it. Like so
you can do it when you want.
But this is what I I understand with
these people here. They tell people to
get a job. When people get a job, they
tell them, "Oh, you're earning [ __ ]
money or no no
when these people are sat, you know,
these people are sat on benefits."
So it's like they tell you to get a job
and I only told them I got it cuz I had
lost it. Otherwise, I would never tell
them. I got something going on right
now. I'm not telling these grasses. I'm
not telling these grasses nothing.
They can't even snitch me to anyone,
bro. The benefits I wasn't earning over
what I was supposed to. So, there's
nothing they can [ __ ] me over with.
You think I would tell these grasses
anything, bro, if I was still doing it? You're mad.
A normal community could you could say
when you're going, where you're going,
what you're doing, but not discussing community. But
you know what I'm saying, bro? Like
he needs to get himself a little job.
Lonely virgin boy Richie. He needs to
get himself a little job.
But I tell you why it's good, bro. The
Uber thing. Yeah. Cuz you can work like
seven days in a month. Yeah. And the
rest you can just go to the gym, enjoy
your life. That's the good thing about it, bro.
That's the good thing about it. Say six,
seven days a week. Yeah.
And then you just go to like you can
just do it when you want. It's good, bro.
I didn't mind it. Me, all the people was
nice. Everyone I met was nice. I just didn't like
um the people I shared the road with. I
don't know how it was like where you
was, but it binded me. There was days I
couldn't do it cuz my back was [ __ ] But
still the best job you can have, I
think, as a second income. Cuz that's
what it is. It's a second income. It's
not a first income. It's a second
income. Which is what people forget,
Cory. They think, "Oh, it's a first
income. It's not a first income." Cuz
you never know how much you're going to
earn with it. One day you could earn
£100, the next day you could earn 20 pound.
It's not a
main income, which is what people forget.
It's a second one or a third one.
Like say you made money off YouTube or
say you got benefits or
I don't know say you made money from
say you was a landlord or whatever. Some
some job where you wasn't working and
you needed a little bit extra money.
That's what that's for. It's not for
anything else. You can't live off it.
It's not to live off it. You understand? So
I worked [ __ ] 8 hours to get £55,
but other days I'd make 100. So
it was better than nothing.
And I saved quite a lot. So yeah,
you could get me best I could do.
Yeah, I think I kind of overreacted a
little bit, but everything just came at once.
It's pretty pretty stressful leaving
losing the house and [ __ ] Uh
to June 4 month budget for month but I'm
back to square one again.
We'll be good bro.
Don't miss the responsibility.
You know you're not missing anything cuz
you done it
done it all before.
And also every year you don't go out
January, February anyway. So you stay
for about 8 weeks anyways.
So you would save like two grand anyways.
Not too bad money
exaggerated a bit more, you know.
is what it is, bro. Yeah.
on the Olympics for laser be.
Oh, I said the boxing bag I can't take
with me either.
I don't need the money for any of them
things, but I can't take it with me. So,
what am I going to do? Just leave it.
You're obsessed with other people's lives, bro.
Obsessed with other people's lives.
Wherever I go, we have a washing machine. So, yeah, man.
Like I said, it's not like you've not
had it. It's not like you ain't had you
ain't lived the life for 3 years.
Is what it is.
You basically need to leave the country again anyways.
Not like a [ __ ] virgin boy.
Not by a virgin boy. You know what I mean?
And then even dealing with people that
when you were trying to
um sell some of the things, the maddest
[ __ ] they'd come out with.
The maddest things they' come out with.
So they asked about the TV. They
thought, "Oh, you have a TV?" And cuz I
had a TV. I was like, "Yeah, how much?"
And then they were like, Um,
[ __ ] what did they say? 6 600
150. I'm not [ __ ] accepting 150 for a
[ __ ] £500 TV. You mad
that with me, but it's my TV, so I need you.
Yeah, Bonnie, if you're watching this,
bro, you need to stay off this [ __ ]
Stay off this self-reflecting community.
You already know, bro. It's full of
nothing but self-reflectors. Yeah. Hello.
Hello, mate. Oh, [ __ ]
What's up? Nothing, bro. Just chilling.
And the same as I got will pay for a
holiday as well. So, you're not in the
worst position. But
yeah, all comes at once and it
just life in it. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm all right, bro. I'm just
chilling. Chilling in the kitchen. Have
a bit of tea. Yeah, man.
Yeah. I got late. I had to do a few
things. I was playing GTA.
Yeah. Sold the washing machine. Now I
need to sell the fridge. Hopefully can
sell the boxing bag since I can't take
any of the things with me.
And then I'll just buy a new box and
bag. But I will have a fridge anyway. So yeah,
people think I'm skinn because I'm
selling a fridge and a washing machine
because I'm moving house.
These people really are stupid, aren't they?
Long story. Lost a house. lost the
income from the house.
I was doing Uber, then lost that. So,
yeah, I had a lot of stretch recently, but
it was nice to have some people reply
back like they actually did care, you know.
But yeah, I just been dealing with a lot
of [ __ ] with
that's reality, bro. Not living a high
life anymore like I was for 3 years.
You wouldn't. It's been 3 years.
You know what I always said? I said, "As
long as I've got money, go back to um
America with the money, then I'd say I
had it made." Simple.
Cuz it doesn't matter how much savings
you got, the money is always going to go
in the end when you when you live off
it. But luckily, I did save some money. So,
have my own money. So, I'm good.
Everyone gets back to reality in the
end, in it.
Good. It is good.
3 years and it's [ __ ] around, bro. But
you know, you're older now. Yeah. Oh, man. Sitting there.
Not really, bro. Imagine in them three
years you had to work.
Imagine dealing with that with the women [ __ ]
You had to deal with women [ __ ] and then
you'd have to work.
Could you imagine? [ __ ] that, bro. [ __ ] that.
That would be horrible.
That would be horrible, bro.
That would be [ __ ]
Yeah, they're just not interested in
this country. Ollie,
I haven't been out in a month, man.
Ain't gambled for ages, ain't drunk for
ages. Just been I just went to the gym,
then done some work and [ __ ]
I basically adjusted to it anyway, so I
don't really care.
It is what it is. Yeah.
No, cuz I haven't been going out. I was
just doing the Uber thing. I don't I am
drunk for like a month.
I do fancy going on a session again. But
yeah, I've got too much things to do,
bro. Not even financially. I've got I
need to know where I'm going. Like
everything's just happening once.
I'll go for a good piss up.
I didn't spend anything, bro. Oh, don't know.
It's mad to think I tried for 3 years
though. Is it Ollie? I'm still single.
All that money, all them dates. It's
crazy, bro. All the dates, all the money
spent in that. Like,
you would have thought you would have
found someone by now. [ __ ]
It's impossible in this country, bro.
It's almost impossible to find someone
in this country here. Oh.
Oh, loads of dates. 200 I've spent before.
Used to go casino a lot on dates. So I
lived the life but
it just goes to show that it is
impossible in this country
like nowadays. every life. Well,
yeah, I paid £700 once on a date.
I think I've spent £700. I spent
but I had the money bro. So
you know I don't know how I would have
done it without this house
having to go out and keep trying and I
don't know how I would have done it.
You probably would have ended up with
like one of these incelss that never got laid.
I think I generally would have ended up
back one of them in cells that
that that never got laid. Bro, I didn't
have the house. Definitely, bro.
It was bad enough with the house.
At least I can look back on the [ __ ] memories. Um,
he still should have found someone. So, so yeah,
and it's not about them. I still have
money. I still have money to do all that [ __ ] But,
you know, there's memories to live back
on in it.
You get what I mean, is it?
Cuz even if I had all that money now, I
still wouldn't be doing it. I wouldn't
still be doing it. I'll be out of here, bro. Yeah.
And when I get one, I'm not going to tell anyone. Yeah.
I just have to live on a grand a month
until then. My boy be going out for a
month anyways, but
it's not going to make a difference cuz
I've been going for like 6 weeks. So,
it's just lucky you're getting in your
late 20s now when it happened.
The amount of women I [ __ ] I traveled.
So, had fun with it. So,
we all got savings as well.
It's bad because it all come out at once
and it's not you you're not used to
having to adjust but we still adjusted now. So
you just adjust. It could take like 3
days, it could take like a week,
whatever. But you always trust
all over England, Wales, Scotland, been abroad.
To be fair, you did live the life. So,
and obviously with that savings, I'll
just put that towards a holiday. So,
Bob's your uncle. I think that's as good
as you was going to get [Music]
because you imagine doing it all now.
Like the women [ __ ] I wouldn't do it
all again. I wouldn't never do it all
Even if I got six grand a month, I
wouldn't do it all again. I'd go out
once a week and that's it. That'd be me.
going out for a drink cuz I wouldn't go
out for a drink. I wouldn't even care, bro.
What the [ __ ]
Dust punk 60s. Nope.
Never in my life.
Well, you just adjust to anyone. Are you getting it?
It's just one of them.
It's just one of them, bro. Oh, [ __ ]
And there's some people, yeah, they'll
sit there with loads and loads of money
and they've got nothing to show with the
money that they they got,
the money that they have.
I mean, they have they have nothing to
show for it. Yeah.
Nothing to show for it, bro.
One second. Let me go back on that. Oh, really?
Really? Really? Really?
You're not like that [ __ ] virgin for
[ __ ] K, are you?
You're not that [ __ ] virgin. [ __ ] know
I think my thing
Bro, I'm glad I'll be back later tomorrow maybe. Denver.