Early
bird catches the [ __ ]
one. You know what? Yeah, I was thinking
of talking about these little bungos,
but I think I already bodied them them
enough last night.
Yeah, man. I actually bied them, bro.
They got [ __ ] in that video, bro.
Yeah, they literally got They literally
got [ __ ] in that video, bro. What's
the day today? It's Friday today.
Okay. Yeah, it's Friday.
Friday today. Friday today. Friday It's Friday.
But yeah, ain't no point, bro. I [ __ ]
bodied them yesterday.
You know what? I could throttle you.
literally throttle you Timothy for
getting me on this bastard community.
Can throttle you with one hand.
Why did you get me into this disabled
community to me?
[ __ ] you. Why did you get me into this disabled community?
[ __ ] it now.
Yeah, I'm free today.
Got nothing to do. I was going to try
and go to gym, but uh yeah.
But yeah, let's talk about these little
sados. How they sit on YouTube every day
stalking people, but they ate the skinned ones.
Like, bro, you know what? Like I always
used to say, yeah, is that their YouTube
activity proves what they are. Proves
they're fat. Prove they're ugly. prove
they got no money. You know what? Yeah.
I was going to say, yeah,
to RJ, if you swear in your kid's life,
if I show you money, you you you'll come
to London, then he would be proven that
I've got more money than all of them.
And he'd be a [ __ ] because you wouldn't
even come here. I mean, I was thinking
of doing that, you know, like this dude
on the video swearing on your kids'
life. Then you get showing money when
you won't be able to show anything and
you won't come here. So everyone's going
to know that you're a [ __ ] We say
everyone's going to know you're a [ __ ]
To be honest, that doesn't actually
that's not actually the truth, is it? Because um
I called that smoking me out last week.
I tried getting him to show where he was
and he pussied out and no one said
anything. So to be honest with you,
you're all biased to be honest.
Actually, you wouldn't even get [ __ ]
It'd be funny for me, but no one else.
All of his little gay little disabled
followers would just like back him up
anyways actually. So saying that, it
wouldn't even make any sense.
Yeah, remember that time I went for bomb
[ __ ] two times. No one even mentions
that. Yeah, what was I thinking?
Stupid. What the [ __ ] was I thinking? I
mean, you could you could literally this
community is so disabled that you could
literally, for example, go to
Birmingham, smack the [ __ ] out of Prime,
and then they'd all be like, "Nah, never
happened." Like literally, like even if
you would win, they would say that you
took an L. That's an example, you know?
Just use that as a just use that as an example.
[ __ ] all, bro. Just chilling.
Just talking about these little bongos.
So, like, yeah, there's actually no
point in asking LJ to swing his kids
life if I show money that he will come
to London because
um nobody would actually take your side
anyways cuz they're all biased.
Even if you take W's, in this community,
you take L's. So, uh yeah.
Yeah, Grezy, bro.
Apparently selling a fridge and a
washing machine when you're moving a
house means your skin. That's new to me.
E, I own them in that video, bro. They
got [ __ ] bodied. See, they're not
they're not so good at bullying people
when they don't talk over people, do
they? Cuz part is they just talk over
people. That's why people can't get a
word in. But when you realize they can't
when they realize they can't talk over
people, they lose. Understand, bro, these people.
I mean, like I say, look me over there.
I call that smoking me out. Someone
that's been on Hangouts ignored me. No
one said anything about it.
They're so pathetic, bro. It's that red
star as well. They're such little lowife
little virgins. I've never known
anything like it. They're obsessed with
other people's lives.
He's calling people's skin. He's the one
that was begging for drinks and Weather
Spoons. It took you 10 years to save up
to go to [ __ ] Vegas and you're
calling people's skin, bro. They're
really really just sados on here, bro. I
should even be on here today, but I
ain't got nothing to do today, bro.
Every day they people leave. I'm Yeah, I
can't take the stuff with me. I mean,
I'm taking the TV and the Xbox cuz I
want to play my little characters,
Reezy. You know, the little characters.
What? Well, I don't I can't take a wash
with me. They're going to give me one. So, yeah.
You think I'd sell the little
characters? Are you mad, Grezy?
No way. No way. Jose.
No way. Jose,
I can't believe these people do this for
years, though. Sit on YouTube obsessing.
I can't imagine being jealous of of
someone like that, bro. Why would you
want me to move up north?
I hate the whole country. I hate
everything about this country. It's not
a certain city. Even though London is the worst.
I bet you didn't believe the cyclist
stories I told you. Yeah, they were
really bad, bro. They really made me not want to.
Like I said, they made me hate. They
made me start hating people.
The women are better up there. No,
they're [ __ ] not, bro.
Westernized country. They're the same everywhere.
They're the same everywhere, bro.
It's all right. I'm just used I'm used to it.
I'm sat in front of the fan. We greasy.
Women are not better up there. They're
all the same, but they're the same
everywhere in the in in westernized
country. In westernized countries, they're westernized.
It's like Manchester. If you go to
Manchester, they're exactly the same in Manchester.
There wasn't like four years ago, but
they're exactly the same. You know,
every time I visit Manchester, which was
10 times Yeah.
It's like a It's like a It's like they
tried to be, how do I explain it? Like
they tried to be from London. They've
got the same attitude, yet it's smaller
and the transport is crapper.
But it's just a smaller London. That's
literally all Manchester is. So,
I don't know if I remember this quality, bro.
No. No. Cuz when I messaged a month and
a half ago, I said, "I'm going to go and
slap you up in front of your boyfriend
on a Thursday, Friday." She didn't
reply. I actually called her the other
day. Greasy. She picked up. Hello.
She was like, "Hello."
Yeah. I was like, "Hey, how you doing?"
[ __ ] I just slapped her up in front of
her [ __ ] boyfriend, bro.
Oh, just USA. Is he
Yeah, she took her Sim out.
She wanted problems, Grievy, but then
she played victim, didn't she? Typical way.
That's probably what a London cyclist
would do, to be honest. Start [ __ ] And
if you actually was to smash their face
and then start playing victim. Yeah,
they're the one that started it.
Just like that woman uh last with the
tattoos last couple of weeks ago.
She stop when she was started running
her mouth, bro. I lit cuz you know the
bike has a stand. So I pulled the stand
back and I said, "Come back and say that
to my face. Stop walking away." I would
have slapped her up in front of
everyone, bro. Who the [ __ ] are you
running your mouth to, bro? You're not
running your mouth to me. And she was
with a guy as well.
You doubt I ever smashed anything. Okay,
good for you, bro.
No, I just told her to suck her mom and I hop.
Yeah, you wouldn't like London, Grezy.
You wouldn't like London. You would You
wouldn't like London, bro. Trust me.
You can't even work in peace. So, you
would you wouldn't like London.
The people are horrible here.
I remember before when I went somewhere
I think I went into a door and this guy
was like he says don't go there and I
said I'll go where I [ __ ] want but we
were both drunk. They just like
they don't they can't mind their own
business. It's it's a sense of
entitlement. They think they can butt
into other people's business. Um, they
like who the [ __ ] do they think they
are? Like even making comments the way
they make comments about it's a sense of entitlement.
Yeah, I've been bullied. Okay, bye-bye.
Um, but they'll never finish it. It
doesn't matter how many there is. If
it's a man, if it's a woman, they'll
never finish it. Uh, Grezy,
they'll never ever finish it.
Don't talk about that on my channel. Um,
yeah, cuz I can't bring it with me.
Yes, for sale. Cuz I can't bring it with me.
Yeah, you'd hate it here, Grezy. You'd
hate it here.
I think you'd react the way I do as well.
They'll be the first ones to play
victim, though. They would be the first
ones to play victim. They've got the
same attitude as well. Like you go
everywhere, you gre you see the same
people with the same attitude.
Yeah, definitely hibernating, bro. I'll
definitely be hibernating. So
I'm moving. Yeah.
No, life's not that bad.
I mean, you could be like these people on YouTube.
Their lives are [ __ ]
Why on YouTube every day?
I'm I'm leaving the country again soon
anyway. So, it doesn't even bother me,
bro. I've got savings. Uh,
like I was saying yesterday, not to be
like a repeat or anything, but the
amount of times I tried and the amount
of money that I spent, you should kind
of have options. You should be with
someone, but there's no point in
thinking about that. You know, it's the
past and we know what they're like in
this country. So,
you know, it's not the worst um
position to be in. So, it is [ __ ] up.
It is. It is [ __ ] up. really really
and nothing. Joe, what what do you mean
I'm a sad man, bro? What? Because I'm
selling a few things cuz I'm moving and
I can't take it with me. Bro, the only
reason I'm not coming on here showing
money again is cuz none of you people
show money. You think I don't have
savings? You You think I don't have
money? You really are obsessed, bro,
with other people's lives. It's it's it's insane.
I was a bit pissed off, but I'm just
kind of adjusted to it now anyway. So
if I don't find anything in a month,
I'll have to leave the country. Lucky
lucky I've got the money to do it as well. So
it's all right, bro. No, I was just
saying to grieve you, Joe, how like in
them three years with all the money that
you went through and the dates and
stuff, how you're still how you're still
single. It's It's kind of [ __ ] up.
It is kind of It is kind of It is kind
of [ __ ] up, though.
is really bad.
But yeah, I start anyways.
It is really, really bad, bro.
Get to me. These people don't get to me,
bro. They get to themselves. These
losers don't get to anyone. They bully
themselves every day, lad. They don't.
They've never got to me.
Isn't that right, Joe? They're the ones
that are psychologically [ __ ] They
have to come on here doing what they do
without failure every day. These losers
don't get to me, bro. They're living
their worst life. You mad? These little
losers do not get to anyone, bro. They
get to themselves.
You know what I'm saying? [ __ ] hell, bro.
And the only reason I used to show money
is cuz I used to have money from the
casino in cash. I don't have cash. I
could withdraw money again and and and literally
just ruin you all again. You know what I'm saying?
But don't I only told you about the Uber
thing cuz I don't do it anymore. You do
realize when I do something again. I'm
not telling you. So I won't be telling
you for various different reasons. I
only said it cuz I don't do it anymore
in this situation
cuz I don't get you mongles anyways.
Like you tell people to work.
Uh you tell people to work even though
you don't work yourselves. And then when
people work, you then take the piss out
of how much money they make. Um
that they don't sell. Um and then they
and then so which one is it? Like I don't understand.
Yeah, I'm selling it because I need to
move. I'm not selling my TV or my Xbox
even though I did think about the TV and
then just buying it again. But yeah, one
guy when he got the when he bought the
washing machine, he said, "Oh, do you
have a TV?" I said, "Let's see how much
he will offer because I really want to
take on a cab." He said 150. I said, "Fuck off."
I'm not selling that for 150. Are you mad?
I told him I bought it for £500, but
yeah, cuz I didn't want to take off the
wall and then move it. But I'm not
selling any of that stuff. It's only the
washing machine and the boxing bag and
and the fridge cuz wherever I go, we'll
have one. So,
yeah, that's all right, bro.
Yeah, I'm moving. But isn't it strange,
Grezy? They tell people that they don't
work and then when they think people do
work, they try to make people lose their
job or they take the piss on how much people earn
again cuz these people are fat and ugly
on benefits. You understand, Weey?
Yeah, I'm not I'm not leaving it for the
new occupants, but it's a brand new
washing machine, which is why I sold it.
Well, it's not brand new. It's not about
a couple of months old. So, I'm I'm not
leaving that. It was proper proper old
and I would have
Yeah, I changed it. Yeah, I did. I
[ __ ] destroyed it, bro.
But you know the whole [ __ ] up thing
about this bridge repair man. Yeah. Is
like all them years of spending money
going out. Yeah. And going on dates and
you still don't have anything longterm.
Tells you all you need to know about
this country is it?
Had somebody from America messaged me
yesterday and I was talking to the one
in the picture. We was talking a little bit but
but then that's the whole point of a new
chapter. You know, you try this country,
you know what it's like, and you leave.
It's It is still [ __ ] It is still [ __ ] up.
It is. It's hard to accept, you know. It
is really, really bad.
It really really really is bad.
It is strange. Yeah.
No, you got something to show. You got garments.
You've had good times. You've traveled.
You have something to show. But most of
your the time you was approaching people,
you know, most of the time you you was
approaching people and [ __ ] So
strange that ain't it? You have
something to show. You have a lot of
things to show. Brand new TV, garments,
travel experiences, restaurants. I got
all the videos. But
now should have found some of them by
now. It's not like you're not f It's not
like you're fat and ugly. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. It's strange. It is strange,
isn't it? It is strange.
And then you get people on the internet
saying you'll meet someone, you just
have to go and speak to people. Yeah. It
is weird. It is pretty [ __ ] up, bro.
And think of in them 3 years if I had to
work, think of how worse it would have
been. You're not in a worse position now
cuz it's like you enjoyed your life,
your peak years for 3 years. you you
knew what it was. You had it. You know
what I'm saying? You still got money.
It's not the worst position to be in. So
imagine you had to work and still deal
with this, bro. I don't think you'd be
alive, bro. I'm not even lying to you. Yeah,
everyone does, bro. Everyone gets women in Thailand. Thailand? Yeah.
You don't You can't not get women in Thailand.
Can't get anything here though.
I just want to go for a drink though,
but I've got so much stress and stuff to
sort out. Just want to go for a drink,
you know, again,
but I'm so busy with moving and stuff. I
don't even have time. So,
but it's not bad.
It's just you should have obviously met
someone by now.
You know what I'm saying? Strange.
I was going out like Wednesday, Thursday, Friday.
[ __ ] Bro, I used to go out like three
times a week. Don't forget I used to win
money in the casino, but it was just crazy.
Really crazy, bro.
I can't believe you didn't find anyone
in them years.
No, not interested in Spain. Full of English people.
I I'm literally going to Asia, bro, to
get away from these people. I hate
England. I hate British people. Oh,
fridge repair man. And basically, um I
started that whole Uber thing. And
sorry to sound like a broken record to
people that's already heard this, but it
made me start hating people,
which I didn't have an opinion on people
before. only women. I don't I just Yeah,
you dealt with [ __ ] in clubs, but
you just thought it was people that just
drunk and it attracted them kinds of
people. But no, no, it made me really
really start hating people like with a passion, bro.
Cuz they'd make me lo they'd be [ __ ]
testing my temper about four or five times. Um
like yeah, it's I don't want anything to
do with any westernized person. It's
that simple. That
I hate England. I hate the people.
Everything about it, bro.
No, you didn't make much money,
but you made money. Extra money. It was
good. And I had nothing better to do. So,
yeah, I was. But yeah, and and you like
people that you got the the the the you
get people on the road that make sly
comments and bro I would have ended up
just running somebody over with the bike.
They get brave. I don't know how Joe
they are so entitled that they can make
slight comments to people that they
don't even know. That is insane. Like we
get a manager, we get if a manager wants
work doing and um
manager that needs work doing and they're basically um
and then they're having a bad day or
someone's having a bad day, but they're
normal pedestrians, bro. This the UK is finished.
And then like I said, the police stopped
me. This is the the police stopped me.
Yeah. cuz I run a I run over a red light
with the bike and they said, "Oh, you
know, you can't do that." No, no, no,
no, no, no. You can get a £50 fine.
No, it's not about ignoring it. It's not
normal. No, no, no, no, bro. It's It's
not normal. Okay. Think Okay. Okay.
Okay. You're telling me that I take it
so much to heart, right? Yeah. Imagine I
done the same thing as them, right?
Imagine I done exactly the same thing as
them. I went around London starting on
everyone I saw because I've had a bad
day or I've got financial problems.
Think about it. Think about it for one
second. If you done exactly the same thing,
you know, the point is everyone's life
has problems in one way or the other.
But we're not so entitled, right? If you
know if we're not entitled to think that
the world revolves around us. You
understand? And no, I don't mind the
police pulling me over there. The
police, they're doing their job. But
I've got nothing wrong with them, you
know. They're doing their job. They're
police officer. There's no hard feelings
with them. I'm talking about people that
aren't the law.
No, no, but you still didn't answer my
question. Say, say it was Say it was,
say it was, say it was the um other way
around. Say it was the other way around.
I went to Liverpool Street right now and
I started starting on people.
Imagine Imagine I just go out right now
and just start starting on people. What
What would you say about that? It's the
same thing. I had this guy yesterday.
Yeah. About the washing machine. He
said, "Oh, is it 2 months old?" And I
was pissed off by this point. I was
like, "Bro, are you trying to be stupid
on purpose? I've listed everything on
the advertisement." And he says, "Oh,
you seem to take your frustrations out
of people because of your ego." I said,
"Bro, that is so not true. You're asking
stupid questions. I'm giving you a
stupid answer. People, uh, they do start
for no reason." Yes, they do start for
no reason. But cyclists do start for no
reason. Yeah. I was nowhere near that
woman with the tattoo. She was some fat
woman. And she said, "Oh, you should be
there." I said, "I will go where I
want." And then she started running up
her mouth and I had to park the bike and
I told her and her man to come back and
stop walking away. part that bike. Yes,
that was for no reason.
So, yes, that was literally for no reason.
I weren't on the wrong lane. I wasn't
anywhere near them. I wasn't anywhere
crushing them. Yes, they do start for no
reason. Yes, they do in London. So, it
really does happen. And you know, next
time I'm on a bike, I might show you.
They literally do start for no reason.
They do. They literally do. They can't
keep their nose out of other people's business.
Like they literally do start for no
reason. But they start something they
can't finish. That's the whole funny
thing about it. Whether it's a bloke
buying a washing machine, bro. But
listen, listen. I've just explained to
you. No, no, no, no, no, no. But then,
but it's not about an ego. I'm just sick
of dealing with stupid people. I don't
have an ego. You know, you're asking a
stupid question. So, I gave you a stupid
answer. And I'm thinking, furthermore,
would I just be doing what you people
do? And and when I said that to him, he
didn't answer. So, hold on. So, you
think I go around being frustrated um
for people? Isn't that what you people
do? Cuz I' i've got experience with it
like riding on a bike. And he said
nothing. Like, there's nothing he could
say to it. So, I mean, you need to
practice what you preach. If I was
really going around starting on people
for my own ego, that's exactly what you
people have been doing. I know because
I've done it. I've done the job for
[ __ ] seven days and I have come
across so many [ __ ]
Yeah. Yeah, I did. I did. I I did. I
did. I was argumentative. Yeah. Cuz
you're Cuz I'm sick of dealing with
stupid people. Simple. I'm sick of
dealing with stupid ass people. Yeah. I
And I aggravated it as well. But I said
to him, "Let me tell you something. I
will finish it. I I will finish anything
that I start. And yeah, I was pissed off.
Yeah. And I did. And I did. And I was
being argumentative. Yeah. But the
difference is I will finish what I
start. That's the difference. I'm not
like these little Londoners, these
little [ __ ] that get in people's
business, then run away. I said to the
[ __ ] "Yeah, you [ __ ] walk away, you
little [ __ ] [ __ ] running up your
[ __ ] mouth. Your your your guy done
nothing." That is not normal, bro. That
is not normal, you know. I do take it to
heart because when you got some little
slag that you don't know, not minding
our own [ __ ] business, did anyone ask
you? You don't [ __ ] tell me where I
need to be. You ain't no [ __ ]
authority. Keep walking. Yeah, we get
that. Listen, Joe, I I get it. We have
bad days. I've had bad days. I'm I
thought I was [ __ ] yesterday. I
probably am [ __ ] to be honest. But
that doesn't mean the world revolves
around me and I take out on other
people. Have you noticed the difference?
That's what you call entitlement, my
friend. You don't go around starting on
random people cuz the world does not
revolve around you. Do you understand?
The world does not revolve around you.
And by you, I mean these people that stop.
So, and they do start for no reason.
They literally do start for no reason,
bro. They literally do start for no
reason. I can understand if there were
police or you've almost bumped into them
or you've almost bumped into their
child. Like, bro, the UK is finished.
Like, you don't even know these people.
And that Sunday, bro, I was going to
really hurt someone. If somebody started
on me that Sunday, I changed. I said,
"Oh, we're not going to have another
repeat of Saturday where they block the
roads." I would have seriously hurt
someone. I'm not even joking. And I
would have seriously seriously seriously
hurt someone. Yeah.
And I would have got I would have
grabbed them by their [ __ ] ear and I
would have gave them a thick ear. Yeah.
Stopped starting something you can't
finish London [ __ ] And I would have
like because that's how they get you in
the end. That's literally how they get
you. Like you don't understand, bro.
You're trying to mind your own business.
Yeah. You're trying to earn some money
and you have to deal with [ __ ]
Like do you understand how annoying that
is? That's not That's not even an anger
problem, bro. And then I would have got
I would have got them by their [ __ ]
ear and I would have recorded them and I
would and I would have boyed them off,
bro. I'm not joking. Yeah. And and I I
would discipline them because at the end
of the day, it seems the police ain't
doing their job. If these people can go
around in this country being [ __ ]
somebody seriously ain't doing their job
properly, are they?
Think about it. The police offered me a
50. They said, "We can give you a 50
fine." And you wonder why people go
around being [ __ ] in this country.
There's no discipline. There's nothing
that stops them. And they block the
roads because of um protests. They do it
a lot on Saturday. So,
but guess what? You never get any of
this. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But guess what?
They deal with customers. No, no, no,
no, no, no, no. But do you know the
difference is they deal with customers
that you know, you know that guy in
Scotland? Yeah. That I was in the pub
with, he was being a bit of a [ __ ]
but he wasn't like he People just had a
bad day. They wanted to be left alone.
They literally start on people. Yeah.
And you're not [ __ ] starting on me. Simple.
And that Sunday, that woman was like,
"Oh, you're a bad cyclist." Okay, think
about it. Why would you say that to
someone? And I just said, "Oh, yeah.
Thank you. So are you." I was waiting
for the perfect excuse to do someone in
that day, bro. I was waiting for the
perfect excuse to do someone in. And I
would have done her in. If she said
something bad, I would have literally
don't know him, bro. In front of anyone
that started that day were going to get
it. It could have been [ __ ] Dwayne
Johnson. He would have got it. But think
of it. What normal person goes around
and saying them comments? Like, it's not
normal, mate. It's not normal. Stop
trying to justify these [ __ ] in
this country. Yeah, but bro, they're
drunk people. Yes, but bro, they're
drunk people. They're not pedestrians.
They're drunk. People talk [ __ ] when
they're drunk. It's a [ __ ] nightclub.
It's full of [ __ ] We know, bro.
Like, it's drinking, not people on the
[ __ ] like, not people on the road.
And it was never any of the customers.
Never had a problem with any of the customers.
And I knew it was this country because
when I started dealing with Chinese
people, they were so nice, so down to
earth. They'd help anyone cuz I met like
a lot of Chinese people and they were so
nice. So nice. So then you get these
[ __ ] I wanted that perfect excuse
on that Sunday, boy. I would have run
them over with that bicycle. Oh, bro, I
really wanted any excuse. I said, I'm in
a bad mood today. Usually I'm in a
[ __ ] bad mood.
But um yeah, but in a club, bro, people are drunk
and they're your customers.
But yeah, you don't get any of these
problems with Chinese people. Isn't that
funny? Isn't that funny how you get none
of these problems with Asian people or
really anyone from third world
countries? You get none of these
problems. Isn't that a thing, Grezy? You
get no disrespect, no dickheadness.
You get nothing. You literally get none
of it. Isn't that a thing, eh? That all
of the people that you're complaining
about seems to be from this [ __ ] country.
Ain't that a [ __ ] madness? Yeah.
Yeah, it's definitely definitely
definitely this country.
Like I was I was lifting this bike up,
right? Uh Joe, I'm trying to lift it up
and the plastic was [ __ ] up and these
two Chinese people came and they helped me, you know. So,
and they said, "Take care." Oh, what a
lovely couple e. Yeah, you you get none
of these problems with Chinese people.
And also when when I used to deliver,
they used to come all the way down,
which they should do, but like a lot of
people don't. So some of them used to
make you travel to the [ __ ] 12th
floor. Like trust me, they are [ __ ]
in this country, mate. Like you didn't
even need to go to Asia before you even
realized it. You get enough like bro you
you get enough of it here.
It could be anyone. Somebody from India.
It could be anyone. But this country you
will not have these problems with. Trust
me. Never. Never have. Never will.
But that's what someone needs in this
country. They need a good discipline.
Just like that [ __ ] You needed a big
discipline. You don't tell me where I
need to go. Why do they feel the need to
Why are they such [ __ ] Let's Let's
get to the point of it. Why are they
such [ __ ] in this country?
Like I said, go watch that 24 hours in
police custody. He got he got uh uh
he got um
10 years for raping four people. Yeah.
Yeah. No wonder people are [ __ ] in
this country. Imagine you can go out and
rape four people and then get 10 and
then get 10 years. You'll be out in 5
Nah, there were single Chinese people as
well, mate. Even the restaurants I used
to go to never have a problem with any
Chinese person. They either keep
themselves to themselves or they're nice.
And it's always been like that for
years. They've never have never had a
problem with any of them. I know they
say there's good and bad, but I have
never met a Chinese person that was a
[ __ ] Even Even when I went to the gym,
yeah, I think it was two weeks ago. The
guy was like, "Oh, how many sets have
you got left?" He said, "Take your
time." never have any of these problems
with anyone but Americans and [ __ ] English.
Australian slightly different but yeah
you'll never have any of these problems bro
getting housed getting getting bro when
people come out of prison they get rehoused
so I mean the sentence is kind of
relevant because you still have your freedom
so he when people come out they get
housed by the council when people come
out of prison
Oh, no. Cuz when my dad come out of
prison, they rehoused them and they
rehoused other people. Doesn't matter
where they put you, you get rehoused. As
soon as you come out of prison, you get rehoused.
Trust me, you do, bro. If you don't have anywhere. So, yeah.
But yeah, this country is um it's it's
in the shambles.
Yeah, but the point is they get housed.
Do you not find it weird, Joe? How all
of them years I haven't found anything longterm?
Yeah, I was speaking to the one in that picture yesterday.
Just talking for a little bit.
It's crazy that isn't it?
Dating in this country really does seem impossible, eh?
or people of certain races.
That's hard to move on from. That is,
bro. It's really hard to move on from.
Yeah. I'm not I'm not capable of a
relationship. Yeah, bro. Let me uh
let me let me show you some messages.
I'm not capable of a relationship,
right? Let me go on to this message. I
haven't approached for 3 weeks. I've not
been out for 3 weeks.
I said to one person, "Hi, it was nice
meeting you last night and chat with
you. How's your day going?" They didn't
reply. Message them two weeks later cuz
you know sometimes I always do that one
more time. Sometimes it's worked. Want
to go for some drinks on Thursday. Hey,
sorry. I'm like speaking to someone at
the moment. Huh? And I'm not the one I'm
the one that's not capable of a relationship.
Well, uh I'm the one that's not capable
of a relationship. Where's this one
gone? I invited this person out for a
nice burger and lobster. They turned
around and said, "Hi, that's very kind
of you, but unfortunately I'm flying out
on Monday, so I'm a bit cramped for
time. It was great meeting you, though."
Met her at the train station. Huh. And
I'm the one that's uh that's not capable
of a relationship.
Have I got any more?
I've got so many. I got someone that let
me know what their schedule would say.
Didn't get back to me. Man, they don't
even give you a chance. But again, I'm
the one that's not capable of a relationship.
Interesting, isn't it?
I'm not the one that's capable of a
relationship. Just like 3 weeks ago when
I come out the gym and I tried talking
to people normally and they literally
didn't even reply.
But I'm not the one capable
relationship, am I? Nah, not me.
They wasn't tourists. She lives here. So
yeah, bro. They're not tourists. They
weren't all tourists. What about them
three people that I approached three
weeks ago outside the gym? Well, nearby
the gym. What about that time, Joe? But
I'm not capable of a relationship.
It's not It's not about people being
It's like what Ant-Man says like we
laugh about it. Just not interested in
this country. It's that simple. It's
plain and simple. They are just not
interested in this country. Simple as
that. That's there's nothing else to
really really say to that, right? The
You know, people like to make I mean,
when I couldn't even get a conversation
out of two people, that was very disturbing.
Again, I've not done this for weeks, but
I've not done anything for weeks. I've
just been busy and [ __ ]
Yeah. You need to tell yourself that
though, Harry, cuz you're also single
forever. So, yeah. So, you think you're
going to go from not have not getting a
conversation, Joe, to all of a sudden
being in a relationship. You see how it
doesn't make any sense? Like I could go
out right now and start a conversation
with someone. I could go live. I've got
two phones and all you're going to get
is the same old.
Like I can make bets on it. Yeah. You're
not single, mate. It's your personality.
Nope. It's not your personality. My
videos prove that. As soon as you try to
speak to someone, they say they've got a
boyfriend. It takes time to get to know someone's personality.
It's nothing to do with personality. I
could literally go. Okay, Joe, do do you
want to do a deal right now?
I'll do a deal right now. I need to get
the money out for you. I need to make
some money. Anyways, do you want me to
go to the shopping mall and I'll go live
and I will do seven approaches? Seven is
my mom's lucky number.
And I can tell you exactly what I'm
going to get. You want to bet?
I don't have a family with my mom, bro.
I see my sister and my mom all the time.
I was out with my sister the other day.
What are you talking about? I see my mom
and sister all the time. Yeah, there's
one sister that I don't speak to. But I
I see my family all the time. You must
be getting me confused with someone
else. I saw my mom yesterday. I saw my
sister the other day. I was out with my
What the [ __ ] We don't even live
together. So anyways, Joe, you want to
bet, bro? I will go to the shopping center and uh
Yeah. Yo, I fell out with my mom and
sister what [ __ ] six months ago.
Yeah. So what? Anyways, so do you want
me do do you want and I'm obviously
going to go and have a bath and stuff.
Do you want me to go out?
Yeah. But you told me that I'm Yeah, but
that's what I'm trying to say. You told
me that I'm not capable of a relationship.
You told me that I'm
You're No, no, no. But you've just said
to me that I'm not capable of a rel I
even do it in the gym if you want.
Like I do it anyway. I do the approaches anywhere.
So you just told me that I'm not capable
of a relationship.
I could tell you I could do like a
correct score, you know, like a correct
score on the on the football. I could
tell you exactly what they will say. Okay.
But you completely ignored the whole
fact that you can barely get a
conversation out of someone that I
invited somebody to burger and lobster
and they said that they couldn't do it.
I love how you choose to ignore what
suits yourself in it.
Yeah. I mean to be honest with you, let
me let let you you know from your point
of view you might think that I'm um full
of hate and ret to tear, but I wonder
where would you be if you was me?
You would have literally killed
yourself. You know, I was thinking
yesterday when I was voice noting my
friend, if anybody was in your position
right now, they would have killed
themselves. Oh, they would have had a
mental breakdown one million%. If you've
been trying for years in this country
and you've been getting the same old
same old same old, you would be full of
hate. Anybody would be full of hate. You
you and I'm I'm the most You might not
think that I'm patient, but I am very
very very very patient. You don't need
to be laidback to be patient. Just
because I have a certain breaking point
like everyone else does, it doesn't mean
someone's full of hate.
Think of it. Think what you would do if
you if you've been trying for three
years and you've gone through all of
this money, you've gone on dates and you
have nothing to show for it relationship
wise. I think anyone would be full of
hate. You know what I'm saying?
So I'm saying so what would you be like?
I'm asking you this question. What would
you be like? You can't answer that. You
would have killed yourself, bro. You
would have killed yourself. Like I I was
saying to my mom, people have mental
breakdowns just moving. So imagine
moving, losing two sources of income and
having to deal with the women [ __ ] and
having to deal with the fact that you've
been trying for years and you've still
got nowhere. Bro, I'm telling you,
somebody would have killed someone by
now. I'm very very patient. Like you you
talk about me. Um you keep No, no, no.
It's not about Yeah. Yeah.
Well, there's two sides of it. I mean
there's there's a negative side and
there's a positive side. Obviously the
the negative side is like ra like you're
normal looking, you're decent looking,
you you have money or you had money, you
smell good. There's no reason with the
amount of efforts that you've put in why
you are not in a relationship. And then
obviously the positive side is well yeah
but you still done things, you still got
experiences. You know this country is
dead. You got money. You save money.
You're still going to earn money. It's
time to leave you know. So, I mean
there's two there's two sides of it
really, but it is still [ __ ] up. You know,
you know, you know, it is still [ __ ] up.
But there's a negative side and there's
a positive side. But if I didn't try for
3 years, then I would have been like,
"Oh, whatever. It's it is what it is."
But I mean, I have given up anyways.
I've given up anyways.
I'm just going to go out for a drink
once a week. And that's just to go out
for a drink. I literally have given up.
I give up when basically it's like no I
get I'll tell you when I gave up when
you could barely get a conversation out
of somebody when you're inviting people
out for steak restaurants cuz yolo you
can't take money with you when you die
and they're still not interested and I'm
thinking [ __ ] this mate I'm not doing
this again I gave up even when I started
doing the Uber
so which is why I done in the first place so
I I had already given
I I'd pro I'd already given up to be
honest with you. So yeah,
well you should have met someone in 3 years.
Like think of all the bad experiences
Joe with USA Izzy with all of these other people.
It's so sad, isn't it, bro? It's really
really really sad.
I didn't realize I was as strong as I actually was.
cuz I don't think my sister or anyone
else can go through this kind of stress
and be okay.
So, it's it's crazy to think that like your
how I never used how I'm not in jail. I
shall never know from beating somebody
up on a night out. I shall never know.
And you still want to tell me that I'm
not stable, bro. Come on.
And you're saying that you wouldn't do
that anymore. So, what would you do?
What would you do?
So, like I was living, no, I wasn't just
doing it. I was living a life. I was
winning money from the casino. I was
getting good money,
you know, and [ __ ] And
but yeah, I tried a lot, bro. I used to
go to O'Neal's every Thursday. I used to
do Thursday to Saturday sometimes. Go
casino Thursday, win money. And that's
how it was. cuz it was just that. So,
but you should have met someone by now,
bro. The way that you look. Like, by
you, I mean me. It's It ain't normal,
man. It ain't normal.
It ain't normal, mate. So, yeah.
Yeah. I call that USA Izzy, bro.
And she picked up Joe. I I told her to
go suck her mom.
I told her to go suck her mom, bro. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, but it doesn't matter though if
you do that because they're still going
to say they've got boyfriends.
They're still going to say that they've
got boyfriends and how I never had
alcohol poison. I shall never know.
Yeah. She's like, "Hello." I said, "Go
suck your rub, bro. Like I said, yeah, yeah.
I [ __ ] hate them little [ __ ] bro.
Hello. It made me use up all my credit
on my other phone.
But yeah, what that's basically what I'm
trying to say, lad. Yeah, I won't be
going on here anyways, bro, for long.
I'm just going to be on here today then.
I'm not here anymore, bro.
But yeah, the whole women thing is
[ __ ] up. You should be in a
relationship or you should have had
relationships. And then that 19year-old
started being a [ __ ] I didn't like her
attitude, but she was all right at the
start when she was younger. But then she
started just being a [ __ ] So had to
[ __ ] her off.
So cuz she tried taking me for a mug and
it got worse and worse and worse and
worse and worse. and she was always
broke and I couldn't save with her and
nah bro [ __ ] all that
and I remember when she started calling
me mate I said I'm not your [ __ ] mate
I don't like being called mate it sounds
common I know you just said it but like
I mean generally when people say it
obviously you don't know my feelings
towards it I don't mind being called pal
or buddy but mate just sounds so common
especially when a woman says it is horrible Yeah.
>> And you know what gave me flashbacks,
Joe? I watched this Uber Eats guy on
YouTube and he brought his bike to Manchester
um to do like he just goes around with
his bikes just just testing different
areas, I presume. But uh he was like,
"Yeah." He's like, "Oh, this is my first
time in Manchester." And I was like,
"This guy is 3 years older than me and
I've been Manchester like 10 times."
Then it pointed to the women again
because I used to just go there. You
remember that time when people was like,
"Keep trying, keep trying, keep trying."
I was like, "I [ __ ] had enough of
this. Keep trying. Keep trying. You got
to keep trying." I [ __ ] one day I
just packed my [ __ ] bags. I went to
Manchester, bro. Guess what? Got seven
seven numbers. They didn't go anywhere.
So, we used to do crazy things. Crazy
crazy [ __ ] things with no plans. I
remember that day as well.
[ __ ] annoying, bro. People on Reddit
was like, "Keep trying." I said, "I'll
show you. Keep [ __ ] trying."
Yeah, I planned it like 1 hour ahead.
I'm [ __ ] going Manchester. [ __ ] it. I
was a crazy bastard, bro. Crazy bastard. Times, bro. Yeah.
So, whatever you say about me, Joe, you
can't deny that I've uh got patience.
You can't deny that I've got patience. today.
No, I'm actually all right now.
Going to go to KFC later.
You surely have to question yourself.
You don't have to question yourself on
this. They're brainwashed by social
media. They've got unrealistic
standards. There's no point me trying to make you
um understand, bro. You're probably in
your 30s and your 40s. Um and you're
never going to understand. Like, so
there's no point even trying to trying
to explain this to you. And these women
you meet are 100% faithful to their
boyfriends. They don't have boyfriends.
And do you know what my friend said?
Yeah. He said, "Who is their boyfriend,
Casper the Ghost?" Because one in five
people are in relationships. And and I
come to think of that. Yeah. And I'm
thinking, "No, he's actually right. All
of the people I know, people I've met
through different things. Literally,
most of them are single. There's
feminists out there. There's women that
hate men. There's women that don't need
men. Who are all their boyfriends?"
Think about it, right? You meet so many
people and they're single. Like whether
you go outside, maybe one in five are in a relationship
maybe. And then you got feminists that
hate men. And then you got men that are
struggling, but all these people claim
they've got boyfriends.
Ouch. The maths doesn't look right
there. The math really does not look
right there. Because if you think about
like this, right? If all these women
they have boyfriends, why is it that
most of the people that you meet are
single? Like people like in their 20s.
It doesn't make Who is their boyfriend?
Casper the ghost. Like it's that is the
truth. There's so many women that don't
have boyfriends. So many. I would say
though, there was one that showed me a
boyfriend that u again 3 weeks ago cuz I
ain't done nothing for 3 weeks. But
yeah, that's just a oneoff. But maybe
they are just in a relationship. But
most of them they don't have boyfriend.
There's no [ __ ] way. And at the end
of the day, you know. Yeah, but it
shouldn't be that way, Joe. It should
and and and it shouldn't be that way
because you're decent looking. You can
hold a conversation. Isn't that what
supposedly they want? What people say on
the internet, they shouldn't be wanting
people that they should be giving people
a chance. They should be giving normal
normallook people a chance, you know? So
that says a lot about their standards.
Simple. They've got unrealistic standards.
It's not normal. Because you got people
on the internet saying women like
confidence. You will find someone and
then the next thing you can barely get a
conversation out of someone.
And bro, I'm not going to sit here and
try and make you understand, bro. It's
it's a waste of my time.
Like the only thing that I can say is
you go out and do it yourself.
like Notorious does. I'm not going to
sit here and try to make you understand
something that you're just never going
to understand. It's a waste of my time
and it's a waste of your time really. So
there you just they do it because
they're stuck up. There's too many stuck
up people in this country that are
influenced by Instagram and influenced
by Tik Tok. They think that they're far
better than they are and they've got
unrealistic standards. So because of all
of the simps, it makes them think that
they're better than they are. So then
they're looking for Mr. Perfect their
whole life and then they don't find Mr.
Perfect their whole life. And then
finally when they're Natalie G's age,
that's when they start settling down cuz
you're not going to have these problems
in your 40s. Once you hit your 40s,
you're not going to have this problem.
Well, I hope not. Anyways, yeah, maybe
40s. Once you get to 40s, you're not
going to have this. You're not going to
have these problems.
So it's because they are made to think
that they're better than they are. So
that's why they've got attitude. That's
literally what it is.
Tik Tok, Instagram, it's all to do with
that, you know.
So they don't even give people a chance.
I wouldn't mind if people actually was
given a chance and then you were [ __ ] it up.
Like my friend was like, "Oh, you know,
with the Italian one, it could have been
you." which yeah there's possibilities
but not really. I mean you was holding
hands, you was rubbing each other's
hands. All you tried to do is kiss
someone. So I mean yeah there is still a
chance but but then I but then on the
flip side of it is like then I turned
around and said to him but then then I
turned around and said to him I was like
okay well maybe but then you got to
think of okay so what about the ones
that you kissed?
What about the ones that you didn't kiss
and you didn't try to kiss? What about
them ones? You you understand? And
that's when you realize like, bro, the
problem is it has to be them. Cuz Okay,
let's just say your problem. You're the
problem on two of the occasions, right?
What about the ones that you didn't try
to kiss, that you didn't try to hold
hand with, and the ones that you
actually did kiss?
Do you understand? And even that Italian
when I was talking to her yesterday, she
was all right to be honest.
So nothing what that USA Izzy said
was was true because even if you did do
something wrong, people don't just block
people like that and disappear. So
but yeah, I said, "What about the ones
that you did kiss?
What about the ones that you was
kissing? What about them ones? What
happened to them?"
So you got to think realistically that
you have kissed people and you have not
kissed people. So what happened to them people?
What happened to that [ __ ] Australian
stripper Greavvesy? Eh. So yeah,
and I understand what this guy is saying
here. This big TJ, you know, because I
used to think that like when people used
to say, "Oh yeah, you should go out and
approach women." I used to think that,
you know, it will change a situation cuz
that's what you're meant your your your
sold the dream really. You know what I mean, Grezy?
But I mean, you've seen my approach to
videos. There's nothing wrong with them.
So, I don't know why
what's the point of having the
conversation. Like, the whole approach
to videos was to prove
what was happening. So, from what I see
in most of the videos anyways are normal
approaches and people not being interested.
So, I mean it's it's in the video. Do
you know what I'm saying, Grezy? So,
I mean, what else is there to say, lad?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I I'm
doing Okay, okay, okay.
But I'm I'm open. Yeah. Okay, bro. Yeah.
So, you tell me what I'm saying wrong.
Right. I have just read out three
messages where I've offered somebody to
go out for a steakhouse burger and
lobster and I have done approaches and
they've said, "Okay, now you need to
tell me what I'm doing wrong because you
always say to me that I'm not open for I
I'm I'm doing everything wrong. Okay.
What am I doing wrong? What? Going to a
a club and speaking to somebody? Going
on the street and speaking to somebody.
Getting a number from a train station
and inviting someone else. Like, we need
to be clear exactly what is wrong here.
Cuz you tell me that I I always think
I'm right. No, I'm wrong. But you need
to be specific on what I'm doing wrong.
But you're not doing wrong. It's it's
literally is it is them. Like if you
think of all of the dates that you've
went on, it obviously is them. Like
you know, and it doesn't matter. [ __ ]
We don't even need to think about the
past. Let's think about the future. I
done approaches on Wednesday and
Thursday about 3 weeks ago. What
happened, bro? What the [ __ ]
So, you need to tell me specifically
what I am doing wrong.
You need to go back to what you've said.
Yeah. You've just said that if I go on
the on the mall in the mall and I start
doing approaches, I'm going to get
nowhere. Why am I going to get nowhere?
And don't just say that it's because
it's in the mall because it's going to
happen in the bar and the club as well.
So, you need to tell me exactly why I'm
not going to go anywhere. Why I'm not
going to get anywhere. It's not the way
I look. It's not the way I speak. It's
not the way I dress. So, you need to be
specific. You understand? You need to be
But you can't. So obviously it's your
it's your race. It that's the only thing
it can be
my language used. Okay, bro.
I might send you I might show you an
approach video that I think you already
saw that one on Tuesday.
Yeah, the one I done on Tuesday. But
bro, you've seen normal approaching videos.
So everything you say doesn't make any
sense because you have seen normal
approaching videos with normal language
with normal personality. So whatever
you're saying does not make sense.
Like all of this is to hide the fact
that they're just not interested because
they've got unrealistic standards. all
of this whole thing that we go on and on
and on and on and on and on and on
about. You know what I'm saying? So,
you know what I'm saying? So,
yeah, if you're blaming race, then I
accept it. But you're not blaming
something that I can't I can help, you know? So,
again, this is not real life, bro. This
is the internet. So whatever people are
saying on the internet, it doesn't ring
right with real life who speak.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no. You tell me what is specifically
wrong with those approaches.
What is specifically wrong with those
approaches? And you see me approaching a
club as well. So you need to tell me
what is specifically wrong with them
approaches like the specifics.
No, you can't. You're just defending
women for the sake of defending women.
You know, it's they're not interested in this country
in like 85% of people or 80% 90%
whatever it is, you know,
and you're saying that I'm the problem.
Look at what that us that USA Izzy did.
Yep. No one told me about that on
Reddit, Harry. Again, this is the
internet. This is not real life, bro. You understand? Yeah.
No, I'm not very selective. You've seen
me in clubs speaking to people normally
and they've pretended they have had boyfriends.
Right or wrong?
Like you're you're very very selective
because you've ignored all of autism.
Yeah, you have got autism. Stop talking
about yourself. Self-reflective. But
anyways, um you're saying that I'm very
selective. Okay. Okay.
How many approaching videos have you
seen on my channel? And how many times
have you brought it up? Never. So, you
are being selective because you're
picking situations like USA Izzy or Sig
and you're being selective with examples
that you're choosing, right? But then
you're ignoring all of the normal
approaches and the people that don't
reply to first messages. And when you
invite people out, they don't meet you.
um they make excuses.
So, actually, you're actually being selective
because I'm pretty sure, I don't know
how many I've got now, there has been
300 approaching videos on my channel.
So, you're being selective.
You're only picking things where I may
have been in the wrong one, two, three, four times.
So, you're actually the one that's being
selective, not me. Selective about what,
bro? I've showed you near enough a million videos.
If this was normal, this person would
have went out with you to Burger and Lobster
or some one of these people would meet
you and then they wouldn't meet you
again. But you can't even get somebody out.
But it's easy, bro. I don't I don't take
offense to it. It's easy to blame the
man. It's easy to do. You know, it
sounds good. It's just the easy thing to
do. Just blame the man. It's just easy, isn't it?
So, but you you're very selective cuz
you've ignored everything that you've been shown.
And then you go on to talk about some
situation about 3 years ago. Come on, bro. Come on.
Cat got your tongue. Where you going, bro?
Um the last was on here on holiday. You
you you got lucky and had a one night
stand. Uh uh you have drank on about for
you spooking and harassing her. Um no no
no no no no no no. Actually get the
story right first. Yeah. So at the end
of the day Yeah.
No, no, no. What you mean is she came
here, she misled people, she used them,
then she made up stories, and then she
started being a [ __ ] Yeah, that's
that's what it that that's what it was.
And then when someone stood up to her, I
was stalking and harassing her. Typical,
isn't it? Yeah.
Cuz you know what? Even with that
Italian woman, I I was speaking to her yesterday.
No problems there. So, you got to
understand, why have you only acted like
that with one or two people? Cuz it's
them, RV. They started wanting to be a
[ __ ] so I was a come back to them.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. Mate, if I always
thought I was right, I would block
everyone. Okay, then you're right then.
You're right and I'm wrong. Yep. I've
not traveled all over the country. Women
don't pretend they've got boyfriends.
Women don't give their numbers and don't
reply. Women don't go on dates to waste
free time. Yep, I don't know anything.
I'm wrong about everything. I've got no
life experience. I haven't traveled
anywhere. I'm a complete introvert. Like
I I Yeah, I've not been doing this for
three years. I don't know anything.
Nope. I'm a stupid idiot that don't know anything.
Are you happy now, bro? Like, I don't
know what you want people to say. You know,
you should be you should be on a date this week.
But yeah, I love how you're trying to
victimize her there like she didn't do anything wrong. Yeah.
Why are you even defending her, bro? Why
are you defending that scumbag? You
people really are simps, aren't you? I'm
not talking about Grevy, but you really,
really, really, really are simps. You
didn't even leave on good terms. That's
the good thing. You know that Italian?
Yeah. She was so nice about like the
last message and you know other people
have got problems as well. Like you
you're you're victimizing
a [ __ ] scumbag. You know,
you know what I'm saying?
Really, really, really bad, bro.
But it's still an experience to add to a [ __ ] collection.
Isn't that right, Grezy? To add to a
[ __ ] collection, mate. Yeah.
But we're talking about like here and now.
We're talking about here and now, bro. I
mean, my body count is shocking as well.
I think my body count's only five
without escorts. It should be in the
[ __ ] 50s with the amount of traveling you've done.
Yeah, you keep telling yourself that. I
mean I mean my I mean Okay, let's let me
give you an example, Joe. My my my
interest is the gym. I've just been so
busy lately. So, um
yeah. Um I've been so busy lately. I've
been to the gym.
So, if I go to the gym and I approach a woman,
what do you think she's going to say?
Should we all put money on it?
I I think I could put money on the
correct score, but I'm probably lose a
lot of money to be honest. So,
boyfriend maybe. I mean, what do you
think they'd say?
probably not interested.
I don't know why people don't just be
honest and say, "Listen, if you're not
if you ain't got a million subscribers,
um, if you're not like a 10 out of 10
white tall guy, you got no chance." Why
don't people just say like, "You're
playing at your own risk." Then then we
wouldn't moan about it. They'd be like,
"Oh, like we know." But no one ever
tells you this stuff.
Like no one ever ever tells you this
stuff. Like they don't say, "Oh, women
have got high standards because of no
unrealistic standards. Sorry. They're
not high standards cuz everyone is
everyone should have high standards."
Like no one ever tells you this stuff.
Like [ __ ] off to Asia. Well, there was
one guy before he did say that women has
unrealistic standards expectations. Go
to a third world country.
Um well one person said it but I mean
majority of them they act like they're
not the problem and they are the problem
because social media is the problem
which has made them the problem. Of
course they're the problem, bro.
Like when did this whole incel thing come about?
When they were um I don't like that term
incel, bro. I don't like it, you know,
because it's like they are struggling
because of women's ignorance and
unrealistic expectations due to social
media and they get picked on for it.
They get literally picked on for
something that they can't help when the
cause of it is not even them. Like
that's what makes me like laugh about it
is that they get called a name, every
name under the sun, and it's not even
their fault. It's literally social media
and society. Do you know what I'm saying?
I mean, I was arguing with this [ __ ]
Australian and she was said, she said,
"I'm an incel." I said, "You're calling
me an incel."
No, I said that incelss don't have a
choice. Why they're incelss? Because
they're not interested in this country.
That's what I said.
Um, and I said, "Oh, you're calling me
an incel? That's cute." You know, that
has no meaning. You know, when someone
calls you an incel, now an incel now
that died ages ago, that incel term.
It's so boring. I said to her, it's like
calling someone a [ __ ] It's boring as
And no one tells you like the games that
they play. Like no one tells you this.
Like women in this country are the
problem. I guarantee I guarantee you.
Yeah. Any of you you go to any other
country anywhere in Asia, you're you're
not having these problems.
Yeah. No, you you don't make it easy for
them. So yeah, so that's why they're in
sales. You know, women do not go go for
them because they've got unrealistic
standards. So that's why they um that's
why they become incelss
and it's not even their fault.
You know what I'm saying? It's like if I
wanted to go out and make a friendship
right now, Greavvesy, I couldn't do it.
You can't even get a conversation out of
someone. It's just pointless topic. It's
pointless talking about it.
Yeah. And men are fine.
I would never bring a child in this
world. Oh, even if I had a partner. No.
No. It's not that, mate. There's people
in Philippines that want money. There's
people in Philippines that want money.
And it's not that. It's the people are
different. In doggy, the people are
different as well. Yeah. When I started
doing this e e uh eba, when I started
doing this Uber, I really started to
notice the difference between
westernized people and Asian people,
even if they weren't from third world
countries. So, mate, if you go to the
Philippines, they actually want
relationships and they don't want money.
Yeah, maybe Thailand, some of them,
yeah, they want money, but bro, it's
it's a whole cultural difference. Do you not understand?
It's just a better way of life over
there. Better people, better women, no
gambling, nice weather here. Gambling
everywhere. I don't even know why I say
gambling. I don't even gamble anymore.
But [ __ ] everywhere, stuck up
women. It's a sad sad place to be in
England. You know, I would actually, you
know, when I started taking the train
yet to go go to the bike every day, I
would actually hear myself say, "I hate
England, man." And I'd look on the
ground like I actually would actually be
depressed in this country.
It's really a depressing place to be
here in England.
I can't think of a worse place to be, bro.
So, yeah, they want money in Thailand,
but they don't want your money in
Philippines, bro. They want relationships.
Actual relationships, you know.
No, it's not. It's okay. Is it not the
unrealistic? No, it's not the
unrealistic standards. Cuz if any of
these people, okay, okay, say any of
these incelss, whoever the [ __ ] they
are, went and spoke to a woman, they're
going to say they've got boyfriends.
They're going to reject them. That's not
their fault. So that's why they're
incels. So they're blaming the real
problem is is social media. And then the
second problem is women.
You know what I'm saying? So,
and then when I started getting Oh,
yeah. I got an escort two weeks ago and
she actually let me finish in her mouth. Grezy.
Yeah, that's another thing. I couldn't
even get an escort that would let me
finish in their mouth 3 weeks ago. I
thought, what the [ __ ]
So, I mean, that started with that. I
think that started the whole like this
country is [ __ ]
Like that started the whole Yeah. This
Yeah. It's like a troll country, isn't
it? Really? Can't beat women. So they
don't have unrealistic expectations. The
women have unrealistic expectations.
Why would insults have I just told you I
can go out to a mall right now and start
talking to people and all I'm going to
get is attitude.
You know, we we we can keep blaming men
and we can keep blaming other things,
but we know that the real problem is
it's social media. You know, I know a
lot of people don't want to admit that
and stuff, but it is. It is. They're all
non-playing characters as well.
Non-playing characters. Same attitude.
You see the same attitude. You see the
same people, same women, same attitude,
same [ __ ] same bus drivers with
the same attitude.
This country is so so depressing, bro.
It's like I don't have to deal with
people anymore on it.
And the thing is with this country, it
never changes. This country never ever Um, [ __ ] Yeah,
they like to make you think that you're
the problem and you're not the problem,
which is the whole point of the approaching videos.
It doesn't matter though, Grezy, cuz
whatever you show them, they're always
going to defend women. Bro, you could
show a woman literally killing a baby
and they'd be like, "Nah, the baby had a
bad personality." Like, you're you're
wasting your [ __ ] time, bro. I doubt
any of these people on Reddit actually
leave the house.
It's a complete waste of time. They're
always going to defend women. So, it's
it's pointless cuz the truth hurts.
They're in denial, bro. So, it's it's
pointless, isn't it? Cuz
even when you show videos, they still deny it.
So there were lost calls, bro. Like even
when you show videos,
I I I read their messages out to you, Grezy,
where I tried meeting people from 3
weeks ago and they weren't having none of it. You know,
they weren't having it at all at all.
No, it's not because I care anymore. Oh,
it's just a whole 3 years thing. If
Monty can get a bird, you can LA. Well,
Monty didn't get a bird. Monty got a
drug addict, alcoholic that would go out with anyone.
So, um, yeah. And the world does not
work like if someone else can do it, you
can. If only the world worked like that.
E, if only the world was that easy.
You No, the Grezy. The thing that I
can't get over is the whole three years.
It doesn't matter what my idol woman is
because you can't get anyone in this country
cuz they're not interested in this
country. So, it wouldn't it wouldn't it
wouldn't make sense me saying what my
ideal woman is cuz you can't get one in this country.
So, I'm going to try and find something
for a month in a month and then I'm
going to have to think about leaving
think again. So, yeah.
It's no life in England, bro. It ain't
no life in England.
Yeah. It doesn't matter what my type is, bro.
Cuz you're never going to get anyone in this country.
I'd go out for a drink today, but I'm
far too stressed.
I've got people coming. I've got things
to do. So, I can't go out today.
I probably won't be able to until I
properly move to be honest. Um, yeah.
Piece the money or the haircut and [ __ ] Yeah.
do fancy a beer and that but yeah. Yeah.
What? No thoughts on the me approaching
and them pretending they've got boyfriends.
That that didn't suit you.
No opinion on when I've invited somebody
out for a date and they make excuses.
No, then guess didn't suit you, did it?
My experiences don't suit these people.
It doesn't suit them. You like that one,
don't you, Greasy?
I just can't get over the threeear ride
and you're still single. I can't believe that.
I [ __ ] was lied to my whole life. Jesus Christ.
I can't believe I was lied to my whole life.
I need to stop talking about this. It's
depressing, bro. It really, really is depressing.
[ __ ] hell. Three [ __ ] years. Jeez.
And then you got people saying that you
will find someone [ __ ] delusional. E
Need to focus on leaving again, I think.
I'll probably need to go to a different
country anyways to start working to be honest.
I don't get anything for
couple of months.
I [ __ ] own RJ
cuz I had to keep canceling orders.
But even if I need to go to America,
I'll do that, you know, to work. I've
got the money. I can go somewhere. You
know what I mean? So, it's not a problem.
So, they sat me off cuz I have to keep
canceling the orders because they kept
um locking the roads off.
would have killed someone by now, Joe.
I think you would have killed someone by
now if you went through what I went
through. Telling you, bro. Somebody
would have killed someone, bro.
I'm telling you, they they they make it
seem like that you're not stable and
you've got anger issues, but bro, you've
been through more than most people with
these women and obviously the situation
I'm in now.
But like, and they they don't seem to
think that you've got patience. Wow.
And then you've got stupid people on the
[ __ ] internet, bro.
Then you got stupid people on the
internet telling you that
you're going to find someone. Yeah.
Um maybe like 190 into
but it weren't even like proper work to
be honest. I remember Sunday. Yeah. It
was so [ __ ] It took [ __ ] 8 hours to earn £55.
Imagine that. 8 hours to earn £55.
It was really bad.
Yeah, it got bad, bro. It got really bad.
But most you can make over 100 in a day.
But yeah, I think people would have
ended up killing someone by now if they were me.
Generally, I'm curious about that
sometimes, you know, what would actually people do?
instantly, weekly. But like I said, when
I find something else,
I'm never going to tell anyone. So, just
to let you know, I only told you cuz I
don't do it anymore. But I will never
tell anyone anything.
So, cuz obviously you get jealous people
on here, but I already got sacked off
anyway. So, yeah.
So, there won't be no I have a job, I
don't have a job. Like I just won't even
I I won't even just say the subject
cuz you got the likes of Red Star and
he's fat ugly [ __ ] self stalking
people every day cuz he's got some form
of jealousy whatever it is. So and other
people as well.
I actually own them in that video, bro.
What could they actually say? There's
literally nothing they can say cuz I'm
right about all of them on here.
I'm right about every single one of them on here.
Their YouTube activity gives them away,
bro. [ __ ] living their best life with
all that money when they're sat on
YouTube every day. Uh, make it make
sense, bro. Come on. We all know they're
fat, ugly wobblers
on this [ __ ] community. Come on, bro.
They're not making money from this [ __ ] place,
you know? And they got no content on
their channel as well. They're like
they've got no content other than talking,
you know? It's bad. And they just
psychologically [ __ ] with their own
heads. I remember when Joe used to say
to me, they they psych they don't
psychologically [ __ ] with my head. They
[ __ ] with their own head. I have to be
on their mind 24/7, bro.
Yeah, it wasn't long hours, but it was
better than nothing.
I'm not saying what my plan is, bro.
Well, well, I can say that's what a plan
is, but you're not going to know where I
am, what I'm doing. Simple. So, yeah.
So, I won't be out for a couple of
weeks. I got to go to the cinema
next week, so I'll be doing that instead.
See, I should be dealing with this
problem with a woman. I should be in a relationship.
Do you understand, Joe? I should be in a relationship now.
Duh. I should be in a [ __ ] relationship. After
all of them years, you should either be
in a relationship dealing with this or
not dealing with this and not in a
relationship. So, it should be it should
be one of the two, if not both, if we
were lucky. So, it's really bad, bro. It
just can't get over them three years.
Can't get over them, bro.
It's really bad. So bad. Three years. Wow.
Generally think you should give up for life.
I don't even know. I'll have to ask
other people what they would do if
they're in my position. It'll be
interesting to see what they'd say to be honest,
but they're just going to blame you to
be honest. But no, I'd see I'll actually
ask them what they would actually do.
See what their what their opinion is.
You're not fat. You're not ugly.
You're not any of these things. You
should have found someone by now.
Guess Reddit was lying when they said
people, you'll find someone.
But like I said, it's it's a good thing
that I've just given up. Anyways, it's a
good thing that I given up when I
basically lost that income to be honest
with you. So, in a way, it could have
been a lot worse. It could have been a
Like, you could be like nonsleg still a
virgin 3 years now and still and not
have the money to go out. But imagine
that being a virgin like him and then
[ __ ] cuz he is a big virgin. big
[ __ ] virgin [ __ ] and then and then
you wouldn't even have the money to even go out.
You know the country is dead. You know
that is you know that they're not
interested in this country.
So it's Yeah, it's good really.
I mean, yeah, you might have had some
one night stands, but you should have
had a lot more, bro.
It could have been worse because 3 years
ago, you might you you might have had to
work and then you would have to deal
with the women and working and then you
wouldn't have been able to even have any
kind of experience because you'd be
working. You'd have no time and you'd
have no money.
Like now, we've already given up and
we've still got somebody so we can just leave again.
So, that's what I'm saying. It could be
worse. It could be starting off now. So, yeah.
So, that's how it could be worse.
Like, cuz when you get to a certain age,
you don't go out as much. I was only
planning to go out once a week. I would
never go out 2 weeks again. Maybe if
it's a bank holiday. So
it it could have been worse because
you could have been 24, 25 now, dealing
with the women [ __ ] having to work and
not having time and then having to deal
with that or just being on benefits and
not being able to afford it.
So you you you wouldn't be able to do
it. And I knew this I did say that once
you work, your problems are going to get
worse with the whole women thing.
um because you're going to have to deal
with the women and working but then but
I had already given up by that point so
it didn't really bother me but I got it
at the right time to be honest with you
because if it was 2 3 years ago
you would be [ __ ] You wouldn't be
able to do it. So
well guess what Joe us Londoners are
stronger than you northerners so we can
take more stuff. us Londoners
um can can take or are built more
stronger than you northerners, mate.
This is why I can take bar stress. But
I'm not a London [ __ ] that can start
something I can't finish. I will finish
anything I start. So I'm not I'm not in
the same I'm not in the same uh position
as as as these [ __ ] Londoners. But
I'm a different kind of Londoner.
I'm not somebody that will make a slight
comment and run away like a [ __ ]
But we are generally built far stronger
than you normally is. So hence why I can
take distress a bit more. You like that
one, didn't you, Grezy? But yeah,
but um yeah, like so yeah, if it was
anyways, if it was 3 4 years ago and you
was on benefits, you'd be [ __ ] or
you'd have to work, you'd be [ __ ] So
I'm not mentally strong. Okay, I've lost
two forms of income. I'm losing my
house. I've tried for years. I've got no
one really to support me. And you're
telling me that I'm not mentally strong?
Bro, you would have had a mental
breakdown. I've had to deal with this
whole women [ __ ] and I'm still here.
Come on, bro. People get mental
breakdowns when they just lose their
[ __ ] house. Not two forms of income.
So, I mean, you would never be able to
deal with that. Never.
So yeah, I am mentally strong. What?
Just cuz I said the whole women thing is
[ __ ] up. It is [ __ ] up, bro. You
can't acknowledge the fact that it's not [ __ ] up.
Like, you really really really right
don't think that it's it's normal to
acknowledge how [ __ ] up it is.
It is [ __ ] up, bro. Like you're not
human if you don't acknowledge it. Like
you you're decent looking. You've been going out.
Yeah, I was going on like that
yesterday. Yeah, cuz I was stressed.
Um but then like
Yeah, it is [ __ ] up. Like the the
situation is [ __ ] up
with the whole women thing. Not now, but
then. Don't you think that's [ __ ] up?
You don't ever look back on anything and
think, "Wow, that's [ __ ] up."
Just like when that guy said he's been
Manchester once and he's 30 and I've
been like 10 times. It made me really
start thinking of the traveling days.
That's that's normal to look back on
things when you're lying down, you know,
and you're not fat and ugly as well,
which is the worst thing.
You're not fat and ugly, which is also
the worst thing as well. So,
like I said, if you look like Timmy,
then it'll be all right, you know. So, yeah,
that's as far as that goes. Yeah,
the whole women thing is really, really bad.
It really is bad.
It's so bad, bro. But I'm not even
moaning about it now because I'm not I
don't try anymore. Like, I don't care
now, but I'm just looking back on it.
It's weird, you know?
Yeah, I know, Grezy. Just like when you
try to speak to some I don't think
anyone's acknowledged any of my
approaching videos. Do you know what? I
don't even know why I bothered making
them cuz it seems like they don't suit
any of you people. I don't even know why
I wasted my time even doing them. You know? So yeah.
Yeah. But Timmy brings on himself with
his gambling. So I mean Yeah. I mean, I
don't even know why I've even done them
approaching videos because they
literally don't suit you. I have I have
showed normal approaching videos in
bars, clubs, to train where people have
literally not even given me the chance
and then you're rambling on about
something completely different. I don't
even know why I wasted my time doing
these approaching videos. They literally
don't suit you. Do you literally just go
on to something completely different?
The whole video
proves what it's like in this country.
It's it's it's it's a real video, you know.
So, yeah, he brings all these problems on himself. I
>> You know what I think it is? I think you
don't want to accept the truth.
That's what I think you you're what I
think it is. I think deep down you know
the truth. It's like what Ant-Man said,
but you don't want to admit it. That's
why I think it is. I think it's like
that with people on Reddit. Like they
know deep down that you know that women
are stuck up and they're [ __ ] but no
one It's like simps in nightclubs. I
think you know the truth, but you just
don't want to admit it.
Yeah. I I want a decent experience as
well, funny enough. I've been trying for
the past 3 years, but all I keep getting
is I've got a boyfriend and time
wasters. I mean, man, I I I I'm more
than you. You know, I'm more than [ __ ] you.
Do you know what I'm saying? So, I I
think you know the truth. You just don't
want to admit it. I think you're in
denial. That's what I think it is. I
think you're generally in denial.
Yeah. I think you're in the dial, mate.
Yeah, you're in denial, bro.
You're really, really in denial.
Cuz if you had somebody, you wouldn't
even be talking about other women. So,
you you contradict yourself.
Yeah. You should be with someone now, to be honest.
I mean, how much longer would it take,
Joe? How much more time and money do you
have to keep spending in this country?
Give me an estimate. You know,
it's annoying, bro. I hate, you know, I
hate even talking about this. It's
[ __ ] annoying, bro.
It's never going to change in this
country. I think people need to just
stop being in denial. I mean, there's literal videos
Like, do you want your memory refreshed?
Do you want me to refresh your memory
where I've approached people and they're
not interested? Like, do I have to
really cuz there is a possibility that
you also forgot what you've seen.
I mean, you ain't seen them for ages.
So, are you just scared of the truth,
though? Does the truth hurt? It's not
it's not bad if the truth hurts. You know,
you know what I'm saying? It's not It's
I know. Like, do you need your memory
refreshed again when you actually go out
and you try to approach a woman and she
pretends she has a boyfriend? I mean,
why why doesn't that suit you, bro?
You ignore the truth because the truth hurts.
That's what it is. So then you go on to
something completely different like USA
Izzy and Sig because you you can't stand
the truth. That's you actually are
talking about yourself there. I have
shown more than enough videos where I
have looked good, where I've gone out,
where I've been normal, where people
pretend they got boyfriends, where
people take the piss. But you seem to
forget all of these experiences so
quickly cuz it doesn't suit you.
So actually you you only got you
actually choose what you want to choose
believe that's what it actually is you know so
why are you scared of the truth anyways
Joe why are so many people scared of the truth
Why are so many people scared of the truth, bro?
Like, why don't you just admit that
they're not interested in this country?
Why do you have to beat around the bush?
I don't understand why you have to beat
around the bush. And
it must hurt you in it, bro. The truth
must really hurt. Yeah.
It's like, have you forgot everything
that you've been shown?
Oh, yeah. There's another one I
messaged. I said, "Oh, let's go to a
steakhouse." They said they've got a boyfriend.
[ __ ] boyfriend. Boyfriend. Boyfriend.
You know, I'd go out today if I didn't
have so much stress to deal with.
Nah, not yet, bro.
I'm missing my hair, bro.
My hair's too long and my beard's too long.
Could go out for a few beers, but it
means me having my hair done. I'm not
getting my I'm not I'm not waiting
around. That's another thing I hate
about England. You got to wait around
for things. Oh, it annoys me. It annoys
me being in this country. I feel like
I've got a bug in my [ __ ] body, bro.
Yeah. They're not interested in me.
They're not interested in you. And
they're not interested in 80% of people.
Yeah. Yeah. And they're also not
interested in you and 80% of the population.
And sing is not going to change that,
buddy. Trust me. Loads of people have tried.
Loads of people have tried, mate.
Loads of people have [ __ ] tried, bro.
They're not interested in me. They're
not interested in you and they're not
interested in 80% of people due to
social media sim. [ __ ] hell.
But then I'll have to have a haircut and
I can't be annoyed get my hair done and [ __ ]
Nah, bro. I'm not going out today. [ __ ]
that. I'm going to get a nice KFC.
So yeah, why why do you people why do
you I'm not talking about Joe and Grezy,
but I really need to understand this.
Yeah. That they're not going to [ __ ]
you. Like you being a simp
man beige man. It's not going to make
women [ __ ] you. Like if you want to meet
me today, we will go for a beer and
let's see how many women are really
interested in you. Come on. if you want
to meet me, I'm I'm more than happy to
meet you. Other than that, I won't be going out. Um,
so like if you want to do that, bro, we
can do that.
Let's see the big man against all the
women. Show me how it's done. I want to
learn from the best.
Would do that with you, you know, you
[ __ ] s. See, they s and s and s, but
they never get laid. Like, this is what
the thing I used to say to scoop is
simps don't get laid. Women take the
piss out of s simps, which is why they
s. They simp because they can't get laid
and they're trying to get laid, but
women don't like them, but they still
stick up for them. It's in denial, bro.
They Bro, I'm telling you, I'm starting
to think at this point they're in
denial. I think they know the truth
themselves, but they don't want to admit
it. I think generally that I generally
think that's what it is, you know? I
think they know what their women are
like, but they just don't want to admit it.
That's why I think they're just scared
to say anything.
So I think it is generally generally
generally generally generally that cuz
you know if you went to a court of law
if you went to court right say you was
up against murder say you was you was
you was you was on a plea for murder
right and you're like I didn't do it I
didn't do it and there's video of you
stabbing someone straight in the chest.
I mean the judge would be like well the
evidence is there like you're guilty
you're guilty. There's not, oh well this
that and oh well like no, you killed
someone, you're going to jail. There's
evidence. But with these people, even
the amount of evidence you show them,
they still choose to ignore it. I think
they know the truth deep down, but
they're scared to say it. I generally
generally think it is. I generally
generally think that is that is what it
is. I think it is. I think I've hit the
nail on the head there.
I think they're lying to themselves, you
know, that's what I think it is.
Cuz if a gay guy was saying to me,
right, I can't find a guy. I'll be like,
[ __ ] off. I don't believe you.
And then when he showed me videos and
then videos, then videos, I'd be like,
well, I've got no reason to disbelieve you now.
I think that's what it is, bro.
I think you're lying to yourself. That's
what I think it is. If you generally do
not think women are the problem in this
country, you're lying to yourself.
Like literally, like you really really
really I don't know how you could argue
with video evidence.
Like in a court of law, that's
different. That's the difference between
um legal and not legal uh and conviction
and not getting convicted. So
it did happen. It did happen.
But you're still arguing with video like
No, you didn't answer my question, Joe.
Did you forget the approaching videos
that I showed you? And do you know what
with the approaching videos? Yeah. You
know, the thing is, Grezy, it's not like
they spoke and they were nice and they
actually had boyfriends or they gave
feedback and think, okay, well, they
literally you can't even get a
conversation out of them.
That's the That was the weirdest thing,
bro. So, I mean, you're lying to
yourself if you don't think they're the
problem, bro. You really, really are
lying to yourself. You know, I've just
said I'll go out in the mall and do it,
but you're not interested.
I might go out today for a few beers. I
don't know, bro.
But I don't want to waste money getting
my hair done.
Nope. They don't give feedback.
And and do you accept that I'm a normal
looking person looking for a
relationship and dating apps don't work?
I mean, you're not interrupting their
day. You're doing a very masculine
thing. You're approaching people. Dating
apps don't work for most people. So,
you're doing a very masculine and a very
brave thing. And it's up for us. It's up
to us to do. And it's up to us to do.
Well, no one asked me to do it. Well,
they asked me to do it. Look, USA Izzy
liked me approaching.
That's why she gave me her booby longs.
So, you're what you're saying doesn't
make sense because some people actually
do like to be approached. That's how I
got in her knick-knocks. Greasy.
That's how I got her boobyongs. So, if
you So, if you
So, if you was to use that logic, Yeah.
Doesn't make sense, bro. Does it? [Laughter]
So, it doesn't make sense. Ah, boyfriend.
I fancy going to a shesh today,
but I don't want to spend too much
money. I don't want to start dipping
into my savings and [ __ ] Yikes.
Look, man. My hair and beard's quite
long, but I guess I could just wear a little cap.
I'm trying to think what I got to wear and [ __ ]
I'm not getting a haircut. No way am I
I'm all waiting around. I'm not spending £37.
I'm not sure.
I'm going to go definitely go for a piss
up today, I think.
What do you think of that? Greavves you
a good old piss up.
Probably get a burger and get on the
beer to be fair. One sec.
Are you going to be ready for it though, Grezy? Ah, boyfriend.
Are you sure you're going to be ready for it?
You know what? Some things there you
just never forget.
Right. Let me see what little clothes
I've got to wear. One second.
Give it a whirl. And it This is only cuz
I actually want to go out drinking. Like
I'm not even going to do any approach. I
don't care about these [ __ ] bro.
The money's going to start drying up
soon, mate. I'm going to have to start
selling my body on the street.
I'm going to have to start being like a USA, mate.
Right. Seriously though,
I've got a little pink dude. Should I
wear a little pink top? What about the
little pink top? I got a little pink top here.
Greavves. I got a little pink top. I'm
thinking maybe the pink top with the
jeans and the cap.
What's the weather saying? It's hot in
it. So, should be all right, mate. Yeah.
Bit creased, but should be all right.
I like pink, you know. I do like pink.
But, you know, you know, Virgin boy,
when I used to meet the virgin, he used
to say that the only color I would not
wear is pink. And that also goes to show
that he was very very insecure about his sexuality
which you know the whole Cheryl Cole
thing the little copycat. I want to
tickle him so bad. You know that it was
all because he's deep down a big gay and
he thought bro why wouldn't you wear
pink? Pink is stick color bro. Oh
actually I've got this DR t-shirt. Oh [ __ ]
Just stop my [ __ ] foot. Actually, I
got the t-shirt. Actually,
that'll get him in, mate. That'll get
him in. But I was going to wear the P
t-shirt, but at the end of the day,
right, it just go show that you're a
little virgin, mate. You're a little [ __ ] virgin.
I used to show that you're a [ __ ] virgin.
Oh, you need to be careful that [ __ ] blood.
You'd have some [ __ ] Oh, you'd have
some cunt's eye out with that.
You would literally have some cunt's eye
out with that.
Yeah, mate. You'll have some cunt's eye
out with that. I need to go for a drink.
I need a I need a [ __ ] break, mate. I
need a [ __ ] break.
Stop music. Can I show you the little outfit
and you can tell me if that's okay with you, boss?
Some of these are a bit creased. So, I'm hoping
I'm hoping that it would it will decrease
as you wear them. Only the bottoms are slightly creased.
Is that okay with you, boss?
So, I got the top, got the combats, got
the cap. I was going to wear the pink
t-shirt, but I didn't. Not going to. Obviously the trains.
I think it looks all right.
You think it looks all right?
They're a bit crease, but they should,
like I said, they should decrease.
You think it's all right?
I'm going to do it today, Grievy. I'm
going to hear fine.
Or I could wear the pink top. I could
either wear that that that with jeans. I
think this is the best thing. But I've
also got a teddy bear t-shirt I could wear.
What about the little teddy bear t-shirt?
I think it's that's the one, bro.
No, I think that's all right.
What do you think, Grezy? With the trainers
or wipe the hat a bit. So, yeah.
Yeah, I think I'm just going to I'm just
going to send it like that, bro. [ __ ] it.
Is that okay with you, boss?
I need it I need it confirmed first by you, bro.
Make sure I've got some [ __ ] stocks.
Oh, [ __ ] me. Here we go. Got some socks here.
You're not a fan of the top.
Well, I'm [ __ ] a fan of it. You can.
So, that's all that counts.
I'm trying to think if my beard and that needs
doing. No, I don't think so.
Think it's all right, mate. I'm going to
wear a cap anyways. Uh,
right. One second, bro.
I'm going to have a little shower. Oh,
you think I'm scared to do these
approaches, Grezy? Nah, mate.
No, mate. Not at all at all.
No, not at all at all. Obviously, that
one gets sent right. I need to
Yeah, I need to have a shower
and then get ready and then Yeah.
do that live in a bit, bro.