Get up there, boy. I guess he got
himself a number.
[ __ ] Oh my god,
bro. Jesus. I'm [ __ ] bro.
I can't lie.
Man, I am [ __ ] I just got a I just
got a bartender's number, man. I just
got a bartender's number, bro. I swear.
I can't, bro. I'm not even out my
[ __ ] area yet, bro. And we we we've
just started, bro. I only got one [ __ ] number.
Yeah, I just I just got on with a
[ __ ] I am [ __ ] drunk as [ __ ]
Hello PJ. Is that a [ __ ] picture of
Tiger? Your avatar? It is indeed. But
have you got a [ __ ] picture of time?
So Timmy, so Timmy, let's see your bit
of cash now. I've showed you 450. I
haven't been out the house yet, PJ. No,
Timmy, I showed you over I showed you
a,000. PJ, I've showed you four I can't
show you any more money until I get to
the bank. I've told you this. So do you
believe now? I get three grand a month.
I think you get about two and a half,
but I won't say three, Jimmy. I get I
get I get three, bro. I swear down,
Timmy. So, how the [ __ ] do you get three
grand? Like, I'm I'm not going to say
what rate pip I'm on and that lot, but
I'm on about two grand a month. So, how
I'm How the [ __ ] do you get a grand more
than me? I'm on exactly the same
benefit. I make money from YouTube.
How do you make [ __ ] money? How do
you make a grand a month off YouTube?
Because I do. But, Timmy, you do not
make a grand off. Of course I do. Yeah,
You're telling me porkies, Peter? No,
Timmy. I mean, I make I make some money
from YouTube, bro. You've been that
you've got you've had a big win on the
gambling and you're not telling anyone.
No, I haven't. I ain't won from gambling
for months, mate. It's dead. The
industry is dead. I promise you. So,
you're telling me the video? I I I tell
you what's happened today. You've been
paid your universal credit for the month
today, haven't you, Peter? What? Timmy,
I lost 200 yesterday and I just showed
you over a grand. But you might have got
paid. You might have got paid today.
That money what you had yesterday was
spare cash. No spare. Timmy, I'm going
out today. I'm going to probably spend
about 300 quid. What? You're going to
spend 300 quid on what a bird? Drinking
escorts, mate. You name it. I'm in it,
bro. You know what I'm saying? Are you
Are you going to go beat Shauny up? He
doesn't meet anyone. He's a [ __ ]
[ __ ] Timmy. You know this. I know
where I know where Shauny lives. Hey,
but you can agree. Hey, Timmy. I've been
to the [ __ ] area three times. You've
seen it though in it. You have seen it
yourself. Do you want to know where
Shauny lives? But have you seen me go
live in his area three times? You
haven't it? Don't lie. Yes, I know where
I know honestly. I know where Shauny
lives. Where? He lives in Liverminster.
No, he lives in Orington. No, he lives in Liverminster.
Where's that? You don't know where
Liverstster is in London? No, I can't
pronounce it correctly. Liverminster,
you know, outside for for [ __ ] sake.
I've been there before when I used to
[ __ ] troll you, but I still do troll
you. Do you know you know where Liver li
I can't pronounce it now. Do you know
that [ __ ] part of
London on the way to [ __ ] Brixton?
Brexton. Can you hear me, PJ? Yeah, I
can hear you. Yeah. What's it called?
Liverminster. Lam. Not pardon. Leam.
That's the one.
Yeah, he he lives there. I've even got
the door number of his road.
Really? Yeah. 22 Court Street. Hey, that
that Sean is a ratfaced little virgin.
Why don't you go to 22 Court Street and
go and give him a good kick in? He
doesn't live there, Timmy. He does. He
does. Go there. Honestly, go to
Levership. Timmy, where are you? Timmy,
where where are you? Wait, where are you
right now? I'm in Liveram.
No, seriously. I'm in Liveram. Okay,
meet me today then. I'm there now. Meet
me there now. We'll go big. Oh, you're
[ __ ] [ __ ] to me. I'm going to have
to kick you, bro. I got a bartender's
number, Harry. I was chatting her up,
bro. I got this bartender's number. I
can't lie. You know what I'm saying? I
got a number, bro. I got a number. I got
an hour. I got a number, bro. Many more
to come, bro. We just come out. We just
come back for a little break. A little
teeth brush. A little
toothbrush. Little teeth brush. And then
we're going to go out again today. But I
got some nice after shave to spraying
that. Oh yeah. I'm having a piss. I'm looking fresh.
See? Yeah. I showed these people money
grievy and they didn't show me nothing.
I just got a bartender's number, bro. I
showed uh £1,000 and
£1,080 and no one showed me nothing.
That's what happened to the money game. We look
back. I showed 1,080. No one showed me nothing except
Baz and I got a bartender's
number. Yeah, man. I I was like, let me
pursue it. I was talking to her for a
little bit in it. I thought, oh, she's
got big tits and that
it need to get that there number. You
know what I mean?
Yeah. Yeah. Bad show money that no no one else
did. But guess what though? Guess what,
Harry? I've got more money than Mr.
Rodent Face. I've got more money than
the rodent face. The rat face bastard.
Oh. Yeah, mate. I I I took out cash for Tibby.
probably got a bartender's number. I'm a crazy
bastard. Everybody knows that you're a crazy [ __ ]
me to me before um
Greavvesy. That was what somebody said
to me before Greavvesy. I'll tell you
what they said. Do you know what they
said to me?
You know what I said to
me? I'm [ __ ] bro.
Look at that fade, bro. That's a banger.
You're telling me that's not a banger,
bro? Look at that fade. Only got a
bartender's number. Look at that fade,
bro. You're telling me that's not a
banger. Look at that to me. You're
telling me that's not a [ __ ] banger.
Oh, that's a banger, bro. Look at that.
Look at that, bro. That's banger,
bro. That's a [ __ ] banger, bro.
There is I showed you some money, you
[ __ ] pratt. It's not my You showed me
400 quid. What? Only 400 quid cuz you
can't have yours in the bank cuz you got
no cuz you're back because you're blacklisted.
I took it from the bank. Oh, that's fair
comment. At least you can have yours in
the bank. Baz can't cuz he hasn't got
any credit rating. Timmy, but why but
why do you want to show the need to show
money, PJ? If I Cuz you kept asking me
cuz you kept asking me to show money.
You the one who brings it up all the
time. You're money obsessed. Okay,
Timmy, let me ask you this question.
Yeah, PJ, if I want to ask if I wanted
to get 10 grand, I could show you 10
grand, but I don't show the need to show
more ones. Let me ask you Let me ask you
this question, Timmy. Okay. Yeah. If you
was on £1,000 a month. Yeah.
How would you could you afford to go to
America or No, couldn't PJ. Yeah. So,
how would you be able to do it then? You
couldn't do it. PJ, at the end of the
day, you I'm not saying you, I'm saying
example, could you or PJ, we all know,
let's be will that you you'll be skinned
again in two weeks. [ __ ] pissed off.
[ __ ] squint. Okay. When you a few
weeks ago when you were [ __ ] mega
triggered and I remember that stream
when you were mega triggered, PJ, you
answer my question. Timmy, you didn't
answer my question though. Yeah. So, if
you was on a,000 pound a month, how long
how could you go to America? Is it
impossible or not impossible? Well, it
depends on your circumstances. If you
live with your parents like Baz and you
pay no rent and no bills, then it's
possible because you can put money easily away.
Yeah, but it's hard to be harder. If you
live with your parents like Harry Ford
and Baz and you [ __ ] can't stand on
your own two feet, then yeah, it's
possible to go to America because you're
not spending any bills, are you? Relying
on your mom and dad to pay for
everything. Yeah, but how long would it
take to save up for? I [ __ ] don't
know. If you stayed in your mom's house,
if you stayed in your box room for a
month and spent 200 quid a month, not
that long, about what [ __ ] four
months and you can go to America.
Imagine that though, Timmy. [ __ ]
hell. What? Being stuck in your Well,
your friend Baz hasn't got a social
life. He spends all day in his parents'
gaff. Yeah, I get 3.3K a month, Timmy.
Really? Is that London?
Yeah. Is that London rates on benefits
now? I take it. No, I do other thing but
benefits, bro. I got my ways.
When you have a brain to me, it's very
easy to make money when you got a brain.
PJ, I know you're not making money.
We've seen your credit file. You've got
a credit card. Okay, I'm making everything.
Okay. Okay. I can even name the credit
card. Okay. Okay. It's a Barclay card.
All right. Okay.
Why don't we show us your Barclay card,
Peter? Okay, Tibus. How do I go to
Amsterdam then? With your Barkley card.
You've never been to Amsterdam? Yes, I
have. PJ, you haven't. Timmy, I know
you. Yes, I have. PJ, I was I've been
there at 19. Yes, I have. Okay, PJ, I
can tell you what countries I've been to
right now. Switzerland, Portugal. I'
I've not been out of all Europe. I'm not
going to lie. I've been to Switzerland,
Portugal, France, Germany. Um, yeah, but
you know, you know
Antman, you know, you know Antman, he's
in Thailand right now. He goes three
times a year. Yeah, but I don't want to
go to Thailand, PJ. I'll get I'll get AIDS. Yeah.
So, yeah, I want to go to Thailand. The
last time I knew somebody went to
Thailand, they died of AIDS. Yeah, it
happens. Yeah. He got bumped by a
[ __ ] lady man and died. Yeah. So
PJ, we all know today was your monthly
payment on the Universal Credit.
So how much money do you think I have
now? I reckon in two weeks you'll be
down to [ __ ] 120 quid. Yeah. But how
much money do you think I have now? I'll
be honest with you. I'd say you probably
got about three grand now.
So how would I be down to 200? Because
you'll end up doing 200 quid a day in
Fishing Frenzy Plus. Then you [ __ ]
cry on your bollocks. PJ, I know how you
work. You'll be bored shitless and
you'll do your bollocks in the casino or
the [ __ ] arcade. Nah, bro. No way.
I'm going out today. Send it. I'm I'm on
a drink today, bro. I'm I'm I know what
will happen. You'll end up in [ __ ]
Lester Square Casino at 2 in the morning
pissed up. Then you'll be crying that 11
didn't come in. Nah. Nah. Not at all.
Not at all. I know the future. PJ. Nah.
And Timmy, you're Timmy, you're the one
that he might be on a bit of a winning
streak at the moment, but it always ends
in tears. But here's the thing, Timmy.
You're the one that sublets. I don't
sublet. Yes, you do. How can I sublet,
PJ? If I live in a one-bedroom flat. You
used to sublet. Yes, you did. What the
[ __ ] are you on about? I've never
subleted in my life. Yes, you [ __ ]
did. So, who do I used to sublet to
then, Mr. Genius? Well, money might have
told me you used to sublet. No, I've
never subleted. I don't know who [ __ ]
tells you your information. You're an
idiot. Okay, PJ, I would never have a
lodger. [ __ ] never. Yeah, you have,
PJ. I've never had a lodger since I was
[ __ ] 19. Sorry, 22. The last time I
had a lodger, I was 22 years old. You
still Do you still make money from
YouTube? No, PJ. How much did you used
to make? Like £400 a month? No, PJ. I
was lucky to make £200 a month. Yeah,
but there was this guy on YouTube
before. He said he made 40 grand a month
on YouTube. Is that [ __ ] Okay. PJ,
is that is that bull? Is that [ __ ]
It depends on your subscribers and
viewers. He had like 1 million
followers. Yeah, that's that's possible.
Yeah. What? £40,000?
Well, £40,000 a year. Yeah. No, a month.
A month? No. You used to get a month?
Yeah. his donations and [ __ ] was getting
that sort of money. But that's a lot of
money it to me. Yeah, but PJ, seriously,
right? That's a lot of money to me. I
can read the future.
You will [ __ ] be skin in two weeks
and you'll be doing your waving streams
and you'll be [ __ ] angry throwing
chairs at the computer
[ __ ] Red Star will be loving the
download button and you watch
Red Star's watching, you know.
once, bro. You know, Wedstar's watching
you as we speak right now. Yeah, cuz
he's a stalker. He ain't got life.
So, even it was Wedar who's wrote a post
and he said, "I can see the future. PJ
will be skinned in two weeks." Yeah. Is
that what he said? Yes. Oh, really? And
and he said that you're a virgin in the
blowjob's the best thing you're ever
going to get. Read his communal post.
says the only thing you can get is a
[ __ ] because you're an ugly [ __ ]
m. Yeah, he is a man. He is skin and he [Music]
m. Do you know what I love about you,
Red Star? Yeah. You've always got a um
screenshot um videos where I like make
faces. I love that. I love that me.
I love that. Me, bro. I love how you've
got a screenshot where I make faces. I love
that cuz you know you can't do it
normally cuz you know [ __ ]
better looking than you, [ __ ]
I'm saying. Yeah, it's true. Is it?
That's the truth,
lad. I need to go out a bit, bro.
Is a guy in a bizil
that you speak the truth to
me. I need to go a bit, bro. I need to
go out and sing a
bit. You reckon I should put the old stony
on? I would give it a whirl. I would.
What do you think, Timmy? Put the old
stony on. I'll keep this
Um, quite warm outside, isn't it?
So, you're always alone. Lewisville
Slugger. Guess what, bro? Guess what
though, you little failed troll. I just
got a woman's number and I'm going to go
out today. You little skinned little
[ __ ] loner. You little failed troll.
I'm not going to block you. I'm not
going to block you. Look at them gappy
teeth, mate. I'm better looking than you
will ever be. You [ __ ] ugly [ __ ] You
little ugly YouTube dependent little
[ __ ] Bro, I'm going to put a
jumper on right now. Yeah, that you
can't afford and I'm going to keep it
on, mate. I've had more women than
you'll ever have. Bro, the gap in my
teeth. There's no gap in my teeth. You
little [ __ ] ugly [ __ ] You little
ugly keyboard lawyer. Yeah, you little
ugly [ __ ] Little downy. Thinking that
you can come on my channel and try and
troll me. You little downey. You fat
ugly virgin downy. Thinking that you can
come on here. Yeah. And thinking that
you can troll me, you little dowy. Suck
your mom, you little [ __ ] Go and slug
your mom, you little [ __ ] Yeah, bro.
Let me put on a jumper that you can't
afford. You little dowy. You little
[ __ ] Little virgin. Mate, you can say
whatever you want, mate. But guess what?
You're the downy little virgin [ __ ]
that can't show his face cuz he's so
ugly. And guess what? I got a woman's
number today and I'm going to be getting
more women's number. You little dowy.
Dowy little [ __ ] And you're not going
to do nothing about it. You're not going
to do nothing. You little dowy. Special
needs. You little special needer. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. And I am having a laugh. I'm
having a laugh with you as well. You're
a Downey with special needs and your mom
sucks dick for a couple of biscuits.
You're a Downey. A down syndrome. And
I'm having a laugh with you as well. And
what are you going to do about it? You
going to beat me? You're not going to
beat no one, mate. You're not going to
do nothing to no one. Yeah, I'm having a
laugh with you as well, you little
[ __ ] downy with your slaggy little
mum. I'm having a laugh with you, mate.
It's just banner. We're having a wable
time. You're not getting blocked. You
and your little downy face, mate. You're
not getting blocked, bro. I don't need
to block you. You're a little downy. Why
do I need to block a down syndrome that
that repeats himself? I don't need to
block you, bro. For what reason? Come on,
man. You know, you little downy [ __ ]
You little fat ugly m. You fat ugly m.
Yeah, bro. You need to tell yourself
that, bro. You've made about a million
accounts to co-respond with me, bro. You
don't need to take it serious, you
little downy. I'm not taking it serious.
You know, you little [ __ ] You little
down syndrome. But what I'm saying is
don't come on my channel trying to
[ __ ] troll me. You never you mind
where I'm going, you little [ __ ]
Little down. I'm going up your mom's
[ __ ] That's where I'm going. You want
to know where I'm going? I'm going up
your mum's vagina. Your mum's [ __ ]
That's where I'm going, mate. You can
get me banned from your mama's [ __ ]
There you go. Your mama's [ __ ] You want
my address? I'll give you my address if
you want. You're not going to come
anywhere, mate. You're not going to come
anywhere. I'm going to go up your mama's
[ __ ] and you're going to watch me do it
and you're going to do nothing about it
when I'm up your mama's [ __ ] Little
keyboard warrior. Shut the [ __ ] up,
[ __ ] Shut the [ __ ] up, [ __ ] How can
you mate? Listen, listen, listen. You're
a [ __ ] ugly little monk that gets
banned on every single account. Yeah, I
turned my camera off, bro. My camera's
on right now. [ __ ] you. I'm better
looking than you will ever be. You're an
ugly fat little manta that can't troll
to save his life. I've got more money
than you. I'm better looking than you.
You're an ugly fat fat. So keyboard
warrior little manta with no money.
There we go, bro. You're an ugly little
[ __ ] that can't show his face. Go and
[ __ ] [ __ ] your mom's [ __ ] You little
[ __ ] up. Yeah. Listen one second. Hold
on. Hold on. I'm going to put my camera
back on, bro. Your voice crack. My voice
didn't crack, mate. Over you. You little
MTO. your slaggy little mom, mate. Over
you, bro. Listen, listen, listen, mate.
I'm talking about you and your ugly mom.
And you're not going to do nothing to
me. You're not going to do nothing to
me, mate. You're the one that keeps
making accounts. You need to calm down.
You and your fat ugly mom. And I'll give
you my address anytime you want, bro.
I've got a gap in my teeth. Okay, bro.
Listen, you are an ugly fat [ __ ] on
benefits that keeps getting banned on
YouTube. Sort your life out, you ugly
[ __ ] Oh, one second. I'll get this out
for Lord J as well. Give me my I'll give
you my address. I'll give you my
address, mate. You're a little keyboard
warrior. Suck your mom. Suck out your
mom, bro. Listen. How many accounts,
bro? Listen. Listen. How many accounts
do you make and you keep getting banned?
Go and suck out your mom. You little
virgin. Your little virgin little
quitter on a grand a month. Oh, sorry.
£300 a month, bro. Come on now.
Yeah. Listen, Lewisville Slugger, you're
a Downey. I love it when when you come
on my channel and you try to troll me.
It's it's amazing because you're so much
of a Down syndrome. You're so thick and
so disabled that we know it's you. We
know because you're so disabled. You're
such a disabled [ __ ] and such a downy
with your ugly mom who's [ __ ] shag
for packet of biscuits. We know it's
you. One second, bro. I'm actually going
to change it up, bro. One sec, bro. I'm
actually changing it up. Hey, one
second. Hey, Timmy. One sec, bro. We're
changing up the gear, man. Easy on the
old John. I got a passport. I got a
passport, bro. I got a bartender's
number. I got a bartender's number, bro.
Fred, I got a bartender's number, lad. A
number. And I showed Timmy over £1,000
and he couldn't show me nothing. Lewis
feel, you're a little m. Shut up, you
little keyboard warrior. Go and suck out
your mom. Isn't it mad how I can say all
of this madness to you and you can't do
a thing about it? Listen, you want the
address? Go and suck out your mom. She
will give you the address. Your little
keyboard lawyer. Bye-bye now, little
virgin. Yeah. Listen. Wait. I'm going to
put my camera back on. She was
kinking. Bro, I got Bro, I haven't even
left my area yet.
G. I ain't even left my area yet.
Listen, mate. I'm telling you what I'm
putting on, bro. Hold on.
I might It's actually quite warm outside today to
be I think it is actually quite
warm. So I reckon this could be
it. I think the old
Stony. Yeah, good old Stony, man. Yes, boys. I
reckon I reckon I can actually do it,
man. What are you saying?
Good old stone. Yeah,
man. I got the passport picture there.
So, here. Good old stone, bro. You already know,
[ __ ] Timmy, you couldn't have bought
that. A gap between my teeth. Bro,
listen. No matter what negative comments
that you try to write, you're not going
to stop the madness. You're not going to
stop the madness. I've got a gap between
my teeth. Okay, bro. Cool. Good for you.
You're not going to stop the madness.
Good for you, bro. You're not going to
stop the madness, bro. With Estonia on.
You and Oh, no one is going to stop the
madness. You can project your ugliness
all you want, bro. Look at my hand.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Good for you. You're
not going to stop the
madness. Isn't that right, bro? The
madness ain't getting stopped.
Never. I don't think so. No. The madness
ain't getting stopped, bro.
Yeah. Why don't I wash my hair? Cuz I
don't want to. Suck your mom. Why don't
you go [ __ ] your mom, you little [ __ ]
How about that one, you little
[ __ ] Bye-bye, little [ __ ] That's not
even RJ, by the way. Bye-bye, [ __ ]
Never get rejected as much as you people.
people, mate. That's a mazer. We can
never get rejected as much as these people, bro.
Trust. Never get rejected as much as
these people. These ugly little
mongos. I'm thinking, should I wear the
stone island or should I just like not
wear the stone island?
What do you think, PJ? PJ, why are you
so [ __ ] triggered?
Timmy, how much a jumper costs? About
300 quid, PJ, I've got one. Yeah, £3300.
Timmy. Yes, PJ. So, what what what's a
300 pound top? Is it going to feed you?
Is it going to [ __ ] get you [ __ ] Is
it going to get you a [ __ ] Yeah.
This is so PJ, you could wear that top
for 20 years and you'll still be a
virgin. Timmy, I've already proved I had
sex. You haven't had sex. You've had a
[ __ ] [ __ ] is not
Timmy, I've already proved to you. PJ,
having a [ __ ] is not losing your
virginity. Timmy, I've shown me in bed
with women in hotel rooms.
You've had sex. I could lie next to her
now. It doesn't mean I'm going to have
sex with her. Timmy, come on. Stop being
silly now. PJ, you're the one who's
being silly. You've got £1,000. No
woman, no friend. I've got over £1,000.
I got over,000. Try again. Even [ __ ]
bangers owning you today. Timmy, I've
shown you over Timmy, I showed you over
£1,000. You can show me nothing. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. PJ, I've got what? 950
quid, but I'm going out with friends
this weekend. Give me my 900 quid.
You've got £1,000 and you're all by
yourself. More than £1,000. Try again.
£3,000. But you'll be It doesn't matter
how fast I've got to me. I've just shown
you money. You can't show me nothing.
End PJ. I've just showed you 430 quid.
If you think that's And I showed you
I've showed you 1100 quid cuz I can read
the future. PJ, in two weeks you're
going to be skinned. I'm going to be
flush and I'm and I'm going to say to
you is a lot of money. So when you got
no money, PJ and I'll show you 500 quid.
You're not going to say that's nothing
on your ass. I showed you over £1,000
PJ. It doesn't matter what you showed
me. I guarantee you in two weeks. It
doesn't matter to me. I showed more
money than you. It doesn't matter who
shows more money or who, PJ. It's you
got It's not about the money game, PJ.
It's about who can hold it the longest.
Timmy, I'm going upstairs. PJ, can you
hold that £1,000 for over? Yes. £1,000
is nothing to me, Timmy. I get over
three grand a month. Try again,
PJ. There's a lot of people on three
grand a month. Three grand. Not you,
Timmy. Not you. It's not you, PJ.
[ __ ] three grand's nothing. This
climate, mate. There [ __ ] people.
Timmy. Timmy. I get more than you a
month. PJ, you don't get three grand a
month. your [ __ ] Okay, I don't get
Okay. Okay. So, you're making this money
on YouTube, PJ. How are you making this
money on YouTube? Okay, I'm not going to
answer no more questions anymore.
Okay, I'm lying. I don't get through. I
just showed you over If you make money
on YouTube, it's very It's very easy to
answer the question. Do you make the
money on ads? Do you get sponsorships?
Obviously, it's adverts, you idiot. So,
you're telling me you make £1,100 a
month on adverts? More than that? Yeah.
Oh my words, you are the worst liar on
YouTube. Okay, Timmy. Bye-bye now. All
right, look at all of these little
negative fat mongos trying to stop the
madness. They're trying to stop me going
out. These little fat ugly mongos. Hey
Fred, these little fat ugly mongos are
trying to stop the madness, bro. Imagine
that. To stop the [ __ ] madness. Yeah.
Due to anxiety, I'm very anxious. Yes,
bro. Yeah, it's supposed to be messy.
I'm leaving it like that. I want it to
be messy. It's supposed to be messy.
Yeah, it's supposed to be messy, bro.
That's the style of it, bro. Yeah. Good
old Stony. Listen,
bro. What was I saying is uh Look at
these ugly fat mongos. YouTube dependent
mongos trying to stop the madness.
They're trying to stop the madness in
their little beds, bro. It's a [ __ ] madness, bro.
It's a madness that they're trying to stop the
madness. Probably going to put a coat on to be
fair. It will never stop, bro. These
people right that say that you've got a
gap between your [ __ ] tooth that
you're this that you're that one. One
second. I need to go piss, bro. It's
they're fat ugly little mongos. These
people right that say all of these
things. Oh, you're this, you're that.
They're fat and they're fat, ugly little virgins.
They're fat, ugly little [ __ ] little
virgins that ain't got a life and they
ain't got the confidence to go out and
get women. So, they're trying to put you
down to their level. That's what it is,
bro. Look, I just showed I went out
today, bro. I showed money. Yeah. These
people can't show me nothing. These people are
selfreflectors. That's what they are.
You got a gap between your teeth, your
this, bro. These people are the same
ugly virgins that have been doing this
[ __ ] now for [ __ ] years, bro.
Yeah. They don't bother people. What?
They're just self-p
projecting. Everything they say is a
self-reflection of their own [ __ ]
lives. Do you not understand? They
selfreflect. Fat ugly skin is all of
them. Think of it, bro. I just went to
the cash point. I would do over a grand
and no one could show me nothing. They're
selfreflectors. They're downies. Just
like that. Lewisville slugger. He's a
downy. Listen, you understand, bro. As
you get to that point,
bro, Sony's good. He's in good shape.
So, yeah, man.
So, just chilling for a bit. I'm going
to go out again. Spend it all night,
man. Spend it all night, bro. Yes,
that's what then I probably need to get
dry clean to be fair.
This story has been going a long while now, [Music]
bro. Yeah, you need these people because
you have now to speak to. Yeah, I've got
no one to speak to. But what I'm saying,
Baz, is these people that say, "Oh,
you're this, you're that." They're just
[ __ ] ugly mongos. Let me give you an
example, bro. Look at that [ __ ]
what's his name? That um that bomb. You
remember that bomb when he used to talk
about people's looks? Oh, you're this.
Oh, you're that. Oh, you're this. What
did he end up looking like, bro? Tell
us, G. What did he end up looking like?
Fat ugly [ __ ] And that's my whole
point, though, is that these people,
they selfreflect their own lives onto
other people. Fat, ugly skin, [ __ ]
virgin. It's all them, bro. They
self-reflect. They look Selfrelecting little self-reflecting. Self-reflecting.
Self-reflecting little mongos. I ain't
going to lie. Well, on YouTube every
day. No life but YouTube. Yeah,
bro. No life but the YouTube. So every
all of these people that say like you
got a gap between your teeth, you're
this, you're that, bro. They're insecure
fat, ugly little [ __ ] Think about it
like this, bro. Look, I show my face. I
don't mind showing my face. I don't
care. These people can't show their face
cuz they're too ugly. That's the
difference, bro. You know what I'm
saying, bro? These people will never
stop me showing my face. These people
will never stop the madness. Yeah, these
people are fat and ugly. They ain't got
a life. They're little
munters. They're no life but your job.
As I would say to Grezy, you
understand? Yeah, man.
up and up. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And I've
been seen with many women. I know he's
been seen with no women. And I've been
seen with how many exactly the lad. And
how many women have I been seen with?
And how many women have I been seen with Marmite?
with? There we
go. There we
go. And how much money have I been seen with as
well? There we go, dude. There we [ __ ] go,
man. I love my hair, bro. I don't think can sit
me. Don't let these ugly fat mongos try
and bring you down, man. In their mum's
bed sit on £300 a month. Ain't got a
life. It's why they do what they do
every day, cuz they got nothing.
It's why they do what they do every day.
Cuz they ain't got [ __ ] nothing in
their lives but YouTube. You understand
me? You understand me,
boss? [ __ ] in their life. They're fat,
ugly little virgins. They ain't got
fuckle of being a keyboard while we are
on YouTube every day. Think about it, bro.
That's it, bro. Man's got a bar, bro.
Man's got a [ __ ] bartender's number.
I ain't even I ain't even left my [ __ ] area,
lad. Yeah, I'm always feeling better,
bro. I'm just talking about these little
[ __ ] Like, these people will never
stop me showing my face. These people
will never stop no madness. They're just
fat, ugly little projectors. They don't
bother no one. I've been saying,
"Bro, I've been saying this from day
one." Yeah, I'm always feeling good,
bro. Don't worry about me, man. I'm
good, bro. Already got a bartender's
number. I look thinner. How do I look
thinner? I was never fat. How can I look
thinner when I was never
fat? Nope. Different
Bob. I look thinner. That's strange. Cuz
I was never fat to begin with. So, don't
know who you wear that one out, but we'll
continue. How can I look thinner when I
was never fat to begin
with? Strange, eh? Uh, we got one bar.
Um, we're on a drink, we're on the
piss, and uh I got one bartender's
number, and I'll be going out again
shortly to get some more numbers. Yeah,
I was going to offer her money, to be honest.
I was to be honest, but I got her number
anyways. I know where she works. So,
just calling it. Yeah, I could have.
would. Yeah, I would give it a
Well, but we'll wait a little bit in it.
We'll wait a little bit, bro. How can
you say that I look
thinner when I was never fat to begin
with? That doesn't even make sense.
No, I was in my area. I just got this
bartender's number in it. We're going to
hit We're going to hit the nightclub soon,
bro. Yeah, if she ghost after a day,
then I'll go back in there, isn't it? I
know she works in it and offer her
money. Yeah, I'll offer her money in it.
We got the cash, bro. Is it? So, it
ain't no problem, mate. It ain't no
[ __ ] problem, bro.
Yeah, I go where I want, wherever I [ __ ] want,
mate. But all of these little mongos
that try to say you got greasy hair,
you're this, you're that. N they're all
fat, ugly little virgins like
Lewisville, Slugger, Traumadal. They're
all fat, ugly little virgins, mate. No
one no one takes notice of them. They're
just, like I said, bro, they're just little
self-reflectors. They're just little
self-reflectors that ain't going
anywhere. No one cares about these all
virgins. These are all low lives can't
get off YouTube. That
can't no life but YouTube. They can't
get off YouTube cuz it's the whole life.
The whole existence. It's all there ever
be is YouTube. You know life. You no life but
YouTube. Yeah. And that's it, bro.
That's it. I'm going to smash it today.
100. Yeah, he's nothing to do with
London. That little rodent face, that
little virgin, that little rat face skin
virgin, he is not from any He's nothing
to do with London. I don't know how many
times I have to say this. That little
virgin is nothing to do with London.
That little [ __ ] virgin with a little
rat face. I'd rather have a big nose
than be a [ __ ] rat looking [ __ ] like
him. [ __ ] virgin. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah,
man. But we'll be out today, bro. We'll
be sending the
uh He's from Play. He looks like a rat.
Don't he look like a rat, bro? Look.
Look at me. Look at my face. Yeah, my
face is normal. I look normal. Yeah, he
actually looks like a [ __ ] rat. He
looks like a rat. Don't Hey, I swear he
looks like a rat. For real. For real,
bro. He looks like a [ __ ] ugly rat.
And he tries to talk about people's
noses. It's crazy,
bro. And he looks like a [ __ ] rat.
Yeah, I'm sending it,
bro. I'm going to brush my teeth. One
sec. I'm going to brush my teeth. I'll
come back. One
sec. Be right back. I'm going to brush my teeth. I'm back
to There we go.
You know what's so mad is that these
people like Virgin Sea with a rat face
can only try to talk about my nose, but
I can talk about everything. His chin,
his ugly face that looks like it's been
thrown acid on. He looks like a rat.
He's balding. He looks imbred. Like I
can talk about a million things but one.
He's ugly. He's on a grown a month. He's
skint. He can't go out and have a proper
drink like I'm going to be doing
today with the keys. And he's just an ugly
rat. You know what I'm saying, bro? And
that's and that's the difference.
There's a big
difference. The big difference,
dad. That's the big
difference. You understand, bro? Yeah.
These little mongos like Lewisville
Slugger, these little disabled [ __ ]
spackers that can't get up on YouTube
are not going to stop the madness
because we know, bro, that anyone they
try to call ugly, they are they are a
million times uglier. That's why they
don't show their face cuz they know
they're ugly. That's why they come on
here under a fake account trying to say,
"Oh, this person looks like this. This
person looks like that." But we know, me
and you know in reality these people are
ugly [ __ ] You understand,
bro? They're ugly
[ __ ] you know. And that's the truth, lad. Yeah.
Got a pass bes as
well. Yes, boy. We got that sorted, too.
Good, man. What's time? Three. It's
almost four. We need to get moving soon,
bro. Woohoo. We need to get moving.
Yep. Yeah. It's sad how how much these
people hate themselves that they have to
come on here trying to talk about the
way other people look and this and that.
Like it's mad how they have to sit on
here and hate on other people when in
reality they're fat ugly little virgins.
It's It's crazy, bro. It is. It's
madness. It's a madness if there ever
was to uh if there ever was to be one. Yeah.
I ain't even had it dry cleaned, bro.
Since I've had it, I've never I've not
had it dry cleaned. Oh, bro. One second.
One second. One sec. I need to get my [ __ ]
ready. Uh, bro, bye-bye now. One second,
bro. One sec. One sec. One sec. One sec, lad.
Bro, I'm a good-looking guy. Thank you,
man. I know I'm good-looking. Thank
you. Thank you. I'm really I really am a
[ __ ] manta. Stop talking about
yourself. It's not nice to talk about
yourself like that. Putting the old
trousers on, then the dias on,
[ __ ] Already got a bartender's
number. But we're going to be getting
[ __ ] more numbers today, bro. There's
nobody that Nope. Nobody but me. Nobody
me. Oh, thanks for calling me
good-looking, man. I really appreciate
that. Yeah, thank you. I know that I'm
not ugly like these little mongos. They
just self-reflect. They just talk about
themselves every day. So, they they
never used to bother us to begin with,
bro. To be honest, because what it is
with this community, right, let me tell
you what it is with this community. They
talk about their own lives. Skin ugly.
No friends. It's all themselves. Night
sky talking. It doesn't bother us. Well,
doesn't bother me. I don't know about
like Monty or all these other people.
They don't bother me because they just
talk about themselves every day. It's
only their own lives that they're
talking about. Bro, you could come on
here looking like my [ __ ] brat
[ __ ] pit, bro. And they would still
call you [ __ ] ugly. You get me, bro?
They talk about their own selves, their
own existence, their own reality. Like
the trousers, bro. Getting it. Oh, man. There you
go. Yeah. I got this bartender's number,
bro. She had
some Yeah. This is why my area as well.
So, yeah. And we we've only just
started, mate. Imagine that. We've only
just started. We have only just started,
lad. Thanks for calling me good-looking
though, man. Thanks. It means a lot to
not get hate for a change. Thanks,
man. I'm going out. Good old Stony,
mate. Good old
stone. Yeah, mate.
Oh, up. Look at these trousers. Up, down,
Ass. Yeah, bro. Up, down, up. You know
what I mean? Stephen
Howard. Yeah, I know. I know I'm not
ugly. I never said I'm good-looking, but
listen. I'm saying that I know that I'm
not ugly like these [ __ ] These people
self-reflect. This is what I'm saying,
bro. These people self-reflect their own
lives onto other people. What they say
don't bother no one. This is what I'm
trying to say to you. I ain't got a blue
stony. It's not my mom's. This one's
good, ain't it? This one's a banger. But
guess what I'm going to put on in a
minute? I'm going to show you,
[ __ ] This is another thing
these people on YouTube can't afford. One
sec. One sec. These thoughts up a little
bit too much. Hold on. All these people
do like sky talking is talk about
themselves. That has to sort of go down, I think.
Yeah, I got a bit fat. One sec. They
only talk about their own fat ugly
lines. Why do every day?
Listen, if you be good
tomorrow, if you be good
tomorrow, I will do a black vlog for
you. How about that one? If you be good,
you have to be on your best behavior, Zippy.
And I will I will do a Blackpool vlog for you,
man. I will do a Blackpool vlog for you.
How's about that,
boss? I think that's sick, isn't it?
Guess what after save we're putting on?
Come on. Guess what after save we're putting
on. Here we go. Yeah. Here we go, lad.
70 worth here. Obviously, it's a bit out
of a a certain virgin's price range. A
little rat face. It's a bit out of rat
faces um rat faces price range. You
know, the ugly [ __ ] with the rat face.
The the the knots. The the [ __ ] with no
teeth. The the virgin. Yeah. Um yeah,
it's a bit out of his price range, but
it gets us smelling really [ __ ] good.
You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
Yeah, it's a [ __ ] banger, bro. I was
spray all over me,
man. Oh, mate. Come on, C. Come
on. Yeah, I'll leave when I'm
ready. Oh, come on. This is going to get
the [ __ ] today, bro. We only got one bartender's
number. This is going to get the [ __ ] in.
This is going to get the [ __ ] [ __ ]
in, mate. Yeah, stop self-reflecting. Go
self-reflect on another channel. You little
spacker. Yeah, you little spacker.
Bye-bye. I don't support West Ham. I hate
football. I'm just taking it in, you
know. I'm just taking it in that [ __ ]
bag of eyes. I'm just taking it in. [Music]
Oh, it's a bagger, bro. I ain't even
sprayed a [ __ ] yet. I think I
got about half
left. Obviously, out of a certain
virgin's uh price range. I'm not going
to get into
that. Who's going to pay for the little
stonies? If I was on a grind a month, uh
Grevy, who's going to pay for the little
stonies? Who's going to pay for the stonies, bro?
Who's going to pay for the [ __ ]
Stonies, bro? Come on. Who's going to
pay for him, bro? Who's going to pay for
him when the money dries up? If the
money dries up, who's going to pay for
the good old
Stonies? There we go, bro.
I hear water. Who's going to pay for it
though? Greasy. Come on. Who's going to
pay for it? It's a true question.
Huh? Who's going to pay for a
greasy? Yeah, that's what that's what's
going to have to [ __ ] pay for him,
mate. Cuz a grand up just ain't going to
do. We can't live on Sean's pittance. Pittance
money, you know. Grand a month. He's on
a grand a
month. Oh, look at that. Grand a month.
Just won't do us. Oh, get it on
me. Come on. Oh, that is lush. That's
what you call lush. Oh, mate.
That is what you call [ __ ] lush,
mate. £170 worth of after shave. I think
I got holes in these buttons as well,
but no one's going to see it. Yeah,
we're going to feel the madness, bro. Madness.
Hot dogs and burgers. Peter Belly's pork
chops, mate. That's what it's going to
be. Peter Belly's pork chops. So, Fred,
what happened to um So, what happened to USA Izzy
then? It's not going to stay in the
Stony, man. Going to get the
[ __ ] dry clean tomorrow. So,
what happened to So, what happened to
USA Izzy then? Um Fred
What happened to USA Izzy then?
No. What happened to USA, bro? Oh,
sorry. One sec. I need to turn the
camera off. Hold on one
minute. I'm going to have to turn the
camera on. One
sec. Wait, there we go. There we go.
What happened to you? What happened to
you, USA? What happened? What happened to you?
Yeah. Oh, that is lost, mate. That is
[ __ ] last to add the
shame. Taking a baby away from its
mama. That was a That was a [ __ ]
class one. That was
You remember that though? Remember that.
Grezy taking a baby away from it
mama. Taking a baby away from its
mama. Peter Benny can't get attached now
because he's already found his mama. Oh,
crazy. That's a
madness. Because he's already found his mama.
He's already found his mama. What
happened with the new channel? Uh Stony
on by the way. Uh what happened with the
new channel is
um yeah, I had to get a new channel cuz
my main one uh the other one got banned.
So that's kind of what happened. Bit of
a bollocks, but
yeah, cuz he's already Hey, what
happened to my mama? Fred, come on, bro.
What actually happened with my mama?
A stony is a stone
island, you know. Good old Stony. So why
why did my mommy leave me then,
Fred? Cuz he's already found his mama.
Oh, that's so cute. He already found his
mama. Yes. I love it. You never heard of
Stone Island, mate? Well, you [ __ ]
have. Now you can.
A look at that sick, bro. Yeah. Good,
bro. Nah, not tonight. But that was two
years ago. Fred, but I'm asking you,
Fred, what happened to my
mama? I'm asking you, Fred, what
happened to my mama? Huh?
What happened to my mama?
Red to my
mama. Yeah, you keep telling yourself that,
buddy. Yeah, but did she she left her
son though, Fred? She left her son. How
could she leave her son like
that? That's child abuse. Leaving your
son like that. No. Taking a baby away
from its mama. Oh, that is not even
funny, bro. That's actually quite sad.
Taking a baby away from its mama. Now,
who else is going to give me the milk and nutrients?
Greavvesy. The milk and nutrients from
her boobies. A bless you. You in your little
ways, you know. You in your little ways. Yeah,
bro. What's difference between the Sun
Island is it's uh their class, bro.
They've got a badge. Get the badge out,
bro. You know, that's what's different.
That's what's good about him. To be
fair, it does need to get dry cleaned
though, to be fair. Yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah. I need to go, Cindy, lad. I need
to go on Cindy's
approaches to get some [ __ ]
Yeah, bartender's number. Yes, she
should be on it, bro. Yes, son.
No, you can't. No, you can't, mate. Has
to be stony. Has to be stony, mate. Has
to be [ __ ] stony again.
Might have bad Wi-Fi. Nah, mate. Don't
have bad Wi-Fi. I'm not skint like you.
Yeah, she was young to be fair. She was
young to be fair. I can't lie. I like
car. I can't lie, bro. Everyone Hey,
I'll never forget that, bro. I woke up
at 5:00 in the morning, bro. The [ __ ]
people next door was making [ __ ]
noise, bro. It was all night long,
Steven. It was all night long and they
wouldn't stop. They wouldn't [ __ ]
stop. I don't have bad Wi-Fi, mate. My
Wi-Fi is perfect. Must be your Wi-Fi.
Your shitty Wi-Fi. But yeah, it was all
night long. It was all night long. I
woke up at 5:00 in the [ __ ] morning.
I swear to God, it was all night long,
mate. I don't wake up 5 in the morning.
I wake up about 7:38. I said to my
friend, "Bro, what the [ __ ] is going on?
I hear something downstairs." You know,
it was all night long. Um because that
account I can't go live on because I've
got too many Streamyards connected to
the account. So yeah, there's a [ __ ] up there.
Yeah, it's madness. It was all night
long. It was all night long, bro. I
swear now. It was all night [ __ ]
long, mate. It woke me up, bro. It woke
up. It woke me up. It was all night long,
mate. It was all night
long. Everyone heard it.
Yeah, I swear down. Looking rough, mate.
Not as rough as you, you ugly little fat
mon. Bye-bye now. Stop talking about
yourself. Stop talking about yourself
every day on your
job. You're no life but YouTube. But you
know life but YouTube. I know you no
life but YouTube. You know what I'm saying?
Grimsy the same little spackers every
day talking about himself.
These people talk about themselves every
day, man. I feel bad for them. They hate
themselves so much. You really think you
calling me this, you calling me that is
going to be
right, bro? No, man. No, no one cares
what you ugly little monies think or
you've got to say about anyone's looks,
bro. Cuz you're just talking about yourself. Your
self-reflectors, little self projecting
self-reflectors. You don't bother no
[ __ ] mate. Friday today.
Anyways, I need to go in a bit anyways,
man. I need to send these approaches to you, lad.
One last spray, I reckon. So, man, 4:00 it
is. Well, mate, if you're not impressed by
that, you'll be impressed. Yeah, I got a
bartender's number today and I'm going
to be doing some more cold approaches today.
Oh, that's so [ __ ] sexy,
bro. I need to spray everywhere.
Everywhere, bro. Like after shave. Sean
can't afford it cuz he's on the ground a
month. Oh yeah, I got a bartender's
number, but I ain't left my area yet,
but I'll be sending it all night. I got
a bartender's number. He was [ __ ]
ace. Oh man, she was sexy. She had some
big tips as well.
I can't lie. I'm
not Caroline. I can't
lie. I can't lie. But I'll never forget
it. I'll never forget it. I'm It won't
be up at 5:00 in the morning. It It
won't be up at 5:00 in the [ __ ]
morning. I will never forget it, bro. I
swear now. I swear to God, bro. 5:00 in the
morning. But hey, I'm going to go,
right? I'm going to go and I'm going to
send these [ __ ] approaches. So, I'm
going now. Yeah. Uh, that's good, bro.
Listen, see you, weirdo. Yeah, you are
the weirdo. Go suck your mom, you little
[ __ ] Anyways, I'm going to go now and
I am going to ABC see you and I'll be
back um well about probably 7:00 in the
morning or later or tomorrow. So yeah,
I'm going to ABC see you. Bye. Many
numbers to come. Bye-bye now.