[ __ ] hell. What a [ __ ] madness.
What a [ __ ] What a [ __ ] madness I
just had, mate. Yeah,
that's how you know they're just going
to run to old bill in it. You just know it, mate.
You just know they're going to run to old bill.
I'm out of here in a month, mate. This
ain't no line for anyone. This ain't no
line for anyone, mate.
This ain't no life for anyone, mate. If
I showed you in the video,
pard him off, mate. Pard him off. He's a
[ __ ] [ __ ] He won't come around
the corner. He's a [ __ ] Cuz he knows
you won't be able to get old bill
around. That's what it is. [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Madness, bro. I'm out of here in a
month. Come on, mate. A month. I'm out
of this country again. Bye. See you.
Yeah, I'm out, bro. I'm out.
>> Bro, do you know what happened, bro?
Yeah, Cory, listen. Yeah, I approached
three people in the space of an hour and
a half. Yeah, I wasn't even that drunk.
I'm like tipsy. Yeah. Talking normally.
They weren't interested. Whatever. I
don't care. Like, I'm drinking anyways.
Yeah. The bouncer come up to me. Yeah.
Bro, he's like, "Oh, can you come with
me?" And I Okay, fair enough. Like, I'm
attracted by whatever. And he and he's
both the guy listen he tries m I've got
a video of this. Yeah. He says oh like
if you give me attitude I'll take it. I
said I'll give you attitude when I want
mate. Like you're in my country. Yeah.
He tries [ __ ] taking a drink off me.
He goes everywhere. I told him listen.
Come on [ __ ] Come on. Come around
the corner big man. Like you think
you're scared. We're scared of you big
Polish bounces. Come on big man. I swear
down I was calling this guy for about 5
minutes. He would not come around the
corner bro. He only wanted to stay
around the cameras so he could get the
old Bill involved. I said, "You're
recording me. I'm recording you, you
[ __ ] I'm recording him." He's a
[ __ ] [ __ ] He ain't about it. He
ain't about it, mate. All he is about is
trying to get the old bill in. I was
slating with him, bro. I said, "You're a [ __ ]
big fat [ __ ] dirty Polish pig."
That's what I said to him. We
listen, bro. I was I approached four
people in the space of two hours. Yeah.
talking normally. No, no, no, no, no,
no. The man comes up to me, says, "Oh,
we need you to like we need you to come
around the corner." I was like, "Okay,
fair enough." But I'm wearing whatever.
He was saying that we've had like
complaints about you. I was like, "Hold
on. You've got complaints about me for
doing what exactly?" But talking to
people normally. I was making friends. I
was speaking to people normally. I
wasn't being abusive. And then he he
said, "Oh, if you give me attitude, I'm
going to take the drink." I said, "Mate,
try and take the drink out of my [ __ ]
hand. You fat cunt." Yeah. He tried
taking it. The drink went [ __ ]
everywhere. I said to him, "Listen to
Listen, bro. Come around the corner.
Away from the cameras. Away from this.
Come on, you Polish pig. Come around the
corner, piggy. He won't have none of
it." He weren't having none of it as
well. I said, "You fat, dirty, stinky
Polish pig." That's what I said to him.
Polish, bro. I told him, "Come around
the corner. I'll [ __ ] you up real life,
bro. It ain't a joke. I will [ __ ] you up
real life." And guess what? If you think
you're going to touch me, I'm come back
with a hammer, bro. Simple. He ain't
about it. He's a big fat. I was pouring
him off, bro. I told him [ __ ] his mom
and everything. I said, "Let's go away
from the establishment. Come on. It's
not too busy. Come around the corner,
you big fat Polish pig." And I said that
to him as well.
I said, "You got a video. I'll put it
up, bro. I'll put it up. Tell me where I
You don't come to my country and try to
tell me where I can go. You don't come
to my country and tell me where I can
go." I said, "Come around the corner
then, big man. Come around the corner,
big man. Come on. Come on. Lose your
license. Come on.
I got kicked out, bro, for starting a
conversation with three or four people.
I didn't do anything wrong. I was
speaking to people normally. I swear to
God, bro. Weren't you drunk? I was
tipsy, bro. I was like about 30% drunk.
Now I'm about 60. And he thinks he I
said, "Bro, you're not going to touch
me, you fat pig." I told him that, bro.
He won't come around the corner. Why are
you not coming around the corner, bro?
Yeah, exactly. You [ __ ] fat [ __ ] I
was running up my mouth and everything,
bro. Yeah, [ __ ] it.
>> Yeah, you'll get [ __ ] up real life.
And guess what, bro? If there is a
chance I would win, I would lose, I'm
coming back with a hammer. Simple. So,
it's over. You might win, but I'm coming
back with a hammer. You Polish pig.
That's I called him that as well. I
said, "You're nothing but a Polish pig."
That's why I called him cuz they love
their pig so much. You [ __ ] [ __ ]
Don't come to my country and try and
start thinking about. And he was just
standing there. I said, "Come around the
corner. Come on, bro." All the staff was
looking back. He start [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
He tried to take the drink out of my
[ __ ] hand. I said, "No, you're not
taking the drink out my hand." Yeah. He
is nothing but a Polish pig. I called
him that as well. Polish as well. Let me
get you a snip. You're a [ __ ]
[ __ ] Yeah. I got a camera as well.
Look, I'll get out, bro. One sec. Yeah.
[ __ ] oldest pig. One second, Bob. One
sec. [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Where was it, bro?
I was calling this guy, bro, about a
million times to come around the corner
away from the establishment. Yeah. Away
from people. And he would not come. He
would not come, bro. He would not come.
He would not come. Yeah. Apparently.
Yeah. Listen. I've got no problem. Yeah.
With Eastern European people where But
you're supposed to be strong. I told you
to come around the corner. I told you to
come around the corner. You wouldn't
come. Let's see, bro.
>> Not even drunk. Not even drunk, bro.
Yeah. Look at him. I was telling him to
come around the corner, bro. Get away
from the establishment. Get away from
the cameras and I'll batter you up, bro.
And I'll make you lose your license. He
wouldn't have none of it. He's a [ __ ]
You're nothing but a Polish pig. And I
laughed at him as well. But I I pred the
guy, bro. And he won't even try to walk
towards me. If he's out, if he's away
from the camera, if he's away from
people, he ain't leaving, bro. You
understand? [ __ ] bro. He's a [ __ ]
He's a [ __ ] He ain't about that life.
You're not about that life, bro. I was
pinging him off. I was telling him to
come out the corner. Come. Come on. I
was telling him, bro,
I didn't even do anything wrong anyways.
But you don't tell me you're going to
try and take my drink out of my hand for
your fat belly. You [ __ ] idiot. Are
you mad? Who the [ __ ] does he think he
is? Mr. B. I told him to come around the
corner. I said, "Come around the corner,
you Polish peak." Polish. Come around
the corner, man. Come on. Remember that
you're strong. Come on, bro. Come on,
bro. He wants to run to the old bill,
which is why he will not leave. He will
not leave around the area. I said, "You
Polish pig." I said to him, "You piggy
lover." I told him, "Bro, yeah." I said,
"You [ __ ] Polish." I said to him, I
was I was trying to wind him up and
everything. He would come out the corner
and I'm like 30% drunk. I said, "Come
on, bad man. Come on. Come on. Come on.
My teeth out. Come on, big man. Come on.
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. You ain't about
that life. He's nothing but a Polish pig
that hides behind cameras. Fat belly
Polish brother. What the [ __ ] do you
think this is, bro? I said, let's get
away from the establishment. There's
women and there's there's people looking
around the corner. Come around the
corner, big man. Yeah. Yeah. I I feel
like going I felt like going back with a
hammer. He's going to call me Bill,
mate. He was going to call the old bill.
He That's what they do in London.
Trying to call him cameras trying to
call me. I'll [ __ ] record you. You
[ __ ] [ __ ] Polish pig. You [ __ ]
pig. [ __ ] bro.
[ __ ] that, bro. You mad. I'll you up
real life, bro.
Like, say a way about things, bro. Say,
listen to night or whatever. Like,
there's a way of doing things, bro. You
will get [ __ ] up real life, bro. I
don't know who you think you are. I
don't matter what bad you think you got,
you will get [ __ ] up real life, bro.
Even if I get even if I lose the first
time, I'm coming back, mate. Even if I
go to hospital, you get [ __ ] up real
life, bro. You don't understand what
city you're in. You understand?
You'll get [ __ ] up real life. I'll
[ __ ] you back to Poland where you come
from. You understand, mate? I'll you
back to where you come from and [ __ ] you
out of that. You [ __ ] pork lo
I told him bro look there you've created
a scene there's clearly people watching
come around the corner and let's go bro
what are you doing [ __ ] [ __ ] yeah
[ __ ] pair of [ __ ] that's what they are really
like bro do your job properly be polite
say things in a way you're not going to
talk over me you're not going to try and
put your [ __ ] hand on me Yeah,
[ __ ] you need to learn, bro. You need
some discipline as well. Take care, bro.
You get [ __ ] real life, bro. Even if
it's not the first time or the second
time, get hurt. Stop your [ __ ] bro.
You're trying to record me. Why are you
recording me? I'll record you. Come on.
Come on. Come on. That's not [ __ ]
Standing by a [ __ ] door like a [ __ ]
Yeah. All around locks circus. When he
knows there's police. When he knows
there's police. nothing but a Polish
pig. And I told him that to his face as
well, bro. Yeah. The staff was looking
back. I told him to cut to come back. Yeah.
Legitimately, bro. He know he knows
he'll get [ __ ] up, bro. He knows he
will get [ __ ] up, bro. [ __ ]
[ __ ] bro. [ __ ] idiot. Look, bro.