Yo yo yo yo yo. runs
except more except for today. This is
Yeah, I need a V. I need a VPN [Music] today.
Not too bad.
You people can keep giving them the past.
See if it's not anymore.
Yeah. Get on the troop today
for the month.
I'm wasting my money in this [ __ ] [Music]
What is it? Oh, [ __ ]
I'm going out again today. Zippy
guy was the he was asking me about the
fridge. She said, "Um, it doesn't work
properly." I said, "No, it's completely broken."
Yeah, I'm sending a broken fridge for
the fun of it. Ask stupid questions, get stupid answers.
You know, I generally can't wait until
this whole thing is over. So, I have to
stop dealing with people in literally
every single way I possibly can. Now,
now the fridge is the fridge is broken.
It doesn't work. It's It's completely broken.
That's That's why I'm selling it. I'm
selling a broken fridge.
Ask stupid questions. Ask stupid question.
You get stupid answers. You know what
I'm saying? It's it's as simple as that.
I can't stand people, bro. But you can't.
This is why I'm sending these people.
People annoy me, bro. People really
really annoy me. Really do.
I really hate people, bro.
It's my last day on YouTube anyways. Um,
three weeks a month. So, [ __ ]
Find somebody that you want to love and
not for sex.
Yeah, we've been planning it for the
past three years, but only everyone got a boyfriend.
I mean, [ __ ] me, bro. Why am I leaving
YouTube? Because it's it's a place full
of weirdos, bro. It's a place full of
stalking little weirdos. Like, [ __ ] this [ __ ] Yeah,
tried um getting me banned from the pub
yesterday and he was stalking me. I had
to report him to the police again this
morning when I woke up. Um, the
stalking, the weirdowness. You can only
tolerate it for like a day or two and
then you leave. It's It's just a weird community.
How did it go? Quite [ __ ] to be honest.
Three numbers, but I've not messaged any of them.
I can't believe I just can't believe it, bro.
This guy just messaged me. He said, "Oh,
is is the fridge in working condition?"
I said, "Nah, it's completely broken."
Nah, it's [ __ ] The fridge don't work.
Ask stupid questions, get stupid answers. Um,
can't wait until this whole thing is
over where I don't have to deal with
anyone ever again or deal with people
again. I really started hating people,
bro. I think a lot of people like that.
I think a lot of people just just hate
people. And I'm I'm just saying they're
[ __ ] annoying, aren't they? They ask
some stupid questions. I mean, I had to
ask I had to repeat myself 20 times
yesterday and somebody still got the order wrong.
This country is so depressing. I'm out
of it in a month. I know I said I was
only going to go out yesterday, but I'm
going to go out today as well cuz I'm
legitimately done. I'm out of it in a
month. So, this last time. So, yeah. [Music]
I'm telling you, this country's gotten wor
like, you know, the thing is, right?
I've got all of it, man. I've already
sent it to the police.
I've already sent it to the police.
Like, it's gotten worse and worse and
worse, bro. Like, at least back in the
day, you could you could get like a date
or something or you can't even get
anything anymore. You can't even get a
conversation out of someone. Um, but I
come back here and I don't like videos,
but I did upload them. But
it gets worse. It's not even the fact
that it doesn't change. Like they tell
you, bro. Yeah, I know. It sucks. And
this is why I don't come on it, bro. And
this is the reason why like I don't come
on for like a week, two weeks, three
weeks is because of these people.
So you get told right by most of the
probably by most of the population that
you shouldn't approach on the street,
you shouldn't approach on on the street.
You should go to bars and clubs. And
then when you're approaching bars and
clubs, which I wasn't too drunk, I can
handle my drink. I know exactly what I
had said. You get barred for talking to
people. Make it make sense. Like
literally nothing in this country makes
any sense. Like I've actually realized
that now. Um, so and then also another
thing I find very very cheeky is they
try to tell you that you can't wear
tracksuit bottoms when you are literally
giving them your money. You're paying to
get guys oh you can't wear tracks
bottoms and I'm thinking like you're
giving them your money. You should be
able to wear what you want. like what
happened to the saying like the customer
is always right
and I was speaking to a manager about
this telling basically about the Uber
and I understood where he was coming
from and but I was saying to him like
you might think that I'm being a bit
awkward and no no no no no no but I'm
I'm not and um he says and I was like
what's the worst thing you've
experienced he said somebody threw like
tried to throw a glass on his head but
the difference is you're dealing with
customers drunk people so you would
expect it. Just like if you was to join
the police force, you know, you could
potentially get, you know, badly injured
by someone. You know, the the the
um the the thing is is that you're
dealing with drunk people, bro. You
weren't dealing with people on the
street. That's the difference. So, I do
think like there's there's a big
difference there. I got like I got where
he was coming from, but
it's and then he was saying, "Oh, the
country's no country is perfect." But
we're not talking about a country being
perfect. We're talking about the people
in this country. Obviously, no country
is perfect, bro. It's it's all [ __ ] But um
you know what I'm saying? Like they're
but we're not talking about countries
being perfect and politics. talking
about the the entitled people in the country
which I kind of felt bad for him cuz it
was it's like he took his time to speak
to me and I don't want him to feel like
I'm wasting his time but and I'm being difficult. So
it's a numbers game, bro. If you told me
that 2 years ago, I'd believe it. If you
told me that two and a half years ago,
I'd kind of believe it. There ain't no
numbers game. It is virtually impossible
in this country now. No,
it is virtually impossible in this
country now. You can't even get a
conversation out of someone to be
honest. I got I got a boyfriend
yesterday maybe twice. I only got it
We say bad. Um
the rest I just did they didn't say anything or
or something like that. But I think I
only got it two times.
I hate this country, bro. Um,
but that I got barred for speaking to
three people, even though people come up
speaking to me normally as well,
speaking to them back. And I was having
this conversation with this woman from
New Zealand for about half an hour, just
getting into real deep combos and combos
and just was on the street drunk and
that and then I was having a
conversation with these two women on the
train and we basically agreeing that
this country's gone to the shambles. I
mean, there's no respect anymore. It's
just too many entitled people. Um, we
were just talking about it and there was
a guy telling and there was a guy he was
was talking about and I told him like,
"Yeah, a kid tried stealing my bike."
Like a 9-year-old tried stealing my bike
or the bike that I rented and and we was
talking about like when we were younger,
we would think to go and steal a bike
because we knew what the punishment was.
And he said that he tries to bring these
kids up the best way he possibly can.
And we're just talking about how
completely [ __ ] up this country is.
basically in other words, even the whole
like train ride home.
Um, and that's how you know it's not on
you cuz you get into these deep
conversations with people. I made I made
some new friends as well. But in in
terms of the whole dating and the whole
women thing, it it has definitely gotten
worse, bro. It has. It really and truly
cuz two two years ago, you could think,
"Oh, well, I had that chance. Oh, I had
that chance. Oh, this happened. Oh, that
happened. Oh, yeah. Okay. It's a bit
hard, but it's always supposed to be
hard. It's never supposed to be easy.
There's nothing worth having in life is
easy. But now it's it's just impossible. Like
just cuz Tik Tok was made years ago
doesn't mean that things don't change
after a certain year. Like back in the
day, [ __ ] changed after 2012. After that
2012 line, when people stopped using
Skype, it went to the shambles. Like we
used to speak about this on
the bodybuilding still multiple times.
Like you've literally you have got more
chance of winning the lottery than
finding anyone in this country. Like
generally you got more I I stopped doing
the lottery and I've never done the
lottery, you know. I was actually
speaking to this guy yesterday about
this. I've actually never done the lottery but um
and I just wanted to go out and enjoy
myself yesterday and then you get bored
for the free people. Make it make sense,
man. Like the [ __ ] So, I'll just go to
the pubs today. I reckon this will be my
last time anyways. Oh,
give it one last two. E
now I'm severely lagging.
Um, I hate everything about this country.
Why am I on a bodybuilding form? Why not?
This was years ago, but you get the point. Um,
but yeah, I got free numbers. I haven't
texted them yet. And the only people
that really seem to be talkative and
normal are like Irish people, some of
the Scottish people, obviously New Zealand.
There was some people that you could
actually have a conversation, not not
women mainly, but there is some people
that you could have a conversation with. But um
it's very hard nowadays to try and to
try and day in any westernized country,
you know, like it's it's sad
and people know it deep down. The
Simpson and White Knights know it deep
down, but they just pretend it's not a
problem, so they just don't say anything
as we know. that. Um, so yeah.
But yeah, 2 years ago I could safely
say, "Yeah, there's chances that you
[ __ ] up. Yeah, you was wrong some of
the time. Now you can't even get anything."
Um, and we're summer now and we've
almost finished summer. So
I was speaking to that Italian one
yesterday as well. She was like, "Oh,
I'm going back to Italy and making these
excuses." trying to basically find out
what the actual problem was was
indirectly without directly asking
and um I said it's got to be heretic
because there's no way bro you was put
off just because somebody would try to
kiss you again it's a form of victim
victimizing so I said you're being that
would not put someone off whether they
was to see somebody or not see someone
again these are all mind games you
understand this is how people try to
play mind games saying how they're going
back to Italy and none of that I I mean,
at the end of the day, it just doesn't
ring right any of it, you know? So,
yeah, I got three numbers, but I haven't
text them yet. I'll text them in a bit.
Made some new friends. Those two women
on the train were nice from ethics.
They must have been full.
They must have been older. Um,
so yeah, was basically just speaking
about how like it's gone through the shambles basically.
It was nice to have some conversations
out some people. People on the train are
just looking cuz they're not used to it.
But yeah, I got I got kicked out of one
place for speaking to people. Fridge
repair, man. Oh, it will always be the
same. This country will never change,
bro. Oh, yeah. It will never change. I
wouldn't even moan about that, bro. But
it it's gotten worse. It's like I was
saying, it's not that it was always be
the same. It's actually gotten worse.
That's the concerning thing about it.
It's actually gotten worse. Like the day
you can't even speak to people in in a
social establishment without it being a
problem is really what has this place
come to? Cuz do you think if I stayed in
that place I was I was expecting to get
anything? No. I I didn't even expect to
get anything. I knew it was just going
to be the same same people, same Tik Tok
brain, same attitude, but I just wanted
to go out for a drink anyways. But
you actually get banned for for actually
speaking to people. Wow. Make it make
sense. These people were moaning that
you you're approaching people in the
street and no
and then you go to an actual
establishment when you're trying to have
a drink and it weren't over and over
again. It was about three people in the
past 2 hours which it doesn't really
matter if it was over and over again.
You're a single man. You you can talk to
who you want. You're in the place for
it. people going out, they're having a drink.
It's it's it's quite a normal thing to
do. But there's always something in this
country, always some [ __ ] always
something that doesn't make it's
actually like you even get bad
experiences even just going for a drink.
That's how bad it is.
I'm not speaking about the women because
they will never change. I'm just talking
about like the whole um
the whole madness of it all, bro. Um,
then you got somebody that can't even do
an order, right? When I just said about
20 times. I understand a few times cuz I
only like cheese and bacon and my
burger. I understand like a few times,
you know, maybe they don't get that
order that much. I repeated it 20 times
and they still got it wrong, which they
refunded in the end. It's like this
country and have you noticed everywhere
you go, the country stinks.
Like if you go to central London, it
always stinks either of [ __ ] or weed.
I've been spending weed a lot lately as well,
but you just walk down some place and it
will just stink of of [ __ ] We like
random places as well.
Yeah, I was getting on with people. I
made some new friends. Um
yeah, this guy was like uh he was an old
man. and he was just waiting for his
child to finish nursery, I think it was.
He's like, "Are you winning?" I as I
don't gamble anymore. Told him the
story, I don't gamble, basically. And he
Yeah. We just got into this conversation
about life and
how this country is and how there's no
discipline and and and [ __ ] Nice guy,
man. Nice guy.
I said to that woman as well in New
Zealand that you're not going to ever
meet a Londoner the same as me.
They give us a really bad name. These
people here. Nope. You still haven't
left YouTube. YouTube is your life.
And you can't take one day off of YouTube either.
Oh [ __ ] One second. Someone sent me a
voice note, bro. Hold up.
Yeah. Antman's like, "Oh, it's just
winding me up hearing about it." Yeah,
it used to happen to me as well. It used
to wind me up watching videos and it it
wouldn't even be happening to me and it
would just wind me up.
Um, it would just wind me up. That's why
I stopped watching videos. Um,
yeah, cuz I showed him the video of me
and the bouncer and that and I told him
basically what happened. He said it just
it pisses him off just hearing it. That
that's what he used to do with me as well.
There used to be this black guy. He goes
around London and he approaches these
women and it just used to piss me off
even though I wasn't even though it
wasn't happening to me. But he'd get the
same old I've got a boyfriend. No, no,
no, no. Just would it would just annoy
me. That's why I stopped watching it.
And I would say to be honest with you,
yesterday was probably the correct
statistics. You got two. I've got a
boyfriend. That's fine. That's normal
people in relationships, but nowhere
near as many as they're making out.
I find it weird they made Julie for
nothing that women obviously like I
don't think they complained bro they
were still in the same place like they
did not complain why would they complain
when they said no I walked away so what
would they complain about and I it
wasn't over and over again it was over 2
hours um I don't I think they
complained. I think they were watching
me on camera and they made it up because
they Why would they complain about me
going and speaking to them? They they
they wouldn't. So, um
it just the whole country just doesn't
make any sense. Like nothing about the
country made sense. They didn't I don't
think they did complain because they
were having a drink. They
Why would they complain? They probably
saw you speaking to people and just
didn't want you in their premises.
Um, no. I don't want to, bro. Like, at
the end of the day, lad. Like, I don't I
don't care. And obviously the bouncer
thing, it's irrelevant if I got beat up
or he got beat up. That's not what the
problem is. The problem is the whole
person that started it. And no, I'm not
going to speak about it, bro, because
I'm just not going to give them my
money. So, no one complained. None of
these women complained because they just
stuck up and they just said no. Why
would they complain about me when they
said no? I left.
So, no one's complained. They've
probably seen you going around doing it
and then they probably just didn't like
it even though it is a social place. And
then I had people coming over and
speaking to me like I was speaking to
this guy from Ireland. He just come from
Ireland. He was a cool guy. Was talking
about life. Some black guy come over to
me and spoke to me, you know, just
normal. There was nothing going on. So,
I mean, no, no one complained about no
one, bro. You think every single woman
just went up to the counter and started
complaining about you when they when
they were just going to leave anyways
cuz they they weren't going to stay
there the whole night? No [ __ ] way,
bro. Think about it. Look at all of the
women that you approach on the street.
Do they ever go to the police? Never in
a million years have they ever tried to
file a harassment order on you. No.
They're talking out their [ __ ] ass,
bro. There's no way three or four women
have gone around
complaining about you trying to get to
know them. And I'm I wasn't too drunk if
I can handle my drink. Yeah, we know how
it is with Ant-Man. And then that's how
I still know what happened with the bouncer.
So, no one's had complaints at all,
mate. You're talking out of your [ __ ] ass.
Cuz I didn't argue with any of them. I
wasn't rude to any of them. They weren't
rude to me. So, what what what's the problem, sir?
So either way, it seems to be a problem
nowadays going into a bar and a club and
trying to meet new people as a single
person, which contradicts everything
that they say to begin with that. Yeah.
Don't approach on the street. Go to go
to bars and clubs. When you go to bars
and clubs, they don't like you speaking
to people. Okay.
Okay. You know what I'm saying? Like
what the [ __ ]
>> Yeah. No one complain about anyone.
No one's complaining about anyone cuz
isn't it mad how if it happened twice a
year how it's always the same complaints
made up complaints
and there's police everywhere in central
London mate trust me
and it's I've never had of all
approaching in the years I've done I've
never had somebody complain
ask a stranger for help so yeah they're
talking out their their backwards us. So,
they seem to make things Oh, that looks
nice, bro. They seem to make things
up as they go along.
He got a fright, mate. I was telling him
to come around the corner,
but that that's only relevant anyways, bro.
See, if you was if you was in somewhere
like Newcastle or Wales, they would have
went around the corner cuz they've got
like a different like in Wales, they
would fight you because I've seen I've
seen like fights happen on the street in
Wales cuz they've got this whole security thing.
Um, and they don't have a certain badge
in certain in London. They've got a
certain badge and they will lose their
badge very very fast if they do
something they're not supposed to do.
You know, London's hot on it.
And I said to him like I I I I'll meet
you after work. It's not a problem. What
time do you finish?
Um but you know, and even if you could
go like that's why I said come when you finish work. Um
but in Wales they would have just went
to round corn and [ __ ] you up. Well,
yeah, they would [ __ ] you up there, but
trust me, I've I've seen stuff happen like jeez,
this guy was a big guy, you know? He was
a big guy. Like, yeah,
it's just people in it.
It's going to be happening, bro. It's
going to be happening.
It is definitely be happening, bro. So >> yeah,
it's strange, isn't it? How like you're
a normal person in society
and like you you have to deal with this
[ __ ] We I was talking to these two
women. We were saying I don't think it's
right, you know, people have to go to
work and put up with these people's
[ __ ] What do you think, Cory? They
they seem to think it's normal, but but
it's actually unhinged.
They seem to think it's normal, but it's
actually unhinged if you think about it.
But then these these are the same people
that go on about things being socially
acceptable. Make it make sense. You know
what I'm saying? So
this country just makes no sense
whatsoever. There's there's no sense to
it, is there? Um, yeah.
Hopefully I can go out today for a drink
and not have any problems. Except, yeah,
the women are going to be [ __ ]
obviously, but I mean, I've already
expected that, so yeah,
you got virgin boy [ __ ] calling the
police. I'm sorry, not calling the
police. [ __ ] trying to get people
banned from pubs when I was literally
trying to help him, Cory. I was doing
nothing but trying to help him. I I
literally said to him, "We can meet
together and I will help you lose your V
plate. Help you lose your VC card cuz
obviously that virginity that's been
lingering at you for 31 years needs to be popped."
And I tried to [ __ ] help him and then
he [ __ ] starts calling up [ __ ]
places. I was going to try and help him
get laid. I think we'd actually be like
a a big tag team together. Oh, and I
banged an escort yesterday as well.
First time I've had sex in [ __ ] 6
months. I was like, "Oh, you can't come
in my mouth." I was like, "I'm just
going to get a [ __ ] and have sex
today. [ __ ] it. I've not had sex in
ages." So, you know, I I admit I I I
haven't had sex for like six, seven
months cuz I just get the [ __ ]
There's nothing wrong with being a 31year-old virgin. You know,
you've been a virgin from a very young
age. What's wrong with being a virgin?
You know, that's why he always does
these videos whispering about virgins
cuz he is one himself.
But I was trying to help him like lose
his virginity, you know, as like an old school friend.
He is a proper virgin, bro. Proper proper virgin.
Oh, I'm [ __ ] shattered, Cory. Now I
am. Now it has caught up with me. Now it
actually has caught up with me. But I'll
be all right. Don't worry, man.
But yeah, it wasn't the women that cuz
we know what the women are like in this
country, but it's the whole like, so
what if you're speaking to people and
you're making friends? So what? You're
not causing any problems. No one's
reported you to anyone cuz they have not
cuz I would have seen it. You haven't
started assaulting anyone or sexually
assaulting anyone. Like
I'm guessing the staff just see you talk
to people and then they just complain to the bouncer
or something like that cuz they ain't no
woman reporting you, bro. Trust me, I'm
telling you they're not.
We haven't had no reports cuz that would
have mean every single person has reported you. No,
maybe they see that you're not in a
group like other people in groups and
you're going around speaking to people. Um,
I got banned before for calling someone
a a [ __ ] calling one of the staff
members an entitled Canad. No, I didn't
call her a Canadian [ __ ] but she was
basically being a [ __ ] and I just called
her a [ __ ] Got barred.
So it's like you let the whole thing
don't make sense with some of it because
like you you you let these entitled
westernized people come in your place establishment
they they come around being [ __ ] and
someone gives it back to them and then
they get bored. And I was saying to this
bar manager, right, this pub manager,
which I respect him because he did sit
down and spoke to me and I saw where he
was coming from. And I was like, I'm
not, you might think I'm trying to be
awkward and whatever that cuz we've had
conversations before, but I'm not. But
you got to understand that
if you stop letting these entitled
westernized people in your premises,
there would not be no problems. The
problems is literally them. like it it
it literally really really really really
really is them. And he was telling me
that he's had bad experiences, but I
said, "You work in a pub, people drink."
I think you're you're Bro, do you think
I've not had bad experiences with with
people that are drunk?
Um, yeah. I had to deal with [ __ ]
almost, mate. I remember before before I
done this whole America thing. Yeah. I
used to have to deal with [ __ ]
almost every time I went out, but I just
didn't say anything and put it down to
drink. Like, you're working in a in a in
an establishment full of drunk people,
you're going to get [ __ ] I was
dealing with [ __ ] on the street. I
told him about the whole Uber thing cuz
Yeah, you'd always get you'd always get [ __ ] Like,
I used to have to like stop myself
smashing people in. I don't know how
many times. Surprised I never to be
honest. But he doesn't seem to think
that any of these people in this country
contribute to the problem.
And like I was just telling you that me
and this woman me and these two women
that were talking was like I think it's
pretty [ __ ] up how somebody can't even
go to work in peace.
You understand? Like they don't even
you're not even able to go to work
without dealing with [ __ ] Do you
not see that as a mad problem?
But then they'll say, "Oh, well we deal
with dickheads." Yeah, cuz you're
working in a club with drunk people.
Like if I worked in a club, right, say
they gave me a shift today to be to be
I'd be like, "Oh, yeah, they're
[ __ ] Yeah, they're drunk." Okay.
So, I don't think he really understood
my point. But um
and I said to him like, "You will not
understand unless you've actually been
through the experiences that I've been
through. Unless you actually have, you
won't really understand." Not saying
that you don't have a life experience.
Obviously, you're 34 and you work in a
in a pub and you're always busy. And I
just said to him, what just happened
back there was not normal,
you know. So,
um, so it is what it is. So,
they don't want you to wear tracksuit
bottoms. Or maybe they just banned me
cuz I wore tracksuit bottoms. No, it
wouldn't have been that cuz I initially
I thought it was the track shoe bottoms
which I would have understood, you know,
just change into jeans. Okay, whatever.
I'm wearing track bottoms. It's getting
a bit late.
And I said, "Oh, is it the tracky bottoms?" So,
I don't understand it really, bro.
You can't even be normal, bro. We're having problems.
But yeah, them women, the only time I
can tell you exactly when women's
complain to bouncers, what will happen
is back to the whole thing is the only
time a woman I'll tell you um
one time someone complained is again
when they could start something that
they couldn't finish. Um, so I think I
was I approached somebody before and a
friend got involved saying, "Oh, like
you bite your nails, that's a red flag."
And I said, "Your face is a red flag or
something like something." I I I can't
remember what exactly what I said. And
then they argued and then as usual, they
run to the manager. Um, so I mean, but
that none of that happened. No one
argued with anyone. Like examples from
like 2 years ago. Um, oh, like I had an
entitled American before. I said, "You
are not talking to me like that." And
she was like with her dad. Um, I was
like, "You are not talking to me like
that. I don't know who you think you are
talking to, but you're not talking to me
like that. No violence. You weren't
going to turn into violence. What did
she do?" She ranted about um she ran to
the manager. So, I mean, there are rare
times where people do complain. Um, yeah.
I mean, and man, when he speaks to one
person, they banned him. But that's
probably because they know what he's
about. They like he's on pub watch. He's
in the town. Whereas me, I'm a normal
person. I haven't had any problems anywhere. So,
just the whole thing is
it's really bad, bro. Yeah.
It was really, really bad, bro.
The world's bad, Cory.
And you know what? A few of the things
come up and I and I and I would say to
them as well, like if you go to um
Newcastle, you meet the loveliest people
there as well. I remember when I got
nicked to Newcastle, um even the police
had banter, but it was actually like
obviously weren't good. I got nicked for
no [ __ ] reason. But I remember this
um the police officer was like, "Oh
yeah, we watched you. You like doing
your hair like like you
watch the live stream and you you done
your hair a few times, didn't you?" Um
and yeah, it was always good. It was
always good vibes there. That comes up.
We start talking about like cities and
um what city is the best for night out and stuff.
Manchester come up and I said
Manchester's just getting like London
now. So that one cost. Yeah. So [Laughter]
you get they can't
tell you whoever
was the worst at all.
I remember when I was staying in
Middlesbr where you have uh Cory. Yeah.
And I I was playing the landlord and he
was the nicest person you've ever ever
been. Oh, don't worry. It's all going to
be okay. You're going to get the train
that cuz the football was playing and
all the all the tickets like really
nicer guy, man. Really is.
Yeah, he he was in middle where he was
really nice guy. He's got some good ratings. Sorry.
And then you come back to London and
they want a [ __ ]
Let's see if we can try and find a woman
that doesn't use social media.
We got piggies for breakfast, matey.
Piggies. Piggies. Piggies.
But yeah, the world has gone mad, bro.
It's gone mad, bro.
I already had my breakfast. I already
had my breakfast, Richie. I had a load of piggies.
Yeah, I had a load of piggies. Um,
Chloe, I had a load of piggies.
You want to see me, bro? I'm getting
one second, bro.
Yeah, I was getting some I was having
some piggies, bro. Look, even a bare
t-shirt didn't stop it, bro. I do need
to go gym tomorrow as well. This will be
my last time out.
You like piggies, Cory. You're not
supposed to be piggies. You're Muslim. And Mitchie,
I can't get over the Stephen King it
film. Mitchie, you'll like it down here,
son. You'll never have to grow up.
You'll like it down here, son. You'll
never have to grow up.
Yeah. You'll never have to grow up.
You'll like it down here, son. Do you
ever have one? Yeah, man.
All right. So, so Cory, how many times
Yeah. Do you think I'm going to hear
I've got a boyfriend today? They all flow. Yeah.
Do you remember when he grabs the child,
he said, "Be afraid." Anyways,
yeah. How many times do you reckon I'll
hear the boyfriend [ __ ] today, Richie?
Hopefully I don't hear it in it.
You will hear it, mate. You [ __ ] will.
Nah. Nah, mate.
Not over 30. Because you know what they
say when they're over 30? Their excus is
you're too young for me.
Their excus is that you're too young for me.
Yeah, that's their excuse. Their excuse
will then be that you're too young for me.
So yeah, we got it all figured out, [ __ ]
I think Virgin Boy should come and meet
me today, bro.
me, man. I help him lose that V plate.
Help him lose that V card. Liy,
I know so many excuses. Anyone would
think that you look like Timmy Eldridge.
Anyone would think that you you look
like um Timmy Eldridge.
That's how bad it is.
Anyone would think you look like him.
I should fight Prime. I'll [ __ ] him up,
bro. Well, I still got his vape.
When this um 19year-old used to come
around and suck my willie, [ __ ]
I got a vape. She used to come around
and suck my willie.
Then we bought a vape.
She used to come around and suck my willie.
That's funny, is it? Used to hug my peeka.
Do you remember LT was trying to get
into um USA Izzy's knickknacks?
Why are you trying to get in her knicknacks?
>> Bro, if I I don't need to fight Prime.
But do you know why you shouldn't even
fight people in this community, bro? Cuz
even if you win, you don't need to fight
these people because even when you win,
they they're all biased anyways. So they
pretend like it never happened. And
these people are not even worth meeting
on it, bro. Like remember that time I
owned the [ __ ] bomb like three times
and no one ever talks about it and you
know various different other times. No
one talks about it. Like you're best off
just even leaving YouTube and living
your life or maybe
just ignore these people if you do come
on it, bro. They know no fighting any of
them. Damn it. I mean, they know where
you live. So if they wanted you that
bad, they they know where you are. So
that's embarrassing, bro.
Imagine that. Like I went all the way to
Birmingham to fight Prime. That is just so embarrassing.
That I call that smoking me out last
week cuz he was winding me up and
winding me up and winding me up and then
reality kicked in again
because it's like they're never going to
meet you and they're not worth meeting.
And it's just embarrassing. Imagine your
mom. Yeah. see that you've gone all the
way to Birmingham to fight one of these
people. It's embarrassing, bro.
These people are embarrassing. You know
what I'm saying?
And that's what these people do, mate.
They try to get other people to fight
their battles. They try to get people's
money stopped. And when that doesn't
work, Cory, they run to the boys in blue.
And the last result is the boys in blue, mate. Yeah,
it's the boys in blue, mate.
It's the boys in blue. Bless you.
Bless you in life.
So, what do you think will happen? Say
when I approach Cory, will I pull
I can't even [ __ ] pull a [ __ ] door
handle, mate. You know,
[ __ ] let alone a westernized woman.
Jesus Christ. That would be something.
So, I can't spend any more money.
So, after today, so if anyone if someone
wants to meet then obviously I can cuz I
know that I've got somebody to meet. But
I can't be wasting any more money now. So,
I think we're wasting enough money in this country. Oh, [ __ ]
Oh, I'm so [ __ ] bro. I'm shattered.
Um, yeah, it was good.
I'm not even going to shower to be
honest. I'll shower tomorrow. I don't
stink anything. Anyways,
I see this black guy on the train. Yeah.
With a woman, Richie, and I think the
the boy was her brother
and it was just so mad.
You weren't that nice.
Yeah, I put I put videos up on my other
channel. One second. Is is is Monty
still on YouTube?
What do you think the problem is with
dating in this country, Richie? Do you
think they've just got unrealistic standards?
Like, I want to do a long video about
this country, but
you better watch it. People better watch
it if I do. It's going to be a banger, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. They got Monty man kicked out the
hotel, didn't they?
I don't know why they do that. Like try
to get people banned from pubs and [ __ ]
Why do they do that?
It's so [ __ ]
for several different reasons because
it's like a you're not going to get
content anymore and b
um and b like in London it's completely
pointless cuz you could just go to a
million and one other different places
and staff changes all the time. So
what's even the point of even getting
someone banned from one place? It just
doesn't make any sense.
understand that. It makes no sense
why you'd even get someone banned,
especially in somewhere like London as
well. They're really [ __ ] [ __ ]
And it's the same thing with Monty. Like
they got him banned out from the hotel,
now he won't come on YouTube.
See, so they everything that they want
they get rid of by glassing. It just
doesn't make sense. It just doesn't
>> Yeah. gay people
Australians should be coming here soon.
So, we meet up for a brew.
Yeah, that 20-year-old don't come around
anymore, Cory. And suck my willie. Like
I said, she used to come and suck my willie. Cory.
Yeah. Come and suck my Pekka, Cory.
That's cute, isn't it? Yeah.
These were the good times.
See, the maddest thing is is that like
even when you go out and you kiss
someone, like you could go out, somebody
would kiss you or you kiss them and
everything would be perfect and they'd
still ghost you
and then they'd still ghost you. It's
It's all It's all [ __ ]
Literally, it's all [ __ ]
And then people would still do it.
Oh, I don't miss these times with these roulette spins.
Look, the guilt. Not even once. Ducky.
Yucky. [ __ ] ducky, bro.
Ducky, ducky, ducky. Oh [ __ ]
Where is everyone, man?
Is £1,200 a lot of money, Richie? Yeah.
Yeah, matey. Yeah. Yeah, mate.
I'm going to go. Yeah, cuz I need to
sort some stuff out. I'm going to go
back out again later and um
I'm going to
be going live. Um cuz yeah,
going to actually enjoy it today.
At least try to. So yeah,
I'll be back later when I come back. So
over and out.