Oh, [ __ ] I'm not
got mad anxiety today, man. the drinking
I [ __ ] days
like [ __ ] did I
thought so but then I like that oh [ __ ]
in a minute
doesn't stop m does it yeah it's my last
live stream by the way for at least two weeks yeah Oh, me
makes me tired. Oh,
Yep, pretty much. Oh, [ __ ] I'm exhausted. Exhausted.
But I'm so like
I think it's so mad how desperate these
low lives are on here to get my attention.
It's the same repeating people. Why you
can't really stay on there for longer
than two days but you start losing brain cells
same repeated people
but then it's like I've been saying for
years it's just jealousy
it's just something going on in their
life if they have to sit on here and do
what they do every day.
So says anything about them, nothing about you.
And you can just imagine what these
people look like. Imagine what these
people are like in real life. They're
coming on here doing what they do every day. So yeah. Oh yeah. Don't disappear.
You're so petted. Stop under. Oh man,
keep an eye on that message as Oh.
Oh, by the way, I got the report thing,
by the way. It took like [ __ ] 15
[ __ ] minutes for
be to do, but I had to do it.
Is is fast enough to run to the police
on people. So, I'll do exactly the same
thing. I don't give a [ __ ]
[ __ ] it. You want to start getting cocky
again, Virgin? The police report start
coming back. Simple, bro. Just sat there
waiting for it, bro.
Skin, big nose, mate. You're skin and
you got a rat face. You [ __ ] [ __ ]
Have you seen what you [ __ ] wear?
You're the one that has to come on the
internet trying to convince people that
you got money. No one else does that
unless they show like loads of money.
Like you are literally the definition of skint.
Like you've been getting £1,000 a month
for the past [ __ ] god knows how many [ __ ] years
and you got no savings and you got nothing.
like you are the definition of of of
skin cuz like you must be skinned to be
wearing that [ __ ]
when you're so desperate to prove that
you got money when you literally have
nothing. Like you literally got your
housing benefit, withdraw the housing benefit from
uh the the the bank and then you act
like you got money and then you put it
back in the bank again. You literally do
not have a penny. I would say I don't
know why you come here calling other
people skin when you are literally the
skintest [ __ ] going.
Who the [ __ ] still shopped in the
charity shop at [ __ ]
It's like I was saying on my video the
other day, if these people got all this
money, why are they sat on YouTube every
day? They don't got an answer
cuz everything that they say is is just
a reflection of their own life. They
talk about themselves. Yeah.
If you had all this money, you'd be
[ __ ] traveling the world. You'd be
[ __ ] You wouldn't be on here. That's
for [ __ ] sure.
They make themsel look such tits really.
They talk about theirelves.
I completely destroyed them. the other
day, but I'm so tired.
[ __ ] hell. And I said I was going to go out
I said I was going to go out again
today. I would [ __ ] probably died, man.
No, I'm going to stick to once a week
maximum. I won't be out for a few weeks
now anyways cuz I got stuff to sort out. So,
Nothing happened to his phone, bro.
Yeah. And a little [ __ ] virgin tried
getting cocky again thinking that
everything that the cop does know you're
not going to get sent to the police. Please, man.
Stop it, man.
You literally never had a job in your life.
You literally have never ever had a job
in your in in in your [ __ ] life. Ever.
The only skin on is you.
Skin boy on the ground a month. All them
years. No one else.
No one else but you, bro. Yeah.
You got all this money, but you live in a bedsit,
man. It all this money, eh? You live in a bedsit.
I'm telling you. Yeah. Most of the
people on here want like £300 a month.
I'm telling you, bro. They're mo they're
most I I I think they are
on the £300 a month. I don't even think
they want a,000 a month.
Uh, you know, right?
Think about it, Grezy, cuz they wouldn't
be on here all day.
If they had all this money, they
wouldn't be on it all day. So, I think
most of these people get money to be fair.
Would you agree on that one?
Yeah, I done some approaches yesterday.
Grievy got some numbers. I haven't
replied yet, but don't don't really care.
I was going to go out today, but I'm too
hung over. So, yeah. Anyways, I said I
was going to go out once a week, didn't I? So, yeah.
Yeah, something like that, bro.
That's what Benny gets.
That's what Benny gets. See that? Oh, [ __ ] I'm fat.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
This is why I don't drink rum
to you. Yeah. Yep. Something like that. Anyways,
I'm glad you see you in two weeks.