Oh.
>> Yeah. Got some time to burn. Got some
time to kill. Press start tomorrow.
Why do these people go on these apps
chair just to have attitude problem? I
[ __ ] don't get it, bro. Honestly don't.
Honestly [ __ ] it. Don't
try and sit. It's a lot quieter. Just
drinking Coke by the way. No alcohol.
Could be like a plug someone. Maybe upstairs.
I want to go upstairs. Oh,
at the end
something there. Oh, lovely.
Nice little spot in the back.
I can't say where I am cuz a certain
certain virgin likes reporting people.
Nah, man. Not on it at all. I want
Pepsi. I don't drink much anymore. You
should know this. But Pepsi,
but thinking, yeah,
going to a gym tomorrow. I'll probably
be approaching all day. I'm thinking I'm
just going to go approach every day for
2 weeks to be honest. I'm running out of
time, mate. Running out of time. I'm
getting [ __ ] old. And we'll see what
the income is. We'll see what the
outcome is in two weeks. Income outcome.
I'm quite frankly got nothing to do. I
can't work for a while now. So,
but yeah, applied for some new things.
Applied for some new jobs. I'm not going
to say what it is. Yeah.
kind of ruins the community, doesn't it?
Had a nice roast dinner, nice pork, just
drinking some coke now.
Seems like how the street is the only
option anyways cuz I mean, you can't
even speak to people on the street now,
in a [ __ ] bar in a club nowadays. So,
I think, yeah, I'm going to have to
start doing that again. It's either that
or do nothing. You know, it's not going
to it's not going to cost you any money anyway. So,
and we'll see what the results are in
two weeks, eh? Yeah. None of them
numbers got back to me, Joe. Nope. [Music]
It's gotten worse. It's definitely
gotten worse in this country.
It has really, really, really got worse.
Worse and not better. So yeah,
it will never change.
I think I'm just generally hoping to
find the [ __ ] um slag again, I think,
with some of these approaches. But you
can't get fack or mate. But at the same
time, there's nothing else to do. So
I don't like admitting defeat, you know.
I'm more stubborn than than Antman, you
know, sort of. Is this on? No, it's I'm
more stubborn than Antman. So that's
where we're at.
Just be sending it hard tomorrow, hard
Tuesday, hard Wednesday. [Music]
I can't believe this is actually the
reality of dating in 2025. Eh, I
downloaded Tinder, Joe. I ain't been on
these dating apps since February.
I just [ __ ] download them. Nothing. [Music]
Nothing at all. Not a sausage.
Mad how racist people can be. Is it?
Yeah. It's mad how racist people are.
[ __ ] mad. Is it
probably be sending it every [ __ ] day.
What do you think the outcome will be, Joe?
Cuz I don't really want to spend money
now unless I actually get a date cuz I
don't have Well, I have money, but I
just don't want to spend the money.
I mean, it happened to be honest with
you. It happened at the right time to be
honest. This situation kind of happened
at the right time.
I mean, we don't ever feel like they're
at the right time, but I think it
happened at the right time. Germany feel
like it did. >> So,
cuz obviously like,
you know, yeah, you're not going to be
on as much money, but I've got savings
and [ __ ] and I'll be working soon
anyways. And it's not like you're going
to be out every week anyways spending
money because you've been there, done,
done it, won a t-shirt with this
country. All you need to be doing now is
saving to leave this country. So, you
haven't really you're not going to be
missing out. Been there, done it, worn a t-shirt. So, um
just going to go back home and chill.
Go gym tomorrow. Send it tomorrow. Send
it every day until next Monday. Um until
not the Monday after, the other the other Monday. So, yeah.
I can't believe you can get banned for
talking to people in a bar in a club.
That is a madness.
What is this country really come to? Jo, [ __ ] me.
Yeah, I don't even like drinking anymore.
Yeah, I don't like drinking no more, man.
It's why I had done it for a month. So,
the other day, so
I got no plan today. I had a roast dinner,
beef and pork stuff. We go home, sleep.
Country is a [ __ ] joke, isn't it?
This country is a [ __ ] joke.
[ __ ] trying to date in this country. E,
it should just be simple joke.
Why can't it just be straightforward?
like you speak to someone,
it's just so mad.
Just doesn't make any sense at all.
Why is it so hard in this country?
Mad why it's so difficult. So yeah. Um,
And it's not even that. So, tomorrow we
have to get numbers and then we have to
get numbers that reply and then we have
to get numbers that actually meet us and
not waste our time.
Right. I think at this point I need to
start doing the lottery. I mean, I don't
gamble anymore, but I think I need to
start doing the lottery.
Oh, that was a nasty bang. That's bang wiping it.
Yeah, these ports are not these ports
are not proper, bro. Saying it's
charging, but it ain't charging, bro.
>> Hold up.
Yeah, I ain't charging.
reality kicking in about what, bro? >> Nah,
I think the reality
that you I just think it's mad. You just
can't find someone in this country.
That's what I think.
It's just gotten worse and worse and
worse. Like I said, just cuz Tik Tok has
was out years ago doesn't necessarily
mean everybody was using it. You know
what I'm saying? So yeah,
we could say that I was very reckless
with my spending, but I still got
savings. I still get money. I still have
money. It's not a problem. But
young as I get another nice holiday out
of that savings. I'm happy, mate. So you
didn't answer my question. If I go out
every day approaching for two weeks,
Joe, what do you think the outcome would
be? You must get eight. You would get
one. You would get a date.
You would get a date, wouldn't you? Yeah.
Yeah, I think you would in two if you
don't every day for 2 weeks. You must do
it. Not drinking. I'm talking about just sober.
But saying that, maybe you wouldn't.
Yeah, I know.
>> Well, apparently I haven't gone compared
to you, Joe.
>> Yeah. Why does this little virgin go on
like he's got money, Joe, when he
literally has nothing? Right. The only
reason the only thing that stops me the
only reason that stops me going and
taking out money for my savings account
and showing it is because I know how
what happens. Yeah. I used to show money
before when I had it in cash. I don't
have money in cash. I don't go casino anymore
and I probably still wouldn't anyways.
Like the only reason I haven't done it
is because none of you people ever show anything.
But why does he go on I went on his
channel like he's got money when he
literally is skint. Like he's literally
the definition of skint as a 31 years as
a 31y old,
>> right? You got no bed. You shop at a
charity shop. When you have show money
in the past, we all know that some of it
was actually his dad's money. You know,
when you um retire, you get a pension.
It's like, why does he go on about money
when he literally has none?
Literally, he literally has no money
like at all. Like he is literally the
definition of skin. Like £800 is a lot
of money to him. He doesn't even have a bed.
Yeah. It's uh
Yeah. [ __ ] man. Amsterdam is okay for
like 3 days. 2 three days.
>> Yeah. It's not No, you can't stay there
for a week. Nah, 3 days maximum.
Thursday to Sunday, Friday to Monday
maybe. But no, not for a week. And the
only reason he chose that option is
because obviously he's scared of flying. So
um so yeah, and he probably cost
about3400. He doesn't have money. I
don't know why he goes on like he's got money.
And his dad actually got a pension. His
dad actually did get a pension. You do
get a pension when you get retired. My
granddad had it. I don't know if my
granddad's still alive, but I remember
my granddad having it. Um
but he ain't got money. I don't know why
he goes on like he's got money. He's
literally he's never even had a job.
I've had three jobs. I've literally had
three jobs. And you might say, "Oh, the
whole Uber thing was shit." It's still
working, mate. You know, I was actually
to say I was actually able to save money
on that. I bought a TV and I didn't have
to spend any of my own money cuz I was
working a lot of the time. Doesn't
matter what it was paying, mate. You
could be paying [ __ ] a pound an hour,
you were still [ __ ] working.
That cunt's never had a job ever.
Never had a job in his life. Literally
not even one job. I've had about three or four.
He's never had a job. And I'll be doing
it again soon. So,
try and get a self-employed job somewhere.
And probably the approaching thing is
probably cuz I got nothing better to do
now. I have to wait around now until I
get offered um
until they offer me the thing in it. So
to be honest, like probably the
approaching thing is part of boarding. I
paid for the gym £23. I've got that for
another month. I can't go out spending
loads and loads and loads and loads cuz
then I would have to dip into my savings
and I wouldn't do it anyways and I've
got nothing better to do. Probably if I
had this thing to still do, I wouldn't
approach. It's probably just purely out
of boredom to be honest.
So yeah, but when I do again, I'm not
going to tell you I'm doing it or what I'm doing.
I'm not going to tell you anything. And
that's not because of you. That's
because of these grasses on here. Just
like when I move house, not going to
tell you where I am, that I've moved.
You've got to understand. So, the only
thing you can really say on here is maybe
you got a date, you don't have a date,
rant, what I done today, what I'm doing
tomorrow, not where I'm going. That's
basically the only thing you can
actually talk about on here. You can't
say that you got got a job. You can't
say who anyone is. You can't say what
you're doing as a job because obviously
the grass is so Red Star the pathetic
bed bound [ __ ] loser and some of
these other people.
Am I looking forward to moving? Does it
sound like I'm looking forward to Yeah.
Does it sound like I'm looking forward to moving?
Happen to move all my stuff and losing a
lot of income. I'm not really looking
forward to it, but I've accepted it now
anyways because I've just accepted that
there's there's really nothing you can
do about it. So,
and I'll just be going on holidays doing
it as as well anyway. So, this is what
it is, it nothing anyone can do. So,
who who looks forward to moving, man?
People get mental breakdowns from just moving
cuz it's stressful. I need to get that
TV off the wall. I need to still try and
sell this washing bag, uh, punching bag.
Nothing nothing to look forward to at
all. It's stressful
and it's also ruined other people's
lives as well. So, I don't know what's
there to look forward to about that.
[ __ ] man. But it is what it is. Eh,
>> it is what it is. There's nothing anyone
can do in it.
>> So, yeah, that's why I'm doing the
approaches cuz I got nothing better to
do for like two weeks. This is going to
be the gym and approaches, I think. So,
>> nope. I don't watch him.
How am I getting on to do better things?
I need to try to find another income
now. How is How is that How is that
moving on to better things?
Yeah, I've got savings. Yeah, I still
get money. Yeah, I can still save,
but not as much as I was. But it doesn't
matter anyways cuz still got my but I
need to try to find a second income
because I like doing that [ __ ] Uber thing.
I like doing the Uber thing
cuz if you was getting 1.5 1.8 it's
plenty. That's more than enough for one
person with no outgoings.
And I actually like doing it cuz you was
you was actually just working and not
spending. So can't do just too many
drivers and just works differently
and they don't just take on um new
drivers. I'm going to have to change my
area. I think I'm going to have to say
that I live in some place in Wales, like
some little town, because there's too
many drivers. But just works differently
than Uber. They give you shifts and they
pick your location. Whereas, like you
have to do this in central London. If
you don't do it in central London,
you're not going to make any money.
Simple. Cuz I used to go central London
every time I would do it. If you don't
go central London, you're not going to
make no money. Simple. There's tourist,
rich Chinese students.
Um, so you'd have to go um central
London. Nah, I'm not work I'm not
working at McDonald's. I want a self-employed job.
I want a self-employed job because
obviously when I have savings and I get
money, it's not like I need to work
every day, but some days I'm bored. I
think, oh, I want to work today cuz I'm
bored. Or, oh, I bought something. I
need to make the money back. If it's not
self-employed, I'm not interested. So, it's simple.
Yeah, it needs to be a self-employed
job. That's not a self-employed job.
>> And also, it's the same as security.
It's not a self-employed job. And even
if you do security, right,
um they don't just give you shifts. Um
you need to know people to get shifts.
So, it's not like, say, for example, you
went for security. Yeah.
Um you went for security. Um you pay
£500 for the badge. I think it's like
£540 bad for the badge. If you don't
know anyone to give me ships, you're not
going to get any shifts.
So, you're [ __ ] Basically, that's if
you was going to go for security. I know
people that's got security badges and
they can't get ships and they end up
working as like chefs.
Um, but yeah, Uber Uber Uber's cuz you
can do it when you want. Um,
had a web breakfast earlier. So, yeah.
Yeah, that Polish bouncer was a [ __ ] the other day.
Yeah, I would have gave him a [ __ ]
good hiding, mate.
You know, I might have lost. I'm not
going to say I would have won. I might
lost to be fair. Some of these Polish
people are strong, man. They're not like
um English people weak. A lot of them
compete, but I would have gave it a shot.
What if we just barely fell out? Yeah,
the winter's better for it to be honest
with you. The the the winter's better.
The winter's better. The winter's better
for this job. The summer is hard. That's
why right on that Saturday when they
blocked the roads when when they blocked
um when they blocked the road,
the weather was perfect that day. I
would have made like 120 that day if
they didn't block the road. The
temperature was cool. It's better in the
winter. It's the hardest in the summer.
>> Yeah, it's hard in the summer. It's
easy. It's easy in the winter. Well, not
win not cold. Maybe March is probably the best. So yeah,
but it would be sustain sustainable. But
if you're getting 1.8 to [ __ ] two
grand a month, it's enough. Simply it's
more than enough for somebody with no outgoings. Again,
Uber is not a main job. Just is not a
main job. People use it as a main job,
but it's not a main job. It's extra
income. That's what people need to
really understand. It's not a main job.
It's just for extra money. I think a lot
of people get that mixed up.
Again, if you make money from YouTube or
you've got your own business or you want
benefits or you make money somehow where
you're self-employed, that's just
for extra money. It's not to make it's
not um to be used as a full-time job. So,
yeah, they had [ __ ] road work the
other Saturday. It [ __ ] ruined the whole thing. So yeah,
>> it doesn't matter if you be fed up.
There's nothing else you can do. You
need the money. So it's simple. It
doesn't matter, bro. I was fed up when I
I was fed up some days of doing it. But
guess what? It's still better than most
jobs cuz you're self-employed.
And you get to ride around and see new
places. Yeah, you do get fed up. But who
doesn't get fed up with work? No one
wants to work.
So is get a different job. It's not easy
to get another job and you can't get a
self-employed job. So no,
I'm happy anyways. 1.7 a month, 2K a
month, it's more than enough
to be honest. So yeah, what's up?
Yeah, I'd rather stay on benefits than
not do a self-employed job.
So yeah, I'll be approaching every day
for two weeks, eh? [ __ ]
>> Oh [ __ ] Yeah,
>> you don't get it. Um, the fact that you
can do it when you want, when you want.
You don't get somebody telling you what to do.
Easy, bro. I had enough of them drivers.
That's why I took a couple of days off
cuz I had enough of these [ __ ]
So, that's the that's the drive for it.
You can do it when you want to do it,
you know. and maybe one day you don't
want to do it again and you've saved up
enough money. So that's that's what it
is. You can do it when you want. You
know, who wants to be waking up at 6:00
in the morning like every morning to to
go to work. [ __ ] that. Absolutely [ __ ]
that. You can work the hours you want.
You can take the hours that that you can
do the hours that you want to do. It
makes perfect sense. You know, sometimes
you might not even need to do the work,
but if you need extra money, you will do
it. I'll give you an example, right? Say
they gave the Uber account back. I could
make £200 in two days. Yeah, routine is
good, but not [ __ ] working. Not
working in a [ __ ] routine. That's
[ __ ] Say they gave my Uber account
back. I could do two days a week, go out
on a night out, and still save. Two days
a week. I could do two days, make enough
money for a night out, and still save
all the rest of my money. Again, it's
it's not a main job. I don't think you understand.
Even if you made 150, 200, you go out
every week, you save the rest of your money.
So that's two days. And also, it's a
good thing because you have time for you
you have time for other things.
If you worked every day, you won't have
time for the gym.
Yeah, that was Sunday. Yeah, that was
Sunday. That was a [ __ ] day. So, I've
worked out and then the other two days,
one I made 86 and one I made
88, 90. But either way, let's just say
give or take
150 to 170 in 2 days. That's more than
enough for two days work and I get time
for the gym and other things. If you
work every day, you don't have time for
other things. I haven't been to the gym
in [ __ ] ages. Well, now I've got
stress now, but I had too much. I was
too busy with Uber. So yeah. Okay. Let's
just say 150 150 to
170 for argument sake. That's enough. If
you've got no outgoings,
what's that extra month? That's 170 170
340. Let's say 350 350 7. That's 1,800 a month
for somebody that doesn't pay anything.
£1,800 is more than enough.
So, I know it is. It's You can make over
£100 a day. You can make over £100 a
day. You can probably make about 120.
You can make £100 a day. So,
you can make over £100 a day if you time
it right. On Tuesday, I done 5 hours and
I made 56. And that was a Tuesday.
56. So, you can make over 100. You can
Trust me, you can.
But obviously, I was new to it. You can
make over 100. Definitely. I was still
getting orders. Maybe 110 to 120. I'd
say roughly 110 to 120 you could do. So,
say 2 days, say any say anywhere from
150 to about 200.
And then you would be on 1.8K
a month. Yeah. With no outgoings. It is enough. Simple.
No, he's not. So what? He's earning So
what? He's earning almost two grand a month.
I don't think so.
So he's earning more than two grand a month.
Really? I don't think so. There's no way
he's earning more than two grand a month.
No, he [ __ ] is not.
He [ __ ] ain't. Are you talking about
that gay guy? No, he's not. No, he's not
earning more than 1.8K a [ __ ] month.
No, he [ __ ] is not. So,
yeah, I need to try and beat someone
anyways before I get really old.
I shouldn't have to still be doing this.
I should be settled down now, mate. I'm
getting [ __ ] old.
You know, I'm getting [ __ ] old, mate.
I should be [ __ ] settled down, man. But yeah.
Yeah. Sat behind the desk. Yeah. And
that's why he's so fat, cuz he doesn't
do anything. At least with the bike,
you're getting exercise. At least you're
not being abused by people. At least
you're not being called a load of names.
You just have to deal with [ __ ]
shitty cyclists that can't that start
[ __ ] they can't finish. Yeah, you sat
behind the desk, bro. Why do you think
he's so fat?
No, honestly, mate, I would I would I
would choose that.
Yeah, I would I wouldn't even do
security. That's I wouldn't even do that.
That that security guard, he would have
got [ __ ] up that day, bro. I swear he
would have cuz I would have went back if
I lost. Trust me, I would have went back.
He knew he'd get [ __ ] up, bro. Like,
they they don't understand that in
London, this is why they don't There's
two reasons why they don't [ __ ] with
people in London. A because they can
they can Yeah. I wasn't getting abuse. I
was getting sly comments.
No, no. I got I got I got sly comments.
I didn't get abuse. I got like stupid
little sly comments. People mumbling
under their breath. And then when I
asked them to come back and stop walking
away and I parked the bike, they walked
off cuz they're [ __ ] So they're
typical Londoners that can start [ __ ]
they can't finish. But the reason they
don't start I'll answer your question in
a minute on people in London is cuz a
they'll lose their badge and b they
don't know what people are carrying in
London and they wouldn't want to mess
with somebody carrying a knife, you
know. But in Wales they've got this
[ __ ] security top. It's red and they
they will fight anyone. They will they
will fight you in Wales. But I know that
for for a fact because I've seen them. I
remember that time the guy almost
[ __ ] landed on me. But in London, A,
they'll lose their badge. There's a time
there's a chance them losing their bad
badge. And B, you could be coming a
knife. They don't know you, bro. You You
live in London.
So they're not they're not willing to
take that risk. But I told him like,
"Tell me when you finish work and I'll
come run, you know, I'll meet you after
work." And yeah, the problem was I went
into uh this the the the bar.
Still don't think I Well, you Oh, I done
a video on this about I actually done a
video where I stuck it on him, but I'm
not putting it up cuz I don't need to
prove anything. But it doesn't that
stuff does not matter anyways, bro. But
I went into the bar. I approached three
women in the space of 2 hours, which I
don't think was a lot. It was 2 hours. I
I spent money on drinks. And even if I
even if I approach 50 people in in 3
hours, you're not single. It's a bar and
a club. You're allowed to talk to who
you who you want. It's a free country.
You're not causing any harm. You know, I
had people speak to me. I had people
approach me. Um I had people approach me
and some black guy did was talking. And
I had people talk to me as well. And we
was talking and normal stuff and
he comes over to me and he says, "Oh,
um, yeah, we've had, um, some complaints
now." Well, no, he pulled me up and I
thought it was the trackuit bombs. It's
got to be the tracksuit bottoms. They
don't like trackuit bottoms, even though
you're technically allowed to wear them
before the bouncer comes. I'm thinking
he's going to make any excuse to throw
me out for the trackuit bottoms. And he
says that we've had complaints. Now, I
have never had a woman complain about me
ever, let alone four people that are not
related to each other that was in a
group of two cuz they weren't
interested. I just, "Okay, I'll just go
back and whatever." Didn't say anything.
Um, so it was the staff. It must have
been the staff watching you speak to
people and then they just like radioed
through to the bouncer which just
contradicts their whole thing because
they tell you that approaching on the
street is weird and now you can't even
go to bars and clubs and even speak to
people without getting kicked out.
Doesn't make any sense. And no one
complained because eventually they just
left anyways. Um, so no one there's no
way any of them they were sat in the
same place and no one come over to them.
Um, so it's like
this does doesn't make any sense. You
know, when I went to Gregs earlier, I
was like one day something in this
country will actually make sense.
Some someday it will make sense, you
know, but it just doesn't make any
sense. You're a single person, you know,
you're you're in a bar. You're not There
was no argument. There was nothing.
There was no argument, no sarcastic
comments, not one thing. And then they
say that you, you know, you have to go
cuz you're Yeah, they just made an
excuse. Personally, I just think it was
the Traxxy bombs. So,
and then oh, so how how that come about
is I said, oh, like this is how people
used to meet years ago. You know, you
only think it's weird cuz of Tik Tok and
Instagram. And he said, "Oh, if you keep
giving me attitude, I'm going to I'm
going to snatch the drink out your
hand." And he tried pulling the drink
out of my hand. I pulled it back. Yeah.
It went on the floor and then like he
tried pushing me. I pushed him back like
and obviously I went outside and I told
him to come around the corner. So like
it's it's even but that's all irrelevant
that who won, who lost, if it never
happened. The point is the whole thing
is weird. The whole thing is [ __ ] up.
like they just contradict themselves.
Like they literally make up the whole
their whole rules as well. And then the
first pub that I went to, I ordered a
burger and I had to repeat myself 10
times to get the I was like what is
going on in this country? I've not been
out for one month. Like think about it.
Yeah. One month and what the [ __ ] have I
come back to? A load of old bollocks.
So um yeah, it just it just it feels
like this country is just designed to
annoy you. I actually feel like it is. But so, um,
yeah, no one complained at all. No one.
That's the only thing I' I've never had
in my my years of approaching is
someone complain or
run to a strange, never had it.
So three and a half years later, what's
the chances that four people, three
people, sorry it was, it wasn't four
people, it was three people, all decided
to dislike complain. It's [ __ ] bro.
It really, really, really, really is [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying, Joe? I had
some conversations with some other
people as well. It seems like the only
people you can get a conversation out of
nowadays is the older generation that
aren't from London and they can kind of
understand, you know? So,
this country is far from normal. Yeah,
it's definitely far from normal.
>> Yeah. So, yeah, I'll probably um
probably avoid that.
So, is what it is?
It's bad, ain't it?
Are you there, Joe?
So, he didn't really have a problem.
It's just I'm not You're not going to
snap the drink out of my hand. Like, who
are you talking to? So, and obviously it
wasn't him. It's somebody obviously
radio through to him. But still, like,
you're not talking to me like that. I
don't care how big you are. I don't give a [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying? So, like
Yeah, it's just it's just negative and I
don't even like talking about it. It's just negative.
>> I mean, don't you think it's bad enough
the whole dating thing and the whole, you know,
the whole like people in this country
without having to deal with that? You
know what I'm saying?
I'd rather have a Guinness, but there's no point.
>> Do I don't want to drink today. Huh?
It's not funny, mate. Everyone in the
[ __ ] street was looking.
Everyone in the street was looking, bro.
It's not funny.
It ain't funny, bro. Everyone on that
street was looking. [ __ ] off me.
It is kind of funny looking back on it,
but it wasn't funny. Then
you'd have to visit me in hospital if I
got this. Why I'm not scared of anyone
is cuz I've been through the worst, bro.
Like I've slept on the [ __ ] stairs,
you know? I didn't know where I was
sleeping. I've been through madness. So,
do you think a bouncer was going to
scare me? Like, think about it, bro.
When you've been through like mad [ __ ]
in your life. Yeah. Struggle where you
don't know whether you're coming or
going. You can't be scared of anyone. You understand?
Yeah. I might have a Guinness, you know. Maybe ever.
>> I never drink on Sunday, bro. No. No.
I want to shot a baby.
>> I want to shot a baby. Guinness. >> Guinness.
>> I love you. You ever had baby Guinness?
Who? It's [ __ ] sexy, bro.
>> Yeah, I'm going to get one. [ __ ]
Even though it's a winter drink, but
yeah, I'm I have to be here for a couple
of hours. Long story. So, cuz I'm locked
out the other house cuz no one's in. So,
I had some piggies today.
I'm still spending a lot even though I
need to really cut back on my spending.
had a breakfast today and I want a [ __ ] drink.
[ __ ] wish it wasn't easy.
I might say, can I have a Guinness, please? Can
I'm just hurt me wrong. Baby, bro. Oh,
>> what does he say? >> Sorry.
>> Can I get a Guinness, please?
>> Can I get a Guinness and a baby Guinness, please?
>> A Guinness baby. Yes, please.
>> So, if I was like the virgin, I'd have
to think about that a little bit more.
Steven Howard would
if I was the uh if I was the skin virgin
a month. I can still say it. I can still
say it now. It say I'm still going to
say it, mate. Even if I get £300 a
month, I'm still going to say it.
Yeah. I need to I need to put the phone
in my pocket though for two seconds cuz
I don't want to drop this drink.
No, it's a goodness and it's a shot.
You okay, Captain?
Thank you, C. That's what I'm going to
say in it. Thank you, C. You ever see
that one of the my friends, he said that
to the guy at work. He said, "Thank you,
cunt." He's like, "What did he say?" He
said, "What's your tongue?" He said,
He's like, "Thank you."
He's like, "What did you say?
What's your tongue?" Is that
what I got?
>> Thank you.
>> It wasn't me, bro. It wasn't me. How
could it have been me? Thank you.
You can you hear me? Yeah. Sorry about
that. I had to put my phone off. Yeah.
So, these are the two drinks that I got.
>> One second.
Let me try and hide everything. So,
these little grasses don't find out
where I am.
We like to try to get people
kicked out of places
cuz they got a life with YouTube.
That's the shot
and that's the Guinness.
So, it's a Guinness and a baby Guinness. >> Yeah.
And you know what? Yeah. I think I'm
actually a a good ex-friend.
A good I actually feel like I'm a good
ex-friend. Like I I literally said that
I I would meet up with the Lanki Virgin
so to help him lose his virginity and he
tried to get me kicked out of pubs.
And I'm glad he did, you know, cuz that
woman was a [ __ ] I repeated myself 10
times and she still didn't [ __ ]
listen. You know what I'm saying? Like I
literally said, "What's in a baby one?"
I don't know. It's just called a baby Guinness.
Um, and I did say like
I was helping him maybe lose his
virginity, but then he tries to get
people kicked out of pubs.
You understand? It's not It's not easy
being a virgin at 31.
I can only imagine, you know, I hated
being one when I was 16,
you know. Oh yeah, Joe, I had sex um 3
days ago. It was the first time in about a year.
Yeah. And she was like, "Oh, you can't
finish in my mouth." So, I thought, "You
know what? [ __ ] this. I'm just going to [ __ ] today."
I had sex for one year. I don't like I
don't care about sex. It's
>> all about the [ __ ] and the kissing. You know,
you know, I was a maybe a year. It's got
to be a year. It has to be a year. Maybe,
you know, it's nothing wrong with being
a virgin at 31. You're just a late bloomer.
Nothing wrong with being a late bloomer.
For the first time in a year, Joe, I'm not ask.
Even the 19year-old used to come around.
I never [ __ ] her. She just gave Peter
Belly a blowj. That's it.
>> That's it. Nothing else.
We did speak about doing anal at some
point, but we didn't get that far. She
started turning all western eyes and [ __ ] so
my sister l had a good dinner.
I don't like drinking. It makes me do
really mad things.
He needs to get laid. That's what I
think. He needs to get [ __ ] laid.
>> I was watching some videos in Glasgow,
Joe, and it looks quite rough there.
It looks quite rough.
I'm going to show my face, but I don't
want these people to know where I am cuz
they tried to Why do they even get
people kicked out of pubs? Because A,
you can just go to another one cuz
there's [ __ ] millions in London. And
B, they're going to lose content.
They're going to literally lose
They're going to literally lose content
by doing that. So, what's Why do they do
it? It's stupid.
No, I'm just having a Guinness and a baby Guinness.
It just don't make sense why
why you would do it.
Just doesn't make any sense at all.
Especially somewhere like [ __ ]
London, you know where you just go to
your next place and next place. Just
doesn't make sense why you'd even do
that. I had a roast dinner today. I had
a breakfast and I had a roast dinner
cooked by Laney. They're sat at home
alone. Ain't got no life. Can't take a
day off of YouTube. They're all skin.
I was saying this, bro. Got my little
cap on. Oh my god, that's a bit dirty. One second.
See me better now.
No, still not gambling. I can't afford
to now, mate. I've got savings and
stuff. I need to do stuff with that
money now, mate. Nah, no gambling. Nope.
Unless you count 20 last Monday, but nah.
Sorry, mate. You can't be doing that again.
Gave up before.
Well, Nicolo, I've actually um said that
I'm going to um be approaching for two
weeks in a row
um from tomorrow after the gym because
this ain't no life, mate. This ain't no
life for any young person.
It ain't no life for any young person.
I went outside. I got three numbers. I
didn't even get any [ __ ] replies.
And I was speaking to someone for
[ __ ] yeah, I'm going to do it. I've
had enough of it, mate. And I've got
nothing better to do because I can't
work yet. So I literally have nothing
better to do, but they don't come and
sit next to me. No, I will I will do it,
bro. I will do it cuz I have nothing
better to do. I can't work at the
minute. So yeah,
I would do it. I've got nothing better
to do and I won't be spending any money. So
trying to find a candidate for baby
Peter. Hey, never happening, mate.
I'm back on the dating apps. They're [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] hell. [ __ ] me. Bro,
this Guinness gets you [ __ ] bro. It's
more of a winter drinkiness.
Back to charging. E.
Yeah, I got no replies.
No replies. Speaking to one for half an
hour from New Zealand.
Just not interested in this country.
Simple as that.
Do you reckon I should I should I should
start Tik Tok?
You think I should start Tik Tok? [ __ ] bro.
>> Yeah, I'm going to have to do it, bro.
No, I'm going to do the baby one after.
Oh, I could do it now.
I'm going to do it after.
But I can't afford to be going that
gambling now, bro. Already wasting
enough money and time doing it. I don't
know what the [ __ ] it's got in it.
Oh, imagine up in USA is his boobies
now, Joe. E,
and you know, I tell you what the bad
thing is with escorts, right? Nicolo and
Joe is all their boobs are all their
boobs are fake. So, you don't really get
much fun cuz they're all most of them are fake.
They spend thousands to have them done.
So, they're no good.
Whereas other people, they're a natural. So yeah, stop swearing.
That's really naughty.
So I was just speaking to that bloke
over there. But yeah, most of them have
got like fake fake ones. Yeah.
Shame that 19year-old was such a [ __ ]
She would have been perfect, isn't it? Yeah, man. Nah.
It's so funny. When I called a [ __ ] the
other day, she's like, "Hello,
[ __ ] pair of cunts."
Nah. And then that [ __ ] bouncer tried
[ __ ] being a [ __ ] Tried
snatching the drink out of my [ __ ]
hand. I pulled it back. [ __ ] went
everywhere. Like the tiny bit that was
[ __ ] back. He tried pushing me. Yeah,
I pushed him back. I told him to come
outside. [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] What do
you think? Cuz you're a bouncer. Yeah.
And you're big that I'm scared of you. I
ain't scared of you, bro. Even if I
would lose, I'm not scared of you. I'm
not scared of no one, bro.
And I'm pretty aware that there's a
chance I could have lost, but
I was willing to take that risk, bro. It
But it's more the numbers that are
disgusting. It is disgusting, bro. It is
disgusting. And it really is in this
country. And one of them I was speaking
to for half an hour from New Zealand. We
just talking about loads of different
things in life and nothing. She seemed
like she would have at least replied
back. Obviously, you always kind of know
the ones that are and ones that aren't.
Strange she didn't reply back. That was
really weird considering like I'm
probably the nicest person from London
she's ever going to meet. And we was
talking for ages. It wasn't like you can
tell sometimes. Yeah. And they're not
going to reply, but
same [ __ ] in it.
Same [ __ ] in it, bro. Oh well.
That [ __ ] Indonesian guy keeps
[ __ ] messaging me, bro. I said,
"Listen, stop inviting me out. I'm not coming out."
I don't know. And she was it was we were
talking about different things like
hobbies and like proper we both
drinking. We was talking like long bro
like proper like good chats for ages
ages bro. And she couldn't even reply.
That's mad. And the other one was Irish
but and then the other one it was like 50/50.
Nope. Stop asking stupid questions. If
I'm surprised by something,
then I obviously didn't do anything
wrong. And they were talking for ages
and ages and ages asking me things like
just norm. And then they don't even reply.
So that's why you need to leave this
country, bro. And I thought, well, maybe
they're busy traveling, but they were
busy traveling. Maybe to Spain. They
said they were going, but then they
still didn't reply. time. Yeah.
You need to leave this country, brother.
That's what you need to do.
>> Yeah. [ __ ] in it, bro. It's Oh, [ __ ]
That hurts my bum hurts, bro. So, yeah.
Not only will it ever change in this
country, it gets worse.
Not only does it not change, it also gets worse.
Nope. I'm out drinking.
Other thing I don't like about goodness
is it gives you the shits.
Yeah. Goodness gives you the shits, bro.
Don't even feel like drinking to be honest.
No, I'm not sending it. I sent it on Saturday.
It was just the same old.
So, yeah, I'll do some tomorrow and I'm
come out to the gym maybe.
Nah, there's no point sending it same old.
It was the same old Saturday as well. Name old.
It will never change in this country. Delayed. Never.
Never. Ever. Ever. Ever. Ever. Ever.
Well, considering I don't gamble. No.
Oh, [ __ ] me.
I think it's time for that Guinness shot, man.
Oh, man. [ __ ]
Yeah, considering I don't gamble now.
Gamble anymore. No.
Oh, look at my little cap. Right.
One, two. Wait. No, let go first.
One, two, 3.
That's so nice. That is Oh,
you never had a baby get this, you
should definitely definitely try it.
It's [ __ ] lush.
How do you explain it? It's sort of like um
no, I might do it in the gym. I might
not. I'm descending it tomorrow anyway.
Sober. Doesn't matter where it is. But
you still got to get the same old.
That baby Guinness is lovely. It's sort of like
chocolate. I think it tastes like
sort of like
you're trying to explain the act. It's a
bit like chocolate gate.
Yeah, it's a bit like chocolate gate.
Does that make sense? If you had
chocolate gate, that's what it tastes like. Yeah.
It's lovely though. Can't have the key
though. [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] that, mate. Yeah.
They're just on.
>> Yeah. But what happens when you
approach? What will happen if you approach them?
boyfriend in it. And you know what's so
mad is I bet you these women Yeah, will
will complain when they're in their 30s,
40s. Oh, I can't find a normal person. I
can't find a nice guy. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no. That's what's going to happen.
That's what's going to happen, mate. Yeah.
Yeah, that's what's going to happen.
He said if he stayed here, he would have
ended up raping someone. And mama said
the other day, if I stayed here, he
would have ended up raping someone.
I was dead. Like it's not funny, but
like it's the way he said it. He said he
would have ended up raping someone.
Yeah, that's what he said. Yeah.
He's [ __ ] mad, isn't it?
>> But what was it? What was he right
about? What about them not being
interested in this country? Yeah, he was
right. They aren't interested in this country. Obviously, bro,
look at my experiences
and they'll be like, "Oh, well, they
aren't interested in you." Yeah. They're
not interested in me and they're not
interested in 80 90% of other people in this country.
I think they're not interested in most
people. I think what it is is the people
that are in relationships met through
work or maybe they got lucky. I mean,
yeah. And like 80 90% of other people
idiot otherwise there wouldn't be so
many people struggling
and everyone says the same thing or most
people anyway. So it's like
yeah, tomorrow's going to be torture.
Tomorrow's going to be [ __ ] But
is what it is, eh? I can't even give
Frankie a world cuz they don't have
fishing friends here.
Maybe I would have like a cheeky uh 20
pounding, but you can't play him here. No,
no, you don't have that slot here.
Maybe, maybe not.
Oh, [ __ ] bro. [ __ ] all the time. The
skinny [ __ ] You got a boyfriend, do
you? Whatever is
I still need to say that one day.
Who do you think would have won that
fight, Nicolo? Me or that bouncer?
I would have [ __ ] slapped him up, bro.
You think I would have won? I think I
would have won here. I'm
I might sound delusional, but I think I
would have won. Yeah.
I should have never turned into that,
right? Everyone in the street was looking. One second.
>> He's going paved. Oh, hello.
No, I couldn't cuz the joke was already
finished or most of it.
What? P it and then ran. Do you reckon
all ped it and then stayed? What them?
You know what I find for so long? Yeah.
If say I had to start here 3 years ago
now like getting less money getting it
being worse getting less money less
money. Yeah it's worse now. Imagine
happen to start 3 years ago now you'd be fed
cuz you even think to yourself sometimes
how do you even get anything like
or death or whatever
now you finally get a conversation out
of someone I mean how and that's how you
know that it's got worse it has to have
got worse because
it was like I keep saying it was it
wasn't this bad two and a half [ __ ]
years ago mate it was bad but it weren't
this bad it's always been bad.
But yeah, it never changes either.
Just gets worse.
Oh, what? There's no [ __ ] paper. Hold on. [Applause] someone.
Stop talking about yourself again. Wrong channel.
Stop talking about yourself. And And
listen, I was talking about this other
day. You know these people on YouTube, bro? Yeah.
You know why they're so obsessed with skin people? Yeah, £700.
Yeah, now I'll be on like maybe 11,200
until I can start working. But I got
savings and stuff. So yeah, three No, it
wasn't 3 years ago. It was more like
four years ago. I was getting like 700.
I just have to save like 300 a month for
something in it.
Yeah, it was 700, but
you just adjust anything you get
anyways. Doesn't matter.
But yeah, anyways, back to these people.
Do you know why they call people skint
every day? Cuz these people are skin.
They don't even get a grand a month,
bro. They get [ __ ] £300 a month.
That's why they're sat on YouTube every
day hating. They got life.
Think about it.
They say, "Oh, you don't know us. You
don't know us." Why they sat on YouTube
every day hating? If they got all this
money and everyone else is skin, why are
they sat on YouTube every day hating?
Think about it, bro. It don't add up.
Just like I said in my other video, cuz
they are the skin ones.
The proper proper skin ones.
Yeah. 700 I was getting. Yeah.
I get like maybe like,00
which is if you save most for a month,
you basically have some more money anyway. So
not the worst.
Well, when you're used to being on like
[ __ ] three grand a month, it
different, but doesn't matter. Doesn't matter.
Got savings anyway, so not a big deal.
It is what it is.
I'm just mad how you uh
how you haven't seem to found anyone, bro.
I'm not getting into it, bro. Anyways,
I'm not getting into it.
I'm just more pissed off the fact we
ain't [ __ ] met someone, bro. Yeah.
Trying to help someone lose their
I'm not talking about it anymore, bro.
Simple. I'm not talking about it anymore.
But we need to sort of change topics.
Shouldn't be what I'm getting. what I
don't have, what I do have. I like we're
not talking about that. Anyways,
just know that I'll always be okay, bro.
Don't worry about me. You know,
it's [ __ ] But it's also a good thing in
many ways as well.
Yeah. I mean, their lives are ruined,
but I'm I'm not [ __ ] But
obviously we're [ __ ] in different
ways. We're all [ __ ] Well, I'm not really [ __ ]
But it's bad and it they're more [ __ ]
than me. Way more [ __ ] than me. Like
they are [ __ ] I'm
[ __ ] temporarily basically. But still,
it's still going to affect me. It's not
even just the income, bro. Because I got
some little savings. It's not like you
don't still get money even though it's
not as much. Still still enough. It's
still enough, bro. Still money.
But think about it. If you get 1100 a
month, yeah, you lived off 300 from say
you you lived off four or 500 for one
month. You was hitting the gym. The next
month you got two grand. So, but they
they are really [ __ ]
But I'm also [ __ ] as well. So,
I'm really really [ __ ] It's not even
just It's not even just about the income though.
Thankful. It's not even just that. It's
just you just [ __ ] it. Hope someone
stole my boss to chair.
No more steak dinners. But USA is in it.
>> Oh, no. Some kind of my hair away then.
I'm having a little drink.
I know. It's crazy, isn't it, bro?
But I've still got money anyways. That's
why I'm doing this two week thing.
But in a way, I tried to see the
positives, Nicolo. I tried to see that
like, yeah, I mean, you still don't have
anyone, but I mean, you still got
savings. You learned that 27. It didn't
take you 31 to go to Thailand. You still
had sex. And you know, there's always a
way out. And yeah, you had some good
Yeah, you didn't meet anyone and stuff,
but you had good times. You had sex,
you know, so it's still better than a
lot of people, but it is just it is
[ __ ] up how you didn't meet anyone.
Yeah. Like there's no denying that. That
That's the most [ __ ] up thing about
it, I think.
So, it's like you're not ugly, you're
decent looking, you're good-looking,
you, you know, you smell good and that,
have money and that and you should have
had some, you should have met someone by
now because obviously you was trying
more than most people, you know. We went
to Wales one week, then the next week we
went to Wales again.
Um, I used to do mad things, bro. So,
it's like that is [ __ ] up. Yeah. But I
just try to see as well, you know what
to do now. leave the country again. So,
so yeah, it's crazy, isn't it?
We still have money anyway. It's not a
problem, but still.
So, yeah. When do these people on Reddit
tell you it's time to call it a day?
You know what I'm saying, Nicolo? Cuz
they still tell you that you're going to
meet someone even though now you're
going to be on less money. M
yeah it would have been the same it
would have been the same result but you
just wouldn't have got laid there'd be
no USA Izzy there'd be no SIG there'd be
there'd be no Nottingham there'd be no Manchester
but yeah you it would basically it would
have been the same as pretty much yeah
but then you got people on Reddit trying
to tell you that eventually you will
meet someone. See, the thing is, I was
thinking about this earlier, Nicolo.
Yeah. If it was how it was 3 months, 3
years ago and you were 6 months in, I'd
believe it. I'd be like, "Yeah, well,
it's only 6 months. I mean, you've had
some dates. You've had some heartbreaks.
You've had some time wasting." I I' I'd
believe it. You know, 6 months in, I'd
be like, "Okay, yeah, we still have some
sort of hope."
Um, you know, but 3 years is is a long
time, bro. Like if you haven't met
anyone now, you're not going to meet
anyone. It's simple.
Not at this age anyways.
Yep. That's all they ever say.
That's all they ever say, mate.
That's all they ever [ __ ] say. Sorry.
But then I wonder what USA is boobies.
Would I, Nicolo?
Nah, we're not at all.
But the hardest thing to accept, Nicolo,
is you don't look like Timmy Aldridge.
That's the hardest thing to accept. Like
you don't look like Timmy. You're not
[ __ ] fat and ugly. So what's what's
the actual reason?
They don't get to know people's personality.
So what what what the [ __ ] you know
what I'm saying?
No, I can still go on dates. I can still
go on expensive dates.
>> I can if I want to for now anyways, but
no, I could
What the [ __ ] was that? No, I could
still do it, but
I don't want to do it if it's certified.
You know what I'm saying? But yeah.
>> Yeah, man. But yeah, the thing the
madest thing about it is you don't look
like Timmy Aldridge,
you know? You're not a bad looking
fellow. You should have met someone.
>> You understand this fellow? Like, you
should have met someone. Are >> you?
Well, they tell you that you're negative
and No, no, no, no, no. You know what I'm saying?
That's what they tell you.
But the only way from now is down. But I
just accepted it, so I don't really
care. The only way now is down. There's
no up, only down. But you just accept it
anyway, isn't it?
I can't believe it. How How did I used
to live for £700 a month?
[ __ ] hell. £700 a month, mate.
But there was this guy, he was getting
40 grand a month on YouTube and he had
no he has no savings. Nola,
imagine that. £40,000 a month on YouTube.
[ __ ] yeah, man. I'm still drinking this
Guinness. How the [ __ ] can you even get
40 grand a month on YouTube?
>> Imagine that just hitting into your
account. Yeah. 40 grand from YouTube.
That is insane, bro. It
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Could you imagine getting that? Imagine
that, Stephen Howard. 40 grand a month
on YouTube. Making 40 grand a month on
YouTube. Imagine I made 40 grand a month
on YouTube. Yeah. And I showed it to
these people and there's nothing they
could do to stop it. They would be like
punching themselves in the face in it.
They'd be going mad in it, Nicola. Yeah,
one gay guy told me to uh use dating apps. Nicola.
Yeah, they told me to use um YouTube.
No, they told me to uh they told me to um
they told me to use dating apps.
Who do you think was the best person I
had ever been with?
I don't know. I didn't really like USA.
I just liked her boobies. And to be honest, not sure.
Not sure actually.
Maybe the 19year-old isn't it? Yeah.
The turn out being fun in it. So
there's a lot of them, bro. There.
There's a [ __ ] lot of them.
I'm going to send a video to these
contacts. I'm going to drink here and
send a video to these contacts. Say I'm
getting on it. >> Yeah. Oh [ __ ]
Got another I reckon
is nothing but a skin virgin. Nice hands.
Who's got nice hands?
Like Nicol like even 3 years ago there
was actually chance that I actually
could have been in relationships and I
[ __ ] some of it up cuz of USA is he
but now there's nothing. Like now you
you literally can't even get anything.
But now you can't get [ __ ] all nothing.
I don't know who had nice hands.
Yeah, I said that Italian one. Yeah, she
said she's going back to Italy. So like
what's the point of even going on a date
with me then? What's the point of going
on a date with me? Holding hands
for hours and when someone tries to kiss
you, you don't want to kiss.
And then you're saying that you go,
"What's the why?" And that's another
thing. They go on dates to pass time.
So, it's like that's another thing you
got to deal with.
That's another big thing that you've got
to deal with is that people just go on
dates to pass time,
waste your time and waste their time.
So, you're going back to Italy. What was
So, what was the actual point of them
going on a date with you then? I don't understand it.
Or maybe like they just they go on dates
as like an interview and they're looking
for Mr. Perfect.
Obviously, Mr. Perfect don't exist.
That's also another thing as well. Maybe
they have like an expectation in their mind
of somebody they'll go for and it has to
be that. And if you're not that, then
they just say they don't feel the vibe
or they don't feel the match or um
>> Oh yeah, the one that I met on Bumble.
Yeah. Oh yeah, I could have been in a
relationship with her.
Could have been in a relationship with
maybe four people, but now nothing.
Yeah. Also, I went to Scotland and all I
got when I went to Scotland was an
escort and come all the way back. I
remember. Yeah. I went that day. I went
to Scotland. Yeah.
Second time I went to Scotland, when I
went on the plane, I went to Scotland. I
was sending it hard, bro. Nothing. I
don't think they said I had boyfriend,
but they weren't having none of it at
all. At all.
Then um I just went to get an escort and
then [ __ ] came all the way back. I
remember waking up in Newcastle. I fell
asleep. I got a train all the way back
from Scotland, all the way back to
London. Fell asleep, woke up in [ __ ]
um Newcastle. That's how far I used to travel, bro.
But now you can't even get a sausage.
Not even a [ __ ] sausage.
That man was like, "You got to leave the
country." He left for a better life.
Yeah, I got caught. Yeah, cuz I I tried
to come up to Nicola so early.
It used to be fun to traveling. No responsibilities,
all that money. Nicola.
It was good times. I must have banged at
least 100 esports.
I There was one month I actually got
addicted to to escorts. I remember one
month I spent about £500
just to get my s to just to get my needs
um like satisfied and [ __ ] You know
what I'm saying?
Yeah. I used to do stupid things with
money, bro. I spent £500 one month just
Yeah, it was fun, bro. But
yeah, I used to be a crazy [ __ ]
Yeah, Virgin Boy has never been to
Scotland, has he? Can't afford it.
He lost his um he lost his holiday
virginity a couple of months ago, didn't he? Yeah.
You [ __ ] virgin.
That's what I called him, bro. You [ __ ] virgin.
You [ __ ] virgin, mate.
I got to say it to myself when I'm out,
bro. You're [ __ ] virgin.
You [ __ ] virgin.
>> Yeah, he's such a virgin. I know, bro.
He's such a [ __ ] virgin. Hello.
>> Little copycat. But guess what? I flew.
He never I'm not scared of heights. >> Nikolai. >> Yeah.
How much money do you think Lo J gets a
month? I think he gets £300 a month.
Yeah, he's skinned. years.
LJ J is skimp. He's on benefits. And you
know how you know he's skimp? Because he
begs for money. All that membership that
begging for donations. Do you really
think somebody that has money would be
doing that? He's [ __ ] skinned.
He's skinned, bro. Look how long it took
him to save up for Vegas. He's skinned, bro. Skinn Flint. Yeah,
you can tell the skin bonds on here
because they sit on it all day
every day. They don't go out.
What do you think of USA? Is he Nicolola?
I can't believe the Uber kept taking me
to where I met her.
I know. What would he be doing in a
[ __ ] What would he be doing in
Amsterdam? He can't even [ __ ] He's got
a [ __ ] disabled dick. So, it's not
like he could use escorts,
but to be fair, he probably should have
just fixed his dick and then went to
Amsterdam cuz then he would actually
lost his virginity.
Yeah, I I done it twice when I was in
Amsterdam. If he went Amsterdam. Yeah.
And he [ __ ] He would have actually
lost his virginity.
Think about that. That was that was
actually the best place.
Yeah, he's a proper obsessed virgin. I
reported him to the police as well one
the other day. I report him to the
police again for stalking. So yeah,
should be getting a unlock soon.
Why did Uber kept taking me to where I
met my mama? Nicolai,
why did it kept taking me to where I met my mama?
Yeah, that's where it ended, isn't it? Yeah.
I went to Amsterdam all by myself and I
stayed in a hostel. Yeah.
>> Yeah. I stayed in a [ __ ] Oscar
school, didn't I? Yep.
Why did the Uber keep taking me to where
I met my mama? Nicolo H.
[ __ ] it up.
It's funny, isn't it? Yeah.
Oh, the fatty now.
I'm going to send videos to people.
Yep. About 20 times.
And I also went to Paddington as well.
No, not P. Well, I didn't go to Pton. I
also went to Battery as well. I went Baty, Kensington, Hammersmith,
[ __ ] the Victoria,
Camden, [ __ ] Angel,
[ __ ] Liverpool Street. You [ __ ]
name it. I've done it all, mate. All on
the good old ebike. Yeah.
It was taking me to where I met my one
night slams, but it didn't take me to
like Stratford or anywhere. Yeah.
>> Yep. That's one. E
had some big boobies. Nicolo. Yeah, man.
What a life, eh?
I don't know why it kept taking me to
where I met my mama.
You're sick and twisted, [ __ ]
I'm sick and twisted for you. Oh. Oh wow.
Elephant and Castle kept taking me there
loads of times.
A bless. That was another one Nons was
jealous of. Was it Nicolola?
Instead of like convincing himself
people hasn't slept with people and
stuff, why don't he just like
sort his dick problem out and actually
maybe Sarah might [ __ ] him.
I mean, instead of being insecure and
insecure virgin, think of it, bro.
I can't believe [ __ ] used to do that, bro.
Like stalk [ __ ] people I've been
with. That's [ __ ] weird. That screams
insecure virgin, is it?
[ __ ] weird, bro. Yeah.
It's weird, bro. Is it?
Yeah. He's He's a weirdo. Do you know
what it is? Yeah. It's because he's a
virgin and he can't get sex and he can't
meet these women. He he wants to he
needs confirmation that you've not
[ __ ] them or you ain't been with them.
It's because where he hasn't had it and
he can't get anyone like normal and
[ __ ] Um that's why he does all all of
this like it's it's a form of like comfort.
Um just like the whole She Cole thing just copying.
I never found any of that funny. That is
that is just copying, bro.
Like he only said that she was
attractive just so people didn't think
he was gay. That is embarrassing, bro.
And you know what he said? I'd wear
every color but pink. Why would you be
Why would you wear pink? I wear pink sometimes.
Like I never met anyone to be so
insecure about their sexuality.
All right. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, that Sherlock Hol thing. Yeah,
he's a copycat. You little copycat. I
wanted to tickle his little belly. You
know, there was one time I met him, I
wanted to just like lift him up and just
tickle him. You little copycat. No mind
of your own. No [ __ ] mind of your [ __ ] own.
Cuz look at look at that picture. Yeah.
Of me with this with this [ __ ] Yeah.
On my YouTube profile.
Yeah. Look, I would say that's better
than Shevel Cole. I would say way better
than Shevel Cole. But would you turn
around and say if you don't like this
person in my picture, you're gay. No. So
it's a trend. It's copying.
It is definitely definitely copying. Definitely copying.
He's a copycat. People used to do it
with Beyonce as well.
People used to do it with Beyonce, bro.
Like Yeah, that's old, bro. People used
to do it with Beyonce.
Well, it's not mad because I live in
London and London's a big city. You
wouldn't bump into someone. It's a big city.
Why would you bump into them? You think
Do you know how big London is?
London is massive, bro. What the [ __ ]
Why did I bump into that virgin?
I used to say to him, "You're going to
die one. You're going to die one." And I
used to tell him that I used to [ __ ]
[ __ ] escorts and [ __ ] He wouldn't believe me.
He wouldn't believe me, bro. He thought
I was making it up. No, he did believe
me deep down, but obviously because
because he's a virgin, everyone else had
to be a virgin.
No, that's all mind games, Nicolo.
That's That's all mind games to try to
get you aggravated so you say stuff so
he could try to get the police involved.
Nope. He's never been to anywhere I've
been except one place. That's what you
call mind games, bro.
Just like the whole um going to a pub
that I don't live anywhere near and
pretend pretending to call me out for 5
minutes then jumping on a train home.
It's all mind games to try to get the police involved.
Like everyone knows that now, bro. Like
even Harry Ford never been to anywhere
anywhere near our visit except one place
once which was in central London. So
that's all mind games, bro,
to try to get the police involved.
Pell is a lot smarter than these uh
people on here, bro. You know,
it's like it's like me, right, being in
in in this pub right now, which is
nowhere near LT, and me start saying the
racist maddest things and then coming
off live for 10 minutes, which is trying
to trigger reaction out of him and then
save all the evidence to send to the
police. Yeah, I'm smarter than that, buddy. So,
and I went to the area about three times
and he wouldn't come out. So, I mean,
come on, bro. Everyone knows what this
kid is about now.
So, yeah. And then tries to make you
look a stalker as well. So, they'll do
that. So, you react to try and make you
look like a stalker.
You know what I'm saying? It's just It's
just It's just a [ __ ] virgin. Literally,
who the [ __ ] has time to do all of this stuff,
you know? Who has time to do all of this
stuff? Even Timmy don't do it, bro. [ __ ] madness.
That the thanks I get for trying to get
someone [ __ ] laid.
Do you miss USA is his boobies? Nicolo.
Nah, Isabella will never meet up with me again.
What do you think would happen if me and
USA is he come across each other again?
What do you think would happen, bro? >> Yeah.
Yeah. I smile though. It I have that cheeky smile.
like I have that cheeky smile.
Yeah. I say, "Come and [ __ ] say it to
me now. You need to You need to watch
that bouncer video, bro." The whole
street was looking
The whole street was looking, mate. The
Oh, bless her.
Maybe she'd give me kissing again,
Nicolo. I do miss them kisses.
I do miss them kisses. Them kisses were nice. You know,
it was done with such passion and such love.
I haven't pulled it up, bro.
>> The whole [ __ ] street was looking for
Yeah, it was done. That kiss was done
with such love, Nikolai.
It was done with such love.
And I said, "Can I get a hand job?" She
said, "There's nothing in that for me." Oh,
>> yeah. That was done with such love and
such passion. It feels nice when you get
kissed like that, you know that.
I know how to push I know. I knew how to
push her buttons
and get her in the mood, you know. Yeah.
I started like kissing her lip and that
and then biting it and that.
Yeah. Then I started kissing her neck
and then then Yeah. Then she done this
and I was like, "Okay." I knew how to
get the [ __ ] in the mood. Yeah. And
that's what I was doing. I was like a
little bit like kissing the lip a little
bit, you know, turning you on after the white wine.
And then she grabbed me and pulled me.
She said, "Listen, look." He pulled me
towards her and then she started kissing
you know this and she was like she
started like she almost ate me up. You
know the maddest thing is Nicolola
is that her and the original Izzy both
come on to me and they talk the most
[ __ ] They're the only two that's ever
come on to me and they talk the most [ __ ]
Yeah, they are definitely two. They're
the only two that have
I'm trying to think. Yeah.
Such passion and such love. Nicolo. Yeah.
Bounces. All right, bro. Usually they're
all right, but he was just a [ __ ] in
London. They're they're all right.
Usually they're all right.
But what would have you done if you got
into a fight with a bounce and you lost?
I would have went back with a hammer,
mate. I'm not going to lie. I would have
went back with a weapon. Yeah.
I would have had to, bro. Right. You
know what I'm saying? I would have had to.
[ __ ] that. We don't take no L's, boy. Yeah.
No, [ __ ] that.
Even if I ended up in the ambulance, I
still would have went back for more. You
know what I'm saying? Yeah.
Do you remember that one in Cardiff,
Nicolo? Do you remember? Do you remember
the fight in Cardiff?
Yeah. That was a mad piss, bro. I was
like, what have I got into?
Yeah, you saw that Cardiff one. Do you
remember Stephen H? That was [ __ ] mad, bro.
No, that was mad. That was mad.
That was [ __ ] mad, bro. It went on
for like 10 minutes. Yeah. All you see
is like I was watching. Yeah. It was
before I walked in the old Cardiff.
Yeah. There's like that bit where you go
down the stairs like next to five guys
and all of a sudden and then all of a
sudden, bam. All you see is like loads
of people falling over. I was like,
"What the fuck?" Like all you see was a
load of people falling over and it
ended. It It went on for about 15
minutes, bro. I'm not even joking. It
went on for ages and the security went
around the corner, didn't it?
You don't remember that? No, it was bad,
bro. It was really bad. Yeah.
No, it was really bad.
No, you remember that, ain't it, Nicolo?
Bro, you do remember that on the other channel. Yeah,
the guy was like, I'm tearing you away.
He wanted some, bro. They were
Bro, that was a madness.
I didn't start. I weren't even involved.
Yeah. Why Nicolo, don't you remember
that? I don't even have the channel to
show you it anymore.
Let me type on YouTube mad. I think it's
titled madness inside it.
>> Definitely. Where was it?
It was mad, bro.
No, bro. Yeah,
>> in London.
Yes, that was a madness.
Ah, they've all got boyfriends.
They've all got boyfriends.
How's it going, Antman? Have another
Guinness. How's it going, Antman? Hello. I
want to find something [ __ ]
No, I don't think anyone has a video
anymore, but mate, it was bad.
I'm surprised someone didn't get [ __ ] killed.
A load of old Bill showed up.
Load of old Bill.
I'm going to have another goodness.
Just got my Todd out.
Oh [ __ ] We're trying to find it. Was it
madness and caught it? Let me see.
I [ __ ] on her somewhere.
Yeah, it happens a lot, mate.
It happens a lot.
Why love a baby one?
for a [ __ ] other [ __ ]
Why not give it a world? I would
give it a while.
I'm having a good [ __ ]
Can I get a Guinness and a baby Guinness, please? >> Yeah.
>> Thank you.
>> Thank you so much.
served. I've been served. Yeah. Cheers.
>> You know that time l come to the house?
That's mad. Imagine traveling all the
way. Yeah. From Ireland to come on
someone's door over YouTube
said you Grezy, you said the neighbors
heard, didn't you? Thank you.
Yeah, by Greasy. Do you remember the um
Cardiff video, bro? You remember the
Cardiff one with all the bounces flying?
You remember that, don't you? On the
other channel. Oh, madness.
Yeah, I'm having a baby Guinness Queen Z.
you remember that green, don't you? that one. >> Yeah.
Yes, you do remember, don't you?
>> Yeah, that C. Hey, look. Look, Rey,
look what I got. Oh, mate, I'm [ __ ] this.
Oh, baby. Get this.
Oh, well maybe I should [ __ ] me.
Yeah, [ __ ] it up, bro. My second round as well. Jeez.
I can't stop thinking when I was
laughing in spec spec spec savers
yesterday with my friend. He said, "Why
are you laughing like a cunt?" I could I
couldn't stop thinking of Bungle. You
know Bungle the bear. Oh, bless you.
Bungled the little bear.
I was dead, bro. You said you're
laughing like a person.
Oh, some of it went on my mustache.
Yeah, I'm kind of missing my mother.
You know who my mama is, don't you? Kind
of missing my mama.
Yeah, I'm kind of missing my mama.
Weezy. How cute is that?
I'm missing all the nutrients. I'm
trying to get the nut I'm trying to get
the I'm trying to get the nutrients back
from um the Guinness.
One of my friends said, "Yeah, how is it
funny, bro? I'm going to be homeless.
How is it funny?" Yeah.
He says, "You think it's [ __ ] funny?"
I said, "No, it's not funny."
I It's not funny, though, is it? No. No.
It's not funny, bro. Someone going
homeless is not funny.
It's not funny, is it? No.
I think I laugh at everything. B.
Yeah. So, does that mean since my mama
abandoned me, Grezy, I'm going to have
problems? Is it going to affect me mentally?
Is it going to affect mentally, Grezy,
for the rest of my life? Then I was
talking about when we kissed and stuff, Greasy.
You know, I was biting her. I was
kissing her little lips like this. Look.
And then I done it one more time. Um,
and she grabbed me. She grabbed me.
Yeah, she grabbed me and started like
really kissing me and stuff.
Why do you think it's You think it's
funny, do you, Harry? You think it's funny?
You think it's funny, Harry, that I'm
going to be homeless. You think it's
funny, do you?
You think it's [ __ ] funny that I'm
going to be homeless? Yeah,
>> it's not funny, bro. It's not funny.
Yeah. The guy was like, I'm not
laughing, bro. He says, "We are [ __ ]
up now." Boom. I said, "We're all fucked."
So, like, "Everyone in the house is
[ __ ] in it." Yeah.
Everyone in the house is Everyone in the
house is [ __ ]
Hey, look. Have you ever had a baby Guinness? Harry,
have you ever had a baby?
Have you ever had a a baby Guinness?
It's [ __ ] lost, mate.
You ever had one?
I keep hearing that Scot Scottish accent
everywhere today. Grezy in two different
pubs I went in. I keep hearing this.
This is Celtic playing or something.
Oh, them Celtic Hey, is Celtic playing
or something? What's they say? Celtics
got to be playing somewhere, is it? Cuz
there's too many Scottish people down here.
Are you sure Celtic ain't playing somewhere, mate?
Dude, I've come across so many Scots
people the past couple of days, bro.
Definitely Celtics got to be playing. Yeah.
[ __ ] I'm Bro, I'm [ __ ] bro.
Yeah. Are they playing Scotland or something?
So, who's my daddy then? Um,
Greasy, who's my daddy? Huh?
Who's my d?
Tell me, bro. Who's my daddy? Huh?
What are they doing with them glasses?
They must um
put in a dishwasher or something.
>> You can get finished classes.
So, who's my mama and who's my dada? Hello, CL.
How can Fraser be my daddy?
I don't have a da. My dad died.
I only have a mama.
Yep. Gym tomorrow, bro. Gym tomorrow, 100%. Yeah, man.
No point starting something you can't
finish. There we go.
You think it's funny? I'm going to be homeless.
Always wanted your phrase. No, the
saying goes like this. Yeah. No, the
saying goes like this. I always wanted
your phrase. Even if it was only up the ton.
Even if it was only up the pun.
That's what there
have a mama.
Do you like my silly little ways?
Do you like my silly little ways? Had a
roast beef today and a roast pork. My
mama made it for me. Yep. I love pork.
I think it's quite
>> quite tasty actually.
>> Oh, bro.
Time for another shot. No, not this shot. [ __ ]
Well, I am [ __ ]
Do you actually think it's funny that
I'm going to be homeless?
I think it's quite funny.
I think it's quite funny. Do you? Yeah.
I I love piggies.
I don't care what they I love piggies.
They're quite tasty. [Applause]
You like my silly little ways. Grooy.
Would you like my silly little A's? Yeah.
>> Lucky it's not white in it. Oh [ __ ] Literally
I took [ __ ] shot. So all of this cost
£16 which ain't bad.
It's not too bad is it? £16, two
Guinnesses and two shorts.
Remember that day in the pub, Gooey?
This is the only time I'm not going to laugh.
That pub in central London
last year ago, bro.
You remember last year them Celtic [ __ ]
were laughing at us? I [ __ ] I [ __ ]
stood my [ __ ] ground, bro. You
remember Tammy? I was trying to track
down Tammy. I still can't I still can't find Tammy.
Tammy from Glasgow. Still can't find the [ __ ] man.
He was a [ __ ] though. He was
Oh, he was a [ __ ] bro. He was a [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. Trying to see if there's anyone around.
Not you. But
right, we're going to do once we split
the G, we're going to do a shot. Yeah.
Did you hear that laugh? It made me laugh. Yeah. Hello.
We can't find him. We know he's in Glasgow somewhere.
Every time I watch Glasgow videos, it
reminds me of him. Rezy.
Yes, Celtic must have been playing
recently, bro, cuz there's been a lot of
Scottish people down here.
Let me see. They must have been playing. One second.
Let me search.
It must have been playing somewhere.
It's somewhere here.
the 27th of July. No, it can't have been that one.
Well, I'm telling you, they must have
been playing someone.
>> There must have been.
>> Does anyone know, bro? No, just having a
couple of drinks for a couple of hours.
Dude, I need to kill some time. So, yeah,
gym tomorrow. So, yeah, man. No. [Music]
Nah, man. It's good to have some pints by yourself.
>> By myself? Who are you with?
Here we go. Where is it? Here we go, bro. Oh,
[ __ ] I've got a nice T. Look at that, bro.
Yeah. Just just killing some time for some reason.
Oh, [ __ ] bro. Really? [ __ ]
People underestimate the effect.
Yeah, you're by yourself as well.
Yeah, I'm by myself, bro. And you're by yourself, too. So, yeah.
You know what? Yeah.
Nah, I've done this before, but it's pointless. Yeah,
I got some big plans tomorrow.
I don't know who it is, but there's been
a lot of Scottish people down here, so
I'm guessing there's something to do with football.
>> Why are you that insecure? You can't go
for a pint by yourself?
Why? Why do do I need to be with friends
all the time?
So, I can't go to a drink and have
I can't go to a drink.
So, I can't go to the pub and have a
drink without a friend. Really? So, I I
can't nip into the pub for a couple of
hours and have a drink by myself.
Why? What's Do I need to constantly be with people?
Do I have to be insecure? Like, what the [ __ ]
I'm not getting offended, bro. I just
didn't know how stupid some people can be. [ __ ] hell.
You have to be with people every time
you go for a drink for like 3 hours.
Really, bro? Come on, man.
Ever need some me time?
Yeah. Well, maybe if you actually got
yourself some friends and you got off of
YouTube, you would realize that you
can't always trust people and sometimes
you need a bit of me time.
I was thinking of going out of London
again by myself cuz sometimes you need a
bit of me time and if you actually had
friends you don't
um you'll come to learn
now you don't have any friends that's
why you you uh you misunderstand
you know once you finally get yourself
some friends you'll realize but
obviously you don't have any friends so
you don't know how the real world works
just another self projector.
He's not a mug, bro. He's just a self
projector like most everyone here. >> Yeah.
He's not a mug, bro. He's just a self projector.
Yep. You're talking about yourself, bro.
You don't have any friends. You're
talking about yourself.
What have I told you about talking about yourself? Bro,
listen, bro. Come on, man. This this
this whole self projection thing is
getting boring now. Like, when are you
really going to pack it in? You've been
doing it for like 12 years, man. Like,
it's boring now. Like, 12 years
legitimately. Even before I was on here,
bro, I've heard stories. When are you
going to really really really stop this?
This whole self projection [ __ ] It's
boring now, bro. Think of it. Yeah. I
I'm guessing you people are
late 30s, 40s. Yeah. Late 30s, 40s.
And you didn't offend me at all, bro. I
I just get offended when I have to talk
to stupid people. That's what That's
what offended me is having to talk to
stupid people. But anyways, like you're
in your late 30s, 40s. It's not the
latest. I mean, you can still get off of
YouTube and get a life and get all of
the things that you tell other people
that they don't have. And I feel like,
you know, it's a good it's a good way to
say it now cuz I'm only here for a
couple of hours.
Um, you can get yourself some money
instead of coming on YouTube calling
people skint every day. You can get
yourself some friends and you could get
the [ __ ] off of YouTube and get a
[ __ ] life. You know, it's not too
late. It's not too late, bro. You can do
all of all of these things again, you
know, especially if you're in your late
30s. You can get all of the things that
you don't have that you tell other
people that they don't have.
What's the point of wasting another 12
years on here, bro? [ __ ] me.
Arms are getting ripped. Not even, bro.
I ain't been to the gym in ages. I'm
starting again tomorrow before I go out
approaching tomorrow. I'm just going to
go to the gym.
I'm not ripped at all, bro. I'm
slacking. I ain't been to the gym for
[ __ ] ages. I need to go again.
Do I have lots of money? I don't have
lots of money. I'm actually losing
Yeah. So, no, I don't have loads of
money, but I have enough money.
I have enough money, bro. I have enough
savings and I get enough money and I'll
be working soon. Hey, Ghosting. Yeah,
I've got an idea. I'm drinking cuz I
need to I'm killing a couple of hours.
Yeah, I've got a good idea, bro. Which
might sound slightly contradicting.
Yeah, but uh um I might sound slightly contradicting, but
I figured, bro, yeah, I'm going to be in
a lot of like increase now. Yeah. In in
income. Yeah. And I should have met
somebody in these three years. So, I'm
going to start the gym again tomorrow
and I'm going to cold approach two weeks
in a row. Like two weeks straight. I'm
going to approach cuz I've got nothing
better to do. I can't work right now cuz
the situation with the whole Uber thing.
I'm not going to sit around all day. So,
I'm just going to send it for two weeks
straight. It's over. I'm not going to do
it drunk and the outcome will be interesting.
Dude, I got nothing [ __ ] better to do, bro.
Uh I can't. It's It doesn't make me
happy, but it's I'm back on the dating
apps, by the way, since I haven't been
on them since February. They're [ __ ]
as [ __ ] as last time, bro.
Yeah, man. I got a got a baby Guinness here,
bro. Listen, I've just gave you advice
and you're still trying to troll me. I
already started a gym, but I just
haven't been for a little while cuz I
just been too busy with [ __ ] But
then obviously after the two weeks I'll
have to give up and leave again.
Yeah. None of them free numbers replied.
Ghosting. Hey bro, I got three numbers
on Saturday. None of them which is
yesterday. None of them replied. None of
the numbers replied.
Not doing any approaches today. There's
no one here to approach.
There's no one here.
I wouldn't anyways tomorrow be doing it. Yeah,
be doing it until this second Monday. So yeah,
I'm [ __ ] bro. Seriously [ __ ]
Yeah, none of them. And you know the mad
thing is Ghost and one of them I was
speaking to them for half an hour. I was
speaking to them for about [ __ ] half
an hour, bro. Nice combo. like proper
big combos and [ __ ] They were from
these uh say it, bro. They were from
Australia and they didn't even reply back.
They They didn't even [ __ ] reply back.
They didn't even reply back, bro. What the [ __ ]
They were never changing this country.
Here's to never changing. [Music]
Oh, love that one. I love that [ __ ]
It tastes like chocolate.
Oh, it's it's [ __ ] yummy, bro.
M. It's like chocolate ghetto
covered in chocolate sauce.
That's what it's like.
I'm going to get another [ __ ] round after this.
This is horrible compared to that.
Ah, I don't post no content on this
[ __ ] channel, bro.
I don't post anything on this channel.
Do you want my opinion? Zippy. Uh.
Uhhuh. Daryl [ __ ] Oh.
So, second round. 6 7 8 We at 24 quid. I spent
24 [ __ ] quid.
[ __ ] Who cares, man?
It's quite cheap. This is actually quite
cheap consider to considering you go
central London, bro. It's actually quite
cheap, isn't it? It's actually quite cheap, bro.
It's actually quite nice.
>> Yeah, you're talking about yourself,
bro. Like I said, you self projectors
don't bother no one. Like, bro, like it
doesn't bother no one.
And do you know why it doesn't bother anyone? because
you're talking about yourself. So when
you talk about yourself time and time
and time and time again, it becomes a
long playing record.
Any effect that you thought you had on
anyone? It stopped 3 years ago. Like
you're by yourself on YouTube. I'm sat
here for a couple of hours
drinking. Yeah, I got a tan. Look,
you're sat on YouTube all by yourself
skin. That's fine, bro. I don't mind.
I'm by myself drinking having fun.
You're sat by yourself on YouTube. You
ain't got no money. I don't care. Do you
understand what I'm saying? So, whatever
you say, it's laughable.
Like, do you remember what I told you
about like the London cyclists and all
of this and all of that? Like, you
remember I kept going on about that? You
call me stinking, guess what? You're
alone on YouTube all by yourself with no
money. Like we were talking about you people yesterday.
You're on £300 a month by yourself on
YouTube. No one cares what you say. And
another thing is, bro, about the me
being stinking. Okay, you're calling me
Okay, you can't show your face.
Doesn't matter, bro. Like, you're you're
too ugly to show your face. Like we all
know what you people are in your 30s,
40s, fat and ugly, no life, no money, no
friends. You have zero effect on
anything you say about anyone.
Because when it got to the [ __ ]
point where none of you could start
coming on camera, it's just laughable.
It's just something to laugh at. You
know what I'm saying? Like you people
are really something cuz all you're
doing is Yeah. which is not you're not
bullying yourself because you can't
really bully yourself like Monty says
cuz he's just stupid. You're just
embarrassing yourself. All you're doing
is wasting more and more years of your
life on here self-projecting. That's all
you're doing. You're wasting more of
your own life that's already wasted. It
doesn't bother us. You know, it it it's
laughable. Like you just come on YouTube
and constantly embarrass yourself every
day because your life is [ __ ] It
doesn't affect me. Look, look, bro. I'm
sat in a pub drinking and having fun.
You're sat on YouTube all by yourself.
So, it doesn't bother anyone.
And that's all I've really got to say to
you self projectors. See, this is what
I'm saying with these people. Like they
don't they don't affect anyone cuz think
of it bro like if they if they affected
me I wouldn't be on camera right now.
They just talk about theirelves. All of
this like comment on YouTube your skin
you're this you're that. All of this hat
hateful [ __ ] it's stigma. Bro listen
what these people have received over the
years. Bullying £300 a month fat ugly.
This is where all of this [ __ ] this
mental [ __ ] comes from. It doesn't
bother anyone them talking about
themselves. You know, they've been doing
it for years and they'll continue to
keep doing it. Think these people don't
even leave their house. Think of how sad
that is. Sat on YouTube all day, you
can't even leave your house and you're
talking about somebody
drinking in a pub by yourself. Bro, if
you actually saved up money next year,
you might actually be able to do that
yourself. If you saved that 300,000 a
month you get, bro, these people are job seekers.
They're on jobsekers allowance. I'm
telling you, bro. Swear to God, bro.
Swear down, bro. That that is what they're on. So,
making accounts all day on YouTube. It's
some It's some sort of bullying that
these people have received when they
were younger. I'm telling you, bro.
something here where they have been
bullied and bullied and bullied and
bullied and bullied and they come on
here and try to bully other people, but
they just embarrass themselves. So, we
just laugh at it. Like, they don't even
stop people coming on YouTube. They
don't control no one's life. They don't
psychologically [ __ ] with anyone's head.
They just embarrass themselves. They're
just something to laugh at. Same people,
stupid little comments, same self
projectors. They're just something to
laugh at or something to fall asleep to
is what don't. Anyways, enough about the losers. You know,
these are the same people that will try
and get you kicked out of a pub. Think
of it, bro. Let's put two and two
together. They're sat here saying that
you're drinking alone in a pub. Yeah.
But at any first given opportunity,
these people will try to get you kicked
out of a pub. Make it make sense, bro.
You understand? So
they just I feel I feel sorry for them,
bro. It's like what I said on my video.
Like I actually really really do feel
sorry for them. If I was these people
Yeah. I was in my 40s. I would I would
literally just come off YouTube and
never come back on it.
But they can't cuz YouTube is their
life. Without this application and self
conject and self conjection, they'd have nothing.
Think of it, bro.
Sad, bro. They really are sad eyes, bro. Really are.
>> Self-reflecting bastards.
It's like the whole skin thing. You got
all this money. Why you sat on YouTube
all day talking to people that you don't
know? No, no, no. Let's get real into
it, bro. Come on. Let's get really,
really, really, really into it. And you
know what? I'm not going to regret any
of this [ __ ] tomorrow. Yeah, think about
it, bro. What is the first word that
come from these people's mouth that any
of you remember? It was that somebody is
skinned and alone. Okay. Why are these
people sat on YouTube every day talking
to each other? They've got all the money
in the world. They're not skin. No, no.
Come on, come on, come on. Let's let's
put two and two together and see if it
adds up for they come online every day
calling someone skin. You're this,
you're that, you're this, you're that,
you're this, you're that, you're this,
you're that. Why are they sat on YouTube
every day talking to each other?
Answer me that question. Sat on YouTube.
Think about it. They tell people that
they got no friends. They tell people
that they got no money. Why are they sat
on YouTube alone every day? Every single
[ __ ] day. Not one day a week, not two
days a week, not two, four [ __ ] five
times a month. Every day they're sat on YouTube.
It's because they're talking about themselves.
Who gave me the answer, bro? You know
MSN, you remember that thing that used
to give you the answer to all your
questions? The robot. The robot gave me
the answer, bro. They're talking about themselves.
Cuz I'd believe it if somebody come on
here for like a month was slating me
about my life and then they never come
back. They never come back again. But
they're on here every day. They're
literally on here every day. Do not
think that's that that's a waste of life
for someone that's got all this money,
all these friends, their life is so
good, but they can't get off of YouTube
for one day. Isn't that a waste of life?
What a waste of life, Mets. You
understand? They ain't got And then you
start p you start building a puzzle what
these people's life is actually like.
£300 a month, got no friends, all sat
alone on YouTube. It it literally the
puzzle just adds up to that. There's
nothing else it adds up to.
They're on YouTube hating as well. It's
not like they discuss politics.
Everything that they do is weird.
If they had a life and they had money,
they would not be on here the way they
on here. It's simple.
It's what they do on here as well. Like
they're self they're self-projecting
[ __ ] That's all they are, bro.
This I've been in this pub for [ __ ] 3
hours. What the [ __ ]
>> Oh yeah, bro.
>> Yeah, bro. [ __ ]
So yeah, they're just self projecting basically.
>> I need to go back on that. Yeah, man.
There's there's machines, but there's no Frankie.
Yeah, but there's no I'm trying to get
rid of this [ __ ] boxing bag, but no
one wants to buy it, bro. I don't know why.
Take it with me soon.
Going to [ __ ] tickle you, little virgin. Oh, [ __ ]
Steven I would all [ __ ]
tickle you. You little virgin.
Yeah, little virgin. Yeah.
Yeah, little virgin. Yeah,
that's what I want to do.
You like that, didn't you? Trying
to get rid of this boxing bag, mate.
>> Let me try and advertise this again. Why
is no one buying it? One second.
I'm getting fat.
I want to play some Frankie.
Hello, Mie. But I'm not going to play
it, bro. No, I'm only joking. I don't
actually want to. No, [ __ ] that, bro.
>> Oh, [ __ ] I'm actually [ __ ] bro. I
might need I might need to actually eat again today.
Hey, Izzy was here. Steven Howard
get [ __ ] that [ __ ] out again. Yeah, man.
Yeah. No, Frankie, bro. No, thank you.
I [ __ ] end up skin like [ __ ] virgin boy.
Oh, I'm [ __ ] so I'm [ __ ] bro. I'm
not even joking. I'm actually [ __ ]
I'm [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, two stakes now. She's a fat She's a fatty.
I ain't gambling, bro.
That No, I don't do that [ __ ] no more.
I'd end up like that [ __ ] that [ __ ] virgin.
Yeah, but these people, they
self-reflect so much.
These people on here self-reflect so
much. Omar, it's so sad.
They're live coming on YouTube talking
about themselves every day. I feel so bad, bro.
I actually do feel so bad.
>> Yeah, proper.
I feel bad for these little self-reflectors. Do you
They're all disabled and they don't even
leave their house.
Cuz you know what I said, Omar? Yeah.
Listen, Omar. Yeah. They're coming here
every day calling people skin, right?
So why are they They say that everyone's
skin and alone. So why are they sat on
YouTube every day then? If they got all
this money, they've got all these
friends. Why the [ __ ] are they sat on
YouTube every day? It doesn't make sense.
Why are they on YouTube every day?
[ __ ] bro. Hold on.
Why are they sat on YouTube every day
then? If they've got all this money and
everyone else's skin, why are they sat on YouTube?
Omar, what do you think the chances of
finding a woman in this country is? I
don't think there is a chance. N7 rocket though.
>> I don't think we've had anywhere, bud.
I think everywhere was I got three uh
Saturday. Yeah. None of them replied.
Well, none of them none of them replied, bro.
Same old e
same old England.
That's what I say about me. I I I just
say same old England.
Same old England. Oh, [ __ ]
>> So, I can show my face. These people
can't show their face.
Do you like my little face, Omar?
Yeah, I've given up as well. But you
know, the maddest thing is that I've
been like I've been everywhere in this
country. I've been Scotland. I'm in
Wales. I've tried for 3 years, bro, and
I haven't found anyone.
But I've basically given up as well. But
I'm going to do some approaches. Yeah.
Every day for 2 weeks and see what the
outcome is. Yep. I'm going to approach
every day for two weeks and I'm going to
see what the outcome is.
Then I'm starting the gym again. So,
do you like my little face, Omar?
I think it's quite sweet, isn't it?
>> Oh, no. All jokes aside. Yeah,
it's [ __ ] up in.
>> Oh, bro, I'm [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Do you know Do you know what
Antman said, Omar? Omar, bro, he's like,
Antman said they're just not interested
in this country.
Is he right, Omar?
Or is he telling fibs?
Yeah, he said they're just not
interested in this country.
That's [ __ ] bad, bro. Yeah, he's
right. Obviously, is it
interesting in this country? That's funny, bro. [Music]
He said, "Yeah, they ain't, mate."
Yeah. Somebody said, "I don't know what
the problem is. You look normal. You
approach normal." But he was like,
"There's maybe there's too many stuck up
[ __ ] in your country."
That's what they said. Yeah.
Yeah. I got free. Hey, Omar, you never
guess what happened the other day. Yeah.
Did you hear what happened to that bouncer?
with the bouncer.
Yeah. If you don't like stuck up people,
you wouldn't like London, mate. It's
full of stuck up people. London's full
of stuck up people, bro. >> Yeah.
>> So, basically, I went to uh I went to uh
the bar on Saturday. Yeah. And I
approached three women in the space of 2
hours. I hadn't been out in a month.
Yeah. And it wasn't over and over again.
It was like in 2 hours I approached I
think it was three. It was three people
in the space of 2 hours. Maybe an hour
and a half, 2 hours.
And even if I did do it over and over
again, I'm a single guy. I'm in a bar in
a club. I'm paying for drinks. You know,
it's normal to talk to people. The
bouncer come up to me. Yeah. And he, oh,
we need to have a word. And I'm
thinking, oh, it might be my tracky
bottoms because I was wearing trackuit
bottoms. I was wearing a tracksuit cuz
you seem to get better success wearing a
tracksuit. But anyways, um he Oh, we've
had complaints about you, which is
impossible because I have never had
somebody complain about me ever. And
I've been approaching for 3 years,
right? So, what's the chances that three
people has just complained about you?
Wasn't too drunk, knew exactly what I
was saying. Um, you know, one of them
were acting like stuck up on that. Two
of them was, but no one complained
because they just left like after a
while. I guess they go for like evening
drinks. And then the bouncer like he
said, "If you come and give me attitude,
I'm going to snatch the drink out your
hand." I said, "You're not going to
snatch no drink out of my hand." And he
tried like pulling the drink away from
me and I pulled him back and then the
[ __ ] glass fell on the [ __ ] floor.
Most of the drink was gone anyways. I
told the guy to come around the corner.
Yeah. I told him I was shouting. Bro,
I've got the video and everything
because bro, it's like what the [ __ ]
These people, Omar. Yeah. They tell you
that, oh, you shouldn't approach on the
street. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no. And
then you approaching a [ __ ] club or a
bar and then they're not and then they
try to tell you that you can't do that.
What the [ __ ] Make it make sense.
So, I mean, I [ __ ] heard it all now,
but that was that. Yeah, that was I
haven't been out for a month. So, yeah.
That's how it is.
Yeah. And I would have I would have And
I'm not saying, bro, that I would 100%
beat him. I'll show you a picture of
him. I'm not saying I would 100% beat
him, but I don't [ __ ] know if I would
have got if I was going to beat him. But
I know I'd get the last laugh because I
would have just went back with a hammer.
Simple. I would have just went back with
a hammer, bro. Yeah.
No, I would I would have I think I could
have had him, bro. I'm not even joking.
Just cuz someone's big, it don't mean nothing.
Like, it doesn't mean anything, bro.
Yeah. This [ __ ] Yeah. I done a video as
well. I was calling him a Polish this, a
Polish that, and he still wouldn't come. So,
[ __ ] in other words.
But how mad is that? How can you get
kicked out of a [ __ ] bar for talking
to people or not?
How the [ __ ] And the only And the
people that reported it was the staff.
It was no one else. It weren't the women
you was approaching. It was the actual
staff. It has to be. It literally had to
be, bro. Because out of all of the
approaches I've done, no one has ever
complained about me. Never, bro. Never.
So what? So you can't even speak to
people in your own country in a bar,
mind you, when you're paying drinks?
Sort it out, mate. [ __ ] hell.
First of all, you don't let free people
in. Then somebody can't come by
themselves. Like, make it make sense, bro. >> Yeah.
They're [ __ ] idiots, bro.
But he's a [ __ ] You just know he would have
uh No, they don't know me.
No, they don't know me. And it weren't
the women. It definitely was not the
women, bro, because they were drinking
with their friend and they never moved.
So, no, they don't know me. I'd go there
the whole time. So, no. So, and it
definitely definitely was not the women.
Um, 100% it wasn't. So,
what is it then? You know what I'm saying? So,
um I got borrowed from one place before
cuz I called a staff a [ __ ] somewhere
else. So, um yeah, we can't even speak
to people in our own country now.
Imagine that. We can't even go to a bar
in a club and speak to people in our own
country. And bear in mind, I hadn't been
out for a month, Omar. I hadn't been out
for a month. So, I'm like, "Oh, damn.
It's gotten worse now, is it?"
I'm trying to think. And I was just like
and people was coming over speaking to
me as well. So it's like the whole point
is to go and socialize.
So I think from now on I'm just going to
stick to pubs. And I think the whole you
can't wear tracks do bottoms is cheeky
Omar cuz I feel like I like who wants to
wear jeans and like the thing is Yeah.
It's not even about the jeans, bro. It's
more like you should be able to wear
what you want. You're paying your money.
Think about it, bro. Yeah. It's not a
private event. It's public. So, you're
paying your money and you're paying your
money for drinks and you're paying money
for entry. You should be able to wear
what the [ __ ] you want to wear. That's
the way I see it.
You know what I mean?
You should be able to wear what the [ __ ] you want.
That's the way I see it. Like,
so that's why I just rather just
approach on the street now. But I don't
really do it anymore.
I've kind of got like not scared to do
it, but I just can't be asked.
There was a whole point where I couldn't
do There's a whole point I couldn't do
it for like a whole week. I couldn't do
it for like a whole week. I was so
mentally stressed and just fed up by it.
I just couldn't be asked. So,
I've done so many approaches, me so
many. But yeah, you should be able to
wear what you want if you're paying them prices. Yeah,
>> I think they just didn't like me in the tracksuit bombs.
So, they just made up an excuse. That's
cuz no none of them women complained,
bro. None of them did. No one even I
didn't even have an argument with any of
them. So, what? And I said, you know, I
said to the bouncer, I said, "Maybe you
should stop letting stuck up [ __ ] in
your establishment then with attitude
problems and you might you might
actually you might actually resolve a
lot of things." He said, "Mate," I said
to him, "Yeah, you maybe should stop
letting people in that don't like being
talked to them, cuz it's a normal thing.
It's a very normal thing to do,
you know. I've made a lot of friends
from going out and drinking." And
I don't know why they done that, but it
was weird cuz I hadn't argued with
anyone or anything.
This country just does not make any
sense, Omar. It makes literally no
sense. And then some of these people
called um up a pub that I was in.
Firstly, she got the burger wrong. I I
actually explained 10 20 times how I
wanted a [ __ ] how I wanted the burger
and then she got it wrong. And then
somebody called up. Yeah. And she was
like, "Oh yeah, you can't record. You
either keep recording or and you you go
or you have to go." And I'm thinking,
"Hold on a minute." Yeah. You're telling
me that I can't record? Why am I Why am
I Why am I not allowed to record in a
pub? I mean, I know it's not a public
place, but I'm sure you can cuz I don't
think it's private. I don't think it's
private property. So, I'm sure you can
record. Like, there's no law against it.
And um I weren't being awkward or
anything, but I'm thinking like it's not private property.
So it's like
and then you know I turn around and I
said, "Okay, don't you have cameras in
the pub?" They like, "Yeah, we got
cameras in the pub." Yeah.
And uh I said, "Okay, so you're
recording me then? I'm not I'm not
giving you permission to record me." So
I can say the same thing. You're telling
me that I can't record myself talking in
a pub. Yeah. So you're recording I don't
want to be on your camera. You're
recording me. So I can I can say the
same thing. You know what I'm saying? I
can say exactly the same thing. I don't
know what the [ __ ] she was, but she had
an attitude problem as soon as I got in
there. I said, "Oh, I just want a bacon.
I want a burger with cheese and bacon,
like no mayonnaise, no lettuce." And I
didn't I didn't mind repeating it three times because,
you know, it's quite unusual like my
order. So I didn't mind repeating it a
couple of times. And I repeat it again
and again and then again and again. And
then she comes over to the table. And
then she came over to the table and um
and was like, "Oh, like we can give you
an American one with only cheese." I
said, "Okay, just give me a burger with
just cheese. That's fine." She come over
with the [ __ ] burger and it had all
[ __ ] on it that I did not want. And then
she said, "Oh, you've got you got to
leave. If you don't stop recording, I'm
going to give you a refund." I said,
"Give me my refund. I'm leaving you a
pub." Simple. Now, are you [ __ ] mad?
You You do not understand [ __ ]
English. Like, I didn't mind repeating
it three or four times cuz again, it's
unusual, but [ __ ] hell, I must have
said it about 20 times and you've got
the whole thing wrong. [ __ ] stupid idiot.
And then imagine, oh yeah, okay, but you
can't come. I said, I don't want to come
in. You're [ __ ] stupid. Yeah.
Firstly, it's not public. It's not a
public um a private place. Second of
all, don't record me then. Simple
[ __ ] idiot, man.
>> They really are stupid, aren't they,
bro? They really, really, really are
[ __ ] idiots, bro. I think they make
up their own [ __ ] rules. I'm telling you,
country's backwards, bro.
I didn't get the burger for free cuz I
didn't even get to eat it. They just
refunded the money. But yeah,
she had an attitude problem as well.
I said, "Yeah, I said you can bore me
all you want. I don't give a fuck."
Simple. Like, you know what I'm saying?
I don't give a [ __ ] mate.
And you know how um you know the
manager, he said to me, "Can you just be
good?" Do you know how I had problems in
that pub before? Right. I tell you what
it was. It weren't even with a woman.
Now, this was months ago. I went over to
this guy. I said, "Oh, I'm sick of the
dating in this country." And he says,
"Oh, I don't want to hear it." I said, I
I turned said, "Yeah, that I don't care
if you want to hear. I'm telling you
about it. Drop your attitude." And then
guess what he done? He ran to the staff
and there was like, "Oh, what's it
weren't even a woman or about women?"
And he's just like, so it's like you're
letting entitled [ __ ] with attitude
in your premises and then if somebody
responds back, oh, all of a sudden it's
a problem. I'm thinking it doesn't make sense.
It doesn't make any sense. Like you're
letting people with attitude in your
premises. Yeah. And then when somebody
gives somebody attitude and then
somebody says something back, but then
he just said, "Oh, whatever." And Yeah.
Like he doesn't seem to understand that
the people are the problem in this
country. I was speaking to the manager
about this. Yeah. And I said to him like
he was outside the pub before I went
back after the bounce issue. I like you
might think I'm being awkward and that
but I'm not. Yeah. I'm not whining. I'm
not trying to fight anyone but he says
oh no country is perfect. It's not about
a country being perfect. It's about the
people in the country. Yeah. No one sat
there saying about oh Asia's perfect. No
no no no no no. No country is perfect.
But we're not talking about a country
being perfect. We're not getting into
politics. We're getting into the actual
people and that and and that is what
mainly is wrong with the country is the
people. If there was no people and you
know it'd be fine.
It got so bad Omar. Yeah. That I wanted
to like just pack in work to do it. Bro
know bro you know I wanted to actually
packing work to do it.
It made me really start like hating
people like the job that I was doing
like the Uber which I like I said I
never had an opinion on it quite I
didn't really know about people or a lot
of people I just thought oh it's drunk
people whatever but when I started the
Uber thing bro
it made me really start hating these
people in this country you understand like
and the worst thing about it was I could
I could compare them to Chinese people I
could compare them to Asian people. I
could compare them to Asian people and
you knew that it was this country
because every single Chinese person and
Asian person um you would speak to
there'd be no problem. They'd be the
nicest people that you'd ever come
across and there was nothing there. So,
and then you get these [ __ ] and
this that this that this that and the
other. And obviously I was delivering to
mostly Chinese people. I've come across
loads of Asian people. So, I knew it was
the people in this country. Straight up, bro.
The nicest people you ever [ __ ] meet,
bro. I'm telling you, they're nice
people. They really are nice. And then
you get people in this. Like, you you'd
be riding on your bike. Yeah.
You'd be working normally and you get
these people on a bike. Yeah. Making
these sly comments that they don't even
know you, bro. I was in Camelin Town.
Yeah. I busted a left. Yeah. On my bike.
Yeah. Sorry if I'm repeating, but some
people ain't heard this. this random
woman with tattoos, fat, ugly [ __ ] she
was. Yeah. Was like, "Oh, uh, you're not
supposed to be here." Look, I said, "I
will go where I [ __ ] want." And then,
uh, yeah. She started running up her
[ __ ] mouth, bro. Yeah. Um, and then
she started running up her mouth. No,
no, no. I [ __ ] I rode back. I wrote I
parked up that bike and I told her to
come back and say to my face and she was
with a guy as well, which it doesn't
matter if she was or wasn't, I would
still do it. I parked up that bike. I
said, "You [ __ ] what [ __ ] Come back.
Stop walking away." Um, so it's like,
"Hold on." So, uh, bye-bye, virgin. So,
it's like the people in this country,
they like to
start on people, but they can't finish
it. which when I was talking to these
two women um that were like a lot older
like 37 40 we was having this
conversation about this and it's
entitlement. Yeah. Okay. You're having a
bad day. Okay. Yeah. Your life's not
great. So what does that give you the
excuse to start making sly comments to
random people that you don't know? What
does not scream entitled about that? And
like they'll try to get involved with
other people's business, but then when
you confront them, they'll run away like
and that's and we was talking and I had
a 9-year-old kid try to steal my bike as
well. Imagine that. Yeah. I had a
9year-old [ __ ] child try to steal my
bike. Let's let's let's keep saying that
it's not people in this country. A
9year-old kid, bro. What the [ __ ] Well,
I'm guessing he was about 10. 9 or 10.
He couldn't have been older than 9 or
10. Think about what you was doing when
you was 9 or 10, bro. Was you going
around central London trying to steal
people's [ __ ] bikes? I didn't go past
[ __ ] 0.2 miles when I was [ __ ] 10,
11 years old.
You've got actual kids. And it was so
bad. I didn't want to put my hands on
the child. I was like, and luckily, no,
he wasn't even black. He was white.
He was actually white. And I I locked
the bike. Yeah. Well, I rented the bike.
Yeah. I was like, "Okay, this kid steals
this bike. I'm [ __ ] I tried locking
the bike, bro, and the bike weren't
locking. Like, you lock it on your
phone. It's like, "Oh, [ __ ] The bike
ain't locking. I don't really want to
put my hands on this kid." Yeah. And
then luckily the security come. I said,
"Oh, can not to be not to be [ __ ] or
anything, but can you get this child off
my bike?" Basically, cuz you know, like
we know the country's [ __ ] I don't
want to put my hands on this kid. And
then the security guard like stuck it on
him. He said, "Get off his bike. Get off
his bike." The kid was trying to run his
mouth and the security guard was like,
"Come on then. Come on then. You [ __ ]
ran off. A kid. A 10-year-old kid. A
10-year-old child. Not even someone.
Not even a 17year-old, bro. Not even not
even a 16y old. That kid could have not
been older than 10.
It was by the garage, bro. By like
Chinatown. I couldn't I couldn't believe it.
But this guy does not seem to think that
any of these people in this country
contribute to any problems. Bro, come
on. Wake up and smell the coffee, bro.
It's [ __ ] up.
This country is [ __ ] up. And like I
said, how I knew how more [ __ ] up it
was is because when you would meet the
Chinese people, you would know the difference.
I remember. Yeah. Do you know what
happened? Um, Omar. Yeah. I was
delivering food to a customer
and do you know what he said? Oh, I
said, "Sorry, man." He said, "For what?
What are you sorry for?" I was I was a
tiny bit late. I said, "Oh, sorry about
that." He said, "For what? You see the difference?
Your country is [ __ ] right? I'm
telling you." He said, "What you sorry for
notice a lot of the Chinese people, they
would come all the way down. See, when
you deliver to a hotel, um, to an
apartment, they're supposed to come
down. Um, and most of they don't have
to, but they're meant to. You know, it
makes our job a lot easier. But they
did. A lot of them did. Most of them did. So,
you can tell it is definitely people in
this country, bro.
Like, they It literally is [ __ ]
10-year-old kid, bro. What the [ __ ]
Somehow the bike weren't locking. And
they said, "If he steals this bike, I'm [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] up, isn't it?
>> Yeah, this country is [ __ ] bro.
It's gone to the shambles.
I think the whole escort thing started
with me, Steven Howard. When the escort
said, "We can give you a [ __ ] but
you can't finish.
>> You can't finish in our mouth." I
thought, "Wow, that's crazy.
I'll do a video on this one day, bro,
and I can't be bothered.
Go to a nice field, maybe play a bit of
GTA and record whilst talking about it.
Keep you interested, eh?
So much has happened in like four weeks. Oh,
[ __ ] me. One second. back. Yeah. visit us. Yeah. Yeah. >> Yeah. Sorry, boss.
One second. I need to call my sister. Hold on.