What the [ __ ]
But the [ __ ] Chinese are [ __ ]
closed. [ __ ] sake.
What is this? Mhm.
What could I eat? [ __ ]
Yeah, I hate it, bro. I just had another
bath cuz my ass was hurting.
Yeah, I hate it, bro. Uh,
new 20,000 piece custody today.
These guys have been talking all day,
you know, bro. They woke me up in the
morning. They're still doing it
all [ __ ] day. They've been doing it.
I come back, they're [ __ ] still doing it.
Yeah. I had to have a bath cuz my ass
I'm trying to think what to eat, me.
Gourmet burger kitchen looks good.
That is [ __ ] expensive.
do like a gourmet burger kitchen. I
can't lie, bro.
Here's me going on spending like I got
loads and loads of [ __ ] money.
That looks good. I had a Weber spoons
earlier was just £8. So, I buy anything else. No.
If you ain't never had gourmet burger
kitchen, I suggest it. It's [ __ ] amazing, bro.
to try, bro. Uh, burger.
You had gourmet burger kitchen before.
It's [ __ ] lush barbecue.
Will I eat again? really
had roast pork but roast beef.
Could you live without pork, Steve?
Stump stamp. Sorry.
Let me see. Did I? Yeah.
Medium pink and juicy. Yes.
Yeah, but how do you get I guess you can
add bacon maybe.
Yeah, but where's the bacon on it?
Call my burger kitchen is lush, bro.
I think you'd have to choose one with
bacon on it and then
take the other stuff off.
There we go. Bacon.
No house. No home relish.
No avocado. No house relish. Just bacon.
Wait. But there's no cheese.
Add cheddar cheese.
Oh, this is expensive, bro.
It's nice, but it's very expensive.
It's expensive, bro.
I mean, fresh start tomorrow and all
that, ain't it?
£18 for just one burger. What? Um,
I don't think so, bro. [ __ ] me.
To be fair, I don't really want chips.
So, I'd want onion rings to be fair.
>> Wait, no onion rings. They sell out.
They sell out onion rings. What the [ __ ]
This is expensive, bro.
£23 for [ __ ]
How could you miss her? You don't even
know her. You've never even met her.
>> £23 for [ __ ] burger meal. No, I just
won't eat today. I already ate pork and
that, did I?
See, once I've had a roast dinner, I I I
tend to not eat again.
I was going to get a gourmet burger
kitchen meal, but it's £23.
I'm not that hungry. So,
why' you miss USA? Izzy, you don't know
her. You've never met her.
You never get to kiss kissed her and
suck her tits and [ __ ] her like I did.
Why would you miss her?
It was £23, but Gourmet Burger Kitchen
is the best burger place you'll ever go to here. So good.
I'm just going to have my Ben and
Jerry's ice cream. I think I already
today. So you didn't answer my question.
Why do you miss her?
Yeah, I need to start saving anyways
before I become poor.
Well, by poor, I mean dipping into my
savings and I'm not dipping into my savings. So, yeah.
Yeah. So, why would you miss her? She
never used to come on here. She bad.
She love bomb people. She bad.
I'm sorry, man.
I think I'm going to go shop. Get some co. Yeah,
I got keys. There was a dead fox here
and it [ __ ] stunk, bro. [ __ ] dead
fox. [ __ ] rank. It was, bro. It's
been there for like two days. It's rank
[ __ ] cancel. Go and [ __ ] remove it.
No, I don't like air fryers. I hate
them. I've used them before, bro.
[ __ ] dead [ __ ] fox.
It [ __ ] stinks, bro. Yeah.
How do you like her? You didn't even know her.
You don't even know her, bro.
How do you like someone you don't know her? Answer
me in that one, bro.
Talking about yourself again, bro. Don't
waste your time on my channel talking about yourself.
Go back to LJ's channel. Don't do it, bro.
She was lovely. She was a [ __ ] [ __ ]
That's what she was. Is
she's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
She was nice at first, then she turned
into a proper [ __ ]
Yeah, she turned into a right [ __ ]
Then I had to go cuz my sister come and
I don't get with my sister. One of my
sisters I do I get with my mom or my
sister just not my other sister. Don't
like her. She don't like me.
Yeah, she did. She also promised me that
she was going to we was going to see
each other again and we was going to get tattoos.
Lowest I've ever been. No, I've got money.
Not at all. I don't know where I don't
know where you get that from. lowest
you've ever been. Bro, I've got money.
Yeah, I'm not going to get as much money
now, but bro, I've got money. I've got
savings and [ __ ]
So, no, it's just something that was
going to happen anyways.
I'm not low. I don't know why you're
saying I'm low. The [ __ ] I drunk
earlier cuz I was [ __ ] cuz my sister
come and I don't like my sister. My
sister don't like me. Only one of them.
So, I just left. Simple.
Now, I'm back here cuz I wanted to get a
proper sleep today. I'm not low at all.
I just feel, oh [ __ ] I didn't have to
work for 4 years. Had that money,
gambled, [ __ ] escorts, traveled, had
some good food. Why the [ __ ] would I be low, bro?
[ __ ] bro. I I've got money. I just
don't want to waste money now. So, yeah.
But yeah, she she also said she we were
going to meet again, but she never. She
also said we was going to meet up again.
We never done a lot of things. So
yeah, I don't I don't really want to go
back to that though. That's the thing. I
don't want to go back to that.
I don't like the area. I don't like the
neighbors. I'm happy here, but obviously
I can't stay here. So, and it's also
ruined their life as well. So this whole
house thing has [ __ ] up a lot of people's lives, you know,
I'm less affected by it, but obviously
cuz they are actually [ __ ] So they
are [ __ ] I'm 50% [ __ ]
Obviously, it is what it is.
That's what you think about it in it.
This is going to have to be annoying budgeting now.
But if you can do it for one month, then
you're basically just back to square one
anyway. So, it's good really.
And then money makes money. But yeah,
there's a [ __ ] dead fox on the road.
It [ __ ] stinks, mate.
Yeah, I got a nice TV, got Xbox. So, I
just hit the gym before starting from
tomorrow. Just have to save it. So,
what a life, man.
But they ruin a lot of people's lives.
Them taking this back.
A lot of people's lives.
See, my [ __ ] to other people is not [ __ ] to them.
Yeah. [ __ ] is it?
No, he's all right. He just needs to get
laid. Once he gets laid, bro, I think he
will stop all of this YouTube [ __ ] and stalking and
and that, bro. like he he once he gets
laid once he actually gets laid I think
he'll be all right.
I was the same when I was [ __ ] 17.
Yeah. I'm just going to go gym for a month and
stay occupied and [ __ ] just go out in a month.
I can't be wasting money now, bro.
I can't be wasting money.
And even if I did, I still wouldn't. So of um
dude, it's just the same old it. Oh yeah.
Can't even approach anymore. Mentally
and physically [ __ ] exhaust me. So
So what can you do brother?
What can you do?
Because I don't like to work. I don't
like to save. I like going out and doing
what I want. I've been used to it for 3 years.
I'm just used to reality now. And I'm
We're all [ __ ] in different ways to be
honest with you. We're all [ __ ] in
different ways. the people in the house. But
I mean, I'm still not [ __ ] compared to
a lot of people, but I am in a way. I'm
not [ __ ] But it was just like you had
to deal with the women [ __ ] and now you
got to deal with money. You know, you
didn't really want to deal with dating
whilst dealing with money. But I mean,
at least you still don't have to work if
you don't want to. So
yeah, lucky I got saved today.
If somebody actually wanted to go on a
date, yeah, I would have actually went
and took him on like on a nice date if I
knew I was going to get something. I
don't mind spending £300. No problem.
But I can't be wasting money now. So,
I can't be wasting money to get nothing, bro.
I don't want to. So, yeah.
No, I'm not telling you, bro.
You can keep guessing, bro. You can keep
fishing info, but I got saving, so I'm
all good, bro. Yeah,
mate. You don't know anything, bro.
Again, you're not going to get
information. I'm not giving information.
Keep guessing, bro. Keep guessing right.
Keep guessing wrong. All I know is I
have money. Simple. I am not going to be starving. So
I wonder how USA Izzy was able to afford
to come here.
Had to save maybe or bumps and months.
Months and months maybe.
If you don't Uber, you could probably go
America. I'd say two months you could go.
How? Who cares? Um because I need to get
because I need to find another income.
That's why I care because the whole
point is not dipping into the savings
and I still got money anyways, but I
don't really want to be spending that money.
So, I kind of care because I need to
find another income.
I can't be lazy like Virgin Legs.
Wouldn't it be nice if they paid you to
go around approaching women? Eh, imagine
they they paid you, right? That' be
lush, wouldn't it? Yeah,
but I do care because eventually I'm
going to need a second income. So, I do
care. I care. So, yeah.
But there are some people that are worse
than me with spending. Bro, I'm actually
all right. Like, I've still got savings
and [ __ ] I'm not even too bad with money.
There are some people that are worse than me.
Someone I know had a lot of money. I'm
not going to get into it. And somehow it's gone.
Good couple of grand they had and it's
all gone and they got nothing to show
for it. See, I had [ __ ] to show for it
when I had money like clothes,
restaurants. I'd be out three times a week.
Don't know what happened to theirs.
Escorts as well. A lot of escorts. Yeah, man.
It is what it is.
Yeah, he is living the life, bro. I
mean, he's a he's a uh he's he's someone
to look up to, bro. He literally is
someone to look up to.
You know, that's somebody that was on
here depressed as [ __ ] Swear they'd
never fly again. He would swore he'd
never fly ever, ever again. And then he
went to Thailand three times in a year
and now he's living there. He's someone
to look up to. And the mad thing is the
people that used to troll him are still on here. So
because I was in a different place than him.
But yeah, Thailand's cheap that anyone
could do it if they save. But it doesn't
matter. He's still he's still come a
long way, you know. So, and the people
that troll him still troll him. So, yeah.
But see, with me, I'm very stubborn.
Like I don't want to leave here again. I
want to find someone here. I shouldn't
have to leave
again. You know what I'm saying? I'm
more stubborn than him.
Like it's it might sound mad cuz I put
myself in a different bracket as him.
Like I don't think I'm better than him.
He's my friend and that he's cool. But I
don't think like cuz of reactions that
I've got in Sheffield and [ __ ] like I feel like
I don't know how to explain it, bro. I
don't want to admit defeat. That's the
thing, bro. I'm I'm a stubborn bastard.
If I was fat and ugly, then I would,
bro. It's not a problem. But you're not.
So, the whole It's hard to explain it. Like,
um, he doesn't come on YouTube no more.
He He left years ago,
but I'm stubborn, mate. So,
I'm a stubborn bastard. And also,
it's the fact that I don't like most
Thai women, but I like some and that's
probably why I won't go back there.
Like, there was some obviously when I
went there, but he obviously seems to
like them a lot more than me.
See, if they like I've said this to you
many times before, if you could go to somewhere
and I go again and again and again like
say you could go to somewhere like let's
say for example India, I'd be there now.
There's there's there's there's no
talking like don't
I say I don't have a life. I do have a
My friend said I think it's the staff.
Of course it's the staff.
Obviously, it's the staff, bro. It was
no women woman has ever reported me for
approaching them. Of course, it's the
staff, bro. They've got a club for
people to meet people and then when you
speak to people, they tell you to go. Obviously.
Yeah. It was cold. So, yeah, if it was
somewhere like India. Yeah. Or
give me another example
cuz I like Indian women obviously. Then
then yeah, we wouldn't be having this conversation.
There's there's no talking about it no more.
Obviously, he seems to like them a lot
more than I do. And you might think that
I'm using that as an excuse, but I'm
generally not cuz I've never approach I
think I've only ever approached one ch Asian woman
in in this country, you know,
you know, except that Australian. So,
it's not excuses. It ain't excuses. I'm
telling you, it's not excuses.
So that's where I think me and him are
different. And don't get me wrong, I
have found the odd one attractive and [ __ ]
I have, I'm not going to lie, but I've
only ever approached one here
and that was that Australian one. I've
I've never like even when I've seen them
in Chinatown, I've never
thought I'd go Thailand and check it
out, you know?
But I think that's where the deep down
root problem comes from. You know, it's
[ __ ] here. You know, you're never going
to get anyone here. But, you know, here
you get people from like all different
countries. And I don't even think it's
that you're living in denial. I think
it's just that they're not your really
your thing. Cuz if they said, "Oh yeah,
you come to India now and you can get
any woman you want." I'm there.
So like that's where I think
I think a lot of it um
a lot of it comes from. Most of it comes
from to be honest. It was good but USA
easily didn't come out
but even like Turkey if they said oh you
can come to Turkey I'd go to Turkey.
I've never been to Turkey. Cyprus, Turkey, Greece. [ __ ] Albania.
It would never happen. A Thai bird would
never say she has a boyfriend. [ __ ]
Albania. Even if they said you go to
Albania, I'm there. Simple. I'm [ __ ] there, bro.
The only two races I don't really find attractive is
he's black and Asian.
But I thought I'd give Thailand a go to
see how it was. And it was good. And it is easy. Oh yeah,
>> but the thing is I should have the only
maddest thing about this Joe as well is
Tyler, you know, Ant-Man's not tried
nowhere near as much as me. Like he's
not tried 10% as much as I have.
Yeah, it will never happen. A Thai woman
would never say she has a boyfriend cuz
even if she has a boyfriend, she's not
going to tell you she has a boyfriend.
Even there's women in this country that
don't say they have boyfriend. Even if
you approach an Indian woman in this
country, right, she would never say she
has a boyfriend ever. Or say for
example, maybe a Moroccan or they never
say they've got boyfriends.
um the weather. Um but they're just not
interested. But they don't say they've got boyfriends,
which uh um
so yeah, the weather and the fact that
there's no gambling and how cheap everything is.
But yeah, they they they don't Yeah,
I hate that [ __ ] bro. It's annoying.
But yeah, Antman's not But yeah,
Antman's not even tried nowhere near as
much as me.
They would just give their number and
not reply or maybe meet you or
Yeah, that boyfriend [ __ ] is annoying,
bro. It is so annoying.
No, I'm not hungry at all.
Yeah, that boyfriend thing is annoying.
You should be able to just go out and
get [ __ ] with the way that I look,
with the way that I approach. That's the
thing that's hard hard to accept.
But then again, you've tried way more
than that man has. Way more, mate. Like
look at him. He's 31. It took him to 31
to do something about it. Do you really
want to still keep wasting time and
money in this country that you're never
going to get back? So,
a hard one, bro. It is a hard one.
I don't know, man.
Maybe I should have tried to make it work with
certain people I had in the past. Maybe.
What do you think, Joe?
Why you had a chance?
Cuz I remember when I was with that one
in Nottingham, I just kicked her out the
hotel when I came.
Could have stayed with her.
But the thing is I kept going on about
USA Izzy and [ __ ]
Yeah, I kept going on about USA
trying to put some people off. They must
have thought I was mad, you know, back
them years ago. Yeah.
Yeah. There's been a couple that's been
my my fault. The one on Bumble, I should
have stayed with her. This was before
USA Izzy. like she generally wasn't
wasting time. She generally just wanted
to take things slow. So
that one from years ago when I came back
from Belgium, maybe the Nottingham one,
the Sig one. Like don't get me wrong,
there's been times where it's been me,
but not lately.
Like that Italian one was going to waste
my time. He was 100% going to waste my
time cuz now she's saying how she's
going back to Italy. And yeah,
I should have stayed with that one from
years ago, man.
Holding hands. I think she generally
just wanted a relationship. But yeah,
there's a few of them, but
not many recently.
Not many recently. No.
Then I had a one night stand on my
birthday as a while.
It's [ __ ] up, is it, bro?
Why do you think women go on dates? I
think most of them go on dates to pass time.
Yeah, most of them do.
How can you hold someone's hand and not
kiss? It's weird, you know.
I don't know. It is hard to tell. It is. Like
You just can never tell, you know, who's
wasting your time.
She is my mother, but she abandoned me.
She's going to come back in like 10 years.
Oh, I'm old. I'm a single mom now.
[ __ ] shut up out there, man.
You'll come back in 10 years.
But she's not nice, bro. She's an entitled [ __ ]
She's an entitled [ __ ] bro. Like,
somebody that's normal. Yeah. Someone
that's normal don't just block someone
and starts being a [ __ ] Even if you did
do something wrong, bro, it's not like
you done something wrong intentional.
And no one else would act like that. No
one. No one else would act like that, bro.
The [ __ ] was drunk. The [ __ ] was
horny. The [ __ ] tried to [ __ ] deny
everything she done the night before and
blame it on me. And then
basically had an attitude about it. So,
and didn't seem to give a [ __ ] So, [ __ ] her, bro.
I don't regret messaging her dad.
I don't regret messaging her family
though, bro. I really don't.
She's lucky I didn't go over there the
first time when I booked her, bro. Seriously.
She's really, really lucky, bro. Telling you.
a 19year-old as well. Yeah,
even the Italian one weren't a [ __ ] I
ra her, but she weren't a [ __ ] Like,
she said, "Oh, sorry." And she gave an
explanation and you [ __ ] tried
to kiss her. So at the end of the day,
bro, if you really did do something wrong,
people, they tend to not ghost,
you know? Like even people that like
you've gone on a date with, they never
just disappear. They either give an
explanation or they never disappear,
bro. That's what I'm saying. Something
wasn't right there, bro. I'm telling
you, something was not right there.
Something was not right there, bro. I'm telling you.
I just can't be bothered anymore, bro.
Yeah. Big up baby Guinness. Big up baby
You like You'll like it down here, son.
Yeah. Yeah, I got to go cinema [ __ ]
on the 18th
and I got to think of [ __ ] that [ __ ] again.
Ain't it Steven Howard?
I always think about it when I go to the
cinema. I'm not sure why. guy.
I can't I don't know why.
Um I know what you did last summer.
Now because of this financial decline,
Joe, I can't even get the Samsung
[ __ ] 7. Well, I could get it, but
again, it means dipping into my savings,
and I'm not doing that for a [ __ ]
phone. I've got phone six, and I've got
a brand new phone that works. So,
I did want that Fold 7, but
there's no way, bro.
I mean, I technically could get it.
Yeah, it's a new one. Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, here we go. [ __ ] me.
It's already out, bro. [ __ ] man.
Just can't do it this year, mate. I'm sorry.
They're out now.
Never, bro. Never. Now, I could get the phone
and either I'd have to pay £500 and then
get on a £500 up front and get a
contract or I could just buy the phone outright.
But I'm not going to
I'm not um I'm not doing it, bro. cuz
it's not worth it for a phone. I've got
a I've got a f I've got a fold six and
I've got a brand new phone.
But yeah, if things were different, I
would have. But maybe I would have
skipped a year anyways to be honest cuz
eight's my lucky number. So you remember
the roulette times, Joe? 811. Eh, don't
miss them times, matey. Don't miss them times.
Yep. Now, I could I could pay £500 to
get out on contract, but I wouldn't be
able to get a year because I wouldn't be
able to keep keeping up with the
payments. £200 a month is a lot cuz I
don't have a side hustle to make money
now at well at the minute. So, but I
could I could buy I could either buy it
outright or get a contract, a 2-year
contract, maybe 60 a month. So,
technically I could do it, but it's just
not worth it.
Yeah. I need to be saving up to go away
again. So, I won't be able to do it.
Simp simple as that. So, um no,
not at all.
What they £1,700, 1800?
Oh, [ __ ] Is it already? It's already in Argos.
[ __ ] me, bro.
Yeah, they're already out. I swear they
were coming out on the 17th.
No, because I can't justify it.
No, cuz I can't justify
paying that money. I can't justify
paying that money. If I still had a
house and I still had the Uber, I just
buy it. But I just can't No, I wouldn't
have bought it to be honest. I would
have got a contract and just paid. I
would have just got a year contract out
and paid £200 every month. I wouldn't
have, but I I don't think I would have
bought it out, right? I don't think I
would have to be fair.
Yeah, they are out. Well, actually, it's
pre-order. You can pre-order it. What
are they, bro? [ __ ] 1,800 [ __ ] pound, bro.
What the [ __ ] They were more expensive
than the last ones.
I would have just basically just got a year contract.
Well, what do you mean seeing nothing
for it? I got laid. I had life experience.
But I wouldn't be able to make the money back.
No. Well, it's either that or you buy it
outright. It depends how much money I I
I could make, bro. But
then you can't justify it, though. you
still can't justify it even if he was
working because a new one comes out
every month, sorry, every year. So, to
be honest with you,
the only way you could justify it is if
you if you pay the £500 and then you
Yeah, I'm going to watch that. I'm going
to watch that. I'm going to catch up.
Don't tell me what happened. Yeah. The
only way you could justify it is paying
£200 a month for a year
cuz you can't pay £1,800 when a new one
comes out every year. It's a new one
comes out every year as well. That's
another thing you got to think of. Like
a new one comes out every year. So, your
only option is is to buy it outright.
Buy it on contract and pay the £200
every month. Yeah, I know what it's
called, bro. I know what it's called.
I'm going to catch up on it. I always
So, as soon as I can get another side
hustle, I'll get it out on contract
cuz a new one comes out every year. So,
I'd rather just pay £200 a month. Um,
and that's it, bro. Call it call it a year. So,
yeah, my phone cost me £400. I bought it
outright. I've got the phone and I've
got the £400 phone.
But yeah, I'm just saying if I was
working, I could pay £200 a month.
If I have no out I have no outgoings.
That'd be like the only outgoing. So I
love my Samsung phones, bro. They mean a
lot to me. So
I'd be willing to part money for them.
You know what I'm saying? So, but at the
same time, I don't think there's going
to be much difference.
But yeah, it's it's it's [ __ ] that
you'll pay £1,700 and then a new one
will just come out next year.
It's not even like two years. Two years.
So it's like
and it's hard to justify £1,800
cuz £1,800 is America. So it's like
I think your best off is that year
contract. I think that's your best bet.
Well, with the money that I'll be on, I
can't keep up with the payments. I'd
literally have nothing. So,
I wouldn't be able to. But, I could
still do a 2-year contract to maybe upgrade,
but I don't have just £500 to throw away right now
and then be no way me making the money
back. You see?
I have to put on pause [ __ ] Yeah.
What if I get ill and can't work? It
would never happen, bro. I want to get ill.
No, it wouldn't happen, bro. And if I
got ill, I just wouldn't work the days I
were ill. So, [Music]
but there's better things in life than
[ __ ] a phone. You know what I mean?
Do women ignore Steven Howard?
You think women ignore? Yeah.
Yeah, probably probably were.
Let me see this phone, bro. Hold on.
I actually think I might get this phone.
I mean, if you get insurance, I mean, I
was paying I was paying the contract. I
was paying the contract, but obviously
the phone got stolen. But if I get
insurance on it, let me see. Hold up.
What are you talking about, bro? One sec.
Let me see this fold thing. Hold on.
So, if you got a 2-year contract,
one second, bro.
It's because they're stuck up, bro.
They're stuck up and have unrealistic
standards and they want Mr. Perfect.
They don't exist. That's why.
So, it's going to be in stock on the 22nd.
Hold on one second. I need to see how
much this phone is going to be a month. [Music]
One second, bro. Unlimited 150.
No, that's way too much.
That's still like £88 a month.
No. Then with the insurance, so you're
talking probably about £100 a month.
It's too much, bro.
Full cover, right? Let me see. £13
a month. It's too much.
It's way too much.
You're best off just going for the year.
That's way too much, bro. Way too much.
I thought I was expensive for like 60 70
and obviously you'd need to get insured as well.
The only thing you could probably do is
get insured and then say that you got it
stolen, but then you're not going to
make money cuz you got to pay £500 up front.
So, you're [ __ ] basically
But you know the thing is with these fold phones,
right? You know the thing is with these
folds, they never go they never ever go slow.
They never ever go slow.
That's the thing with these cars. They
never go slow. The battery always stays good.
Trust me, bro. These folds, they never
go slow. You could have them for a million years.
Yeah, women are being [ __ ] again.
They're being [ __ ] again, Grezy.
I wanted to get a Chinese today, Greasy,
but they were all closed.
Yeah, they were all closed, bro.
Why do I go up north? I've been up north
a million times. There's nothing there for me.
Oh, Grezy, I'm going to have to give you
a timeout, mate. Your iPhone. Yuck.
Yuck. My mommy had iPhone.
Going to have to give you a little time
out for that. No. Yuck. Yuck. Jumping
all the way.
What the [ __ ] We can't let any iPhone
users in our in our chat.
What the [ __ ]
What? Yeah, but why would I move up north?
Unless I can live with Greasy. Me and
Greasy could privately rent.
No, I'm not interested in going up north, bro.
There's nothing there. There's nothing
in this country for me.
My mommy was My mommy's really pretty,
isn't she? Grezy.
You like my mama?
I think I have a picture of my mommy somewhere.
That's my mama.
Somebody said to me that I look Syrian.
They said, "You look Syrian."
I look Syrian.
They said that I look Syrian. Yeah,
that's not my mama. Yuck. Yuck.
L Grezy. Thank you, [ __ ] Uh, thank you,
Greavvesy, do you ever sometimes just
get your pecker out?
Like randomly you'll just be walking and
you just get your pecker out. Huh?
Sometimes just get your pecker out.
I just I just won't do it because
there's no point. Oh,
do you remember Peter B can't get
attached now because he's already found
his mama? Do you remember Grezy?
These people used to come on here and
mock me in it, bro.
Yeah, I sometimes get mine out randomly. Yeah.
And I said to one of the people, "So, if
she's my mommy, why was she snogging me,
Grevy?" And they were like, "It was
motherly kisses. She was giving me
motherly kisses, Greavvesy.
So, Grezy, you get £1,200 a month. Yeah.
So, how how long did you say it would take?
How long did you say it would take to
save up for you to go America?
6 months, maybe.
It would take you about six months if
you lived off like
500 pound a month. Probably like
[ __ ] long time, bro. Maybe uh four.
If you had an Uber, you could probably
do it in two months.
I think with the Uber, you could do it
in two months.
If you had a house, you could do it in
one month. You could do it every month.
So, with the Uber probably two, I'd say
you could do it in two.
I reckon you could if you had if you had the Uber.
I used an e- pedal,
so it was a pedal bike, but it was electric.
Well, you fancy giving it a little Well,
yeah, you'll probably have better luck
to be honest because there's too many
riders in London.
Oh, I did. I only took a McDonald's
order once because of that reason. And
it's not even just that. It's not even
just the drink spilling. It's um when
you go to McDonald's, it takes ages for
them to give you the order. And you
could have probably done about two,
three orders by the time they give you
the food. Yeah. I had to do McDonald's
in [ __ ] Waterloo. Imagine that.
Yeah. It's fun. You make a bit of money
and there's less drivers in your area as
well. I'm on I'm trying to get more, but
I'm on a [ __ ] waiting list cuz
obviously I'm in London.
But yeah, McDonald's is [ __ ] Don't
accept McDonald's. It's too busy.
Yeah, give it a whirl.
Sign up with Uber Eats. It's
self-employed as well. You won't make
much money where you are, though. That's
the problem. Because you're not in
London. you you won't make much money
unless you go Manchester, but you're
still not going to make a lot of money.
But give it a try. Give it a while, you
know. But I rented the bike.
See, I I I was renting the bike every
time I done it. And obviously it was
like £12, but obviously I'd make the
money back. So So
yeah, you I rented a bike.
So the only problem is you probably
won't make a lot where you are. But
still do it. Still do it 100%. Try it,
you know. But
the problem is it's here in London you
get loads of rich people ordering food
so you have more work. But try it. You
got nothing to lose, bro.
But yeah, I was renting the bike £12
every time I on it. So, cuz I just
didn't want to buy a bike and,
you know, risk it getting stolen and
that kind of [ __ ] And then if the
battery run out, I'd be [ __ ] Whereas
this one, I could just change it. So, I
I was renting them.
But yeah, give it a try, bro. Give it a
try. You might even be able to do on a
normal pedal bike. Yeah.
Depends how much you need the extra
money. See, I liked getting out the
house and doing something and
I didn't have to think about women
because I was too busy with that. So yeah. Yeah, bro.
Yeah, I walked past a dead fox. It's
still there from two days later. Greasy.
It's [ __ ] disgusting.
Yep. So, I'm going to try other ones
now. Why does that pay better? Yeah.
I tried everything to appeal it and they
just weren't having it at all. at all.
Not at all. At all, mate.
But I liked it. I like the fact that I
could spend money and just make my own money back.
No, I'm [ __ ] They were not going to
give me a buyback.
No, I'm a [ __ ] mate.
Had some nice roast pork today. Greasy.
It's hard to eat right now cuz I got a mouth. Oh,
hello Kieran. You okay, boss?
>> Yeah, but obviously you're allowed to
have your own account.
You're allowed to have your own account,
bro. But I'm [ __ ] now cuz I need to
find another side hustle. So, I can't go
around spending money and
it's just about getting the money back
now. You see? So, I'm [ __ ] basically.
In other words,
yeah, that virgin got me [ __ ] banned
from the [ __ ] Tottenham Court Road pub and
he's such a [ __ ] virgin.
[ __ ] bro. You got me [ __ ] banned. [ __ ] virgin.
Yeah, man. He's a [ __ ] proper virgin, bro.
You know the one I'm talking about.
[ __ ] hell, man. Yeah,
[ __ ] such a virgin he is. I had to
report him to the [ __ ] police again
the other day. [ __ ] virgin. Yeah.
Oh, because I was recording and the
staff was giving attitude and yeah, I
just told them to [ __ ] off and I left. Bro,
yeah, I can't I don't I went out on
Saturday. I got three numbers, no reply, bro.
This country will never change.
[ __ ] Rocky White. It will never
change this country, bro.
Yeah, we're just not interested in this country. Oh, nice.
They're just not interested in this country, Kieran.
I [ __ ] got kicked out of somewhere
for talking to people, bro. What is
life, bro? Like, I don't even go out
anymore, bro. That was the first time in a month.
by Kieran. They're just not interested
in this country.
Do you remember that Kieran? They're
just not interested in this country.
Oh, [ __ ] I was drinking today, bro. I
had baby Guinness.
Bad baby Guinness.
How are you with money? Are you still skin?
You're not still skin, are you, Kieran?
You're not sure gambling, are you?
Hope you're not still gambling, mate.
Just sw that a long time ago.
Yeah. I hope you're not still gambling.
You're on about a grand a month in it,
Kieran. You're on about a grand a month.
And you [ __ ] gamble through the roof, don't you?
Yeah. I don't even gamble no more. Me,
bro. I haven't for ages properly.
I don't have money to be losing now, bro.
You're on about £1,000 a month, aren't
you, bro? I'll be on £1,000 a month
soon, bro. How depressing is that?
More like £1,100.
It's pretty depressing, eh?
At least I got savings in it.
Yeah, it's pretty depressing, eh?
Yeah, I get I'll be on like,00 now, bro.
So, I'll be But basically,
that's why I'm trying to find like
another thing I could do for extra money now.
Yeah, I had to pack up work, didn't I?
Is that right, Greavves? You had to pack
up work. Yeah, that sounds so funny saying that,
but I should get this some money this
month as well.
All right. [ __ ] bro.
Yeah. [ __ ] had to pack it all up, didn't I?
Do you even know what that means? Pack up work.
Mate, these [ __ ] have been talking all
[ __ ] day, Griezy. They woke me up
7:00 in the morning and they're still talking.
I'm going to [ __ ] go out there and
tell them to [ __ ] pack it in if they don't stop.
[ __ ] 7:00 in the [ __ ] morning, bro.
I thought it was someone in the house. I
thought it was someone in the house,
bro. What a [ __ ] them, bro.
Yeah, the neighbors, bro. And obviously
they're talking English, so it can't be
anyone in this house.
I wanted to I wanted to go over there
and [ __ ] them hard, bro. I swear down.
These two [ __ ] guys, bro. [ __ ] annoying.
I thought someone was in the house.
I wanted to go and [ __ ] them hard. I
swear now, bro. Like, I'm not gay or
anything in here, but I was the [ __ ] them hard.
Yeah, I got a lovely fan.
I got a lovely fan, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. I remember when I meed that USA is
all her friends and [ __ ]
All her friends.
A lot of them blocked me.
Who is that? Oh [ __ ]
I don't like that Dave, you know.
Yeah, these people, they didn't get me
sacked, bro. They didn't even know what
I was doing. I told them after I'd
already stopped the job, bro. cuz they basically uh
I got banned on my account for a
different reason, bro. They tell it's
because they're spastics, bro. They're
on £300. They don't have a job
themselves. We was talking about this
earlier when I was drinking in the pub.
They tell people that their skin and all
of that and all the it's because they're
talking about themselves. What they
really need to do is tell themselves to
get a job.
It's because they're sat at home lonely,
no friends, no money. Um,
then that's why, bro. So, yeah.
Yeah, it's hard nowadays to make money, is it?
Yeah, I don't really come in here much
anymore, bro. It's just the same repeating people
to be fair.
It's same old boring, bro. Same old red
store. Same old N legs.
Yeah, I get like [ __ ] I'll get like
1100 power now.
But I got no outgoing. So
yeah, you said that's not bad, is it?
Grezy £1,100 a month if you have no
outgoings in it.
That's what Greasy said.
Lucy said it's okay.
If you'd have to pay rent, you'd be [ __ ]
So, how do you afford McDonald's and [ __ ]
Yeah, I'll be saving maybe like
try and save 500. Yeah.
I swear if they don't stop, I'm going to
go there and I'm going to [ __ ] them hard.
I want to [ __ ] them really hard, bro.
Yeah, it's the same old on that camera, bro.
Who is that?
I swear that greasy I'm going to [ __ ]
them really hard, bro.
If they don't shut up next door.
You like when I say that, ain't it?
Bless you. If you save £500 a month, then Greasy,
bless you in life. Bless you.
Oh, bless you.
Trust me. I'm going to become rich.
You watch, bro.
I wish I was rich like greasy.
But don't forget I got a nice TV. Greasy,
if I still had that Uber, mate,
I have a lot more money.
I don't think Grezy wants to work. Do you Grezy?
TV, some savings. So, it's not all bad.
It's not all bad. I should get some
money this month as well. Hopefully.
Wish I could keep this house, man.
Wish I could keep this house ging, man.
But they're taking it back.
I'm going to miss that three grand a month, bro.
I missed that three grand a month, matey.
Oh, [ __ ] Uh, I got savings, bro. So,
Grezy, you think it's funny, is it?
But the tenants are going to be
homeless. You think it's funny, is it?
I was laughing. They said it's not
funny. I said, I'm not laughing. I'm
[ __ ] as well.
In the long shore of it, we're all [ __ ]
And who's going to cook my little food
now as well? I missed a little cooking.
When I had that nice meal yesterday, it
sent me straight to sleep.
Yeah, we're all [ __ ]
So, just accept it. You know, we're all
[ __ ] bro. All of us are [ __ ]
Yeah, they sent a letter through the post, bro.
[ __ ] bastards, bro. Had to [ __ ]
sell the washing machine and [ __ ] and
Yeah, man. So, [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah. I saying to this guy in Leeds, "Do
you go out for a night out anymore?" He
says, "No, smashing the gym and work, that's all."
Yeah, that's what I'll be doing now, mate.
Can't afford it. It sounds funny, but it
ain't funny. It's [ __ ] up, bro. It
ruined people's life. Like, take this
house back. They've actually ruined people's lives.
I'm financially going to lose.
I don't really want to [ __ ]
make I don't really want to go back to
my [ __ ] moms.
Don't know where I'm going. I have to
move the TV. They're [ __ ] cuz they
would have nowhere to go.
They get no good money as it is and
they're not going to find as good as a
landlord. All [ __ ] in different ways.
And I offered to pay the rent as well.
Like I offered to pay the rent and they
just weren't having none of it.
I offered to pay the rent weekly. I
would I would have done that, but they
just weren't having it at all at all. Yeah.
So, it's been stressful in it,
which is why I started the whole Uber
thing. But, you know,
but I didn't like the responsibility
that come with the house.
Like if I had it my way, I'd be like,
"Fuck you. Take the house and give me
the Uber back." Because I just didn't
like the responsibility.
Even though he was getting a lot of
money for not working, I just didn't
like the responsibility sort of thing.
Nowadays, I would say that because
obviously like I've done the nights out,
I've done the traveling, I've done the
nice meals. So nowadays, I probably
would say that
because I could still be on like two
grand. You don't need thousands and thousands, bro.
Yeah, I've got some savings, but I just
need to make money another way now. And
there is no way. So, I just have to try
to save money that I get cuz there is no
way to make money nowadays. But yeah,
the house was good, but I just didn't
like the responsibility. Cuz with the
Uber, it's fine. I could easily live off
that money, bro. 1.5 to 2 grand a month.
That's easy, bro. And I wouldn't even be
going out much anyways now. So, that was easy.
But it was just the whole
It's not just the money side of it. It's
the whole house. I need to move the TV.
They've just ruined people's lives, bro.
Taking this this back. They don't realize it.
But yeah, that's basically what I am
doing. I've got the gym to go to, so I
won't be out in a month or four months. So yeah, man.
H in lead. He said, "Oh, have you got
yourself a woman yet?" I said, "Nah,
none are interested." Yeah.
Yeah. I like interesting, man.
Well, it's not the greatest earner, but
it's a side hustle. I mean, I made £90
in like 10 hours, but it's better than
nothing, you know?
And if you get a deliveroo, they pay
even more money.
So, you can make money. Yeah.
Yeah. I just said not interested.
Bye-bye. Not reading that.
I make another account.
So yeah, that's it, bro. But it doesn't
matter anyways. Uh
yeah, like the thing is Kieran, bro,
like I don't really come on here anymore
cuz you need to understand, bro, that
these people will never stop.
Like you know that Red Star and like a
few others, they will never ever ever ever ever.
They will never stop, bro.
They will never ever stop.
You do realize that, bro?
I never stop, bro. I'll never leave you
alone, bro. Someone gave me the best
advice on YouTube before
I said you need to come off YouTube,
live your life. They're never going to
leave you alone.
Which I did basically take their advice, I guess.
I really need to more.
Yeah, it's the truth. It
doesn't matter who it is, bro. They never stop.
They never stop, bro. Yeah. Okay. [Music]
Yeah, I don't really come on much
anymore anyways, Kieran, bro.
It's the same repeating people, is it?
It's the same repeating people every day.
I got some ice cream. I might just have
I should get some popcorn. Yeah.
A couple of days. I wish they wouldn't come. Hello. [ __ ]
No, they're just not happy about it. But
there's nothing I can do about it, is
it? They're not beefing cuz I let them
know well in advance.
It was like the most awkward like
conversation. I was like, "Yeah, you
kind of got to go."
It's not funny though, bro. They're
ruining lives here. Like especially when
you offered to pay the rent. I offered
to pay them the rent as well and they
just weren't having none of it at all.
The house is all [ __ ] up as well. So
just making people's life difficult here is it
offered to pay the rent too and they
wouldn't have it. Yeah.
Now I got to move that TV somehow.
[ __ ] [ __ ] in it. I have roast pork
today, Kieran. Roast pork and beef. Yep.
Anyways, I'm gone. Yeah, I'll be back. I don't know. Never hopefully.
so yeah, in a bit.