Y
some frag man. Oh [ __ ] Motor clear.
Oh [ __ ] that was nasty person now.
Yeah, I've tried the old apps out again
because people kept telling me to go on them
dating and that stuff.
They're just as [ __ ] as they was in February.
I got told to use dating apps.
They're [ __ ] [ __ ] as they were back in Jan.
Weren't February. It was actually January.
A gay guy said, "Oh, you should try the dating apps."
I'd give him a little try. [ __ ] load
of old [ __ ]
So they asked me where I lived. I said I
lived in East. Where do you live?
Southeast elephant and castle. They said
they lived. I said, "Okay,
we should meet up sometime." There's
like, "Oh, I've got family coming
around." And just say, "Oh, shit."
Really? Some of them didn't reply.
See, that's the thing in this country.
It never changes.
That's the thing. In this country, it
never ever changes.
Same old [ __ ] Never changes. Oh, [ __ ]
I like this car, man.
It's nice and fast. It's either
It's weird, man. You start on dating
apps, they tell you to go out and
approach, then they say the approach is
weird, and they tell you to go back on
dating apps, and then when you go back
on dating apps, it's just time wasters.
Um, I you don't know why. I know why. Validation, attention.
I mean, it's easy to know the reason why
they won there.
and they'll be like, "Oh, you're
handsome." And no, no, no. And then they
don't. And when you try to meet
or or try and talk, they're not having
any of it.
That's why I don't use them. That's why
I use them like once a year, bro, for
like 5 days. I don't use them. It's [ __ ]
I don't know why people tell me to um
use them and they don't even work.
[ __ ] I was trying to go on Bumble, but
but um Bumble
is [ __ ] It doesn't work on my phone, bro.
So, yeah, man.
Strange, isn't it?
I love these new cars, bro.
But yeah, never changes in this country, sadly. Never has, never will. Oh, dead.
I feel [ __ ] My body's hurting, man.
Think I'm [ __ ] depressed, to be honest.
My body aching, bro. I think it's got
all that stress in it. Yeah.
Hope I got [ __ ] sleep there. >> Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] me. At least I've kept off the
gardening and [ __ ] in it.
I think you just come, you just realize
in the end that [ __ ]
it's [ __ ] dead now, ain't it? The
industry is [ __ ] dead. So,
you just realize the industry is dead
and it's just a waste of time and money. Yeah.
Oh, I can't wait to leave again, bro.
Country's [ __ ] depressing. My [ __ ]
back is aching and everything.
It was some more out for taking that. [ __ ] bro.
I was flying as well. Yeah,
this country will never change, bro. [ __ ] never
was crying faster.
Think about it, bro. Yeah.
How delusional do you have to be to
think that one day uh you'll wake up and
all of a sudden it's just going to
change when the same thing's been
happening for years?
It's just so the news is it
this country is depressed but it really
is depressing in this country but
it's a depressing life in England but I hate England
all the way
Oh, I'm just going to have this bottle
of Coke now.
>> But yeah, so depressing here in England.
I hate it.
Anyone else find themselves depressed in England?
in this country.
You're not living in this country. You're existing.
Oh, [ __ ] man.
morning back on Hey chicken.
I said if I was before due to meet she
text me a voice excuse said she couldn't
meet I called her line she blocked me oh
really sounds like England to me
yeah sounds like an England problem
yeah just sounds like England And
I had one that I approached in a in a
Weather Spoons and [ __ ] not Weather
Spoon, the train station.
[ __ ] [ __ ] was telling me she's
flying to [ __ ] Singapore.
Yeah, I read your comment, bro. This
time was like England to me. Nothing new.
I'm back on the dating app show cuz this
gay guy said, "Oh, you should give
dating apps a try. You should give
dating apps a go." So, I thought, you
know what? Just more than sorry, I
downloaded them yesterday.
[ __ ] croc of [ __ ] mate. Same as January.
Typical England. That's all I know, mate.
You not realize that it's never going to
change in this in this country, bro.
Well, there's not even no point in moing
about it anymore. It's just England.
Been going on for [ __ ] years, bro.
But yeah, I run the dating apps and
they're [ __ ] [ __ ] again. Same old
Same old matches don't reply replying
and don't want to meet. Same old same
old same old
same old depressing England
playing some grand here.
The football will be back soon. At least
you can start betting on the football
again. I'll start betting on the football me.
That's the only thing I'll be betting on
now. I don't dam anymore. So just a football
will never change in this country. Not
when it comes to women and data. Never.
But actually it will change. It will get worse.
That's why I just hold on to the good
memories nowadays because I realize
you're never going to get any more new
memories here. You're never going to get
any more new memories because it's just the same.
Things will never change in this
country. I've been doing it for years.
[ __ ] years. Years, bro. [ __ ] Oh,
he's wearing purple.
But yeah, I'm on this Tinder app. It
didn't let me [ __ ] download Bumble
for some reason. But yeah,
I hate this country. My back is aching as well.
Try again with an Indian. Good luck.
Do you mean an Indian that was born here
or an Indian that was born from India?
Either way, you got no chance because
you get Indians in London.
So yeah, they're even harder to get
with. Even if they come from India, you
can't get them, bro. We get loads of
Indians in London. And the ones that are
born here are [ __ ] stuck up to [ __ ]
more than the white ones.
And then the ones that were born here,
they will just reject you, you know, in
like a different way. You have to leave
the country. If you're serious about
dating, you really want to date, you
have to leave England.
You have to go to Asia like China, Thailand,
Cambodia, Vietnam, Philippines.
Like you you uh Yeah.
No, it's not easy at all, mate. It's even harder.
Noah, you need to leave the country. If
you're if you're serious about dating,
you need to leave the country.
Yeah. And it shouldn't even be like
you've tried everything. You should be
with someone now. You're a decent looking fella.
And by you, I mean me. You're a decent
looking fella with good approaching
skills. It shouldn't be this way. But it
is this way. My [ __ ] back is hurting me, bro.
No, but you find them in the Philippines.
My [ __ ] back is hurting me, bro. I
think it's [ __ ] stress and [ __ ]
I hate this country. I [ __ ] hate it.
You understand? I [ __ ] hate it with a passion.
It's such a depressing backwards. Oh,
annoying country. It's so annoying.
Country annoys me, bro.
I don't know about you, this country annoys me.
Yeah, speed dating. I could try it, but
I don't think I would try it in London.
Have you ever heard of a place called
Reading? Uh Reading, Joe, have you ever
been to Reading?
Well, I've not tried speed dating, bro. The [ __ ] Speed dating.
Speed dating, bro. And man tried that.
No one popped his balloon.
What's there? Nothing
really. Just like some clubs and [ __ ]
No, speed dating is worse. But Joe is
right. It is something to try cuz you
got nothing to lose by trying. But it
won't work for various different
reasons. But we'll still try anyways.
But it wouldn't work because why would a
woman go speed dating when she can get
any man she wants? Think of it. You got
Tik Tok now. You got dating apps. You
got Instagram. A woman who's a four,
five out of 10. Look at [ __ ] USA for
example. Can find sex, confined
relationships. The only person only
woman that wouldn't be able to find
anyone in this country is probably a 50y old
with kids. That's the only
women that I can imagine going to them
places because why would a woman You
need to understand you need to
understand this, right? Why would a
woman go speed dating when she can find
anyone she wants? And don't listen to
their excuse. Oh, only men want us only
for sex. That is [ __ ] There's loads
of people that want relationships.
There's loads of people.
No, my sisters don't hang around with
her friends and sister's friends can
reject you as well. So, that doesn't
work cuz your sister's friends can
reject you. And all of my sister's
friends are married and got kids and
they don't really they don't really see
their friends anymore. So, so that's not
going to work. I tried that [ __ ] when I
was 17. But anyways, back to the speed dating thing.
It doesn't work like that. It's the same
as just going and approaching a random person.
Back in 2009, it would work. Back when
there was house parties, you could you
could do it through friends and sister
friends. That would work. It has worked.
But nowadays, nah. Nah. It's the same as
you just talking to somebody in the
club. They're just going to reject you.
They don't care if they're your sister's friends or
trust me. And it's not a good thing
either because you really want to be
with somebody that knows your sister.
So I wouldn't want to be with somebody
that knows my sisters or my friends. And
you might sound like I'm being difficult
and I'm being awkward, but I'm not.
You know. Well, bro, we know that most
of these women ain't got a boyfriend.
What? What? What? What do you mean? And
you know they haven't got a boyfriend.
We know that most of these people don't
have a boyfriend.
Why does nothing work? Because it's a westernized country
full of stuck up people that base their
standards on [ __ ] social media.
That's why nothing works.
No, I'm not doing it, bro. I can't be
[ __ ] I can't be bothered. [ __ ] all
that. I know I said I was going to do it
in it. I woke up this morning. I told
that man about it and I was like, "Nah,
[ __ ] that, bro."
I think I'd end up doing somebody in by
the end of the [ __ ] day if I did.
[ __ ] that, bro. I don't know what I was
thinking saying that.
But yeah, Joe, we know that most of them
don't have a boyfriend. What's What's
that got to do with anything?
Why does he pretend to have a woman?
Because he's a fantasist.
That's none of your business.
Yeah, that's none of your business, bro. So, yeah,
I am [ __ ] bro. My back and
everything. So tired.
So yeah, in reading there's just some uh
there's just some um [ __ ]
bars and clubs and [ __ ] So yeah.
So yeah, it's impossible, bro.
I'm back on these dating apps. Let me
see if any more reply or
it's impossible in this country, but [ __ ]
that charger better be there.
Do Viper. Is that that sad old keyboard
warrior of a man?
Is that Is that that sad old bastard
that self projects every every day on
YouTube for years? I remember that [ __ ] Yeah, man.
Yeah. What's your opinion on it, though?
Yeah, I do remember this this vibe on a
sad old man. I remember him, bro. He
used to [ __ ] on my thing. Sad old bastard.
I remember exactly who that is.
Does anyone else feel depressed in this
country? I feel so depressed in this country.
So many different reasons in this depressing country.
It's impossible everywhere in the West.
Oh, so where where do you think it's possible then?
How he gets women? He doesn't get women.
He's a fat old ugly man. He doesn't get women.
And if he [ __ ] does,
it's [ __ ] 50y olds. He doesn't get no
[ __ ] women. He's a stand old man. Um,
what kill the rest social media,
Instagram, Tik Tok, people base their
standards off of that now. So,
[ __ ] I can't come over.
You're not in the You're not in the
wrong plate. You're in the wrong
country. That's what you're in.
Oh, I moved. Ah, [ __ ]
I've already done approaches in Maiden and Reen.
Don't you think? Don't you remember
that? Which I was thinking of doing, but
I've already done it.
It's not London. It's England. It's not
It's not London. It's It's literally England.
It's any westernized country. It's not a particular city.
And it will be the same in Blackpool as
well. And I have done Maiden Head and I
have done Reen. Do you not remember that
time I went out all day going all around
London doing approaches like two years ago? Shepherd's Bush
all around the West. Shepherd's Bush [ __ ]
reading Maiden Head. And I come back at
like 10:00 at night and it was the same
old boyfriend [ __ ]
It was the same old boyfriend [ __ ]
Boring, bro. There's no particular place. So
I'm leaving the country again. That's
the only thing I'm doing.
The only thing I'm doing is leaving the
country again. [ __ ] this.
3 years is a long time for nothing to
change, bro. It's a long time and it's
only gotten worse.
It's only getting worse and it's only
gotten worse. So,
you don't need to try anything but leave
this country really.
It's never ever ever going to change.
You got nothing left to prove, bro. [ __ ]
You literally have nothing left to prove.
No, I didn't get any women at all, bro.
I went to Thailand and I got rejected by everyone.
Stupid questions, stupid answers.
That's why I said to people on
marketplace, Joe, they ask stupid
questions, they got stupid answers.
Have you ever heard that saying? No. I
went to Thailand. I went to Asia where
people from the west all over go to get
women. And I and I didn't get no women.
No. No. No. Not at all. No,
no, none at all, mate. None at all.
Stupid questions get stupid answers.
Nah, these people in the marketplace was
doing my head. Somebody asked if the
washing machine was working. I said,
"Nah, it's broken. It's [ __ ] It's broken, mate."
I said to him, "Nah."
I said tonight it's broken. And he put
he put a thumbs up.
Stop. What are you [ __ ] asking stupid
questions for, [ __ ]
[ __ ] Why you ask stupid? You know I've
noticed. Yeah. You know that you know
the thing that I'm going to be most
happy thing about when I move. Yeah. And
[ __ ] And I get myself sorted. I'll be
so glad to be away from people. Oh, I
hate people so much. Obviously have to
deal with them at the moment. trying to
get rid of some of these things and
[ __ ] I just can't wait to never have to
deal with people for a long time, you
know? They're [ __ ] [ __ ] hate
people, you know.
They're going to be so stupid.
This [ __ ] just run me over.
This [ __ ] just run me over, John.
No, it doesn't. It doesn't get me mad,
bro. I just don't understand how you can look normal
and you can't even find anyone in your
own country. It's mad.
Oh, he's dead.
I love GTA, bro.
You can be normal looking, decent
looking, whatever, and you can't even
find someone in your own country. It's
[ __ ] disgusting, isn't it?
It's [ __ ] disgusting. Like, is it?
It's disgusting, bro. Nope.
And neighbors are okay. Most neighbors
keep themselves themselves.
Neighbors are not a problem.
They don't really say any they don't say
anything to you. Except where my mom
lives, they're all [ __ ] nosy bastards.
Two-faced nosy [ __ ] bastards. But
here they don't get any problems. They
keep themselves themselves.
They say hi, you say hi, they walk.
Sometimes, most of the time, they don't.
They just keep themselves themselves,
which is the way it should be.
But where my mom lives, the neighbors,
not all of them, but some of them are just [ __ ]
Bro, even if I was to get another
delivery service, I'm not telling you
anything. So, like, like I was saying
yesterday, there's no point anymore
saying, "Oh, you working?" Oh, no, no.
Like I'm not get giving in getting into
any of the these combos anymore. I only
got I only told you about it because
uh yeah, you are single for life. Yeah,
we know that you're single for life, bro.
Um but yeah, I only told you about it
cuz I didn't do it anymore. So
yeah, so I told you in it, but I'll never ever
ever say anything ever again, bro. And I
wouldn't have said anything ever again.
I would have made you forgot the idea.
But since they [ __ ] terminated my
account, I thought, "Fuck it."
Yeah, I don't want to move up north,
bro. Cuz I still like London. I just
don't like the people in it.
Say, say you get another delivery job.
Yeah. For for example. Listen, listen,
bro. Yeah. How am I going to make money
up north? You're going to not make money
up north, bro. You're not going to make
money up north. So say there's less
opportunities up north
and the women are still the same there.
North is the same.
Like it's and there's just going to be
less opportunities, less restaurants, less opportunities.
It's And the women are the same as well.
Yeah. The people might be friendlier,
but the women are the same. So,
so I wouldn't,
you know, I was thinking to move to
Scotland, like Ed, if I was, if I was to
move anywhere else, it would be
Edinburgh. And I wouldn't even move.
That's like the only probably other
place you can maybe make money.
If you go into like another delivery
service with that I would I think I
would there but that's I wouldn't be
able to do that anyways because of Laney
and [ __ ] So
but even still like if you get another
delivery service you won't make any
money anywhere but London. So
it's just the people that ruin London unfortunately.
So entitled [ __ ]
No, I'm seeing him later. So
yeah, my second favorite city is
Edinburgh. I have to say it is.
That's why I was telling Greg to go
there. It's a nice city, man. It's a
nice city. It's a lot cheaper than
London, you know, and I think you would
like it there.
People go there for work. I mean, there
is some work up there, too. But if you
go somewhere like Manchester, it's [ __ ]
Manchester is [ __ ] It's just a smaller
smaller wannabe London, and people have
got the same attitude.
All right, Harry, you are single. You're
talking about yourself. Like, I've had
more women than you. I've had more sex
than you, bro. Like, you you are single.
Like, think think about it, bro. Okay.
I'm going to be single for life. Yes.
Like you, you are single for life. I'm
not the one pretending that I'm in a relationship.
No, no, no, no, no. I I know you're not
trolling, but bro, you are single
yourself and you're the one that has to
pretend that you're in a relationship.
That's even sadder that you have to you
have to keep pretending that you're in a
relationship. I don't pretend I'm in a
[ __ ] relationship. You have to
literally pretend that you're in a
relationship. Does that not seem sad to you?
You got this relationship. You've got this money,
but you're on YouTube every day. Doesn't
look right. No, I'm not being triggered,
bro. I'm just saying that you're the one
that has to lie about being in a
relationship. Okay. Can we hear your
burden? Because we can hear um Triple H's girlfriend.
I don't know anything about you. I know
that you're a [ __ ] I know that when me
and London Taylor come to um when me and
um uh Liverpool and separate times, you
didn't come out. So, I know one thing,
you're not about that life. And I know
one thing that you can't prove that you
got a girlfriend. I know them two
things. I know that you're not about
that life, bro.
Like you talk about nons legs and no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no
no no no but let's really keep it real
bro like when I was in Liverpool you was
nowhere to be seen
when [ __ ] London Taylor went to
Liverpool you was nowhere to be seen so
at the end of the day bro like yeah
you're not the one saying sorry to some
muppet bro because you can't even leave
your house when somebody comes to your
city think about think about it bro yeah
yeah just think about this for one
second I came all the way to Liverpool,
which is about 240 mi away all by
myself, bro. And you all went quiet.
Please don't talk about people being
about a life and not about a life. And
I'm not about that. I'm not talking like
I'm strong and I'm some hard man, bro.
Like, I came and you was nowhere to be seen. [ __ ]
You see how mad it is? And you're
talking about how you're going to do
this and that, bro. Triggered. No one's
triggered, bro. They're telling you
facts. Why is it every single time
people tell you facts, you say that
they're triggered? Triggered at what, bro?
He's probably at work. He doesn't work.
And Liverpool is not huge. Liverpool is
very, very small. Anywhere in Liverpool
is about 15 to 20 minutes away from the
city center. Don't even try using that excuse.
Yeah. Even London, you ain't got no
excuse. And London's the biggest city in
England. So, nice try, but cute little
excuse there. I know you're trying to
get reaction, but yeah, Liverpool is not
huge. Somewhere that is huge is London.
And even in London, you can get anywhere
to anywhere in no time. So, try again
with your cute little excuses. So, yeah,
Liverpool is not [ __ ] huge. Oh, are
you [ __ ] mad? small bro compared to
[ __ ] London and [ __ ] Birmingham.
That time I went to Birmingham. [ __ ]
Money Mike and Timmy was there in no time.
Yeah. Okay, bro. No one's saying that he
lives in the city center,
bro. No one is saying that he lives in
the city center, but I was in Liverpool
all day and all night. Who said that he
lives in the in the city center? He was
I was in Liverpool all day and all
night. So yes, Liverpool is so big that
you can't get somewhere all day and all
night. Okay, bro. Liverpool is really
really that big. Who said that you live
in a city center? Of course you don't
live in a city center, you fool. You're too skinn.
Anyways, moving on now. [ __ ] hell.
Why are we getting on to this [ __ ]
anyways? So yeah,
Liverpool Liverpool is not huge.
Liverpool is [ __ ] huge. [ __ ] off,
mate. Liverpool's [ __ ] huge.
Is it [ __ ] mate? Is it? [ __ ]
In Liverpool, you've got one main town
center. I I'm not getting I'm not
getting into this anyways, bro. I'm I'm
not talking about this. [ __ ] bro. Why
do we even talk about this [ __ ] All
we know is that when you go to
Liverpool, Harry goes quiet and all the
other people from Liverpool go quiet.
End of that's already been proven.
So that's it. Um anyways,
I think this Joe guy is Scottish.
No, you can get loans here. You can get
loans here in England. You can get loans
here, but I don't get loans because I
don't want to [ __ ] I I don't want to
pay them back. I don't want to get
loans, bro. I'd rather just work for
money. I don't want loans.
Yeah, I know people that got loans and [ __ ]
Like two different ones, but I'm not
getting loans, bro. [ __ ] that. So, yeah,
I am not I'm not getting no [ __ ]
loans. [ __ ] that.
But I think this Joe guy is Scottish.
I think he knows Tam. I think. Yeah.
But I couldn't move anyways cuz So yeah,
I know people they just got these loans
and they didn't even do anything with
the money. They got like two different
loans and they didn't do they have
nothing to show for it. Yeah. So,
but I'd rather just work and [ __ ] So,
when I can so
but yeah, I couldn't cuz Elani have to
be here and look after Laney. You see,
Scotland's a bit too far, you know.
No, I'm not going uni. [ __ ] that for a
game of soldiers.
Have you ever heard that saying, Joe?
[ __ ] that poor game of soldiers.
Yep. [ __ ] that poor game of soldiers, mate. You better man.
But I think that would be a lovely site.
Like a nice little house in Edinburgh.
A little doggy. GTA 5. Nice TV. What a
lovely site. Grezy. A little baby with a
Celtic baby, bro.
Oh, what a lovely sight.
That's what That's what you call like
the dream right there, is it? That is
what you call a lovely sight.
A little Celtic baby, bro.
Yeah. Yeah, I do need to do something,
bro. Again. Yeah.
Yeah. I know Celtic is Glasgow, but you
know it's I know it comes from Glasgow,
but it's still Scottish, isn't it? I
mean, I mean, I think they're Rangers,
aren't they? I'm sure some people from
Edinburgh support Celtic. And I'd call a
baby Tam. Oh, how cute is that?
A Yeah, you do need to do something. You
need to leave this country
again. That's what I'm saying. Yeah.
Yeah, but I just put it in the Celtic
baby go in it. How cute is that? Oh, that's
Well, do you think if I go to Glasgow,
I'll pull Joe, I'll probably get [ __ ] stabbed up.
I know Celtic is Glasgow, bro. I know it
is. It's It's Yeah, I know it is. But
I'm just saying that's why I put the baby in.
Yeah, you should do, bro.
Moving stressful, bro.
You never pull here, mate.
[ __ ] never pull here.
Yeah, I thought the night out in
Edinburgh would have been better than [ __ ]
I thought it would have been better than
Newcastle, but it wasn't. I thought it
was actually going to be a lot better
than it was.
I don't think anyone said they had a
boyfriend. I don't think No, they never
I would I would have definitely
remembered if they did, but they never.
But I still thought Newcastle was better
cuz I thought, yeah, you know, Scotland,
they love drinking. You know, Irish and
Scottish people, they love drinking, you
know. You know, they drinking a [ __ ]
daytime and [ __ ] like all throughout the
day. Yeah. I'm thinking it's going to be
this big thing, but
still ended up [ __ ] an escort and
getting the train back. So,
I thought it was going to be better than
in terms of like a night out. I think it
was I thought it was going to be better
cuz everywhere closes at like 2:00.
But I can't complain. It was very cheap there. So
yeah, it was very cheap there, was it? Yeah. [ __ ]
But yeah, there's not there is something
you need to change, bro. Change countries.
Have you just been ignoring me for the
past 41 minutes? Yeah, you do need to
change. Change countries. Oh [ __ ]
[ __ ] think flipped around, bro.
Yeah, that's what you need to do. You
need to leave this country again.
Think we should still give somewhere
else another shot one last time. But
should you? You don't need to do it
though, bro. You've been everywhere in this country.
What will make it Think about it now.
Yeah. What will make it all of a sudden
make you meet someone now?
Like say you went to Leia for example or
you went to Sheffield next week. What
would make you so sure that after all
these years and all that money you've
gone through and all of the people that
you've met this time round you're
suddenly going to find a wife? You're
suddenly going to find a relationship.
If it's not happen in in in years and
years of traveling, right, what makes
you think it will be different this time around?
You know, and if I could get and it's
only gotten worse. I mean, yeah, people
say that you can't predict the future
and rare and this that and the other and
but I mean, if something's been
happening for [ __ ] 3 years,
I mean, you kind of have a pretty good
idea what the future holds.
That's my logic anyways. I don't know about yours. Yeah.
She doesn't. Well, we know the reason,
but she doesn't she doesn't have an
opinion on it. We know what the reason
is. There's too many stuck up [ __ ] in
this country. [ __ ] Tik Tok. [ __ ]
and you didn't answer my question why I
just asked you as well. Tik Tok, Instagram,
that's it's pretty simple why you can't find someone.
It's literally this country. That's
literally what it is.
But anyways, like if you could give me a good reason,
then I wouldn't mind going to Scotland
again and spending money again or going
Newcastle again or going Leeds again. If
you could give me a proper explanation,
then I I I I I could understand it.
But you you can't cuz 3 years is quite a
long time, you know? So
my logic is if it hasn't happened now,
it's never going to happen.
Like that's that's literally it.
And when I said I I wanted to travel and
have a drink somewhere soon, that's just
to get some head space to get out of
London, you know, because it does get a
bit too much sometimes,
you know. So that's what I meant by
going and drinking somewhere. But yeah, man.
But then if there was an actual
extraation, then I could understand it.
But I don't, like I said, 3 years is a long time.
It's not like it's a year or
I don't know 6 months. A year would even
be all right cuz people don't find
people in a year. Like you not everyone
will find someone in a year. A year is
not that long.
I believe your your your I believe your
past dictates your dictates your future
when it comes to dating. Yes. When it
comes to your dating life, see now like
obviously I don't get as I won't get as
much money now. I've still got savings
and [ __ ] but I know deep down like,
yeah, something's going to come up like
some other delivery job's going to
accept you or something's going to come
up or worse comes to worse, you're just
going to get used to living um
living off the money you get or
something something's going to happen.
It's not all going to be bad, but with
the dating, it does dictate your future.
It does dictate your future
because in 3 years, like if the same
thing has been happening, the boyfriend
[ __ ] the all the [ __ ]
then how is it going to all of a sudden
change now? Do you stay here?
No. Okay. Okay. So,
you seem to think so you you've you've
gone all around the country,
Scotland, Wales, you even left the
country. You've got I've got a
boyfriend. You kept dealing with these
game games and [ __ ] but you think after
3 years all of a sudden something's
going to be hunky [ __ ] Dory and it's
going to all of a sudden just stop.
Can't see it. Can't see it, bro.
Can't I can't imagine that after 3 years
all of a sudden it's going to change it.
The world don't work like that. So when
So yeah, I I do think when it comes to
dating, your past dictates your future.
Definitely 100. When it comes to dating,
I do. Yes. 100%. Because
even even if you speak of recent
experiences, I don't even go out much
anymore. What happens when you go out,
right? Let's let's let's play let's play
two sides of a coin here. When you go
out, what happens?
When you go out approaching, whether
it's sober, drunk, what usually happens
most of the time that you go out?
So there you go then. And if I decided
to go out on Thursday, what what what
would your money be on? Come on, you
like to gamble. Like, bro, I'm so
confident that I even said that [ __ ]
William Hill needs to bring out a
[ __ ] new market when it comes to
dating. And I would I'd keep all the
business the bookies wouldn't be in
business anymore cuz I'd be right. I bet
the correct sayings in order what would
happen. I'd be rich. I literally would
be [ __ ] rich. I could tell you what
would happen, when would happen, how it
would happen, and the time it would
happen. I'm that confident.
So, I think it does predict
uh your dating. Yeah, it does predict
your because if it didn't something
would have happened by now,
you know, something would have happened
by now. Like it's it's that simple.
That's that's it.
Something would have happened. It
doesn't matter. Bro, listen. It doesn't
matter whether it's a festival. It
doesn't matter if it's a library. It
doesn't matter if it's bars, clubs, the
[ __ ] hospital. It doesn't matter
where it is.
It's still going to be the same.
I don't do it anymore, bro. I just told
you I went out for a I I went out for a
month. I went out the first time of the
month and I said that when I'm earning
again, I will go out once a week for a
drink because sometimes there's nothing
else to do. Yeah, I do it because
there's nothing else to do. I know I'm
not going to get [ __ ] off, but what else
is there really to do?
But I know in my head that you, you
know, you're going to get [ __ ] off.
It's just something to look forward to
to go out and drinking once a week,
which I won't even be able to do now
anyways. But yeah. So yeah,
I know it's damn sure I don't even get
my haircut anymore.
Yeah, but I I am going to do it because
I like to go out for a drink.
I am going to go out for a drink. I'm
going to go out for a drink. I can't
work at the minute. So, what else am I
supposed to do?
But like I said, 3 years is is a very long time.
So, if something Okay. So, if
something's not changed in 3 years,
when is your bet that you think it's
like bear in mind, we've been all over
the country. We've approached thousands
of people. When when is your guess that
it's going to change?
When is your guess? When is your guess
that it's all of a sudden just going to change?
Cuz you do realize it's just delusional.
If something was going to happen, it
would have happened by now. It it does
it doesn't matter. If something was
really going to change, it would have
changed by now. Is that a lie or what?
cuz you're saying right that your your
past doesn't dictate your future, right?
So think of the first day you done this.
What has changed in 3 years? So it seems
that it very
if we it seems that it does dictate your future.
It seems that it does dictate your
future very much. So
that's the way I see it.
Got a message on Tinder.
So yeah, like I just feel like if
something was going to change, it would
have changed by now
with all the money you spent, with all
the traveling you've spent.
But then you got people saying that you
don't know the future, but you got a
good idea. You got a very very good
Okay. If I went out today and I done approaches,
what would what would you put money on?
Okay, let's put it this way, right? You
went out today and you done approaches,
what would your money be on? [ __ ]
a feet of [ __ ] bro.
Okay. Right. So, when I So, when I go
out and approach and I get told I've got
a boyfriend or when I get numbers and
they don't reply or they [ __ ] me around,
that's that's me being negative, is it?
Oh, is that what that was? Okay.
Okay. Fine. All right. Okay, interesting.
That must have been all in my head then,
is it? Last week must have been all in my head.
But yeah, I definitely think
if you was going to meet somebody, you
would have met someone by now.
That's that that's that's what I
generally think anyways. But cuz think
of how much your life changed in like 3
years. You got older, you got more
money, you done more traveling, people changed homes.
So much things has changed. But the
dating scene is the same.
Doesn't look right, does it? Really, so
much things will change in 3 years, but
not this. This stays the same.
Okay. But I don't think that you're
educated enough to understand what I'm
saying, right? because you're talking
about how your future does not your past
don't dictate your future. I have just
told you I've traveled all over the
country. I have done so many different
approaches and I'm in the same position
and you're still trying to give me hope.
Like I I think you're the one that's not
educated enough because you clearly
don't understand what I what I'm saying.
So, and yeah, it's no one else's fault.
No, you're right, bro. It's all my
fault. Women are not stuck up. The the
the whole dating scene is not been
[ __ ] Yep. It's all me. I'm the big
bad w. Is that what you want to hear,
bro? Like, I'm happy to agree with
anything you're saying.
But realistically, what you're saying
doesn't make any sense because if if if
your future if your past did not dictate
your future, you would be married by
now. you'd be in a relationship by now.
You'd be sat here playing GTA with
someone by now.
So, it it does it does because it's the same old.
It's not anyone's fault. Well, well, it
kind of is. I mean, it it has to be
someone's fault. Like, you're you're
decent looking. There's nothing wrong
with you. And then you get these women
rejecting you. So, I mean, it's got to
kind of be someone's fault. Like, I know
that's not what what you hear. I know
like you don't want to admit that women
are stuck up and their standards are unrealistic.
It's definitely got to be someone's
fault, bro. How can no one be the blame
to for any of this?
It can't be both at all.
But it doesn't matter anyways. Why are
we talking about that, you know? So, yeah.
No one's life is the same after 3 years.
You know, you you what you're saying
does not make any sense, right? You
would have found someone in 3 years. End
of story. If your if your if your past
did not dictate your future, you would
have found someone. You've been all over
the country. It's what like Ant-Man
says, you need to leave the country. End of [ __ ]
You're [ __ ] delusional, bro.
Three years is a [ __ ] long time. Do
you not know how long that is?
So, one day, right, you're going to go
out in London and it's going to get be
completely different. No one's going to
pretend they've got boyfriends. You're
going to get several dates and you're
going to get in a relationship. Do you
not realize how stupid that sounds?
Like, do you not understand how
ridiculous that sounds? Think of it,
right? It It's been going on for years.
So, you think you're just going to go
out one day and it's all of a sudden
going to be different? Yet, it's getting
worse, but you're telling me that I'm not educated. So, yeah. So, yeah,
that doesn't make sense. If it was a
year, I'd agree with you.
If it was 6 months, I'd agree with you.
I'd be like, "Oh, well, yeah, it's been
a [ __ ] 6 months." But, you know, they're
just like, "It is whatever." Only 6
months. Only 8 months, but 3 years. It's
a long time, man.
That's a long [ __ ] time, bro.
But all of a sudden,
You're saying that the future does not
dictate the the past don't dictate the
future yet. This has been going on for 3 years.
Oh, right. Interesting. It
been going on for 3 years. Eh,
that's mad, isn't it? But you remember
Greasy that your past does not dictate
your future. I'm going to remember that
next time I go out. If I can go out on
Saturday um or whenever I go out again,
I'm going to remember that. Even though
it's been going on for 3 years and it's
just getting worse,
you never know when it's all of a sudden
going to change. Wow.
Strange, isn't it? Three years, mind
you. Three years. A whole three years.
I'll remember that next time I go out
when I can't be bothered to.
Yeah. You're going to go out one day and
no one's going to pretend they've got
boyfriends and no one's going to act
stuck up. H I pay good money to see that, mate.
I pay good money to see that day. Yeah.
I pay good money, bro.
really like talking about this. This is depressing, bro.
It's [ __ ] depressing.
I mean, do you understand the point I'm
trying to make, Green? Let's Let's put a
Let's put a Let's put a poll up. Who do
you agree with, me or Joe?
which I don't care who agrees with me or
don't agree with me. Like I just I don't
think he understands right that he's the
one saying that I'm not educated enough
or something. Yet he's trying to tell me
that in 3 years something's all of a
sudden going to change.
How is it even possible? You know,
and it's not and it's the amount you've
tried as well. It's also the amount
you've tried. It's not like you just
went to work like a normal person and
you was on and off the dating apps
because I mean sometimes it can take
people years you know but if you're out
almost every week traveling around the
country and in 3 years you have still
not found someone
but because you got to understand 99% of
the population has not tried as much as me
which is also another thing you might be
you might literally be um also
forgetting as Oh,
it's like say someone like Greavvesy
that doesn't try. Could take him 3
years, 4 years, 5 years,
3 years, 5 years. No one really knows,
you know. But when when you've been
trying and trying and trying, you should
have found someone in 3 years,
you know. Yeah. I've had chances
about three times.
Yeah. Wow. Congratulations. I've had
about three chances.
So, I've had three chances, mate.
Listen, listen. Let's talk about the
chances we had.
The 19year-old turned into a [ __ ]
Sig. So, you had Sig, then you had
maybe a one another one night stand,
then maybe who was the other one? I forgot.
uh the one from uh when I come back from
Belgium. So yeah, you might have had a
couple of chances, but you should have
had more chances than that.
You should have had way more chances
than that with the amount of effort that
you put in. And I mean that's disgusting
in itself to be honest with you. That
like you've tried more than anyone in
the world and what you've only got like
you only had like four chances.
I couldn't do with a 19year-old. She
kept wanting money.
She kept demanding money and she just
turned out to be a [ __ ] Not at first.
At first, yeah. She like this mature
person that gave good advice and just
like way more mature than me and then
she just turned to out to be entitled
and she started like calling me mate and
that and I was like listen listen I'm
not your mate personally. Yeah. And I'm
not your ATM so stop asking me for
money. He just kept it just got
annoying, bro. I'm was trying to save
and I got this [ __ ] asking me for money.
There's not going to be a next time.
That's the whole point. There's not
going to be a next time because it's got
worse because it's also got it's gotten
worse now. So, there won't be a next time.
Yeah. Now, there won't be a next time
cuz it's it's gotten worse.
So, there won't be a next time.
And you also didn't say what USA Izzy did.
So nah, bro.
So that's why I had to swerve her. She
kept asking me for money, but it was annoying. [ __ ] off.
And then she started just getting
really, really entitled. I couldn't do it anymore.
She would have been all right if she
weren't a [ __ ] She weren't even ugly at
all. At all. There was nothing wrong
with her, but they just didn't like her attitude. You understand?
And that 19year-old wasn't a it was that
was the best chance for like [ __ ]
that, but not dating. You can't date a
19year-old at [ __ ] 27, bro.
Yeah. You know, the maddest thing is you
know that Ukrainian one. Yeah. This is
how you know that they they want Mr.
Perfect. They don't exist because they
knew they know what you look like,
right? They know a bit about you. They
know your personality. They know your
personality because they they've met you
in person. And then I remember I
remember this day as well, bro.
I think it was around December. We was
talking about how uh our New Year's
resolutions, looked good, dressed good,
had money, you know, still coming in.
And I literally done nothing wrong on
that date. And then she still said how
about how she doesn't build a
connection, which at that point I didn't
care because I knew this was going to
happen. But I was like, so they
literally want Mr. Perfect then. That doesn't exist. Yeah, literally. And
yeah, and then obviously the Indian
solicitor as well. And that's what it
was [ __ ] with my head, that Italian
one, bro. But I just realized now that
she was just making excuses like the
rest of them, cuz now she's going on
about how she's moving back to Italy.
And yeah, it's just
they just go on dates to pass time,
something to do, not to actually get to
know you and and stuff. You know what I
mean? They don't they don't care about that, bro.
Look at that one that [ __ ] that
approached me and then tried saying they
didn't feel the vibe. The one I had to
limp on the I had to limp I had to limp
on that date too and I wouldn't mind.
She was 32 and she was like a 4 out of
10. And I'm like, I'm lowering my
standards. It's like you're lowering
your standards for them cuz that would
actually approach me. You're actually
lowering your standards and then they
still think that they're better than
you. That's that's that's that's the
[ __ ] up thing
is that they lower their standards. You
lower your standards for them. Yeah.
And then they [ __ ] you over. It's weird. But yeah,
but it will never change, bro. It will
literally never change, honestly.
No, she didn't say she had a boyfriend.
I assumed she had a boyfriend. I don't
know who the guy was, but I assumed it
was. I don't really like her anyways.
But yeah, it would never change. It will
never ever change in this country, bro. Ever you know. So, yeah.
But yeah, your past definitely dictates
your future when it comes to this. Cuz
if that wasn't the case, right, every
time you go out, it would be different.
But it's always the same.
Boyfriend, stuck up people.
Your past definitely dictates your future.
Definitely. Definitely with this it does.
Well, I don't know what your opinion is, Nicolo. But
cuz you will go out with people and you
can even kiss them. You can not. It's
like that Italian one. I don't even know
why go on a date with someone. Like what
was even the point? You want to hold
hands and flirt, but then you don't want
to kiss and then make up an excuse. It
just It's honestly like they're taking a
piss, isn't it? It generally feels like
they're actually just
taking a piss.
Like it is literally It is them that are the problem.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] depressing as [ __ ] eh?
Yeah, it's depressing as [ __ ]
It's so depressing. Especially
when you don't look like Timmy Aldridge.
You know what I mean? You don't look
like Timmy Aldridge. So yeah,
it will never change this country. Never.
Never. I'm sure of it, bro. I'm sure of it. Yeah.
What do you think would happen if I went
to Newcastle on Saturday, Nicolola?
What would the result be?
What do you think the little result would be?
Load of polit
What do you think they'd say?
Where the [ __ ] is Tam, man?
Where the [ __ ] is that guy with his
friend with the beard and the cap?
Yeah, that's cute. That was my dada.
And USA is he was my mama.
They got a family picture holding me in it.
Tam is my daddy.
He's a Celtic fan.
I don't know how I can find him. If I go
to Glasgow, there's a Celtic store by
the by the by the station and I can ask about Tam.
Yeah, there's like a little family photo
of us together grievy. Ah,
that bloody Glasgow accent [ __ ] goes
through my [ __ ] head.
Do you reckon he still meets up with his
little friend Nicolo?
Ah, that's so cute, isn't it? Fellow.
That's so and and and King's little
puppies as well. And King's
and King's puppy, didn't it?
Would you like to see King's puppies,
Gooy? If you had puppies. Oh [Applause]
yeah, there was a dead fox, bro. I
walked past it. It [ __ ] stunk, bro.
Have you ever smelled a dead fox?
It was left there from like three
[ __ ] days ago. It [ __ ] stunk.
But yeah, have you ever smelt a dead fox music?
It's [ __ ] rank, mate.
I still remember the smell as well, bro.
Yeah, me and this Indian guy, we had our
[ __ ] top over our [ __ ] face. Like,
is that [ __ ] coming from that fox
that's still there?
The [ __ ] council, man.
The council should [ __ ] get rid of it. Boozy.
You think it's [ __ ] funny?
And literally, why do you keep going on
different accounts as well?
You know that you're under the sub accounts.
Yeah. [ __ ] day apps have gone [ __ ] dead.
Yeah, it smells like it was rotten. It
was definitely rotten.
[ __ ] horrible, mate. One second.
I want I want Tammy back. Back.
Do you um do you lie?
He said, "I think you need to see a
psych." He said, "I think you can
benefit from seeing a psychiatrist."
In good faith, I think you should
benefit from seeing a psychiatrist.
Tammy, you and your little words, you
and your little Scottish advice.
You remember that? Yeah.
Yeah, you're that [ __ ] You've been on
so many accounts, Nicolo. I know who you are. Yeah.
Yeah. Bless you.
You like the thing with the boobs and
the nutritions, don't you, Greezy? And the nutrients.
Yeah. You say Izzy had natural boobies.
You like natural boobies.
Do you remember when people used to say that [ __ ]
You remember when people used to say
that [ __ ] bro? Go suck your mom's gun.
You remember that?
Go suck your mom's gun.
People used to say that school in it.
Do you remember that? People used to say
that in school, bro.
You remember that?
Suck your mom's gun. Yeah. Bless.
I'm just playing Franklin.
He's going to knock someone flying.
Greavves. He's going to knock someone
flying in a minute. Yeah.
Yeah, Grezy can't live without women.
Grievy can't live without women and sex.
It's It's his It's all his life. It's
his whole life.
Sad, isn't it? [Applause] Yeah.
Bless you then, Grezy.
Bless you. But I think you masturbate
sometimes over USA, don't you?
I think sometimes you do. Yeah.
Do you remember you [ __ ] Do you
remember Grezy? It was funny, is it? You [ __ ]
You remember? You [ __ ] >> Yeah.
I think sometimes you have a little
rank, don't you, Grezy? Over. Yep.
So what happened with the whole story
between Britney and thingy? Do you
remember when I used to Do you remember
when I used to ask Do you remember Bar
Quest? Easy. You The ball.
Yeah. Do you remember what I said
before? Yeah. What happened with What
happened with Brit? What happened with
Brit? Um Britney and Sean.
Yeah. Oh, that does.