Wan, Oh, what's that?
You know what he's saying, but I just
been so busy, man. So busy.
It's not even a joke.
Not even a joke, mate.
He's always in a bad place, man.
It's always in a bad place, brother.
You should know this, man.
Yeah, I've just been so busy, bro. I'm sorry.
I just banged an escort me dad. Yeah, I
was trying to get a [ __ ] in call,
right? Sorry, an out call. They were
trying to charge like 250 [ __ ] £300
and I can't justify that, man. So, I
just went up the road and just [ __ ]
one. Same thing about coming in their
mouth. So, I just [ __ ] [ __ ] the
Yeah. Yeah. It's a lot, bro. Of course
it's a lot.
Of course it's a lot, bro.
You mad or an escort? Of course it is.
Would you pay that if you were single
and you was addicted to sex? Nah, bro.
Maximum like 150, 180.
And they've all got attitude as well.
One second, bro.
Would you pay would you pay that D? Nah,
you wouldn't pay that, would you, lad?
Yeah. Would you pay it or?
You wouldn't pay it, would you, lad? One second.
One second. Why I need to do this?
You getting a new folder, Daz?
You getting the new fold?
I actually gambled today. £10 at the
pub. Well, I actually put £10 in the
slot machine today, actually.
That counts. But I don't really do it anymore, mate.
I got to be fooked.
No, I don't do that [ __ ] anymore, bro.
I'm trying to sort myself out. I need to
I've got so many things and I'm nowhere near finished.
Nope. Much to your uh disappointment, eh?
I need to order a new TV cuz I had to
sell that one cuz I couldn't bring it with me.
Just in the process of uh doing it now.
Had so much stress. They just Oh, it's
so bad. It's almost all over. So,
it's not good, bro.
Had a Guinness today cuz of it all. And
I put £10 in fish and venge. I don't
gamble anymore. Like, serious, bro.
Yep. On my main channel, got videos.
No, that's wrong. You [ __ ]
Oh, [ __ ] hell, Kieran. What a [ __ ]
day I've had.
What a day I've had, mate. I don't even
know where to where to begin, bro. So, I
had to sell the TV and [ __ ] cuz I'm
moving. So, I'm going to I'm buying I'm
buying a new TV now.
Um sad, man. Like,
moving out the house and that after all
them years, bro. I have problems. I had
a Guinness. I put £10 in Fish and Frenzy
today, actually. It's [ __ ]
I' just been stressed. But yeah, I'm
getting a TV now cuz I got my Xbox. So,
70, which should leave me with two
grand. Should be all right.
The ride was
70. Yeah, I was going to get a inco escort.
Um, an alcohol escort, but they were
asking like 250,300 and I can't justify
it. You know, I need ways to make money
now. I'm not racking it in. You know
what I'm saying? It's too much money.
So, I just went up the road and paid 70
for a [ __ ] and a [ __ ] job's a grim.
But I put £10 on the fish and frenzy cuz
I was drinking. Bro, I don't I don't
gamble, bro. Really?
Let me just make sure I put that. Bro,
the police in this country are [ __ ]
You're Brazilian, bro. The police in
Hey, Kieran. You never guess what? Yeah,
I police station today. They want to
tell you the story.
I need to make sure I'm I'm writing this
TV thing right, bro, before they deliver
it to the [ __ ] wrong address.
This is a main channel that no one knows about, bro.
Yeah. Do you know what happened? I went
to the police station today, Kieran, cuz
I had to follow up this report. Yeah.
The police told me to go to the police
station cuz basically um
it's so weird being in this house now
with no one in it. of me. But um I had
to go police station cuz they told me
that I need to go to the police station.
And they made up every single excuse not
to deal with it again as usual cuz
they've got their favorites in this country.
Then the other police officer said, "Oh,
are you Peter?"
Said, "Yeah." I said, "Oh, we haven't
met before, but I need to invite you in
for a voluntary interview because you
said something to some woman on
Instagram about 7 months ago." I said,
"Hold on. You've just contradicted
everything that your colleague has just said.
It's just a long story. I'm very
stressed, bro. I've had a long day. I
need to buy this TV again. So,
so yeah, it's a long day, bro. So, I
went and bang this school cuz there was
no way I'm spending 250 on an escort. £7
is nothing, bro. That's all right, is
it? But they pay [ __ ] 250.
So, yeah. Kieran, the thing is you got
to understand in this country, right,
the police have their favorites, I had
something going on in my house today in
madness. Yeah. Where somebody could have
seriously got hurt. I'm not I'm not even
talking about it. The police wouldn't
come out, bro. Couldn't get through to 999.
Couldn't get through to [ __ ] bro. They
would not come out. They've got their
favorites, bro. The sooner you
understand that, the better.
You know, they've got their favorites.
They favor nons and women. That's what
they favor. Like the sooner you get that
in your head, the better, bro. I've got
it in my head. Cuz you got one police
officer saying they can't do anything
because it's social media and I need to
report it to this and I need to report
it to that. But then the next thing they
they're inviting me for a voluntary
interview over the same thing. So make
it make sense.
No, it's just a long story, bro. It just
could have it could have just went into
a madness, bro. And someone also stole
my after shave as well.
Yeah, someone stole my after shave, but
they had no smell to it and was just
pointless stealing it to be honest. Stupid.
And I asked them, no one would admit it.
So, [ __ ] them, bro. Just a madness.
So, yeah. Anyways,
the police have made money anyways cuz I
sold like most of the [ __ ] But the
thing is they they've got their
favorites. The police have got their [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. One of them wouldn't open the
door. He thought I was going to [ __ ] him up.
He's like, "Oh, like, yeah, you're
screw. You're going to hurt me. You're
going to hurt me." So, I'm not going to
hurt you, bro. Just [ __ ] open the
door, bro. The [ __ ] It was a madness.
No, it was a madness, bro. It went funny
today, bro. And then you go and steal my
[ __ ] off this [ __ ] What's the
[ __ ] point of that?
It's a madness, bro. What is the point?
The after shave don't even smell
anymore, bro. It's just stupid, bro.
Whoever done it, I don't know who done it.
It's silly. Really?
Could just buy a new one that actually
smells. So, it's like
And they say that Muslim people never steal. Huh?
You know what? Back when we was in
school, Yeah. we believe a white person
would steal. We'd believe we'd believe a
black person would steal. But somehow
Muslim would Muslims will claim that
they never steal.
It was a madness, bro. It was just a
[ __ ] complete and madness, bro. And
it still hasn't ended.
Almost almost there.
But yeah, the police have got their favorites anyways.
They got their favorites for real.
But no one would admit who stole it. So
I was thinking of just getting a new one
tomorrow. 200 one. Yeah. Like a 200
pound one. And just shoving it in their
face and saying come and take the piss.
Now look, this is a new one. Yeah. This
is a new one, bro. Like she smells.
Yeah. Terry, you've got a [ __ ] life.
Another thing is stop Another thing is
Yeah. Stop begging to LT, you little
[ __ ] with no kids about how you Oh,
you're not about that life. You're not
about that life, bro. You know what? I'm
going to come there tomorrow. I'm going
to I was waiting for you to come on my
live stream yet. I'm going to wait for
you to come to I'm going to go there
tomorrow and I'm going to embarrass you
again. Watch. I'm coming tomorrow. I was
waiting for you, bro. I was waiting for
you. Enough said. I'm coming for you
tomorrow. You're telling people about
how you're not the one, bro. You would
get slapped the [ __ ] up. You're not
about that life, bro. Stop it. You were
the one congratulating grasses. Yeah,
you were the one congratulating gr
congratulating grasses and you're
claiming that you're you're you're
claiming that you're [ __ ] what is it?
That you're you're on uh what was it? Probation, bro.
No, I had to sell it cuz I'm moving.
I've just bought another one because I'm moving house.
So, I sold loads of [ __ ] I didn't need.
Made some money. So
yeah, cuz I'm cuz I'm moving.
Be a skin. Oh, talking about yourself,
bro. Talking about myself on that on
this channel, matey. Yeah, I'm just
buying myself a£500 TV and a £500 phone.
I'm so scared, bro. Yeah. So, bro, like,
if you really want to put it to the
test, lad. Well, it does make sense
because I'm moving house, you [ __ ]
idiot. So, yeah, it does make sense.
Anyways, I'm Let me order this [ __ ] TV. [ __ ]
My stress doesn't stop here, mate.
Doesn't matter how much I sold it for. I
got got a good price for it, but I'm
moving and I don't want the hassle of
taking it down and risking it getting
damaged. So, yeah, I'm [ __ ] bro. Basically.
But yeah, the aftershave thing is stupid
to be honest.
Yeah, cuz it's like they don't even
smell anymore. Like, why would you even
steal it? It's so stupid.
It's so mad I'm selling everything I
own. Yeah. Okay, bro. You keep telling
yourself that. But bro, you know you're
not about that life. So why do you come
on here doing this [ __ ]
So anyways, we're not talking about it
anymore. So right, I'm ordering this new
TV. Anyways, it's actually gone down in
price as well, actually. It's when I
last bought it. So anyways, moving on.
So yeah, basically they've got their favorites. Um,
Kieran, they've got their favorites. I
don't know who [ __ ] stole it. I
pulled every single one up about it and
they would not tell me who done it. So,
but it's stupid because I'll just buy
200 power, but it's not a problem. It's
stupid. It's old. It's an old one as
well. So, what I'm basically saying is
don't believe Muslims don't steal
because they do steal. Did you? And I
was like, "Bro, I know where my stuff
was." Yeah, I know where my stuff was. I
wasn't even in the room, but it's just
stupid, bro. That's [ __ ] [ __ ] Really?
Stupid. Really? It's just stupidness.
I'm just going to buy another one. It's
just stupid, you know? What even the
point of doing that, bro? It's just so dumb.
It doesn't even smell anymore, so they
stop smelling after a while.
Yeah, I don't really come on here
anymore. I'm just bored sat here [ __ ] doing nothing.
Right. Anyways, let me let me try and
order this. Tell you a second.
But yeah, Kieran, bro. So they were
basically telling me how they can't do
anything because of social media. But
then the next thing
they're up your ass over something about
7 months ago.
Make it make sense. Corrupt police
officers and the fact that they wouldn't
come out today. Someone could have died,
bro. You don't know, bro. You don't know
how things happen here. Like somebody
could have died. They're [ __ ] What is
the point of them even having a [ __ ]
station, bro? I don't understand.
But yeah, Terry, don't talk about people
not being a one, bro. When you're not
about that life, you're not about that
life. And you will never be about that
life, you sad [ __ ]
Uh, congrating up grasses. That's how
you know someone ain't about that life, bro.
Yeah. Okay. It doesn't make no sense.
I'm not going to argue with you, bro.
Yeah. Okay. It doesn't make any sense,
bro. Good for you. If it doesn't make
any sense, dude, then stop talking about
it, bro. It
Yeah, it doesn't make any sense.
Yeah, about that, bro. About that.
Pulled any women? Well, considering um
I've not had time to go out and I've
told you specifically I'm done in this
country and it's the same in this
country. No. Do you think I've I've got
time to be going out?
Do you think I've got time to be going
out, bro? I' I've got stress. I don't
know where I'm [ __ ] going. Do you
understand? And you're And you're asking
me if I've pulled any women. You're mad, bro. And
you've been pulling people. So, what
does that make you? Uh that makes me
doing the same thing that you people
have been doing for years, which is what
the police told me to do. That's that's
doing what you people keep doing to
protect myself because you are grasses.
That's playing you at your own game.
That's what that's called. And it's
called like there's no other way to get
you. You will never meet anyone. You
grassing other people. So no, it doesn't
make you a grass. It's called doing the
only thing you can do. what you people keep doing.
Yeah, I'm not rich at all, bro. I wish I was rich.
I still got to get the Samsung Galaxy
Fold somehow. I'm not rich, mate. I'm
not rich at all, bro.
Yeah, it's called being a grass. Okay,
bro. Yeah. Anyways, I need to ban this
account, bro. [ __ ] weirdo. But yeah,
Kieran, legend, legend.
Yeah, I've done my balls in. Yeah,
that's a bit hard considering I don't
even gamble anymore.
No, the fold's about 16,700.
Um, well, considering I don't gamble
anymore. I mean, that's a bit hard.
Another thing that you don't listen to.
Well, I gamble. Well, to be fair, I
gambled £7 today at the pub when I had a
Guinness. Guilty. Bro, I don't gamble
anymore. I could never do my balls in.
Right. I'm trying to order this [ __ ] telly. Yeah.
All right, Kieran, you still there, man?
What the [ __ ]
Yep. Your skin. Your skin. Hey, bro. The
thing is, Kieran, another thing, you
know, when you said that it's the same
old. It's the same old. It is. It is the
same old skin people.
Yeah. But guess what? I've got more
savings than you and I've got more money
than you'd ever have, Terry. Yeah.
Yeah. But I can make money. That's the
thing. I've got a brain. I can make
money. I've got savings, [ __ ] Have
you ever heard of what that is? Anyways,
so yeah, I can't trust my 250 [ __ ]
pound, bro. Anyways, let me buy this TV.
You keep distracting me. I've got to do
the whole thing again now.
Right. Let me deliver it.
What's the date today? Okay. 2:00 p.m.
Terry, your skin. You don't have no
money, bro. You look at your trainers.
Yeah. You want to start talking to
people about money? You want to start
talking about [ __ ] this, that, and
the other when you're the one. Look at
look at your trainers, bro. You're
talking about money, but look at your trainers.
Right. Are you going to let me 200 p.m.
One second. I need to do this properly, bro.
And you're talking about money. Make it make sense.
It's not looking right, bro.
But hey, anyways, the people you keep
going on about money is is because you
people don't have no money. Do you not
understand, Kieran? Like, have you not
figured what this [ __ ] out is now about
these people coming on here talking
about money every day? It's because they
don't have no money. They're all skint.
That's why they're sat on YouTube every
day. You have you not put the like
patterns together, bro? Like, how many
years have you been on here? They all
come on here talking about money because
they ain't got none. That's why they're
sat on YouTube every day and they
project their own life onto other
people. Do you understand? They
literally just talk about themselves.
That's why it's just pointless what what
you said, bro. Cuz they've got all this
money, but they're sat on YouTube every
day and still no one has answered why
that happens because they ain't got no,
bro. These people on £300 a month. They
don't even get a grand,00200.
They literally don't get anything.
They're literally [ __ ] skimped.
That's why they're on here every day. I
I've got so much stress, bro. Finally,
I'll be able to settle down soon. But
yeah, let me buy that TV again. [ __ ]
hell. I'm buying the same [ __ ] TV again.
No, he's on 800. He's already said what he's on.
Yeah. You think I'm rich, mate? I wish I
was [ __ ] rich.
That was a nice escort.
But you, Terry, you don't even get a
grand a month. You get about £300 a
month. Have you seen your trainers?
Terry, have you seen your trainers? If
you got £1,000 a month, bro, you would
you would be wearing them trainers.
Like, bro, we all know that you're a
keyboard warrior. I'm told you I'm going
to come tomorrow and we'll see what
you're all about. Simple, bro. Yep.
Broke is a joke. You're talking about
yourself again, bro. If you got a grand
a month, you'd actually be able to buy
some decent trainers.
Look at what you wear. You're a [ __ ]
You're talking about a grand a month,
but you're a [ __ ]
Got more money than you would ever have. Believe that.
You don't put your your your life on
social media anyways. I'm banning these
[ __ ] I want to actually have a
normal chat, bro. And they're just
ruining it. Ruining it. Yeah. I was
selling my [ __ ] on Facebook because I'm
moving. That's what people do when they
move house. They sell washing machines
and used fridges. Yes, that's what
happens when people move out of their house, [ __ ]
[ __ ] off, you [ __ ] virgin. Go get
laid. Anyways, are you going to come out
tomorrow, [ __ ] boy? When I go to your
area, Terry, are you going to come out
tomorrow, [ __ ] boy? About I'm not the
one. Are you going to come out tomorrow,
[ __ ] boy? Cuz we had we had it today
where somebody was [ __ ] scared to
open the door. Terry, are you going to
come out tomorrow? so I can rag you
around. Yeah, I'm going to come
tomorrow. I need to stay in this yard.
I'm going to go live 2 p.m.
Yeah, you little [ __ ] boy about how
[ __ ] emailing people saying, "Oh, I'm
not the one. I'm not the one. I'm not
the one. I'm not the one. I'm not the
one. I'm not the one." Well, you're a
[ __ ] [ __ ] buff. Yeah, you know you
didn't come out last time because you
would have got [ __ ] up. Listen, bro.
Listen. Remember when when I went to
your air and you didn't come out? You
little [ __ ] idiot, bro. [ __ ] off,
man. You're not about that life, you
little [ __ ] Shut the [ __ ] up. You get
[ __ ] up if you come out tomorrow. Just
like the last time. And anyways, and
anyways, [ __ ] That's what people
do when they move house. They sell
things. Yeah, that's that's literally
what they do. What do I have, Fruit
King? more money than you, better looks
than you, hair unlike you, live in a
better place than you. I don't sound
like a [ __ ] click like you.
Everything that you don't have, bro.
What do you have, bro? So on YouTube.
Who sells things when they move house?
Literally almost everyone. You [ __ ]
[ __ ] Anyways, enough about my life.
I'll see you tomorrow at 2 p.m. You
wanted to know the [ __ ] time. That's
going to be the time, [ __ ] You
little [ __ ] [ __ ] keyboard warrior,
bro. Trying to tell LT about how you
know this person and how you know that
person. Like, [ __ ] bro. You don't know no one.
One second, bro.
All right. I'm still haven't got this TV
yet cuz of you [ __ ] No,
but yeah, Kieran, have you reported it?
I I Anyways, I'm not talking about my
life, bro. I'll see you tomorrow.
I will see you tomorrow.
See you tomorrow, bro.
Yeah, [ __ ] boy. I'm not the one.
Yeah, he's a [ __ ] bro.
Let's stop giving him attention.
But yeah, they've got their favorites,
basically. Yeah. So,
I wish I was rich, bro. I wish I was rich.
I ain't rich, bro.
I ain't that guy.
Yeah. Are you going to pretend you're on probation again?
Card numbers invalid. Well, that's impossible.
Are you going to pretend you're [ __ ]
We got to see King tomorrow as well.
Call numbers invalid. That's literally impossible, bro.
card number. One second, please.
This is not possible, bro.
But anyways, bye-bye now, you little sado. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Bye-bye, [ __ ] I don't let spastics
on my chat.
One second, bro. I'm trying to do this [ __ ] here.
Yeah, we need to stop letting spastics
on on the channel as well.
Yeah, they're just ruining the chat.
these little self-reflectors.
So anyways, Kieran, why you still gambling, bro?
No, this isn't right, bro.
Okay, I think I typed that bit wrong. Hopefully,
you got that gambling [ __ ] Zippy.
There we go, lad.
If it lets me do it, I don't think it will. No,
I need to verify, I think. No.
No, I need to um verify my thing cuz Oh,
for [ __ ] sake. What a life, man. What
a [ __ ] life.
I'll just order it tomorrow, bro.
Yeah, cuz I got some online banking thing.
Yeah, I You wouldn't like my life at a minute, bro.
You wouldn't like my life at a [ __ ]
minute, would you? K.
You wouldn't like my life, mate.
I don't own a bed. I mean, I've got a
500 pound bed, but okay. Anyways, we're
banning these little [ __ ] 40year-olds.
[ __ ] We're not entertaining these
little self projectors.
How much do you have all together now, Kieran? [ __ ]
That's the problem, bro. But no, I sold
a washing machine and fridge because I
couldn't take it with me, Kieran. And
everywhere everywhere you go, it's going
to have it. So why am I taking all that
[ __ ] with me?
Probably just go to my back to my mom's
anyways for a little bit, to be honest.
So, why would I take everything with me?
Only thing I take with me is my Xbox
and [ __ ] I don't need anything else.
Yeah, I don't think I'll ever go back to
the gambling, bro.
I need to find ways to make money now, bro. [ __ ]
Like, properly make ways to make money
now, bro. I still got some money coming,
but nah. [ __ ] bro.
I was always PlayStation, but I
switched. So, I'm going to get this TV tomorrow.
Yeah, I see that, too. Bye-bye.
So, yeah, bro. Now, Daz,
I just need a break, bro. Like, Kieran,
if I told told you that how much stress
that I've been under the past [ __ ]
It's actually giving me anxiety, but I
don't get anxiety, bro.
You know, I just don't get it. You know
what I mean? But by the TV, chill out
for a bit, try and figure something out.
This is hard life, bro.
I'm not planning to work for a couple of
months anyways. So, yeah.
But I'm done with that gambling [ __ ] bro.
Cuz the thing is, if I wanted to get the
TV, I would have had to
get the TV off the wall, pay for a cab,
risk the TV getting damaged. there's no
point. And I also made money on other
things like the phone and [ __ ] Sold the
phone I didn't need didn't want. So yeah, bro.
Nah, never, bro.
Yeah, even that I wish I could have done
with that grand now, matey.
I could have done with that [ __ ] forground now.
[ __ ] could have done with it, mate.
Could have done with it.
Oh, we used to have like [ __ ] 6K,
bro. [ __ ] Those are the good days,
Kieran. But [ __ ] still got money.
Like what people don't seem to
understand, but it's just
mad that you went out for 3 years and I
didn't meet anyone in them three years. mad.
But we got a football next month, so
make money on that in it. I'll be
gambling on the football. But
yeah, I did. Anyways, bye-bye.
Why these people saying you've bought
this, you've bought that, you've not
bought that? Like, bro, I got an Xbox,
I've got a TV, I got designer clothes,
I've got a phone, I got a bed, I got a fan.
like you know what I mean K these people
are just self-reflectors
but I need to go back and do after sh
but I won't be going out for a month
anyways I got things to deal with so yeah
it ain't Good, bro.
It ain't good, man.
We're actually [ __ ] bro. Yeah. Oh,
[ __ ] We're actually [ __ ] bro. Oh, bro.
Talking about yourself.
Stop talking about yourself, bro. You're
boring the whole chat talking about yourself. Yeah.
How do you think you can make extra
money nowadays, Kieran?
You can't, bro.
There There is no way, Mr. Magua.
You [ __ ] sc bro.
Do you think that's weird having three
years I didn't meet anyone? Ken.
Yeah. It's weird, isn't it?
Yeah. It's weird, bro.
I can't go out at the minute. I've got
so much stress. Like, you you wouldn't
even be able to go out and drink.
You understand what I mean, Kieran?
Where you at, bro?
[ __ ] my bro. Imagine
still being a virgin at 31.
Imagine still being a skint virgin at
31. That's even worse. Being a skinned virgin.
Being a skint virgin at 31 is even worse. Bye-bye now.
[ __ ] One time.
That's even worse.
Being a skinned virgin at 31, I think
that's even worse to be fair.
Mentally obsessed virgin at 31 is
definitely worse. People live with their
mom at [ __ ] 40, bro. 2 3
9 + one. I'm trying to calculate money here.
Oh yeah, I got money up my mom's as well.
I'm not your [ __ ] mate. Get that
through your skull, buddy.
I'm not your [ __ ] mate. Dude,
that's what I tell you ain't it.
I want your [ __ ] mate.
You had any?
Oh, you're [ __ ] mate.
Don't even know you from Adam.
Oh, your [ __ ] mate, mate. Yeah, mom.
Talking about yourself again. Bye-bye.
Talking about yourself.
Have you noticed, Kieran? They've got
nothing better to do in here but talk about themselves.
It's [ __ ] sad, isn't it, bro?
She's a 10 out of 10. Ah, she's not a 10
out of 10. Stop being a s.
[ __ ] s. Simps everywhere.
Stop being a s, man.
Stop being a s, brother.
She's like a six. Anyways, I'm not
talking about them. I need to change
that picture anyways.
But yeah, Kieran, it's going to be sort
of hard now. cuz
I won't have time to go out now. I've
got so much stress financially. I don't
want to waste the money even though I've
got the money.
Yeah. Anyways, bye-bye. So many self
projectors today. What the [ __ ] I
thought I banned them all. These all self-reflectors.
So, yeah. And I don't want to waste the
money financially on it.
You know what I mean, bro?
Yeah, it's what you people do every day.
Sat on YouTube skin talking about yourselves.
What do you mean? Welcome to your world, Karen.
Why? Why you say that, bro?
We'll go for a piss up. Wait, when I'm
settled, but soon as I'm settled, we'll
do it. Well, I mean, I'll do it.
I can't be asked with dating. I don't
have the time. Soon, I won't be able I
won't have the money to waste. Do you understand? So,
no, I can't be asked with dating.
No, I can't
cuz it's just the same in this country.
It's the same old boring, bro.
But yeah, it's going to be the money
side of things soon now, Grezy.
And then uh Kieran
cuz it's quite expensive to go out now
is it? So ouch
be [ __ ] soon in it. Nah.
Bye-bye. Go self-reflect on another channel.
Remember the last time you went out on a
night out? Uh [ __ ]
Kieran, how comes
Muslim people so know so many people,
do you think? It's weird, isn't it?
Have you noticed that, Karen? Yeah.
Why don't you try dating Ken? You'll like it.
You like dating, bro.
Wait, I need to come off this [ __ ] for a
bit. I need to sort some things out, bro.
Do you remember that USA is he came? Oh,
[ __ ] I called her the other day. Yeah,
she's like, "Hello,
I'm not getting into it, bro.
Getting into it."
Yeah. She's like, "Hello."
You always had your eye on her eye,
didn't you, Karen?
You always had your eye on her, didn't you, lad?
Didn't you, Laddy?
You always had your eye on a little
ming, didn't you, mate?
Be honest about that, Kieran.
Yeah, you always had your eye on a little mini, didn't you? [ __ ]
need to go gym some [ __ ]
does just fine on a grand a month, don't you?
But yeah, I won't be on here for a while
after today, bro. I got some things to sort out.
It's the same spastics every day, ain't it?
Same spastics every day, bro. Okay, bro.
Oh, my phone's almost had it as well. Almost. Almost.
Just going to start leaving the phone like that.
No, I spoke to him. He says he just
doesn't come on here anymore.
Oh, [ __ ] me. I'm fat.
>> [ __ ] virgin.
Stupid virgin. See, and and and and the
thing is Kieran. Yeah. You know, with
these people, bro, why do you hear everything?
They never ever stop. This is another
reason why you need to to come off of
this site like even like you do 2
months, 3 months, four months is they
never ever ever ever ever stop.
Don't know if you noticed that.
They never stop their obsession, their
jealousy, their self projecting. Like
they literally never stop.
Like word, bro. They never stop. Never
ever ever ever ever ever.
You understand, bro?
You'll be same people to when you and I are dead.
Same obsessed, jealous, self-projecting
people, bro. You see it every day.
No, you people on YouTube have never
ruined my life. That's the difference.
Like you've you people on YouTube have
never ruined my life. You've tried so
hard, but it's never worked. You've
tried hard, but you never It's never
worked. You ain't that my kids took off
me. You ain't got my money stopped.
You ain't stopped my sub money. Nothing.
You tried. You did try like loads of
times and I give you that. But the
problem with with this is that there's
only so much you can do behind the
keyboard. This is what I used to say, Dad. Like
when you're behind the keyboard and
you're a coward, there's only so much
you you can do. Anyways, bro,
these people will never ever stop, bro.
I'm coming off of YouTube again. They
will never ever stop. Seriously, bro.
Do you still Do you still see that
Ronald Pump, Kieran?
Do you still see that Ronald Pump?
He told me before, you're better looking
than them, you got more money than them,
and it kills them. Get off of YouTube
and live your life. Bro, I might have to
start listening to He's right though. He
is right. Better looking, more money.
Come to think of it, bro. These people
are on like 300 pound a month. They're
skinned to the bones of their ass. And
it's why they're on here every day. Look
at the time me and you are talking,
Kieran. It's almost 1:00 in the morning.
We don't sit all day on YouTube waiting for content.
Especially if you had all that money,
bro. Think of it. We got all this money,
bro. Think about it. Yeah. You have all
that money. Yeah.
And they're on YouTube, bro. Like,
they're not they're
What is this 6%, bro? Yeah,
that's that's where it comes from, man.
It comes from It comes to jealousy with
these people, these mongos. That's why
Monty don't come here no more, bro. Why would he?
You know what I'm saying? about that
[ __ ] Why would he, bro?
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, I'll let you in, bro. Join again. Yeah. >> Hi.
>> So, I'm not going to porn bomb you.
Relax. I'm not [ __ ]
>> Hi, Jimmy. Yeah, be honest.
>> How do you live off £800 a month?
>> I'm not on 800 pound a month PJ. I'm on
nearly four grand a month. Yeah,
>> I've got a very successful little eBay
business which I'm not telling you as okay.
>> Hello. Can you hear me?
>> Yeah, I'm just going to kick it. I'm
just going to kick this bastic, bro.
Listen, Ken, bro. Yeah, you need to get
off this [ __ ] brother.
>> Listen, mate. I got off it for 6 months.
I just come on here like every night
just to check on it.
>> They're never going to stop, bro.
They're never ever going to stop. You do realize that?
Yeah, I know. It's the same [ __ ] that I
had like when it was about 6 months ago
or so with Ellie.
>> What did you think of the whole What did
you think of the whole police thing? I
told you they're bro. I'm telling you.
Yeah. They got their favorites, bro. I'm
telling you. There's something up right there.
>> What do you mean?
>> Like when I went today, Yeah. I went to
report the thing I sent you and they
say, "Oh, we can't do anything cuz it's
social media. Report to YouTube." But
then when when I get reported, they're
up your ass. You see what I'm saying? If
you've sent me anything, I haven't it
the email that I have with you is about
2 years old. I haven't been on any email
like since then.
>> Never mind. I never mind.
>> It doesn't matter. Anyway, I know what you mean. >> Huh?
>> Yeah, because I tried to log into that
[ __ ] account and then it tried to say
that um uh there suspicious activity or
whatever. It weren't [ __ ] me. Then I
got paranoid. So, I just [ __ ] pitched
the account. You know,
>> these people are weird. They're obsessed with it.
>> Yeah, I know. I listen, mate. I always
watch in the background, but I've
stopped commenting. I mean, I've
commented the last couple of weeks cuz
I've got [ __ ] all else to do cuz it's
hot. I want to stay at home because of
my air conditioning.
>> I can't go out. It's [ __ ]
And listen, if you don't live in London,
you don't realize how hot it is here.
it. So, I'm just at home in the [ __ ]
air conditioning and I've just been
watching you and I've been watching Lord
Jay. I know you don't get on with him, but
>> Have you been out drinking?
>> Yeah. Well, I live right next to a pub
in it, so I'll go there in it.
>> I won't have the time or the money to it soon, mate.
>> Yeah. What's going What's going on with
the um the job? I guess you've lost that
then, is it?
>> Nah, this is a long story, bro. Don't be
asking. It's long, man.
>> I bet that was awkward, though. You told
me about the [ __ ] conversation you
had with the tenants.
>> It was just It was bad, bro.
>> Yeah, I would have been the same as
well. I wouldn't even know how to I
would have probably just left and just
let them figure it out to themselves.
>> No, it's it would have been worse.
Yeah, I know that sounds bad, but I
would have just left them. I would have
just left them and let them figure it
out themselves. Wouldn't you b up? [Music]
>> They don't understand. Do they not
understand that it's basically just
[ __ ] everyone's life up? Do they realize that?
>> What is it? Is it it it's that new
[ __ ] I I keep seeing that news thing
about the new section something where
they're where you know like if you're
renters they're basically kicking you out basically
>> you know.
>> Yeah. But you don't understand that
they've basically ruined people's life
doing this and it
>> Yeah, I know. But I mean that's [ __ ] all
you can do about it.
>> Think about it, bro. Yeah. They had to
like some of them didn't even find a new
place. They've got to find another
landlord. I've lost money. I' I've got
to find somewhere else to live. Like,
it's it's bad, bro. It's like It's so
bad. It's worse than you can imagine,
bro. And and obviously you come from
>> Yeah. The thing is, listen, look for
another place. You can listen, go to
news agents or corner shops. You'll see
little signs up on the window. If you
can't find it that way, go back to your
[ __ ] mom's in the meantime. and then
>> build it up and then piss off again. Cuz
obviously now you've now you know
freedom. You obviously you're not going
to want to go back to your mom's in it.
>> No, I still it's still freedom. I just
have my own room. No, it's all right,
bro. It's not
like the money side of it as well.
>> Yeah, I know. But I just I I just know
what it's like with you. like you you're
going to go back there and then I don't
know how these [ __ ] people find out
where you are but they always find out
where you are and then >> life.
>> Yeah, but how do they know PJ? This is
what I always said to you before. How do
they [ __ ] know?
>> You tell me how you tell me how they know, bro.
>> I don't [ __ ] know. I don't know, bro.
Obviously. What? What do you think? I'm
giving them my address.
>> Obviously not.
>> No, but I think maybe you're I think
maybe you're being friends with people.
>> We're not really friends.
>> No, bro. I don't tell anyone my address,
bro. I never have. Not even women I've
met. Never, bro. No one knew where my
mom lived. [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Listen, mate. You listen. Me and
you are on a level, so it doesn't really
>> Yeah. I'm being real with you. I'm being
real with you. Okay. Okay. Listen, bro.
Who do you think found the old address?
Who Who you remember who found the old address?
>> I wasn't on here at the time. I wasn't
on here at the time. You told me a G or
the G or whatever.
>> Yeah, it was. It was It was
>> Yeah, but how did he know?
>> I don't Well, obviously I didn't tell
him, did I?
>> Yeah, I know. But then how did But how
does he know? Do you know what I mean?
>> Yeah. I don't because probably he found
my name on Facebook and then found it that way. >> Maybe.
>> How did they How did they find these
other people that that that got do that
got docked? How did they find them?
>> I don't know. I know when I know like
about a year ago when I was off my
[ __ ] head and I was arguing with that
LT on here. I know I have [ __ ] docks
myself, but I didn't give my address,
but I gave the >> Yeah,
>> the the location kind of if that makes sense.
>> And that Terry is a complete and utter
[ __ ] house, bro.
>> He ain't going to come here. He's a He's
a [ __ ] idiot. He told me to go to
South. I'm not going to South. [ __ ] him.
>> He was He was emailing [ __ ] LT. Oh,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no. And all
that, bro. But he's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
bro. He ain't about it.
>> Yeah. Well, I hope LT [ __ ] turns on
him and [ __ ]
>> No. Yeah, he did. He already has. He
already He already has.
>> Oh, you see that that tells you how long
I haven't been watching you. I I I I
sometimes check in, but I don't hang
around if that makes sense. >> Yeah.
>> You know, when you when you click on
someone and then you just you'll be
there for a couple of minutes, you [ __ ]
this, I'm going.
>> Yeah. You know, same with like Lord Jay.
I mean, I get on with Lord Jay. I've
never fallen out with him, but I
sometimes click on it. I think this is
the same old [ __ ] [ __ ] off. You know,
>> it's always the same old [ __ ] bro. Hey,
have you noticed I've not been on before
for like weeks and [ __ ]
>> Yeah, I know. I noticed that, but I
can't be bothered. It's just the same
old projector, same old repeating, same old people.
>> I bet you I bet you were heartbroken,
weren't you? You know, like that day
when you went back onto Lord James and
you were arguing, I bet I bet you
thought Art was like, "Why the [ __ ] did
I do that? I could have just ignored them all."
>> Yeah. Yeah. You were just giving them
what they what they wanted.
>> Same with me. It's the same with me.
Like sometimes when I come on yours, not
you. I mean, it's just like the way you
talk to me, then they all [ __ ] come
in on me. It's like, "Fuck off, mate."
>> I just think it's mad how they never stop.
>> You're not mad.
>> It's the same with me. Like if that time
I went in on Belly and [ __ ] Fat Dan,
if someone came to you the week after
said, "Oh, he did this, he did that."
I'm guessing you would have said, "Well,
it was [ __ ] all to do with me." But >> yeah,
>> for some reason, whenever I I go into
anyone else's chat in the past, it was
always like PJ, PJ, PJ, I don't. Yeah.
>> Do you know what I mean? I don't give a [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> This person's skin, that person's skin.
We hear it every day, bro. We hear you
every [ __ ] day.
>> Yeah. See, and the thing and the thing
with me, PJ, is I don't give a [ __ ]
about money. Some I've always told you,
PJ, and you know this. I've always told
you there's weeks when I'm skin and
there's weeks when it's [ __ ] coming
out of my ass, you know, like money. I
>> I I haven't been skinned for [ __ ]
years, but I probably will be now at some point. Yeah.
If you're a gambler like me at some
point, it it's just up and down. That's
why I always say money comes and goes.
Same with [ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ]
Oh, that's sexist. That's sexist. I
don't give a [ __ ] Money and women are
the same [ __ ] thing, PJ. They come and go.
>> Well, I don't even gamble anymore.
Know you don't believe that, but Yeah.
>> Good on you. Yeah, I I do believe you
because at the end of the day, you just
get to the [ __ ] point where and I'm
[ __ ] near that myself and I'm just
thinking, you know what?
>> The whole like mood swings and the same
conversation and it was just it's just
doing you no good, mate. That's why I
just packed it in.
>> Yeah. I mean,
it's still uh you get good uh wins.
Yeah, I still listen another thing I
heard you say like like about the I
don't know where you're going with it
like a,000. Yeah, I it's actually 1,000
100. Listen, I've always been honest.
I'm on benefits. I don't give a [ __ ]
But I also get other money. Do you know
what I'm saying? >> Yeah.
>> Like my
like where I live, my dad brought that
house for me and my mom, but my mom's
still alive. So obviously she's still
here, but I get a thou uh on benefits I
get about 1.1k and then >> yeah,
>> he said me about400.
So that's about one.5K
a month I get. So yeah, listen, I've
always been honest. I don't give a [ __ ]
And then other you know what I mean? So
listen and another thing PJ if anyone
ever comes on it calling you skin and
that just know they're skint themselves
>> they talk about themselves no I know
here bored it's the same [ __ ] I used to
do when I first came on here and I got
brain but started making troll accounts
I think you knew all about that but when
I started making troll accounts
>> people started getting brain saying
skins listen mate they're all [ __ ]
skin themselves [ __ ] them
>> on here every day Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? So I never lie about it.
>> Yeah. I was saying, yeah, like they all
and another thing is Yeah. They're
saying, "Oh, why did you sell things?"
Because I was moving house, you idiot.
That's what you do when you move house,
bro. When you move into
>> I saw I saw that, bro. You know what I mean?
>> What? So, I'm guessing the fact that you
sold all that, are you going back to
your mom's before you find out where
you're going or what?
>> Yeah. So, I got my Xbox. I'm going to
get a new TV. I've got a bed. I've got a
phone. There's a washing machine. Why
Why would I bring all that stuff with
me, bro? Do you get me?
>> Yeah. Just save it and then
You know what I say is I always say that
to people. Just if if you want to get if
you want to move on and you're on
benefits like the way I am, just [ __ ]
live cheap, eat cheap, and [ __ ] save
and then just move on. Is it? That's
what Yeah, that's what I'll be doing now, mate.
>> Yeah, but it's [ __ ] hard though in
the summer months though, is it? It's hot.
>> Yeah, it is.
Why you think you
>> You think you seem to remember in the summer it
>> Well, no. It's not that. It's just like
you just got like with me like cuz I
live right near a pub. So just cuz I
know people who go in there, it's just
so tempting to go in there and just like
to have a chat with them, you know.
>> Today I had to get this today.
>> I did the Cronin side. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Anyway, O can I ask you a
question? Like um I want someone
question if if you don't want to if if
it's too awkward, don't. What happened
when you know like when you've got Nick?
Did they ever mention me or like or my [ __ ]
>> YouTube name or what? >> No. >> Never.
>> No. Oh, that's all right then. Cuz I
know that Sean said, "Oh, yeah. I'm
going to the police about you. They know
all about you." It's just like I never
heard anything about it.
>> You just need to ignore it, bro. They're
never going to stop. >> Yeah.
I don't know if you're sub to his
channel, but he put up a [ __ ] video
of his him with his nan. Like, are you
[ __ ] mad putting that up?
>> I don't watch that version, man.
>> Yeah. Well, she had sunglasses on. I
think he thought he was being [ __ ]
clever, but it wouldn't be that hard to [ __ ]
stalk his Facebook, pretend to be
someone, and [ __ ] get on his Facebook
and [ __ ] find it. Find who that was.
I remember that whole um USA Izzy thing.
You found it funny, isn't it?
>> Yeah, I found it funny, but I don't know whe
>> I'll be honest with you, PJ. It's a bit
[ __ ] in the past. I know I've I
messed up with Izzy and all that lot
like the original Izzy when I [ __ ]
went messaging her and [ __ ] but I don't
think I do that with the American Izzy
cuz I just think when I looked at her, I
thought this is more [ __ ] trouble
than it's worth. I just [ __ ]
>> Well, you started messaging Izzy. Yeah.
>> No. Well, no, not the the American Izzy,
but I did it with the original. You knew
that anyway? Like about that? No, I
didn't know that. What the [ __ ]
>> Yeah, this was before we all before me
and you made up and [ __ ] And but she
didn't [ __ ] She did. She did reply,
but it was all just a bit like
>> who are you?
>> And so I said I said, "Oh, because at
that time me and you were beefing." So I
was like, "Oh yeah, I'm beefing with
that PJ. What's up? Who the [ __ ] are
you?" And that's I can remember that.
Who the [ __ ] are you?
>> Yeah. I was a bit like, "Oh my god." I
was like, "Oh yeah, I know who your ex is."
>> And she didn't respond. And it was just
it was weird. It was me talking to
myself kind of thing. And then in the
end, I think I blocked her cuz I was
thinking this is [ __ ] weird. >> Yeah.
And then when I saw the American one, I
was just thinking this is never going to
be this is going to be a non-starter
because I do have an Instagram, but it's
a fake one and it's just like zero zero zero followers.
>> You said with that whole you said with
that whole like LT messaging her, you
said I was behind it, wasn't it?
>> Say that again. You were that whole LT
messaging her. You said I was behind it
all in it.
>> I can't remember, but you probably were.
Yeah, but I don't give a [ __ ] anyway.
>> How do you make that one out though? Huh?
>> I don't know. Like I just find it like
I've always said to you, I said, "How
did people find out who you are?" Like I
just think that you say something and
then you wanted to know like what she
look like and that. So I gave him her Instagram.
>> Yeah. But she's a catfish, bro. Mate,
I've seen her pick.
>> Yeah, I know. That's how he That's how
he found her. Is it? That's how he discovered her.
>> Yeah, but to be fair to LT, I don't
think he bothered with her, did he? >> No.
>> Yeah, I think he knew that that was a [ __ ] cat.
You think it's funny in him, man.
>> Yeah, but I want to know who that [ __ ]
I want to know. Who was that guy that
you said? You remember your message on
Instagram? You said, "Oh, this is your
ex." And then he he [ __ ] went mental.
>> Yeah, he was getting He was that D,
didn't it? Damn it. His name was
>> That was funny. I mean, to me it was
funny, you know, where you thought that
you you had another ally and then he
just turned around and went, you know
what? [ __ ] you as well. It's just like,
what the [ __ ]
Yeah, he was a [ __ ] isn't it?
>> It's the same as like, you remember when
that [ __ ] Tiger turned up on your
street? I just had this mental image in my head
>> of your neighbors pulling back the
curtains and see
>> Timmy running around the [ __ ] god.
Imagine Imagine you now just opened your
curtains and you just saw Timmy doing
flying kicks around your guard. You'd be
like, "What the fuck?" >> Yeah. Yeah,
I don't know. My humor is [ __ ] I find
all that [ __ ] funny.
>> Hi, Wickle. Rocky, you don't even Who
the [ __ ] is this? >> Who?
>> Can you hear me? >> Yeah. Lord
PG, let me in. Something to say to this
guy. Listen, mate. If you want to let
him in, you can let him in. He don't
know who I am.
>> Hello, big nose.
>> [ __ ] virgin.
Go sort your ugly face out. You look
like a rat, you [ __ ] skin ugly bastard.
>> I wish you [ __ ] kept him in. I wish
you'd [ __ ] kept him in, but it's all
the same. Yeah, it's the same with that
ugly bastard, man. We're [ __ ] getting
a minute. High Wickham
Rocky. This is Shauny [ __ ] long legs.
First of all, I don't live anywhere near High Wickham.
>> I would get [ __ ] laid, you [ __ ]
virgin. Get off [ __ ] YouTube.
>> Honestly, PJ, have I ever said anything
about Just be honest with me. Have I
ever said anything about H Highwick?
I don't think I have.
Hi, Wickham. Rocky, what the [ __ ]
He doesn't know who the [ __ ] Are you there?
>> Yeah, bro. I'm here, bro. I'm here.
>> Are you there?
>> Yeah, bro.
>> Yeah. What's up?
What's he on about?
>> I was just talking to someone and then
Bro, just don't give it any attention,
bro. Just leave it.
>> You know what I mean?
>> He can come in. If he wants to [ __ ]
come in, he can come in. I mean, I know
that's Shauny. I'll have a [ __ ] word of him.
>> I don't give a [ __ ] Otherwise, I'll
just talk to you.
Man, you got quiet.
Is he gone? It's gone. [Music]
PJ, you're quiet. Hello. Uh,
if you're gone, PJ, just cut the the
live. I'll talk to you later.
>> Anyways, bro, sorry, man. I was doing
something. Can you hear me? Yeah.
>> Yeah, I can hear you. I was just about
to just say that if you were gone, just
cut the live. I'll talk to you later,
mate. Listen, stop saying that people
have got a big nose. Cuz look at your
ugly [ __ ] rat face, you [ __ ]
At least I don't play on the [ __ ] At
least I don't At least I don't pray At
least I don't play on the vulnerable,
man. Like [ __ ] you, you [ __ ]
>> PJ, you might as well just go back to
[ __ ] laying in on this guy because he
started to get brave lately, which means
>> I don't want to give him attention, but
he just wants attention because he's a
sad little loser who who who he's a sad
little virgin loser. Yeah. who his mom
used to starve him and he takes out the
world. He just wants attention, bro.
Even Tom Woods knows what he's about.
>> I know that, but I'm just saying that
the fact that he [ __ ]
>> You're a sad little virgin.
>> He's got brave recently. He's got brave
recently. Started posting again, which
means that the police have told him,
"Listen, mate. Nothing's [ __ ] going
to come off this."
>> That's what's happened.
>> Well, then they not Yeah. Well, bro, I'm
I'm not coming on after uh tomorrow for
a little bit. Like month, two weeks, month maybe.
>> If you want to keep arguing, bro, you
can waste your life arguing with this
stupid [ __ ] You know what I mean?
>> Yeah. Let me just say this one thing.
Hi, Wickham Rocky. Listen, a few years
ago, I did well, I'm not going to
[ __ ] tell you who. I knew a [ __ ]
family. I had I did go back and fors to
highwickenham but I haven't been there
for for months but listen even if you
know what just sayum if you want to be
oh I know where you live well [ __ ] go
to highwickham then I'm not there I'm in
well I can say where I am I'm in [ __ ]
Hayes west London come there if you want
to [ __ ] do something and I'll meet
you at the [ __ ] station but you're
not going to come so [ __ ] off shorty
Man, are you tired?
>> I don't know. I just saw that high W and
this is going back. Do you know what is
that? His information is so [ __ ] out
of date. It's just like [ __ ] off, man.
But do you know what? If he wants to let
everyone think that I know where he
lives, well go to High Wickham then and
you just wasted
20 quid of your [ __ ] money. You know
what I mean?
>> Yeah. Literally, bro. And