Uh, delinquent
people. Why is that all burning?
That's not the first one. That's the third one. Oh [ __ ] Oh, what?
I need to [ __ ] sleep now, man. Oh [ __ ]
What the [ __ ]
I don't turn on.
No, I'm not back, mate.
But I'm reunited with King.
I'm reunited with uh Kingling.
I want to play some Franklin, but I
can't be bothered to unplug that off, bro.
No, went out yesterday, bro. It was the
same old. But to be honest with you, it
was so fun yesterday.
Oh, do you know what? Yeah, I was like,
I have to go out today cuz yesterday I
was so [ __ ] and stressed I thought
I've got to go out with a drink.
Nah, just seeing him. Anyways, we're not
talking about my living circumstances.
No up. Anyways, yeah, I went out uh
yesterday grievy cuz I was just like
[ __ ] stressed and [ __ ] I didn't even
spend money to be honest, much money,
but it was the same old [ __ ] H even
though like 20% I only acknowledge 20%
of it. You have to acknowledge how
[ __ ] up it is. You can't be in denial
at the same time.
It will never change in this country. Never.
Never. I was starting to look homeless
as well, bro. So, I had to get a trim in that.
Uh going to Frankie, bro. I told you
about a million times. I don't gamble anymore.
So, stop uh stop trying to encourage me
to gamble. I'm not Monty or [ __ ]
Timmy. I told you I don't gamble. And
when I say I don't do it, I mean it. So
stop doing that on my channel. Thanks. So
yeah, it will never change in this
country. Oh [ __ ]
Literally, bro. So yeah, your past uh
um your past does future when it comes
to dating in this country. One million
million%. You're going to laugh at this
Grezy. I was speaking to this guy for
about 25 minutes. I got his number and
he literally come back for me like 5
hours later. Like, you are not the
problem, bro. You know, yesterday was
actually so good. It doesn't matter how
many weeks I'm zero gamble. I'm not
going back to it. Simple. I don't
gamble. End of just stop putting [ __ ]
like on my channel. Um, I had a good
time yesterday, bro. But the dating
thing never changes here. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I got a guy's number. It's
called connecting with people and making
friends. Yeah. There's nothing gay about it.
Even though in your shallow stupid mind
that you think it's gay, but I can
assure you that we're not gay. But
I mean, yeah. Why is that weird to you?
Like building connections. You people
sit online every day talking to each
other cuz you ain't got a life.
And you're talking about me getting a
guy's number. No, no, [ __ ] You
sit on here all day talking to each
other, talking to men. One sec. One sec.
One sec. I went out. I got drunk. I made
some connections. Okay, I admit that.
You people sit on YouTube all day
talking to men all day, day in day out.
You're literally sat on YouTube talking
to each other and you're all men.
So, uh, yeah. Don't talk about me
getting some guy's number. Yeah,
trying to turn it into a sexual thing.
You need to look at yourselves.
[ __ ] you know, that's how immature
you are. You You know what? Yeah. You
people there, you need to grow up.
That's another thing. You people in
here, you really, really need to grow
up. Like, you know, you're you're double
my age, right? Right. You're double my
age and you're so immature.
So immature. Like when when when are you
people going to grow up?
You know when when are these people
going to grow up and stop acting their
shoe size? Actual age and not your shoe size.
Grow the [ __ ] up. So what? Yeah. I had a
few drinks. I met some people. I made
connections. And [ __ ] what? You
always go on about [ __ ] friends all
the [ __ ] time, you know.
But yeah, it doesn't change in this
country, Grezy, bro. Never will change
in this country.
I only stuck to the beard to be fair. So
the whole point is your future does your
past does dictate your future here in this country.
So of course it does.
Yeah. Get Yeah. Because it's immature
cuz Yeah. Because we know what you're
getting at and it's boring and it's
immature. Yeah. It's boring and it's
Yeah. So [ __ ] what? Cuz we see where
where you're getting at because you've
been doing it for years.
You understand? Yeah. You've been doing
it for years and years and years and
years and years. So we see where you're
getting at with it.
You know, that's why it's bad. We see
where you're getting at with it. You're
trying to make a se a sexuality thing.
Yes. That's what you're that's what
you're getting at with it.
You know, [ __ ] hell, bro.
Do you see me traveling to different
countries to meet men? You know, think
about it, bro. One sec. One sec.
Do you see me traveling to different
countries to meet men like L J? No.
That's what you call sus.
That's what you call [ __ ] sus. Not
somebody being pissed out of their
[ __ ] head. People coming and speaking
and then you're making connections.
So no, I had a good time yesterday
though, man. I met these lads from
Birmingham. They were sound as [ __ ] We
got the baby Guinness and everything. It
was sound, bro.
Yeah, at least I messaged some people.
Weren't I going to Amsterdam? No, I went
to Amsterdam to go on holiday. Yeah, I
went on Amsterdam to go on holiday.
That's why I went on That's why I went
to Amsterdam. Never ever gone to another
country to meet another man. Never in my
life. That's what you call sus.
That is what you call sus. Not giving a
man your number that you're speaking to
in a [ __ ] pub to try and make
connections. So no, I've never gone to
Amsterdam to meet a man. I went to go on holiday.
And when he came, he came because he was
visiting anyway. So no. So
it's getting boring now. The whole
you're gay. It's it's boring now. But
you just need to grow up. A lot of you
on here. That's what you need to do. You
need to grow up, man.
I got a new setup, by the way, Grezy.
But yeah, the whole women thing as [ __ ]
bro. I started looking homeless and I
had to go to the barbers.
Anyways, moving on now. Grow up. Um,
went to the barbers, bro. I got some Citroen.
But yeah, Grezy, it doesn't it doesn't
change in this country.
No, bro. It doesn't ever change in this
country. Yeah, if I didn't go out
yesterday, Grezy, I would have went mad
cuz I'm still waiting on things and
stuff. So, I would have went mad if I
didn't go out. And I didn't even spend
that much. £60, £70. It's fine, you
know. I would have went mad.
Yeah. It would never change. You had a
woman You had a woman ghost you,
huh? Okay. Yeah. That's England for you.
Get used to it.
Yeah. A woman ghosted you in England.
Yeah. Get used to it. Simple, bro.
Yeah, got to keep up your hygiene. Uh,
I'll repeat myself again. I'm not Monty
Man or Timmy. So, stop commenting on my
channel like I'm Monty Man or Timmy. You
can't troll me. I'm not Monty Man nor am
I Timmy. And I think you need to really
really understand that. So, anyways, yeah,
gives you the best chance. Yeah, keep
dreaming, bro. But yeah, so what? A
woman goes to you. Okay, that's England
for you. That's good old England.
You know, like I'm I'm not even moaning.
I'm not even moaning about it because
it's just the same old in this country. But yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. You really don't know anything
about women. I actually feel sorry for
you people, bro. It just goes to show
lack of life experience.
I had a mad day yesterday, bro. [ __ ]
Nah, I don't I don't really come on here
anymore, bro. It's like I was saying to
that [ __ ] uh Rocky Roid. There's no
point. It's just the same old same old
on here. Same old repeating people. Same
old projectors. I don't really bother
with it anymore. Me.
Yeah. I said I I said I looked homeless.
Then I went to the barbers and then I no
longer looked homeless. You people
really are slow in here, aren't you?
Not to like start insulting you people,
but you you got to be some you've got to
be [ __ ] is it? Some of you on here,
you got to be [ __ ] [ __ ]
Like I I actually think, bro.
Yeah. Well, you can keep missing them
cuz I'm not arguing with stupid people
in this community anymore.
Stupid stupid people that ain't got a
life. Nah, bro. I'm good.
Oh, [ __ ] Almost spilled everywhere.
Yep. This country will never change ever. Sad, bro.
Um, I can call you slow because you are
slow. Stop acting like you're slow then.
Stop saying stupid things.
Stop saying stupid [ __ ] things. Oh, I
I notic you didn't like that when I said
about traveling to different countries
to meet a man, is it? That's what you
call sus, bro. That is what you call
very, very sus.
You know what I'm saying?
You know, you people sit in your houses
all day. You ain't got a life. And then
you start [ __ ] trying to talk about other people.
Then you try to call people skin, but at
the end of the day, you don't know about
anyone's life. That's the most funniest.
Do you know that's the most funniest
thing, you know? Yeah. The past two
weeks when I was telling people the
situation, they literally thought like,
"Anyways, you're banned. Bye-bye now, Sebastic." Um,
they actually think that they know your
financial circumstances when they don't.
They just think everyone's just like
them. You know what I'm saying? Like
skin ain't got a life. They They just
think everybody is like them. It's mad,
isn't it? I don't have loads and loads
and loads of money, bro. I've got enough
to do what I want to do with it.
But they they just think everyone lives
their life. It's so weird. It is really
really really weird, Grezy. They think
everyone is living the life that they're
living. Skin on YouTube every day. Can't
ain't got a life. It's the truth, bro.
And I'll be real. I ain't got nothing to
do today. I'm just chilling, bro.
But yesterday was a very, very weird
day, Greavves. Yeah, I bumped into
someone. You know that?
Do you know that uh Pakistani woman that
I met and then she she tried ghosting
me? I I ran into her yesterday. It was
so awkward. Oh my god. Um and she was
telling me some of her problems and
[ __ ] I was like, "You wouldn't want to
have my problems. You wouldn't want to
have my problems, mate, because it would
have killed you." Trust me, I've been
through a lot of [ __ ] But I thought now
I've got no responsibilities. I can do
what I want. It's good.
Yeah, Greavesy. It was a It was a weird
day yesterday, bro. It was It was a good
day, though. I enjoyed it, bro. I
enjoyed the people I met and stuff. It
was It was good.
Um, done an approach at a train station,
said they weren't interested, even
though I was looking slick. Same old England.
Um, on another few, all had boyfriends
apparently. Speaking to this older
woman, we were speaking for 20 minutes.
It seems that the only people that you
can get conversations out of, Grebsy, is
either older women, Australian people,
or [ __ ] men. That that seems the only
people you can actually get a
conversation out of. It's bad, bad, bad.
Then I went to approach this woman and
then it turned out to be the one that I
had met them two months ago. Greasy.
She's like, "Oh, don't you know me?" I
was like, "Oh, yeah, yeah, the person
that was ignoring." Um,
it's just so [ __ ] up, bro. Like, I'll
do a video about this one day about this
country. I can't be bothered, bro, for now.
But I do accept it. I I understand the
problem. I get it. But I can't help but
acknowledge how [ __ ] up it is. I think
that's normal, is it, Grezy? I think all
of the people that don't are in denial.
How can not 20% of you just think like
this is completely [ __ ] up? It's not
normal. Even 15 20% you you would, bro.
You know what I'm saying? It's [ __ ] weird, man.
This country has gone through the shambles, dad.
And um yeah, anyone would think you're
fat and ugly. Have you been hit in the gym, Greasy?
Yeah. anybody would think you're a fat ugly bastard.
I've actually moved out of here now.
So yeah, I need to hit that status.
Still the same.
You'll find a bird eventually. Yeah, you
keep telling yourself that.
You keep telling yourself that, buddy.
They just come. Yeah, you keep telling yourself that.
Three years in counting. That's a
massive loy mate.
Yeah, you keep you keep telling yourself that, buddy. Uhuh.
You keep telling yourself that if it
makes you feel better. Yeah, man.
Even though Grezy,
you've been all around the country, all
different cities and everything, and
you're still single and you've been out
in London a million times, and the
problem is still happening, and it's
getting worse, you will meet someone
because all the evidence supports to one
day you're going to wake up and none of
these things are going to happen.
You're not going to get the make believe
boyfriends. You're not going to get the
attitude. So, one day you're going to
wake up and all of a sudden it's going
to change. I'm not putting my money on
that, bro. I mean, I don't I don't
gamble anymore, but if I was to bet, I
wouldn't put my money on that, bro. You
might as well just burn your money. All
the evidence supports
that it's not going to change
because your past dictates your future.
When it comes to this in this country,
it does with anything else. It doesn't.
You know, you don't know what's going to
happen. But with this, you know exactly
what's going to happen.
And I went out cuz I had I wanted to go
out anyways. So that's the reason I went
out. But at the same time, you you will
still acknowledge how [ __ ] up it is. So
um you don't just wake up one day after
years and years and years and suddenly
the country is completely different.
You know the baddest thing is Grezy, you
can't even get housed in this country as
a British citizen. They don't even see
people as priority even as a British
citizen if you're disabled. Like we can
go on and on and on and on and on about
this country a million. It's just it's
just [ __ ] up. It's just a [ __ ] up
shitty depressing annoying country. There's nothing really else.
I was not going to sit in all day
yesterday, but I would have went insane
if I sat in all day yesterday.
Went out. It was good. But uh
I think I've got a logical point. What
do you think, Grezy? This is what I was
trying to explain to Joe earlier uh
somebody the other day is that if you
was going to find somebody, you you
would have found someone by now.
It's that simple. It doesn't make sense.
That's what I'm saying. So,
but people tell you you'll meet someone,
but the evidence suggests different. And
we don't even care, but it's just
something to like to talk about. But it
just it just doesn't
it just does not seem like it's likely,
bro, cuz it was it would happen by now.
That's what I'm saying. It would have
happened by now.
There's no hope. Deep down, you don't
have no hope. Which is why you only do
this [ __ ] when you're drunk. Which is
why you do it because you're going out
anyways. Because there is no hope.
That's the whole that's the whole point of it.
You wouldn't go around approaching
people sober, would you? Why? Because
you have no hope, you know? But with
when you're when you're drunk, you're
just like drunk anyway. So you think,
"Fuck it." But you that's why you have
no hope. I don't even think I can do him
sober anymore. Well, I did well I did do
one yesterday so but and now I've lost
all confidence in it as well because
it's never ever ever ever going to
change in this country and it's
something that I've accepted now. So that's it.
No having a lamb shank. So yeah.
No, you didn't give any advice, bro.
But yeah, I think with this country,
I was speaking to a couple of people
about this earlier. Yeah.
Um, and I'm thinking what has changed in two years?
What something has definitely changed in
two years? You know, I was speaking to
my Italian friend about this
and they couldn't tell me. So,
but it's not it's not normal.
And yeah, basically she was telling me
how she's been depressed and all of this
grievy and stuff. She's still not
interested in dating and no no no no.
It's just the same old, you know,
yesterday was just a really really weird day. Um,
it was just so many weird things happen, bro. So,
but no, I don't think you got any chance
in this country, bro. Really? Now, I can
safely say it. I can safely cuz don't
forget I had my head on yesterday and I
just wore a little cap. I can show you
me yesterday, bro, if you want. One sec.
What else? I was looking. Yeah.
me yesterday. Goozy. One sec.
Tell me I'm not looking clean, bro.
What a weird mouthing cuz uh yeah, I
don't want to put a video up.
Tell me I was not looking. Look at me,
bro. Look at me yesterday. I was clean as [ __ ]
I was clean as a [ __ ] bro.
Look straight out the barbers.
I go everywhere with my little cat now.
Still get the same old
same old boring I call it.
But we're too we're too old now to start
throwing uh tantrums around, bro.
I think it's more I can't believe it to
be honest with you.
I think that's what it is. Like I'm I
just to me I just can't believe it.
Like when you go out and it's like [ __ ]
It really does predict your future, doesn't it?
Your past definitely dictates your future.
I'll start gambling again when they
offer a market. there for on that [ __ ]
I look clean as [ __ ] bro. Look at that
for a month in it.
Started looking homeless, so I had to
like get a haircut and [ __ ] But yeah, I
don't think you can [ __ ] do anything, bro.
England's a sad place to be, eh? Sad
place to be. busy.
Yeah, Andy is uh Andy is still in ignore
like the last time, bro. [ __ ]
Yeah, it's not my life, Greaves. Yeah, I
assure you it's not my life. It's just
every single time you go out, right?
You're just reminded of how [ __ ] up it
is. Cuz obviously you do it when you're
drunk, don't you? You know, when you're
drunk, you do it when you're drunk. So
like, I don't know. You just kind of notice
how [ __ ] up it is. I don't know, bro.
It's weird. It's [ __ ] up.
But yeah, it'll never change.
See the difference with Ant-Man is like
obviously when you know he used to try
every week and stuff but he never ever
tried as much as me. So I feel like I'm
in a position to complain
like so you're you're you're completely
in your rights to moan and complain or
not. You know what I'm saying, bro?
cuz no one can tell you to try cuz
you've already tried more than anyone in
the world. So it's not even like people
can say, "Okay, get off your backside
and and because obviously you've already
done it." So
no one can um
no one can tell you anything. But
King's not met Franklin yet. You know that Grezy
not upset about the house thing and the
money greasy because at the end of the
day do you know what I am? I'm not
[ __ ] bro. I'm back to reality.
That's what I am. I'm just back to reality.
I'm not [ __ ] No, I I I know, bro,
that in 3 years I was living in La La Land.
In 3 years I was living in La La Land,
bro. That's what I was doing. I was
living in La La Land. Now we're back to
real life now. You understand? So,
but yeah, I was basically telling that
woman, you wouldn't want to be me, mate.
what I've been through the past [ __ ] few weeks,
it would have [ __ ] it would have it
would have killed you, mate. Trust me,
the stress of it all and everything. But yeah,
have I don't know.
Maybe I do, maybe I don't.
You know what? Every time I have king, I
think of you, Grezy. With King, I always
think of you.
Do I do I not? Let me have a look.
I'm not sure if I have king.
You tell me.
So, no dates this week. Yay.
Same old England. Yay.
Show you this picture.
I like King HQ. Oh, oh, Grezy.
What the hell?
Who knew? Eh, a little Frenchie. Oh, [ __ ]
He's not met Franklin. He loves Franklin. Oh,
you love King. Why do you love King so much, man?
But yeah, the whole dating thing is
[ __ ] up. So, this was me yesterday
after I had my hair and beard done. I
think I look pretty good. Pretty cool.
What do you think, Grezy?
I look pretty all right.
Seem to s suit the black better, but
no, same old.
Ed is not interested in this country.
Oh, I almost shot myself yesterday. Grezy.
Yeah, almost shot myself.
Yeah, I literally almost shot myself,
bro. I was very close.
Very, very, very close.
It was horrible, bro. Oh my god, bro. I
almost pooed myself.
So, what's your opinion on this whole
dating thing, bro?
Yeah, I went out yesterday. I didn't get
nothing. Coke, friend. All I got was
I've got a boyfriend. I've got a
boyfriend. I mean, I got three numbers,
but none's replied back yet. But I made
some really I met some really cool
people. One guy even came back for me.
Okay, I think that guy was gay, but I
didn't even know he was.
I think he must have been. But he didn't
come across as it. He didn't give off
them vibes. We were talking Greasy for
about 25 minutes. Yeah. He was a lot
younger than me, right? Um and was just
talking and like cuz he come here by
himself. I was okay whatever. He didn't
give give off any vibes that he was,
which it doesn't matter if he is
anyways, you know. And then five late
five hours later, he he come back
to see and all the other people, they
were all in relationship. So, it's just
weird. Like these people come on and
they make it about a sexuality thing.
Oh, you got a guy's number and they make
it like a sexuality thing. It's just
immature. It's really, really weird.
Very, very, very weird. It's just
immature, man. But yeah, I got [ __ ] all
yesterday, bro. Same old H1.
Same old I've got a boyfriend. Oh, [ __ ]
It will never change. It will only It
will Well, it will it it will change
because it will get worse.
It will get worse. So, it will change
So, that's how it will change. yeah,
it definitely definitely is women in
this country. It it has to be at this
point. It has to be.
Oh, do you want me to put the little
video up with the baby Guinnesses?
Why have you got my picture, you weirdo?
Yeah, you can change the picture. I'm
banning you, you [ __ ] weirdo. Stop
stealing my pictures, you [ __ ] freak.
You [ __ ] weirdo.
But um what was I saying? Gre, you want
me to put up the baby Guinnesses?
Do you want me to put up the baby Guinnesses, bro?
You little weirdo. See the men's pictures?
Yeah, you can get going, you little weirdo.
Yeah, man. Anyways,
no. Go on, Grey. I was with my little
mates. Greasy. With my little mates, bro.
These people are weirdos, man.
It's back to reality now, Grezy. So,
that's all it is.
Yeah, I was with that Pakistan girl for
like maybe 40 minutes
and she said to me how she stays in bed
and doesn't want to get up and that I
wish I could be depressed like that, but
cuz I have things to do, mate. I can't
[ __ ] lie in bed. So,
but yeah, whatever whatever whatever uh
whatever reason it is, you know, like
it will never change in this country,
bro. And I don't know what evidence you have
supports it. You know what I'm saying?
If there was some evidence that actually
supports it, then I would understand.
But no, I think Saturday I'll give it
one last hurrah.
Then that's it.
It will never change ever.
Never. And the thing is I've got money.
I can go on dates. I can I can go on
dates. I can [ __ ]
Do you know what I mean, Gav? I can go
on dates. It's not a problem. It's not a
problem at all if I could have something
scheduled, but nothing nothing at all. Whoop!
I look clean as [ __ ] bro. What the Oh my.
One second, bro.
Oh, [ __ ] I need to try and get this
fold somehow. Grezy.
Oh, I wish there was a way to make
another. I've got the money. I can do it, but
be nice as if I can make an extra £500
so it doesn't come out my own money. But
[ __ ] knows, bro. I still haven't heard
from any of the jobs that I've applied for.
And I've noticed that as well. Like you
can save 250,300 a month. It's not too bad.
I have no choice. You know what I'm saying? So,
but I just bought Oh, I had to reby the
TV, didn't I? So,
that left me with like 1.7. So, I still got money.
I'm going to struggle. [ __ ] yeah.
One second. Oh [ __ ]
I don't know money
in a minute. Anyways, bro, I need to do some stuff.
It's very bad, bro. It seems everyone wants [ __ ]
Mr. Perfect and [ __ ]
Oh, who's that? I'm not interested in
this country, but Oh, man.
So mad to think about the amount of [ __ ]
we've actually dealt with in this country, bro.
It's so bad, ain't it? So bad. is bad.
Yep. They've all got boyfriends
apparently. One sec. Uber Yeah.
[ __ ] sexy, bro.
[ __ ] hell, man.
I bought her baby Guinness. We was
having baby Guinness. So, yesterday I
didn't even spend much.
Didn't even spend much compared to
um the the
[ __ ] that I actually had done, you know.
What the [ __ ] blocking.
That wall was beautiful.
I met somebody that was the same age as
me, lives in my area, lives like two
minutes from me, and he thought, "Oh
[ __ ] everything happens for a reason,
you know." But no, just the same old
This is all too much, mate.
You This is all too much, is it? Yeah, that
light [ __ ] really
bad. Is it? Oh, [ __ ]
I don't even know why I get this TV, but
I I don't even use it. I even watch TV, bro.
Oh, we had a baby. Get this together.
How cute is that? [ __ ] hell. Top shot.
Why does this Indonesian guy always talk
about positivity and [ __ ] He doesn't
even approach. like he doesn't even
approach and he's like, "Oh, well, he
doesn't go out for women." Well, I
don't. I'm just not in denial about how
[ __ ] up it is.
It is [ __ ] up.
Like, they're in denial, bro. When they
say like, "Oh, I'm only going out."
Yeah, you're going out to have fun. But
they like they're still in denial because
don't seem to address how like [ __ ] up
it is. They don't seem to think that
there's like a problem when there is, you know.
And I said, "Well, if they don't reply,
then it's obviously negative, isn't it?
Because you're not going on a date.
You're not meeting them again. So, it's negative."
You know what I'm saying?
So it's negative obvious obviously it's negative.
But that guy didn't give off any vibes
that he was gay or anything.
So some people you can't tell.
[ __ ] that's a madness, bro.
I have a grenade. I shall never know.
I shall [ __ ] never know to be fair.
Yeah, just guys reply straight away. Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] Uh,
boss talking to this person. Wait a second. One sec.
We need to get some uh Nothing.
I want to go. I think I'm too [ __ ] to
go though. Greasy.
Oh, if I can have a snooze now, I could
probably go later.
But it's trying to get sleep, man. You're [ __ ]
I'm trying to think what I had. I think
I just had beer, didn't I? Uh, hey.
I'll be about