What?
[ __ ] Yeah, I'm back now.
I say I'm going to do something. I
[ __ ] do it, man. Um
Um, yeah, man.
What the [ __ ] [ __ ] mate.
Yeah, the horror film was maybe six out
of 10. very predictable like they always are nowadays.
So it was okay. Second.
See my thing is not open.
What the [ __ ] bro?
What's even the point, bro? I don't even get it. What's wrong?
I want to give that person my thing on
Instagram in case that JB Thompson
stalker. That's why I don't want to give
them my channel, bro, on that platform.
I want to know this country will never
change. But it's just something to do,
you know. [ __ ] it.
It's just something to do. But it would
never change, bro.
It does predict your future.
Your past does dictate your future.
to do with date. When it's to do with dating anyways
to do with dating in this country,
I was in a cinema and I was thinking,
well, the money thing ain't even that
bad to be honest with you. Still got
savings. You don't know what's going to
happen and [ __ ] like that isn't even
really a major problem.
That's just like what it is, you know,
terms of like dating and it never changes, but
not same old.
Uh went out yesterday. Um
Oh, [ __ ] man. Had a good time
yesterday. Met loads of people. just
come back from the cinema. Yeah, just
same old England as I don't know what
what what else to say. I think we need
to stop like start going into things and
stuff and then just call it the same old
England. I got three numbers. I got one
reply, but I met like loads of cool
people and [ __ ] So, it was it was good.
Yesterday was good, man. I had to go out
yesterday otherwise I would have went
bad, bro. I had to get a haircut and
[ __ ] anyways. But it would never change
in this country, bro.
Never. Your past literally dictates your
future when it's to do with women in
this country 1 million%.
Um, but it is what it is, isn't it? It's
just I'm just acknowledging how [ __ ]
up it is. I'm not complaining. I'm just
acknowledging how it's not normal. Um,
and the film was uh I know what you did
last summer. That was the one.
in this country.
It's so weird as
I was having baby Guinnesses yesterday
and met some people and that. It's a
shame, man. It is a shame. Didn't even
spend much to be honest.
It never changes, bro. Never.
I just say some painkillers, bro.
But even the horror films are really predictable now.
They're all predictable. Like once
you've seen one, you've basically seen
them all. Still got some popcorn and
[ __ ] left cuz I don't want to waste it,
you know? So expensive.
You're a [ __ ] people have.
So yeah, never it'll never it will never
change this country, bro, but never never never
and you know the thing is that people
say, "Oh, why do you still do it?"
Because there's nothing else to do.
What else is there to do than to go out
and drink? I can't even work at the
minute for various different reasons. So
what what else do you do but go out and
drink? Well, you've lost hope, bro.
Why do you think you only do it drunk?
Because you literally have lost hope.
That's the whole point of it. You have
lost hope, which is why you only do it
when you're drunk. I don't want so stay
at a train station, but you get my point. Like
that's the whole point is cuz you
actually have lost home. That's what I'm saying.
It's proper [ __ ] up, bro.
It is proper bad. It is proper proper
proper bad, bro.
But no, it will never change. It will
never change, bro. Never.
It will never change in this country. Never.
Never. Potter. It would always be the
same. Well, actually, no, it will
change. It will get worse. So, actually,
I would say it will change.
But that Jo here that tries to say that
your um your future does not predict it.
It does it does it does dictate your future because right
you did it does because if it didn't it
wouldn't be the same [ __ ] every time.
Do you understand guys? It would it
wouldn't be the same old [ __ ] every
time. If your if your past do not
dictate your future. So listen right
like let's go by your lo with money and
stuff it's different with other things
it's different no one knows what can
happen you might go out tomorrow win
five grand you know no no one knows but
with women it is the same because what
you're going to suddenly come across
someone that's not stuck up somebody
that's not westernized
somebody that doesn't do all of these
things that it's only took what 3 4
years it doesn't even seem possible Bro,
it does not even seem possible.
I'm just looking forward to next month,
bro. So, I can bet on the football. It's
going to be [ __ ] ass, man.
The weird, man. The ghosting, the
blocking, the boyfriend [ __ ] It's
[ __ ] boring, bro. I'll be on the baby Guinness tomorrow.
Then I run into that. Oh, dad, you
remember that Muslim girl I told you
about from a couple of months ago,
right? I bumped into her yesterday.
Yeah, it's very awkward.
You never know who you're going to bump into.
Yeah, it'll never change this country, bro.
Never. I'm I mean I'm talking to one but you know
it is bad bro. It is very bad.
Yeah. This guy is still an ignore. This
black guy from America,
he's still an ignorer.
That's what I am doing, guys. That's
what I am doing, mate. But obviously,
bro, the reason I went out yesterday is
because I have loads of like stress now,
but no responsibility. So, obviously, I
got to got rid of the house. And then,
um, it's like a waiting game for things.
So, I was like, you might as well just
go for a drink. You have nothing to lose
spending [ __ ] 50 60 quid and I needed
a haircut anyways. I was starting to
look [ __ ] homeless. So I had to go
out. So yeah,
not ignoring you. You haven't asked a question.
Yeah, you do need to go Asia, bro.
You need to stop being in denial. And
and do you know all of these people that
don't moan about it? If they're in
denial, it's they're scared to say what
they I'm not even moaning about I just
think it's [ __ ] up
how you can be normal and you can't even
get anyone in your own country. Bro,
Daz, you're not going to believe this.
Yesterday, bro, I was speaking to this
guy. He was 18, right? Rocking for about
25 minutes. Now, I don't know if he if
he was gay. I don't think he was gay. Um,
he's fine. And was talking and that and
he come back 5 hours later to see if I
was still there just to see if he got
the right number. And I met like loads
of other people. It's not you, bro. It's
not you at all at all. It can't It isn't
It is them. It's It is literally It is
literally them. Like, even when I was
back at the cinema, I was just at the
cinema now. You see the look on people's
[ __ ] faces, bro. They're all stuck up and westernized.
Will never ever ever change this
country. Never. The only people that you
you get a conversation out of is like
[ __ ] Australian people or the older generation. So yeah,
it's sad, bro. It really is sad.
I'm just not in denial, bro. I'm not
That's it. I'm just not The difference
is I'm just not in denial. Daz
like that Indonesian
trying to say oh about negativity. He's
just in denial.
That's what you call plain and simply in denial.
So yeah, it's bad. one second.
Yeah, as a virgin boy been on. You know
what I ate today? Nice lamb shank. I was
at my mom's jail and I had a nice lamb shank.
But you know what I hate about lamb and
chicken? It always gets stuck in your
gums and then you got to [ __ ] use
salt water to get it out. It's [ __ ]
horrible, man. I was thinking, [ __ ] my
mom's never starved me. I had two lamb
shanks. My mom has never ever starved me.
That's where I think all of this um
[ __ ] comes from. It's lack of um lack of
mother present cuz obviously no mother
figure cuz obviously we understand that
like your dad is you know you speak
about sex and all of this [ __ ] but you
got to understand is your mom carried
for you know nine months. You know, I
think a mother,
you know, when you don't have a mother
figure, you know, and your mom starved
you, that's that's probably why he's so
[ __ ] up, to be honest with you, bro.
That's why he gets assy about people
seeing their mom and living with their
mom. It's because his mom never wanted
him. See, with my dad, right, I saw my
dad a few times. He just didn't bring me
up and then he died. Okay? And what? I
wasn't abused by any of my [ __ ]
parents. You know what I'm saying, bro?
He was starved by his [ __ ] mother.
That's why he's so [ __ ] up. Yeah.
Yeah. Do you understand, bro? That's why
he's so [ __ ] up cuz he never had no mother figure.
You know what I'm saying? Stephen, I was
thinking about it like eating this lamb
shank. I couldn't even finish it. It was
two lamb shanks, right? And then you've
got someone who's whose mother starved them.
Do you know what I'm saying?
That's why he's so [ __ ] up, bro.
Yeah. That's why he's so [ __ ] in his head.
Yeah, obviously. But I'm just using as
an example. So, yeah.
So, yeah, that's why he's so [ __ ] up.
I think he needs to get laid. Personally,
I don't know what you think, Steven
Howard. I think he he he really does
need to get laid. Yeah, man.
But yeah, he's never had no mother figure.
That's what it is. Like, yeah, my dad
might have [ __ ] died, but [ __ ]
that's what happens. People People die.
You know what I'm saying? It is what it
is. But [ __ ] Yeah.
And he's still a virgin as well.
Cuz I was thinking about this, bro.
Sometimes I do actually think about
this, right? Yeah. When he's messaged
like USA, Izzy and all of these people.
Um why does he constantly seek
validation that people have not had sex?
Like let's just say that you did lie
about having sex with USA Izzy and all
of these other people, which I haven't
lied about, but let's just say
theoretically you did. Why would
somebody care so much when they
obviously knew that something happened?
Like you got to understand why would
somebody care so much?
It's got to be because they're a virgin themselves
and they're convincing them. It's like
they need validation that no one else
has got it because they're still a
virgin. You understand, bro? So it does
it doesn't make sense if you actually
put the pieces together. Yeah. It
actually builds up something.
cuz he's cuz he's a big virgin. Like I'm
I'm not even saying that to to wind
anyone up, but he's he's been he's been
doing it for years, bro. Like back when
I was 17. He's been doing it for [ __ ] years.
And then he says that he doesn't wear
pink. Why would you wear pink? I wear
[ __ ] hell. Why why would somebody be
so insecure about their sexuality?
There's nothing wrong with
the like if if somebody thought I was
gay, I'd be like, "Fuck you and still
wear pink. I'm I'm comfortable with my
sexuality." You know what I mean, bro?
Like [ __ ] I'm going to put a video
up, Steven. Yeah. And I'm going to send
you it, bro.
What's in your hair? Nothing wrong with pink, bro.
I'm putting a video up, bro. So, yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] I'll be on the drink again
tomorrow. Got mate doing this haircut.
I like baby pink. What's wrong with baby pink?
But like I said, that's where the whole
chevel co thing come from. It's just copying.
That is literally copying, bro. Yeah. If
she was lying naked in your bed and you
was pissed out of your [ __ ] head,
you wouldn't say no. But to say that
someone's gay for not finding her
attractive, no, that's just copying.
That's just self- projecting. Literally
copying, copying, copying, copying. They
used to do the same with [ __ ]
Beyonce. They used to do the [ __ ]
same with [ __ ] Jennifer Aniston,
copying each other. They used to, bro.
Beyonce was a mad one, bro.
But it's all copying. But people used to
do it with Beyonce as well. She's old
school, bro. I remember the [ __ ]
donkeys years ago. People used to go on
and on about her.
If you don't like Beyonce, you're gay.
Yeah, that's just what people used to
do, bro. It's just copying. Copycats.
I don't like copycats, man. I hate copycats. Oh [ __ ]
This was yesterday, but I had a lot of fun.
[ __ ] it. I can't ignore that. [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah, I was good, bro. I had fun yesterday, bro.
Can't beat summer Thursdays, eh? Oh
yeah. I hate that the lamb gets stuck in
your teeth and it causes like a minor
infection. I hate it.
So I hate eating lamb.
Go out tomorrow, get rejected again. But
it's better than nothing, is it?
Um, it was good yesterday, but it was
actually a laugh.
It was a laugh, bro. Oh, [ __ ]
Piece of fing setups.
Yeah, the country's [ __ ] bro. You
can't even get rehoused.
It's like what Bomb used to say in that
like he has no clue how it works,
right? He has literally no clue how it
works. He thinks that you could just
like go and just [ __ ] go and get
rehoused. He thinks that like when
someone's homeless, yeah, you can just
go and they'll help you. No, no, no, no,
no, no. It doesn't work like that. It
doesn't matter if you're disabled,
[ __ ] anything. They don't they don't
help you unless you're a [ __ ] woman
with a kid, which I think is wrong to be
honest with you cuz the way I see it,
right, is that these people choose to
have kids. Kids don't just suddenly grow
in someone's stomach. Like they they
shouldn't be priority. Like the people
that should be priority are [ __ ]
disabled people cuz they can't help
being [ __ ] disabled wherever the [ __ ]
wherever the [ __ ] is wrong with them. I
don't think women with children should
be a priority to be honest cuz it's not
like it's not a choice to have a child. Um
I don't know maybe maybe a lot of people
would agree with that but I I don't
think they should be priority
to be honest.
And then people that can't help stuff or not.
The country is [ __ ] bro.
And they favor. And you know what? Yeah.
I don't have no problems with black
people or anything. Yeah. But unless
you're [ __ ] this is not to be racist
or anything, bro, but this is reality.
Yeah. Unless you're African, they don't
care. And that is facts when it comes to
housing. I probably shouldn't even say
that. But unless you're African, like
not not even Jamaican, bro. Not even
Pakistani. Not even No. Unless you're
African, they they don't care.
They get all the houses, bro. If you was
African, they give you a 10-bedroom.
They'd give you a 10-bedroom house.
They would, bro. Trust me. But I do
think all of the people that work there are African.
That is 100% facts, bro.
[ __ ] is that, bro? What the [ __ ] But
yeah, let's like obviously they wanted
to know like a bit about me. I said,
"Oh, like got this foot condition and I
was lying it down hard on them, bro."
Like told them about anxiety. They
didn't care. They don't give a [ __ ]
unless you're African. They don't care.
They literally don't care, bro. Um,
it's madness, bro. It is actually mad
how [ __ ] up this country is.
They really, they really literally they
don't care, bro. And then you got bomb,
right? Thinking that someone can just go
and get a house. He's stupid. He has no
clue. He has no idea how how it works, bro.
You what? So what? something up to
£1,000. Yeah. Good luck trying to find a
property that's that that that you can
get for about £1,000. Yeah. Good luck.
Good luck with that, mate. Good luck
with that in London.
Uh stop talking about yourself, bro. Ask
yourself that question. Why can't you
get a job instead of being on benefits
and YouTube all day? Ask yourself that question.
Literally, ask yourself that question, bro.
people that work that's got all of this
money does not spend all day on YouTube.
You need to ask yourself that question.
Not me. Yeah.
Yeah, it is. And I'm not even racist,
bro. I don't care about anyone, bro.
I've got Muslim friends and [ __ ] but it
it it's it's facts. It is reality, bro.
He was African, mate. They'd give you
everything. It's facts. It's not even
racism. It's the truth, you know?
But yeah, women with with a kid should
not be priority. No way.
Yeah, of course you do, bro. You know
what I find so funny, bro? How you all
claim that you work, you all claim that
you got all this money, but you're sat
on YouTube all day. Doesn't look right,
does it, bro? Yeah.
Yeah. Why don't you mind your own [ __ ] business?
That's another thing. Let's just say
that you do work and I'm wrong. Okay.
Why don't you mind your own business?
Why don't you mind your own [ __ ] business
and worry about your life and not other people?
You know, why don't why does it matter
if someone works, don't work on
benefits? Is it any of your business?
[ __ ] they don't these people on here
really really really are so why do they tell people
they tell people to get a job right when
it's not even any of their business and
even if somebody got a job they try to
get them sacked
why don't they just mind their own
business and worry about their own life
you know normal people bro they don't
care about anyone's life but their own
life but here they seem to care about
other people's life more than they care
about their own life. It's so weird, bro.
And even if I did work, I wouldn't tell
you I work. I only mentioned to you
because I didn't do it anymore.
When have I Wait, hold on. What am I
talking about? I'm talking about
working. I'm not I'm not talking about
working. You've literally just come up.
We was talking about houses and Africans
and women with kids.
And you're talking about working.
No one's talking about [ __ ] working,
bro. You're the one that brought it up.
What the [ __ ] Worry about your own
life, bro. It'll get you get it will get
you further in life. Yeah.
Yeah. Bomb used to think that you could
just go and [ __ ]
Bye-bye now. Oh, [ __ ] idiot, bro. But
anyways, yeah. bomb. You used to think
you could just go out and get rehoused.
He's an idiot.
Yeah. Anyways, I bumped into that. Oh,
Steven, do you remember that Pakistani
girl I met two months ago? I bumped I
went to approach someone yesterday and
it was her. I said, "Oh, you remember?"
I was like, "Oh, yeah. Yeah, the ignor."
And he was like talking for like an hour.
Some of these people really don't know
what problems are, bro. I would swap my
place with anyone right now. Well, not
now. Life's not bad, but like the amount
of stress I was under, these people
really really wouldn't want to be under
it, bro. Trust me, really bad.
You're telling me how she can't get out.
Yeah, seriously. Yeah, we bumped into
each other. Um, and she was saying how
she got problems and she's depressed and
No, no, no, no. I even gave her some
tips. So I said, "Why don't you go to
sleep at the same time and wake up at
the same time every every day? It will help you."
I said that um but
yeah, I I wish I could be depressed, but
I'm too busy. I can't be, you know.
But yeah, I bumped into her anyways. Um
yeah, you're so weird.
I'm not going to message her again. I'm
not bothered by her again, bro. I can't be bothered. So, yeah. [ __ ]
You could never change.
Yeah. She's like, "Oh, Peter, don't you
remember me?" I was like, "Oh, yeah, I
do remember you. The one that's ignoring me."
So, yeah. She trying to say she had
issues and [ __ ] So, whatever.
I We all got issues, eh?
Let me have a look.
Yeah, it's pretty good, man.
It's all [ __ ] mate. It's all bollocks.
And this is what I mean, Stephen. Yeah.
They tell you about why don't you be
friends with someone first, bro? We
[ __ ] met about three times and she's
still full of [ __ ] So, just leave her
to it. E. Yeah.
See, people don't understand that. Like
when they tried to say, "Oh, why don't
you be friends with someone first?" And
to tear and Yeah. Like it's as easy as
that, bro. Like look at look at this situation.
I don't know. We should go cinema and
like always, but it's just it's just
impossible in this country, bro.
It is impossible in this country, man.
It will never change ever. Yeah.
Talking like she wasn't [ __ ] ignoring
me for [ __ ] god knows how long. And I
said to her this morning, "How are you
today?" She just ignored. So,
I mean, if people was really that damn
bad, they they would accept the help.
You know what I mean? They would accept
the help. But yeah,
I just told her some of my problems as
well, like the income, the house, and [ __ ] But
come to think of it, I'm not even in the
in the worst position now.
Yeah. Okay. You might not get as much
money, but you've been there, done it,
worn the t-shirt, you've been to steak
restaurants, you've got designer
clothes, you've got something to show
for your money. It's not really
It's not really a problem.
But it wasn't just that. It was the
whole [ __ ] thing about it. Like it
wasn't money. It wasn't even just money.
Money is easy, bro.
Yeah. Thank you, [ __ ]
Yeah. I went back to my old barber after
all that time. But doesn't matter, mate.
Doesn't matter what you have, they're
still not interested in this country. So,
you know what? You can't fault Ant-Man,
you know? Like, you really really can't.
Like, I know like a lot of people don't
like him, but think about it, bro. He's
been to he's been to Thailand three
times and he's now living there.
[ __ ] hell, bro. Like, you can't fault
the guy. Really, if you think about it,
think of what he was like when he was
first on here. Yeah.
But I guess I was just [ __ ] in denial
as well probably in many ways just
thinking that it was going to be different. But
it's not. I used to think, oh yeah, but
maybe Ant-Man's a bit like creepy or I
don't know. Not not to sound like I was
better than him, but maybe
like say that like I don't know, bro.
Just different than him. And maybe I
thought like I didn't have to go and do
it. I guess I was also in denial as
well, thinking that I wouldn't have to
leave this country.
You know, a small part of me was really
hoping that, you know, like, yeah,
eventually it's going to change and but
no, it doesn't.
It really doesn't change here in the slightest.
Sad, bro. Very sad.
See that? Say I'd be happy with her.
That one that Muslim to be honest, I'd
be happy with her.
Even if you didn't have sex for like 2
months, I don't care about that. But you
can't even get [ __ ] anything from
anyone. That's the thing.
It It is bad, bro. It
come away. pain is horrible, man.
But you can hate him, but you can't say.
But think about how he was on YouTube
years ago, bro. And now he's in [ __ ]
Thailand. He's living there. Like, think
about it, bro. If you compare it to
other people on here, they're doing the same [ __ ]
on here still projecting.
And look where he was, bro. He was
eating cold beans out of a tin. Now he's
in Thailand living there where these
people are still doing the same old [ __ ]
as they were years ago self projecting
like that [ __ ] Terry weasel
like that Terry bro he's a [ __ ] weasel bro
I need to be careful what I send on
Instagram cuz we got that [ __ ] Dam Thompson stalker Yeah,
we're [ __ ] weirdos on here, bro. Weirdos, man.
That's what I'm saying, bro. Like, look
at where he is now. Back when where he
was, what he was doing.
That should motivate you, bro. Anyone,
you know, even if you hate him, bro,
it's still a good thing, you know. >> Yeah.
Yeah. This guy called Andy was ignoring
me on Instagram. from Steven Howard. I
said, "Oh, you still an ignorer." Yeah, man.
But with that Jamie Thompson, you've got
to understand it. It comes down to jealousy,
you know? It comes down to [ __ ]
jealousy, bro. Like, think of it. Yeah.
Even now, you say you get a grand a
month. Yeah. It was like £1,100 a month.
You got no outgoings. Yeah. Think about
it, bro. You can do what you want.
You're better looking than them. you
have a better life than them. And they
can't stand it. And that's why they do
what they they do every day on this YouTube.
The whole like stalking and that because
it's it is jealousy. They don't want to
admit it to themselves, but it is
jealousy, bro. That's literally one of
the main things it comes down to in this
community is jealousy. Hate and
Nothing else, bro.
And then they're mad as well. But [ __ ]
why would a married man be stalking
another man all day on YouTube? Ask
yourself the question, bro.
He's not better than me, bro. That's why
he stalks me every day.
Because he's not better than me. He
wants to be me.
Yeah, you know what I mean? But [ __ ] I
need to get that new Samsung fold
Steven, but I don't really want to pay
£500 out right for it, bro.
I can get a 2-year contract and pay like
£94 a month, but I've got to pay like
£500 up front. I mean, I don't really
want to I don't really want to do that, you know? Yeah. [ __ ] Oh [ __ ]
Oh [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] Where?
I don't know where he's from. I don't
know where he's from, bro.
Not this planet, bro.
Yeah, you're talking about yourself
again. See what I mean? All of all of
this is just self-p projecting.
I think their disabilities get you
confused with themselves.
Like they are literally
just talking about themselves
every day. They're just talking about
themselves because if they're not
talking Okay. Okay, if they're not
talking about themselves, let me ask you
this question then. Why are they sat on
YouTube all day every day? Think about
it, bro. You know what somebody said to
me today, Steven Allen? I told them
about like I met like a few different
people and stuff
and you know when you talk and you're
drunk, right, and you just exchange
numbers to to make more connections,
right? And you know them being immature.
Oh, that's gay getting the guy's number.
That's gay. Well, no, it's really not.
People do it for various different
reasons, right? But then I turned around
and said, well,
I turned around and said, okay, so what
about you people talking to men on
YouTube every day then sat on YouTube
all day talking to men?
So, yeah. Okay. I was speaking to women.
I was speaking to some men. Okay, fair
enough. What? You're sat talking to men
all day on YouTube? They couldn't answer me.
They can't answer me, bro.
Listen, Steven Howard, I don't know what
he's got to do with this community.
Listen, these people on here, they are
on £300 a month. They're not even on
£1,000, £1,100 a month. To be honest,
that's not even bad compared compared to
some what these people get. But trust
me, bro, these people are on that
universal credit. I'm telling you, bro.
I'm telling you. Because if their lives
are so much better, why are they sat on
YouTube all day every day? No one can
answer it. Literally, not one person can answer it,
you know? So, it's just like it doesn't
make any sense. All of this money,
better life. Why are they the ones sat
on YouTube every day then?
That's the way I see it.
So, I was out all day yesterday. are
[ __ ] busy today as well.
They sit on YouTube because they ain't
got a life. That's what it is.
Little keyboard warriors. Angry
40year-olds. That's what they are.
Bitter, angry 40year-olds.
They ain't got a life.
Am I lying?
They're in They are in denial. They're
in denial about their own lives. That's
what it is. you know.
So yeah, I said, "Okay, what?" So I got
a few guys numbers to make connections.
Okay, but don't you sit on YouTube? And
then and then also what I said, Stephen
Howard was, um, okay, what about LJ
going to another country to meet men?
I've never gone to another country to
meet a man ever in my life.
And they said, "Oh, well, didn't you go
to Amsterdam to meet a man?" I was like,
"Well, no. I went to Amsterdam to go on
holiday." Literally travels
to meet men in in a different country.
Literally a different [ __ ] country.
Imagine that, bro. [ __ ] another country
to meet a man.
And they're talking about somebody in a
pub getting pissed up just [ __ ] uh
exchanging numbers. Yeah, I met somebody
from Manchester. I met some people from
Birmingham. Yeah, it's called [ __ ] socializing.
What the [ __ ] But yeah,
but I would never travel to another
country to meet a man. That is some
batty boy [ __ ] Batty boy [ __ ] bro. No
way. No [ __ ] way. That is [ __ ] weird, bro.
Like all them times I used to go to
Scotland and that I just went [ __ ]
you know what I mean? I just went cuz I
I went to Birmingham before to meet
Money Mike but that was when I was
younger bro and I didn't really have any
friends and I did leave the country and
it was more like I wanted to go there
anyways sort of thing but he goes to
different countries to meet men at his
age. He's [ __ ] weird bro. He is. That is weird.
That just that just tells you he's a loner. So yeah,
everything is just about their own life.
Just about their own life, bro.
That's all, bro. No hard feelings. Yep.
Hopefully we can try and get a meat.
I got one reply, but yeah, man.
I can't wait until the football starts,
bro. I'm going to win some money on that football, bro.
I'll probably put like 150 on two teams.
I don't gamble anymore, but I will
gamble the football. Defo, bro.
When that football comes out. Oh, [ __ ]
I only wear shorts and a t-shirt and a
cap nowadays because it's so um
um what's the word? It's so uh
it's so muggy outside. So yeah,
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Can't believe she blocked me. I bought a
baby Guinness to come.
[ __ ] hell. It's so weird how people
can be so different when they're sober
than when they're drunk.
It's so weird, isn't it?
I'll probably put like 150 on two teams.
It probably be the only way to make
money is football to be fair. Horrible man.
Do you remember when people trying to
get me kicked out of the pubs? It's so
weird. That is so stupid, bro.
I can't believe somebody would actually
do that. It's so weird. Uh
yeah, pretty much. But not on slots,
only like football. That's why I'll be
betting on the football again. That's if
I don't have a job by then. I'll
probably have to do that.
But I'm all right. I've got money. I've
got savings. We're We're talking ahead.
Oh, you just save benefits. That is
literally the only way. What's the
point? Oh, you never guess what happened
yesterday, Nicolo, man. [ __ ] me. You
wouldn't even believe it.
No, you wouldn't even believe the day I
had yesterday, bro. It was [ __ ] mad.
It was the maddest one I had for for a
while. I just come back from the pictures, actually.
I was mad yesterday. I bumped into that
Pakistani girl that ghosted me.
Yeah. She just looking I went to
approach her and it was her. I didn't
even realize. Not that I care. Like I
was saying, I [ __ ] approached you.
You ghosted me. You're not You're not
with me. I can talk to who I want. Yeah,
it was proper awkward, bro.
Did you manage to um
nah, most of it was the same old
boyfriend? Not interested.
Um I got three numbers, only one replied.
Met some lads. We had a great laugh. Um
then um yeah, I went to approach someone
and it turned out to be that Pakistani girl.
It was proper awkward and we started
talking for like an hour and she still
was full of [ __ ] as she always was.
Nah, it was quite bad, bro. It was it was Yeah.
Just just same old England, isn't it?
Like what Antman says, not interested in this country.
Simple as that. Oh, [ __ ]
I know you're taking a piss, but it's
true though. Yeah, you're taking a piss
out of it and you're laughing at it. But
it is true though. It is the truth. It
is the truth. Bro,
I was lucky to get one message back.
You're not not going to believe this. I
met somebody. They were from Ukraine.
And I said to him, "Oh, what do you do
for work?" So, I work at TK Maxx. He
said it like ashamedly. I said, "It's
nothing to be ashamed of. It's a job is
a job. It is what it is." And I said,
"Oh, which one? Was it like the Tnical Road one?"
She said, "The Stratford one." I was like, "What?
I live in Stratford?" I said, "Oh,
where? Where?" She said, "So does she."
I was like, "Oh, really? What what
Strapford do you live at?
Um she was like um Maryland. I was like
no way. I what you live in Maryland?
That's where I live. Like any anyone
would think it was you was making it up,
bro. Um and then I said, "Well, how old
are you?" And they said, "27." I was
like, "No way, bro. This is [ __ ]
getting weirder and weirder and
weirder." Got their number. They didn't
reply. So stay old in it.
I'm not complaining about it, Nicolo.
I'm just not in denial.
I'm just not in denial to
to um not basically voice how [ __ ] up
it is. Cuz that Indonesian guy, he's in denial.
Like he calls me negative and he doesn't
even approach anyone. That's what I
don't understand. like he he's scared to
approach anyone and then he's trying to
say that oh you're negative but oh you
know you you go out and have fun which
is yeah you should go out and have fun.
I was going out and having fun. I went
out yesterday to have fun and I needed a
haircut anyways cuz I looking homeless.
Yeah, but at the same time you also have
to acknowledge how [ __ ] up it is.
That's that's that's the whole point of
not being in denial, bro. It's not
funny. It's He's in denial.
He is just in the Nile, bro.
Like, no, don't get No, I I'll tell you
why I went out yesterday, Nichol. I went
out because I was under so much stress
and all of the things now is just a
waiting game. So, now I've got no
responsibilities. Don't have the house.
I'm a free man. I've got no
responsibilities. I've got savings. So,
I thought, you know what? I need to go
get my haircut anyways. and I just fancy
a drink. I went out cuz I wanted to go
out, but obviously I was still going to
speak to women when I was out. I only
done one sober because I couldn't be
bothered doing any more sober.
But either way, he's in denial.
That's what it is. He's literally I've
never known someone so scared like him.
I used to go out with like the tenants
and that and even they would do it and
they don't drink cuz they're Muslims. So
he is in denial, bro. very very in denial.
But yeah, it does predict your future.
Your past does dictate your future with
women in this country. It definitely
definitely definitely does. Think of it,
Nicolo. Yeah. Do you really think I care
about money? Yeah, I might have lost some money.
Yeah, you might have lost some money,
but money comes and goes. you might win
a football bet. Like, who really knows
what's around the corner? Think of our
life. 1 year, 2 years, 3 years, how it's
all changed. We've got savings and it
was going to happen anyways. No one
really can predict the future. But with
women, you can because one day you're
not just going to wake up and people are
just going to start being interested and
stop pretending they've got boyfriends
and give you. It doesn't work like that
because if it did, it would have
happened by now.
Oh, cuz he was causing a madness in the
house. I was knocking the door. He's,
"Oh, you're going to hurt me. You're
going to hurt me." I said, "I'm not. Let
me in so I can get my stuff." Cuz I uh
he was trying to cause madness and I I
lost my key. Remember I lost my key in
Wembley. I said, "I'm not going to hurt
you. Just let me just come let me in the [ __ ] house,
bro. A madness, bro. It's all over now." Anyways,
yeah, with the whole women thing, you
can predict your future.
The Sorry, the the the past does dictate
your future. My bad
cuz it's still going on. It's still happening.
So, and obviously I've got a pass with
it like the traveling and that. So, no. No,
no. He said he's going to call me, but
when he invites me, I was I was going to
say I'm not going to go, but I am going
to go. I am I am actually going to go to
that interview and I'm just going to
keep going on about what I've reported
and they've done nothing about it. So, I
am actually I am going to go. I'm
actually definitely going to go and I'm
just going to keep going on about you've
not done anything about things I've
reported and I'm just going to keep
going on about me.
So I'll say to him, I'll come. It's not
a problem. I'll come, but I just know
what's going to happen. You know,
we're sick of you [ __ ] racist [ __ ]
pigs in your favorites. It doesn't mind nothing.
It's bad enough you can't even get
[ __ ] housed unless you're [ __ ]
African, you know? It's like,
but I will go 100%. I'll go, but I would
just keep going on about me me me me me
me me me me me me me me me me me me me
me me me me me me me me me me me me.
That's all I'm going to do.
cuz you're [ __ ] pissing me off now.
You know what I mean? [ __ ] racist pigs.
We were just talking about me and Steven
how I think it's wrong how they put a
woman with a child as priority when it's
it's a child to it's a choice to have a child,
you know, whereas it's not choice to be [ __ ] disabled.
But they don't even consider that.
Obviously, you lie down fick on them,
they don't care. They don't give a [ __ ]
Obviously, I just lined it down thick on
them. I exaggerated it, obviously. But
it doesn't matter, bro.
No, I told them I had a foot condition.
I told them I was [ __ ] disabled. And
they just don't care. They Unless you're
African, they don't care. Like, not even
Jamaican, not even Pakistani.
Not only African. Unless you're African,
mate, they don't give a [ __ ] That's not
racing. That's facts. Anyone Anyone will
tell you the same [ __ ]
And we was just talking about how
Bomb used to say, "Oh, you know, you can
go out and and they'll pay it." No, they
won't because they will only pay it to a
certain amount, which is what, maybe
a,000 £1,000 maybe. And good luck trying
to get a property in London for £1,000.
So, he doesn't know anything, mate.
Um, yeah, but he pays for it.
He pays for it. And I think he got a
bidding thing. But in terms of like
emergency accommodation, right, you
won't unless you're African, they don't care.
Like and that's that's facts. That is facts, bro. [ __ ] me.
So yeah, they couldn't answer my
question as well. though I mean
that's why all of them are African the
workers and stuff
about the foot condition they don't give
a [ __ ] they don't give a [ __ ] look at
most of the people that are on the
street now they're all English people
which I am English I am white
I am what I'm call Turkish but I am
white most of me is white. So therefore
I am white. If you want to get technical
about it, I'm English.
Whereas these people that for example
are from Pakistan, which I've got Muslim
friends, they're not they're not
English. No, no. I I am because my dad
was English. My mom's half Turkish.
She's born here. She's been here whole
life. And she's never spoke Turkish. And
my granddad spoke English. And my
grandma spoke English. And my grandma
was white. So, I'm I'm actually English
if you want to actually get technical
about it. So, there you go. You might
look more Turkish than you are, but
you're technically not. You're white.
So, that's it.
That's why it's so hard trying to
explain this stuff to people.
So, you are English. You're white. I
mean, I got a UK passport.
So, I mean,
I am white. I am definitely definitely English.
I've got Pakistan friends, bro. I don't,
you know, I'm [ __ ] I'm not racist,
but I'm saying my It's very hard to try
to explain this to people. When somebody
from Pakistan, right, for example, they
say that they're English. Yeah. They
will be from Pakistan. Let's just use
them as an example. And their family is
from there. So to me, you're not from
England because your family are not from
England. And it's not spoken in your
language. it's not spoken in your
household. Whereas me, it was always
spoken in my household. And my mom's not
Muslim. My dad's not Muslim. And my
granddad wasn't Muslim for my my
understanding. So even though he was
supposed to be and obviously Yeah. So
no, I'm not from Pakistan, bro. You deaf.
I just I just gave you an example. But
you people on here are really stupid.
Some of you, man. Really? But yeah, you
are you're definitely white. You're definitely English.
You just take after your mom's side
more. It happens, you know. But yeah,
they don't help, mate. My My mom was my
mom was has been trying to sort out for
me, which is why I went out cuz I
couldn't be listening to it. It's just
it was doing my head and that's why I
went out drinking.
No, none of my family are Muslim.
I've got Muslim I got Muslim friends.
None of my family are Muslim. None of them.
And I'm so little Turkish, I might as
well not even be Turkish. So,
it's weird. And that's why I think
another another problem with the dating
is is obviously cuz I look more Turkish
than I am. So, they're actually racist themselves. Christian,
I'm not Christian. I'm atheist.
There's not helpful ones. We were just
getting the same old. There's not
helpful ones, mate. Unless you're African,
they don't care.
Like, the only thing they're going to do
is put you in a hostel. That's it.
They're not alpha ones. They literally
do not care. Unless you're African or
you're a woman with a kid, they don't care.
Which is what I was trying to explain to
this stupid bomb mug before, but he
wouldn't listen. They don't give a [ __ ]
bro. You could have no legs and they wouldn't care. Nope.
But that's all. So yeah,
but that's probably why you struggle
with dating as well cuz of your because
of what race you look like cuz obviously they're racist.
So that's that's probably another reason
as well to be honest.
But they don't give a [ __ ] Nicolo, bro,
you could have no legs. They wouldn't care.
No. No. They wouldn't help Venom. They
help African people.
They they they would only help African
people. He's Jamaican. They're not going
to help a Jamaican person. They'll help
you if you're African.
Yeah, they are. Because I I notice it,
bro. Cuz you're decent looking, you
smell good, you still got money, and you
still can't find anyone. It is your
race. Of course, it's your race. Well, I
mean, even though you're caught Turkish,
but you look more than you are. So,
that's what I noticed. Like, you either
have to be black or white.
That's the thing.
Even though like being Chinese or Indian
is probably worse, but your race where
basically no one gets with like not um
how to explain it. You're like you're
basically like a nationality that no one
gets with basically.
That's why you don't really see many
Asian people, women, Asian guys with
white women. You only see it in
Birmingham. You don't see it here.
Cuz here you can't get with white.
You can't get with Indian
cuz obviously white people prefer white
people or black people. So you can't get
with that. So
you're basically you're basically [ __ ]
Maybe Albanian, maybe.
No, they don't help Pakistani people
either to be fair. They don't even help them. So
probably that Pakistani again. Yeah.
Yeah. It's weird.
They don't help them, mate. They help
Africans. They don't, bro. They don't
help them because the tenants were
Pakistan and they never got no help. One
of them is still homeless.
They don't help them, mate. They [ __ ]
don't, mate. You don't understand what
they they used to do. Yeah. They used to
pay me rent and then they'd be skinned
for a month. This is what they used to
do. They used to get £600 a month. maybe
about £700 a month.
They used to pay me rent, then they
would send money back home, and then
they would be skinned again for another
month. They they don't get help help
like you think they do. They had
nothing. Literally nothing.
Like even now, I'm not on I'm not even
on like a lot of money, but I'm on I
don't have any outgoings.
So, mate, they they don't have what you
think they have.
And I used to say to them as well, like,
what what are you gaining from being here?
That's what I used to ask like seems
like a struggle every month cuz I'm not
going to struggle every month. I mean,
I'm not going to have as much money
coming in, but I've still got savings.
I'm not going to struggle. Um,
they're not going to give you it.
So they're not going to give you it,
bro. Did you not just listen to what I
was just basically saying for the past 10 minutes? So
yeah, they're not going to they're not
going to give you anything, bro. So
unless you're African. Bum bum.
So yeah, they don't have anything, mate.
I used to think that to be honest.
I tried once. My mom was literally on
the phone for the past 3 days.
So no, we didn't just try once. She tried continuously.
So no, she tried more than once. She was
being thrown to pillar to post to pillar
to post to pillar to post. And what they
basically said is they can offer you
like a hostel or
a shared accommodation. They said,
well, obviously we're appealing it, but
yeah, it's it's not as easy as that.
It's not as easy as that. So, yeah.
Anyways, let's not talk about this for
now, bro. It's it was giving me a
headache yesterday. This is what this
one of the reasons I went out drinking.
I met a lovely little lad from Kenny
Minister Nikolai. He's a lovely little fella.
He had a He had a block a black country
action. A bit he speaks a bit like this
is from the black country. He speaks a
bit with this. They speak a bit like
Yeah, that's how they talk, bro.
Why? Why? Why did I go for that? Uh
because you wouldn't be able to make
money from it.
That's how they talk. Very deep. But
yeah, it was a great laugh yesterday. A great laugh.
Antman said that if he stayed in his
country, he would have ended up raing
someone. He's [ __ ] in it. Yeah.
Uh I do and I I do want a place for myself.
They all speak a bit like this from W.
It's a very It's a very Yeah, they talk
they talk like that a bit.
But he he's a pretty cool [ __ ] you know.
Yeah, he's he's a good [ __ ] He is.
Yeah, he's a good [ __ ] bro.
He was a nice laugh. They bought me
around. I bought them around.
Yeah, man. It was fun.
You know what we was talking about?
We was talking about, you know, Virgin
Boy. Yeah. When he always hates that
people live with their mom and stuff. We
were talking about how it all stems from
childhood cuz you know where his mom
used to starve him and stuff and he had
no mother figure.
It really [ __ ] with his head.
with me and Steven was talking about
that. Like with with me,
my dad was around a little bit, but then
he died. But I feel like your your
mother, you have a different
relationship because your mother carries
you for 9 months. So I mean like I feel
like your mother is more important than your dad, you know?
So where I was eating a lamb shank
today, Nicolo. Like I was having my mom
made me two lamb shanks. I could only
finish one. And I was like, "Shit, I'm
eating this lamb shank." Yeah. With
[ __ ] mash and and and virgin boy's
mom used to starve him.
That's why he hates people living with
their mom and and seeing their mom and stuff. Yeah.
To be honest with you, I'm out most
today anyways, so it doesn't even matter
who the [ __ ] I live with to be fair.
And he project and that's why he stalks.
And I was saying to Steven Howard as
well, yeah, let's just say that I did
lie about sleeping with Morgan. Let's
just say that I did lie about sleeping
with all of these people, which I'm not,
right? Well, obviously I'm not [ __ ]
lying, but let's just say, for example,
you was telling lies. Why is he asked?
Why does he feel the need to constantly
get validation that you ain't done
anything with these women? It's cuz he's
a big fat virgin himself. It makes
sense. He is a big virgin. Like, ask my
mom. Yeah, he used to when I used to
tell him about these escort stories, he
wouldn't believe it. He used to say,
"Nah, it never happened. That never
happened. That never happened." Even
before I started like meeting like
people normally and [ __ ] Yeah. That's
because he's a virgin himself. That's
why. It's cuz he's a virgin. get laid.
I just think he needs to get laid to be
honest with you, Nicolola. I think once
he gets laid, he'll be a better person.
I think he need I think he just needs to
get laid to be fair. Yeah.
You remember the dates I used to go
Nicolo? Man, it's funny, isn't it?
Sometimes I think of you. I was in a
cinema today. I didn't think of Did I
think of USA today? I think I did. No.
Yeah, I think I did to be fair
saying that they missed the home.
How can he be my daddy? He's black. And
that's not like racism to black people.
I'm not racist, but I'm just saying I'm
stating the obvious.
They are that is that is who they favor sadly. Yeah.
But yeah, they don't It's mad how you
don't even get help. It's It's mad how
you don't even get help in your own
country. Do you not think that's [ __ ] up? Like,
oh, I can't be bothered talking about it
now. Just guys messaging me. Just give
it a rest. Yeah. [ __ ] hell, bro.
today. I think I found a new daddy from Birmingham. One's 41, one's uh
one's um one's 41 and one's 30. So, it
looks like I'm going to be going into care soon.
I'll be going into care soon. If I don't get housed,
I'll be I'll be in care at a very young
age. Yeah. I'll be put into care.
That's just so annoying, bro. That I
I'll [ __ ] go to Glasgow and I'll
never [ __ ] know where that Tam is.
That's [ __ ] annoying.
But I found a new daddy from Birmingham anyway. Suck. Yeah.
Yeah. I found a new dada.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
But yeah, the whole money the whole
money thing didn't even really bother me that much.
Not really, bro.
It sounds mad, but it's like, okay,
yeah, you might not get as much, but you
you don't have any outgoings. You know,
you're going to make money again
eventually. Like, it's only is not
really a problem. It's not like you've
not had the high life a million times.
It's not like you, you know, you you
don't have designer clothes. What are
you doing? You're leaving anyways. So,
it's like we'll make money on that
football anyways, bro. Don't worry. When
that comes, I'll be making money on the
football again. Trust me, bro.
Trust me. Money ain't a Money ain't a
problem, bro. Really,
comes and goes. It's not anything.
Yeah, I had a tenant saying that they
miss me and [ __ ] Nicola.
Yeah, it was emotional, bro. It was really bad,
dude. That was one of the worst things as well.
The money and that it's not really like
it's you're just back to reality.
That's what I was saying. You're not
you're you're not [ __ ] You're just
back to reality.
You're not you're not in La La Land
anymore. You know, where you have money
coming out your ass. You're just back to
reality and you're probably still going
to be better off than most people
anyways. So, you're just back to
reality, that's all. You're just back to
reality. You're not going to be rich.
You're not going to be skin. You're just
going to be normal. That's it. No more
La La Land.
That was La La Land them three years,
bro. Telling you. So, yeah. Yeah.
It's [ __ ] up though, man. It's [ __ ] up.
Yeah, I'll be out tomorrow. Get rejected.
Getting rejected by women. Come back on
what's important. Oh,
yeah. I'm just in reality now. I'm just
This is just reality. Not [ __ ] not
rich, not poor. I've got savings. It's just reality.
You're just reality. It's just reality
now. You're just like a normal person.
It's all you are. Well, I bought a new
TV, by the way. I had to reby the telly.
I do need to get that fold phone,
though. But see, I'm thinking I I want
another way to make like £500. But I
can't think of any. I've got the money.
I've got the money. Of course, I've got
the money, bro. I've got savings app.
It's like I wish there was a way to just
make a quick 500, but and I ain't
getting into gambling again. So,
just hope one of these jobs get back to
me, man. But
no, what I don't understand is that like how Joe
like how Joe Yeah. says that the past
doesn't dictate your future when it
comes to dating in this country. I don't
know how he possibly
can say that after all I've tried yet,
all of the places I've been to. I
[ __ ] went to Wales twice in one in
two weeks before,
but he doesn't seem to think after all of that
that it predicts
it does predict your it does predict
your future. What the [ __ ] How can it not?
How could it not, bro? It What? One day
we go out, it's all of a sudden going to be different. No,
to be honest with you, the only reason
I'm probably trying is cuz I'm bored.
Like, if you if you want the God's
honest truth here, I I'll tell you a few
reasons why. A, I like to go out for
drinking. I'm under stress at the
minute. B, I've got nothing better to
do. If one of these jobs got back to me,
I'd be working and [ __ ] off again.
It is probably just boring.
I think it generally is something just to do.
As as mad as that sounds,
it's boring as [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying? That's bored.
What am I going to sit at home and and
drive myself mad? [ __ ] that.
We'll never change in this country. Never.
Prove me wrong. Prove me wrong, bro. And
I take about everything I say. Yeah.
Of course it predicts your future.
It's the same old. You remember we used
to do Thursday till Sunday, bro.
Do you remember Nicola old train
the [ __ ] you want about?
Do you remember USA is he Nicolo and her boobies?
See you can't even get anything like that anymore.
It's not like you can go out and
actually get laid or get dates. You
can't get nothing.
And it's been going on for 3 years as
well. It has been going on for years.
It's not been 6 months. It's been going
on for years now.
Yeah, I do.
And it's just never going to change,
bro. Yeah, I done a few escorts the
other day, Fruity. Yeah, bro.
But the only thing with escorts is they
don't let you come in their mouth. most of them.
So, I just have to I I'm used to getting sex now.
Yeah, I [ __ ] one last week
and then the week before that as well.
I can't be bothered arguing. I don't
even like the sex. I just like the
[ __ ] me, but if they don't let you
come in their mouth, I just get a
[ __ ] and then just [ __ ] them. Simple.
I don't know why they would let you come
in their mouth. There's nothing wrong with come.
It's not that bad. [ __ ] sake.
It's weird, isn't it?
But yeah, when I was working, I didn't
even try. I just used escort me to be
honest. I only try cuz I've got nothing
better to do. So,
literally, I wasn't even trying when I
when I was working. I was just using escorts. So,
oh, I just bang my [ __ ] head on the wall. [ __ ] Oh, [ __ ]
Anyone would think you're fat and ugly,
Nicolo. Anyone would think you're fat
and ugly like bomb. The way you get
treated like in this country, eh,
I took some cocoon more, man. It makes
you so high. I love it, man. Yeah.
Yeah. You can't even [ __ ] probably
come the virgin, but he beats it so much
cuz he can't get laid. Oh,
USA is he
like USA is he?
She was so weird, wasn't she?
Do you know what? I never really had
someone just ghost like her. Never, bro.
I've never had that since or before.
She [ __ ] must have been cheating on
someone, bro. 100%.
She gave it, but she couldn't to She
gave it, but she couldn't take it. Could
would go around being a [ __ ] but then
when it when it came back at her, she
didn't like it. Yeah.
[ __ ] [ __ ] mate.
Yeah, proper trump. Where?
Do you remember? You'll be my 25th. Oh
my [ __ ] god, bro. I thought I was in
a horror film, bro. I swear down.
Well, I could beat her new boyfriend up.
Well, I believe it because I'm I'm
living it, Nicolo. I'm I I believe it
because I'm living it.
I believe it because I'm living it. So, yeah.
I could beat her new boyfriend up.
Maybe nowadays I don't go gym and that.
Do you remember the neighbor Nicola? N I
don't I don't bother with the neighbors
and [ __ ] for my mom's sake and that I
can't be asked. I don't want to give
people excuses and [ __ ]
the neighbor and that man.
No. Well, you're just being negative, Nicolola.
Like, tomorrow when I go out, I'm going
to meet someone. Why are you being
negative, bro? Your past don't dictate your future.
I mean, yeah, it's been going on for 3
years, and yeah, you always go out and
it's the same. It's the same old, but
tomorrow is going to be completely different.
You're just being negative like all of a
sudden tomorrow no one's going to be
stuck up. Everyone's going to be
interested. No one's going to pretend
they've got I mean, yeah, it it hasn't
happened for 3 years,
but you're just being negative.
Everything's going to change tomorrow
because your past don't dictate your future. So,
you have to keep trying. You know what
I'm saying? I mean, yeah, I've been to
Wales three times. I've been to
Scotland. I've been all over England and
I'm still single. But that's maybe because
I don't know, maybe it was just not the
right time. But trust me, eventually you
will meet someone.
[ __ ] But um yeah, tomorrow will be
completely different. I might even bring
you along with me.
You're just negative. Yeah.
Oh, I miss that 19year-old when she used
to come around and suck my dick, man. It was nice.
It was nice, bro.
She actually looked good as well. She
wasn't even ugly. and she looked better
when she gained weight, but she just
became too entitled
and she kept wanting money. I said,
"Fuck off. Go get your own money, you cunt." So yeah,
I just say to the [ __ ] that you
swallowed my babies.
I can just say to her, "You swallowed my babies, bitch." So yeah.
And that only fans one. Do you remember
that Only Fans one?
I always used to bring her to my moms. I
used to just [ __ ] her, bro. Oh man. Yeah.
I bought us a [ __ ] Chinese.
Yeah. She used to come around when the
tenants were there and that in it. I
used to invite around and she used to
just suck my todd. Yeah.
Yeah. It will never change in this country.
I used to like her when she used to suck my todd.
What do you think, Nicolola?
Yeah, it was cute, man. Those
were the days.
I don't know why no one likes sucking toddes.
It's actually better than sex.
Do you remember Scott Nicolo?
Do you remember Scott?
Yeah. Once I start this working, I'll
just use escorts.
Yep. Well, to be honest with you, I did
have other chances like Nottingham and Sig, but
and that one cuz I used to just go out
on the dates
um talking about USA, but that was back
then. I mean, I did have chances back
two years ago, but now you can't get
nothing. It's gotten worse. It has
gotten worse. It has definitely gotten
And obviously that one that I met on
Bumble, but that was years ago. Now you
can't even get nothing.
It's funny cuz when you're actually
ready to to to now meet people, you
can't. But when you're not and you're
still [ __ ] because of what someone
done to you, you meet all these people.
Now you you can't even meet anyone.
Can't even get a [ __ ] date for [ __ ]
sake. I can go on a date and spend two300.
It ain't a problem, bro. I got money,
but you you can't do it. Can't do it, mate.
It's better than that.
It is bad, man. One sec it.
I know it's bad, is it? Even the money
thing didn't work. I don't know how I
used to have the confidence to I don't
even have the confidence nowadays. I
don't think I don't I don't think it's
the confidence. I just don't think I
have the energy.
I just don't think I even have the
energy anymore, mate. Well, why would
you? You've tried You've tried more than
anyone in the world. The fact that
you're even still doing it, you're crazy, bro.
Loads of them are fat.
So, I think that person on Reddit was
right. Nicolo, what do you think?
They said maybe too many stuck up
[ __ ] in your country. I think so.
I think they're right now.
They said maybe too many stuck up
[ __ ] in your country. Well, obviously, bro.
And if you see if you look around and
you see women, you'll see that
judging by their face, they've all got
the same attitude.
They're all NPCs. They've all got the same attitude.
You see the same people. You see the
same attitude everywhere.
It's weird, is it?
USA is he had some nice booties, bro.
They have the same attitude. I can't I
can't explain it.
They're all stuck up. Yeah,
maybe I'll just go somewhere else
tomorrow. Just where have my little legs
take me? What do you think, Nicolai?
Where have my little legs take me? Eh, yeah.
You say easy
and saggy boobies. E,
do you remember when I was kissing
someone before Nicolo and I started to
feel something in my toger?
I started feeling something in my todding
clubs nowadays without getting kicked out.
I think that's why I just stick to pubs.
I just mainly uh I mainly just stick to pubs now. Um,
what they say they'd get with you.
Even though Spain is full of English people.
Yeah. They would they wouldn't reject
you. They would they would all get with
Can I show you something, Nicolo? Sir,
I need to find a tab.
One sec. Oh, [ __ ] me. I'm tired, bro.
I'm a bit hungry, you know.
Yep. And the maddest thing is not not
one of them women complained about me either.
Not one of them. Never had a woman
complain about me. Never out of all of
the people that I've approached.
But yeah, I know it is mad. I mean, I
know you're taking a piss and whatever,
but it is mad. I know you're taking a piss.
But it's true though, is it? It is true.
I'll do a video about this country when
I when I have time. Bro,
I kind like a Macadox.
I kind of feel like a McDonald's, you know.
You look at this. This is all all we
ever get. Nicola.
You know what I've never had which I'd
want is like a [ __ ] in the morning.
Never had a [ __ ] in the morning, bro.
Must be nice, eh?
I fancy a Big Mac. Anyone
else ever fancy a Big Mac? Let me see.
It's just the same road, is it?
That can't be 25. This is it.
No, it can't be.
Burger King is 24 hours.
Yeah. I always say I think you're cute.
Did I say I think you're cute or
That's why I stopped watching them
videos, bro. Cuz that I just Yeah.
That Burger King shot at 4:00 a.m. Does
it? What the [ __ ]
Maybe I'll get a Burger King.
I don't even know that really.
But after tomorrow, I really do need to
start saving some money, bro.
If I wanted to leave again.
Yeah, I'm going to get a bacon uh double
cheese XL burger.
I used to get the same burger as Bob.
Bacon cheese XL. You don't you don't
even need to remove anything.
Yeah. One second. I'm going to order
this Burger King.
It comes at 4:00 a.m. Jeez.
Did you used to like my approaches,
Nicol? I used to be a mad bastard in it,
doing them sober and all of that. Yeah. Crazy, eh?
Imagine Virgin Boy trying to do it.
[ __ ] hell. I can't imagine it.
Imagine Virgin Boy trying to do it. [ __ ] hell. Jesus.
You say Izzy had big boobies.
She had big boobies.
I was like, "Oh, bro." I was like, "Can
I see your boobs?
Is that cute, Nicolo?
The worst is when you watch a horror film.
Yeah, that but most but women hate all men.
Women hate most men though,
Nicolo. They hate you. They hate me.
They hate everyone.
It's not just me. They hate everyone.
They're just stuck up [ __ ] bro.
Let me get this burger. Anyways,
they hate you. They hate me. They hate
that black guy that does approaches.
Yeah, they hate you as well. Yeah.
They hate you. They hate Antman. They
hate me. They hate that black guy.
That black guy gets the same [ __ ] as well.
Yeah. They get with 10% of men.
Yeah. But the thing is they get with
like 10% of men
which is which says it all. Maybe 80%.
No, 20 10 20% says it all.
So yeah, they get with people, bro. But
they get with like 10 20% of people.
And yeah, that's what I mean. But I and
a lot of the people that are normal just got lucky.
They just got lucky. Do you know what I mean? So,
but yeah, they get with them kind of people.
That black guy goes around doing it and
he gets the same old [ __ ] as well.
Boyfriend, boyfriend, boyfriend.
Let me order this burger. Bro, you're
putting me off. One sec.
Yeah. I don't want the chips. I just
want the burger.
I like actually
just want a burger.
Want a burger, bro.
Saying that the coke probably [ __ ]
warm to be honest.
So, how do you meet someone in this
country then, Nicol? You can't
I don't think you can. Can you? No.
£14 for burger
and a drink.
Sounds good to me.
Can I ask you a question, Nicola? Why
does Virgin boy call me skin?
I'm not skin. Nah,
cuz they're not going to do that. So,
what's the point of asking them? Why
does Virgin Boy call me skin?
I don't understand that.
Yeah, I just bought the burger. Why does
Virgin Boy call me Skint, Nicolo?
Oh, [ __ ] I'm tired, bro.
Why? Why am I skint, bro? What the [ __ ]
Why does Virgin boy call me skin?
How can I be skint, bro? What the [ __ ]
Oh, honestly, ask me. Answer me. Why
does Virgin boy call me skin? Huh?
Yeah, he is skin. He's You remember when
he was showing £800 like he's got money
and you know a lot of the money that he
shows is well it's not anything anyways
is his dad money.
So sometimes his dad gives him money
when he sucks his dick but that's about
it. He ain't got no money. He ain't got
a pot to piss him.
He ain't even got a [ __ ] bed.
He is [ __ ] proper skin that kid.
Proper skin. Like even now, bro.
Uh you've never encountered them with uh
you you have encountered them problems.
That's why you date disabled people.
You literally have encountered them
problems, Virgin boy. which is why you
paid for dating apps and you only target
disabled people. You You literally have
encountered them problems, Mr. Ugly.
That's why you pray on vulnerable people.
Um, and you're in a dysfunctional
relationship where you don't even get
sex out of.
You're literally a virgin. Like, we're
not even saying that [ __ ] to to try to
annoy you or anything.
You literally are the definition of a virgin.
And and and actually, bro, I I don't I
don't judge you. Like, if I got abused
by my mother and I got starved by my
mother, I'd have some problems.
I'd have 32 [ __ ] minutes for a
[ __ ] burger. £40 for a burger and a drink.
Very normal working woman. Nothing
normal about the wolf. Looks like a
[ __ ] [ __ ] But that's even worse
to be honest in a relationship and you
still and you're still a virgin. That's crazy.
Then yes, you have encountered these
problems. That's why you pay for dating
apps. You was literally on about five
different dating apps. Let's listen to
this virgin, right? I have not
encountered any of these problems yet.
He was on four different dating apps.
Okay, bro. Go read back what you wrote.
You [ __ ] virgin. You need to get
laid. Literally, you need to get laid.
If you come out with me tomorrow, I help
you get laid so you can finally pop that virginity.
Same thing that I offered you last week,
but you wouldn't do it. And then you
tried getting me pub. You really think I
want to see you die a virgin?
Do you? I don't want you to die a
virgin. It's already bad enough being 31
and you still got that vcard. That
replay. Still a virgin. A [ __ ]
virgin. I don't want you to die. One,
I'm not going to stand here and let you
die a virgin. No [ __ ] way. You're
coming out with me tomorrow.
You're coming out with me tomorrow and
you're going to [ __ ] get laid, you [ __ ] virgin.
You [ __ ] virgin. You're going to get
[ __ ] laid, mate. I'm telling you.
I'm telling. And what was you? Why did
you say that you'd never wear the color
pink as well? You know, you're also
insecure about your sexuality as well.
which is the whole Cheryl Cole thing.
Copy that. Anything to follow a trend.
Bless you. You know, I just want to pick
you up and just rub you. You know that.
Anything to just follow the trend. You
wanted to fit in. You wanted to fit in
with the crowd. You're a little copycat.
I've had more women than you. And she
ain't [ __ ] nowhere near as good as
you're making out. And I've had more
women than you.
[ __ ] been laid more times than you
ever will. You [ __ ] virgin.
You're a copycat. You are proper proper
Proper proper proper copycat. You are
a proper copycat. You ain't got no mind
of your [ __ ] own.
No mind of your own, mate. [ __ ] hell.
You need to get laid. Honestly, you need
You really, really do need to get laid.
Yeah, you're a [ __ ] You're a proper
virgin. You are.
You're I brought it up to you because I
kept saying that people keep copying each other.
But no, you're you're you're you're a
[ __ ] virgin, mate. You're a [ __ ]
virgin. You know what? My mom cooked for
me some lamb shank.
But I bet your mom never never cooked
you any of that because she starved you.
You you you your mother starved you,
mate. Your mother Your mom starved you.
She literally starved you. You've never
had your mom cook you a l shank. Nah, mate.
Nah, mate. Never. You You was literally
obsessed with somebody in Canada.
Somebody in Canada. I used to have to
listen to your [ __ ] every [ __ ] time
about you're going to go to Canada and
how you made up a suicide story.
You You didn't even have the money to go to Canada. She
You can't go all the way to to to
Canada. You don't have the money. And
she's not interested in you.
Mate, I'd rather live with my mom than
live in a [ __ ] bed sit like [ __ ]
you, mate. And the only reason you
didn't live with your mom is cuz your
mom abused you again. Mommy problems.
You're projecting your mommy problems
onto me again. Yeah, but I'd rather
[ __ ] live with my mom that don't
starve me than live in a bedit like you.
Yeah, I literally would rather live with
my mom than live in a bedsit like you.
with no [ __ ] bed in it. [ __ ] any
day of the [ __ ] week. Might as well
be in a [ __ ] hostel. But again, it's
all mommy problems. All of this, you
live with your mom, it's all mommy
problems because your mommy starved you.
Your mom starved you and abused you. You
have mommy issues. It's no It's no
different than somebody that hasn't had
a father figure. A mother and son's bomb
bond is stronger than a father and son bond.
It's not like your your mom died. She
literally abused you.
She used to set the dog on you.
You was put into care at a very young
age because of it. You know that's
serious serious [ __ ] You was put into care. He
he was put he was put into care at a
very young age.
That's that serious [ __ ] He was put into care.
He was put into care at a very young age
because of it. So it's not like you your mom died.
Your mom actually abused you.
[ __ ] abused you, mate.
And then I know everything, mate.
Everything about your father. I know everything. And also,
you told me before that your um the
reason that you don't wear pink is
because your your dad wore pink once in
Manchester and he got attacked. He was
in the gay village and he and he and he got attacked.
Yeah, that's that's another thing I
forgot that you told me. Yeah, you got attacked.
in the gay village in uh Manchester wearing pink.
I know all of these things, you know.
Yeah, I know all of these things.
Pulled my [ __ ] off to Australia. No
one was going to find out what he done.
Filthy bastard. Filthy [ __ ] bastard.
Filthy filthy [ __ ]
Filthy, filthy, filthy bastard.
Mick Jonathan Robinson.
Predator, mate. [ __ ] Predator.
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] Predator, mate.
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] predator, mate.
Got your mom and she was 14.
14 years of age. That ain't on that,
mate. 14 years of [ __ ] age.
14 years of [ __ ] age, bro.
That ain't on.
What the [ __ ] does a [ __ ] 42y old
have in common with a 14y old
at a very young age because of it? Yeah. No. Oh,
was it wasn't you diagnosed with autism?
I'm pretty sure you was diagnosed with
autism, wasn't you? Bye-bye, mate.
See you later. Take a break.
That's how dedicated I am to these horror films. available
says that you've never encountered these
problems. That's because you've never
gone out and spoke to women because you
got no life experience.
That's why you've never encountered
these problems because you pay for dating apps.
Yeah, you would do if you lived in the
[ __ ] real world. Again, another one
who's in denial. You're [ __ ] in
denial, mate. That's what you are.
You know, all of these people that
pretend it isn't this way. They're just in denial.
They're just in denial, lying to themselves.
You know, they're in denial. work.
Like I said, this Indonesian fella,
it's just in the Nile.
What do you think, Steven? Yeah,
is in denial, bro. Definitely denial.
got like 70 pound in the draw as well. Yeah. [Music]
Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro.
Yeah, man. Why do people go on about
like living with people's moms and [ __ ]
They go on like it's it's [ __ ]
it's like it's actually relatively
normal nowadays. You know, a lot of
people that I meet live with still live
with their parents
or they even a [ __ ] box room. What
the [ __ ] bro?
That's definitely mommy issues. That is
definitely definitely mommy issues.
Who the [ __ ] is this weirdo?
Oh, you're also bold. You're also
projecting with the receding thing as well. Also projecting
[ __ ] My burger should be in a minute.
Yeah, man. [ __ ]
Oh, the charger here.
You don't know who you are, mate.
Old Skype chats. Don't know who the [ __ ]
you are, man. [ __ ]
Oh, do you remember that Canad Oh, do
you know what I noticed? Hey, do you
remember that um Canadian guy Chad when
uh Jaden tried exposing me? The guy that
I used to speak to in 2012 is I remember
Peter. You know what I've noticed with a
lot of these people from Skype, right?
So, you know how they were a few years
older than me? like I was like 14 and
they were 17, 18 and they used to try to
take the piss on that and then now
you're an adult when they don't want to
argue with someone that's an adult now.
I noticed that like cuz I'll just wreck
them in every argument
like Chad and
Oh no, that's that virgin. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye virgin. Can't pull the wood over
my eyes. [ __ ] off.
That's Virgin Boy. I can tell by the camera. Bye-bye.
So, uh, I noticed they were more than
happy to argue with a child, right? Or
somebody that they deem more intelligent
than, but when it's to do with arguing
with an adult, they don't want none of
it. I noticed that, [ __ ] [ __ ]
Cuz they know they can't win an argument
with a [ __ ] adult. That's what it is. [Music]
back with my little burger.
>> Yeah. So, they're not so big when
they're arguing with a [ __ ] adult, are they? No.
Yeah. That Chad guy from Canada. I used
to remember him.
You want none of it, mate.
No, you're not coming in. Bye-bye.
Not so big now, are you? You can't.
His name is Chad from Canada.
Quite sad what they used to do, you know.
Some of the things they used to say was pretty sick.
But they won't argue with that, mate.
They can't do it to someone they can't
bully. I noticed that.
used to say some sick [ __ ] bro.
Oh, this burger is lush. [ __ ] lush.
That's the prison.
I'm going to take the piss now. outside there.
[ __ ] off your [ __ ] version.
[ __ ] off, virgin. I knew it was you
trying to get in, you [ __ ] virgin.
[ __ ] off, you weirdo. Don't get laid.
Leave me alone, you [ __ ] virgin boy.
Now, this is another one right.
Claims they've got a girlfriend. Claims
they're not skin.
Claims that I'm this. claims I'm that,
but they're still obsessed with me every
day on YouTube.
Read into that what you will, man.
Comes down to real bad jealousy on this community.
Real real bad deep jealousy.
It's way that I can be jealous of
someone that they don't even really
know. Yeah, it's [ __ ] weird.
There's definitely some jealousy, but it
has to be.
for them to sit on here for years doing this.
They really are. I feel sorry for them,
but I couldn't imagine waking up every
day being jealous of someone. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye now, little fella. Bye-bye, mate. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye, little fella. [ __ ]
See, I'm having a piggy little I'm
having a a piggy burger.
So, obviously I'm not moving, am I? Hello.
[ __ ] snake, mate. [ __ ] dragon.
God bless you.
Leave me alone. You virgin. Oh,
it's wrapped up nicely.
Panda supporter. off. This country
that burger was delicious. They gave me
some free chips, but I don't like the chips.
I don't like the chipping.
[ __ ] That is spinning, bro. [ __ ] Oh [ __ ] That's SP.
imagine that e
and still a virgin. [ __ ] I could
imagine it. He used to drive me mad at [ __ ] 16.
Used to drive me man at [ __ ] 16.
I mean that still a virgin [ __ ] mate.
Wow. I am stuffed, mama.
I'm stuffed. Mama. Right.
I'm out of here. See you later.