So,
>> you can probably guess what they said to be fair.
>> Yeah, man. How we doing?
>> You can probably guess what they said.
Same old England. That's just going to
cut off like
this. I know.
will never change here. Your past can
change the future.
[ __ ] depressing. All right.
I just end
same old England where your past
where your [ __ ] past dictates your future.
Your past dictates your future when it
comes today in this country 1 million%.
[ __ ] 12 nil, bro. What the [ __ ]
>> We're like 12 nil. You can't even get
even get a conversation out of someone.
But don't forget, yeah, one day you're
not going to wake up and everything's
going to be perfect. Even though this
has been going on for 3 years and it is
continue to it is continuingly going on.
You're going to wake up one day and it's
going to be perfect.
[ __ ] go. I don't want Seriously, bro.
Bad bad bad. This country will never
change. The only the only time it will
change is when you get killed and then
you maybe there's some afterlife, but it
ain't changing here, mate. Never. Not
anytime soon. [ __ ] 12 to one. 12 to
one. I have this sorry 12 nil.
Basically, think about [ __ ] 12.
Same old England. It's not negative
saying it. It's not negative saying it.
This is the [ __ ] truth. The cold hard
truth. It's called not being in denial.
Hold on one second. One second. Let's
not even talk about what's the truth,
what's not the truth. Let's just say
we're not in denial.
It will never change.
Be denial. But
That's my friend. Let's go. Let's go.
Maybe 11. Maybe 11. I must know.
That's a good question
still happening. I think that is I think
it's a logical question.
It's a logical question. Yeah.
>> We've said it will never change in this
country. Never. [ __ ] never. Ever. Ever.
Never ever ever
said to my friend. And I said, "Have you
been dealing with this [ __ ] for years
that don't change? Have you been dealing
with this [ __ ] for [ __ ] years? The
same old boring in this country?" Yeah,
that's another question I want to answer
for. Have you been dealing with the same
old bore in England for years? No, you
haven't. The same old [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Second. Hold on a minute. One second.
Because it's the truth. Yeah.
You You can't answer it because it's the
[ __ ] truth. And why is this [ __ ] not
replying as well? I'm going to stick it
on her today as well. You told me you
was going to come out today. Yeah. I was
going out anyways. You were supposed to
come out today, [ __ ] Yeah. And you're
not out. And now you're trying to like listen.
I'm going to spam call this person, bro.
I'm going to spam call them. I swear to God,
>> I want someone to start me today, bro.
I'm waiting for someone to start me
today, G. I'm waiting for someone to
start me. I really, really am. I'm
waiting for someone to start me today, bro. Not even.
Yeah, you come out. What the [ __ ]
Same old England.
England will never change.
Always talk about how the past how the
past doesn't dictate the future. Yeah.
Your past don't dictate your future. So
they say this has been going on for
years and it is still happening and it
happened today as well. When does it
change? Come on. Come on. Let's start
talking about it now. Come on, bro.
But no one can answer because they know
I'm right. It's the truth. It will never
change for the hair. It will always be
the same old same old. Not interested
people. It would always be the same old diet now.
Bad bad bad sad sad sad life here in
England. I'm booking this flight, bro. [ __ ]
Literally, [ __ ] this. So, I'm booking
these flights later cuz I'm going to end
up doing something. I need to book these
flights in later.
I'm going to book these flights later.
I'm going to go to the ATM. I'm going to
have to cuz this is this is this is this
is sping out of control, bro. Yeah.
There's nothing wrong with you, man.
You're not [ __ ] You're not fat.
You're not ugly. There's nothing wrong
with you. There's literally nothing
wrong with you. Like, there's nothing
wrong with [ __ ] Timmy Aldridge. You understand?
They don't give you no answer. They're
all stuck up. That's the difference. And
when you got somebody trying to tell you
that this is going to change, it never
changes. It will never change. It has
never changed. And it will never change.
There's nothing wrong with you. Like
there's nothing wrong with the other 80
90% [ __ ] people. There's nothing
wrong with you. The way you look, the
way you talk, nothing. They're just all
stuck up. Simple as that. I'm booking
these flights. [ __ ] this.
pound. [ __ ] this man.
[ __ ] this one. Game of soldiers. [ __ ]
this. This ain't no life for any here.
This is no life for anyone in this.
It's no life for anyone here, mate.
There ain't no life for anyone here.
There's nothing wrong with you, mate.
Look, I'm wear my little cap.
I'm wearing my little cap today. Had to
change. It started raining. It started raining, bro.
I don't even think they know these things themselves.
things themselves. It's so stuck up.
They don't even know themselves. That's
how stuck up their brains they are.
They've got no substance.
They just copy each other. That's what
they [ __ ] do. Same old lookie. Look,
you look at Timmy.
You look at me. Yeah. Do I look anything
like Timmy? Do I act anything like
Timmy? No, I don't. Look at me. I would
say I'm relatively normal. Whatever the
[ __ ] normal means. And still nothing
changes in this country. Nothing is
about to change in this country. And it
ain't never changing in this country.
Yeah. Lisa, go tell that to the 12 women
that rejected me today. I'm booking
these flights when I get back.
I'm these flights when I get back. This
ain't no normal way for This ain't
normal for anyone. Lisa, this is not a
normal life for anyone. I'm out of here, mate.
Why? They land on the
Lisa. These people don't drag me now. No
one cares about these people. Why are
you talking about these people? Anyways,
people being go that tell that to the 12
women that rejected me today. Yeah, go
tell them that. No one cares about these
people, bro. Lisa, you don't need to
tell them. You don't need to tell me. Go
tell it to them women.
I'm I'm leaving this country. I'm I'm
out of here. [ __ ] this. This ain't no
life. Ain't no life in this country.
Ain't no life in this country, bro.
You don't need to tell me that. You
don't need to tell these people that.
You need to tell these stuck up women in
this country. That's that's the only
people need you need to be cuz no one's
talking about people's looks.
You need to tell these stuck up women.
You need to tell that woman in weather
spoons that for some reason can't give
me. Don't tell me that. There's no point
telling me I can't do anything about it.
I'm not brains. You know what I'm
saying? I'm trying to go tell it to
these [ __ ] women. Don't tell me. Don't
tell me. We can't do anything.
>> Yeah. Just like you, you little virgin.
You've been You've already been rejected
your whole life. In your 40s, ugly fact.
In your 40s. You've already been rejected. Yeah.
>> Lisa, listen. Yeah.
You've already been rejected. That's why
you're in your 40s. skin on YouTube.
Okay, Lisa, I'm lying. Okay. Okay. No,
it never happened. Lisa, I'm completely
lying. Just like I'm lying about
approaching that person right opposite
there. Yeah. Yep. I'm completely lying.
Yep. I've got nothing better for you to
lie. Yeah, I'm lying. Yep. I'm lying. Yeah.
Sure. Yep. I'm completely lying. Yep.
Oh, damn. You got me. I'm lying. Just
like that person right opposite me. I
didn't go to them like about 15 minutes
ago. I didn't go over and speak to them.
Now you're like, "Yeah, I'm lying."
Yeah. Well, at least they got me, man.
Yeah. Yeah. You got me. I'm completely lied. Yeah.
Yeah. You Yeah. I'm lying, aren't I?
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Listen, I'm live. Do I
need to do one live to show you? Like,
not right now. cuz there not many
people. But do you want me to come live
and show you
>> because you obviously don't believe me.
I don't know if it doesn't suit you to
believe me or whatever it is. Do you
want me to do it?
Go next slower and maybe do it.
You want me to do it? I I'll do it.
Done. I I'll do it. Yeah.
Lisa, it doesn't suit you.
I'm saying it doesn't suit you.
This is [ __ ] weird. It's not even
funny. It's [ __ ] weird. >> Um,
they can't even hear me, bro. Anyways,
I'm out of here, bro.
>> [ __ ] depressed. I need to book these
flight as I'm going to end up doing myself.
Like, if I don't book this flight today,
bro, I'm going to end up doing something
to myself. Ain't no normal way of
living. This ain't no life for anyone in
this country any father. I'm going to
move my money tomorrow and I'm pushing
these bikes on when I go back to booking it.
Anyways, I'm gone now. Maybe the rest of
my night and I'm booking these flights
when I come back. [ __ ] this. I'm booking
them today when I come back. This ain't
no life for anyone in this country. [ __ ]
this. Yeah. One time.