Oh, did you do my bed today?
>> Thank you.
You never know when you'll fall in B. [Music]
I'm so sad.
So sad, but I'm a bit much. Same old
England. [ __ ] hell. Is that what
they're charging nowadays? 35 [ __ ]
quid to get in.
Sounds like an England problem to me.
[ __ ] hell. Same old bor in England, eh?
never changes or never has and it never will.
Oh yeah, I forgot when the hell did I?
It's all right.
Yeah, man. It's all right, bro. I mean,
Yep. Same old England. 85 quid. Why
would you pay £30 to get in somewhere
when you could just pay like 70 school? Madness. Um,
I put that there.
But yeah, um, anyone that wants to ask
me how this is,
it's the same old England. I think I can
say that better than anyone else to be
fair. I'm booking these flights in a
minute. [ __ ] this.
One second, bro. I'm going to go to BA area. BA
National. They've all got boyfriends, lads.
Well, I think I got five numbers,
but nah. Same old I've got a boyfriend. Typical England.
Nonsense. I'm going to look up these
flights now, bro.
I don't say I'm going to do something
and don't do it. This This has got to
stop in this country, mate. This is This
is honestly [ __ ] horrendous. Oh [ __ ] One sec.
You know, they're trying to charge £35
to get clubs. I need out of it, bro. I
need out of this country ASAP. This
ain't no life. Trust me, this ain't no
life for anyone.
You see, even more so, I think I had one
rubbing coat to be fair. So,
it really, really, really doesn't
change. I'm not in denial. And you know
what I was saying to this guy in Canada?
From Canada. Yeah. I said, "You can keep
laughing, but you're just in denial.
Laugh all you want, bro, because in 10
years, good luck, buddy.
Um, I said you laugh. I would laugh as
well cuz I used to be in the Nile like
you, you know. So, but no, it's just a farewell England.
Today wasn't as good as yesterday. Nothing.
This will never change in this country.
I'm booking these flights. One second.
Where's this BA? Where's this BA [ __ ]
uh advertise um website? Sorry.
No, it was really bad today, bro.
Saturday evil was I look [ __ ] good as
well, bro. It's come back [ __ ] Yeah,
I had a nice t-shirt, bro. Nice hat, nice t-shirt.
It never ever changes. Never.
It was really bad. Really bad. Anyways,
it's okay to go out once we've got these
things booked. We need that out of this
country. This ain't normal. This ain't
normal. And and you know how you know
this is so [ __ ] up here. You will see
normal guys. Normal looking guys with
the most ugliest girls. That's another
thing. How was Thailand? It was very
good. Um I'm just booking another flight
to go there now actually. One second.
I'm leaving this country again. [ __ ]
this. One second.
I went out today brick wrong. Same old
I've got boyfriends. Same old stuck up
women. [ __ ] this for a game of soldiers.
I am slow down here, bro. I'm not doing
this no more.
I'm not continuously getting disrespected much stronger.
book for them. One sec. Hold on. I'm
looking at these dates. Yeah.
Yeah. I done 11 approaches sober today.
Uh Brit Bong saying, "Oh, not
interested." What does someone do to get
someone interested in this country? E,
that's the million dollar question.
They don't want people that look good.
They don't want people that smell good.
They don't want people that are
confident. Sad sad sad place here in England. Even
think of a sad place to be fair.
It's like you don't even get treated
like you're human in your own country.
You know that's like sort of like
various things with different things.
You know what I mean? It's really really bad.
Yeah. Past definitely predicts the
future. I can definitely tell you that for nothing.
It will never change here. It's so sad. So sad.
I'm booking these flights.
This ain't normal. Don't you just ain't normal, bro?
Whatever normal means. Stay a
[ __ ] Ain't it, bro?
When did the change
said I'm not spending [ __ ] £35 to get
into a place that's ridiculous.
guess about five numbers. I reckon
must have been about five, I reckon.
Must have been [ __ ] I need to keep I
keep counting to you. [ __ ] that.
This country is too depressing.
I did it. Uh, I got a shag.
Um, yeah, man. I got I got a boyfriend.
Yeah, I got loads of I got a boyfriend.
If that comes to the shack, I just
booked again, by the way. I thought,
[ __ ] this, mate. I was I was in I was in
this web spoon, bro. I said there's no
way I'm going through another year of
this again. I'm not voting for another
event. Hell the [ __ ] no. [ __ ] boyfriend [ __ ] [ __ ] this. No.
It never changes here in England.
that changes here in England, bro.
I got so much [ __ ] today, bro. I have a
boyfriend. I have a You know what? Yeah,
we need to just stop going through
the things that happened because it's
just the same old. Well, there's no
point. It is the same old as last time
and the time before us. That's all you
need to know. Five shitty numbers that
probably won't go anywhere.
I was about to hit Fabric's um LT's
favorite nightclub, but they're trying
to charge 35 quid to get in. I thought
I'm not paying £35 to get into a [ __ ]
rave. [ __ ] that. So,
um same old England. There's there's
nothing really to go and get into. Same
old. It will always be the same old and
your past predicts your future.
>> Yeah, it would never change in this
country. I booked Thailand, by the way.
800 quid to flight me out of here soon.
[ __ ] this. Absolutely. [ __ ] this, bro. I
ain't doing this anymore, mate. I'm
putting a And you know how [ __ ] up
this is, Nicolo. Yeah, you know this country's [ __ ]
You will see, right?
average looking guys, all right, average
looking guys or even decent looking
guys, right? With [ __ ] ugly women
like with women with like glasses and
[ __ ] That that's how [ __ ] up it is.
That's how you know this country's damn bad, bro.
But yeah, this it definitely definitely does
definitely does predict your future um
your your past in this country. It will
never change. Never.
It's the same old boring. I can say
everything. I can say everything better
than Ant-Man, bro. We'll never change
here. It's sad. It really is sad here.
It's a sad place to live in England.
Nah, you can't get nothing in this country.
You need to leave. I was having this
conversation with this guy on the on on
the train and he said, "So, what's your
plan now?" He says, "You need to leave."
cuz I told him about Ant-Man keep
telling me that I need to leave and
leave and leave. He said, "You need to
leave." Simple. That's what he said.
There's nothing else. You need to get
out of this country. Simple. Like
there's there's nothing else
off. You know, ignore Jo saying that,
you know, you never know your past. Your
past definitely dictates your future. I
look [ __ ] good today as well, bro.
Like I might as well I got my [ __ ]
after shave [ __ ] stolen maybe. But
[ __ ] bro. Like I look clean as [ __ ]
today, bro. I was looking fresh.
Nothing. Same old.
Yeah, bro. So I just went back. I
thought call it a day. Got four numbers. I'm leaving. Business now.
I am not [ __ ] paying £35 to get into
a [ __ ] fabric. So you're [ __ ]
having a laugh.
It's good though. At least I got
something to look forward to now.
Can't get anyone in this country. It
doesn't matter how you look, you know. I
look [ __ ] good today. I did. I look
[ __ ] banging, bro. Still can't get no
one. You can't get anything, anything,
anyone. Nothing depressed. That's all
you do is end up depressed. But at least
now I know that, you know, a couple
weeks to go. Countdown. I'm on a
countdown now, bro. It's all good.
Where'd you get them flights booked,
bro? It's all good. Trust me.
Oh, I met some lads from [ __ ] Nottingham.
Yeah, I did actually live in approach to
sober. I actually did, bro.
I actually did.
Yeah, you meet them at work. Yeah, of
course you do. Well, I know where I'll
be going. I'm out of this country. I'm
I'm going Thailand. I've already booked
the flights. Can't [ __ ] wait, mate.
Now all I need is this application to be
done now. Like I can't wait now.
Yeah, it doesn't seem so bad when you
got something planned.
Yeah. And then you see these guys that
look normal and look decent and you see
the kind of women that they're [ __ ]
with. That's how you know the country's
[ __ ] up. I was speaking to this guy on
the [ __ ] train
and we were just talking about the the
whole like madness and the whole GTA 6. And
I said to that guy in Canada, "You can
keep laughing, bro, cuz you're in denial.
You are in denial if you think it's
never going to change in this country. I
look [ __ ] good today. I should have
got somewhere today. I look [ __ ] clean,
bro. Do you remember that good old boss
t-shirt? It just goes to show that it
will never change ever in this country. Never have
forever [ __ ] will.
Yeah. Full of in full of uninterested
women. No thanks. You can do it though,
but I'll be leaving the country.
Nicolo, I got into this [ __ ] again
because of bored him, bro. I got into
this [ __ ] again because of boredom. I
should have never tried again.
You know, it will never change. Yeah.
Never. Never change.
Never. Cuz it would have already. You
know, you might have been you might be
brain damaged, right?
I I want [ __ ] out of this country, bro.
When I come back, I book them flights
straight away again. You know, you know,
I'll do what Ant-Man done. Teach
English. [ __ ] this.
There's got to be a better life out of
England. There's got to be more to life
than this, you know?
There's got to be
[ __ ] that looks like cut.
Yeah, it is pretty depressing, eh?
it is depressing in this country. I find myself depressed.
That's why I had to do something about it, bro.
Yep. Lonely women that pretend they got
boyfriends. I had one woman today said
that she wouldn't give her a number cuz
I'm not in her social circle. Just
another excuse, eh?
Just another load of [ __ ]
Yep. It never changes here.
It actually makes you [ __ ] depressed, don't it? doesn't it?
This is [ __ ] depressing, bro. It
never changes. Never changes in this country.
But apparently your past don't dictate your future.
Yeah. Yeah. Whatever. Anyways, it's not
my problem anymore, mate. I'll be off
Thailand again soon, so it won't be my problem.
It's not my problem anymore.
Simple. So, yeah.
I can't believe you can be good-looking
and you can't even get a woman in your
own country. [ __ ] hell.
You can't even You can't even get a
woman in your own [ __ ] country.
[ __ ] hell. How depressing is that?
How [ __ ] depressing is that? Anyone
would think you're [ __ ] fat and ugly.
When was the last time you [ __ ] you
you you you actually checked your
[ __ ] weight, bro?
Anyone would think you're [ __ ] fat
and ugly the way you get treated in your own country.
This is why I'm leaving, bro. Even if
I'm going to be on a bit less money like
Antman. This ain't no way to live. This
ain't no way to live. This ain't no
life. in this country. It can't be. It
can't be normal. Whatever normal is,
this can't be it. I know it can't be it.
Same old boyfriend [ __ ] Same old. Yeah.
How the [ __ ] are your How does your f
How does your past not dictate your
future then? Still waiting for that
answer, but no one can answer me.
It's been the same old every time you go
out. It's been the same old for years
and it's continuously being the same
old. Um, but the past don't dictate your future.
I'm not so sure about that. It is
literally dictating it. Every single
time that you go out, it is dictating it.
Same old boy in England.
But it literally is dictating it cuz
every single time you go out it's it is
literally doing that exact thing.
Yeah. I'm getting out of this country
anyways. I booked a flight. So
this ain't no life mate for anyone.
Yeah. You can't get nothing in this
country, mate. Oh, [ __ ]
The only thing you can do is befriend [ __ ] men.
Don't dictate your future. So they say,
so they say. Yeah.
And I ain't got a [ __ ] hold of my ass.
Go to guts. Why do I go to guts? Yeah.
[ __ ] depressing, isn't it?
Yeah, is depressing
holding this country. It's same old it.
Let me check on my applications. One sec.
set it anywhere. No.
I watch porn go to sleep.
You watch porn and then you sleep.
That's [ __ ] man.
Yep. Same old in this country. Greasy.
One club was trying to charge me £35 to
get into this club.
And I thought, "Fuck that." £35.
I just called it four or five numbers
and then I went home. Called it four or
five numbers and I just went home. I
booked Thailand by the way um just
before you joined. I'm out of this
country, bro. I meant everything I said
in Weather Spoons. This ain't no life
here. We make jokes about this all the
time, but I can't live like this
anymore, bro. In this country. It's not
normal. I don't want to live like this
anymore. It's not a normal way to live.
You know, I need a better life. And
you're not going to get a better life in
this country. Not why you keep dealing
with this. You know, it ain't no life,
bro. It ain't no life for anyone. You know,
£900. The flights cost me £900.
You need to get out of this country,
bro. That's what you need to do.
You need to leave. You need to leave England.
That's what you need to do.
I said to this guy in Canada as well, I
said, "You can keep laughing, bro, cuz
you're in denial.
You won't be laughing in 10 years time
when you're my when you're my [ __ ]
age. What are you? You're 18 now." You know,
when you're 18, like [ __ ]
you're um you're not going to be
laughing then, mate. When you're 28,
he's not going to be laughing, mate.
Especially in Canada.
See, these people are in denial. You
see, that's what they're called, grievy.
They're called in denial.
They seem to think everything's funny.
uh good, hunky dory, because they're
delusional. They're they're in denial.
That's what these people are in denial.
I don't know what it is. I hate my
problem anymore. So,
I looked good today as well, Greasy. I
looked good today as well. Yeah,
but I couldn't pay £35 to get into a
[ __ ] rave. That's ridiculous, bro.
Why' I pay £35 to hear about I've got a
boyfriend? Think about it. You got £35
in your hand. Yeah, you can pay 70 80
quid to get an escort. Why the [ __ ]
would you pay £35 to get into a [ __ ]
rave just to hit boyfriend?
35 [ __ ] pound. When the [ __ ] did
ticket stop coming 35 quid?
But no, it will never it it won't change it ever. Sadly,
sadly it will never change.
It is a It is a shame, you know.
At least I won't have long left until
I'm out of here again.
Depressing, bro. This country, I hate it
so much. I hate everything about it.
But Grezy, so
you still didn't answer my question,
right? Is that how does your past not
dictate your future when this has been
happening for years and it's continuously happening?
It is it's still predict it's still
dictating it. You're saying that your
past don't dictate your future, but it
is. It's just it is dictating it. It's
dictating it right now because we went
out today and it is literally dictating
it just like Thursday.
What does not what is different about
any of it? You tell me in the past 3
years what has changed
in terms of this? Nothing. It stayed
exactly the same just like it would
always stay exactly the same.
It will never change.
[ __ ] never until you leave, which is
what I'm [ __ ] doing. I booked these
fights. I'm [ __ ] out of here. Yeah.
No. Yeah. No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. Greasy, greasy, greasy. Listen. you
know, with the whole money thing
when we was talking about like money and
losing money and stuff, I was sat in the
cinema thinking, yeah, okay, you might
have lost a bit of money, but you know,
you don't know what's going to happen
tomorrow or the next day or next month
or you don't know what's going to
happen. You don't know what's around the
corner really. You had a good run for
it. Good run from it. But with this, it
never changes. with this. It has been
constant for the past three years. You
know, you've tried more than anybody in
the world and it continues to happen. It
is continuously happening. So, how could
it possibly change? But it has been
happening for years.
It is still happening.
When would it change? You got a logical
You've got a logical point with it. This
has been going on now for [ __ ] years,
mate. Before I could even grow facial
hair. So, no. Yeah, people's life
changes, but not with women, not with
dating. It never changes. We don't wake
up all of a sudden and everything's perfect.
Cuz it it would not make any sense what
you're going to wake up one day and all
of a sudden what? People are not going
to pretend they've got boyfriends.
People are not going to be stuck up.
Someone's going to give you a chance. in what universe?
Because it's not planet [ __ ] Mars.
That's what I'm telling you. So,
you know, it's not about comparing. It's
like that would never happen because it
would have happened by now.
That's the other point to it. Like, you
might think I'm being awkward and I'm
being difficult, but I'm not. I'm
telling you really how I see it.
It would have changed by now. It would
have changed by now. Trust me, it would
have. But it doesn't. It stays the same
because then if it if then if it doesn't
stay the same, right, and you've got
hope, that means basically that you're
going to wake up one day and it's going
to be completely different. How how
could it be completely different?
What? People are going to pretend they
don't have boyfriends. People are not
going to give you attitude. People are
what? What? So, one day it's just going
to all stop.
Come on. Whilst we're having a conversation,
let's talk about how one day it's
completely going to stop. You know,
I got so many I got a boyfriend today,
Grezy. Jesus Christ. Anyone would think
you're fat and ugly. It's disgusting. Anybody
would think you're fat and ugly the way
these people go on. [ __ ] hell. Yeah.
Surprised I ain't got [ __ ] alcohol
poisoning to be honest. But it won't
change in this country. There's like no
hope. Like I only do it cuz I'm bored
and I've got nothing else to do. I don't
have no hope. That's the whole point.
There is no hope.
You seem to think people do this [ __ ]
cuz they've got hope. No, I ain't got no
hope. I just didn't have anything better
to do cuz I'm still waiting on things.
You know what I'm saying? I've got no
[ __ ] hope. Hence why I do most of
them drunk. I done some sober today cuz
I felt energetic. But I ain't got no
hope. It's always the same. It will
never change. Never. Never. Never. Never
Things don't just suddenly change after
3 years, bro. You know,
if you want to change your life, you got
to want to change. And that's leaving
this country. If you're really serious,
bro, that you want a better life, you
need to leave this country.
You want to want to change, you know,
you you you know, you stay in this
country, you're just going to carry on
being depressed and you're going to it's
going to drive you mad. You know, the
thing that drives me mad the most is
that that you're not ugly. There's
nothing wrong with you. So, you
shouldn't be dealing with this.
That's all my That's my thing. But, you
know, you need to know also that you're
not alone in it. Like, Grezy, there's
decent looking guys, right? No homo. I
was speaking to this guy on the train,
right? And his girlfriend's got glasses.
She's not the best looking. And it's
madness because you're not a loneliness.
Like, even other people need to lower their standards.
It's not normal. Like you want a better
life, you would leave. Simple. Um cuz
this is not normal. This is really the
same old now. It really, really, really,
really is the same old.
I don't know how many times you have to
go out until it changes. How many times
until this changes? How long and how many times?
Think about it, Grezy. How long for how
long do you have to keep doing this for?
And the thing is, I I I don't think I
necessarily care. I just think it's all
wrong. I think it's all wrong and I
think it's all [ __ ] up.
That's what it is. Cuz I've gotten into
this [ __ ] again. It's just so messed up.
And it all starts from Yeah.
And I'm all and I and it all starts from
um the whole like
you go out, right? And you're going to
speak to someone when you go out
cuz it happens cuz you go out anyways.
And then you're going to acknowledge how
[ __ ] up it is because you're not in the Nile.
See this guy from Canada and that
they're in denial. They don't seem to
think there's a problem. And then that
starts and starts and starts again. It
all starts from going out,
which is why I need to start working
again, bro, before I go [ __ ]
Thailand. You need to literally But now
it's not going to be bad cuz I know that
I'm leaving now. So there'll be nothing
to moan about when I go out again.
Cuz every time you go out, it will
remind you why you've only got a few
weeks to go before you go. So
you should be able to go out and just
easily get dates with the way that you
look, the way that I look. You should be
at ease. You should be able to go out
and just find someone. But it doesn't
seem you can do that.
And every single time you go out, it
just seems to annoy you.
Annoy you more and more and more and
more and more and more and more.
You know, that's why, you know, it's it
is annoying. It is [ __ ] annoying as
It is sad, bro.
So, yeah, I need to get one of these
[ __ ] thingy jobs again, bro. Yeah,
I think How many numbers did I get?
How many numbers do I get?
Five. I think I got about five.
[ __ ] it over.
Now do you believe I've got anxiety grievy?
Now do you believe it? Grievy.
What's that other cunt's name? [ __ ] [ __ ]
There's one I'm missing.
Oh, five numbers up. Okay. [ __ ] hell.
Want to see King Greasy?
I've done a lot of approaches.
How many times do you have to keep
dealing with this piss taken?
It's really bad. Greasy. Like it's
really really really bad.
But I guess other people lower their
standards because you see who they end up with.
Yeah, five numbers is not that bad, is it, Grezy?
Hopefully we get some replies. Eh,
they're just not interested in this country. Ant
man, right? Listen to him, bro. He's
motivating. He's in Thailand, bro. He's
living in Thailand.
Been call him when he was on YouTube.
He's a [ __ ] legend, bro. He's in
Thailand. He's living in Thailand. He's
living the dream, bro.
is living the dream, Greasy.
He is living the dream, bro. As much as
you don't like him or you hate him, you
can't deny that, bro.
I had one woman that said she wouldn't
give me her number cuz I'm not in her social circle.
You know what you need to do? Just go
Thailand. We've booked it now. Let these
people rot, bro. Let these people rot in
their 30s and 40s and then they can moan
about how they can't find someone. No,
no, no. Just leave them to it. That's
what you should do, bro.
Cuz think of it like they can live
delusional for the rest of their life in
their 20s, but when they're 30 in their
30s and 40s and no one wants them,
that'll be on them. Social media won't
save them then, will they, Grezy? Social
media won't save them then.
Social media won't be able to save them then.
Yeah, I met some lads today from Nottingham.
They're like, "Seek."
Oh, their Nottingham accent was very
strong, bro. It's a very strong accent. Uh,
it's a very strong accent, bro.
Yeah, I don't want today. Sorry, not interested.
Why are they not interested in this
country? What? What? What? What is it?
Why don't they give people a chance?
It's so weird.
It's so weird, bro.
I can't waste money on escorts anymore, Grezy. Bro,
that was not the point of today. The
whole point of today was going out
trying to [ __ ] see how it is on that.
But yeah, it will never ever change. >> Never.
35 to get into a [ __ ] club.
Hey, Stephen. How you didn't ask me how
my night went?
You didn't ask me how my night went.
Same old England. If that answers your question.
Same old boyfriends. Same old [ __ ] I
got five numbers.
But yeah, it will never ever I don't
even think Yeah. Do you know what? Yeah.
I don't even think you can get a date in
this country anymore now. I think even
if you you know before you could get
like little dates if you went out every
day. I don't even think you can get that anymore.
anymore. I really think you can't get nothing here.
I really think it's gotten that bad now.
Look at all of the guys that are in
relationships that have to even lower
their standards. It's so bad.
You know, there's this guy on a train,
proper white guy and [ __ ] blue eyes
and his girlfriend was like a four out of 10.
So, you're not alone. Don't think that
you're alone. Do you know what I mean?
That's that's it. When you know,
the only thing I get out of this is
meeting new friends. That seems to be
the only thing I get out of this going
out is meeting new friends.
like just me and that's the only good
thing about this.
Yeah, I had one rum today, Grezy. I
tried to stick to uh beer, but I can't.
Sometimes I can't.
But yeah, the money doesn't bother me, Grezy.
£1,100 a month. It don't bother me
anymore because money comes and goes.
You can't take it with you when you die.
I know deep down it's not going to be forever.
But I know with women it will never
change here. Never. It will never change.
I know that for a fact. It will never change here.
I always find Thursdays better greasy. I
don't know why. I met some cool lads.
I spent £70 today, Grezy. That's not too
bad, is it? 70 quid. And that was including food.
That's not that bad, is it? 70 drinking, including food. No.
Do you believe on 11 approaches sober
greasy? And I [ __ ] did. I [ __ ] did, mate.
I [ __ ] did before I started drinking.
Same old England, eh?
Same old England.
I [ __ ] did, Greasy.
Do you believe I did do it? So, I did, bro.
I don't know. A lot sober, bro.
But yeah, I think even if you went out
every day, you still wouldn't even get a date. Nah.
So I said to this woman, "Oh, so you
won't give me a chance because I'm not
part of your social circle?" That
doesn't make any sense. Well, because
I'm not a part of your social circle,
you wouldn't give someone a chance.
They're [ __ ] idiots. [ __ ] them, bro.
Let them get to their 30s and 40s when
social media can't save them anymore.
Let them, bro. Just let them live in
denial. Let them live delusional.
And I got boyfriends. [ __ ] me, mate. You
don't even want to know. It was really
bad today. I'll show you what I was
wearing as well. Actually,
I looked good as well.
was me today there.
One second, bro.
Good as well, bro. But yeah, it was a
lot of uh I got a boyfriend today. Same old England.
Same old England, eh?
This is why you can't do this sober,
bro. I done it sober. Yeah, that's what
I was wearing today. I looked good, bro.
My cap should be coming in a couple of
days. Grezy, I got some caps coming. I
told you about earlier. Yeah,
that's sick, bro.
Oh, why have I got a picture of my mommy?
Crazy. Why have I got a picture of my mama?
Why is that on my thing? That's weird.
>> Stephen, can you tell me when it's going
to change in this country?
Nah, it will never change in this country. Never.
Never. Bro, I wouldn't mind if you was
[ __ ] ugly. I wouldn't mind if you was
fat and ugly. I really wouldn't.
This woman said, "Oh, I work in
McDonald's. I got a number." I said,
"You don't need to be ashamed." Why do
these people think that where they work
is bad? It's a job. A job is a job at
the end of the day. You know, someone's
got to start somewhere.
Like, I feel bad when people like have a
job and they're ashamed of what they
were doing. And
you know, it's like
it's a job, is it?
I was [ __ ] doing Uber. That was
paying [ __ ] [ __ ] You know, it is
what it is.
She works a McDonald's.
Maybe she can give me some McDonald's.
But yeah, you're never going to stop
hearing the I've got a boyfriend.
Yeah, I think Grezy, that's one of the
reasons why you can't really do them
sober. Cuz when you do them sober like
me, it starts to affect you. Whereas
where you're drunk, you don't really
care, do you? You're just pissed. You're
just drunk. So [ __ ] get drunk and whatever. Um,
so I actually did do 11 sober. I did
actually do some sober
cuz the thing is obviously you're sober
in it. So when you do them sober, you're
going to start thinking, well, [ __ ] why
are you not being given a chance here?
There's nothing wrong with the way that
you look. There's nothing wrong with the
way that you talk. That logically
doesn't make any sense. And then you
start questioning your own questions,
you see, which you should do, you know,
so you should. There's nothing wrong with you.
You shouldn't be in this position.
You should be with someone Sorry. [ __ ] knows.
Now you believe I've I don't have
anxiety in it. Steven Howard,
I don't have anxiety. Matey,
you think I've got anxiety in it?
Grievy, don't be silly.
I have anxiety, bro.
So, I just wish there was a way to stop.
This guy was like,
"Oh," he said, "I can't go in the pub."
I said, "Why can't I go in?" He said,
"Oh, you're a bit drunk." Um, and I
said, "Well, that's a bit disgusting."
He said, "It isn't." I said, "Well, it
is." And then he was trying to say I was
being violent. I said, "Being violent?
What the [ __ ] I'm standing right here.
I've not put my hands on anyone. This
This country is is disgusting, bro.
It really really really is disgusting.
It really really is. This country is
disgusting, bro. It makes me sick.
Oh, and guess what? Do you know that guy
that I was speaking to, the 18year-old
Grezy? He's not gay, by the way. He's
actually not gay. I was speaking to him
and he says he's not even gay. So yeah. Yeah.
So that's something. Okay.
People just like me, bro.
Have you ever heard the Nottingham
accent greasy? It's very, very thick.
It's a very thick accent, bro.
It's very like It's like um
I don't know, bro. It's [ __ ]
I just think these women have got delusional standards.
That's what I personally think. me.
I personally think they've just got
delusional stand. They've just got unrealistic expectations.
That's what I think it is, bro. They're
trying to charge me £35, Stephen Howard,
to go into a club. I I'm not paying £35
to get into a club.
Um, so yeah.
Yeah, I'm not paying that. [ __ ] that.
£35. They were trying to charge me. I
said, "You can just get an escort for that." Basically
£20. I don't I wouldn't mind paying £20
because I I don't mind today. Like, not
35 quid. I couldn't bring myself to pay it.
Especially when you're just going to get
the same I've got a boyfriend, so it
doesn't make any sense.
I just try to stick to clubs um to pubs
nowadays. Creepsy, I don't believe in this whole
clubbing thing. What's the point? It's
just the same thing like paying to get
pot blocking bounces. I just don't
understand. You might as well just stick
to a Weather Spoons.
Well, it's the same old a Weather
Spoons. They're always going to pretend
they got boyfriends. So it's
I don't understand like
I'd rather just go to a weather spoon as me.
This woman was supposed to meet me
today. I don't know what happened.
But it doesn't matter cuz if she doesn't
meet me tomorrow, I'll be [ __ ] calling her.
I'll be [ __ ] cooler though.
[ __ ] cool, mate. Yeah.
What do you think the solution is,
Stephen Howard? I generally do think it is Thailand
cuz this guy on the train was telling me
like, "What? What are you actually going
to do then?"
He said, "You need to do what your
friend told you to do."
I just guessed I didn't have to I just
was hoping I didn't have to take the way
out that ant landed.
I just thought for like ages that like I
wouldn't have to go down the same route
he did. But I guess I was also in denial
to an extent
cuz I just didn't I didn't see myself
better than him. But I thought myself
was different. I thought my life I
thought I was different than him
in a good way. But nah,
you'll be next to him, mate. You'll be joining him. Nah.
And the Indian people are starting to
say they've got boyfriends now as well,
actually, which never used to happen.
So, it will get it does get worse and
worse and worse.
The UK is finished, bro. It generally is finished.
Don't know what
what people do, bro. [ __ ] those. >> Yeah.
Do you think that your past don't
dictate the future, Steven Howard?
that it definitely dictates the future,
mate. It definitely does
cuz here we are still having the same problems.
Oh, still no one giving you a chance. No
one even gives you a chance.
It's [ __ ] up, bro. Who's up?
Well, yeah, pretty much it does. Cuz
when you go out, right, it's always the
same. I have a boyfriend. I have a
boyfriend. I have a boyfriend. Why would
all of why would it all of a sudden change?
Like it's clear they're not interested.
It's clear they've [ __ ] based their
standards on social media, whatever it
is. Why would it all of a sudden change?
I don't even think even if you went out
on the street and you don't approach us
now, you'd even get anything.
It will never change. Never.
It's a shame though. It is. It is sad.
Like I find it quite sad. Me, I don't
find it funny. I think it's just sad,
you know. I think it's sad,
Oh, you can't find someone in your own
country. I just think it's sad me, you
know. I'm glad you find it funny. I just
find it quite sad,
you know. I think it's sad me.
You must have thought I was mad doing
him sober today, didn't you, Greasy?
Yeah, not interested.
Bad. It good looking guy, nice cap, nice
little beard. Can't find someone in your own country.
Really, really is sad, isn't it?
I think it's sad, mate.
really do think it's sad, you know.
I think it's mad sad.
I'll put I'll put the video up for you
if you want.
There you go.
You like my little cat, don't you, Grezy?
Well, I'm going to show you it. Yeah.
Stay single, mate. Best way.
Yeah, I'm going to show you this video. Grezy,
some people are just not meant to meet someone, bro.
But like I said, I don't think it's the
fact that I care. I think I just can't
get over how [ __ ] up it is.
That's what it is. I I just don't think
I can get over how [ __ ] up it actually is.
You know what I mean? Steven Howard.
One second. My video's uploading. Bro,
you like them lads I met on Thursday,
Greavves. It was a good laugh, mate. It
was a good laugh.
There you go, Grezy. Tell me I didn't
look good, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, that was me earlier, bro.
Sad place to be here in England, eh? Grizzy,
it's a sad place. Oh, it's a boss
t-shirt, bro. I've had it for a while,
but I just never worn it.
Yeah, I look sick yesterday, did I? Yeah.
Yeah, bro. I bought some new caps. I got
free caps for £11. They're coming.
They're like animated ones.
But same old, not interested.
Same old, not interested in this
country. Same old. Oh, [ __ ] Yeah.
Same old, eh?
Same old. Not interested, bro. I don't
even know why I'm wearing these caps. I
got like a full head of hair, but I
think it was wearing it when I used to
do the Uber to block the sun from my face. But
yeah, not interested in this country. You know,
not interested in this country, mate.
Yeah, it's bad.
So, when is this going to stop? Steven
out with this whole boyfriend [ __ ]
When is this going to stop? Yeah.
Yeah, I would give it a whirl. Well,
usually I would.
Yeah. I do like my little cap.
I want to put this
I want to put this video public.
Do you think I look good? Grezy,
do you think I look good in that video? Greavvesy,
you think I look cool?
I think I look pretty good.
What do you think, Grezy? Oh, you should
see my little caps that are coming. I'll
show you them when they come. Yeah.
Yeah. Not interested. Hey,
they just aren't interested in this country.
Is that man right grievy when he said
that that they just got interested in this country? Well, obviously
if you go by me mine and his
experiences, well, obviously, yeah,
I know I can fit any style really, bro. But [Music]
but it doesn't really matter what style
you have because you're always going to
get I've got a boyfriend.
Oh [ __ ] I've got a bone to pick with
that Lord Lord J by the way. All right. So,
you know what he said, Steven Howard?
Oh, I knew I had something to say.
Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ]
Listen, you know, let me tell you
something, bro, about this LJ. I
actually caught some of his live stream,
right? Let me tell you something, Grezy.
Let me body this [ __ ] Yeah. So,
he was trying to say, "Oh, why do I keep
going on that I've got savings?" Uh, cuz
I do. Uh, it's not a big deal to have
savings. Then he was like, oh, he doubts
that I have £500. I'm thinking, why
wouldn't I have £500?
He is the one that's sat there on
YouTube every day trying to convince
people that he's got money. Think of it
like this, Steven Howard. Yeah.
Bye-bye, Virgin. Um, listen to this,
right? I've gone on that L J's channel,
right? And he's got a store.
Uh, he's brought out some merch, but
there's no substance behind any of his
merch. Think of it, bro. If this LJ
really had money, do you think he would
swallow the only bit of pride that he's
got left to make an extra few quid?
Think of it, bro. If someone's getting
three grand a month, three half grand a
month. Let's just say for example, he
says that he makes money on property.
Why is he so desperate
to swallow his pride just to get a tiny
bit of extra more money? It doesn't make
no sense. It doesn't make no sense. See,
when big YouTubers used to bring out
this merch and do anything for money,
they knew they would gain millions
because they've got like a big fan base.
He literally has hardly anyone watching
him. The people that do watch him are
skint. Why is he begging for money on
donations and [ __ ] bringing out
stupid merch that's not going to make
him much money? Because he is skint.
It's the other way around, bro. [ __ ]
more like £300 a [ __ ] month. It
doesn't make any sense. You see how it
don't make sense any of it?
Skim as [ __ ] bro. Why the [ __ ] wouldn't
someone have £500?
What the [ __ ] Why wouldn't someone have £500, bro?
Like, I told you I'm getting I'm I'm I'm
I'm I'm getting less money now. I would
never beg anyone for money. Never beg
anyone for money, bro. You mad. [ __ ]
that. So, that's how you know he's skin. Yeah.
Need to give me some advice. Stephen
Howard, what do I do about this women [ __ ]
I think you can do it.
Just ignore it, Stephen. How the virgin
just wants attention. Just ignore it,
bro. Let's just carry on talking about something else. Yeah.
Oh, someone showing their dad's money
again. What have I told you
about showing people your dad's money?
Bro, you literally are trying to
convince people that you got money
again. [ __ ] hell. Just stop it. Stop
it, you little skin flint. Stop taking
out your [ __ ] housing benefit trying
to convince people that you've got money.
[ __ ] you are literally skinted in a [ __ ] skin.
Like, no one cares what buddy you show,
bro. Listen, listen, listen, listen. You
got shown [ __ ] £5.7,000
in cash. Come back when you can show 10
grand. All of this you showing £1,000 in
20s and£10 notes, bro, your skin. Why
have you got so many £10 [ __ ] notes?
[ __ ] hell. You really are trying to
convince people that you got money. It's
so sad. It's really, really sad.
You're talking about money being bum
chains when you don't even have a bed.
Isn't that madness? You're talking about
money being bum chains when you
literally you don't even have a bed.
You do it like every month, bro. Show
your housing benefit. Like, talk about
skint. [ __ ] me, bro. Like, listen. If I
go if I go into my bank account, bro,
and I withdraw money again, I will own
all of these again. But I'm never
showing these people money ever again.
I've actually got money in the draw, to
be honest, but I'm never showing them
money ever again
because they've been shown [ __ ] 5.7
grand and no one's doubled it.
You really, really need to get laid by
Steven Howard. He really really needs to
get laid, doesn't he?
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Why is he calling these monthly benefit
money bum change? I don't get that, bro.
Calling these monthly benefit money bum
change. What the [ __ ]
That is sad, man. That is sad.
He really thinks he's got money, doesn't
he? I feel sad. I feel bad for him, bro.
I really feel bad. He actually thinks
he's got money. Steven Howard.
And he literally has nothing. Like, how
many times has he tried to convince
people with these little£10 notes and 20
notes that he's got money, but we all
know that he ain't even got a bed? He
literally hasn't even got a bed.
It's funny, isn't it, bro? Yeah.
Needs to get laid, bro. Seriously needs
to get laid.
I think Yeah, he needs to get laid, bro.
Thinks he's got money. Sad, bro. He's
like the skinniest person I know.
along with LJ as well. They're both
skinned, bro. They're both [ __ ] skinned.
Both skin, bro. Both skin.
That's so sad.
Bum chains, but he hasn't even got a bed.
Why is he calling these life savings bum change?
Steven Howard, why is he calling these
life savings bum change? He's literally
skint. Why? Why is he talking like he's
rich when he is literally the skintest
person? I I know. Him and L.
They're [ __ ] skint as [ __ ]
Why is he talking like he's he's rich
when he's literally skin?
[ __ ] could buy you a bed.
I think it's sad, bro. Me,
right? You just you just described
yourself skin bun. You're skint and
you're a bun. Have you seen your face?
You look like a rat.
Have you actually seen your ugly face?
Have you seen how you dress? You are
literally the definition of skint.
Like the definition of skin is yourself.
You dress like a [ __ ] You've got no
bed. You literally are skint.
You didn't go on holiday until you was [ __ ] 31.
Like the skint one is literally yourself.
And you are months. Have you seen your
face? You ugly [ __ ] You ugly bastard.
Oh my god, bro.
Ugly [ __ ] [ __ ] ugly [ __ ]
Yeah, sorry about that, bro. Someone
messaged me. Yeah, he needs to get laid, bro.
He really, really needs to get laid.
I think it' be the other way around.
He really, really, really needs to get laid.
Trying to convince people that he's got
money. It's really sad, bro. How
desperate can someone really be?
How desperate can someone be?
How desperate can someone be? Steven Howard,
how desperate can someone be?
Someone that doesn't have a bed.
Somebody that dresses like a [ __ ] shows
his whole life savings and he calls it bum change.
[ __ ] hell, bro. That is sad.
It really really is the definition of
skin. I I feel sorry for him.
Feel sorry for him.
Yeah, he he really does need to get laid, bro.
He really really does, bro. Do you know
what? I'm I'm so glad he does this,
Stephen Howard. You know that
just tormenting himself. I actually I
actually like this, bro. It's actually
funny cuz I just know that you've got
something that they want. They spend all
day on stalking you. They don't leave
you alone. It's pure jealousy. That's
what you want, bro. You know, living in
these people's head rentree. You got
something that they don't have that they
want. They can sit and call you this and
call you that and
they're the ones that are obsessed with
you every day on YouTube because you got
something that they want that you have
something that they want that they don't have.
So that's why they do all of this and
probably more money better looking than
them. Truth be told, yeah, they want
here every day doing this year in year
out. Definitely definitely definitely jealousy. Definitely jealousy.
I think it's cuz I'm better looking than
them personally, bro. I think they're
jealous of my looks to be fair. And
they're lying to themselves. Like they
know deep down, bro. They're lying to
themselves when they're saying that
you're skin bun. They're literally
talking about themselves.
[ __ ] hell, bro. Like, you know what I mean?
They really really really are just
talking about themselves. Yeah.
Yeah. It's nice to be better than
someone, bro. the joys of being better
than someone uh Steven Howard.
But I think it's cute how he tries to
convince people that he's got money. I
feel I feel bad though.
I feel bad. It's cute. It is cute though.
But no, he definitely does need to get
laid, bro. All right, we'll just side. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
Low rate. Yeah. Yeah.
I feel like I think it's mad how he
tries to convince people that he's got money.
I think it's bad, bro. I think it's really bad.
convincing people that Yeah.
He really really really really really skimp.
They walk and eat.
He needs to get laid. Oh, [ __ ]
You think I've got anxiety, don't you, Steven Howard? Nah. [Music]
What are they? [ __ ] bagels.
Yeah, I met some woman say she's her
name was Frankie. I said, "Oh, like
Frankie the fisherman." I said, "Like Yeah.
Frankie. [ __ ] Name was Frankie.
Like Frankie the fisherman, you know. Oh, [ __ ]
Frankie. Oh, that's funny, bro.
I don't think I've ever met anyone called Frankie.
Bro, we need to set up a donation, bro,
to try and get Virgin Boy laid. like
call up like an escort or something.
You reckon we should do it?
He needs to desperately get laid. Like
honestly, he needs to really get laid, bro.
He needs to get [ __ ] laid, bro. Imagine.
Oh my god. a,000 maximum.
I really feel bad, bro. He's so
desperate to try to convince people that
he hasn't got that he's got money.
Look at that, bro. Have you noticed
they're always in 20 notes as well? That
is literally about 800 quid.
£800 to a,000.
But guess what, Stephen Howard? It's not 10,000.
[ __ ] He's so sad trying to convince
people that he's got money. Oh my god,
bro. You know, I'm tempted one more time
to just beat these people at the money
game, but I can't be asked, bro.
Every time you show money, they all run
away. So, there's no point pulling out
like 50s and [ __ ]
Look at that, bro. [ __ ] sad.
Thinking that he's got money.
Think of it, bro. Yeah. Look at the [ __ ]
I've got, bro. I've got a bed. I've
traveled more than him. Bought a TV the other day.
I've got designer clothes. What does he have?
Think about it, bro.
I got designer clothes. Telly. I've got
designer clothes. I've got a TV.
so many different things and uh
and he has nothing.
Think about it, bro. Yeah, man.
He's so sad. Sad, bro. Showing these benefits.
So sad, bro. Sad. He has to try to
convince people that he's got money.
I'll never show people money ever again on here. No. Yeah.
He really does need to get laid.
Let's set up a um GoFundMe, bro. Yeah.
Do you know who I'd love to get my hands
on? Stephen Howard, that chase.
You know that Chase? I'd love to get my
hands on him, bro.
I'd love to get my hands on him. We all
know that he's that [ __ ] Red Star account,
but they're both [ __ ] because when
they've both been in London, have you
noticed they'll never tell you when
they're in London?
I would [ __ ] them up, bro. Like, both at
the same time. Yeah.
Both at the same time, though. Yeah.
Me, bro. I'd love to get my hands on
that chase, bro. I swear down.
Yeah, bro. They're all sados.
Get me banned from the pub, you little virgin.
They basically said to me, right, that
oh, if you carry on recording, you got
to leave. You didn't get me banned from
no pub, you little virgin. And even if
you did get me pub uh banned from that
pub, you know, there's like millions of
pubs in London.
Like, do you actually hear yourself?
Like, if you actually got me banned from
one pub, guess what? I would just go to
the next pub next door, you [ __ ] virgin.
You [ __ ] freaky little virgin.
Why would you even brag that you got
someone banned from a pub? You didn't
even get me banned from the pub, you virgin.
And even if you did, what? There's like
millions of pubs in London. There's
literally not even no point. You're such
a virgin. [ __ ] hell, bro. Such a
little sad little virgin.
He needs to go and get laid. He's
literally a low life, bro.
Really, really is a low life. Really is.
Such a virgin.
He really is such a virgin.
I feel sorry. I do feel bad though, bro.
I couldn't imagine being jealous. I
couldn't imagine being jealous like him
every day, bro. I couldn't imagine being
jealous of someone all day, every day,
bro. Could you? I think it would drive me mad.
It would drive me mad if I could be
jealous of someone all day, every day. I
I could I couldn't do it. Me, bro. I
couldn't do it. I'm telling you.
Ah, [ __ ] me, bro. I couldn't do it. Oh,
Yeah, I can do it, bro. One
I eat McDonald's or not.
I'm trying to think if I should get
something to eat.
What do you think?
What? What do you think, bro?
No, I don't have any.
I don't really want to get anything
sort of thing.
Why these bagels are allowed? [ __ ] off.
Why is everything allowed, man?
No, I'm not watching it, bro. I heard about it.
I see some piggies. Steven Howard.
Unless I get some fried some grilled chicken, but uh
I fancy some piggies.
Is that cute?
Yeah, this virgin, he needs to get laid, bro.
Really does need to get laid.
Everything's open, bro. Everything's open. One second.
One second. One second, please. Shut up.
One second while I'm ordering some food.
Shut the [ __ ] up.
Shut the [ __ ] up, you [ __ ]
Yeah, but this virgin is definitely definitely obsessed.
But why don't just leave me alone? Even
one Listen, bro.
Your man child, mate.
I think I need to get [ __ ] laid, mate.
No, I need to get laid, bro. Desperately
need to get laid.
But I do need to stop this. I need to
really start saving money now, bro.
cuz I'll become back in
like that virgin.
I got about 2K I think. Yeah.
Well, I'm going to order this food. Are
you going to stay with me? Yeah. Are
>> you going to stay with me whilst I order
this food, matey?
So, I do need to really start saving, bro.
Like, I can't really be afforded to go out anymore.
I don't want to spend all my money. All in
2K is a lot for a single person in it. Yeah.
Oh, that is the mill. Okay. I didn't
realize that was the mill. One sec.
And you're going to die one. You're
going to die a virgin. You're going to
die one. You're going to die a virgin. Steven Howard.
I can all [ __ ] die one me, mate.
Okay, I've ordered some food.
I think I've got some money left. I
think it's like 2K.
I need to start working soon, bro. I
need to start working soon, bro. For
real. For real. Yeah,
I need to start soon, bro. I swear down.
I need to buy the Samsung Fold soon, but
it's not on my pro. I need to buy it,
but I don't really want to waste £500
right now. I'm trying to I can use a
[ __ ] up phone now for when I need to
meet some women and then Yeah,
it's [ __ ] up.
We ordered some chicken delayed.
I might get lane to try and make me some
pork. I'll buy like a pork joint and
that in it.
Fancy a bit of piggies, bro.
Yeah, I got some numbers. So,
better than nothing, is it? Hopefully I
get a meat out of one of them. But
see, you can't work. See, the difference
is you can't work and date. You see, cuz
it it it's like a full-time job trying
to date. So, you can't work and try to
date at the same time cuz
it's like trying to
It's like a full-time job in itself sort
of thing. So, um,
so you couldn't work.
It's bad, bro. It's bad.
When will USA Izzy come back? Steven Howard. Never.
Yeah, pigs fly, mate. The pigs fly
30 minutes now. [ __ ] off. Can
Do you believe that I done 12 appro like
11 approaches today? Sober Steven Howard.
I [ __ ] I did, bro. I actually did.
What joking, bro? I [ __ ] did. I did.
I fully did, bro.
Yeah, I don't I don't like 11 cyber,
bro. And mad energy, bro.
It ain't nothing to me, bro.
Yeah, but those are just the ones that
done so. But
you're going to die one. You're going to
die one. You're going to die one.
You're going to [ __ ] die one.
D virgin. You are one. Bro,
you like USA easy, don't you? Steven Howard
What do you reckon if I paid
£35 to get into that place today? Steven Howard,
what do you reckon would have happened
if I paid £35 to get into that place?
might have met someone. Do you reckon? Uh,
you know, I would love to go to Belfast
and kick the [ __ ] out of this L. Bro,
I've just seen his video about being
banned from Belfast.
I don't want to, bro. [ __ ]
I don't want to waste money on the [ __ ]
That's the thing.
I don't want to waste
and I wouldn't accept donations from
people. I don't want donations. I I
don't I don't I don't want donations, bro. Yeah.
26 minutes. Come on. I want my [ __ ] chicken, man. Yeah.
You think I'd actually be scared to go
to Belfast by myself, Steven Howard?
You really think I'd be scared to go to
Belfast by myself? Of course I wouldn't be, bro.
It'd be a good video in it. But
I just um
I can't be bothered, bro, wasting money
on it in it.
What do you think?
You think I'll be scared to fly to Belf?
Steven Howard? No. I've been to Scotty
Land by myself.
I've been to Scotty Land by myself, bro. [Music]
Who do you think would win a fight?
Steven Howard, me or him? Who do you think?
Who do you think would win? Me or him, Steven Howard?
Oh, imagine PJ. USA PJ. I'd beat USA PJ. Yeah, man. Oh [ __ ] [Music]
He's not far at all, man.
beat his girlfriend up in front of him, bro.
Okay, but I'm here.
So, what do we do about this whole women
thing, Stephen? How I booked to go to Thailand again?
The flights cost me £900.
I booked them earlier, bro. Yeah.
What's a good idea? Oh dear.
[ __ ] [ __ ] this bro. They've all got boyfriends.
They've all got boyfriends. Steven Howard. H boyfriend. [Music]
We've all got boyfriends, lad.
Come on, chicken. I'm [ __ ] starving, you [ __ ]
You know, I met this woman. She was
going for for rave. [Music]
Come on, bro. I'm starving now.
Starving like how Virgin Boy was starved
by his mama.
That's why he's salty about people
living with their mama cuz his mama starved him.
Stephen, I would
there was another protest.
Yeah, you'll get a bird. Yeah, I've
already got money, bro. I've got my own money.
No, you'll never get birds. You need to
leave this country, which is what I'm doing.
Got it all booked. I'm out of here, man.
Here she is.
Lady Earth, lad.
Nothing wrong with living with your mom.
at all. Well, it depends what your life
is, you know, if you're out all the time
like me or if you work. No, there's
nothing wrong with living with your mom.
It's not that bad.
It's not nowhere near as bad as that
virgin makes out.
There's You go out most of the day,
don't you? What do you do, bro?
I run a lot. I live with mom. I live
with tenants. I live by myself. And
Yeah, it's not nowhere near as bad as
that virgin makes out. Um, you know,
you're out most today anyways, aren't
you? So, what the [ __ ]
And sometimes your mom needs you
depending on who your mom is. So,
there's nothing wrong with living with
your with with one parent. I'd say one
parent. Nothing wrong with it really.
It's nowhere near as bad as as that
virgin makes out.
So what you say you live with your mom
and you're out all day and
and and your point is okay the [ __ ]
weird is it? That's just mommy issues.
It literally makes no difference if an
old woman is in in the house or not.
No, no, no.
That only fans woman used to come around
when I used to live with my mom. No problems.
No problems at all.
There's nothing wrong with living with
your mom. Really,
there's literally nothing wrong with
living with your mom. And I've lived by
myself. I live by myself. I live with tenants. Uh,
trust me, there's nothing wrong with
living with your mom. [ __ ]
Yeah, there's nothing wrong with living
with your mom
at all. Really?
Living for my mom than live in a bedsuit.
Isn't that right?
Come on. 15 minutes. 15 [ __ ] minutes.
You think there's something wrong with
living with your mom? Nah, not really.
Why would you? I mean, I worked. I lived
by myself. I've worked doesn't make you
get women. You remember when people used
to say that, Stephen Howard? Steven
Howard, you know, you you you know, once
you once you work and you live by
yourself, do you remember them excuses
people? I worked and I live by myself
and I was going to the gym. It made no difference.
Yeah, it was good living by yourself,
but there's nothing wrong with living
with your mom.
There's nothing wrong with living with your mother.
You live with your mom, but do you
actually live with your mom? No. No one
cares. The only reason he cares is
because his mom starved him. So, he's
got mommy issues. It doesn't really
matter to be honest. I'm out. I I I was
out all the time anyways. I'm out all the time, you know?
I'm out [ __ ] all the [ __ ] time.
Doesn't matter who the [ __ ] you live
with, bro. What the [ __ ]
It was better living with tenants and
stuff, but that's cuz I used to stay in more. You know,
I was out all day today and I was out
all day yesterday.
A lot of people live with their parents.
You know, a lot of people, you know,
even women, a lot of people live with
their parents. It's not it's not unheard of.
Do you know what, right? I would love
for this [ __ ] to actually have to pay
rent and see how he talks about people
living with their mom
like cuz this virgin got given a house
even though he might have waited a year.
Do you know what? Yeah. If the if the
council you know what I want the council
to do take that cunt's house away from him
and then [ __ ] him actually try and
pay rent and see what he talks about
people live with their parents.
[ __ ] parents, bro. Every [ __ ]
loads of people live with their [ __ ] mom
or their [ __ ] parents or their
[ __ ] dad. Loads of people do. Loads
and loads of people do, bro. It's common
now. You know,
there's not really a problem in it to be honest.
Long as you just don't get in your mom's
hair and you just don't stay in all day,
it's fine, bro.
I lived with about six people before.
I've lived with six people. [Music]
Suppose I fell asleep. Yeah. Not
[ __ ] one, mate. You're going to
[ __ ] die one.
You're going to [ __ ] die one, mate.
Do you think it's weird how Virgin Boy
hasn't even been to Scotland or Wales?
That's the next thing Virgin Boy would
be doing is going to Scotland to copy
me. [ __ ] Virgin. [Music]
I like Laney. Laney's Lane is cute.
Where the [ __ ] are these [ __ ]
I should have been nearly there. That
doesn't make sense.
USA is a Steven Allard. Oh. Emperor said to daddy [Music]
They just stayed interested in this I'm safe. kid.
You don't like King.
Listen, Steven Howard, can you tell me
when am I going to go and approach
people and not hear the I've got a
boyfriend [ __ ] please?
Can you tell me when I'm going to stop hearing it?
They boarded the [ __ ] house up as well, bro. Oh, [ __ ]
H. So, I'm never going to I'm never
going to stop hearing it.
It's annoying. I'm sitting deep here with it. Me, mate.
Look at that ugly face. Oh my god.
I got pictures of that ugly [ __ ] on my
channel, bro. God, he's an ugly bastard.
An ugly skint bastard.
Ugly skint [ __ ]
Is it out? Can't be outside, can it? No. [Music] [ __ ]
Come on, you [ __ ] [ __ ] man.
God, these [ __ ] Steven Howard,
I'm hungry, bro.
Hurry up, man. But
I'm waiting, bro.
What's your favorite food, Steven Howard?
What old bike?
Did you like the little Uber videos, Steven Howard?
The little me on the Uber bike.
How can I work, man? I've got anxiety.
How can I work if I've got anxiety, bro?
How can I work if I got anxiety, bro?
Yeah. You like them? Yeah.
plenty more where they came from, mate.
I need to lose weight. No, I [ __ ] don't.
I'm not fat in the slightest. Lose
weight. I got no weight to lose, matey. Oh [ __ ]
Nah, not me, bro.
I need to go to gym though, to be fair.
I need to go to gym, bro.
But I ain't that time. I got so much
[ __ ] to do.
Why do you need to lose weight? Are you fat?
Greasy is a fat [ __ ] in it.
At least you're not lanky, mate.
At least you're not lanky like that
virgin. [ __ ] hell.
Come on, mate. I'm [ __ ] starving here.
I'm starving. I'm almost as starving as
like [ __ ] Virgin boy.
Oh, is it 3:00 in the morning, bro?
How can I do Uber if I've got anxiety?
Steven Howard, how can you How can you
do it, bro? [Music]
saying nearly there
[ __ ] still waiting for it.
He's mad, bro. He's actually [ __ ] you
know. He is actually [ __ ] you know.
He was going to go [ __ ] Canada over
someone that didn't want him.
Someone that didn't want to know him.
I didn't want to know. [Music]
It's not funny, bro.
This could be a thing.
Mr. Guy goes back. Could be. What's up?
No. Where's that food, bro?
Someone's lost or something, bro. [Music]
One second. Here it is.
One second though. [Music]
All right, bro. You good?
>> At least a close call to be fair. Thank
you, Bobby. Yeah.
>> Oh [ __ ] I don't stop me. But I don't
want to tip him.
You need to set up a gofundme Howard.
I want to get that virgin blade.
Why do they give you [ __ ] nasty coke, man?
They always give you foreign coke. It's [ __ ] wrong.
me up on me. Get that virgin laid.
Got the merch.
Let's get him laid. Come on.
He needs it. He needs to lose it. Stop
laughing at me, bro. Always take the
piss out of me. [ __ ] [ __ ]
How are you that he's a virgin? I'm 100%
certain he's a virgin. him million% Chicken. No chicken.
Why do you live with your mom anyways?
Can't believe he's never had a job.
Can't believe he's never had a job. Even I would
never had a [ __ ] job.
Maybe you could have got a job at McDonald's
to do well.
You know what I find with people like language? Yeah.
Is that they're more than happy to like
bully people when they think they can do
it. Yeah. Like when you're a bit
younger. Like people on Skype used to do
it to me, but they wouldn't do it to a
[ __ ] adult, would they?
Now you're an adult. They wouldn't do
it, would they?
There's these people on Skype. They used
to say horrible.
Oh, I got some sweets from
when I message them now like I'm an
adult. They don't want none of it. Yeah,
you're not fast enough to do it to a
[ __ ] adult. Oh, yeah. You come
just like Virgin Boy. Don't forget we
was quite young then.
Yeah, there used to be this guy in
Virginia, North Carolina. They used to
talk mad [ __ ] about my family.
Bear in mind I was only [ __ ]
I don't know must have been about 15 14
15 must have been about 18 17 18 they
were older than me
now when I messaged that one of it
like that guy from Canada remember that guy Chad
yeah he was [ __ ] big then he tried
being big on YouTube until you knocked
them with [ __ ] intelligent
Yeah, they were horrible. I found them
describe days. They were horrible. [ __ ]
my going to die. Yeah, I'm going to come
back in 5 minutes. Don't
I'll be back, bro. [Music] Uh,
Sorry, bro. I'm just eating some sweets.
Some chicken. Oh, no. Some sweets. Oh, [ __ ]
I love them. You know them pick a mix.
The cherries. I like the cherries.
But as I was saying, yeah, they're
they're fast enough to bully kids, right?
14, 15. But when you become an adult,
they back off. I noticed that.
Which is no different than any than
someone just picking on women really. So
they just contradict themselves. Yeah.
is that Chad guy knew he could win an
argument with me cuz obviously I was a
child like 14 [ __ ] 15. Now he won't
even dare. He'll comment on [ __ ] but he
won't argue. Same as that Joshua, same
as that Jeff. Same as all of them Americans.
Same as Virgin Boy as well to an extent.
They're all big when they're bullying
[ __ ] people a lot younger than them
when it counts like um
when you're not an adult sort of thing
when you're a lot younger than them when
you're not an adult. But now Yeah. Anyways, [ __ ] Oh,
I'd rather [ __ ] live with my mom than
[ __ ] live in a bed sit with no bed in
it, mate. Tell you that much. Yeah. Nothing
wrong with living with your mom.
Nothing wrong with living with your mommy.
Some guy was like, "Oh, at least you tried today."
Yeah, you've been trying for [ __ ] years. So, yeah.
Oh, well. Oh, [ __ ] well. You're [ __ ]
Where are you, mate?
Let me [ __ ]
Anyways, I'm gone. See you later.