Oh [ __ ]
Oh [ __ ] It's not plugged in, is it?
So therefore, that can't be
cuz it's not plugged in. Oh [ __ ]
£35 to get into a [ __ ] rave. [ __ ]
that, bro. Anyways, I'm coming off this
[ __ ] I'm after today. Anyways, man,
it's getting [ __ ] weird again with
these little creepy losers.
It's getting weird again, bro.
It's getting [ __ ] weird.
Five. That is five. Yeah.
One, two, three, four, five.
What do our pictures nowadays? Any
success? Um, what do you think? We're in
England and it's been the same old for years. So, no.
And I need to get this phone as well and
they're not it's not in stock. trying to
get this old phone and it's not in stock
until the 7th.
So once I get this phone, I could
probably go out one more time and then
I'm done cuz I need to save now
cuz I booked these flights. So I can't
afford to be spending any more money in
this [ __ ] old country. So once I get
this phone, that's me.
So So yeah,
why would you think anything would
change when the same thing's been going
on for years?
I don't understand that. How you
possibly think it could change when it's
been going on for years and it continues
to get worse and it continues to
dictate. You know what I'm saying?
How why why would it change? I don't
understand. How could it possibly change? Huh?
I get I'm getting some nice pork from me as well. Yeah.
Obviously I did, but we're not in
Thailand now. We're in England.
But no, you'll never get success here.
It would always be the same boyfriend
[ __ ] The whole country is a dive, bro. The [ __ ]
It will never change in this country. Never.
Even Joe Even though Joe says your past
don't dictate your future. Well, it's
still dictating it. It's It dictated it
yesterday. It dictated it Thursday.
It dictated it the week before that. It
dictated it the past of a few years. I mean,
the same people are in England. The same
people have got unrealistic
standards. So, what's going to be
different when you go out again?
I done 11 of them sober yesterday. It
reminds me why I don't do them sober.
What? What's going to happen literally again?
What will happen again when you go out again? Bro,
I only went out cuz I had nothing else
to do. So, yeah.
Yeah, good for them. There's also
millions of people that are single.
There's also millions of people that are
single. And there's also millions of
people that have to lower their
standards. So, my videos prove
everything when you try to start a
conversation with a stranger. There's
also millions of people that are single.
Um, most men are single. About one in
four men are in a relationship. Tells
you all you need to know. Every single
person, not well, not every single
person, but lots of people I come across
are single. Most of the people I know
are single from different social circles
from which is how I know they don't have
boyfriends. Most of the people that I
come across are single. So nice madeup
statistic. And also the people that are
in relationships or with ugly women.
Most of the days nowadays, most of the
people that are with women nowadays,
they are hunching below, mate. That guy
that I was speaking to on the train
yesterday, he must have been [ __ ] a
normal looking person, right? And his
girlfriend was a plain jane with glasses.
Tells you all you need to know. And I
saw it a few times as well. I'm thinking
[ __ ] So even now when these people are
getting in relationships, look at the
people who they ended up with.
And the fact that most most of the
people I know, most of the men that I
know, so whether they're tenants,
whether they're people I met on a night
out, whether they're people I know
online, they're all single.
They're literally They literally are all single.
Like the most of the people I know are
single. I'm I'm not even joking. Let me
let me see. I'm trying to think
of them are single. There are some that
are in relationships.
These people are single.
These people are single. The tenants are
This guy's single.
So what you're saying doesn't really
make a lot of sense because most of the
people are single. Most men are single.
One in about four men are in a
relationship. And when they are in a
relationship, look at who they're in a
[ __ ] relationship with,
mate. There are many, many, many, many
single people. Many, many, many, many single people,
you know. So, no. [ __ ] mate. I
know. I've gone out. I've been there.
Done it. Worn the t-shirt. And it
doesn't matter even if there were loads
and loads of people in relationships.
You've proved with your videos that you
can't get in a relationship. So other
people are irrelevant. Even if that was
true, even though it's not true because
I know people and I know that most of
the people that I know are single. So
that doesn't make any sense. Whatever
statistic you're trying to come up with,
it don't make sense because most of the
people I know are single. That's what I'm saying.
Yes, there are. And I've also had
chances of being in relationships. And
yes, there are people that's not been in
relationship. There's people out there
that are virgins.
And I've had chances to be in
relationships. And I basically have been
in a relationship. So again, try again.
Stick to what you first said. Yeah. And
don't try try and change the subject
because you're you're wrong. Like it's
it's [ __ ] I can go on my WhatsApp
right now where I I can tell you all
these people that are not connected to
each other and they're all single. Yeah. So,
yeah, most of the people I know are
single and they're not connected to any of them.
Uh, it's not about a mindset, it's about
reality. It's not about mindset. It's about reality.
It's not a mindset thing. It's reality.
I went out yesterday and I'm living
proof of it. them pretending that
they've got boyfriends. I'm living proof
of it. It's not being optimistic. It's
being real with yourself, which is what
the approaching videos show. It's
reality for not getting success.
And we just go round and round in
circles. And this is exactly why I
booked Thailand because of these same
conversations. Like as soon as I got
back in here yesterday, I booked
Thailand because it's no way to live.
We're just going round and round in circles again. So yeah,
you know, and it's even I noticed even
the people that were in relationships
who they were in relationships with,
which also told me a lot about myself.
So you got one decent looking guy who's
fully white with a plain Jane.
So I mean that just tells you there's
better people than me that are single.
There's people that go to the gym.
There's people that got six packs.
There's people that have good jobs and
they still can't find nothing.
Like you think of yourself, but there's
people that are better than you that
still can't find no one. And if they do
find someone, they're [ __ ] the plain
[ __ ] jame. You know what I mean? So,
it's not about mindset. There's too many
stuck up [ __ ] in this country. That's
literally what someone on Reddit said
and that that is the truth.
I'm not in denial. all of this whole
like, oh, it's mindset and all of this
stuff that people make up. I'm not in
denial. It's not even about me
complaining. I'm not in denial.
I'm really, really, really, really not
in denial about this. So many people are
in denial. Just like that guy in Canada,
I said to him, "You can laugh all you
want. You're in denial, bro. You won't
be laughing in 10 years when you're
[ __ ] especially in a country like that."
So, no, they're definitely suckup
[ __ ] in this country. Like, I I I've
even watched other people approach.
Yeah. And they get the same [ __ ] Ain't
ain't that a thing.
Ain't that a thing that you're watching
other people get the same old black,
white, [ __ ] whatever skin color that
they are. That just goes to show you
that it's them. Two people that are
completely not related, right? Doing
completely different approaches and
they're getting the same old. Isn't that
a coincidence? Huh? No. It's these
[ __ ] in this country. 1 million%. You
have none of these problems in Asia.
None of them at all. At all. All of
these people that blame other things is
called in denial.
And they'll learn that as well. You
know, as they when they're old and
they're rocking in that chair and they
still haven't found anyone from sing.
They just would know all along that
they're just [ __ ]
in denial. What the [ __ ] is going on
here? Autism, mate. Yeah, you have got
autism. Stop talking about yourself.
Yeah. Yeah, you do have what been refunded.
One second. What the [ __ ] is going on here?
They might refund me the money and they
gave me the cups for free.
But yeah, the thing is I'm not in denial.
One sec. What the [ __ ] is going on here?
I just bought these.
I know there's nothing wrong with being
autistic. Tell that to yourself because
you're the one that's got it. There's
nothing wrong with being autistic. I
know. Tell that to yourself. You're the
one that's got autism.
I know, bro. What the [ __ ] Hold on.
Of course there's nothing wrong with it.
You've got it yourself,
you know. So yeah, one second.
What the [ __ ]
Oh, I received two.
That doesn't make sense. One second. Hold on.
I don't understand. This doesn't make
any sense, brother.
You've never had a woman in your life.
That's why you're sing. But that's the
thing is you've never had a woman in
your life. Yeah, you have got autism.
That's why you resort to uh that's why
you resort to sing.
This don't make no sense whatsoever,
mate. You've never had a woman. So, I
mean, that's that's that's not possible.
You've got a bird next to you right now.
Keep telling yourself that. I swear
these are the same spastics, bro. I'm
leaving after today. Anyways, this um
community anyways but I've got stuff to do.
I'm leaving this. I said this earlier
that these these people here are proper proper spastics.
So many in denial simps. I don't know
how how many years can people live in denial for?
You would think that I would simp women.
Here's the thing, Greavvesy. Yeah. You
would think, right? I listen um Harry,
you have always been single and you will
always be single. Tell yourself that.
You know the thing is Grezy, anybody
would think that I would be the one sing
women since I've had more women than all
of these people. Anyone would think that
I'd be the one I'd be the one sing. But
they don't get no women
and then they simp
bullying me. But no one in here could
ever bully me. Are you [ __ ] mad? You
people bully yourself. Anyways, I'm
trying to [ __ ]
understand what what what is the refund
about? But um anyone would think I'd be
the one singing women, but I'm not in
denial. I'm not living in denial. I'm
not scared to say what I see. I say how
I see it. But these people don't get no
women and they simp over them. It's
weird. That's so weird.
I'm not scared.
I don't understand. This doesn't make no sense.
What the [ __ ]
I don't want I want them caps. But yeah,
I'm not in denial. Yeah,
I've had five one night stands. I've had
[ __ ] I've had kisses. I've had
dates. Basically been in a relationship.
But I'm not in denial.
That's the difference. I'm not in denial
about what they're like. And I won't
defend them because I'm not in denial.
So I don't know why they children.
Yeah. So, oh [ __ ] Why are they in denial anyways?
These people really are in denial. They
don't get no women, but they still Why
is it always the people that don't get
women are the ones that simp?
Because they think by sing it will get
them women. I don't know why they do it.
Simp will never get you laid, which is
why you're sing in the first place, cuz
you can't get laid. It's [ __ ] up, is
it? It's actually a madness, bro. Yeah.
And you know what's so mad, Harry, is
that you talk about depression, but
you've been on it for years and you
can't get off YouTube.
So, what does that say about your life,
bro? You've been on it for years and you
can't get off it. And you're what, in
your 30s, 40s?
That's what you call depression, me, lad. Yeah.
I don't know why they defend women. It's
so strange. I [ __ ] hate him, bro. And
I've had more than anyone on here.
I'll be honest, bro. I went out the past
couple of days cuz I was [ __ ] bored.