Whoa. [ __ ] [ __ ] was it
They'll make up their mind one day.
[ __ ] hell on this [ __ ] Reddit.
They'll make up their mind one day. E.
Yeah. [ __ ] hell, man.
So they tell people to try and when
people try, they get called desperate.
make it make sense. [ __ ] hell, bro.
Which one is it?
[ __ ] logic, bro.
[ __ ] stupid dog. Shut up. Yeah.
[ __ ] it. Why not, bro?
This country sure is [ __ ] depressing.
Oh, I tell you that. Depressing old England
where nothing changes in it.
And the and you know you the only reason
you go out is generally because there is
literally nothing else to do.
If I didn't go out every Thursday, I
would be I'd go insane. Just like I'm
going out this Thursday. You don't have
no [ __ ] hope. Of course you don't.
There's just literally nothing else to do.
There is no [ __ ] hope in this [ __ ] country.
Everyone's moving to [ __ ] Thailand
now. [ __ ] hell. I saw some reals on
it. [ __ ] normal people are just
moving there now. You know,
you ain't got no chance, no hope in this
country. It is [ __ ] depressing.
At least we still got a bit of money
left to leave, which is a good thing it just know
nothing, bro. Just chilling.
You know that Joe F. Yeah. He doesn't
know what he's talking about yet. I was
actually thinking about this last night
before I went to bed. What he says makes
absolutely no sense. He says that
people like do this stuff for a
reaction, but they he doesn't understand
that they they are reacting for a
reaction. So that's where it doesn't
make any sense. So they're reacting to
you every day being triggered by you to
get a reaction. It doesn't make any sense.
literally and I and I tried to explain
to him a million times like these people
do this even if they don't get a
reaction but they just weren't listening
anyways. Anyways, yeah, Ghost and I went
out on Friday and Saturday
just same old England to cut a long story short.
Yeah, just the same old England if that
answers it. Same old Boring, bro.
No, he doesn't troll me, bro. He's too
thick to troll.
Uh, I mean, are you surprised, bro? I
mean, it's been going on 3 years.
No, no one's getting a mod. No, I'm
about greedy. I mean,
it's been going on for 3 years, bro. I
mean, what what do you expect?
I'm used to it now.
Like, are you not used to it? I'm used
to it, bro.
I'll be real. I go out every week now
because that's the only thing to look
forward to in this country.
I'll be real with you. I mean,
what's what's there to be surprised?
It's never going to change here. Or are
you expecting it is going to?
No, no, no. One uh one did. No, one did.
And uh after about four messages, I Oh,
you want to do something Thursday? And
then they said, "Yeah, sure. Where are
you thinking?" And so I told them where
and then they stopped.
Yeah, you always get numbers, bro. You
don't ever go out and not get numbers.
It's not possible. What normally happens
is you'll get numbers,
they either don't reply, they reply,
then stop replying,
or they will reply and waste your time.
Um, and then they'll just stop replying.
I had one say they don't want to go on a
date because they like to get to know
someone first. It's just a huge waste of
time in this country. That's all it is.
Um a boring to road.
It's not weird, bro. It's just England.
There's nothing weird about it. It's it's England.
It's the same old. It's like what me and
Ant-Man used to say. It's to be
expected. The [ __ ] is to be always
to be expected in this country. It will
never ever change. It will only get worse.
I mean, I'm not surprised. It's [ __ ]
England. It's been happening for years.
What do you think's going to happen? One
day you go out and people are not going
to be stuck up and they're actually
going to be normal. Like, bro, come on
now. Nothing's Nothing's ever going to change.
There was nothing wrong to begin with.
It's them. It's the same old England.
I done about 11. Oh, Ghosting. [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] I forgot to tell you. I
don't really do these approaches sober
anymore. But I done him last week. Where
was it? Saturday. Was it a Saturday? I
done 11 sober. Nothing. Just people
saying they weren't interested. And
I done 11 sober, bro. It was winding me
up, bro. I swear to God, it was winding
me up. I just had a drink. Um, they just
weren't having none of it at all. And it
was sober as well. Those were like the
sober ones. And I'm thinking, well, but
people online telling you that it's
going to change and no, they must be
living in La La Land because this never changes here. Um,
no, not all of them. No,
I think one said uh no, another one said
sorry, not interested. Some ignored.
Yeah, just the same old same old. But
we're supposed to believe that one day
it's going to get better. Huh? Yeah. No
chance. Not in a million years.
Anyone would think you're fat and ugly,
Ghoston. That's what makes me die about
it, bro. Yo, that that's what makes me
die about it the most.
That's what makes me laugh about it the
most is anyone would think you look like
Timmy Eldridge the way you're treated in
your own country.
But then I was going to go fabrics, but
they were trying to charge £35 to get
in. And obviously I need to save money
now. I don't get as much money now. So,
and I wouldn't spend it even if I did
get more money. Um, so I thought, okay,
I've got five numbers, so I don't really
need to go. I'll just go home. So yeah,
but you never know, maybe this Thursday
everything will get better. This will
never ever ever get better, bro. Simple.
It will never change in this country.
Yeah. I got five numbers on Saturday.
One of them replied. I messaged them all
one more time again cuz that's what I
do. Saying, "Oh, go Thursday." No.
Sometimes it works. Nothing. Then
there's a [ __ ] doormat.
So it will never change in this country. Never.
Nothing at all, bro.
Bye-bye, weirdo. I'm not going out this
weekend. Did you not just hear what I
just said? I just said I'm going out on Thursday.
I don't do weekends mainly. I just do Thursdays.
Don't like the weekends. Too many [ __ ]
But yeah, just the same. Oh, nothing changes.
I've got 176 contacts since having this new phone.
Yeah, I'm going out. I do Thursdays.
Um, normally I just do Thursdays and
sometimes I do the Saturday, but I won't
be able to afford to do the Saturdays now. So,
yeah, sometimes I do Saturdays, but
mainly I do Thursdays cuz Thursdays are
better here anyways. I don't like Saturdays,
too many [ __ ]
and um, younger people, but
to I can't even really afford it now to
be honest with you.
I got about 2k left and I need that to I
need that to last
cuz I ain't got it coming in now. So yeah,
in all if I was to actually save money
so that's why I'm basically [ __ ] now.
So yeah, and it still continues to not [Music]
load of uh ghost. Are you trolling me, bro?
Are are you trolling me?
I mean, I've literally specifically told
you that they're not interested in this
country and I've literally told you what
I've what I've done the past two weeks
and then you're telling me that there
could be loads of women. Yeah, women
that aren't interested. I feel like a
lot of you people don't listen to
anything that I tell you. So, I feel
like Yeah, loads of women that aren't
interested in this country.
No matter how many times you have to
keep going over it, over it. I tell you
the truth, I'm only going out Thursday.
Be loads of Northerners down for it. Not
at all. I've been up north about a
million times. I'm still single.
I'm still single. Honestly, the only
reason I'm going out Thursdays is I'm so
[ __ ] depressed and stressed by
various different things. I'd go insane
if I didn't go out once a week.
Yeah, it's a chance. So, even though I
have been up and down the country for 3
years, like you might think I'm being
awkward, you might think I'm being
difficult. Let's speak realistic here. I
have been to every single city in
England you can think of. I've been to
Scotland. I've been to Wales and nothing
has worked for years. So you think the
next time I go out all of a sudden it's
going to be different? I ain't buying
it. Not buying it one bit. I'm not
putting no money on that, mate.
Yeah. I don't feel like feel like any of
you listen to anything I say. I mean,
yeah, I've heard about this Oasis thing
and Yeah. There might be people and
what? They're all of a sudden going to
be interested. They're all all of a
sudden not going to [ __ ] you around.
Really? Even though it's been happening
for 3 years. Okay, man.
Okay. Yeah. Suddenly one day you go out
all of a sudden it's just going to
change. Delusional at its finest, bro. Yeah.
It will never ever change in this country. Never. [ __ ] never.
[ __ ] never ever ever. I just go out
cuz I just I want to stay in.
It will never change or women never cuz
it would have changed by now. If
something was going to happen, it would
have happened by now. I think that's
logical. I think that is actually like a
logical thing to say.
I generally think it is like a logical
thing to say in it. I think it's logical me. Yeah.
We don't go out because we have hope. We
have no hope. That's that's that's not
what we're going out for. We know it
will never change and never in this
country forever and always
the same old. We go out because it's
because there's nothing else to do,
you know, and it's fun.
Can't work at the minute. Can't do
anything at the minute. That's that's
the only reason I go out.
That's the only reason I I go out. I
don't go out cuz I've got hope.
You don't have hope.
I just like getting drunk and waking up
with it still in me. And yeah, like but
it will never change in this country.
Never. Because it's been going on for
years. That's just in denial to think
that. And it and they're trying to
charge you £35 to get into a [ __ ]
club. What the [ __ ]
£35 to get into a club?
No. The piss taking,
the trolling, the boyfriend [ __ ] is
never going to stop. It's never ever
ever ever ever going to stop. Uh,
stop talking about yourself. Anyways,
I'm not acknowledging the self
projectors anyways. They just get
blocked. All right, Steven. Do you hear
LJ trying to say that he's on 2.5K a month?
Not in a [ __ ] million years. I asked
him, right, how much do you get? And he
said, "Well, after everything, 2.5K,
not a [ __ ] chance." He's on £400 a
month. Yeah. No. No. [ __ ] 2.5K month
that lives on YouTube begging. Oh my
god, bro. That's funny. That's funny as [ __ ]
That is funny as [ __ ] mate. [ __ ]
2.5K a month in [ __ ] Ireland. Yet,
you're begging on YouTube. [ __ ] off,
bro. Don't even sound believable.
don't even sound [ __ ] believable, bro.
Not even in the slightest. Does that sound believable? You know
what's happening? Um, just very depressed. Really
fed up. Fed up with life. It's like I
have every Thursday to look forward to.
Now, now I'm like Ant-Man. Now I'm
actually like I'm actually going out
because there's just nothing else to do
now. There's no hope with women. There's
no hope. Nothing. I just go out cuz
there's nothing else to do. We lit There
is literally no hope in this country.
I've accepted that there's no hope.
I'm only going out now until I find some
sort of side hustle. Then I'm leaving again. Simple.
There's literally just leaving.
I like going out cuz I like meeting new
people and it's just fun. But you
literally have no hope in this country.
There is no hope. I used to go weeks
without going out.
I got so much stress.
That's one of the reasons I go out. So yeah.
Nah, it will never change. Five numbers
only one replied then they stopped replying.
Yeah. But somehow we can't. The past
can't predict the future.
So they say, huh?
Well, it doesn't look good. That's all I
can say. It definitely doesn't look good. Yep.
Oh, bro. I really want to make some
money on this football.
All I need to do is win two double. Both
teams will score in a row.
You know, I was actually tempted to play
roulette today, but I'm never going back
to them days. [ __ ] that, bro. Like, I
might not I might not get as much money now, but
I still have some savings and [ __ ] so
whatever. I'll never go back to that
[ __ ] [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] that, bro.
Happened to be [ __ ] skinn and [ __ ]
stressed. Oh, no. Never again going back
to them days.
Yeah, stop talking about yourself.
Anyways, I'm not acknowledging these
self-p projecting sad little weirdos.
I've got it all figured out.
100 pound on both teams to score returns
350 to 380. Another both teams to score
returns 14500 pound. Dumb.
I'm going to I'm going to get some both
teams to score and watch.
If we don't find a side hustle by then.
If we find a side hustle by then, then
I'm not doing it. But if we don't, then
that's looks like that will be the only way.
I hate gambling. I hate anything about
The only reason I ever go back to it is
cuz I need more money.
Simple. I hate gambling.
So that's it. I started actually hating
it. When I started giving up on it, I
actually started just hating it.
It just stopped interesting me, you know.
[ __ ] that, bro. [ __ ] that.
It's bad, bro. Gambling is bad.
I don't like gambling.
I'd rather just go get [ __ ] drunk.
I think it's cuz nowadays that I know
how hard it is to get money.
Like how hard it is and
you know what I mean? So it's like
it's like L. There's no way he gets 2.5K
a month. There's no way, bro. If you was
left with 2.5K a month, you wouldn't be
begging on YouTube.
He doesn't get nothing, mate.
Why don't you just be honest? Like me, I
get £,100 a month now. I'm basically
[ __ ] now until I find a side hustle.
I've still got savings and [ __ ] But why
don't you just be honest with yourself?
Why do you have to lie? I don't
understand why the people need to feel
the need to lie. I told you how much I
get. Rocky Roy tells you how much he gets. Now,
you know, I've got savings and [ __ ] but
it's it doesn't matter. Like, we Why
don't you just be honest with yourself? You know,
honesty is the best policy.
I'm not rich.
Um, I'm not rich, bro. I'm [ __ ]
I'm pretty [ __ ] basically.
But then you get people like Virgin Boy
and [ __ ] Lord J trying to convince
people they got money. It's silly.
They need to be honest with themselves, bro.
No, I don't think so.
They need to be honest with themselves,
man. You know,
which I don't care what other people have, bro.
I I just told you I've just got about 2K left.
It's more than enough for me.
But I know why you get these people that have to
pretend that they have all this money
when in reality they don't have nothing.
It's [ __ ] It's just silly.
But yeah, the the stuff with the it
would never change in this country with women. Never.
Never, never, never will it ever change
in this country with them. Never.
We should have a We should have a date
this week, bro. What the [ __ ] We should
have a date this week. Nothing.
We should actually have a date this week. But no,
we got nothing.
Nothing at all at all.
You still there, Joe?
You know, Antman said he would still do
Thailand only if even if he just got
benefits. He said he'd live on £50 a
week. I couldn't do that.
cuz I'd want to go out drinking and
[ __ ] I couldn't live off £50 a week.
Some people would have to if they wanted to save.
Well, see, you either choose one or the
other. Like me, when I go out drinking
on Thursday, I'll make sure I don't
spend more than £70. I can't afford it.
And it's not even that as well. It's uh
the fact that you don't need to spend
any more than that because you've done
it a million times. Spent two300 on nights out.
Yeah, I did. So, I can spend like 60 70
80 a week.
Um, and obviously
still save as well, but I can't spend
more than that.
So, yeah, then I cuz just can't afford
it. Simple as that. So, yeah, I might
afford it. I don't mean technically
can't afford it. I mean, if we spend
more and more and more, we won't be able to save.
But at the same time, if I don't go out,
I'd go mad.
Yeah. I don't know.
I mean, obviously you can gamble to try
and win more money, but then if you
lose, you are [ __ ] That's the
problem. You're [ __ ]
You're literally [ __ ]
So, and ch and more often than not, you
will lose. So, there's
Yeah, there is people that live about 50
a week. You You'd have to do it.
You'd have to do it. I mean, I still got
like around 2K, but still,
I can't be wasting money anymore. I
don't have it to waste. I don't have it
to give. Simple. So, yeah. Yeah.
So, I probably spend about 70 80. So, yeah.
Oh well, is what it is, isn't it?
But we don't have to lie like L and
Virgin Boy having to convince people
that they got money when they have
nothing. Literally nothing.
Virgin boy literally has nothing.
Shows the housing [ __ ] benefit every
[ __ ] month to try and make it seem
like he's got money. What a sad, bro.
What a [ __ ] sado. Yeah.
Well, like I said, if I find a side side
hustle before August, then obviously
there'll be no football bets. But if
not, then that's what it's going to have
to come down to.
That's what it's I'm not used to this
life, bro. I'm not used to sitting
around being lazy. You see, I'm not used
to it. I'm used to doing stuff in life, you know,
either working or going around or being
proactive. I'm not used to it.
You know, it's all right for people like
Laney. She's old. She's She's had her
life. She didn't lose her. I lost most
of my income. You know what I'm saying?
So, I lost most of my income. She didn't
lose most of hers. I lost most of mine.
That's the difference. So yeah,
it's [ __ ] depressing really.
And then you can't even get a [ __ ]
date. What the [ __ ]
You can't even get a [ __ ] date.
Nah, bro. Just some money I was making,
so I just don't get as much anymore.
out on Thursday. It's going to be the
same old same old boyfriend [ __ ] It
will never change. Nothing will ever
change. I went out Thursday, Saturday,
and I can't even afford it. And I went
out Thursday, Saturday, and I got what I
[ __ ] got [ __ ] eight numbers.
Not even a [ __ ] sausage.
Somebody agreeing to go out. Oh, where
are you thinking? Told them where to
where we're going. Stop replying.
[ __ ] hell. Tik Tok really [ __ ] this
dating game up, didn't it? It really
[ __ ] this dating game up.
It's madness, bro. I spent 150 in them
two days as well, which I won't be able
to do Saturday this week. I can't afford
it. So yeah, I need to be saving for
other things. I need to be doing other
things with the money. I can't be going
doing that [ __ ]
How I do what anymore? Well, I go out
or approach what?
Well, I go out cuz I'm bored and I've
got a lot of stress.
So, if I didn't do that, I'd be depressed.
So, yeah. Well, I am [ __ ] depressed,
which is it's something to look forward
to, is it?
But there's no hope in this country. I
have no hope in this country. It will
never change. Ever. Never.
Never in a million years.
Sad is it?
What do you want me to do, bro? Go out
on the street every day and start
approaching people every day for two
weeks. Yeah, you can get [ __ ] bro.
I'm not doing that.
No, it's depressing. I done on Saturday.
Yeah, I done like 11. So, it [ __ ]
made me depressed
cuz it's not normal. It shouldn't be
this way. You're you're a good-looking
person with a nice little cap, a nice
little beard. You should be able to get
someone. This is not normal.
This is not normal, bro. It's not normal
at all. And when you're sober, you can
actually understand it. Whereas when
you're drunk, you don't really care cuz
you're drunk and you're just enjoying it anyways. So,
oh yeah, back in 2009.
Yeah, you used to be easy back then. Now
you can't get nothing, bro.
You can't get nothing. You literally
can't even get a date. You can barely
get a response.
I got five numbers on Saturday. I think
I got one reply that agreed to meeting
me and then they just ghosted. So
yeah, it's just really really really bad.
They will never change this country. So
what do we do every day? Go on the
street and start approaching
in hopes to get [ __ ] someone interested. Yep. Uh,
put some more numbers here.
And I think I got three on Thursday. Was it three?
how many? I don't think any of them replied either.
Gets worse and worse and worse.
Maybe one replied.
But yeah, they replied and they they
agreed to meet and they wanted to know
where. So I told them and yeah,
just not interested in this country.
Wait, where is
Yeah, they're not interested in this
country. They base their [ __ ]
standards on [ __ ] Tik Tok, bro.
What's them other numbers? Who are them other people?
They base their standards.
I think I got two numbers on uh one
second. Let me I got two numbers on um Thursday. Sorry.
They all base their standards on social media.
So they've all got the same unrealistic standards.
Yep. But it's to be expected.
But guess what? There is something you
can change. You can leave the country
cuz obviously we we know like, oh [ __ ] uh
Subzero is getting off to Portugal.
Well, he'll have a hard time doing that
on £300 a month.
Yeah. Jetting off. What? Being on
YouTube all day on £300 a month? I don't think so.
That Subzero ain't got a life.
That's why he's on YouTube every day.
Have you seen the correlation? How these
people can't take one day off of
YouTube? That's all you need to say to
them. They can't take one day off of
YouTube. It's their life. Simple.
But there is one thing you can do. If
you can leave the country, that's
something where where like mate, even if
you have to live off 50 quid a week to
leave the country,
I mean, you can do that. So, I mean,
nothing stops you doing that.
But in terms of the dating game in this
country will never ever change. They all
have the same unrealistic standards by
what they see on [ __ ] Tik Tok and [ __ ] Instagram.
I'm I'm sorry. One second. Let me
Yeah, it was two numbers on Thursday.
Yeah, I'm sure it was two numbers. Well,
it doesn't matter anyways.
It's sad how you can't even meet someone
in your own country. It's crazy, bro. Is it?
Sorry, I just can't get over it. Sorry,
bro. I just can't get over it. Sorry to
sound like a parrot.
I mean, realistically, there's no point
even going out Thursday, but we're not
going out for that. That's the whole
point. We're not going out for that [ __ ]
We're not going out for that, bro. So,
what do you expect somebody to do? Go
out on the street approaching every day
for two weeks to get a date? I'm not
doing that. And no one should have to do
that. It's not normal. It's not [ __ ] normal, bro. So yeah,
it's a bit rude how none of them how
only one replied out of five numbers.
That's crazy. But sometimes I've had
three numbers all reply. Sometimes I've
had nine numbers. None of them's replied.
And I think it's it's all dead now, bro.
like the whole approaching thing.
Everything's [ __ ] social media now.
Everything's [ __ ] Tik Tok.
So yeah, you got no chance in this country.
Not a single chance. Not a Merlin of a
I'm trying to see here. No, never.
It will never change.
Oh, no. I did get three numbers that Oh,
yeah. Listen to this one.
We were supposed to meet uh the other
day. Yeah, they said, "Oh, I'm not not
much." So, I did get three numbers for
Yeah, I do remember this. Not much. Just
in bed, you same. How come you didn't
meet today? I guess you don't want to
meet. I'd rather get to know someone
before I meet them. I said, "Well,
that's how you get to know someone by
meeting them." No. Well, you're clearly
not going to be going on a date with me
then. So she turned out to just be a
[ __ ] [ __ ] So that was the third
number. Yeah, I remember now. Yeah. So I
did get three numbers Thursday. I knew
there was one missing.
Uh and that's the one I was supposed to
meet in another one. It just never
changes. Same old England, isn't it?
Just like Thursday when I come back on
Friday, I'll be like, uh, same old
England. Nothing much to report. So
it will never change in England. Never.
It will never change in this depressing country. Never. Let's
say uh over there.
That makes no sense because
this this person says, "Okay, see, I'll
tell you things. Don't take offense. A
YouTube interview can be creepy. Let me
give you an example." Try to think that
you're a woman and a man like you
approach that and if you don't feel
safe, how do you expect? But that
doesn't make sense because they will
give their number, reply, keep replying,
then stop replying. So that's just an excuse
cuz if you didn't really feel safe,
right, you wouldn't give your number.
And we're having the same conversation.
We're going round and around in circles
again. We're going round and round and
round and round and round in circles again.
So you're just making excuses for women.
We're just going round and round. We're
having the same argument again and
again. So, let's just cut that [ __ ] off
because it doesn't make any sense
because they wouldn't reply to messages
that I know I'm right, bro. Like, I'm
not going to [ __ ] sit here and argue
for [ __ ] sake. I know out of everyone,
bro. Like, I've been [ __ ] Scotland.
I've been to [ __ ] Wales. I know this
[ __ ] You know what I mean?
And what about the bars? And what about
the clubs? The [ __ ] bro? Like, stop making excuses
for [ __ ] sake. Like not every single
woman is is afraid of men. Stop talking
[ __ ] You know what I mean?
They talk [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
We're just going around and around in
circles. We're having the same We're
having the same argument over and over
again. This never changes, bro. This is
exactly what I'm saying. The same
conversation with the same stupid
people. No, I'm not even in bed.
whole dating thing just [ __ ] annoys
me, bro. I hate it. I hate it.
I [ __ ] hate it, bro. It never changes.
It's so annoying. Like, you know what I
mean, bro? It is so [ __ ] annoying. It never changes. It literally
ever changes ever.
Hey, bro. Cory, it's so annoying, bro.
Like just just the whole thing of it is
just so [ __ ] annoying.
Do you know what I mean, bro? Like it's
so [ __ ] B. And you know the thing is,
bro, it's not like you're fat and ugly.
You know what I'm saying, bro? Like Like
you know how you say you hate Timmy?
Yeah. Look at Timmy. Like he's fat and
ugly. Yeah. He's not one of the worst
people on it. But look at people. Yeah.
Like [ __ ] Timmy Eldridge. Yeah. It's
not like you're [ __ ] fat and ugly
like here when you can't even find
someone in your own country. It's
[ __ ] There's so many things that are
[ __ ] up about There's so many things
that are [ __ ] up about this country, bro.
It's weird, is it, bro? It's [ __ ] up.
I thought I'd mention Timmy cuz you
don't like Timmy. So,
but it is funny, bro. How I've been
talking about this for 9 years. I've not
been on it for 9 years.
It's [ __ ] depressing.
It's [ __ ] depressing, bro.
And it's so depressing. It never changes
ever. Never ever changes.
No, I thought about relaxing, bro. I'm
not in denial. I'm just saying it how it
is. I'm not in denial, bro.
I'm not in denial. I'm just saying it
how it is. It's [ __ ] annoying, bro.
Like, I go out to have fun, but the
whole thing makes no sense.
Have I been gambling? Uh, I don't gamble anymore.
Why are you asking me if I gamble when I
literally tell I've literally told you I
don't gamble anymore?
I think some of you have got [ __ ]
memory loss. You don't listen to
anything people tell you.
Why are you asking me if I gamble and I
literally don't gamble anymore?
Some of these people have got memory loss.
Memory loss, bro. Definitely.
But why would you think I gamble when
I've specifically said I don't gamble anymore?
Who wouldn't be down, man? Same old [ __ ]
with the dating in this country.
Yeah. And pigs will fly soon as well,
Richie. Yeah. And see this all of this
stuff that people say, Steven Howard, it
would have happened by now. Think of it.
Yeah. You're getting three grand a
month, right, for 3 years. You're
traveling up and down the country and
you're getting nothing. It's the same
old boring. Back back in the time back
in the back before any of this [ __ ]
it's the same old boring. Imagine that
you're on three grand a month. Yeah. And
you're not working for three years.
You're nothing but traveling, bro. Which
is what I was doing. And you've not met
anyone in them 3 years. And so what? All
of a sudden now you're on less money.
Um let's say you're on less money now.
And you go out one more time and then
what? Suddenly you're going to meet
someone. It would have happened. It
literally literally would have happened
in them 3 years.
It would have happened in them three years.
Literally, if something was going to
happen, it would have happened in them three years.
Generally, would have happened in them 3 years, bro.
One million million% it would have
happened. You would have met someone by
now. You wouldn't be here right now,
you know, [ __ ] dealing with this
[ __ ] So yeah,
you would have met someone in them three
and a half years.
Them three and a half years. You would
have met someone. I think it's like
three and a half years. Three and a half
Especially on that kind of money, mate.
[ __ ] hell. You know the amount of
money we used to have
still never made a difference. We was
also working as well. We was also going
to the gym. Nothing. So, I can actually
say I've done it all. I can actually say
I've done it all, bro. And to be left
with 2K, I can say I've done it all. Simple. Yeah.
And now I'm Yeah.
No regrets from my end.
I used to have 50 pound notes coming out my ass.
I mean, I still got I still got a lot of
money, 2K, but [ __ ]
Well, you have to give up because
nothing's happened in 3 years. So, if
something was going to happen, it would
have happened by now. That's my logic.
Yeah, bro. Probably kill yourself. I
mean, your your your options right now
is you either kill yourself or you leave this country.
You know, the stress that a lot of
people have have uh put me under. I'm
not going to lie to you, bro. I was
getting some homicidal thoughts. I'm not
even joking. That's how you know you're
[ __ ] up in the head. You either kill
yourself or you leave the country and
you start a new life somewhere.
That's like literally all I have. You know,
you either kill yourself or you leave the country.
You start a life somewhere else. That's
that's literally the only option I have.
And I was getting some like nasty like
homicidal thoughts and [ __ ] bro, which
I've never got before. That's from
depression. If you look it up, you can
actually see people people get like that.
Cuz if you was going to meet someone,
you would have met someone by now.
That's the difference.
I know it. You know it.
always think I've gambled, but I
haven't. I don't gamble, bro. I actually
don't even gamble.
Nah, I don't even gamble. What the [ __ ]
Nothing changes in this life, bro. Nothing. Nothing, bro. Seriously,
the change. You should have found
someone by now.
You're not succeeding in anything. It's
the same old England.
Every time you go out, it's the same old England.
You can't think positive. All you have
is negative. There's no being positive.
Everything is negative. I went out
Thursday, I went out Saturday and it was
all negative. Same old with women. You
could go out a million trillion times
and it would be the same old boring. I
could bro, you know, the maddest thing
is you can go into an online casino
right now and you could win two grand,
right? So say that you've got two grand spare.
You could go out every week, right,
spending300 pound on booze until all the
money run out and the same thing would
happen. You could have a same You could
literally have a night out every week. 1
2 3 4 5 6 Let's say about seven nights
out. You could go out for seven weeks
straight, right? Hing it up, approaching
and it would be the same old story.
Literally like it would be the I don't
know why it's the same old, bro. It
would be the same old.
It would be the same old boyfriend. It
would be the same old [ __ ] It would be
the same old same old never ending.
I can't believe I'm not got a date this
week. What the [ __ ] The amount of I
[ __ ] tried them two them two [ __ ]
days. I don't even have a [ __ ] date this week.
What the [ __ ]
But we're told to believe that. We're
made to believe that one day you'll wake
up and everything's perfect.
You're in La La Land, bro. One day
you're going to wake up and everything's
perfect. Well, that doesn't actually
ring right because think of them two
days. That was Thursday and Saturday. I
didn't even plan to go out Saturday. I
got enough numbers to have even got one date. So yeah. Yeah.
I'm on like a codable every day now, bro. Literally,
this life really, really is depressing.
And you know what, right? It's not even
so much the whole like, oh, you don't
get as much anymore cuz I live the life.
I proved what dating was all about in
this country. I lived the life. I I have
no regrets, you know, to still have
money left. But
I shouldn't still be dealing with women
at my age.
I shouldn't still be dealing with it.
I should not still be dealing with this
[ __ ] You know what I'm saying? Got a
TV, got a bed, got a home. I shouldn't
still be dealing with this in my life.
You know what I mean?
I shouldn't still be dealing with it. I
shouldn't still be having to try. I
should at my age be with someone.
Doesn't matter where the [ __ ] they're
from. You know what I mean?
It's insane, bro.
It never changes ever.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Never have, never will.
It's annoying, isn't it? And it never changes.
You should be with someone.
Yeah. Stop talking about yourself. Bye-bye.
Stop talking about yourself. It's not
nice to call yourself disabled.
Uh, let's see.
Like I said, bro, if I'm all of these
things, you you people would be sat on
YouTube every day.
Like, there's no need for a reaction.
There's no point in giving a reaction to
these people. If everyone is so skinn
and everyone is so disabled, why are
they the ones on YouTube every day?
End off. That's all you got to say, bro.
That's how they show everyone what they
are. You understand, Cory? That That's
how these people show what they are
by what they do every day on YouTube
sat online repeating themselves
all alone. They prove what they are
every day, talking about themselves.
Yeah, but it's the truth though, Richie.
Cuz if everyone if everyone's so skinn
and disabled, right? Why are they sat on
YouTube every day
repeating themselves? Come on. Come on,
bro. Why are they sat on YouTube every
day by themselves, repeating themselves
if everyone's skinned and disabled
answer, bro? It's not funny.
Why are they on YouTube sat alone
repeating themselves on live streams if they
Bro, you're boring. You're boring. Bye-bye.
It's cuz they're talking about
themselves obviously, bro.
They wouldn't be on here if if they if
they weren't any of these things,
but I think it's not necessarily I even
care about the dating thing. I just Rich
I just think I can't get over how [ __ ]
up it is.
Like I don't know. Like I'm trying to
make it make sense, bro.
I I think I just can't get over how
[ __ ] up it is. You know what I mean?
I just can't get over it. It's just mad
to me, bro. You know what I mean?
Yep. So they say. So they say, Stephen
Howard. So they say
all of them are, bro. All of them are.
Yeah. When you least expect it. Yeah.
That's what they say.
I could understand it, bro.
Uh, you don't know where I am.
And also, bro, you don't know where I
am. And if I was at my mom's, no one
would care about your letters because
everybody knows what you people do on YouTube.
So, I mean, bro, I'm not even at my
mom's. And even if you think I am,
you're more than welcome to send
letters. No one cares about your
letters. You know, when you sent them
the second time, everyone was just like,
"Oh, yeah, just people on social media.
No one cares. No one is ever going to do
your dirty work. Not the black man, not
the neighbors, not the [ __ ] boys in
blue. No one's ever going to do your dirty work."
Like, bro, I was living in Stratford for
[ __ ] what, almost a year? Yeah. You
knew where I was. And I I've been told
you to write them letters. Write the
letters all you want. No one's going to
do your dirty work.
Like, understand that, [ __ ] boy.
You can send whatever you want. No one's
going to do your dirty work. No one's
going to kill me. No one's going to come
in the door. Simple.
You're boring, bro. Go back to being
section again. You're boring.
You don't know where I am, and you will
never know where I am. That's the whole
That's the whole good thing about it.
You will never know where I am.
Sad little [ __ ]
Yeah, I'd rather have no bird than have Natalie G. Yeah, definitely.
Cory, listen, bro. If I If I Bro,
listen. Yeah. And let me tell you something. Yeah.
Talking about yourself again. You You
see these people, bro? Yeah. Like that.
Triple H. I'll be real with you. Do you
know why? You know why I didn't actually
to go Newcastle, bro? I I be cuz, bro, I
know what these people are about. Like L
Triple H, Virgin Boy, even that Joe. I
know what they're all about, bro. I've
done this so many times before. Like
when I used to go up north and none of
them would come out. That's why I don't
do it because I know what they're about.
LT knows what they're about. Like
between me and him, do you know how much
money and time we spent traveling up
north numerous numerous numerous times?
Bro, you don't even know. Like I went to
Newcastle three times. You see it? Yeah.
He didn't come out once. That's why
like, bro, if if this was back in the
day and I didn't know any better, I
would Newcastle literally this weekend,
bro. This weekend coming, I would be
there just like I did with Bomb. Just I
went like I went to all them other
places, but I know what people on here
do, bro. They try to wind people up.
They're never going to meet anyone. Then
they all stick up for each other. But
bro, if I didn't know any better, like
it's like that that smokeoky me a couple
of weeks ago when I said, "Oh, like show
me where you are, agreed to the meet and
I'll meet you." Bro, if this was about 2
years ago, I would have been went there going live.
But between me and LT, the amount of
times we went up north and went live and
they didn't come out and bro, we don't
the whole [ __ ] UK. We know what these
people do on here now.
That's why no one bothers with them. You
know what I mean?
Like that Triple H and that line using
an example. We know what they do on
here. Same with Virgin Boy, you know?
They're all the same on it. All of them.
Triple H, Dom Bomb, uh, [ __ ] Lord J,
[ __ ] Trevor Dawson. They're all the
same on here, bro. Like, everyone knows
what they do on here.
>> No, I wasn't with LT the whole time.
I've never met LT, but he used to go up.
I used to go up north. How the [ __ ]
could we We were enemies, you [ __ ]
idiot. I've never met him.
Don't even know what he [ __ ] looks like.
We were enemies, bro. But I'm saying
he's done it. I've done it separate
times and no one ever comes out. That's
why I didn't go to Newcastle, bro. Like,
yeah, I just said it cuz I was mad, but
bro, we all know how the cookie crumbles.
The amount of time and money I used to
[ __ ] waste trying to [ __ ] lead
these people, bro.
Now, I went to Newcastle three times,
bro. And that Triple H didn't come out
once. Not once. And every single time I
went there, I addressed him, bro. Now,
he wasn't my pal, bro. When he's trying
to say, "Oh, this guy owns you and he
bullies you." Like, he what he does on
here is he comes on here and he [ __ ] sto
with a person that knows that's never
going to meet me. The guy's never ever
going to meet me, right? The guy's never
ever going to meet me ever and he knows
this. So he will come on here like [ __ ]
sir which I think is a bit cheeky
because he's not come out the three
times I've went to Newcastle. Yeah. And
he will continuously come on my channel
Cory. He will continuously come on my
channel when [ __ ] start knowing damn
well that the person's not going to meet
me and he's not going to meet me. And I
don't like that bro. I don't find that funny.
Trust me bro. I don't find [ __ ] like that funny.
Yeah. So, like it's No, he's not my pal,
bro. The only one I like on here is Unworthy Clock.
I think he's a cool guy, bro. I've met
him. He's a nice guy. He stayed out of
the drama and yeah, he's he's Charlie's
good, man. And obviously you, but you
didn't meet me when I was in Newcastle,
but I mean, you're not coming on here
trying to [ __ ] stir
and I've done it with him three times.
That's the difference.
Yeah, Charlie's a sound guy, bro. Trust me.
And even Tiger, to be honest, man, I
don't even really have any problems with Tiger.
But that trip rates is continuously
coming on here, trying to [ __ ] stir time
after time after time again and again
and again and again and again. You know
what I'm saying, bro? And I see what
he's doing cuz I'm not stupid.
You know what I'm saying? But trust me,
bro, if this were a couple of years,
like I said, if it was 2 years ago, I
would went there and started talking
about his kid. I'm I'm not joking, bro.
I would have went up there on this
Saturday and I would have started
talking about these kids. Trust me, bro.
I would have if I didn't know any better.
If I didn't know any better, bro. Trust
me, you don't know me, bro. I used to do
it all the time with Bomb with [ __ ]
Bro, I used to go to [ __ ] mad places.
I went to [ __ ] Middlesbrough when
they come out. God, bro. We know. We
know what these people are about.
They're just trying to get a reaction
and just annoy people.
You know what I mean?
Yeah. You know what I'm saying? They're
all the same, bro.
I can give you a few examples. Virgin
Boy, Bob, Trevor Dawson,
[ __ ] There's a few of them as well,
bro. There's a there's a few of them.
I'm trying on here.
But do you know anything that
contradicts itself? Um, Cory is is is
they this is what I was trying to
explain to Joy. They say, "Oh, they do
all of this stuff for a reaction." But
the thing is, bro, is that even if they
don't get even if they don't get a
reaction, they would still do it. They
would still do this [ __ ] Even if they
didn't get a reaction, they would still do it.
And what are they doing to get a
reaction? They are reacting to you being
triggered by you. So, the whole thing
doesn't make any sense. So they're sat
on YouTube on another account being
triggered by you
reacting to you to get a reaction from
you. Doesn't make any sense. So it just
doesn't none of it actually, bro,
bro. No one cares about that guy in
Birmingham. It's old news now, bro.
We've all seen how you people act when
people come to your cities. No one cares about [ __ ]
um prime suddenly that catches someone
off by God. That happened like years
after as well. No one cares about that,
bro. Stop living in the past.
So there's no point wasting£3400
going to Newcastle
when no one on here is ever going to
meet you. It's the same, bro. It's the
same thing if you went to Glasgow. None
of them would meet you. Do you think
that Shagger would try to meet me? No,
he wouldn't, bro. Do you think that
Shagger or that TR would ever try to
meet me? They would never, bro.
Never. Never. Ever. So, yeah.
But yeah, if I didn't know any better
with that Triple H, I would have went up
there and I would have started talking
about these kids. Trust me. But we all
know that how the cookie crumbles with
these people. And it's quite
embarrassing as well.
And that's it, bro. That bro, it doesn't
make any sense. Like they, like I said,
bro, they can't go there. They do what
they do every day because they're
jealous. It's just simple as that.
They're jealous. Simple as that. You're
reacting to get a reaction.
It's what they're doing to get a
reaction. And then like I said, even if
you don't react to them, they will still
do it, which is what I was trying to
explain the other day, but the guy kept
talking over me. So, so yeah,
they don't do it for a reaction, bro.
They do it because they're jealous and obsessed.
Cuz what the [ __ ] are they doing?
They're the ones that are reacting.
They're the ones that are doing videos
and videos of they're wasting more time
than you giving a reaction. So, it
doesn't make sense. Yep.
So yeah, bro.
What do you reckon Thursday is going to
be like when I go out again? Thursday
and yeah, Tramodo, you can send letters
wherever you want, bro. You don't even
know where I am. Good luck with that
one, buddy. Waste more of your time and
waste your money.
No one cares. You don't even know where I am.
And you know, between two of them houses
that everyone knows about what you do as
well. So, yeah.
Good luck with that, buddy.
See, the thing is, right, these people
think that they're psychologically
[ __ ] with your head, but you're
actually [ __ ] with their head because
they're the ones that have to come on
YouTube every day obsessed doing videos
on you just to try and get a reaction.
So, actually, you're actually living in their head.
You're actually living in their head, Red Free.
You're actually living in their head.
If you think about it, [Music] Yeah,
we uh we never change dating in this country, bro.
Nah, no GTA stream yet, bro.
I've got the Xbox. I got the TV. I can
do it. But yeah.
Oh, really? No one cares, bro. He's not
getting my attention.
Good for him. He's not getting my
attention, bro. I'm not even going on it.
I don't react to losers. Sad losers
told me if he pays paid for my flights,
I'll go there. Pay for flights, you'll
come here. Simple. I don't care. I'm not
going on it.
I don't care about them little bully
victim losers, bro. Let them crack on.
I need to get a [ __ ] adapter for a
plug, bro. [ __ ]
Yeah, he's talking about himself, bro.
He's calling himself a loser. Like I said,
I'm saying to my face,
I don't care about ignore them little
losers on this channel and dog. The little spastics. Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] I found out with a flu, bro.
No one cares about that loser.
Red Star. That's what I'm saying, bro. They're obsessed.
That's what I'm saying. They're reacting
to me. This is what I was trying to say
to Joe, bro. Richard, I've just gone on
it, bro. They're reacting to me.
They are literally reacting to me.
They're so obsessed. Oh my god, bro.
They're They're reacting to me, though.
This is what I was trying to explain to
this Joe EA, bro. Is that the ones that
are triggered because they keep reacting
to me by wasting their time on me.
They're reacting. I love it.
On YouTube, stalking me, obsessed,
reacting to me. I'm doing something
right, bro. Yeah,
I've got all of these old people
obsessed with me, bro. I'm winning. I
love it, bro. I love it.
Skid [ __ ] 40-year-old virgins
obsessed with me. I love it, bro.
Reacting to me every day.
That's where just none of it makes any
sense, cuz they're actually reacting to
you. They're actually obsessed with you
because for every one thing that you
say, bro, they've said about a hundred
different things. You know what I mean?
Isn't it mad, Richie? Yeah. How they've
got all of this money, but they're sat
on YouTube all day stalking.
Isn't that a madness, bro?
Everything just points to their own
life. Have you noticed on here, Richie?
Everything points to their own life.
Sat on YouTube every day. That's what
That's what you call the scenes, bro.
Reacting to me. You know what I'm
saying? Richie, they're reacting to me,
bro. I love it.
You know what I mean?
Sat on YouTube obsessed.
Uh I love these people, bro. It's funny
cuz they're reacting to me. Go back on
the thing, bro. Look how much they're
reacting to me. >> Yeah. >> [ __ ]
Like they're calling people skin, bro.
But we all know that these people are
skinn on YouTube every day. All sat
alone on YouTube every single day and
got nothing. It's like Richie, bro. You
know them times I go to the pubs? Yeah.
Once a week, twice a week. Oh [ __ ] bro.
Do you ever see these people on you? You
ever see these people at the pub? Nope.
They're sat on YouTube skin waiting for
their benefits. So everything that they
say, it's just about their own lives.
Sad 40year-old bully victims. Think
about it, bro. No one can join the hangouts.
Not one person can join the hangouts.
You know, they're just skint little
jealous 40year-olds that ain't got
nothing but an application.
Skint disabled people that's got nothing
but an application that react to me
every single day.
These are the proper bunters, bro. Do I
Bro, do I have to put the link up again?
Do I have to put the link up again? People
join, bro. They talk about them. I'm I'm
surprised, bro, to be honest, how they
can can keep talking about themsel every day.
It's a madness, isn't it? [Music]
I always win, bro. Always.
I'm not [ __ ] fighting these mongos on here, bro.
If he comes to London, I'll fight him.
[ __ ] fight these mongos.
You don't need to fight any of these
people, bro. They come on here and do
what they do every day cuz they're
jealous. They don't even Bro, you don't [ __ ]
Everything that they do is jealousy.
That That's another That's another thing
that I think I thought of yesterday as well, bro.
Is that they do
all what they do on here because they
are jealous and they are living their
worst life. That's also another thing to think of.
they're living there. You obviously have
something that they're jealous of. This
is what what I was also saying the other day, bro,
is that you clearly have something that
they're jealous of. For them to come on
here every day reacting to you and being
triggered by you non-stop. You you
clearly have something that they're jealous of.
That's another thing you need to also
consider. You know,
it is pure obsession and pure jealousy.
It's not what like we used to do. Yeah.
We used to write something to Timmy.
Yeah. And we used to get like a reaction
out of him. These people are absolutely
obsessed day in and day out weakening in
jealousy. Like it doesn't matter. I
don't know what that they're jealous of.
Maybe you got more money than them.
Maybe you're better looking than them.
Um it is definitely jealousy, bro. Cuz
it's it's a lot different than what
people used to do with Timmy. Timmy used to [ __ ]
people used to write stuff for like
three minutes and then just get him
triggered because it was funny. But no,
these people do it for beyond the
reaction, bro. Because A,
even if they don't get a reaction, they
still do it. B, bro, they're reacting to
you every day. They're being triggered
by you every day. So what? They're being
triggered by you to get a reaction.
Do you understand, bro? So none of it
makes any sense.
this constantly the same [ __ ] Yeah. Well,
>> yeah. Nobody cares, bro.
Like I said, he knows where I am. The up is there.
>> These jealous people.
>> You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
Yeah, no one cares, bro. Anyways, let's
stop talking about it. Let's stop giving
them attention now anyways. It's what
these little 40y old losers crave.
It's what these little sad, jealous
losers crave. Let's stop giving them
attention. Anyways, stop bringing up on
my [ __ ] channel.
Sad little losers. It is funny though,
the last thing I want to say. Don't you
think it's so mad how it's always the
same losers like Red Star?
They're They're clearly jealous of
something, bro. Clearly clearly jealous
of something. They're clearly jealous of something, bro.
I'm not going to say what it is. I don't
know what it is, but they they Steven
Howard, they're clearly jealous of
something. for them to sit on YouTube
obsessed every day reacting to you
because that they're reacting to you by
doing these videos and writing about
you. They are being triggered reacting
to you. So why would somebody do that
every video on YouTube for no reason?
Cuz it's something that they're jealous
of. That's what I'm saying, bro.
Anyways, [ __ ] enough about these losers.
I'm going to have to try and figure out
how to stream GTA. But yeah, that's
that's that's what it is, bro. Yeah.
They're clearly jealous of something.
Yep. You're talking about Yeah. Yep.
Smoking the tide. You're talking about
yourself again. It's not nice to talk
about yourself. I've got more money than
you would ever have. And I've got more
friends than you'll ever have. Stop
talking about yourself. Go back to LS
and go self-reflect on there. This ain't
a channel for you to self-reflect your
life on. You little self-reflecting
little jewelry [ __ ] Oh, and you're
another one that never said anything
when I was in Newcastle. Mate, how long
are you going to keep self-reflecting your life?
I'm in a house right now and I've got
more money than you and I've got more
friends than you. What the [ __ ]
Why do you keep talking about yourself?
It's not nice to talk about yourself
like that, bro. It really, really isn't.
Why do you keep listing things that you don't have?
Like what is with you 40-year-old losers?
>> I don't understand. Why do you talk
about yourself so much? It's depressing.
All they do is project their own life.
Self-reflected little losers.
It's really bad, bro. H.
It's really, really bad. How about they self-reflect?
Sad, sad, sad.
self reflectors. One second, [Music] bro.
Sorry about that. But yeah,
Yeah, bro. [ __ ]
Yeah. What are you saying? Greasy, man.
before I'd come on [Music]
the same projected on large a greasy the
same people that are reacting to me
every day. Wow.
I feel so sad how much bully victims
they are. Yeah. That they have to come
on YouTube every day trying to bully
other people. I feel so bad for these
bully victims. Can you just imagine like
how bad their real life is? Wake up,
[ __ ] can't even get out of bed, can't
leave the house. And then when they try
to leave the house, every day, every
time they try to leave the house, bro,
they probably just get bullied. These
people, you know what I mean?
Sad little bully victims. Have you got
on it, bro?
Sad little self-projected little bully victims.
These people, whether they really are
something to laugh at, you know what? I
should actually just come on in more
often to be honest, bro. They're
actually something to laugh at. These absolute
absolute bully victim spastics sat on
YouTube every day. I could actually say
that as well, bro. Sat on YouTube every
day. Ain't got a life. I love it, bro. I
love it. Sat on YouTube
every single day. These bully victims
never been seen with a friend. Never
been seen with money. Can't get off of YouTube.
You know what I mean?
They really are the true bully victims
of society. They are something to laugh
at. Really are.
these little bully victims.
There's something to laugh at. You know
what, Greg? I'm actually going to start
coming on here every day, bro. Like, you know,
they really, really, really are
something to laugh at. They really are
these sad little spastics that can't get off YouTube. Yeah,
they really really are something to laugh at.
Sad little YouTube keyboard warrior cowards.
They are truly are something to laugh at. Yeah. Yeah. But
you know what? We should all Why don't
we all come on the hangouts and talk about this?
We should do that, bro.
All come on the hangouts and talk about
this. How does that sound?
But they can't come on the Hangouts,
bro, cuz they're too disabled.
They're too disabled and too ugly. They
can't come on the Hangouts. Isn't that
right, Grezy Boss?
Yeah, I did. They're too [ __ ]
[ __ ] and too ugly. Yeah, man. Sad.
Yeah, these people just want a reaction by reacting.
Let's swerve the little losers. These housebound losers.
It is, to be honest with you, it's
amazing how they can do it for so many
years. You must have something they're
really, really jealous of.
They must I I really am trying to
understand what they're jealous of to
come on YouTube reacting to me every day
and they're reacting to me and I'm not
even saying anything. I mean, they've
got to I've never known people to be so
jealous of one person. It's
>> it's just it's crazy to me. I mean, it's
good, but it's crazy, isn't it?
Cuz they don't understand that these are
the ones that are triggered. These are
the people that are reacting every day.
They're writing 50, 60, 70 [ __ ]
100 comments reacting to you every day.
So, I mean, you you have something that
they're jealous of.
Definitely definitely have something
that they're jealous of.
Yeah. What's up, bro?
Yeah, man. Anyways, so
with this GJ
enough about these
repeating triggered losers,
they ain't got a life, man. They ain't
got a life. Set on YouTube every day.
All of this, bro. You know what all of
this is, right? Is to try to get people
in a hangout screaming and shouting and
that's what all it is. It's not going to
work. It's literally
it is not going to work, matey.
We know that none of you people ever
going to come on the hangouts. None of
you people ever going to beat anyone.
Like, it's not going to work, bro.
It's not going to work.
sitting on [ __ ] Hangouts arguing with
a bunch of people that's never going to
meet you. [ __ ] that.
Nah. I don't get a kick out of arguing
with pathetic people that ain't got a
life. Jealous people that ain't got a Nah.
So yeah. Nah, I don't find it funny me,
bro. I think it's pathetic.
One second. You want the link?
Anyone that wants to talk [ __ ] on large
A's, why don't you join the hangout? Come on.
Don't any of you little bug guys.
One second. Let me put the link up.
What? One second.
phone's going to break one day.
This phone's going to break one day. So,
let's see. Out of all of you, yeah, that
go a talking [ __ ] how many of you
cowards can actually come in hangouts. Come on.
Let's see how many of you can come in
the hangouts. Start talking. Start
showing your face. This will show what
you little bugos are really about. You
little spastics of this community. Yeah,
you little weasels. You little self-reflectors.
All of you, man. All night. Mike, Red
Star, why don't you come and hang out? Come on.
You're too much of an ugly [ __ ] bongo
to come in hangouts. And that's also how
you beat these people
cuz they can't join Hangouts, bro. So,
here we go. Someone want to join? >> Hello.
>> You're all right, lad.
>> Who's this?
>> It's Smokey B.
>> Uh, no, it's not. Who's this weirdo?
>> Oh, you are you that keyboard warrior
voice a reason? Yeah.
>> No, it's Smokey.
>> I don't argue with keyboard warriors.
Bye-bye. Don't beat anyone. See you
later, [ __ ] You're mad.
And you're done. Bye-bye now.
See you later. [ __ ] bug guys. Bye-bye. Get alive. Bye-bye. Uh
All right. Listen, Red Star, come to Hangouts.
Listen, listen. Red Star, come to Hangouts.
Come and hang out. Come and hang out.
Come and hang out. Red Star, come to Hangouts.
Come to Hangouts. Come and hang out.
Come to the Hangouts,
Red Star. You don't really know one, you
little keyboard warrior. You can't even
join the hangouts. [ __ ] hell. I don't
want to speak to a [ __ ] [ __ ]
making silly voices, bro.
If this Red Star really bullies people,
he will come in hangouts. See,
Red Star, all that spazz,
come in hangouts. If you really If you
really bully someone, come in hangouts.
Oh, [ __ ] hell. They can't come in the
hangouts, bro. What the [ __ ] Jesus Christ.
Jesus Christ, bro.
These people really are disabled. Do you
know what? I actually feel sorry for
them, Steven Howard. They really,
really, really, really are disabled.
Dis that's why they're on YouTube every
day. Cuz they're disabled, isn't it?
That's got to be what it is. They're
skint and disabled. That's why they're
on YouTube every day. Let's look at the
evidence even now with you. They call
people skint. They call people disabled,
right? But who's the one that can't get
off of YouTube? Who is the one that's on
YouTube repeating themselves every day?
These people are cuz they are the
disabled ones. Think of it, bro. Don't
It's not about you're this, I'm that.
No. [ __ ] you. You're this. These people
are proven to be disabled skinned people
every day because they can't get off of YouTube.
Every day their life proves it when
they're on here every single day sat
alone on YouTube.
You know what I'm saying, bro? Like it's
it's they are the proper bully victims
of life, bro. I feel bad for them. I
really really feel bad for them, man. you know,
and yeah, don't join that [ __ ]
hangout, bro. The thing is what they're
trying to do, Steven Howard, is they're
trying to get you on a hangout so they
can shout over you, talk over you, and
repeat themselves. Think of it, bro.
They're all on YouTube now cuz they're skin
[ __ ] Ain't got a life. None of these
people got any friends. That's why
they're on here. They want you to join
so they can shout over you. This is what
they'll do, bro. You'll join the
hangouts. They will shout over you, bro.
Yeah. And shout continuously shout over you.
[ __ ] put things up so you can't even
defend yourself. Like, bro, [ __ ] these
people, bro. They're all sat at home on
[ __ ] YouTube. They ain't got no life.
They're all skint. That's why they're on
LJ's talking the same [ __ ] now, bro.
Yeah. It's They're all skint low lives.
Skint disabled low lives. That's what
they are, bro. They ain't got nothing.
Literally [ __ ] all. They've got nothing
in their life but YouTube. Literally nothing.
They want people to join and start
[ __ ] shouting over people.
They're sad skinned little jealous
disabled people all sat at home just
like what you said. Sat at home on YouTube,
which is what they do every day cuz
that's their life.
That is literally all they have in their life.
None. It's been established that none of
these people are going to meet anyone.
You know what I'm saying? Just leave
them. They're sad little disabled people
on pip. All of them people right on Lord
J Steven Howard. They're all disabled.
All skin. All got no money. All
obsessed. They're all just they're all
they're everything that they call other people, bro.
sad little disabled people that don't
leave their house. That's what they are, bro.
You know, bro, you know the maddest
thing is Yeah. You know, with these
people, bro, if you if you touch them,
bro, you know they pulled over with one finger.
These disabled people, you know that,
bro, you know these disabled fat, ugly
people sat at home on YouTube every day.
Yeah. You know, if you touch them with
one finger, bro, they'd fall over.
They're [ __ ] absolute disabled
bastards, bro. They're something to
laugh at. Triggered. Look how triggered
they are, bro. You should go on L J's.
You should look at how triggered they
are. They're so triggered. They're
triggered, bro. Look how Look how
they're typing about me. I love how
triggered these little 40-year-old
spastics are. The joys of being on £300
a month. It just goes to show that
you've got a better life than them. More
money. It just goes to show, bro. Bro,
Steven, listen, brother. They're sat on
there typing, typing, typing.
They're typing, bro. These little
spastics are typing.
It's so nice being better looking than
having more money than them. Look at the
little spastics. They're sat on YouTube
all alone on their lonesome.
Why are they all sat on YouTube alone?
Mr. Loners, Mr. lonely. They're all the same, bro.
To be honest, bro, we shouldn't be We
shouldn't bully disabled people, bro. We
shouldn't bully these disabled people. Honestly,
we need to stop bullying these disabled
fat people, bro. Come on, bro. We need
to stop. We need to stop, bro.
I mean, it's bad enough that they're
triggered every day. We need to stop it, bro. Really?
I think I'm going to play some Franklin
in a minute. Bye-bye, [ __ ] Yeah.
Sad the table. People ain't got a life.
Oh yeah, Smokey B. You bullied me so
much, bro. That's why when I asked you
to show where you wasn't Milton Kings,
you shut your mouth. Isn't it funny how
all the you are the same on here, right?
You claim that you bully people, right?
You claim that you bully people, but you
can't even meet anyone. You don't, bro.
The only thing that you bully is
yourselves. Fat ugly people sat on
YouTube every day. The only thing that
you bully is yourself. Fat ugly people
on YouTube, which is which is the truth,
bro. Like, bro, you get asked. Isn't it
mad how like most of you people you get
asked to show where you are? And only
you people can do it because you people
are fat ugly people on YouTube every day.
You know, fat ugly people with no money.
So the only people that are getting
bullied is yourselves. That's it.
All of these people are in their 40s.
They're all on benefits. They've got not
a pot to piss in, which is why they're
triggered on YouTube every day. This is
why they're triggered and obsessed on
YouTube because they're all bully
victims. Do you understand Steven
Howard? Every time these people probably
try to leave their house, they probably
get [ __ ] slapped up. Every time they
probably try to walk to the corner shop,
right, they probably get slapped up,
bro. Do you understand?
It's because these people are just fat, ugly people.
That's what they are, bro. Fat, ugly
bully victims. They're the real bully
victims, bro. Why do you think none of
them can come on Hangouts? Why do you
think none of them can come on Hangouts?
Cuz they're all fat, ugly bully victims.
It doesn't matter what they write on
YouTube. They're on YouTube every day.
They're [ __ ] sad, fat, disabled bully bully victims.
That's what they are, bro.
Anyways, let's stop talking about these
little mongos now, bro. [ __ ] know.
We've already triggered them enough.
Jesus. So, how the [ __ ] do you stream on this Xbox?
I've never done it on Xbox before, bro. Yeah.
Reacting to the same disabled people
every day. Well, they're actually
reacting to us to be honest. They're
actually reacting to us because they're
the ones that are writing [ __ ] all day.
That's how triggered they are.
They have to come on YouTube every day
triggered because you're better looking
than them and you've got more money than
them. Not me, bro. Not me.
They They're [ __ ] They're [ __ ]
bully victims, bro. They're absolute
bully victims. Why do you think they
have to come on YouTube every day
triggered? Because they're absolute skin bully victims.
Why do you think they talk about skin so
much? cuz they're talking about
themselves. They are the real skin ones.
£300 a month, £400 a month. Universal
credentials as I like to call it. Why do
you think they they call people skin?
Cuz they're sat indoors all they skin themselves.
Sad little bully victims.
And you've got something that they're jealous of.
Oh, listen. You got something that
they're [ __ ] jealous of.
Think of it that right now, Stephen
Hour. Do you think any of these people
have got a Xbox, a phone, a TV, designer
clothes, and two grand in their bank?
Not any of them. And you think any of
them are in their 20s? No. Do you think
any of them have any of these things? Do
they [ __ ] have any of these things, bro?
They don't have any of these things.
That's why they're sat on YouTube every day.
You understand? Yeah, I'm a [ __ ]
That's nice, bro. Come and say to my
face. You are a [ __ ] All of you
people on YouTube are spastics.
Oh [ __ ] Yeah, you people are the true
spastics. Sat on YouTube every day skin.
Yeah, you are [ __ ] Stop talking about yourself.
You people are the biggest [ __ ]
spastics. Can't get off of YouTube.
Can't even leave your house. Yeah, you
are the real one. Real true spastics of
life. The biggest spastics of life.
Yeah. Stop talking about yourself.
You know what I need to do, Stephen
Howard and Grezy, bro? I'm going to give
you my new channel. Yeah.
And don't say you don't want it because
if you actually want content, bro, then
you're going to have to see it, bro. I'm
I'm going to give you my new channel at
some point, bro. I want to get away from
these little spastics on this projecting
community. And they just ruin
everything. They actually ruin
everything on the channel, bro. These
little mongos, these little disabled
people. They ain't got a life.
Do you know what I'm saying, bro? Like,
they're [ __ ] disabled as [ __ ] Like,
I'm telling you, bro. I'm just going to
tell you, Steven, and a few other
people, and that's it, bro. Like,
I want to be playing Franklin, and
people I don't want these [ __ ]
40-year-old spastics following me, bro.
These little mongos that ain't got a life.
[ __ ] little mongos. Yeah, stop
talking about yourself.
Yeah, you're talking about yourself, but
the difference is you're already bored.
Stop talking. Yeah, bro. It This
community is just full of
self-projecting spastics, bro.
Like, we should just go on our main
channel and then you can watch it here.
You are skinting.
That's why none of you people show
yourself cuz you're fat and ugly and you
can't get off of YouTube. Yeah. Try and
try and join again. Try and join again. Listen, bro.
Oh, he's owning me, is he? Yeah. Well, I
mean, I offered to pay for his flight
and he won't come here. You people don't
own anything, bro. You're living your
worst life. Stat on YouTube. No money,
no life. All you have is each other to
to [ __ ] talk to. You You people are
continuously being owned by life. You're
the spastics of life. This is why you're on here,
mate. Life is owning you. No friends, no
mother talking about yourself again.
Anyways, we're not even reacting to
these people anymore, bro. Let them keep
reacting to us.
I feel so I feel to be honest with you,
I actually feel privileged.
Don't chat, you coward munching spas.
Listen, bro. If you've got anything to
say, you can come and say it to my face.
Yeah. If you've got anything to say, you
can come and say to my face. If you're
not going to come and say anything to my
face, stop writing stuff behind the
keyboard, you sad little 40year-old
virgin low life.
You know, you are the spaz. All of you
people are spazzes. That's why you're on
YouTube every day by yourself because
you are the ultimate spazzes. Skin
spazzes ain't got a life.
Anyways, bye-bye spastics, [ __ ] mongos,
jealous people. All of this, right? It
just shows your jealousy. All of this
going online talking about me every day,
it just shows all of your jealousy. I
love it, bro. I love it.
That's good, man. That's really good.
>> You're not allowed to talk about me, big nose.
>> Bye-bye, Virgin. Man, this jealousy
towards me, bro. Do you know what? I'm
actually going to stay on here, you
know, because having these people, what
have I got that they're jealous of?
Like, bro, like, what? Why are they so
jealous of me? Is it Is it cuz I'm
better looking than them? Is it cuz I've
got more money than them? Like, literally,
is it because I'm better looking than
them? Is it cuz I got more money than
them? Like, let's let's talk about it,
bro. Come on. Let's stop talking saying
that you're this, you're that, and let's
just stop the name calling. Let's
actually be real about it. Why are these
people so jealous of me? I want to know
what I have that they don't. Cuz when I
called my mom the other day, I said to
her like, "This is mad.
You'd give up life." Well, why do you
keep talking about me every Okay, okay,
you're not jealous, right? So why are
you so obsessed with me? Yes. Okay. I
have nothing. Okay. Okay.
I have nothing. I've got absolutely no
money. Got no clothes. Got no TV. Got no
Xbox. Okay. I have nothing. Your life is
perfect. You've got all of this money,
right? I'm [ __ ] So why are you so
obsessed with me? Because it's jealousy.
The only thing it points to is jealousy.
You're coming on here every single day
calling people this, calling people
that, calling people this, calling
people that, being spastics on YouTube
every day obsessed, but you're claiming
that your life is better than theirs.
Bro, you're in denial. If you think that
you're not jealous. You are in denial.
It's clear jealousy. Think of it, bro. I
don't waste my time on people that I'm
better than. I don't sit around talking
about a [ __ ] ratfaced virgin on a
grand a month because I know that I'm
better than them. So what you're saying
does not make any sense.
Of course it's [ __ ] jealousy. Of
course it is. Of course it is. So you're
sat on YouTube, right? Repeating
yourself every single day like a
[ __ ] but your life is better than
mine. Bro, just get real with yourself.
I think these people can't stand the
fact that you're better looking and you
got more money than them. That's what
that's what I personally think it is. If
I was going to put money on this year,
like right here, right now, I'd say it's
because you're better looking and you
got more money than him. That's what I
think it is. Like what Ronald Pump said.
What do you think, Steven Howard?
Let's like actual put like guesses on
it. That's what my money would be on.
My money is that No, no. I think that
they're jealous because you're better
looking than them, you've got more money
than them, and you're younger than them
as well. Because obviously, a lot of
these people are quite old. That's where
the jealousy comes into it. That's where
the obsession comes from, where they
come online every day reacting to you,
being triggered over you to try and get
like a 10second reaction.
That's literally the only logical thing
it can be is jealousy. Because it's not
like they come on here for like five.
No. They spend their whole life being
obsessed with you constantly,
constantly, constantly, constantly,
constantly. Then a normal person would
think, well, hold on. Why would anyone
do that if they're better than this person?
Because the only thing it could be is jealousy.
You know, I've had a lot of people say
to me like a million times, right, that
you know, you should be a psychologist.
They actually said that to me cuz that's
the only thing it can actually lead to.
There's nothing else it can actually be.
Definitely definitely jealousy.
It is definitely 100% it is jealousy on here.
You know, like this ratfaced virgin, he
he knows that I'm better looking than
him. I get more money than him.
I've had more women than him. And he
hates it. This is where the jealousy
comes from. It is what it is, bro. You
are better looking than all of these
people. You have got more money than all
of these people, bro. Listen, how much
money have I shown on here? And you've
got a better life than them as well.
It's just like what that Ronald Pump
said, more money, better looking, and a
better life. And it kills them. He's
right. He generally generally is right
because think of all of the people that
on here. Yeah. Not many people get
targeted. Timmy doesn't get targeted.
Really, Monty never got targeted in the
way that I got targeted. So, it seems a
bit strange. It's your looks and your
money they're jealous of 100%. They're
jealous of it because if they wasn't,
bro, they wouldn't waste their life
being triggered over you every day and
being obsessed with you every day.
That's what I'm saying. And I have to
say it that way cuz obviously Joe X like
their whole life is being obsessed with
you. That's what I'm trying to say to
you, bro. You know what I mean? So
they're a lot worse looking than me,
bro. So that's where the jealousy comes
from. And they've obviously got no money or nothing.
Cuz if they had money and they had a
life, they wouldn't be on here every
day, bro. They would not be on here every day.
So it's clear it's clear as day that
they're jealous of something, bro.
Well, they wouldn't be on here every day
doing what they do. Simple.
So, I don't think I'm wrong in saying
that, bro. Definitely jealousy. 100%.
They're just little weirdo spastics.
They're just [ __ ] They're just a
bunch of weirdo little spastics on here,
aren't they? Steven Howard. They're just
weirdos. Weird disabled people. Bully
victims. That's what they are, bro.
Yeah. It's [ __ ] weird, bro. Is it?
I just can't believe these people, bro.
They're [ __ ] like, what the [ __ ]
I've never known people to be so jealous
of someone, bro. Like, in my whole life,
I've never ever known people to be so
jealous of of a stranger. It's [ __ ] wild, bro.
They have spent, bro, about literally an
hour talking about me.
[ __ ] madness. They're up. They're
[ __ ] jealous, bro. They've got some
serious serious serious serious problems.
So that's it, man. It's [ __ ] weird.
An hour. They've been talking about me
for an hour, bro. And they're trying to
get a reaction out of me, Stephen
Howard. That's them reacting. Them doing
all of this stuff, bro. Yeah. Is
reacting to me. So that doesn't make any
sense. Today I've been reacting.
You know what I'm saying? Reacting to me, bro.
They're just low life scum, aren't they,
bro? There's there's nothing else. And
have you seen I have actually tried
meeting that uh LJ, but he doesn't want
to meet anyone that's not disabled. He
just wants to keep arguing and arguing
and arguing and arguing and arguing, but
he doesn't actually want to meet anyone.
Because if you've actually seen the last
few times I've been on there, all he
does is sort of change the subject
section. He just wants attention.
He just wants attention. He just will
try and change the subject. Change the
subject again and change. He doesn't
want to meet anyone. This is what these
little retards do. They just want to
annoy people, but they don't actually
want to meet anyone.
Unless they're [ __ ] disabled as
[ __ ] Timmy. Do you understand? And
then and then and then what's going to
happen is they're just going to shout
over people and shout over people and
shout over people and shout over people.
That's literally all they want to do. Yeah.
[ __ ] dog, bro.
See, now they're on to someone else now.
Why don't they just leave people alone,
bro? Now they're going on to someone
else. Why don't they just leave people alone?
What the [ __ ] It's so It's mad.
Smokey be talking about people's family.
Bro, no one cares about you talking
about people's family because you're
never going to say anything to anyone's face.
Milton Kins boy. Yeah. Do you remember a
few [ __ ] weeks ago I tried to meet
you? You didn't want to meet me. You're
just a little Milton Kins key.
No one cares, bro. You can bring up
family all you want, but we just know
that you're never ever going to say
anything to anyone's face.
You're just a [ __ ] Milton Keen boy. So,
no one really cares about any of these
pe these people, bro. They're little,
bro. These people are just [ __ ]
disabled. That's all they are, bro.
They're just disabled people, bro.
That's all they are. Like, you'll touch
them and they'll fall down, bro. That's
what they are. Yeah. Yeah,
they're [ __ ] weirdo, isn't it, bro?
Someone else that gets that's that gets
But look, they're all talking about
other people's lives. Have you noticed?
They all come on here every day and talk
about other people's lives when reality
they're the ones that are skin on
YouTube every day. Isn't that funny, bro?
You know that it's all about other Well,
let's talk about these people's life.
£300 a month, sat on YouTube, ain't got
no friends, all skin. [ __ ] Friday,
Saturday, they're all on YouTube. Let's
talk about these people. Steven Howard
sat on YouTube skin every single day.
Why do you think none of them dare to
[ __ ] join the hangouts?
They're [ __ ] all they do is talk about [ __ ] money.
Money and other people. These little
[ __ ] virgins ain't got a life. They
ain't got no money. That's why they sat
on YouTube every day.
[ __ ] Hiccups had a nice lamb shank today.
They're [ __ ] weirdos, bro. Is it?
They really are weirdos.
Proper disabled. Is it?
They're sat on YouTube disabled. Talking
about people doing a delivery job.
These people are real bully victims,
Grezy. They really are.
They really are well and true. True bully victims. Yeah.
Anyways, how are you today, Grezy?
I'm depressed today, man. Going to go
out for some drinks on Thursday.
I had a nice lamb shank today. Can't be
wasting money on uh takeaways.
Yeah, I've not been good, greasy. Life's
just been getting worse and worse and worse.
Bad experiences with women, getting
intrusive thoughts and [ __ ] I went for
a walk earlier.
This life never gets better, does it?
I generally think if I didn't have
Laney, I generally think I would do
myself in if I didn't have Laney
cuz it's not fair, you know, for parents
have to deal with a child dying.
Yeah. Just just life just gets worse and
worse and worse. Screamsy, I went out
Thursday, Saturday, I got eight numbers.
them two days I only got one reply. They
agreed to me and they stopped. So it
just gets worse and worse and worse, doesn't it?
Gets worse and worse and worse. The only
good thing about life is sleeping, bro.
Oh, sleeping. That's the only thing I
get out life.
Just life don't change, Grezy. Just life don't change.
I can't believe Virgin Boy. Yeah. Called the police.
Like imagine that. Yeah. Calling the
police on someone and then you're still
obsessed with him.
[ __ ] hell. He is definitely jealous or something.
Definitely. Definitely. He is definitely
He's such a nasty little virgin as well.
He is such a nasty nasty little virgin.
You know that that's what he is. He's
such a nasty little [ __ ] virgin. Yeah.
[ __ ] nasty little virgin.
Isn't that right, Steven Howard? Ugly [ __ ]
Yeah, such an ugly bastard.
Funny enough, I need to see a solicitor
tomorrow. Anyways, I've got a solicitor's appointment
that's got to be added to it as well. Yeah,
Virgin Boy knows he's [ __ ]
Yeah, Virgin Boy knows he's [ __ ]
Yeah, Virgin boy knows he's [ __ ]
That's what it is. Police have said [ __ ]
off. Virgin boy knows he is actually [ __ ]
Virgin boy is obsessed. He is [ __ ]
obsessed. I've never known someone
someone so obsessed in my life.
I've never known someone to be so
jealous of someone. It's quite scary, isn't it?
Yikes. It's quite scary, is it, bro?
He needs to go get laid.
Jay Thompson is still stalking me again.
You know what it is? I think that
they're jealous cuz you're better
looking than them. I've got three or
four [ __ ] stalkers on here, bro.
Stalking me every [ __ ] day. Every [ __ ]
Three people. I think they're jealous of
your looks. That's what I think it is.
Sorry to sound like a fame bastard, bro,
or something, but it is it's it could
only explain why grown men would be
obsessed with another grown man.
Greavves, I'm trying to get to the
bottom of it. I'm really really trying
to get to the bottom of why they would
come on here being obsessed reacting to
you every day nonstop for years and
years and years if they weren't jealous of you.
I I I can't think of any other reason but jealousy.
You know, we're all we're all entitled
to uh different opinions here. People
don't get blocked for having different opinions,
but it seems very very strange, doesn't it?
Seems like they're jealous to me. But
cuz why are they stalking you every day?
Why are they following your every move,
following your every move, you know? Strange.
[ __ ] Now they're going to about Timmy now.
Now they're going on about Timmy.
What the [ __ ] bro?
These people are sad virgins.
No one tell me about them again, bro. Please. Yeah.
Monty's calling me.
Who does me? Steven Howard.
Yeah. Money wants to join.
Yeah, I got eight numbers them days. Uh, Thursday, Friday,
same old. No. Uh, one reply, then stop
replying out. Eight numbers. I didn't
even realize I got eight numbers.
Eight numbers I got in them two days. I
didn't even [ __ ] realize it was that
many. No, I got two replies. Actually,
both said they were going to meet me and
then they never. But don't forget,
Nicolo, your past don't dictate your
future. We've got this Thursday.
We've got this Thursday, bro.
Yep. No, the past will don't dictate
your future. We got this Thursday to
look forward to. I'll be out on Thursday
again drinking cuz I go out every
Thursday. Can't do two days a week now.
Can't afford it.
Hopefully I can win money in the football, bro.
Yeah, I'll win money in the football
next month. Uh hopefully.
I don't know, bro. But yeah,
but remember, bro, your past don't
dictate your future.
Even though it has been going on for
years and it continues to happen, but
you never know, bro. Yeah,
But yeah, it never changes, bro.
Well, you've just answered your own
question, bro. I don't know why people
keep telling me to keep trying when I've
tried more than anyone in the world. I
don't know why people are telling me to
keep at it.
I don't know why people telling me to
keep at it when I've been doing it for
years to be honest. Someone was like,
"Oh, you going to do any approaches sober?"
Yeah. They've got no life. They've got
no money. They've got nothing. We know
about these little self projectors. They
were going on about me for like 1 hour,
bro. These little sad little cowardly
little [ __ ] mongos.
They ain't got a life. They're sad spastics.
They've got no life. That's why they sat
on here every [ __ ] day, year in year
out. These little disabled mongos. They
were going about me for [ __ ] an hour.
There you go. One link. Oh, [ __ ]
They got life, bro. sat on YouTube skint every day.
That doesn't make any sense because
you would have met someone in 3 years.
If every woman was technically
different, you would have met someone in 3 years
with the amount with the amount of
traveling and trying. If that's the
truth, you would have met someone in
them 3 years.
Technically, if you go by the
statistics, right, if they were all
different, you would have met someone by now.
So, that doesn't even make any sense.
I've been all over England, Scotland,
Wales, stores, malls, libraries, coffee shops,
[ __ ] you name it, I've been there. [ __ ] Sara.
Like, you might think I'm being
difficult, I'm being awkward, but I'm
not. I'm actually not, bro. I order it
all on my channel as well.
I've been all over England. I've been to
Scotland. I've been to Wales. I've been
to every city you can name of except Yeah, mom.
>> Yeah, bro. What's up?
>> Yeah, sorry. I [ __ ] up.
But there is no faith. If you was going
to meet somebody, you would have met
someone by now. Simple.
It's been years, man. Years.
It's like I gave that 2K example, that £2,000 example. So, yeah,
it's fake money.
No, it's not a fake. Why does it?
>> Yeah, bro. These bastics never stop on
here, do they?
>> No, they never stop. They just the same.
I don't come on anymore. Yeah.
>> It's just the same disabled people
obsessed every [ __ ] day, bro. They
don't stop, do they?
>> You ain't got a life,
>> you know.
You ain't got no life pe yet
sitting on YouTube with a pair of trees
having a con.
>> So it's still the same people, you know.
>> Yeah, I know it is.
Most of them are some now, some not.
>> Yeah, they can't get off of YouTube on it.
No need to call us. Tell us to get
alive. But they're the ones who got
There's no point going life anymore.
I've gone now. There's no point. That's
why I haven't been live.
>> Yeah. It's a good thing, isn't it?
>> Hasn't been live either. We both
>> They got you kicked out the They got you
kicked out. They got you kicked out of
the hotel. Morning. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. In black.
>> They're weirdos, bro.
>> Yeah, they're freaks.
>> Yeah, they call me skin. They call Yeah,
they call me skin as well.
Yeah, they call me skin as well.
>> DJ, if they if they weren't skin, they'd
be out. If they weren't
>> That's what I Bro, I said the same. Bro,
I say the same thing. I said exactly the
same thing. If If we're skinn, right,
why are they the ones on YouTube every
day? That's what I said. That's what I
said as well.
>> Cuz you got no life. No entertainment.
They said the fat bastards, the old pensioners, PJ. >> Yeah,
>> that's it. We're old [ __ ] idiots,
man. And there's only this all to be to
be honest with you, PJ. There's only so
many young people in this community. The
rest are older than me and you and Natalie.
The youngest ones are in this community
who's actually younger enough. That's
[ __ ] Jaden and Jaden's mate. That's
all I know. Who's the youngest in this
community? Are them two?
>> But but the rest of them, they like in
the 50s to 40s to 60s. >> Yeah.
>> And that's not [ __ ]
Well, how old am I? 35. Most of these
are made in a already in a
>> Yeah, I don't really cover them anymore.
>> I don't really cover any
probably YouTube is actual content
instead of sitting on YouTube. I with a
couple of spastics. >> Yeah,
>> that's what it is. It's a [ __ ] sat on
a [ __ ] computer. Can't go out because they're bedridden. Yeah,
>> lazy bastards.
Are you skin?
>> I need the advert.
I'm always skin PG.
>> I'm always
a bit skin to be honest with you.
>> Are you Are you actually skinned? >> What?
>> Are you actually skinned?
>> Yeah, I'm actually skinned. >> How?
>> Completely skin. Broke out my eyes. Do
you want to see my money? >> How?
>> I got flies flying at my wallet. People,
>> how are you? How are you scared when you get money?
>> Because your boy, >> huh?
>> Everyone gets money. Everybody
>> How did you How did you run out?
>> How did I run out? >> Yeah,
>> I haven't run out of money.
I haven't run out of money. Nobody's
rich in this world, PG. Money go comes and goes.
>> So you've got zero pound.
>> Money comes and it goes.
>> So you've got zero pounds.
>> I got zero. Yeah, I've got
Yeah, I've got zero pounds. PJ, >> really?
>> Why? Yeah, really proper brought me proper bridge.
>> Yeah, right. Why?
That's a good thing. You
>> your virgin friend keeps stalking me.
>> Who's that? He's my 13 friend.
>> Virgin long legs. The the virgin.
>> Is he your boyfriend name? Well,
>> I'm sure with you, PJ, he needs
>> he needs to get laid.
>> Yeah, I think I think
>> I think he's got feelings for you, PJ.
>> Can you Can you help him get laid? He
needs to get laid.
>> I think he's got feelings for you.
>> Yeah, I don't have for him. He's a [ __ ] virgin.
>> Help him.
>> Hey, hey, can you help him get laid, please?
I can't help him lay an egg. PJ, >> why?
>> He needs to lay egg on his own.
>> Can you help him?
>> Why don't you bend over for him? PJ,
>> why did why
would you why did he call me a virgin?
>> Because he because really you are a
virgin. Have you ever been bumped before?
What do you mean?
>> Have you Have you been bummed before? What? >> No.
Tokyo agents to answer that question. PG
at least if you say multi. Have you ever
been bumped before? No. Have I fought
being bummed? But if
>> Why does he But Bonnie, why does he call
me a virgin? >> What?
No, I think it cuz he fancies you. He's
obsessed with you in it. He's always
obsessed with you. He's always on your
PJ. Just think about it. I think he's
got the ops for your PJ cuz he's always
on you. It's all about your own legs.
that I do always the time.
>> It's because you are the one who gave
him that [ __ ] friendship PJ. That's
what it is.
>> I can't even hear you, Monty. But yeah. I'm bro.
cuz I couldn't hear you, man. Yeah. Heat.
What the [ __ ]
I should have a date this week.
know how many approaches I done. If I
got eight numbers from [ __ ] Thursday
and Saturday, I must have done a lot of approaches.
You can't get nothing in this country, mate. Yeah,
this country is [ __ ] depressing, bro.
Oh [ __ ] I hate this country.
Hate the people in it. I hate the women.
I hate everything about this [ __ ] country, bro.
If you don't have one date from any of them approaches.
Can't believe you ain't got one day out
of any of them approaches. [ __ ] hell.
What am I doing on Thursday?
You know, I might not even go out
Thursday to be honest with you, bro.
Yeah, they're just evil bastards. I
don't know how I ain't got a [ __ ]
date this week.
I might not even go out Thursday to be
honest, bro. That's just so demotivating.
[ __ ] eight numbers.
That's [ __ ] madness, bro. So, I don't
know how many people I approached. If I
got [ __ ] eight numbers in two is
Yeah, life sucks, bro.
Well, at least we can pray we all die in
our sleep, eh?
Yeah, it's really bad, bro.
Maybe I might not go out Thursday. I
don't know yet.
I stay optimistic. There's nothing to be
optimistic about, bro. If something was
going to change, it would have changed by now.
That's the truth. Yeah.
Yeah. I was going to play some rouette
today, Steven Howard, but I never did.
You should be proud of me, man.
Should be proud of me, matey.
telling you to keep out here.
Something was going to happen. It would
have happened by now, bro.
It would have [ __ ] happened. if
something was going to happen by now.
They don't seem to acknowledge that.
Doesn't make sense. Doesn't make sense.
I don't really think you you need to
give up and leave the country again,
bro. Honestly, this is going to keep
happening and happening and happening
and happening and happening and it's
never ever going to stop. It hasn't
stopped for years. And it's never going to stop.
Things don't just change after 3 years, bro. Yeah, man.
I think you should book that oneway
flight, bro. Uh,
and teach English and just live in
Thailand. Bro, there's got to be
something more to life than this. This is depressing.
Every week it's [ __ ] depressing.
What's life than this?
Nah, it wasn't on [ __ ] It wasn't on um
It wasn't on the form. It was on [ __ ]
online. I was going to, but I never done
it. I was trying to make some extra money. Yay.
Not that I need extra money, but just
something to do, but I never.
Yeah, I've got about 2K left.
3 years is a long time. You know, 3 and
a half years is a is a [ __ ] long time
to meet someone. When you're on three
grand a month, right? You're on £3,000 a
month. You're not working. That is a lot
of money and a lot of time, you know?
millions of guys who go through the same thing. You think
you think millions of guys who go
through the same thing say the same
thing. But the difference is millions of
guys have not tried as much as I have.
That's the whole difference. And a lot
of them people don't live in this country anymore.
So that's the whole difference.
That's the whole difference.
Not Not one of them [ __ ] thought, "Oh,
one day I'll go to Wales, then the next
day I'll go to Wales."
They never done that [ __ ] They were not
mad like me.
I'm living proof of it and I had all the
time in the world. So you think one day
you're going to go out and all of them
years of trying it's just going to change.
I didn't work for years, bro. So I'm I
know I know.
[ __ ] I know about this. If something
was going to change, it would have
changed by now.
So, does that also mean that there's not
someone for everyone?
So, yeah. Millions of guys
have not tried as much as I have. And
it's been going on for years as well. [ __ ] years.
I used to go casino on the front on the
win money all the time.
Then I'd go
then I'd take it through all the way to
the Saturday. Approach approach. Nothing nothing nothing
all throughout. And I used to do it
every week. Every single week I used to
do it. every week.
It's like what ad man said. He said,
"Yeah, you go out and you get the same
result." It's like you ain't got a
million Instagram followers. You ain't
got a million Tik Tok followers.
So, they're not interested.
That's what he said. Yeah.
Is Antman right? Steven Howard,
he says, "Yeah, that's what I used to
do, but you ain't got a million Tik Tok followers."
Oh, so they're not interested. That's
what he said.
That's what man said.
Nothing will ever change, bro.
Not much, bro. Just depressed.
How are you?
Yeah. Depressed in England. depressed
and man's like they're not interested
unless you've got a million Tik Tok
followers. Grezy or Instagram followers. Yeah. Here
we go. Being compared to other people
again. I always like being compared to other people.
It's so lazy, Reezy.
you know, comparing somebody to another
person, it's so lazy, you know,
I agree with you, but I think it's lazy.
Oh, just compare them to this person or
just compare them to that person. It's so lazy.
Yeah, I want out of this life. Do you
greasy? It's too depressing.
It's so [ __ ] depressing this life.
What's your opinion on it?
I think the whole dating thing makes you
depressed. It makes me [ __ ]
depressed. Even though I don't go out
for the dating, when I look back on it,
it's just depressing cuz it shouldn't be that way.
You look back on it and it is actually so depressing.
It's actually so [ __ ] up. It's actually depressing, you know.
It's just never ending.
I just guess I guess there's just not
someone for everyone. Grezy.
No, I don't think I don't think Snapchat
is the worst.
I think Instagram and Tik Tok is the worst.
No, I think Instagram and Tik Tok is the worst, bro.
I think Snapchat is quite minor.
Yeah, man said they're not interested
unless you've got a million subscribers on Snapchat.
So on uh Instagram and Tik Tok. Yeah. >> Yeah.
Never change, Grezy. Never change. Never.
They still tell me to try even though
I've tried more than anyone in the
world. Greasy, would you say that I've
tried more than anyone in the world? I
say I would actually say I I have.
I honestly would say that I have. You know,
I honestly would. I honestly you know
how like I bro
[ __ ] knows bro. Honestly, bro. Yeah,
I know how delusional it sounds, but I
think I have.
I think you have tried more than anybody
in the world. Three years,
three grand a month going here, there, everywhere.
I've been places. You haven't even been
greasy. I think you try more than you've
tried more than anyone in the world.
Definitely. And I've also think that
I've met more women than any anyone in the world
because the approaching obviously in it. So
I generally think I have bro
or it's at least a close call
and we're still dealing with the same
problem. You know what I'm saying? We're
still dealing with exactly the same problem.
You shouldn't be dealing with this, bro.
It's not normal.
You should be on a [ __ ] You should be
on a date this week. You should be on a
[ __ ] date this week.
What's your opinion? We
going to wake up one day and
everything's going to be perfect.
Everything's going to be perfect. I want
out of this [ __ ] life, bro. I want
out of it.
Why don't you tell us what you think, Grezy?
This life is [ __ ] depressing.
Oh, bro. I just can't get over how
[ __ ] up the dating game is. You know,
I don't I didn't even go out them two
days to date. I just went out cuz I went
out and then I'm just acknowledging how
[ __ ] up the whole dating game is.
It's [ __ ] depressing, bro. Anyone
would think you're fat and ugly like Timmy
bad, bro. It is bad.
I get up at like 10:00 nowadays, bro.
Yeah, I get up at like 10:00, which is
not like me, you know.
It is actually [ __ ] depressing. Actually is
They're not interested.
>> Yeah, they're not interested in this country.
They'll get to a point one day where you
even get a million [ __ ]
followers and they still won't be interested, you know?
Yeah, it's really bad.
money side of it. Uh, Grezy. Yeah, cuz I
had um 2K. I have 2K. Still get money
and whatever. I got the TV, the Xbox,
phone, and that.
You're not serving.
I don't think it is necessarily that,
bro. I think it's how much you spent in
them three and a half years. The things
you done and the dating game is still
bad. It's still still depressive.
That's what I think it is.
Obviously, the money loss is [ __ ] up
as well, but I don't think that is what
all it is to be fair.
It's the dating game in this country.
It's [ __ ] depressing.
There's no reason why you're you
shouldn't be s now. You know,
this is just depressing, bro. [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] depressing, bro.
[ __ ] hell, man. That's mad, bro. The
amount of times we used to go out and
out and out and out and out. I can't
believe it, bro. Honestly, that is [ __ ] disgraceful.
Yeah, one second. I'll be back later
anyways. I'm going to put some more
approaching videos up.