Yeah, one of them replied,
but it's like three out of eight.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] weird, bro.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] weird, isn't it?
[ __ ] so weird, bro. Yeah,
guess I won't be going to their work cuz
they replied, eh? Wow.
Yeah, it's funny.
We don't want that person, mate. No. [ __ ] that.
This Jamie Thompson is a proper stalker, isn't he?
Yeah, he's a proper stalker. This uh
Jamie Thompson, e proper stalker. Proper stone. N
can't afford it. 1.7,000.
I ain't paying that, By.
I'm not rich like I used to be, Batty. No, matey.
Are you getting it?
No, I ain't getting it, bro. Yeah, man.
Would you pay that for a phone? 1.7K.
Would you pay that? [ __ ] that. It
[ __ ] ridiculous, is it, bro? Nothing mad. [Music]
Terry, give it up, bro. You've been
doing this for years, Terry. Terrible
trainers. You little batty man. Go seek
some attention on another channel, you little weirdo.
Bro, how do you know you people? I don't
know how you don't have no shame. Like,
I don't know how you let people run you
out of your area and you still come on
here like nothing's happened. Like, you
really have no shame. Like, really, you
really really have no shame.
You're some little [ __ ] with shitty trainers.
Some little bully victim. And you keep
coming on YouTube. I don't know why you
keep coming on YouTube, bro. It's really bad.
You're just some stupid little bully
victim [ __ ] with shitty trainers.
I don't know why you keep coming on
here. You're an absolute victim.
You're an absolute victim. I don't know
why you keep coming on here.
I came to your area and you didn't come
out. You absolute victim.
Why do you keep coming back on YouTube, victim?
You're all the same. You I noticed that. You nons
[ __ ] Bro, you you laugh at yourself.
Listen, mate. You're 4 foot to tall. You
got shitty trainers. You got ran out of
your area, bro. You're laughing at no
one but yourself.
City trainers 4 foot tall
got run out of your area. Bro, you're
laughing at yourself. Do you think
anyone could ever do that to me? You're
a keyboard warrior. Shut up, bro. You
laugh at yourself. Look at you. 4 foot
two tall. Shitty trainers got run out of
your area, bro. You're the only one that
gets laughed at.
You're a victim. You're an absolute
victim, Terry. I've got more money than
you. You don't even have £1,000.
I'm selling my TV and [ __ ] bro. I got a
TV right here. Want me to put a camera
on? I've got a TV right here. Selling my
TV and [ __ ] Got an Xbox. Got a TV, bro.
You don't even have £200.
Stop it. Stop it, bro. Stop embarrassing
yourself. You don't even have 200 quid
to your [ __ ] name and you're talking
about a [ __ ] thousand, bro. your skin
and then a skin flint. No one takes you
serious now. Not even LT. No one. No
one. No one. Why did I turn up the other
day? Why didn't you turn up when I went
to you last time? I tell you why I
didn't turn up the other day. Do you
want Do you want to know why I didn't
turn up the other day? I can actually
explain to you why. Because you do the
same [ __ ] All of you little keyboard
warrior scumbags on here, you do exactly
the same [ __ ] You, Triple H, the rest
of you, you all do the same [ __ ] That's
why I didn't come the other day. Just
like last time when I come, you didn't
come out. What was the excuse last time?
Tell everybody the excuse last time why
you didn't come, bro. You're all a waste of time.
You do all the same [ __ ] Then you stick
up for each other. That's why no one
takes you serious no more. That's why
nobody wastes their money on you because it's boring.
We done the same thing with nonslegs.
We've done the same thing with you.
We've done the same thing with Triple H.
Have you noticed how you all do the same
[ __ ] Don't meet then you all stick up
for each other. Then you still try to
aggravate people. That's why no one
waste their time on you anymore.
Terry, terrible trainers.
That's why we don't waste our time on
you anymore, brother. Yeah.
Bro, cost. Bro, I've got more money than
you would ever have. You don't even have
£1,000. Look at your trainers. Look at
your trainers and look at my trainers.
Bro, shut the [ __ ] up. I already turned
up to your area and you didn't your
[ __ ] ass didn't show up. Stop doing
what nonslegs does. Stop doing what
Triple H does. I went to your [ __ ] ass
area last time and you did not come out.
Yeah, you [ __ ] terri terrible shitty trainers. [ __ ]
You [ __ ] [ __ ] with your shitty
trainers. Yeah, remember last time I
come, oh, I'm on probation. I'm on
probation. I went to your area and you
did not show up, [ __ ] boy. Why don't
you tell everybody? Yeah, bro. I was
selling things cuz I was moving house,
but bro, look at your trainers. Look at
them Trumpy trainers. You're coming on
here talking about, buddy, bro. Look at
your trainers. Do you reckon I could
ever be seen in them trainers? Look at
them. You [ __ ] [ __ ] You trampy
little [ __ ] No wonder you're single,
bro. Look at them trainers that you're [ __ ] wearing.
Look at them trappy dirty trainers and
you're talking on a grand a month
wearing them shitty trainers. You broke
ass [ __ ] Bro, you know when everybody
like you know when you used to speak
about you was having kids and you know
these people, you know them people. Bro,
you don't know anybody. You don't know
anybody, bro. You are just some big
little [ __ ] that didn't show up when I
went to his area. You're some little
[ __ ] with shitty trailers with no
money that does not show up anywhere.
You're a Triple H. You're a nons legs.
You're a Mark Samson. You are all the
same. Every single one of you are the same, bro.
Look at your trailers. Look at your
And you're talking about me, bro. Look
at the state of them Trumpy trailers.
That's how you know you was always a
bully victim. You just know that every
single time this guy tried to go to
school, this guy got bullied. Look at
what he's wearing, bro. Look at what
he's Bro. I've got more money than you,
bro. Should we start showing each other's gums?
Should we start showing you Thomas
trainers? Bro, I would never be seen in
them trampy trainers what you're
wearing, bro. Never. You don't even have
a grand. You're [ __ ] skint. You're on
£300 a month. You skin bully victim.
Don't make me come to your area and
bully you again, bro. Please do not make
me come to your area and bully you
again. You want me to come to your area
and bully you again? And you're going to
have to use probation as an excuse.
Anyways, why didn't you come last time?
Why didn't you come out last time,
[ __ ] boy? Boy, [ __ ] boy, why didn't
you come out last time? I love how you
tried [ __ ] using the excuse. [ __ ]
boy, why didn't you come out last time?
Listen, listen, shitty trainers. [ __ ]
That time when I was going to smash your
[ __ ] face in, you ugly [ __ ] Why
didn't you come out? Tell everybody why
you did not come out last time. You
would have got [ __ ] up. You [ __ ]
skinned bastard. Shitty trainers. Little
bully victim. Try to [ __ ] beg LT.
You're about this. You're about that.
with your shitty trainers on benefits.
You benefit broky boy. Listen, bro. Look
at my life compared to yours. Do you
think I'd ever be seen in them dusty
trainers like you? You [ __ ] single
broke [ __ ] You think somebody could
ever run me out of my area, bro? Like I
run out what? Like I run you out of your
area, you skint flint [ __ ] £300 a
month boy. Yeah, that's what you are,
bro. Look at them trainers. Do you think
anyone can take you serious running
around in them shitty offright trainers
with your [ __ ] self? You [ __ ]
[ __ ] letting somebody come and boil
you off in your area and you're talking
about how you're about this and you're
about that. Get away with yourself, you
little [ __ ] skid bastard. Look at
you. You're a [ __ ] bro. You're a [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, you got boyed off last time.
You're a Triple H. You're a Nlegs.
You're a Mark Samson. You're a Mark
Samson. You're all the same. Bye-bye
now. [ __ ] boy. Get banned.
And you're banned as well. [Music]
I had to block this clown. So anyways,
Terry is just another um
Mark Sabson legs. They're all the same
kind of breed, bro. They're all the same
kind of breed.
the same. I've noticed that, bro.
They're all all these mongos are the
same on here, bro.
This Terry, this Triple H, they're all
the same. I've noticed that. Most of
them are the same on here, aren't they?
And they've got absolutely no shame whatsoever.
They've got literally no shame whatsoever, though.
It's really bad. Like, they have no shame. [Music]
God. Didn't he didn't he used to say
three Didn't he used to say three grand
a month was nothing?
Didn't he used to say three grand a
month was nothing, bro?
Yeah. Yeah, he did.
This guy's a fantasist
trying to say, "Oh, did you say you was
going to come?" No, no, no, no, no. And
I literally did come to your area and
you didn't even show up, you [ __ ]
idiot. We don't waste our time on people
like you anymore.
Because you're all the same. You get
people to go places and you don't turn
up. Just like Mark Samson, just like
Triple H, just like Virgin Boy, you're
all the same. Every single one of you,
you're all the same.
So yes, all the same. [Music]
I can't believe Terry's from London and
he and he acts the same as all of these
weasels. Bad, isn't it?
Then to meet anyone, he's not ever going
to show up anywhere.
It's funny how you sit there and you
talk about money, right, when you're
look at the trainers that you're wearing.
Look at the trainers that you're
literally rocking, bro. You're a [ __ ]
You [ __ ] [ __ ]
It's so sad how these middle-aged men
have to come on YouTube for attention
and a reaction in it. It's so sad.
It's so sad, isn't it? Like really sad. Mr.'s asleep. Let's see.
And if this person meets right, I'm
going to take a really flow with them
and I'm going to and I'm going to prove
to you how they just waste people's time.
Well, we're going to say, let's just say
for example, free day chair and they'll
still waste time
because that's what they do in it. >> Yeah.
I'll show you, bro, if they come out. Yeah.
This is what it's like in this shitty country.
I'm trying to think of my [ __ ]
Bernard Terry, you just laugh at
yourself, mate. Look at you. Look at
you. Your [ __ ] self and your traders.
Reason you didn't come out last time is
cuz you knew you was going to get [ __ ] up. Yeah, that's
that's the only reason you didn't come
out cuz you knew you was going to get [ __ ] up.
You're the same as Triple H. You're the
same as Mark Stson.
I probably shouldn't even mention Mark
Samson to be honest cuz he's going to do
a little pretend call out video tomorrow probably.
You're all the same there.
Like you you [ __ ] you're all the same
there. Smokey B, Triple H, you're all
literally the same. You all talk, but
when someone actually comes to your area,
um, you know,
Oh, block people then, bro. Broky, I've
got more money than you. Look at what
you're rocking and look at what I'm
rocking. You are broky, bro. Stop
talking about yourself, [ __ ] boy,
because I'm going to have to come to
your area again and make you not show up
again, [ __ ] boy. Look at them trainers
that you're rocking and look at the
trainers that I'm rocking. Bro, you're
not about that life. How many months was
you begging LT? Oh, I'm not the one. I'm
not the one, bro. You got drugged
around. You got [ __ ] up the first time
and the second time you didn't come out,
bro. You're an actual bully victim. Like
imagine you walking around London with
them shitty trainers. Bro, do you think
I wouldn't be seen dead in them
trainers? You look like a [ __ ]
You actually look like a [ __ ] [ __ ]
You look like a [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. It's
It's unreal. Have you seen what you're
rocking? You are the well and true
brokie, bro. You really are. Look at
them trainers. Look at them [ __ ]
You're not about that life. Stop it, babe.
You're not about that life, bro. Stop it.
Come to Stratford right now and I'll
stay live. Okay. Okay. Okay. Come to
Stratford right now and I'll stay live.
Okay, bro. Come to Strapford right now
and I'm going to stay live and show
everybody what you're really about.
Terry, terrible trainers.
Tererry terrible trainers, right?
Tererry terrible trainers. You were
saying about to LT about you're not the
one, you're not the one, bro. You was
you was going to get slapped up that
day. That's why you didn't come out. You
was going to get slapped up, bro. Really
was going to get slapped up. Bye-bye,
Va. You was going to get slapped up.
Come to Stratford now and I'm going to
stay live. Let's see what you're really,
really, really about. Come on.
Come on. Simple. I'm gonna stay live,
bro. Come on.
Let's hear these excuses. Just like
Triple H, just like [ __ ] Mark Samson.
Just like Virgin Boy, just like Smokey B.
You all It's like you all come from the
same mother. You're all the [ __ ] same.
You sad bastards are all the same on here, bro.
You really, really are all the same.
Like, bro, come on. You know you'd get
[ __ ] up. How long was you trying to
[ __ ] convince LT that you're about
this, you're about that, you're about
this, you're about that, bro. I don't
come to your area anymore because I know
what you do. The same as Triple H, the
same as Mark Samson, you do exactly the
same stuff. It's funny now, bro. It's
something to laugh at. It is actually
You are actually all the same. You do
realize that you are actually all the
same. You lot.
The amount of times me and LT used to go
up north. None of you little [ __ ]
used to come out. Then we decided to
stop wasting our time, wasting our money
because you don't come out anywhere.
You're boring, bro. You're really, really boring.
You don't want to come today? Okay. Come
tomorrow. Come tomorrow and go live. Simple.
You won't know cuz you're a [ __ ]
You're just about You're just about
talking [ __ ] on a keyboard. I failed to
to turn up twice now. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. I went to your area and
you didn't come out. Stop. Stop. Stop
trying to change the subject. No, no,
no, no, no. I didn't fail to sign up
anywhere. I went to your area and you
did not come out. That happened. I was
in your area. You didn't come out.
Everybody saw it.
So, actually, right, you might actually
want to uh get it right because I came
to your area and you did not come out.
That was not a fail. Yeah, you're a
[ __ ] [ __ ] Imagine that. I came to
your area and you didn't even come out.
Imagine that, bro. That's worse. That's
worse than losing.
You're like Triple H, bro. You're you
you you're all the same. You know that
you are all the same on here. You know
that you really are all the same on
here, man. It's actually funny. It it
really is cuz you don't cuz deep down
you know that you're a [ __ ]
you know, but you have to you have to
put a front on. Anyways, come to
Strapford tomorrow then. Not a problem.
How many times have you said you're
going to do my windows in and you
haven't? How many times have you said
you're going to come out and you
haven't? Just come to Stratford tomorrow
then. No problem. It's too late now.
That's fine. Come to Stratford tomorrow. Simple.
Job done then, isn't it? Yeah. You came
my area, I come out. I came to your
area, you didn't come out. So now it's
your turn to come to my area then.
I think that's that's fair to be fair.
You're not going to come out, bro.
You're all the same on here.
You, Triple H, Mark Samson, Virgin Boy.
Is it funny how you all the same on here?
I just think you want attention, don't
you, mate? It's okay, Terry. I'll give
you some attention.
Oh, bless you. You want some attention, don't you?
It's all right, man. It's okay.
Yeah, bro. I'll give you some attention
if you want.
I won't be out on Thursday. I can't be bothered.
So what are you coming out or what?
[ __ ] what the [ __ ]
And you keep talking about me selling my
things? Yeah, I was selling my things
cuz I moved house. So that's why I was
selling things cuz I moved house. You
[ __ ] idiot. which is what people do
when they move
to a place that had them things already
in it. You [ __ ] [ __ ]
Why are you so asked about what I do as
well, you weirdo. Just know that I'll
always have more money than you, bro.
And no matter where I end up in life,
I'll never be rocking them dusty, dirty
trainers that you're wearing, bro.
Believe that. Before talking about
people's finance financial
circumstances, bro, you might want to
change them [ __ ] trainers that you
got on you.
So, one second. So, yeah.
Why would they buy new? What are you
talking about? Why would they buy you
new? You [ __ ] Listen, bro. You want
to talk about people being broke? Have
you seen your trainers? Have you seen
your trainers? Look at them trainers.
That's exactly what a broke man would
wear, you [ __ ] idiot, bro. I've got a
TV. I've got an Xbox. I've got a phone.
And I got more money than you. So, what
does that what does that mean? And look,
you're avoiding the the the subject of
meeting. This is why I don't go
Newcastle. This is why I don't go Milton
Kings. This is why I don't come back to
your area because you do all the same
[ __ ] All of you do exactly the same
You do exactly the same [ __ ]
Trust me, bro. If I didn't know any
better two years ago, I would have went
to Milton Kings. I would have went to
Newcastle and I would be at your area
all in less than a month. But we kind of
know what your pe what you people are
about now, isn't it?
Yes, because where I was going had a
fridge and had a washing machine, you
[ __ ] Why would I take it with me if
where I was going has a fridge and has a
washing machine? That doesn't make any sense.
So anyways, that's why I don't waste my
time with you little [ __ ] now.
Yeah, cuz you're just all little sad.
You just you just don't want to meet
anyone, bro. Just just admit you don't
want to meet anyone. Just give it up,
man. Please. Just give it up now.
You don't want to meet anyone.
That's it, man.
It's all right, bro.
It's okay, you know.
Yeah, just admit it.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But Okay. Okay. Okay.
So, why didn't you why didn't you come
out last time I was there? Okay. Okay.
Yeah. Yeah. And you also told me to come
to your area last time. And when I came
to your area last time, you didn't come out.
So, I mean, I can literally do what I
want, bro. And the only one that looks
stupid is you because I've been to your
area and you didn't come out.
So, you No, no. You told me to come to
your area. I came to your area and you
didn't come out. So, I can do I can do
what I want.
I done the same with Triple H's, bro.
[ __ ] hell. I said, "Oh, I'm going to
come to Newcastle. I'm going to come to
Newcastle." But I didn't because I know
what you people are about. When I
finally calm down, I realize, "Oh, [ __ ]
We all know what you all about. You're
going to get us to come all the way
there. You're not going to show up.
You're all going to stick up for each
other and pretend it never happened.
Been there, done it, worn the t-shirt.
Get [ __ ] You're all the same. Every
single one of you." Yeah.
Yeah, that trip Rachel was winding me up
the other day as well.
Okay. Yeah, you're talking about
yourself. I've had more women than you
and I've been with more women than you.
Well, must be talking about yourself.
Sounds like an immature thing.
I know. That's why I've just had more
women than you.
I know. But yeah, and then I just
realized like it's just a complete and
utter waste of time. I've done it with
Bomb. I've done it with Virgin Boy. I've
done it with Trevor Dawson. Done it with
Mark Samson. You're all the same, mate.
That's why when people were talking about
that Triple H thing was the worst thing,
though, cuz I had actually went there
about I actually went I actually went
three times and he didn't actually show
up. That was the badest thing about it.
You're all the same.
Yeah, you are an ins.
You're a s as well. Women don't like
simps. That's why you're still a virgin.
Yeah. Women don't like simps like you.
That's why you're still a virgin.
That's why women don't like you. Cuz
you're a s. S.
You're a s. Anyways,
so yeah, I I mean I've been to Newcastle
three times, bro, and that [ __ ]
didn't show up once. So I just like,
bro, you're being silly here. Are we
really going to waste £400 for someone
to not show up?
New people never show up, bro.
Trust me, if it was if it was about a
year, if it was, bro, I'm telling you,
it's about two years ago, I would have
went there and started talking about his
kid. Trust me, bro. If I if I didn't
know any better with these people, I would have.
But I think between me and LT, I think
we've we've proved a point more than enough.
We also done different people. Some of
us done the same people as well. And you
all don't turn up, mate. Same as
Liverpool, same as Manchester, same as
[ __ ] I mean, he done Nottingham, he
done Glasgow, I done other places. None
of you ever turn up. So, it's just
laughable now, you know?
But if I didn't know any better, bro,
trust me, I would have I would have
spoke away his family and his kids. Trust me.
But that's what you people want, in it.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah. But guess what? You're not behind
me, bro. I came to your area and you
didn't even come out. That's even more
embarrassing. I came to your area, bro,
and you didn't even come out.
I've got [ __ ] all, bro. I don't come on
YouTube every day. You're the one on
YouTube trying to wind people up. You're
the one who's trying to wind people up,
but then when people come to your area,
you don't show up. So, what do you have
in your life? You're the one coming on
here trying to wind people up. When
people come to your area, you don't show
up. What do you have in your life, bro?
Hey, listen, Juliet. Stop being a s. We
all know you're a man behind that
account. S never got a man laid, which
is why people still simp.
Stop being a s.
We all know that women are stuck up
[ __ ] in this country. You know, the
maddest thing about this, right, is I
was saying this the other day is I've
had more women than probably most people
in this community. I'm just not in
denial. You see these people right on
here, they're in denial. They don't get
women. They've hardly ever been with a
woman. Some of them have never had a
woman, but they still stick up for them.
That's called pure and utter in denial
where I've had more women than they and
I'm I'm I'll tell you they're stuck up
[ __ ] And I've got I've got videos
where I'm in bed. I've had sex. I've had
[ __ ] I've pulled so many different
people. I'm not in I'm not in denial, bro.
That's the difference. I'm not in denial.
They're [ __ ] [ __ ] I'm not in
denial, bro. I don't need to lie to anyone.
Whereas you get these guys that's never
had women but they defend them. It's
weird is it? Yeah.
Yeah. Okay. You all laugh at me, bro.
No. I went to your area and you did not
come out again. You keep changing the
subject. You told me to come to your
area. I came to your area. You didn't come out.
I think everybody was laughing at you
and no one cares about what you people
laugh at. You people ain't got a life,
bro. You don't even leave your house.
You're all skinned on YouTube every
single day. Do you think anyone cares
about you rejects or what you rejects
laugh at? Deep down, you know you're
laughing at yourselves. Sat on YouTube
all day on benefits. What are you
laughing at, bro? You're laughing at
yourselves. And we're all laughing at
how I came to your air and you didn't show up.
[ __ ] Listen, you are the same
people that are all old on benefits
rejected on YouTube every day. You're
laughing at yourselves. Yeah.
Okay, I will.
You know, but yeah, it's very weird how
you get people don't get women
like don't get them or whatever had them
and they still defend them. That is odd,
bro. That's just in denial.
I tell you straight, they're [ __ ]
and I've had more than them. That's the
most shocking thing about it.
Anyways, why is this lock? Oh [ __ ]
bro. I went to your area and you did not
turn up. Why do you not Why don't you
tell anybody why you did not turn up?
I don't say anything about kids, so I
don't know what the [ __ ] you're talking
about. Listen, Terry.
Listen, I've already explained to you
why I didn't show up. Why don't you
explain to everybody why when I went to
your area, you didn't show up. It's the
same reason I didn't show up to Triple
H. Because you're all the same on here.
It's the same reason I didn't go to
Milton Kings, cuz you're all the same on here.
Yeah, you're all the same, bro. You're all [ __ ]
In reality, you're laughing at
yourselves, Terry. Mate, you're in your
40s. You got no money. You're wearing
dusty trainers. What could you laugh at?
What could you possibly laugh at yourself? So,
so yeah, bro.
But I thought you was a guy
cuz most guys I don't get women. They
seem to defend women
which like I said is quite strange
cuz you would have thought me of all
people would be defending them. I don't
defend them. I think they're [ __ ]
in this country anyways.
Not Asia but in this country. Yeah. I
think they are [ __ ] I hate all of them.
At least I'm honest. Like, at least I'm
honest. I don't give a [ __ ] bro.
Listen, you're changing the subject again.
What the [ __ ] You're changing the subject again,
bro. You can't you stick to one subject.
This is Voice of Reason, I reckon.
Jamie Thompson, maybe Virgin Boy. I'm
telling you, it's one of them. One second.
There we go.
>> There you go. Bye-bye, Virgin.
There you go. You have to wake up pretty
early to fool me, [ __ ] boy.
Um, so yeah, I I I find it very strange
even like people like him
that has to date disabled women that
can't get laid still defends women. It's
the definition of uh being in denial. I
knew it was Virgin Boy straight away.
See, I know all the tricks and the
trades to all of you people now. You're
boring, bro. You're boring. And Terry,
listen. You've been shown six grand. So
now it's your turn to show 10 grand.
Terry, just you need to just pack this
whole YouTube thing in, bro. You really,
really need to stop it. Just like Triple
H, just like the rest of you, you know.
Please stop it, man. It really, really is.
But listen, Terry, like I live in your
heads, rent free. Like, you have to come
on YouTube every day reacting to me
being obsessed with me. I'm the real
winner. I'm the real real winner of it
all to be honest. Cuz you have to come
on, you virgin boy, Jamie Thompson, like
you have to come on YouTube every day
being obsessed with me reacting to me.
I'm doing something, bro. I'm living in your head.
Yeah, I'm broke, bro. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm broke. Terribly. I'm broke,
bro. I'm starving. So, at the end of the
day, So, at the end of the day, man,
like you're the one coming on YouTube
every day reacting to me without me even
doing anything. You virgin boy, you know.
Virgin boy, bro. [ __ ] virgin.
Yeah, we laugh. We laugh, bro. You laugh at yourselves,
bro. You laugh at yourselves. You come
on YouTube every day. Every single day.
Skin, no life. You laugh at yourselves.
I laugh at you every single day when you
you have to come on YouTube every day.
Just face it. You're all jealous. Yeah,
you're all in your 40s. You ain't got no
money. Peter Belly's got something that
you don't have. Just face it, bro. Cuz I
know for a fact, bro, if I was better
than someone, I wouldn't be spending all
my life stalking them, being obsessed
with them, or I quote laughing at them.
Just, bro, we all know that a lot of
people are jealous of Peter Belly. It's
fine. It's fine, bro. It's fine.
You don't laugh at anyone, bro. They're
jealous of something.
That's why you won't leave people alone,
bro. Think of how it makes no sense,
bro. You have to come on YouTube every
day and you won't leave people alone.
Please, you're jealous. You've been
losing. Stop it. Just stop it. Just stop
it. Please. Just stop it now, bro.
Abby, let's just look at me and look at you.
You know, and and do you know what? You
keep talking about these people on here,
bro. You're all skin. If you people are
not skin, it's like what me and Monty
was saying earlier. Why are you all on
YouTube every day? If you weren't skin,
you wouldn't be on YouTube every day.
That's actual facts. You wouldn't be on
YouTube every day if you weren't skin.
That's all I say to it, but I don't even
argue with it. you. It goes to show that
you people are skinned and got [ __ ]
lives because of what you do to try to
get a reaction. But do you know the
funny thing is about it? Yeah. Is
you're doing stuff for reaction, but
you're reacting to get a reaction.
That's funny. You're being obsessed.
You're spending all this time reacting
to get a reaction. That just goes to
show that your life is [ __ ] that you
have to do this every day. That's what
That's what it shows, bro.
It shows pure and utter jealousy. You
don't see it, but I see it, bro. I see
it. It's It's obvious. It's [ __ ]
obvious, bro. Everyone has seen you,
bro, with your dusty trainers and your
[ __ ] self and your ugly face. Look at
you, bro, and look at me. Please stop it, man.
I'm bading you now. Anyways,
you people are clearly jealous of something.
You're clearly clearly clearly clearly
jealous of something where you have to
come on YouTube every day reacting to
get a reaction. You're clearly jealous
of something. Clearly.
Oh [ __ ] And fun fact, I'm the only one
that gets targeted as well.
They're in denial, bro.
And you want to try and talk about being
rejected, bro? You got rejected by
[ __ ] Britney. You wouldn't leave
Britney alone. A [ __ ] 14year-old in
Canada. And I didn't want you. You would
know all about being rejected.
You rejected little bastard.
Reacting for a reaction.
That's why they contradict themselves
because they're reacting for a reaction.
reacting for a reaction,
which doesn't even make any sense
because they want a reaction, but
they're reacting for a reaction. It's like
you got no man.
>> There you go. [ __ ] off, virgin.
[ __ ] off, you ugly virgin. Go get laid.
[ __ ] off, you ugly virgin, and go and get laid,
you ugly [ __ ]
[ __ ] off, you ugly [ __ ] and go suck
your dad's dick for some extra bit of
bum change, you [ __ ] virgin. And this
is what I'm saying. Yeah. Anyone who's
watching this, it shows these people are
jealous of something, bro. These people
are clearly clearly jealous of something
to be sat on here doing this every day.
They clearly have to be They clearly
have to be jealous of something.
They're jealous of me. I know they're
jealous of me. 1 million% they're
jealous. For them to do this every
single day, they're in denial, bro. Go
take a leaf off your own [ __ ] book.
They're literally reacting to you every
day. They're being obsessed with you
every day. They won't leave you alone.
They're jealous of you. It's the truth.
It's the I know they don't want to admit
it because who wants to admit that
someone's jealous? It is pure jealousy.
You got something they want, bro. I'm
telling you. You got something they
[ __ ] want. Better looks, better
money. It's something. It's It's It is
something, mate. I know this is 1:00 in
the morning, but look at it, bro. I've
got teeth in my mouth. I don't have to
date a disabled. I don't have to show
bum chains trying to make it seem like
I've got money. You understand? Like, if
you want to start talking about facts,
I'll lie the facts on the table right now.
I have teeth in my mouth. I don't have
to date disabled. I've never been with [ __ ] disabled.
[ __ ] kiss a [ __ ] lot of [ __ ]
not so good-looking people in my time
when I've been drunk. I think we've all
been there, but never ever have I had to
date a disabled person. Never, bro.
Mate, have Okay, Terry, have you seen
Have you seen your trainers? Have you
seen your face? Have you seen your
height? Have you have you looked in the
mirror? Why would you laugh at me? I've
got a better life than all of you. More
money, better looking. Okay, bro. Look
at this. Look at your height and look at
your trainers. Look in the mirror and
laugh at yourself. Not someone that's
better looking than you. Someone that's
got more money than you. How could that
be something to laugh at?
I'm better looking than you. I've got
more money than you. How could you laugh
at me? Like, we've all seen you with
your shitty trainers. I'm better looking
and I've got more money. How could you
laugh at me? Like you're genuinely, bro,
you're actually in denial. We've all
seen you, bro, next to the black guy
that got in that that stood in front of
the vi in front of the fight. How could
you laugh at me? You're wearing shitty
trainers. You're 4 foot tall and you're
a 40 odd year old man. How could you
laugh at me?
Just like how could Virgin Boy laugh at
me with no teeth in his mouth. showing
his bum chains thinking that he's got
money. Like, at the end of the day, bro,
it's it's Listen,
who could you laugh at, bro? Yourself.
How can you laugh at someone that's got
more money that's better looking than
you? That doesn't even make any sense.
That literally does not even make any
sense. Like, I've got a better life than
you in every single angle.
You and Virgin Boy.
You and [ __ ] Virgin boy. Look how
desperate you are. Yeah. To try to get
people nicked. It just goes to show that
you people really live [ __ ] lives. You
people really really do live [ __ ]
jealous lives. I feel sorry for you,
bro. That's probably why, you know, most
of the time I don't even kick you.
Sorry, I got DC. But yeah, I was just
saying you literally
you literally look and he's still going
on about my sloppy seconds. Bro, you
people are so jealous of me. Like this
just goes to show. Like, bro, I love it.
Like you're still going on about my
sloppy seconds. All because your
disabled girlfriend won't give you no
sex and you're still a virgin. I said
this all along, bro. I've been saying
this all along. I knew he was a [ __ ]
virgin. I said it from day one, bro.
Yeah, bro. Just cuz you're a disabled
girlfriend don't give you any sex,
virgin boy, doesn't mean any of any of
the women I've been with has given me
sex. Mate, you're still a [ __ ] virgin
at 31, bro. Begging a [ __ ] girl in
Canada that's what, 14 years of [ __ ]
age. And you're still a virgin. I I hit
a nerve in that one, didn't I? Cuz you
are a [ __ ] virgin. It's the truth.
It's the [ __ ] truth. You're [ __ ]
big virgin. That's why you do all of
this [ __ ] about like people don't sleep
with this person. It's cuz you're the
biggest virgin going. And it's the
truth. It's the [ __ ] truth, mate.
It's the [ __ ] truth.
Anyways, I've got nothing. You You're
talking about yourself, Terry, again.
Talking about like all of you people,
you do all of this [ __ ] out of jealousy.
All of you on here are [ __ ] fat,
ugly, low lives, skin. You ain't got
nothing. And that's why you target me
because you're jealous of me. And that's
the truth. I know you don't like the
truth, but it is the truth.
Like Ronald Pump said, more money,
better looking, and it kills them. It's
the truth, mate. You're better looking,
you've got more money, and it kills
them. That's why they never leave you
alone. And it is the [ __ ] truth.
Because if it wasn't the truth, bro, get
on with your life, bro. Leave me alone.
But you can't. Yeah, it's that is the
truth. Cuz I don't just have one
stalker. I've got about three or four
stalkers. And they're actual stalkers.
They're not even just like trolls.
They're actual stalkers.
Bro, 1k a month, mate. I've got more
money than you will ever have. You don't
know how much money I have.
I remember when you used to say 3k a
month is nothing, bro. And and it is
jealousy, bro. It is definitely
definitely jealous. Jealousy. Think of
it. I'm probably the best looking than
anybody on here. I've got more money
than most people on here since£300 a
month. So yeah, it does make sense.
It's It is pure jealousy. I know we
don't like the word jealousy. I [ __ ]
hate using it. It's cloudy. But you are
jealous of something. It's clear as day,
bro. You don't leave people alone.
You've been doing this for ages. I've
got [ __ ] emails.
It is pure jealousy. It is. Of course
it's [ __ ] pure jealousy. The
amounting stalkers and haters I've got,
you're just jealous. That's all it is.
We don't care about you, bro.
Cuz you wouldn't waste your time. If you
had a better life than me, you had more
money. You wouldn't even bother.
But you do, and you don't stop because
it's something you're jealous of. Simple.
It is. It definitely is.
No, no, no, no. You was trying to say
before 3K a month is nothing, bro. You
know, you keep talking about this money.
Why? If you've got all of this money,
why are you wearing secondhand trainers?
You ain't got no money, kid.
You don't bring nothing home. You ain't
got a miss. Shut up. Just like you tried
to say that you you know what? Yeah. Why
don't you stop proving stuff, man?
Why don't you stop proving stuff?
You're making us look bad here. You
know, you're really making us look bad
here. You're just like Virgin Boy.
You're just like You're just like Virgin Boy.
You really don't leave people alone, do
you, bro? You would have thought you
would have got bored. You You thought
you would have got bored of this by now,
but you don't.
You just make a [ __ ] out of yourselves.
Think about the reality of this. Yeah,
I'm better looking than you and I've got
more money than you. Now, me and you
know that as a fact, but then you're
trying to say that you laugh at me
and I've got better trainers than you.
I'm better looking than you, got more
money than you, and I've got better
trainers than you, but you laugh at me.
That doesn't make any sense.
Who would lie about having kids? There's
a lot of people in here that's lied
about having kids.
I'm better looking than you. I've got
better trainers than you and I've got
more money than you. That's been proven.
You see, when it's to do with me, you
and Virgin boy, that's been proven. Same
same with that Virgin. Better looking
than him. Had more sex than him. had
better looking women than they never had
to date a disabled. That's been proven
though. These are things that have
actually been proven.
That's actually been proven because
we've actually seen what you people look
like. You see what I'm saying? But
you're saying that you laugh at me? So,
it just doesn't make any sense, does it?
And there is people that's lied about
having kids on here. Bomb. Bro, look at
you, bro. You lied about knowing people.
You tried to betray that you was this
big [ __ ] gangster. But you're not
though. You're just some stupid little idiot. Beg
that just tries forcing it.
You just don't leave people alone, bro.
What What is going on, man? What is
going on in that head of yours?
Cuz it's us three here now. Me, you, and
Virgin boy. It's confirmed. I'm better
looking than both of you. And I've got
more money than both of you.
But you're laughing at me.
But bro, you're laughing at me.
You're laughing at me, bro. That doesn't
make any sense. But you're laughing at me.
But how could you laugh at me? That
doesn't make any sense. And yes, I have
had a girlfriend. And you don't even
have a misses. You're the one that's
lying that you've got a misses and kids.
You don't have a misses and you don't have kids.
So stop talking [ __ ] You ain't got
a misses and you ain't got kids. And
until you can prove it, you don't have
it. Simple. Just like you, you know,
you've lied about other things, bro. I
can say that I can go on any community
and pretend I'm a millionaire. So, at
the end of the day, bro, you don't even
have a MS and kids.
You You can't prove it. So, at the end
of the day, bro, there's it's you're
laughing at yourself.
So, where we're standing right now, I'm
better looking than you. I'm better
looking than Virgin Boy. I've got more
money than both of you. I've had more
women than both of you. And I've got
better clothes than both of you. That's proven.
Bro, listen. Well, join the hangouts and
let's hear your misses. I don't give a
[ __ ] about your kids cuz you don't have
any kids. And even if you did, I don't
care. Let's hear your misses. If I put a
link out, let's hear your misses.
And I basically have had a girlfriend
anyways. But that doesn't even matter,
bro. Whoever have haven't you're
pretending that you've got a misses. Yeah,
virgin boy is so [ __ ] He's He's
trying to get my attention, bro. He's so
trying to get my attention.
God, he is such a virgin.
Jesus Christ, bro. Yeah,
you can't wake her up, Terry, because
she doesn't exist. Why are you not in
bed with her? Why the [ __ ] are you not
in bed with her?
No, Terry, you did. You tried betraying
that you were some sort of gangster. Oh,
I know this person. I know that person.
Yes, you did. Cuz you used to say it to
me as well.
All right, bro. This the stalking's
getting weird again. Uh, Cory, imagine
boys [ __ ] stalker be. Oh, these
people really, bro, I've got actual
stalkers on here, Richie. Richie, bro,
I've got actual stalkers, bro.
Like, not even people that try troll me.
I've got actual stalkers that want my
ass, bro. I'm going to have to leave
again, bro. It's getting creepy. I'm
going to have to leave again.
Oh, I've got these people that they
actually Do you know what? They might
not actually be jealous of me. They
might just want to [ __ ] me. They might
find me good-looking and they just want
to [ __ ] me or something.
Yeah, of course you have. Well, come on.
Come on my live stream with your Mrs.
Dent. Really? Why don't you come on my
live stream with your Mrs. Dent
tomorrow? We Let's hear her.
This is getting weird again, bro.
These people want my ass.
These people want my ass, Richie, bro.
[ __ ] they want my ass, man.
They're [ __ ] They're [ __ ]
closeted, bro. I'm telling you, they're
Yeah, they're weird, bro. I'm going to
have to go back to my main channel, I think.
No, no, no. Listen, Kobe, they they
actually stalk me, bro. Like, day in day
out. Day in day out. Day in day out. Day
in, day out. I think it's mad weird,
isn't it? They spend But the thing is
that they're in denial because they're
the ones that are psychologically being
[ __ ] up, bro. Cuz think about it, bro.
They're reacting to you every day.
They're doing videos of you every day.
So, you're obviously owning them, bro.
You're obviously owning them. Like, they
happen to email you. They have to come
on YouTube triggered about you every
day. And I don't even respond nine times
out of 10.
I'm actually like in their head, bro.
Like, it's actually I'm actually owning
them, bro. You know that? Yeah.
You own them just by living, bro.
They're reacting to you every day
without you even doing anything.
That's [ __ ] wild, bro.
But then they claim that they're not
jealous. Well, they must be, bro. to
waste all their life on you.
For them to waste all their life on you
every day. Every second of every day
they waste their life on you. It's some
form of jealousy, bro. I'm telling you,
it has to be. Who the [ __ ] would waste
their life on someone? It's so weird, isn't it?
And the thing is, nothing that they do
bothers anyone. We just laugh at them.
They don't bully no one. They don't put
anybody down. They don't stop people
showing their face. They just embarrass
themselves on YouTube every day. That's
all they do.
They do all of this, bro, cuz they're [ __ ] skin
on YouTube every day. Oh [ __ ] I need to go piss.
Every person that posts about you gets
tracks in gets tracks in and many likes.
What did that tell you? Uh that that
tells you that it's a [ __ ] community
for the spastics
and you all follow each other. Bro, I
just I just gave you an example, Terry.
You're the same. Triple H is the same.
Mark Samson's the same. Virgin boy is
the same. Bob's the same. Smoky B is the
same. Well, you're all the same spastics
on here. So that that that's the answer
to your question. You're all the same spastics.
You sit online every day, all day, every
day, posting about me. You waste your
life on me, whether you like it or not.
Um, you're al Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. You You are all spastics.
Have you seen what you do on LJ's every
day? Yes. You're all spastics. Have you
seen what you do on LJ's every day? You
all repeat yourself. You all call other
people what you are.
Yeah. Yeah. You're spastics and you're
not normal. Yeah. Yeah, you think it's
normal to come on here every day
self-reflecting, putting yourself down
every day. You all put yourselves down.
Calling yourself skin, calling yourself
that you ain't got a job. You all put yourselves down.
It's not nice to talk about yourself like that.
Yeah, it's all nice to talk about
yourselves like that, is it? Huh?
Yeah. I was speaking to some woman,
Terry, that I met at the pub. Yeah.
Met at the pub.
I met the [Laughter] Yeah.
We had a pub.
I make you laugh, didn't it?
>> Yeah, we met at the pub. Terry,
But listen, Terry. Terry. Terry. You
don't find that funny that we met at the pub.
We did meet at the pub, bro. We was
talking at the pub. It's how adults meet.
Yeah, it's how adults meet, bro.
Uh Greavvesy doesn't agree with me. Me
and Greavvesy uh
never agree on anything. Actually,
we never agrees with me on anything. Oh, [ __ ]
Just cuz you can't meet anyone at the pub.
I'll be working soon as well, Terry.
I'll be I'll be working with some guys from Birmingham.
Um they do some call out jobs
and um yeah they get just under 5k a
month so I'll be working with them. I
bet that make you jealous.
Yeah. But you know what I find funny as
well? How you people are sat on YouTube
every day ain't got a life. That's even
worse. You know what's worse than
sitting in a in in a pub when you're Jack Jones
is you people being sat on YouTube every
day they no life. That's even sadder. Yeah.
I mean that's how we know that you
people are actually skinned because
you can't get off of YouTube. Not even
for one day. You go on Lord Jay's, you
go on Virgin Boy, and you will see the
same people. And you're thinking, "Hold
on a minute. If these people have got
all of this money, if these people have
got all of this money, why are they on
here every day?
It doesn't really make us. It doesn't
make sense. If they've got all of this
money in the world, why are they on here
every day hating on different people?
It's cuz they're all [ __ ] It's cuz
they're all [ __ ] skinned. It's cuz
it's cuz I'm all [ __ ] skimp. But yeah,
sat on YouTube every day. Only a skimp
person would do that.
Only Oh, [ __ ]
>> Only a skimp person would do that.
Literally only a skinned person would do that, mate.
You go on L JS, you see the same people
every day, the same spastics,
but they call everyone else skinned. If
they weren't skinned, they would go out.
They wouldn't be on YouTube every day. [ __ ]
All that work on a bike, bro. I got I
got £100 in one day and then £100 in another day. [ __ ]
But yeah, I need to come off YouTube
again soon. You people are getting
obsessed and I think it's best for me to
come off for a couple of weeks because
uh you people seem to be triggered
triggered every day on YouTube.
How many hours?
I think it was eight.
Why does it matter how much I was how
how much I was earning? Bro, you don't
even work. You don't even have a job.
Oh, [ __ ] You don't even have a [ __ ]
job, bro. What the [ __ ]
You don't even have a job.
And you're trying to hate on me,
bro. You don't even have a [ __ ] job.
You don't even have a job. when you're
trying to hate on me. How does that make sense? Huh?
Yeah. People make more these.
Bro, you don't even have a job.
So what if they make more McDonald's?
What the [ __ ] are you talking about? You
don't even have a job.
Just like Virgin boy,
they have had a job.
Yeah, you're not going to get what you
want as well, Virgin Boy.
You people are [ __ ]
weird, bro. You You're clearly jealous
of something, man. What is it with you
people? Come on, man. you know.
Yeah. I'm I'm coming off tomorrow, bro.
You're You're getting weird again, bro.
I don't want to fuel your Peter belly addiction.
You're [ __ ] weird, bro. You You I
actually control your whole life.
I actually control your whole life, bro.
Just being alive. You know that. You
know, you're the ones that are triggered
every day. You You people are really the
ones that are triggered every day by my
existence. I love that.
Uh, okay. Well, why don't you show me
that 10 grand that I've been waiting
for? I've been waiting for that 10 grand
now since last summer, but you can't
show me it. Well, you don't have a job.
You don't have a job. Shut up. Just like
you don't have a Ms.
Oh my god, this guy is obsession.
I'm going to have to do a video to Joe F.
I'm going to have to do a video to Joe.
Jo, this is getting weird again, bro.
It's getting weird again.
That's how you know they're triggered.
You literally own them in every aspect.
Coming online triggered every day. Oh,
you know what? Yeah, I'm going to do a
video to Jo.
I'm getting It's getting weird again,
mate. It's getting really really weird
again. You have to come online every day triggered reacting.
[ __ ] hell. And obviously I'll say
I'll say virgin boy.
I don't see it, bro. I don't go on LJ's.
What does he say?
What did he say, man? I don't go on DJ,
so I don't know.
Not that I care anyways, cuz it's not
like I'm going to be meeting him. See,
it's a bit different now.
No need to be meeting anyone on here,
bro. You all
I'll do a video chat, Jo.
Yeah, I don't see what he writes. What
does he say? Yeah, but guess what, bro?
Look at the rest of you people. But you
know when you say the rest of us, but
look at the rest of you's skin, fat,
ugly, no money. So all you're doing is
laughing at yourselves.
I just gave you about a million and one
fun facts that it's proven I'm better
looking than most these people and it's
proven I've got more money than most
people and I've got a better life than
most people. But realistically, you're
in denial and you're just laughing at
yourself because the rest of you are on
YouTube every day all skin.
That's proven. So really, you're just
laughing at yourselves,
but you try to make it seem like you're
laughing at someone else. How can
someone like you laugh at anyone?
How can somebody like you laugh at anyone?
It doesn't really even matter about the
money to be honest. But uh yeah. Well, I
think we can say more money as well. We
can actually say more money as well cuz
you people are like £300 a month. So, I
guess more money is relevant. Yeah.
Living on 1k. No, no, no, no, no, no.
The rest of you, the the rest of you are
not homeless. No, the rest of you are in
bedsits living off 300 lb a month skint.
So, no, you're not you're not living off
1k a month. You're living on 300 a month
skint in a bedsit overweight, fat, and
ugly. That's what most of you people are
living. You're living on less than 1k a
month. Fat, ugly in a bedsit by
yourself. That's what the rest of you on
here are living. That's literally the
life you're living. And you don't even
get 1k a month. You don't even work.
Just like you don't have a misses. You
don't even you don't even have £1,000 to
your name. What are you talking about?
1K a month. You ain't even got £1,000 to
your name, let alone £1,000 a month, you
silly dork. Mate, you know, you say 1K a
month, right? You can easily go out and
and live some kind of life with 1K a
month. That's how we know that none of
you even get 1k a month because you're
all sat on YouTube every [ __ ] day on
your lonesomes on your Jack Jones
talking about other people. If you
weren't skimp, you wouldn't be on here every day.
So whatever you say, you're on YouTube
every day. So you just look stupid.
But no, you don't get one a month, you
get £300 a month. So yeah.
Well, I'm I've got more money than all
of you. Why do you keep calling me
broke? I've got more money than all of you. Oops.
I've got more money than all of you. Why
do you keep calling me broke? And you're
calling me broke, but bro, I don't I I'm
not going around wearing shitty
trainers. You are. I'm not going around
wearing shitty ass trainers.
I'm not going around wearing shitty ass
trainers. So, who's the one that's
broke? You are. You're the one going
around wearing shitty trainers. Not me.
You don't know how much money I've got.
You don't know how much money I have.
You don't know how much money I get. I'm
not the one walking around wearing shitty trainers.
I'm not walking around wearing shitty
trainers. You are.
You're living a poor life. Not me.
You are walking around in shitty
trainers. But you want to talk about
people being poor, bro. You don't know
how much money I have. You don't know
anything about me.
[ __ ] hell. How much money do I have
right now? You don't even know. You're an idiot.
[ __ ] hell. You don't know how much
money I have. That's the thing.
You little skin bongo.
Oops. Nope. I get more than that.
You don't know how much I get, bro. And
you don't know how much I have.
So, try again.
But you people don't even get 1k a
month. You all skin. You all skin on
YouTube every day. I don't even know why
we're having this conversation.
You all [ __ ] skin on YouTube every day.
Like, you don't need to worry about what
I have, what I get. Just know that
you're skinned and you can't even afford
new a new pair of trainers. That's all
you need to worry about. That is
literally all you need to worry about, matey. Oh [ __ ]
you know. Nope. I try to get more than that.
[ __ ] I try to get more than that. But
bro, you can't even afford a new pair of
trainers. Why are you worried about me?
Bro, I think that you need to just stop
all of this [ __ ] now.
You really, really do.
It's no good for your mental health.
Come on now, bro.
You don't need to worry about what I
get. I have more money than you will
ever have. Don't worry about me, matey.
But yeah, I laugh at you people sat on
YouTube every day.
I sat I laugh at you sados sat on
YouTube every day ain't got a life.
That's what I laugh at. That's what
everyone really laughs at. Laugh at you
fat, ugly [ __ ] disabled people on
benefits. Ain't got any money, ain't got
no life. Everyone laughs at you, bro.
Everyone laughs at you.
You all skin. That's why you're on
YouTube every day. Skid. You wouldn't be
on YouTube every day.
Ain't that something? Okay,
you was trying to say [ __ ] three
grand a month is nothing before.
Is it funny how none of these amounts of
money is anything to you, right?
But you're the one rolling around in shitty traders.
Isn't that funny? Hey, that 1K is
nothing to you. 3K is nothing to you.
But you're the one rolling around in
shitty ass trainers.
No one else, bro. Like, you don't know
what I get. You couldn't, bro. You're
rolling around in shitty trainers.
What the [ __ ]
You couldn't survive on three grand a month.
Oh my [ __ ] god, bro. You're rolling
around in shitty trainers.
You can't survive on three grand a
month. That's how we know you're just a
complete enough fantasist.
You the one You're the You can't survive
on one grand a month.
You can't survive on three grand a month. Sorry.
Oh, [ __ ] me, bro. You really are a fantasist.
You really, really, really, really are a fantasist.
You actually are a fantasist, aren't
you? You're just like all of this Triple
H and all of these little [ __ ] on here it
rent is 1,900. Well, if you had a MS,
then surely to God, you would be
splitting the rent.
You're a [ __ ] idiot, bro. You can't
survive on three grand a month. You
really, really are a fantasist.
Yeah, you're actually a fantasist, bro.
I can't lie.
But that Joe can say what he wants, bro.
It's not a problem, man. You're all the
same on here. So that's it.
You have to come online triggered every day. So
madness. It's mad how you little mongos
have to come on here triggered every
day. Is it
reacting every day?
You could. Yeah. You're a fantasist,
bro. You're an absolute fantasist.
You're an absolute fantasist, bro. Absolute fantasist.
You really are,
mate. You're a [ __ ] that can't even
afford a new pair of trainers.
Please just stop it.
Just stop it now.
It's embarrassing. It really is. Virgin boy.
Anyways, I'm going to have to uh
do a video soon, bro.
And I'm going to talk about you in it as well. Oo,
I just play some Grand Theft Auto. Yeah. Oh, [ __ ]
Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro.
Yeah, but you're saying all of these
things, but you can't prove none of
these things. So, you don't you can you
only you're only as good as what you can prove, bro.
You don't live in a three bed house. You
don't have a car. And you don't have a
job. And you don't have a MS cuz you
can't prove anything.
So, just stop it, bro. It's It's embarrassing.
It's embarrassing, mate.
You people never change,
bro. You're only as good as what you can prove. Seriously,
you're an idiot, man. I'm going bed, bro. You're balling,