Love it, bro.
[ __ ] hell. Still stalking me on
Reddit, bro. I I love it, you know, man.
I was just having a piggy sandwich and I
just just love how like, oh, [ __ ] You
people just keep showing yourselves up,
being triggered, reacting to me. how
like I actually live in your head. I
love it, you know? I actually love it.
Like it's not Oh [ __ ] It's not even
anything to be triggered over because it
just goes to show that you are really
the triggered ones. Sat on YouTube every
day fat skinned and jealous. And I love
it and I love it. Wednesday as well. I
absolutely love it, mate. Sat on YouTube
every day, all skin, all ain't got a
life. Literally waiting for that Reddit
post. To be honest with you, it actually
made me laugh. It just goes to show that
yeah, everything that you try to call other people
I know. I know. Yeah, bro. So, it
doesn't even trigger anyone. It's
actually quite funny to be honest. It
just goes to show that you're everything
that you call other people. Skin m you
just It's just all your fat ugly selves.
Like, imagine that. Like, you you have
to sit on there, bro, waiting for that
post. That's how much you react to me. I
love it. I actually love it. Yeah, bro.
But it's not if I insist, bro. It's
logic. If nothing's changed in 3 years,
right? Say you've gone out for three
years, [ __ ] and you've tried and
nothing in them three years have changed.
You're not just It's not just going to
suddenly change. It's not just going to
suddenly change. And also, it's gotten worse.
Say 18 months. 18 months. Maybe
even me all you want. I don't believe in
it. So, no, I actually say 18 months. I
think 18 months is a fair
I think 18 months, maybe 20 months,
maybe been less than 2 years. You see,
it was a lot different. Now, you can't
even get conversations out of people.
Yet you expect somebody to believe that
the next time that they go out, all the [ __ ] stops. Even though
yeah, that's just delusional. But
anyways, back to these people stalking
me on Reddit, man. I love it, man.
sitting down all day on Reddit waiting
for any sort. It just goes to show that
they're all fat, ugly, and skin. They
their activity online, right? It just
gives themselves away
constantly. It's why they come on here
for entertainment, bro, cuz they're all
skin. They don't leave the house.
They're all [ __ ] disabled. They're
all disabled [ __ ]
I bet you about [ __ ] most of them are
[ __ ] 1500 [ __ ] stones to be fair,
bro. They're all fat, ugly stalkers.
That's literally all they are cuz
they're all skin. They're living their
worst life, bro. Tormented every day.
Waking up upstairs. Tormented every
single day of their fat, ugly lives,
bro. It's the truth. I can say it better than anyone.
Stat on [ __ ] the internet every day, stalking someone,
being tormented and obsessed every day,
reacting to me every single [ __ ] day.
That's a reaction. It's the same thing, right, as
uh when you when you go on the chat and
people wanting you to type back. They're
[ __ ] typing, bro. You know,
oh, [ __ ] I [ __ ] tired ain't gone. It
just goes to show that you've got
something they're really really jealous
of. It just goes to show more and more
and more. You know, every year these
people in this community keep doing
this. It just goes to show about their
own lives. You know, that's what it
does. The more and more these fat ugly
monsters do this, the more and more and
more it goes against them. You know that
It just goes to show more and more and
more and more and more and more and more
what these people really really really
really are about. You know, every day
they do this on [ __ ] Reddit. I'm telling you
just it it says everything about
themselves, you know that that's
literally all it does.
Proper fat ugly low lines in it. [ __ ]
hell. Reacting to me every day. It's
it's it's mad, bro. They're clearly
jealous. Like I was eating these piggy
sandwiches and I I'm looking at I'm
think you they're clearly jealous of of
something, bro. to sit online every day
doing this stalking year in year out,
year in year out. They're clearly
clearly jealous of something.
That's like the realest that's the
realest thing it can be. Think of it, right?
What are we, bro? What are we
apparently? Yeah. Oh [ __ ] What are we apparently? Skin.
We're apparently a mont and we're
apparently bored. But they're the ones
that are on YouTube every day stalking
you. Why the [ __ ] are they wasting their
time on a supposed skint monster? Their
precious life every single day where
they've got all of this money, where
they're better looking than everyone,
where their life is perfect. So why are
they sat on here doing this every single day?
Because they are the fat ugly skinned
muners. It goes in reverse. You don't
understand, bro. It goes, it's like a
car going in reverse.
Oh, [ __ ] And the only reason I say
jealousy, yeah, I tell you the reason,
obviously, it's jealousy in the fact
that they ain't got a life as well, is
because, like I said, Timmy doesn't get
it. [ __ ] Monty doesn't get it. They
only seem to stalk me nonstop cuz
obviously they're jealous of you, bro.
For them to do it year in year out.
You're still stalking me on Reddit, bro.
Like I' I'm I'm sat here having a piggy
sandwich and you're still stalking me on
Reddit. Like you need to be refreshing
that page, right? Every second. That
just goes to show that they're skin fat
ugly muners. It just it just it just
keeps telling me about their lives when
they keep doing this whole stalking
thing and reacting to me and being
triggered by me by Jojo being triggered
by me making videos on me. It just goes
to show that there's something that
they're jealous of that that that's all
it says. That literally all it boils
down to like a boiled egg. There's Oh,
[ __ ] you. Franklin go. It is clearly
clearly something. It is clearly clearly
clearly something. But you just sit on
Reddit all day waiting for any little
post any little Peter Belly content to
obsess and react over. Bro, they are
reacting to me. No, no, no, no, no, no,
no. Listen, listen, listen, listen. They
are reacting to me. You don't understand
what they're doing. They're typing,
typing video after video after video
after email. They are reacting to me
more than I could ever. So, why are you
saying that I'm reacting to it? I'm
telling you what they're doing. And
they're reacting to me.
They're clearly jealous of something.
They clearly clearly are cuckoo in with
the brain, bro. Like I'm telling you,
there's there's there is clearly
something that they are jealous of that
they don't want to tell anyone.
Yeah. No, I know. I'm I'm just saying
it's just weird. It just creeps me out.
I I know. It just creeps me out cuz I
just don't know how somebody could be so
jealous of a stranger.
And like I said, every time they do
this, it goes to show more and more that
they are the skin m. The more and more
they do this, the more and more and more
it goes to show. It's like what me and
Monty was saying um yesterday is that
hold on a minute, they're the ones that
are calling people skin, but they're sat
on YouTube every day. They wouldn't be
on here if they weren't [ __ ] skinn.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, man. They're clearly jealous of
something anyways. They're clearly
jealous of something. [ __ ] it's
weird, bro. I've never met such people
in my life.
I feel bad for them. I actually really
really feel bad for them. They never
stop as well. Like I feel bad. Like a
part of me reacts to it cuz I feel bad.
Like I want to react to these little
losers because they don't have anything
else. This is why they don't leave people alone.
This what that Ronald Pump said. He's
like, "They're never going to leave you
alone. Just leave YouTube." He was
right, bro. He says, "You're better
looking than them. You got more money
than them. And you got a better life
than them." It's the truth, bro. Cuz
since that guy went, they ain't stopped.
I've noticed that on this [ __ ]
Reddit, on this YouTube, they literally
do not stop.
I've noticed that as well. I've noticed that, too.
They're clearly clearly jealous of
somebody. Clearly jealous of somebody.
They are, bro. Like, this is weird, bro.
What the [ __ ]
They're sat on YouTube reacting to me
every day for reaction. Reacting for a Weird, bro.
No, they don't get me fuming, bro.
They're just weirdos. They don't get me
fuming, bro. They're just Oh, [ __ ]
Almost went over there. They don't get
me um fuming. They're just weirdos.
That's what they are. They're just
stalking weirdos. They ain't got me
fuming, bro. I'm sat here playing GTA.
I've got them fuming. They won't They're
triggered every day on YouTube, making
videos, making posts. That takes some
triggerless to be doing that every day.
Yeah, they're they're definitely jealous
of something, bro. They're definitely
definitely jealous of something.
Definitely definitely jealous of I've
never known such jealousy in my life.
You know that? I really have never known
such jealousy in my life.
And then then they'll turn around and
say, "Oh, well, what's there to be
jealous of?" Well, you're the one
wasting your life every day being
triggered to try to get a reaction.
What is your What's there not to be
jealous of, bro? You know what I'm saying?
They never leave you alone as well. I've
noticed that as well with these with
these weirdos. They used to do with LT
as well. They never leave people alone.
It is some It is some jealousy, bro. I'm
telling you it is
sat on YouTube. These fat ugly muners
can't leave their house. All [ __ ]
complete bully victims. None of them got
none of them have got a pence between
all of them. That's how skimp they are.
They're just [ __ ] absolute mongos.
[ __ ] fat disabled bongos. That's
literally what they are. They ain't got
a life. They have to live jealous of
someone else every day. That's the
truth. That is the honest to god truth.
They're jealous of me. I know they don't
like to admit it, but it is the truth
because you wouldn't do this what you do
every day. Wasting your life reacting
videos, videos, posting, reacting. Who
the [ __ ] would want a react? Who would
react for a reaction from somebody that
they're better than? It doesn't make sense. So,
have to talk about these people once in
a while, you know. Oh, [ __ ] Nice.
Anyway, back to the press in England. Eh,
still no reply. Eh,
but yeah, they don't get me fuming, bro.
I'm just talking about them. They're weirdos.
It just goes to show that they're
jealous every every day of their life on
YouTube. That's that's the only thing I
need to say, bro. Like, that's it. They
don't get anyone fuming. They're just weirdos.
Simple. And they react to me more than I
could ever react to them. Again, I live
in their head. They don't live in my
head. That's the difference.
Fat, ugly, jealous weirdos.
This is a good car, bro.
What's everyone doing anyways? I just
had a piggy sandwich.
Sat here depressed.
You don't see me [ __ ] stalking people.
I mean, it should just be so easy to
just have a heart attack in your sleep, but nah.
I want out of this life. Lucky I've got
this GTA and this Xbox and this TV.
I want out of this life [ __ ] ASAP,
bro. I've had a good life, bro. Good [ __ ] life. Yeah, man.
yourself would be the only way out of
something. I never ever would ever imagine that.
And to be fair, I think in another 27
years the suicide rate will be going up
and up and up and up and up. to be
honest with you, due to all this social media thing.
See, at first I thought it was actually
the money, but it's it's not money cuz
we have we still have money.
Um, and obviously we still get money and
[ __ ] So, we're still a lot better off
than a lot of people. But yeah, I think
it's the whole women and the whole
dating. It's enough to get anyone down.
It's enough to get literally anyone depressed.
I think it's enough to get anyone down, mate. Yeah.
I don't see anyone anymore either. So,
there's another thing.
I just feel isolated.
Yeah, I think suicide is literally the
only way out.
But honestly, my situation is a lot
different to other people's. You know,
I've still I just had this guy a minute
ago on Instagram saying, "Oh, you never
know what's around the corner." I know.
I know because I've been living it for 3
years. So, three and a half years I've
been living this life. So, I know
exactly what's around the corner.
And again, I'm not being awkward. I'm
not being difficult.
Yeah, you get you get a job.
Yeah. Same back to you. You get a job. There should be
welcome back to them [ __ ] [ __ ]
depressing days again, bro. Really,
I feel exactly the same as I did like
[ __ ] a year ago.
Nothing literally ever changes, does it,
in this life,
and then you have to look at other
people, they get sex and whatever. Well,
not other people like women and [ __ ]
It's not a life it's not a life you want
to lead where the odds are against you
in this country and it's not a it's not
a life you want to live.
It's really bad.
really bad, man.
But you never know, one day you'll wake
up and everything's different. Women are
not stuck up. You start getting better life experiences.
Never in a million years. If I generally
thought life was going to change. You
wouldn't feel like this. Generally, life
will never change. Never.
And another thing is with these weirdos
on here, right, I've noticed, right,
they bring up the same [ __ ] like women
and kids and [ __ ] Like that's how
autistic they are. They obsess over any
little thing people have said in the
past and they make it an excuse to be
jealous of someone even though like
they've literally started. And I'm
thinking, what the [ __ ] That was ages
ago. But they don't care. It's just an
excuse for them to go at someone to be
jealous. Like they don't really care.
Like in a way they like it, bro. They
like it when people react. They used to
love it when people react.
They never leave you alone, bro. I'm
just on Reddit right now. They never
stop. They never ever stop.
generally are severely jealous of me,
bro. Like, I'm I'm just going on this
now. Not reacting to these weirdos
anymore. But yeah, I just wanted to say
that they they are severely severely
severely jealous of me. And I hope they
get the help that they need. That's the
only thing I can say, bro. Literally,
they will never ever leave you alone.
It's like what that Ronald Ronald Pump
said. He was right, bro. They will never
stop. never stop. Bam. Bam. [ __ ]
smash you in your face. They'll never
ever ever ever ever ever ever ever ever
ever ever stop. Which is why which is
why I made a new channel, but I don't
really use it. I've got loads of videos
on there, but I don't really use it.
I think for your own sake, you should go
back on that channel
cuz they will never ever stop on it.
Never. They will never ever ever ever stop.
Never ever ever ever ever ever ever stop.
And what's the whole point of it now?
What what do you need to prove on it?
You've already proved you're better
looking than them all. You've already
proved that you got more money than
them. You've already proved that they
will never ever stop harassing you and
stalking you. Like, what's there left to
really prove? Nothing.
You give them content, they're jealous.
They can't leave you alone. And it just
goes on and on and on and on and on and
on and on and on and on and on and on
and on and on.
Yeah, they're stalking me on Reddit
again, Nicolo. They've been stalking me all day.
Mad that ain't it, bro.
Yeah, I need to go back on that main
channel, bro. I think I'm going to
delete this channel for real. For real,
bro. I'm going to delete this channel.
I'm deleting this channel, bro. I got my
main anyways. Not not today, but I'm
going to have to delete at some point.
Like actually delete it.
It's weird, bro. Yeah.
I'm thinking of ending it, me just the
whole like knowing that it's never going
to change. It's horrible, bro. Really?
It really is horrible.
I'm [ __ ] depressed, man.
I'm back to like a year ago, bro. Like
just severely severely depressed. Nothing's changing.
It's horrible. I want out of this life ASAP.
Oh, this person didn't reply back.
Anyways, by the way,
same old, same old, same old. I want out
of this life.
blame lady for [ __ ] having me in the
n in having me late, bro. I wish I was
born in the 1980s. Believe that back in
the old vintage days where you could
actually be in love and find someone and
society weren't [ __ ] up and you know,
nothing ever changes. It's like you're
being tormented by being alive. That's
actually what it feels like. You're
actually being tormented by being alive.
So yeah, I won't even be going out tomorrow.
Yeah, I won't be out tomorrow.
Yeah, I don't want to torment myself anymore.
Yeah, I went out [ __ ] last week. I
got eight numbers. That's enough numbers
and it just never changes. Never ever
ever changes. Never. Never has, never will.
I'm ready to die, bro. I'm actually at
that point. I'm actually like fully like
Yeah, I'm actually fully there, bro. I'm
actually actually fully there. Really,
bro? Really? Yeah.
That's why I say that people that have
kids nowadays is kind of cruel because
of the um day and age and [ __ ] Do you
know what I mean?
Yes, she is [ __ ] into sex.
This was something else. It will never
change. But I really, really, really
want out of this life.
Really, really, really want out of this
life. I'm telling you, I want out of it. You know, really do.
It never changes. I've been listening to
it for years and years and years, bro.
You know what's around. You don't know
what's around the corner. Anything can
pop up. It's just a blip. N.
That's all I've been hearing for years
and years and years. And every year it's
been the same old, you know. Well, it's
got worse in two years, sorry. But, you
know, it's been the same, you know. It
just never ever ends. It never ever
changes, you know. It's the truth. It is
the truth. It is generally the truth.
You know, I don't even think it is
depression. It's legit. It's a legit reason. Bro,
I know you're taking the piss out of me,
but I'm just going along with it anyways.
The only thing you could do is just kill
yourself and hopefully you wake up another person.
And hopefully there's an afterlife.
That's the only thing you can do
because it will never change, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. The only thing is you can kill
yourself and hopefully that you wake up
in an afterlife. Yeah.
It's really bad, isn't it?
It's super bad. It never changes. If
it's not changed in 3 years, it ain't
going to change now. Yeah.
It's really bad, bro. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, man. What do you do, eh?
I just play GTA and sleep all day, me. Yeah, man.
This life ain't ever changing.
Never ever ever.
It's like there's no point even going
out now. Even approaching anyone
cuz where it's all [ __ ] more so like
Tik Tok and Instagram now. You got no chance.
No chance of a family. No point of a
love life. No point of sex.
No point of nothing.
Nah, that don't even interest me anymore.
No, I'm good, bro.
I'm not gambling anymore. I'm probably
not even going to gamble on a football.
I don't gamble, bro.
That makes it even worse. And even if I
win, I'm still going to be depressed.
So, there's no point. So, there's
literally no point
cuz even if I won, I'd still be
depressed cuz I've still got money. So, yeah. Yeah,
it's so bad. I just wish it would
change, but it never ever changes.
It just never ever changes. Ever. Never
Then you got women that can get sex
whenever they want. They can get
relationships whenever they want and
you've just got to be sat there
depressed every day of your life.
[ __ ] ain't no life for anyone, mate.
It's no life for anyone.
And that's the thing in life. You go
backwards. You don't go forwards. You go Backwards. Yeah. So yeah.
Yeah. We'll never change this life. Never.
Never. Ever. Ever. Ever. Ever. Yep.
Yep. I still hear the same [ __ ] I hear
when I was 15.
I've been hearing the same [ __ ] from
when I was 15. Even now at 27, you know,
you don't know what's around the corner.
Um, things can change in a flick. Well,
then to that I say to them, then if that
is the case, then why hasn't it changed
in 3 years?
3 years is a long time, right, for
something just to click and change. So
why has nothing changed in 3 years?
That's what I turn around and ask them.
And to that they have no response.
I you're saying that things change in a
flick of a finger. Why has nothing
changed in 3 years then? because nothing
will ever change. So
yeah, it's depressing, bro.
I'll be deleting this channel soon anyways, bro.
Like for real, for real. I'm deleting
the channel. I'm just going to go on my main.
I don't want Fat Thompson and [ __ ]
Virgin Boy keep [ __ ] stalking me and
trying to like get on. I don't want to
give them entertainment. Um
because they're just creepy, bro.
They're very very very creepy. And I'm
going to block all the emails as well.
They're [ __ ] freaky weirdos, bro.
They're never going to stop ever. I
thought in a year they would have got
bored and they would stop, but they
never stop. That's why I'm deleting this
channel. I got nothing left to prove
anyways, bro. So,
I've got nothing left to prove to these weirdos.
Yep. Talking about yourself again, bro.
Back to LJ's channel, you [ __ ]
Back to LJ's channel, you [ __ ] bro.
Don't do on this channel.
Yeah, they're nowhere to be seen. What
did I just say to you, bro? I as it
stands on this community, right? I've
shown the most women, the most money,
the most friends, the best looks. I've
proved all I've needed to prove, bro.
I'm deleting my channel. Simple. I'm
deleting my YouTube channel, bro.
This YouTube channel here. I'm deleting
it. Like, just deleting it straight. So
yeah, they definitely want your ass,
bro. Listen, listen, listen, listen, listen.
Listen. I'm the only one on here that's
been seen with money, women, and
friends. None of you's ever have. End of.
So that's it. I've proved all I've
needed to prove.
So you people approve nothing but
stalking people on YouTube every day
projecting and you people never stop as
well. You people never ever ever
stop. That's another thing. These people never stop.
You know the mad thing is when I was on
the phone to lady the other day um
Nicolo I was saying to her yeah she
doesn't really understand how much I
hate some of these people here. He
hate some of these people here and how I
would just love to get my hands on one
of them. Like, you don't understand.
Could be anyone, bro. Triple H, Virgin
Boy, [ __ ] different people, bro.
I'd love to get my hands on them, but
they they're just low lives. I've got
nothing in life. That's why I'm deleting
my channel, bro. That's why I'm honestly
deleting my channel. I'm leaving the low
lives to it now, you know?
H because I hate them. I hate them
because of what they do. They're scum.
They're low lives. I hate them. And if I
ever got my hands on one of you people,
bro, you better run. I'm telling you. Yeah.
Nah, I don't project anything. You
people project your skint fat ugly lives every day.
Um, so yeah,
I I hate these people. Well, there's
reasons why I hurt Well, there's reasons
why I hate the Virgin.
I hate Pat. I hate the Virgin.
[ __ ] I hate them, bro.
cuz I hate what you do and what you try
and do. I hate them all, bro.
I hate all of you on here.
Trust me, all of you. Most most of you anyways,
you know, cuz I see what you do.
And like I said, if I didn't know any
better, bro, I would be in Newcastle
this week. If I didn't know any better,
I would have been in Milton Kees last
month. It's like I was saying yesterday,
but I'm not going to do that because we
all know what you people do. You annoy
people. You get people to go to your
area and then when people go to your
area, you don't show up and you pretend
like nothing ever happened and then you
all stick up for each other. We all know
what you people do now. You've been
doing it for years, right? So, yeah, I
think it's good that you calm me down.
And you told me the other day, Joe,
don't stress. You're not going anywhere.
Yeah, I ain't going anywhere cuz I know
what you people do. So, it was actually
it was actually a good thing that I did
calm down actually. And then you come
online and then you pretend like
nothing's happened. That's the most
annoying part. Like you come on here,
run up your mouth. Yeah. You're this,
you're that, you're this, you're that.
And then somebody from London will come,
right? You don't show up and then you'll
pretend like nothing happened and you'll
just come on YouTube like it's normal.
You ain't got no shame.
I am going Thailand. Yeah.
That's what that's what I hate as well.
That's what I hate. You've done it with
me. You've done it with LT. You know,
any toty kid asking stupid questions again.
Stupid questions. Stupid answer.
Stop asking stupid questions.
Yeah, stop asking stupid questions.
So, yeah. I don't know why you do that anyways, but yeah.
So, I hate all of you on here, bro. Most
most of you people. I actually do,
except for one worthy clock. Griezy, Steven Howard.
Um, there a few people on here. That's all right.
Yeah, I'm getting stalked bad, bro.
Emails being stalked on Reddit the lot,
bro. I've got actual stalkers on here.
Actual stalkers. They want my ass, bro.
I need to delete my YouTube channel.
Yeah, proper stalked. Proper stalked.
Yeah, properly, bro. Properly
all day as well on Reddit, man. They've
been stalking me on Reddit, man. All day.
They've got some weird obsession with
me, bro. It's weird. I'm going to delete
my YouTube channel, man. They want my [ __ ] ass.
Yeah, it's weird.
Like what Ronald Pomp said, better
looking, better life, more money, and it kills them.
I think he should be a psych
psychologist as well, to be honest.
Cuz ever since he's not been on it, they
haven't left me alone. He's He's clearly
right, isn't he, mate? They They don't
leave you alone. It's weird.
Yeah, I'm deleting my YouTube channel
anyway as well, so I'm just going to be
on my main now. Yeah.
I want out of this life. Nothing ever changes.
Nothing ever changes. Joe,
don't have kids nowadays. Societyy's
only getting worse.
Society is only getting worse, man.
Yeah, I won't be out tomorrow.
Go out tomorrow to what? get rejected
again and again and again and again and
again. I think we got that. We got that last week.
We live, we get tormented, and we die. Don't we?
You know what? I think I've actually
done some approaches when I was like 21,
22 as well.
Not as much. No, this has been going on since [ __ ] 21.
No, not 21.
It's been going on for about 4 years.
Solidly. It's been going on for about 4
years. So, if nothing has changed in 4 years,
then I don't think anything is ever
going to change.
You don't just wake up one day. Think of it, bro.
If you tried multiple times in a week to meet someone
and you've been doing this for four
years, right? Think of what's the odds
that just one day in four years you go
and everything's different. It's lottery
odds, bro. It's lottery odds.
Think of it. Yeah, I think it has been
going on for about 4 years actually
cuz I used to Yeah, I think it has been
going on for about 4 years.
Four. It has been going on for about 4 years actually. Yeah.
But we're supposed to believe
that the next time you go out,
it's all going to be different. Not
believe in it, bro. Don't buy it. Not
believe in it. Don't buy it. Don't even make sense.
What would have happened by now?
4 years is a long time. You would have
met someone by now. Simple as that.
Just sitting depressed all day, mate. Sitting depressed.
Sitting and depressed. Nothing to do.
Should be on a date this week. D with
all that approach in last week. Should
be on a [ __ ] date.
Should be on a date. Yeah, bro.
Let's see if we get a reply off this person, eh? Yeah.
I mean, they live right in the same area
as me, same age as me,
but all of these coincidences are just
to be mocked. You're never going to meet
anyone. You would have met someone by
now. I'm sticking to my guns, bro. 100%.
12 years is a long time. Enough.
Yeah, I won't be 30 cuz I'll be dead before then.
I know I won't be 30 before I know it.
I've got three years to go. I'm nowhere near 30
and I won't be 30 soon because I'll be dead. So, yeah.
So, I've messaged them, see what they say.
Probably get ignored again. Probably get
rejected again. Just like life in England, eh?
Well, is there any point living? I mean,
you can't even get a relationship. You
can't get a sex life, even though it
seems women can get sex when they want.
Is there a point of being alive to Oh,
[ __ ] Is there a point of being alive to be tormented?
I mean, don't you think you've been
through enough in your life?
It's [ __ ] It's not mental at all.
I've done a lot in my life. I don't care.
Keep going out. Keep getting rejected.
There's not more to life than sex. Go
tell that to women that that have sex
all the time. Go tell women that have
sex all the time, which is most of them,
that there's more to life than sex. If
that was the case, then they wouldn't be
in relationships with people. If there
was more to life than sex, right? Then
why is there people in relationships?
There is people out there that are in
them. They wouldn't be in them.
They wouldn't they wouldn't have
relationships. They wouldn't be in relationships,
you know, or having sex with people even
though most people aren't in them, but
there are people that are in them.
So why are they in relationships? They
must have seek out for relationship.
They must have seek out relationships.
So they must have seek out
relationships. So what makes when when
people say to me, oh like why why do you
need a relationship? Why are people in
relationships? That's what I ask them.
Why are there people why are there some
people in relationships then? Why do
they need relationships? So yeah,
we uh they reply to then stop replying.
Same old, eh? Same old England.
It's like a mystery box, but you know
exactly what you're going to get.
[ __ ] I feel like depressed like a year ago, bro.
Well, you seem to I tell you not to, but
you keep doing it. But I I asked you not
to, but you do it anyways. So, if
there's no need for a relationship
and you're asking me why I need a woman,
why are there people in relationships
when you actually do see them? Not not
obviously most people aren't, but you
still actually see them when you go out.
So, why are they in relationships then?
Doesn't make sense, you know? So yeah,
so yeah, it's just going to be it will
always be the same in this country. It's
like what Adman said, it will always be
the same in this country.
Rejection. Rejection. Rejection. Um yeah. Yeah.
It would always be the same in this
country. Is it
should be on a date this week.
Should be on a date this week. But nope,
no, not on no date this week.
Sat at home twiddling my thumbs.
I'm sat at home twiddling my thumbs.
That's what I'm doing. Sat at home
twiddling my thumbs.
Mad, is it? Yep.
So, mad Joe, you never know what's
around the corner. You never know who
you're going to meet when no one's
interested in this country. Eh, that's a
funny thing, isn't it? That's a funny
thing, is it?
And not to mention the people that we
have met. Look at all of the nightmares.
You know, USA is look at all the [ __ ]
that happened there. But don't worry cuz
one day you will go out and everything's different.
4 years later, everything's different.
Look at all of the madness that happened
with people as well.
Look at all of the madness that happened with people.
Jesus Christ. We We forgot we forget to
talk about that sometimes as well.
We can't go out without hearing boyfriends.
We can't go out getting a conversation.
If we do get a date, they'll just waste
our time like that Italian. It just goes
on and on and on and on and on and on
and on. It goes on and on and it goes on
and on and on, you know.
It's [ __ ] depressing, man.
I wish I was back in the house with them tenants
cuz now you really know how much it gets you, man.
It really, really does get to you. I'm
depressed again like I was a year ago.
Literally like I was like a year ago.
Having to think about this [ __ ] every
[ __ ] day. It's [ __ ] depressing.
[ __ ] live by your [ __ ] self, eh?
Uh, it never changes. So,
I said, "What day do you want to meet next week?
Probably won't get a reply."
Never will ever change. Never
like I said. Oh, I've got two bullets here.
Anybody would think that you're Timmy Eldridge.
These are the kind of experiences Timmy
Eldridge should be getting.
Timmy Eldridge should be getting these experiences.
Yeah. Timmy Aldridge.
Can't get anything, mate.
I think I was born in the wrong era, bro.
Oh, I was born in the wrong decade.
I was definitely born in the wrong decade.
You can't make money nowadays.
You can't meet anyone. What What life is
it for anyone here?
So what what is it?
What is life like for anyone here?
My eyes have gone all dry and [ __ ]
That's how you know your mental health's
playing up when your when your eyes my
eyes go all dry.
Like dry eyes. Yeah. Dry eyes. Dry eyes.
So we get dry eyes.
So yeah, you tell people that they don't
need this, they don't need that, why do
they need this? But then why are people
why do you see some people in
relationships then? Even if it's like at
like a [ __ ] bar, surely they don't
need each other then because so it
doesn't make any sense.
You always compare other people. Even if
people tell you to not do it, you still
do it because you think that you've got
a valid point. So yeah,
I'm surprised I haven't lost all my hair
with amount of stress and [ __ ] to be honest. Yeah.
I never had mental health, you know, the
past year. Oh, [ __ ]
But like the past year, I never really
had it, you know.
I was pretty all right, but now I've
gone back to being depressed.
Yeah, I've gone back to being depressed. Hold up. No, mate.
You don't even get people come around
and see you anymore. So,
I used to always be around people. I'm
not around people anymore. So,
it gets worse.
Yeah, it's horrible, man.
But one day we'll wake up and
everything's perfect, Grezy.
One day we will wake up and everything's perfect. Yeah, right.
Yeah, right, mate.
I just don't understand how people give
you advice when no one's interested in this country.
That's what I'd love to know.
They ain't interested. But people tell
you how you're going to meet someone and
all of a sudden it's going to get better
and no no.
I would just love to understand it, man. Yeah,
but they still tell people you're going
to meet someone.
I don't get it, man. I really don't get it.
I mean, why didn't you meet someone in four years?
Why didn't you meet someone in four
years? All that going out, all that socializing,
man. Makes you wonder, don't it, Grezy?
Makes you wonder, eh?
Oh, Franklin's gone flying. Jeez,
that is mad. Franklin just went flying. Franklin,
where the [ __ ] You went flying.
Never will change. Never.
Trying to figure out if I can trust
Grezy with my main channel
cuz I am actually deleting this channel
Grezy because the stalking is becoming weird again.
Like I actually get stalkers on the
actual actual stalkers.
Yeah, they've been stalking me all day, bro.
All day they've been stalking me.
That's mad, bro. I am deleting this
channel. 100% I am deleting this
Stoken. Stoken. Stoken. Stoken. Stoken. Okay. Yeah.
I already forget about
Yeah, man. I just went that Red Stars
channel and I'm I'm seeing some of the
people that comment and it's mad how
much these people talk about themselves.
It's mad how much you see people
actually talk about themselves. It's
actually mad. Like you see the comments
and stuff like these people are in their
40s skin on YouTube every day and they
think they're in a position to talk
about other people.
They literally like like like I keep
saying but if they weren't skinn they
wouldn't be on YouTube every day all day
every day. They wouldn't be on YouTube
sat indoors at home. Simple. So I mean
that's that's all you got to say back to
them bro. That's the only response you
have to give to them is that if everyone
else is skin, why are you sat on YouTube
every day on live streams all day every
day and can't take one day off of
YouTube? That's all you got to say
to these mongos. That's it. Enough. So, yeah.
What the [ __ ] You should have went
flying, bro. What the [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm deleting my YouTube channel anyways.
Yeah, I'll be deleting this YouTube
channel anyways later. Uh
Yeah, it's fair though, ain't it?
Greasy. A lot of people move there for a better life.
For a better life. You know, ain't no
life in England. Can't even get laid. Yeah.
You can't get a laid. You can't get any
dates. You have to put up with the
[ __ ] year in year out. Year in year
out, year in, year out
for a bad life. Yeah.
There's nothing here in England. That's
for sure. is depressing country. Uh, nothing. Mm.
These people in this community really
are [ __ ] fat bongos.
They really are fat bongos. I ain't got a lie.
What the [ __ ]
I had to make a new Reddit.
Thompson, the big fat stalker.
The big fat jealous stalker.
Reddit, bro. Yeah, made another Reddit
account. These people can't find me.
This woman says she's not into sex.
Grievy, do you believe her?
Every woman's into sex. That's [ __ ]
I think that's [ __ ] Do you
Yeah, right. The [ __ ]
telling me that. Yeah, right.
I think it's [ __ ] me, bro. You're
telling me there's actually women out
there that aren't having sex.
[ __ ] yeah, right.
I don't believe it. I don't believe
there's women out there not having sex. No way.
They're just giving it to these
crackheads and [ __ ] drug dealers.
That's who they giving it to.
To these [ __ ] crackheads.
There's no way there's women out there
not having sex. There's no way. No way.
Jose, are there women out there not having sex?
You actually believe that?
No [ __ ] way.
No way. They're having sex with someone.
How often would you say they have sex with it?
Probably a lot. Is it?
I think probably a lot.
No, they're [ __ ] someone.
They're [ __ ] They've got to be [ __ ] someone.
No, they've got to be sagging someone.
I sat depressed.
It's horrible, isn't it?
It's starting it.
I don't think I'm going to go sleep soon.
I know one slagging and no one shagging
virgin boy either. That's why he's still a virgin.
I generally generally do think suicide
is the only way out.
I generally generally think it is like
despite people's [ __ ] advice, you
know, keep trying no, I generally think
suicide is the only way out. That way
you never have to think about it anymore.
You're never going to have to think
about this, that, this, that.
I've already taken them.
I've already taken them. Hey,
I've already been taking them.
Generally, suicide is honestly the only way out.
Being depressed every day, rejected.
It's not no life for anyone's.
No life for anyone.
being depressed, being rejected,
being frustrated every day. It's no life
for anyone. It really, really is no life
Hearing that I got a boyfriend [ __ ]
it's no life for anyone. When you ever
just not ever want to think about it ever again,
I don't live with Laney.
But I do have cocoonals because of my
foot when I had that foot problem.
I think you need to kill yourself.
You've been trying for [ __ ] 4 years
and you've not gone into one
relationship. Your body count is [ __ ]
basically nil. Yeah. Like you should be
you should have been with someone.
You shouldn't be still dealing with
this. You're good-looking. You're not
ugly. You should be with someone. You
should be having a sex life. You
shouldn't be in this position. It's no
life for anyone.
It's no [ __ ] life for anyone.
It really is no life for anyone, bro.
And no one understands cuz women get sex
whatever they want
and other people ain't tried as much as
me. So no one understands it.
They get sex whenever they want. That's
why it's funny when they try to give
people advice because they get sex
whenever they want. They're shagging all
the time. You can't get no one.
You literally can't get no one. You
can't do anything. You can't change a
situation. You can't do nothing.
That's madness. That is madness.
And you don't even have a date this
week. Not even a date. How depressing is that?
Not even a date this week. You went out
last Thursday. You went out last
Saturday. You should be on a date this
week. Sometime this week,
just sad, sexy, frustrated, depressed,
or even just frustrated every [ __ ]
day of your life. Never changes. Never Madness, it
yep. It's sad, but I want out of this
life for real
before killing myself.
[ __ ] Laney would have to die before I
cuz Yeah, I would [ __ ] do it, bro. I
swear to God I would [ __ ] do it if it
wasn't for Laney. I would. This ain't no
life. This ain't no life, mate. I'm
telling you, it ain't no life.
This really ain't no life, man.
Ain't no life for anyone here.
There ain't no life here.
That's why I I fighted to not go out
tomorrow because it's just going to
drive you over the edge when you try to
speak to people again and they say
they've got a boyfriend again and again
and again and again and again. You know,
there's no reason for it. You should be
you should be with someone. You should
meet someone. You should be on a date
this week. You got eight numbers last
week. You should be on a date this week.
There's no reason for you to not be on a
date this week.
There's literally no reason why you
as soon as I moved in that house, I
weren't depressed anymore. As soon as I
moved out of the house, I'm depressed again.
That's mad, isn't it?
That is a madness.
It's only down from here, matey. It's
only down from here.
Is that right, Gregy? It's only down from here.
[ __ ] a change clothing in about
[ __ ] two three days. [ __ ] hell. Yeah.
But I'm not going to keep being treated
like this by women every every day of my
life. [ __ ] this. I'd rather kill myself.
Ain't no life. [ __ ] ain't no life for anyone.
There ain't no [ __ ] life for anyone, mate.
It really ain't no life for anyone.
I woke up and smelt the coffee ages ago, you know.
It's bad, is it? Very bad.
Yeah, I got a cocoon war cuz I had a
foot that foot problem
and obviously I didn't finish the
course. So, I've got my own cocons.
I just take my own cocons.
Um, so yeah. So yeah,
just being sad and depressed. Eh,
what kind of life is that, Grezy? What
kind of life is that?
So, you don't need to be skinned to be depressed.
You don't need to be skinned to be depressed.
No, man. You don't need to be skinned to be depressed.
No, I got money.
It doesn't mean anything, bro.
You're still going to keep having bad
experiences with women every day of your
life. if it doesn't really mean anything.
So yeah, go tell them, bro, to stop
[ __ ] having sex and stop getting in
relationships since people don't need
women and women don't need men. Why are
there people out there in relationships?
That's a good question
cuz they obviously were seeking for it, weren't they?
So, it doesn't make any sense.
Franklin, you've gone flying again. Yep.
Bad, bro. Just depressing life. Really, really bad.
I don't know why I wasted my time
getting a haircut. [Music]
I don't even want to waste my time.
I don't do any of the missions. I just
[ __ ] go around [ __ ] around on it.
They say they're not into sex. Well,
they are. They're shagging someone.
They're [ __ ] shagging someone.
You don't think that they're shagging
someone? Grezy? Of course they are. They
can't live without sex.
Just like men can't live without sex.
That's [ __ ] You know,
probably somebody with a [ __ ] million
[ __ ] Instagram followers.
Someone with an million Instagram followers.
Nah, they're shagging someone.
They're shagging someone, bro.
Everyone's got needs.
So they must be shagging someone.
They have to be shagging someone. Oh [ __ ]
And obviously they don't need to use
escorts. So they must be [ __ ] they
must be shagging someone. Definitely.
They're just [ __ ] anyways.
Isn't it mad how I've had all these
women and I still tell you I hate them?
What they do, what they like. Isn't it
mad how like I'm not in denial? And if
anything, I should be the one defending
them, but I can't. I hate them. I
actually do hate them.
I'm not even joking. I generally do hate
them. Really, really do.
I really really [ __ ] think they are
scum of the earth. I really generally
think they are, bro.
And if anyone I should be the one
defending them. I hate them. I [ __ ]
hate them, bro.
Not even joking, bro. I actually really really do.
You really don't understand.
But then you get these guys that have
never been with women or maybe just
can't get women now and they'll defend
them. It's weird, isn't it?
I've given them so many years to prove
me wrong. I've gave them so many years
to prove that they're not all the same.
And no, no, no, no. And they just prove
to all be the same
in one way or another. They all prove to
be exactly the same. They prove it every time.
The piss taking, the ignoring, the
boyfriend, the ghosting, the leading on,
they all prove to be exactly the same.
I noticed that over the years. They all
prove to be exactly the same.
What is reality? Yeah, that you need to
kill yourself. That's the reality.
You don't understand. I'm a lot
different than Greavves. I've I've
traveled. I've been where I've wanted to
be. I've done what I've wanted to do. I
don't need any goals now. I've done
everything I've wanted to do. I just
want to drop dead.
There's no goals to be had.
You know, I've done everything I've
wanted to do.
Grieves hasn't done anything and he's
older than me. No offense.
So you you know what I mean?
I can't even [ __ ] go out tomorrow,
bro. I can go out, spend £100, whatever.
Whatever, you know, save.
I can go out, but there's no point me
going out cuz it's just the same old
same old. Boring. I think I got my
money's worth on the haircut.
Well, that's the reason I can't do it
because a lady. That's the whole reason
I can't do it.
You should just be able to meet someone.
You've tried more than anyone. I should
be on a date this this this week. Why
the [ __ ] is this woman not reply back?
She's reply back. Ask me questions. I'll
reply back. No reply. So,
what is it? Another 3, four years of
meeting people that aren't interested. Huh?
Meeting people that aren't interested
for another 3, four years. Yeah.
Another 3, four years, eh?
It's so bad. See, when I was back at the
other house, I had people around me all
the time, you see. So, I couldn't think
of the stuff
cuz I was constantly like sort of with people.
Whereas, when you're by yourself,
you get time to think of it.
message, voice notes.
They're all the same.
All the same.
It's bad in it. Flies.
Yeah, we'll never change. Never
never never never [Music]
depressed over this whole women thing.
It's enough to make anyone depressed.
I remember one time. Yeah.
I remember one time, bro. Come back.
Boyfriend. I've got a boyfriend. I've
got a boyfriend. I kept hearing it, bro.
I kept hearing it, hearing it, hearing
it, hearing it, hearing it.
>> Came back, bro. [ __ ]
I came back hearing it, hearing it.
Hearing it. I went back to that kitchen.
I pissed all over the floor, bro. Bear
mind all the all attendants were sleeping. Yeah.
I went back, bro. I pissed all over the
floor. Smashed up the mug and
everything. Yeah. It was It was during
the time of um It was during the time of Ramadan.
Yeah. So, obviously, they used to wake
up like 3:00 4 in the morning. That's
like I remember this as well. They're
like, "What the [ __ ] happened?" I was
like, "I slipped."
I said, "I slipped in it." They said,
"Oh." And obviously the the piss dried
up in it. Yeah.
Our food have been our food have been
outside. Our food have been outside,
bro. [ __ ] food have been outside,
bro. Everyone heard it.
Oh, look. She's replied back. So, let's
hopefully we get a little me out of this. Hopefully.
I'm looking a bit silly with my beard
and stuff. Oh, look. We got a little reply.
That seems to jiggle it. Should it laminated? Yeah.
I pissed all over the floor, mate. Yeah. Yeah,
they they wondered what happened. Yeah.
Yeah. She replied back. She said, "What
day does she want to meet?" See, this
this could be perfect
cuz they're the same age as me. They're
exactly the same age as me. They live
right next to me and they work in a
shopping center that I live near and
they're actually the same age as me
and they're born in April just like my
mama. My mama was in April.
So, I'm going to show you how these
women are time wasters. Yeah. So, when
this one comes out, I'm not going to do
no kissing, no sex, no nothing. And
we'll see. Yeah.
It's the one that I met when I was with
them Birmingham lads.
These Birmingham lads. Do you remember
when I met the Birmingham lads the other
day with the baby Guinness? They were
cool lads. They were. I said, "Hold on a
minute, lads. I'm going to send this one
here." And they all watched me. They
watched me do it.
Yeah, greasy. They watch me do it.
Oh, look. I'm playing Franklin.
Oh, do you know what? King's not even
met Franklin yet. Franklin,
go over here, Franklin.
No, over there, actually.
Well, obviously I don't have much money
as I used to now. So, yeah.
come at the right time though really
because of um which I don't really care
about money anyways is what it is.
I'll never go back to gambling. I don't
think but a month is a long time so I
think I would have figured something out
by then. I never ever want to go back to
that gambling [ __ ] ever again.
Cuz if you gamble benefits, yeah, say
you got a payment of £600, 630 and you
gamble. Yeah. You might win more, but
then if you lose, you're [ __ ]
And I don't want to be doing that
[ __ ] [ __ ] again, bro. I'm not doing
that [ __ ] again.
I've got 2K. It's enough.
So that's it.
We're going to go back to them days,
bro. But they were the depressing days.
They were the depressing days, bro.
I don't know why I used to put myself
through that. I was mad, you know.
So, she's saying she actually does want
to meet. So, we'll see.
I think I need to find someone now, bro.
I'm getting old.
You know, I'm getting old. So,
we'll see. Yeah.
But like I said, I'm not going out
tomorrow. [ __ ] that. But
it's not even the money side of it. I
just can't be [ __ ]
Yeah, I went out them two days, Gonzie.
I was doing a lot of approaches. I was
trying to meet somebody before I went completely skint.
So, I wanted to say, "Oh, yeah, I've got
2K. I've got someone. Uh, you get £1,100
a month. I we can just make it work." You know,
I was just trying to find them before
the all the money stopped, you know what I mean? So,
well, I should be happy, man. I've got a
nice bed, a nice Xbox, a nice telly,
two grand. You know, life could be worse.
But I don't have a candidate for baby Peter.
So, what's what fun is that if you don't
have a candidate for baby Peter? Yeah.
Do you still gamble, Joe?
>> Yeah. But then this person replied and
then it made me happy. So yeah,
I'm not completely [ __ ] yet, but then
if they don't meet me, they live in my
area, so I mean [ __ ] they're going to
[ __ ] see me, you know.
But then if they don't meet, then I am actually [ __ ]
Like I am literally I I am leaving, bro. [ __ ] this.
Yeah. You do you believe I don't gamble
anymore? I don't gamble.
I go to these weather spoons all the
time. I don't gamble. I don't have the
money to do it anymore.
I don't have money to be wasting. I
don't do other things with it. So I don't
but I might do the future.
Might do in the future, but I doubt it.
[ __ ] that. That's what it reminds me of
these days, man. The gambling days and
the more days. But I would I gamble again. Uh
yeah, maybe the football, but that's it.
If I can't find a side hustle by then to
make more money, then I'll have to
gamble on the football.
I'll have no other choice.
Like I said, the goal is 100 to 350. 350
to,400. Bam. Done. two football bet one
wins which is quite will be quite hard
to get two in but maybe just 100 to 400
but that's only if I don't find another
thing if I find another thing then I won't
cuz I don't really want to be getting
into that [ __ ] again you know
I mean you're not going to do your boo
you're not going to do your balls in Oh,
you're not going to do your balls in on
football, are you? Let's be real.
Could go to university. I could get some loans out.
To go to university, get some loans out.
So yeah, let's see if this person wants
to meet anyways.
[ __ ] sake. [ __ ] sake, bro.
These [ __ ] bro. These [ __ ]
They'll be the death of me one day.
There really will be the death of me one day. Swear down.
I mean, even if one meets you, that's
pretty bad, isn't it?
Million approaches, eight numbers, three
replies on one meat. It's pretty [ __ ]
bad, isn't it?
So, yeah. Remember [Music]
the 19year-old Joe?
He used to suck my todder.
Oops. Left, right.
Yes, he used to suck my todder.
He works two days a week.
Yeah, I'm just going to meet her around
that area then
where we both were. I don't I don't
actually live there anymore. I've just
moved out from there, but she'll think
that I live there
on a Thursday.
I'm not. So if you work two days a you
work two days a week,
she's got to be [ __ ] skin, is it?
She's um Ukrainian.
She's the same age as me as well. So
yeah, Thursdays around the area will be
good, man. It won't be too busy. I'm not
going to go to a Weather Spoons, but she
only works two days a week. She must be
[ __ ] skinned. I know what she does.
I'm not going to tell you what she does,
where she works
cuz we got a certain virgin on here that
likes to stalk people. But yeah,
you know, I just met them in a pub in
central London and they were like, "Oh, um,
they said they work here." I was like,
"Oh, what? You work in the Tottenham
Court Road one?"
They said, "Oh, no. Uh,
no. Um, what do they say?
Strapford." I said, "Oh, okay. I live in Stratford."
And I said, "Well, like where?" I said,
"Oh, so do I." I said, "Oh, I live in I
said, "I live in Maryland." And they
said, "Oh, I live in Maryland as well."
I said, "What?" Cuz obviously where we
met was far away from there. Most of the
people there were like, "Dude, don't get
people from East London." Then she said
she was the same age as me. And yeah, I
was talking to her. Yeah.
Yeah, she does.
It was when I met them Birmingham lads
and the other guy as well from London.
We were all getting on it, man.
Yeah, Thursday was good, but Saturday
was [ __ ] for some reason.
No, it doesn't sound suspicious at all.
It sounds normal
actually. It sounds very normal.
Yeah, I met a lot of Ukrainians here
recently. Oh, [ __ ] They don't say they got boyfriends.
That's one thing about them is they
don't actually say they got boyfriends.
It's either they say no or they say yes.
No, it's not the same. It's not the same
birthday. She doesn't have the same
birthday month as me. She's born in
April. I'm born in October.
It's not sus at all. When I was doing
Uber, I met a guy in central London. He's Turkish
and he lives on the same road as me.
There's a guy that works in the O'Neals
in central London and he lives in the
same on the same road as me because I
see him. I said, "Oh, you from O'Neil's?"
She's not born in the same month as me.
I'm born in October. She's born in
April. And I have actually met somebody
the same date of birth as me in Newcastle.
I have actually met someone, they've got
the same date of birth as me. They live
in You remember that one in Newcastle I
went on a date with? They've got the
same date date of birth as me.
27th October 1997.
Same date of birth.
And they actually proved it as well.
We'll go to Ukraine. Grezy. Uh, no. Yeah,
she's not born in the same month as me.
We can't give too much info away cuz
obviously virgin boy. So, uh, divergent. [ __ ]
Oh, [ __ ] My caps should come soon,
Grezy. My little caps. Huh?
What are you talking about?
Yeah, my little cap should be coming soon. Greavves.
I'm not going out tomorrow, bro. I can't afford it.
Oh, and I need to meet this [ __ ] next week.
She comes out. [ __ ]
How cute is that? Groovy.
Hope you got a time waster like that. Italian.
No, we don't want that, matey.
Down, down, down. I can't afford it,
Joe. I can't afford it, matey. Nah. Brying. Oh, bless.
I think I want to have a baby. Greavves.
I want to have a baby now.
I want to have a bubba.
Then they'll give me free housing.
Then I could sublet all the rooms. [Applause]
Then I could sublet all the rims. Think
about it. Greasy.
Then I'd have a be a better life for me
and baby Peter. Grimsy.
A How cute is that? Huh?
How cute is that? Grezy.
Well, I look after the bubshin. The bubshin.
Well, you don't think I can look after
bubins, bro. I'm an uncle to many children.
Don't be so nasty.
I let all the rooms there. Yeah,
crazy. I know you miss them things every
week, right? Ah, boyfriend.
But mate, I don't think I'll be able to afford it.
And they've all got boyfriends,
mate. I won't be able to [ __ ] afford it.
[ __ ] The time already
got five friends.
Yeah, it might be funny to you, mate,
but it's not funny to us when it keeps happening.
You know, we're trying to find a
candidate for baby Peter and they're all
saying they've got boyfriends. It's [ __ ] annoying.
Well, hopefully this person will meet me
and they can be my new mama.
Franklin, you're going to go flying in a
minute. Franklin. Oh, you didn't go flying. Hello, Franklin.
I can't believe you stay in month to
month, Grezy. You stay in month to
month, don't you?
You stay in month to month, don't you, bro?
I don't think I could do that. me matey.
I like to go for a drink, but I won't be
able to [ __ ] afford it every week now, matey.
You can afford it, but you just won't be saving anything.
That's the thing.
You can, but you just won't be savored.
That's the thing. [ __ ]
That's mad, bro.
How do you do it, Greavesy? Don't you
want to go out and pull some birds and stuff?
Go for some little kisses.
I used to do it every week. Me two
weeks. I used to do I used to do it,
bro. Like [ __ ] used to be ace.
Used to have some kisses, kiss some boobies.
Um, so we touch some boobies and stuff.
I can't do that anymore, bro.
I don't have the energy. I can't afford it. [ __ ] Yeah.
Well, don't you want to have sex and stuff, Grezy? bless you.
Bless you in life.
Bless you. Then if it would take you uh
4 months to save to go to America, bless you.
Bless you in life. Then if it if it
would take you 4 months then bless you.
Bless you in life. [ __ ] man. Yeah. Heat. Hey.
Hey. Bless you then.
Bless you then. Greasy,
have you ever got drunk before? Grezy
what it's like? How it feels?
Well, bless you then.
Bless you then, Grezy. Hey, favor.
God bless you.
Did you see the Was the people in the
pub looking at me, do you reckon? The
other day, Grezy,
you reckon they were looking at me?
You reckon they were looking at me? Huh?
Do you think they were Do you think they
were looking at me?
But yeah, I did like them lads that I
meet met from Birmingham, Grezy.
I think I might be in love.
They were cool guys. They were
Yeah, there were cool guys there were
quite good looking Grezy as well.
Oh, that that the one that lives near me replied back.
This one said she will meet me and she
lives up the road and you know what? If
she doesn't meet me, I'll go to her
workplace and beat her up. I'm only joking, bro.
I do remember Nicolo. It's the same atmosphere.
Yeah, I know where you got that from.
You You got that from um Monty Man, is it? Nah, bro. Nah.
I met a few Ukrainians actually the past month.
I tell you what though, they never say
they have boyfriends. Never. Even the
Russians never say it.
They even just say yes or they say no.
But they never um
This is how you know these people in
England are lying because why is it that
Russians and Ukrainians and [ __ ] they
never seem to have boyfriends, right?
Then as soon as you speak to an American
and in English, they all seem to have
boyfriends. It's [ __ ] stupid, bro.
It doesn't make sense. Yeah,
this person is still [ __ ] messaging
me on [ __ ] Instagram, bro.
But like I said, Greasy, at least I've
got at least I've got Franklin,
you know? He cheers me up. So yeah, I
didn't pay almost £500 for a [ __ ] TV
for nothing, you know.
But yeah, I'd have to give this uh this
week of miss.
I could go out, but um
it's not about the money. It's just I
can't be bothered to go out.
But let's just hope this person beats me
and I never have to ever try again
cuz I have been sending this [ __ ] recently. So
see the thing is I don't like playing
the long game.
Do you understand what I mean? I don't
like playing the long game.
What do you have to do with some of these [ __ ]
I don't like playing the long game. E.
Uh, it's the same atmosphere.
See, you even take the piss out of Monty
Man as well, don't you, Nicolola.
She's the same age as me as well.
Same age as me, bro.
Good in it. Same age.
I have to be careful with what I say on
here though, Nicolo, cuz obviously Virgin Boy
know [ __ ] Virgin boy is like jealous.
You know the [ __ ] virgin. Yeah.
One second. What?
Oh, let them try. Let them try. Zippy zippy.
Let them pop sippy. Huh?
God bless you. One second. I'm just
making a couple of
moves here. I'll be back in two seconds approximately.
Yep. I'm just just making a couple [ __ ]
Is that all right?
Is that all right with you?
One second. This way to the top of
Sorry about that. I was making a couple of [ __ ]
I'm playing Franklin. Hang on a minute.
You like that little voice, Grezy?
Franklin goes flying.
Is that what happened to you?
What happened to you? Thank you.
I told you that everywhere the coaster
Oh no, it's almost
It's almost packed up.
The car is almost packed up.
Why you still in there, Frankie?
Thank you, Lyn.
Yeah, I'm running them over.
I'm running them over with my big my big vehicle.
There's my big vehicle.
You should You should already know.
Do you remember Peter Belly and his
little cat boozy? Why do you take the
mick out of me? I've got some lovely
caps coming actually. Yeah. Oh [ __ ]
Oh [ __ ] hell. Grezy.
Do you think if you got more money a
month you would go out drinking then?
Grieesy. Would you go out drinking then
if you if you got more money? Oh no. Oh man.
Yeah, I like I like going out and having
a little drinky.
I think it's quite cool
to be honest with you.
You get to speak to loads of [ __ ]
So remember that time gre I got a
[ __ ] in the weather spoons toilets.
That was quite cute, wasn't it?
You have to admit that was quite cute, wasn't it? pressure. Oh, Franklin,
are you okay? Franklin got hurt, Grezy.
He just had He just got hurt.
I'm surprised he's still alive, to be
honest with you. [ __ ]
So, Greavvesy, what obviously me and you
disagree with a lot of things, right?
What What's your opinion on Virgin Boy?
Like nonsense. What's like what's your
opinion on him?
What's your opinion on the Virgin?
Quite creepy or what's your opinion on
on the Virgin?
What's your opinion on the Virgin?
I'm I assume you've seen like what's
what's been going on on her and stuff, you know?
dress is smart. He doesn't dress smart,
mate. He dresses like a complete virgin. [ __ ]
is a f
He's a [ __ ] virgin. Wave a look how I
dress and I've had more women than him.
Dresses a man should do dresses how a
man should do. He can't get any women.
I've had more women than him. Grezy, he
dresses like a complete and utter virgin.
You're taking a [ __ ] piss, son.
No. What what a man should do,
Greavvesy, is actually wash his hair and
actually use proper products. His hair
looks like he's dipped it in [ __ ] a
load of grease.
It's like he's dipped it in a load of
[ __ ] grease. That's That's not how a
man dresses, mate. He's a complete and utter virgin.
Where is he? [ __ ] He looks like a
[ __ ] [ __ ] That's not how a [ __ ]
man should dress, bro. I wear anything.
I wear tracksuits. I wear blazers. I
wear caps. I don't wear caps.
And I guarantee you, mate, I've had more
[ __ ] than him. More [ __ ] than you
ever ever get.
No, but what he wears, he looks like a
[ __ ] the the shitty cheap suits that
he wears. He literally looks like a [ __ ]
Do you not remember that I used to wear
a suit, bro? He's clothing is is
literally what tramps wear.
Literally is literally the biggest [ __ ] going literally.
So, no, not not usual suits that normal
people wear. Just just the [ __ ] that he
wears. He looks like he looks like a [ __ ]
He has got no fashion sense whatsoever.
Got no fashion sense in the slightest.
Let me actually look. Actually, I've not
looked for a long time to be fair. [ __ ]
no. He looks like a [ __ ] [ __ ]
and he and and he seems to uh
think that he he's got money when he
literally has nothing. I don't know why
he has to betray that he's got money
when he literally has nothing. He's lost
the money game time and time and time again.
He literally has to try to make it seem
like he's got money.
I think that's the sad part. I need to
get an adapter, bro. [ __ ]
Well, he's he's [ __ ] skinn than a
[ __ ] skin flick.
He's a He's a He's a [ __ ] He's
[ __ ] skint. Oh [ __ ] He's skinting
than a [ __ ] skin. Easy. Thinking
a [ __ ] skin, mate. freaking skin.
Is he really?
He wouldn't be the first, bro. He
wouldn't be the first.
I've got a lot of people obsessed with
me on this community, bro.
A lot of people.
He's not the first. He won't be the last.
You and your little ways baby Peter