Oh, [ __ ] hell.
Change man. Actually, I've been late
last night and I'm trying to get this
guy to understand. He doesn't seem to
process these days. We won't be reacting
to these bosses anymore. Anyways, we
wasn't reacting. I was just trying to [ __ ] explain
explain something, you know?
You know what I mean? Sure
about that, bro.
Don't know who the [ __ ] you are, man.
I'm going out today for a few uh drinks
cuz I'm not getting that like virgin boy.
about that video, man. Just had to like
explain this [ __ ]
But obviously before I go out, I have to
change my bed. I always change my bed
and I have to change my bed. I know I'm
going to go out, but [ __ ] yolo it. Yeah,
I should have got more thumbs up on that
video cuz uh what I was saying was right, bro.
I can't do this. Awesome. Oh [ __ ]
Let me try and do these buttons, bro.
Yeah, that's me, man. It's me.
One second, bro. Hold on. Oh, it's a sick one.
That's why [ __ ]
Do you like my newest video? I think I I
talked a lot of sense in that video. I
think I think it is the truth. I don't
know about you, but I think it is the truth.
I think it was a banger, really.
Yeah, it is the truth, bro. Like that it
does come down to jealousy with these
people in this uh community. I I think
it's a banger.
One second. This
I don't know how people spend 150.
Yeah, I'm from London. I don't know how
people spend 150 on nights out, bro. I
will go out drinking and I won't spend
nowhere near that. One [ __ ] 50.
Never. I think I've done it once when I
was going to really expensive places.
I had Downs or something. Why? Someone
that's better looking than you has got
down syndrome. But you must got be
mistaken with yourself.
Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah, you must have got
me mistaken yourself, bud.
They took somebody to put a washer on the floor.
You must have got me mistaken with
yourself. Probably was looking in the mirror, bud. Yeah,
you probably looking at yourself in the
mirror. I must see yourself reflected on him. I [ __ ]
Oh, you're talking about yourself, mate. Oh [ __ ] Self-reflector.
You don't need to worry about where I
go, bro. Don't worry about where I go.
You don't need to worry about where I go, bro.
Just be out today, bro.
Is that okay with you, boss? No. [ __ ] off.
sink it. None. No one's ever recognized me. Never
Yeah. You okay, boss? Why notorious? How
are you, boss?
I went out twice last week, bro. [ __ ]
I got eight numbers and I've only got one meat.
I've only got one meat, bro. It's
[ __ ] terrible, is it?
It's terrible, bro.
I'm going out again today, bro. Oh,
don't be depressed. Don't be depressed,
notorious, boss. Go out and have some
drinks. That's what I'm doing today, bro.
Some kid chasing me. Yeah, no one cares
about that stuff, bro. That's all old.
No one cares about that. Stop living in
the past. We're living in the future.
Yeah, I'm sending it today, bro. I've
got Asperers. Now you must be talking about yourself. Nah,
now you must be talking about yourself,
bro. I ain't got autism.
Nah, you must be talking about yourself, bud.
No talking about yourself on my channel, please.
Yeah, I'm sending it today, notorious,
mate. I'm sending it hard, bro.
I'm sending it hard. Yeah,
got somebody that wants to meet me
tomorrow at North Street. So, yeah. Hey,
notorious bro. You want to uh what do
you reckon estimate I'm going to spend today?
Now I'm thinking zippy about 80 quid.
Do you like my video? Do you like my
little video to Jo? I was really trying
to make him understand but he wouldn't understand.
People say they spend 150. I end up
spending like £80.
Nah, you won't spend £200.
You won't spend 200.
Nah, that's very very unlikely. It
normally ranges from 70 to about
if you got like a proper proper mad one.
Anyways, bye-bye. You probably spend
about 130. I don't know how people spend
your I think I think that's going over
the top, bro. I spent it once when I was
going to these expensive clubs and I was
buying other people drinks but nah bro
I'm sending it hard hard notorious like
hard hard bro
I got eight numbers in [ __ ] two days
notorious bro I'm doing them sober as
I see. Notorious. I prefer Thursdays.
Stop talking about yourself. Anyways,
Notorious, bro. I prefer Thursdays. Have
you ever done it on a Thursday?
Thursdays are the one, bro.
Thursdays are the [ __ ] one, bro.
If you ever on Thursdays Yeah, bro. Nah,
>> I don't like Sundays, bro. No,
it gives me bad memory. Sundays, bro.
When I was doing that Uber, it took me
[ __ ] 8 hours to get £55.
8 hours to make £55, bro.
[ __ ] 8 hours.
No, I don't like Sundays, bro. My
favorite is I think it's Wednesdays and
Thursdays or Thursdays and Fridays. I
don't like Saturdays cuz like with
Saturdays, there's too many [ __ ] Notorious.
There's too many [ __ ] on Saturdays,
bro. Too many [ __ ] about Yeah.
Too many [ __ ] about, bro. You know
what I mean?
Too many [ __ ] about
and there just a younger um
younger [ __ ] younger crowd, you know?
That's why I don't like Saturdays. Too many [ __ ]
You're the person I meet next week. I
met them on a Thursday. I I approached
them in the pub. Notorious.
And my little friend I made watched me.
How cute is that, Nilius?
I was thinking of that USA Izzy, you
know, when before I went before I went sleep yesterday.
I was in the room by myself. I was
thinking about that USA is notorious.
I couldn't stop thinking about you. You
know what, bro?
It was [ __ ] hot, man. >> Yeah.
Yeah. It's very cute. It's going to be a
cute site today. Notorious boss.
It's going to be You don't do You don't
do the approaches anymore.
>> You don't do the approaches anymore, Notorious. No.
You don't do them anymore, boss. Why not?
I'm going to do some sober as well. I
don't usually, but I will
have my little happy clap on.
Did you watch my video to Did you watch
my video to Joe? Uh,
did you watch my video to Joe F?
Did you watch it? Huh?
Did you watch my video to Joe F, bro? Yeah, man.
Yeah, man. I was basically saying that
like these people stalk me every single
day cuz they're jealous. Cuz if they
wasn't, they would just like not waste
their life on you. I was trying to make
him understand, but I don't I don't
think he understands. I said that like
if you're better than somebody and
someone's really a skin mto and they're
all of this then you would leave them
alone but you can't leave them alone.
So that obviously means you're jealous.
That's that's what I'm saying bro.
And I was just saying various different
things and how it just makes no sense. You know
these people do what they do on here
every day cuz they're jealous, bro.
That's the cold hard truth of it.
If you're this and you're that, why are
they reacting to you every day? Why are
they wasting their life stalking you and
reacting to you and they're reacting to
you as well? Because all of this
stalking on Reddit,
they are reacting to get a reaction.
Doesn't make any sense. Think of it,
Notorious, right? Say there's a woman
that's a complete scumbag who is no good
and she's just not a very good person.
Would you waste your life on her or
would you go and find someone else?
Would you waste your life stalking every
day unless you was in love with them or
whatever? You wouldn't. You'd go on and
you'd find someone else. And same thing
goes with this.
The fact that they spend all day every
day that they won't leave you alone.
They'll be on their deathbed, bro. and
I'll be like, "Look at all of the years
they've wasted reacting to me and stalking me."
That's the difference, bro. And let me
tell you something, the tourist. Do you
know why I don't meet these people
anymore? Like, I didn't go to Newcastle
before that Triple H and I didn't go to
that Milton Kings because, bro, they're
all the same on here. You go to the
area, no one shows up. Um, they uh they
don't no one shows up and then they come
back on YouTube like nothing's happened
again. That's why I don't [ __ ] with it.
That's why I don't bother with him, bro.
I was just trying to explain with this
[ __ ] Joe because he doesn't seem to get it.
Um, so yeah,
but yeah. Well, anyways, we're going to
be sending it today. Anyways, I need to
put some washing on
and then we always have to get back to a fresh bed.
I'm going to wash my hair. Put my little
cap on. Put my little cap on. Uh, put my
little cap on. Victoria. Oh, that's so
cute. Is it?
Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ]
Bro, you can't You know what? You can't
even do that nowadays. It's getting so
hard. No, I don't think you'll get a
kiss, bro. It's so hard nowadays. You
can't even get that.
That's the That's the That's the maddest
thing about it. You can't even get that. Oh,
you can't even get that nowadays. But
yeah, anyways, if they weren't jealous
of you and stuff, whatever, they'd leave
you alone. That's that's the difference.
But they're giving you attention every day,
so doesn't look good, does it?
And then he'll be like, "Oh, well,
they're doing it for
>> Hopefully it's not raining." And then
he'll be like, "Oh, they're doing it for
reaction. And they're doing it for
reaction, but they're not doing it for
reaction because they are reacting,
which is what I tried to explain a
million times. And then he doesn't
understand it cuz he's a [ __ ] idiot.
And why the [ __ ] would you want a
reaction from a skin mon? That doesn't
make any sense.
And then you realize all along
what it points to is jealousy.
That's the thing.
Then they say then they say, "Oh,
there's not or there's nothing. Oh, it's
not." Oh, there's nothing to be jealous
of. But no, no, no. On YouTube, wasting
their life away.
You got [ __ ] bra today.
Don't underestimate the old Thursdays jealousy.
>> It's like what Ronald Pop said before.
You're better looking than them. You got
a better life than you. You got more
money than them.
>> It's the truth though. It It's easy.
Oh [ __ ] I'm just going to wear my
little cap and my little shorts. My
little cap and my shorts. Notorious,
what do you think?
We're going to bother with the jeans to be fair.
I hope I don't get I've got a boyfriend
today. Do you think I'll get it? Huh? Yeah.
That's why they waste That's why they
waste all their life talking to me.
Look at Virgin boy. He looks like a
[ __ ] rat. That ugly rat face. He
looks like a [ __ ] He looks like a [ __ ] rodent.
He looks like a [ __ ] Ronin, bro.
Jesus Christ. I'm [ __ ] younger. I've
got more money. I'm better looking. I've
had more women.
Better women. Like, just just put put
the evidence there, bro. No.
I hope I don't get the I've got
boyfriends today. Bro,
have you been getting it recently?
They got boyfriend.
They've all got boyfriend.
I don't care, bro.
You got a lot of washing here.
The hell did you do all these things?
I [ __ ] [ __ ] you up, you little virgin. Virgin, boy.
I hate the imaginary
boyfriend as me.
I hate me.
That's [ __ ] annoying, bro. Ain't it?
reading. You've been getting it as well.
The boyfriend [ __ ] hating me.
So, yeah. Anyways,
why have you got so much [ __ ] stuff here, man?
You shouldn't put a wash on if you're
not going to take it out.
What the [ __ ]
You shouldn't leave us like that, you know?
[ __ ] hell, man.
these people. Hey, notorious. These
people never leave me alone. They never
leave me alone, bro. Help me.
But yeah, it is it is clear that it is
cuz you're better looking than them. Oh.
what it is.
>> Yeah. Just say to them, I used to say to them me.
I used to say to them that I am your I
am your boyfriend.
That's what I used to say to them. Me I
used to say that I can be your new
boyfriend. That's what I used to say.
Oh, I used to say that I had a boyfriend.
Got boyfriends, man. Don't be silly.
Victorious. One in five men of relationships.
There's so many single people out there.
>> Yeah. All these women claim they got boyfriends there. Virgin boy.
Virgin. Virgin. Virgin boy. Virgin boy.
Bye-bye, Virgin. Another virgin. Another
[ __ ] that comes from LJ's another
skin self. Here's another thing. Yeah. I
know you you like LJ Notorious, right?
But um here's the thing. Yeah. If these
people weren't skimp, why are they on
YouTube all day? You know these these
little mongos on on on Laur's, right?
They sit down and they call people skin
all day. But why are they sat on YouTube
every day if they've got all of this
money and everyone else is skinn? That's
what I don't understand.
They wouldn't be on here if they weren't
skint. I'm not going to be on it. I'm
out all day today, bro.
You shouldn't take your [ __ ] out, bro.
One second, man. Yeah.
I told you, you know, Antman. Yeah. He
said to me that they're just not
interested in this country. Is that true?
They're just not interested in this country.
Is that true? Yeah.
I'm interested in thinking about you, boy.
That's for sure.
The rest is dead. But I'm sort of send
it there cuz got nothing else to do. So
and I'm not skin like these people on YouTube [ __ ] virgin mate.
We can spend 200 pound today. Don't
really want to spend 2000 pound.
Um, but obviously I could. Not a problem.
It's not a problem, mate. Yeah. Brazil.
Brazil is a lot easier.
Yeah, man. It's not a problem, mate. A
skin virgin like these people
sat on your tube every day. Oh, my little caps.
I don't think they're coming. Yeah, man.
Yeah. South America. Brazil. Yeah, bro.
I had some Brazilians. They were a lot
easier. Wasn't they zippy?
Yeah, I'll be out today getting rejected. Let's see.
But it's not tit for tat though because
they're the one. No, no, no, no, no. But
here's the thing though. It's not tit
for tat because they're the ones that
start it. They're the ones that have a
channel dedicated to me and won't leave
me alone. So therefore, it's actually
not tit for tat. It's not tit for tat
because they're the ones that have got a
channel dedicated to me and they keep
stalking me. So actually it's not tit for tat
because if they didn't say anything I
wouldn't be talking about them and I
wouldn't be and I don't post about them.
So actually it's not tip for tat. It's
actually them starting it. Put this
watch out. I'm going out for a few drinks later.
Yeah. But it's not No, no. It's not the
point of being the bigger man and not to
react. I'm telling you why they're doing
it. I'm explaining to you why they're doing it.
We're not talking about reacting or not
reacting. I'm explaining to you why
they're doing it and who who and how it
makes no sense other than fantasy.
That's what I'm trying to explain. I was
just saying to Notorious right here,
right? If you come across a woman who
was a scumbag
that done this, that done that, that
done this, would you would you keep
talking to her every day unless she was
in love with her? No. You'd go and find
someone else. So, they could just be in
love with you. I mean, that's also a
possibility. They could want to [ __ ]
with you. They could want your ass. But
yeah, I think it's probably deep down
they know that you're better looking
than them and you've got a better life
than them as well. Just like what Ronald
Pump said. Oh, I'm going out today by the way.
Yeah, I'll be going out today. Yeah.
Going for a few beers. So, I said I
work, but I've got nothing better to do, bro.
So, that's what I'm saying, bro. You
wouldn't give scumbags. That's That's
what I was saying basically earlier.
You know, that's the only thing it can
be. We only we only get limited time on
Earth. You understand? We only get a
limited time on Earth.
>> Yeah. I said I wasn't, bro. Oh, yeah.
And I've got a better bed as well. I
just explained to you that me and um
Virgin Boy, I I I actually spoke facts
like about how I've got a better life
than him in every way. And I'm also
better looking than him and everyone
knows that as well. So, I mean, go I
said I wasn't, but I'm bored today. Yes sir.
So we can go out and spend we ate skin
night and certain people you understand
we don't have to come here show our housing benefit
you know we don't have to do that [ __ ] mate
I have to get I have to get back into a
clean bed every time I go out I like to
get back into a clean bed but yeah you
got better like and it doesn't really matter
you got more money than him as well 2k
whatever 2k better better life, you
know, in every way. In every way, shape or form
[ __ ] start raining today,
no continue, mate, cuz I just want to go
out for you today. I'm still meeting
that woman next week, but
I had one that said we're supposed to
meet today and then they block me. What
the [ __ ] But the cycle don't continue.
I've just got nothing better to do.
I like to go out and meet new people.
Why has she done that? [Music]
What the [ __ ] is that, bro?
Well, I won't be. Maybe I'll go out
Saturday. I don't know.
I don't think I will. One second.
I'm trying to work this bastard machine.
That's the risk we taking it. No, that's
the risk we take.
And no. Why? Why did you say that's
going to happen? It's going to be
different today. Remember, your past
don't dictate your future.
I'm going to do a sober approach today
for my friend. He wanted to see some
good n ridiculous.
That's not going to happen.
That's That's not going to happen. God,
your past don't dictate your future.
No, Thursdays are better. You meet
better people. You make better friends.
I met them Brummy lads on Thursday.
Why are you being negative, Joe? Your
past don't dictate your past don't
dictate your future, you silly goose.
So, being a silly goose,
you're going to go out today and it's
going to be completely different. Even
though nothing's changed in 3 years,
it's going to be completely different
when you when when you go out again.
Why wouldn't it be? And I mean, yeah,
it's been happening for 3 years, the
same old, but today is going to be different.
Stop being a silly goose. Remember, the
past don't dictate your future. Stop being negative.
Oh, right. So, it's realistic when you
say it, but then when I say it, it's
negative. You really are a silly goose.
I was in bed alone yesterday and I was
thinking about that USA Izzy Joe.
Oh, I was just thinking the whole time
of you know what and stuff. Oh, it was sexy, bro.
I was having a little play. I'm not
going to lie. I was having a little play.
I was having a little play. Not going to
lie. No, not really, bro. Not I don't I
don't have to, bro. But seriously, I did.
I actually did right here. Nah,
I didn't masturbate. I just touched it a little bit.
Thinking of her boobs, you know, you know. Yeah.
Oh, washing machine.
The washing machine's on, John.
Yeah. The washing machine's on, John.
Nah, not me. I think Virgin Boy does
that. He can't get USA out of his head.
It's all he goes on about.
Poor Sarah. E.
She must get a good [ __ ] Iden.
She must get a good [ __ ] Sarah.
I actually feel sorry for her.
Just give, if you're watching this, Sarah, listen.
Yeah. Give the kid some sex. He's going
on 31. He's never had it. Please, can
you can you take his virginity?
No, you're not seeing the washing
machine, matey. You can get your own
washing machine. But yeah, please can
you give this virgin boy some sex,
please? cuz he he he's dying of it. He's
Yeah. You know, I'll be I'll be
completely honest with you here. Yeah.
This Sarah, I wouldn't even approach
even if I was pissed out of my head. I
don't go for
I don't go for special needs. You know,
you've seen a lot of people that I
approach, but I don't go for special
needs. So, I wouldn't even approach even
if I was out my [ __ ] face drunk. But
hey, give give that give that kid some sex.
Give some kid give that kid some sex, mate.
I got I got one when I was [ __ ] 17.
Me I used to I used to tell the stories
that the virgin didn't believe it.
Ah, she doesn't suck no mate. They've
never been in.
And and think of it, bro. What What time
would they have to be intimate when
they're on YouTube? Maybe they stalking you.
That's another thing.
Also, their YouTube activity proves also
that they don't have it because they
wouldn't have time to be on YouTube
stalking you every day. That's another
thing. How have they got more time on
their hands than someone that's not even
in a relationship?
So, yeah, he doesn't nothing. He's still
a virgin. Probably the most that they
probably had is they probably kissed
each other on the cheek. Maybe maybe by
doing a hand job, but that's it. They've
never done no sex. No sexual activities.
Not at all, mate.
So, yeah, I need to go out there and
send it. I might get a Weather Spoons
burger. I like them Weather Spoons
burgers, you know. They're quite tasty.
They're quite hasty, aren't they? Sippy.
They're quite tasty, aren't they?
How many numbers? How many numbers we
predicting today? Anyways, [ __ ]
How many numbers? Ew,
to be honest.
How many numbers? Yeah, you betcha.
I don't understand. These people sit
there and say that they [ __ ] that
they that they what's the word? They
[ __ ] um that they spend £200 on a
night out. That is bollocks, mate. You
know, every single time I've gone on a
night out, I'm spending about 80 to about 120.
And 120 I mean like really getting on
it. I don't know where £200 comes from,
but I don't think you could actually
tolerate that amount of alcohol. I mean,
I done it once, but I was going to a
really expensive place.
No, don't be so negative, Joe.
Stop being so negative. Your past don't
dictate your future.
>> Don't be ridiculous, man.
>> There you go.
I'm having a piggy burger today.
I'm going to send them sober as well. Watch.
Send one to my friend as well. Yeah.
Oh, the truth hurts. Nah, you're just
negative. Joe's being negative. Can you
tell Joe to stop being negative, please?
You're going to go out today. You're not
going to hear I've got a boyfriend.
You're going to get some nos and you're
going to get a lot of yeses, and people
are going to want to meet you. Stop
being so negative.
He's so negative, Greasy. You know,
even though this has been happening for
3 years and we've gone through a lot of
money and we ain't met anyone. You're
just being negative. Oh, my Xbox um
subscription come out today. Grezy. £14.99.
Yep. But if I don't pay it, I can't play Franklin.
So I had to pay it.
>> Yes. The passing it come out a lot
quicker. Actually I do have two
outgoings. I've got like 3040 outgoing every month. Yeah. Come on.
I'm going to have loads of baby
goodnesses. You betcha.
You bet your beta. Oh, [ __ ]
Well, I need to wait for this wash to
[ __ ] finish. Going to take a couple
of hours. Grezy
straight in your pocket. Is that cute? Please again [ __ ] ass
otherwise we'll be screwing McGome trust me
Yeah. No, that's all.
And why did you say to that red star
that, "Oh, you don't know what I'm
doing." Bro, you can't troll me. You're
not intelligent enough to troll me.
You said, "Oh, you can't clock on what
I'm doing trying to suggest that." You
don't troll me, bro. You don't troll me
in the slightest. No,
you don't troll me, Nate.
You don't mean mate. You don't mean
Not me, mate.
I've got two. I've got eight
on that [ __ ] Wednesday on the
Thursday and Saturday. Quite a lot for
two days, isn't it?
Yeah. But I know you. He was He's a
[ __ ] idiot. Yeah. He was trying to
call you sad that he's the one that sat
on YouTube every single day stalking. A
[ __ ] little weirdo. Yeah.
Yeah. I saw that little. It made me
laugh because everything that he wrote
just applies to himself. He's balding.
He's the ma. He's got a receiving chin.
He can't grow a beard. Like he's
literally just writing about himself. I
actually do feel bad about these people
putting themselves down every day. It
might not be good for their mental
health yet. They sit online every day
putting themselves down like they do.
They literally sit online and put
themselves down. It's bad. I feel bad for them
all. Bro, everybody on this community
will literally agree that I'm a million
times better looking than you. So why
you keep putting yourself down is just
beyond me. Look who you are with. Look
who I have and look who I have been
with. Look at the women that I have been
with and look at who you are with. That
tells you all you need to know.
I didn't even notice to be honest. He's
such a [ __ ] virgin. He needs to get
laid. Honestly, he needs to get laid,
bro. People like that just need to get
laid honestly. Yeah.
Such a virgin. Imagine that. Yeah, bro.
Imagine calling the police on someone
trying to [ __ ] them over with the
police. Yeah. And then in the end it
doesn't work and then you coming on
YouTube trying to get in someone's hang
out and you're telling me that's not obsession.
You're telling me that is not obsession
and jealousy. Like imagine that you call
the police. Then you call the police on
someone and then you get bored like a
month later and then you're still
harassing them. That is madness, bro.
That is obsession. That That right there
Really and truly obsession.
That is really and truly obsession, bro.
To the maximum.
Or should I go to Liverpool Street
today? Nah, I might go Liverpool Street on Saturday.
Actually, I might go Liverpool Street on Saturday. Maybe. Yeah.
[ __ ] for ages.
I might get like a nice old tie curry on
Saturday or something. I ain't been
[ __ ] ages, man. Well, on a well on a
night out there. Yeah.
But anyway, hopefully this person meets
me next week and
yeah, be in a relationship soon.
Yeah, he's a [ __ ] What do you
expect? He's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
He's a [ __ ] He's a [ __ ] bro.
What do you expect?
When was the last time he was in Manchester, Joe?
When was the last time you was in Manchester?
Remember the last time you was in Manchester?
Oh, [ __ ] me, bro.
No, but seriously, how much do you think
I'll spend today?
Honestly, I think about 80 to 100.
Yeah, I've been to Manchester for a very long time.
During that time, right where these
people on Reddit kept annoying me,
saying, "Oh, you got to keep trying. You
got to keep trying. You got to keep
trying." They're like, "Keep trying,
keep trying, keep trying, keep trying, keep trying."
They like, "Keep trying, keep trying,
keep trying." I like, "Fuck this."
literally went to Manchester and went
out spent it like just before Mother's
Day and I got nothing.
I'm sure you keep [ __ ] trying. Yeah.
Yeah. It's obvious that you live near Newcastle.
I would say that you live in Carle
on it. I would say that you must be you
must live somewhere like near Newcastle
because property hours from Manchester
and you're saying you're up north.
You're not Scotland. So you must be you
must be Jordy Land.
That's the that's the only thing it can land.
It's got to be Jordy Land. It's got to
Yeah, you must be Jordy land.
That's the only thing it can be is Jordi land.
I can't believe this person, this other
person gave me their number, said they
were going to meet me
and then they didn't meet. They
literally arranged to meet and then they didn't meet.
They literally arranged to meet and then
they didn't meet. That doesn't even make
sense. But does that make sense?
They actually gave me their number
outside of rave. We was we they agreed to meet.
Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ]
I'm trying to think what to wear today, bro.
I might wear my little polo shirt.
I'm not sure actually what I'm wearing
today. I might wear my little boss polo
t-shirt with my little cap. I'm not sure.
I've got lots of clothes to pick from. Um
um I'm not sure.
I've got a long sleeve Ralph Lauren H.
I'm not sure now what to wear today, you know.
Maybe the polo with the with the cap. I
think that's a good that's a good little look. Yeah.
Got my little cap.
I have to wear my little cap nowadays.
Anyone would think that I'm insecure I
wear this cap. I just like the caps now, man.
Yeah. Oh, rest be assured, bro. None of
these people have made me insecure about
my [ __ ] hair or anything. These
little virgin will never make me
insecure. D. No lie. They got no life.
But you chill.
Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, I got this boss polo. What do I wear today?
I can wear these
with ripped jeans
and a cap
with my little new trainers.
What do you think? What do you think, Joe?
No, I don't. The caps ain't come yet.
I was thinking maybe this with the
ripped jeans, but then the kind of the
collar kind of needs ironing.
Um, after this wash is finished.
No, I think I'm just going to wear the B
t-shirt with shorts. These
virgins will be sat on YouTube today.
What? You got no life. But the YouTube
Yeah, they ain't come today, bro. They
haven't come yet. They might come, but I
don't think so. Maybe tomorrow.
Maybe just wear shorts. I think I'm just
going to wear shorts. Shorts, long
sleeve t-shirt, and a cap. My little
happy cap. I call him my little happy
cap. I got it from when I was doing the
Uber. It blocked the sun out my face. It
doesn't matter anyways. You got you had
a haircut. You're wearing fresh clothes. Um,
yeah. I like that boss t-shirt as well.
Rock it. Oh, man. Yep.
These shorts, I got them from Amazon. £10.
that with a little cap and the little trainers boozy
going to be finding a little candidate
today or trying to be finding trying to
find a little candidate for baby Peter.
Can we have an estimate on how much I'm
actually going to spend today?
No. Like seriously,
I'm I'm thinking about 100. I'm
reckoning about 100. I don't think
you're spending more than 100.
You know what is so good, man? When you
don't the less you spend, it's actually
the better because I don't know. I think
when you spend loads and loads of money,
it sort of takes the fun out of everything.
Unless you go abroad, then obviously you
do spend loads of money, but I mean like
here it just makes it a lot more better
when you've spent. I don't really like
to spend more than 7080
really, but I don't really spend more
than 70 and 80. 7080. What do you think, Greezy?
>> No, not really, bro.
150 is too much
rip bank account in it.
But again, we're not some skin little virgin.
But we can take we can take the hits, mate.
Still waiting one day. See if somebody
shows me this 10 grand. But I won't be
banking on it, bro.
I'm still waiting for, like I said,
somebody to show me this 10 grand, but I
don't think it's ever happening.
But they expect me to keep [ __ ] participating.
They expect me to keep participating in
these silly little games.
that they've already lost. It's crazy.
Yeah, I think that's about right. I'd
say about 60 on drinks. Well, like I
said, I stick to beer nowadays, but
I stick to beer nowadays cuz of the
hangovers and [ __ ]
Yeah, man. You want to see my little costume?
I'll show you my little costume if you want.
Yeah, I'll show you my costume. I got
this, this, the shorts, and the hat. The
sun kind of [ __ ] the color up, which
is why I ordered new ones.
I got these little shorts. They look
sick. It's still quite humid out there,
isn't it? And you can get in places with
them shorts as well cuz they're not like
that's your bottom shorts.
They don't just do them on the street. Simple. So
I think it's wrong how they they tell
you what you can and can't wear when
you're the one that's paying to get in.
You're paying to get into places
and you're also paying the drink prices
and they try to tell you that you can't
wear tracksuit bottoms. I think that's
just weird. I think that's just weird. Me,
>> bro. I don't know about you, but I think
that is [ __ ] up, bro.
Cuz you're paying their prices. You know
what I'm saying?
It smells like someone's just done a piny. poo.
Doesn't matter if it's a private own
place, bro. No one's staying there. It's
not. We pay their prices. We should be
able to wear what we want.
When they try to tell me you can't wear
That's why I just stick to these pubs
you see cuz you can just wear what you want.
What the [ __ ] is wrong with wearing
tracksuit bonds, bro? It's not like it's
a private event or like a wedding. It's
a [ __ ] club. It's a [ __ ] bar.
I remember that [ __ ] the other day.
Yeah. Oh, you can't come in the club. I
was like, you know what? Yeah, I'm not
going to beg you. Fair enough. And I
think I was just disgusted because when
they say no, I'm not begging you. I'm
just going to go. Simple. I'm not going
to beg in my own country to get him somewhere.
Like that's not what I'm doing. Yeah.
And then he was like, and I just said,
"Oh, I think it's so disgusting."
And he said, "That's not the word." I
said, "Well, it is the word because it's
the word I'm using." That's why I said,
"Grievy, it is disgusting." And he was
trying to be a proper proper awkward
bastard. Yeah, proper awkward [ __ ] And
then he was like, then he was trying to
tell me how I'm being violent when I was
stood at the same place the whole time.
And I was like, "Bro, have you got
memory loss or something?" I was
literally stood at the same place the
whole time and he was trying to say that
oh you're being violent. I thought what
the [ __ ] He really is a [ __ ] idiot
and is he
violent? What? By standing there and
arguing with you when I'm nowhere near
you. Yeah, bro. I'm really violent.
What's up, please? Yeah,
but it doesn't matter bro anyways cuz
you know that's like I said that's why I
just stick to these pubs now. Really? I
try to stick to pubs now because of this
reason because of this problem. Um so
hopefully we can get into some club
today hopefully. But
if not then well that's it.
It's not coming from here.
It's not coming from here. They be
It's not coming from here, Zippy. What
do you think about that, Joe? It's not
coming from here, Zippy. A bless.
But yeah, anyways, I was thinking about
USA Melons yesterday when I was trying
to sleep at like to 1:00 in the morning.
like 1 in the morning. It's a shame she
doesn't have a better face.
I was actually kind of thinking of the
story before I went to sleep. It's just
so mad how that come about. Breezy,
do you remember the whole family and
[ __ ] Oh, mate. Do you remember the
whole family and [ __ ] I don't actually know
to be honest.
I just know they were I just know they
were humongous. BBC
you in your little Calvin Klein bra
travel around traveling around giving
your body for stakes. Oh, bless you.
Isn't that right, Grezy? Oh, bless you.
Bless you in life then.
But yeah, they were I don't [ __ ] know
how big they were. I was just squeezing
them the whole time. I'm not sure.
Bigger than [ __ ] Sarah's.
Let me ask you this. Right. Who who
who was the virgin with? Who was the
virgin with before Sarah? Does anyone know?
And there were any there were very very
very very short short relationships.
Short. I don't know. You might not have
been on it, but do you remember who the
virgin was with? a fat, ugly, single
mom, a lesbian looking. I have literally
had way better women than he has, but
I'm the manta. Whoopsie. If King was
here, I'd ask him to explain. I' I'd
explain the logic.
Uh, so yeah. And maybe not some of you
didn't remember, but yeah, he was always with [ __ ]
just ugly things. Ugly things. and he'd
be on like a weak relationship and not
get any sex and then they'd leave him.
Trust me, bro. Yeah, I Oh, [ __ ] I can
actually show you one of these one of
these exes actually. They're all fat,
ugly, and disabled.
Oh, bro. Actually, they are. You know,
go and search Ashton Frost.
Yeah, bro. Ashton Ashton Frost her name is.
So, yeah. Go look her up, bro. Fat and disabled.
That's her name, bro.
But I'm the M. I need some piggies, bro.
But I'll just wait and just have some
some food at the pub. Yeah.
Leave me alone. Leave me alone. Let's do
So, I wonder what this person's going to
do when they meet me. What it's going to
be like, Joe. What do you think it's
going to be like when this person meets me, boss?
Not going to lie to you. I've got my
todd out right now to be honest. Just
about to hit the bath.
I've kind of got my toodger out today to
be honest. Grezy,
for the whole nation to see.
The whole nation, Grezy.
The whole [ __ ] nation.
The whole nation.
Oh, best shot. Oh, [ __ ] You know what
that mean? Squeezy. The whole nation. Yeah.
Yeah. Whole nation, matey.
Oh, I got my little cat. To be fair, I
do fancy some piggies, bro.
But obviously, we need to do these approaches first.
But USA, would you agree Greavvesy? USA
is he had some nice melons.
Would you agree Greavvesy? Yeah,
Grezy like them.
Grezy wants to sleep with her.
Don't you, Grezy? You want to sleep with her? Right.
The wash is still going.
Yep. One sec. I'm trying to think of something here. Um
Right, I need to jump in this shower.
So, um, be back in a bit. Anyways, tactic hunts. Right.