Get up outside number still there
one bro [ __ ] one
my battery life is definitely gone as fine
on this phone. I'm telling you,
the battery is going on this phone,
mate. This phone has almost had it. I'm telling you, bro.
This guy, this guy trying to meet me
there cuz he knows I'm out here
approaching. He can get [ __ ]
literally, mate. Listen, you can [ __ ] right off.
I recorded approaches. I recorded too.
Yeah, I recorded too. I recorded two. [ __ ] off.
I recorded too fast and then I sent it
to people's Instagram. They were trying
to get it but
try to wipe his [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Should be
as [ __ ] bro.
Three, [ __ ] Three. We're
getting six though. 100. We're
definitely getting six. 100%. I got two
of them, but we're getting six 100%. I a
[ __ ] [ __ ] I didn't even know that.
[ __ ] [ __ ] We're getting
m We're getting sick.
We're getting six [ __ ] numbers. We've
already got three. We got three by like 400 p.m.
>> Yeah, it's banging here, bro. Banging.
Look at that one over there in the
white. I can't live
over there in a minute. Give it a while.
What do you got numbers?
[ __ ] off there. Yeah. Yeah. >> Master
So, it should be here tomorrow.
Now, I've already said it. I got three
numbers. I got three numbers by 400 p.m.
by 400 p.m. I already got four. I
already got three numbers.
I just don't about four in these places,
bro. My boyfriend.
I had it down for a bit.
I've been sending it all night, mate. I
got three numbers in like 2 hours. I got
three numbers like 2 hours. I just got
one outside as well.
[ __ ] boyfriend. [ __ ] every time.
Every [ __ ] time. Boyfriend. I [ __ ] had enough.
Seriously, I've had enough of it, mate.
I've already got three numbers. I got I
got three approach to sober videos to
come and I got one number and I got the
others of it. It's not free. I pray I'm
[ __ ] going. I'm [ __ ] going over there.
Yeah, I'm going.
It's got to be the same [ __ ] [ __ ]
again, isn't it?
Too many stuck up [ __ ] in this
country, Dad. Too many [ __ ] up [ __ ]
in this country, Dad. Too many stuck up [ __ ] countries.
I'm out three. Three, bro.
>> I need to go in a minute, guys. I need
to go over there, bro.
Need to get distracted by the fish tank.
I got three up so far. I got three
numbers. One of them was sober. I got
three numbers. I got one number sober
and the other two were slightly tipped.
Got a little yank, but I've been sending it hard.
I need to go in a minute. I need to chat
about [ __ ] white. I got three
numbers. Three numbers so far.
And all by myself.
We're getting sick.
They never reply, bro. They will never
reply. They're all the same, bro. But I
got Danish week anyways, bro.
>> Oh, [ __ ] You're getting licky, bro.
Lick your ass. I'm getting licky, bro.
Boom. I'm going to wake up some hangover.
>> What do you want to do? Give it a whirl. I would
[ __ ] it. Give it a while,
mate. It's [ __ ] shitty England.
I'm going to go. I've already got three
numbers. I've already got three numbers, mate.
I'm just chilling, bro. [Music]
I got some approaching video. [Music]
That's I've only got three numbers in
like space 2 hours earlier. I've been up
for like 7 hours though
in the space of 7 hours. Yeah,
I've got three numbers. One of them was
sober as well.
I'm dead. I'm dead, bro. I need to find
a bit though because I need to do some more approaches.
All right, somebody else.
I got the rum.
The rum rum rum ramic calls bro. [Laughter]
>> Mix it with the rub. Mix it with the high.
I recorded three approaches. I recorded
I recorded them. I put them on YouTube. Anyway,
don't chat this. I'm going to talk to
this white woman here. Wait, I'm going.
I'm going. Said, "Fuck it off. I'm going
out here, bro.