Get perfect.
Where's that pocket? back
for ages, bro. [ __ ]
Yeah, my bed for ages, bro. My mom Big long day.
There's a sit.
There's a sitcom CD.
Zippy zippy loop. No, [Music]
it's not too [ __ ] about you ain't got a
word to say just England. What you
getting mad about, bro? Mad.
I don't get mad. I don't get mad about this [ __ ] No. Oh man.
Yeah, my friend boss bangers, bro.
What was that? [ __ ] Oh [ __ ]
My friend, bro, I just text me.
I'm trying to make Bro, What?
Hey, That drunk Mississippi go simple. I believe the better
to be honest.
Are you going than anything. [ __ ] me. Oh [ __ ] I'm
going to be sleeping cuz I'm
literally dropped some as well which I
probably shouldn't have done But
obviously if I go out Saturday again,
I'll be refreshed.
If it was a fly day, I wouldn't have
shoot on the ground.
But seriously, we do need to give up the
country for real.
went to Emily, you know, younger.
Where the [ __ ] is where is Grey?
Where is horrible [ __ ] Love Gy.
One second. [ __ ] One second.
Stop talking about yourself.
You're not talking about yourself on my channel. Little self.
No self-effective on my channel.
Oh [ __ ] Is that
no self- afflecting skimp people on my channel matey?
Oh [ __ ] One second. Let me go.
Sorry about that, bro.
Yeah, no self-reflection on my channel.
Don't talk about yourself in another
channel. You weirdos. [ __ ] self-reflecting.
So, I went toilet. I'm back.
Are you sitting there working again?
Yeah, you're talking about yourself,
man. Quit talking about yourself like
that on my channel.
[ __ ] five numbers.
Stop talking about yourself.
Stop wasting your life talking about
yourself. It's not good for your mental
health. Stop reacting to people every
day on YouTube. Um um [ __ ]
That was leg, bro.
You're calling yourself a mon. It's not nice. Yeah, there
on the train, but it sort of [ __ ] it up. [Music]
Man, I'm bad. I don't know today on the [ __ ] train, bro.
[ __ ] off you little virgin. Stop
reacting to me every day.
You [ __ ] virgin.
Yeah, I don't want on a train completely
sober, bro. That deserves membership,
bro. I was actually recorded to Yeah.
with me, bro. Unbelievable.
So jealous and obsessed. I've never
known anything like it in my whole life.
had some Chinese pork road.
I want to play some fat game, I reckon.
touching your body. Your fire is [ __ ]
Jeez, [ __ ] on this bro. I am a mad mad bastard. Oh, please. Sorry. Hold on.
Right. He's got my clock.
Go self-reflect on another channel.
I'll be leaving YouTube tune anyways, mate. Oh,
get that fan in my [ __ ] face. Oh.
Oh, too weird. Too many obsessed
[ __ ] creepy people.
Oh my god. [ __ ] Franklin. Ranking.
To be honest, I thought I was going to
get about three numbers today, not five.
And we'll do Saturday as well, maybe. Depends. Um
yeah, I'm a crazy bastard and I really
we need to stop soon, bro, cuz we need
to start [ __ ]
doing [ __ ] bro. What the [ __ ]
I learned some I don't know approach on
the train sober today. I'm [ __ ] mental, bro.
I'm [ __ ] That's why I should be
getting a [ __ ] monthly [ __ ] subscription payment.
Yeah, I met that Indonesian guy. I said
to him, "You're a big cunt." I bought
him a [ __ ] baby Guinness and a
Guinness and he still wouldn't do it.
He's too scared, bro.
He is too scared.
You know what, bro? Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro.
This guy is too scared.
I got some juicy numbers.
I think if you do Saturday, we'll get 12
between two days.
He's going to go fine now. Oh, told you.
You should have told that woman to mind
her own [ __ ] business.
I would have told her to mind her own [ __ ] business.
So obviously she's got a black
boyfriend, right? So she has a black
boyfriend. Yeah. So what are you doing?
You're talking to other people, which is
fair. Mind your own [ __ ] business. Is
it any of your business? Mind your own [ __ ] business.
Lucky they didn't [ __ ] call me over.
I would have told him.
Mad, bro. He should have told him to
mind their own [ __ ] business. The [ __ ] bro?
I would have done mate. [ __ ] you.
You know what? I've even seen other
people lowering their standards now.
Like even like you even see black guys
nowadays. Yeah. And they're not pulling
what they used to pull, bro.
They're not [ __ ] pulling what they
used to be able to pull,
just like certain other good-looking
guys. The country's [ __ ] mate. It's
gone to the [ __ ] The country has gone
to the [ __ ] shambles, mate.
Go, go, go. No. No.
There we go. Oh, Franklin,
how many things we got to you now, bro?
Thank you, bro.
Must have spent £100 today.
I spent more than
I was hoping to.
Let's put it that way. Oh,
it's all good.
Change gun. Come on.
It's just like that Ronald Pump said,
eh, you're better looking than them.
You've got more money than them. And it kills them.
You know, some things people say on YouTube, right?
It it it sticks with you. you know,
actually does stick with you.
Could be from 10 years ago, million
years ago. And it is actually, he's
actually right. Like, if you think of it
right. Oh, I like this white car, bro. I
am better looking than them. I have got
more money than them. It's the truth.
And it kills them. It is actually the
truth, you know. It really is.
That is honestly the truth. No true
words spoken, bro.
Get off YouTube with your life. It's the truth, man.
You're better looking than them. You got
a better life than them. And you got
more money than them. It's true, don't
it? Really, if you think about it,
that is actually the truth, man.
That's why that [ __ ] Jamie Thompson
keeps stalking me every day.
He's a [ __ ] fat loser.
You was emailing me earlier. Loser.
Loser. Loser. Loser. Oh, I made it perfect.
Oh yeah. He doesn't want to approach
because they say they've got boyfriends.
Like, bro, think of me. I've been all
over the country. They [ __ ] say it. I
still do it.
I still [ __ ] do it. You know
what the [ __ ] man?
I'm trying to think if there was ever a
Weather Spoons in Wales. I don't think there was.
Not what I can think of.
I can't I can't think of it man. [ __ ] Never mind.
Can't believe that number I got today. over.
[ __ ] legend, bro.
I'm actually a legend, man. Oh, [ __ ] good.
That was funny thing. Trying to make
your bed drunk. All
right, I'm gone, bro.
Peace out, [ __ ]