Get
out. [ __ ] sea, bro. What the [ __ ] always
happens. How are we today? Me thinks me thinks.
Oh, passport done. Done it this morning.
So, I got a passport now. Was actually
going to go Blackpool before the
passport. But yeah, [ __ ] it, bro.
It No, I'm not texting any of them yet.
I'm going to text them at 11 because
11's my lucky
number. Yeah, yesterday was fun, bro. Oh
my god. I had 620 in one like one of my
accounts. Yeah. By the time I drunk, got
a haircut, ate and like 150. I [ __ ]
went through 500
quid just like that, bro. What the
[ __ ] Oh, my money's no object.
E, it was a blast though, man. And
that's me done for the month cuz I had
to do the pass. I know. I filled the
passport. I filled the passport out when I come
back. Yep, she was out, bro. She was
out. I know you. I said, if I was
ignoring you, why would I come over? But
yeah, it was fun, bro. It was fun. That
was one last hurrah from for the month
because I I need to I had to do my
passport and that. So, that's all done.
Done that this morning. Done some
chores, done my football bets, and I'm
back in the old
nestic ready to text these little numbers. A
yeah, can't beat the smell of bleach in
it. It was good, bro. But I went through
500 quid. Obviously, it's not a problem for
me, Fred. It'll be a problem for Sean
cuz he's on a grand a month. A grand a
month just won't cut it. Like, think
about it, bro. That's actually madness.
I got my hair done. I got my hair done,
bro. Check this out. I got my hair
done. Um, I got my [ __ ] hair done, bro. Passport.
Drinking. No, they didn't know each
other. They just met
yesterday. He's my
friend. She didn't know who he is. [ __ ] 500
quid. [ __ ] a grind a month. You to
grind them up. Grind them up. Just don't
cut it. Gone in a day, bro. 500 [ __ ]
quid. That's basically the better part
of £500. Got on passport, drinking,
haircut. [ __ ] it,
lad. But I got four numbers. I'll text them soon.
Yeah. You've applied to renew your
passport. Oh, yeah. I had to renew that
passport. He didn't get [ __ ] No.
I told him, "Hold my hand and we'll go
over and chat them [ __ ] up." I said,
"Once he holds the hand, bro. Once he
holds the hand, we're going. Once you
hold on to my hand, we're going." Yeah,
that's what I said to him. Hold the
hand. Hold the hand, mate. Hold the [ __ ]
hand. No, he didn't. I did. I got four.
Well, I got three. I got four all in
all. Plus the bartender, but three like Yeah.
It was a blast, man. It was a blast.
That burger almost killed me, lad. Nah,
that little [ __ ] rat face. Little
rodent. Where's his [ __ ]
money? I was saying yesterday, I want to
see your money, rat face. I want to see
the signs of money. I got my money out.
Where's yours, you little rat? You
[ __ ] rat face
bastard. You little autistic rodent
looking [ __ ] Where's your [ __ ]
money? I want to see some of your money.
But I guess you can't when you're on a
grand a month and you probably spent
your housing benefit paying
housing. A grand a month just won't
do. Nah. See, look how No, I sent it to
the passport office. I've already sent it
off. It was a headache, bro.
the post office
earlier and to send it to the passport
office and then they're going to send me
a new one renewed. Yeah. So, what I done
is I got my haircut yesterday. I done my
I went to the post office to take
pictures and then I filled it in online
when I come back from drinking. So, I
took the pictures before drinking so I
wasn't completely [ __ ] So, they gave
me a code and yeah, it's crazy, bro. and
all that admin [ __ ] They say it's £88,
but you still got to pay nine pound for
the delivery, which to be fair is cheap,
man. Like£10. It works out less than£10
a year for your passport. That's [ __ ]
cheap. Rail cards 30 quid and you can't
leave the country with a rail card. To
be fair, it is cheap. £100 for 10 years.
Come on, bro. I paid 30 a month for my
rail card, £30 a year for my rail
card. I saved a lot of money, though.
That rail card's definitely worth it. You
know, I used to travel everywhere, so it was good,
bro. It was fun, bro. It was
fun. Sean can't do that on a grand a
month, though, can he,
Fred? I know. I saw him when I was 17.
Sh's never left the country. He can't
afford it. He he he can't afford it. I
don't know how he could talk about my
nose when he literally looks like a rat.
So, we've already established I'm better
looking than you. We've already
established I've got more money than you
because when I showed money yesterday,
you all ran away again. I had to get
money out for Timmy and he didn't show
me nothing. I showed him over well over
a,000 pound and they still couldn't show
me nothing. This is why I don't show
these people anything anymore because
they never show you nothing. They all run
away. What it is with these people is
they want to see money because these
people don't have money. You know what
I'm saying? They don't know what money
looks like because they don't have it.
And because they've got autism, that's
why they always want people to show
their money. I can't even believe I went
to the [ __ ] ATM and just took money out like
that, you know? But I did. Yeah.
But it was annoying yesterday, bro. I
heard about like um loads of makebelieve
boyfriends. It is annoying, bro. I'm not
going to lie to you. Even though I went
out to have fun and that Yeah. And I can
afford to do and I got numbers. It It
does get annoying, bro. I'm not going to
lie to you, bro. Cuz I got sick haircut
yesterday. I was looking sick. Like
smelling nice, stony. It makes It just I
feel like every time obviously I had
fun, bro. It was
fun. Feels like every single time you go
out, not that I really care about
anymore, but it's like it's like you you
feel even more
hopeless cuz and we we said it, bro.
I've done some on the street. I done
some [ __ ] everywhere really. And it's
like you feel more and more hopeless cuz
it's like, well, hold on. If a decent
looking person that's smelling good,
that's got money can't get nothing, who
can get something? No, I don't want to
comb my hair, bro. I'm good.
does. It wouldn't make a difference
anyways, mate. Listen, you could go out
smelling like [ __ ] It still wouldn't make a
difference. I remember I went out one
Thursday looking like [ __ ] [ __ ] with
trackuit bottoms and I got more. Oh, you're
um because she said that she's not going
to [ __ ] unless I convert to Muslim. Did
you not hear the
conversation? And I don't really like
her like that. I like her to help me get into places. But
yeah, you're not going to get with me,
bro. She's [ __ ] Musl She said if I
convert, I'm not converting to no
[ __ ] Muslim, bro. [ __ ] off, you
know. Yes, but then I'd have to convert
and I'm not doing it. No, bro. Who
cares? It's one person. We chatting up
other women, bro. [ __ ] her, man.
Oh, I done a I done an approach in the
Weather Spoons as well cuz I done an
approach in the Weather Spoons. Yeah,
even though we got numbers and it was
good and last Friday was good. It's just
it's annoying, bro. Here in the
Makebelie Boyfriends, it is it is
[ __ ] annoying, bro. And I didn't
really just go out for that. I actually
went out to have fun, but it is so
annoying. God, it's so annoying,
bro. But I was telling Antman about I
was like, "I hope you're looking forward
to coming back to this." Like it makes
me just want to go to Asia,
bro. Because it's sort of
like why? Like you shouldn't have to
disrespect yourself to get something in
this country. You might as well just go
to Asia. Like at this point, you might
as well just go to Asia. Why do you
think I'm not going out for a month? Why
do you think I'm saving money? What? Cuz
cuz I I have I can go out every week. I
can go out every day if I want. I'm just
not doing it. It's a waste of time and
money this country, bro. They're all
just the same [ __ ] you know? I
haven't even messaged these numbers yet,
but I know like kind of [ __ ] scared cuz
I won't be going out for a month. And to
be fair, the only reason I went out is
cuz I had to get a haircut for my
passport. And whilst I had my haircut, I
was like, "You might as well just go out
and send it cuz you got your haircut
anyways." But I got my passport sorted
now anyway. So, I won't be going out for
a month. We got some horror films to
look forward to as well.
So, I will be done for a month. We we
basically saw into March as well. So,
yeah, I'm done.
does get it does get boring, bro. It
does get really boring.
Sad though that Sean's 30 and he's never
been abroad. He's never even been to
Scotland. He hasn't even been to [ __ ] Scotland. [ __ ] hell. Yeah.
But it was fun, bro. It was
fun. No, it's not. Actually, as a game,
bro, I thought I felt like I was giving
birth cuz I can take Spice normally,
unlike a certain person. Not going to
mention any names. So, I thought, "Fuck
it. I'm up for a challenge." But when it
when I had to sign a leaf. Yeah. I was
like, "Okay, now I'm a bit scared cuz
what if I end up in hospital?" It's like
bungee jumping. You got to sign your
life away, bro. You know what I'm
saying? Um, it was good though.
Yeah, it's not going to give me the
[ __ ] I'm going to go for a vinoo today, reckon.
Yeah, I come home
showered. I found a new barber shop now as
well. She does hair. Very good. [Music]
suck. I really like you,
mama. Okay. So, you want to know um the football bench?
Yeah. So, and all of the women were
different ages. Some were 18, some was
in their 30s, one was the same age as
me. So, we got kind of a few different
age ranges as well.
So I got both teams to score. Neither
team to win Fleetwood versus Knox
County. Both teams to score on either
team to win Harrington.
Aington I don't even have to pronounce
that. And 20 returns 153. Then I two
pound change and I put two pound on three
draws. On three draws. Oh yeah. Oh, they
put a note for the draws. So I got I got
three draws two pound return
67 worth a while wouldn't it? I would.
Yeah I would. So all in all 22 on the football
done. Imagine they both come in eh. That
would be a lovely
site. The reason I picked Aington this
time and um Fleetwood is because there's
always goals in them games. I'm sort of
studying it a bit now, you
know, trying to anyways. Yeah, that's that's
haircut. Yeah, the slower the
better. That's what I say. The slower the
better. The slower the better. What
about you, Fred? Can you do a grand a
month like Sean's on? Mate, I can't do a
grand a month, Sean, because who's going
to pay for the little
stonies? Who's going to pay for the
little stonies? If I was on a grand a
month, like Sh, who's going to pay for
the little stonies? Who's going to pay
for the little
stonies? Ah, come on now.
Who's going to faith for the little?
He's on a on a grand pitt
p. We spent half a [ __ ] grand
yesterday. No, you can live off a grand
a month. It would just be a [ __ ] life.
It like you could have like a home gym
and work out and but one going out and
drinking it's over. So
yeah, look at me. Yesterday I spent 500 [ __ ]
quid [ __ ] just on passports and [ __ ] I
mean yeah I
mean it'd be [ __ ] You could only save.
And I mean, Greavves was on 750. I
remember being on 750 when I was [ __ ]
22 a month. It's not enough money,
bro. When I used to meet Izzy and that
£750, I always would run out of money.
Always would run out of money, bro. I
can't lie to you, bro. I always run out of
money. Like, it's not enough, bro. But a
thousand. I mean, yeah, you you just
adjust to it.
But it's no life for any young person,
is it? A grand a month. Grand a [ __ ]
Y a month. [ __ ] get that a week,
mate. I pretty much get that [ __ ]
week. So, what happened to my mama then, Fred?
What happened to my mama?
Fred. Huh? What happened to my
mama? Oh, West Ham's probably playing
tomorrow, ain't it? Go wherever Peter
Betty's little legs take him. Yeah, man.
Feel like the dating thing is getting
odd. No, I don't tell anyone about her,
bro. I don't like her. Right, let me
message these numbers now. This
Go black. How can I go to Blackpool when
I don't have a passport and I'm
nuts? How can I go to Blackpool when I
ain't got a passport and I'm nuts? Come
on, bro. Stop being
stupid. I'm not wasting any more money
in this country, lad.
has replied still.
Okay. Oh, she replied straight away.
Okay, so we've got one that's replied.
Well, we need to message the other ones
now. [ __ ] me. Okay, then. That's madness
still form right here. Hold on so I
don't [ __ ] this up.
I got another
number. I didn't gamble
again. Who's the other number I got? One
second, bro. I'm trying
to Oh, one's already typing. So that's two replies. Get
in. That's how many have we how
message? One second. One, [Music]
two. Oh, we have messaged all of them.
Yeah. I need to start going for people
that look more like me.
I need to go for people that actually
look like me,
bro. I feel like I've got more of a chance with
them. I actually feel like I've got more
of a chance with people that look like
me. Cuz people are attracted to their
own race. You know, someone that's white
and blue eyes just I don't look nothing like them,
though. Of course they're not all
Muslim. What? Why were they all viewers?
They're just They're all
different. Okay, I need to go anyways
cuz I'm going to type to these [Music]
people. Anyways, I'm gone. I'll be back later.