thinking of doing this today.
This little experiment
to see who can
Oh, [ __ ] Who can and can't live without your living. Yeah. Yeah, man.
As soon as the experiment Yeah. After today,
go on YouTube for one week and then go
back on YouTube and see who's been on
it. Then we'll see who the ones that go live.
Yeah. Know he's got a life and he don't
drink for me today.
Good old cinema. I'm going cinema. Oh [ __ ] That's
and that's how you know who ain't got a
life but your children in that week after today.
Yeah about YouTube
little fat [ __ ] that sat on there all day life.
No way. [ __ ] [ __ ] YouTube.
I got killed. Here we go.
The stars don't [ __ ] on this.
These people really really have really bad autism.
Really really bad autism.
You know what? I was But
just speaking to something about sh I
think it's the [ __ ] truth, you know,
like how long are these people in here
going to keep doing this for every day?
It's mad to think like their routine is
to come on here, go on YouTube, self
project every day, all day for years.
It's mad, is it? It's [ __ ]
And I don't Do you know what I do? I
don't even think
that they realize that they're actually
talking about themselves.
That's the weird thing.
That is That's the most [ __ ] up. I
don't even think they realize they're
talking about themselves.
Where the [ __ ] is that? It's weird.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] [ __ ] weird.
They've been on here for years doing
this. It's mad, is it?
They're just low lives.
They're just low lives on this community.
All they are.
How many years can you keep doing
something for? Huh?
Crash spamming wallet. What?
No life back to you. Yo,
I'm leaving this community soon. I'm
leaving this YouTube [ __ ]
I've had a long
I've had a long think, man.
Not sure, mate. You tell me.
I just had some lovely pork. What if I
cinema on a bit? Yeah.
Just playing some GTA.
Good old pictures.
Good old pictures, mate.
We should go to the pictures, LT.
But I'm actually coming off this [ __ ]
soon, bro. But I don't know how I got
back on this [ __ ] again.
I was off it for ages, bro. I got
[ __ ] learned in again.
These [ __ ] losers, bro.
These absolute losers. One sec.
One sec. I'm doing something.
Yep. She will always do that. Uh-huh. One second. Yeah, bro.
Yeah, she's always going to do that
with that um Arsenal mark. Sorry, I was showing someone.
Yeah, she's always going to do that. Yeah, man.
You out on the piss today, LT? I was out
on the piss [ __ ] last Thursday, last
Saturday, and the Thursday. So, I've
been out three times in like
a week, man. I need to calm down.
[ __ ] that. I'm just going to go sit
more. I can't be last drinking today, bro.
I'm scared, man. me matey
to be fair.
[ __ ] that up, bro.
If you do this yet, if you do this two
weeks, two days a week or every day,
you'll be skin like virgin boy.
You know what I mean?
How was benefit off? [ __ ] hell, bro. Right,
let's have a little look.
There's so many fantasists on here, man.
You remember when Bomb used to try and
say he spent two grand on a night out?
So many fantasy on here.
I'm leaving this place soon. For real.
I was off of it for weeks and weeks.
Bro, I don't need YouTube like J.
I don't need YouTube like [ __ ] LJ.
No, I don't remember. I've got memory loss.
No, I've got memory loss, man.
Go see the B a bit. Yeah. Cheaper than
[ __ ] going out [ __ ] drinking, is it? [ __ ]
No, I don't care about that keyboard
warrior and stop bringing it on my
channel. This is another thing. They
seem to like bring drama on your
channel. I don't give a [ __ ] I don't
care, bro. I don't care about none of them.
See, I get it as well. I get them, bro.
[ __ ] I I get these people [ __ ]
bring up [ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ] about
them, bro. They're never going to meet
me. They're never going to let me meet
them. So I don't give a [ __ ] about them, bro.
We was talking about this in it the
other day, LT, how they do this for year
in, year out, year in, year out. These
people [ __ ] autism. They're [ __ ] disabled, bro.
They are actually proper disabled.
That's probably where they get
the whole uh disabled thing from, cuz
they're disabled themselves.
probably getting himself mixed up again.
How they do this every day, bro? It's
mad. That's how you know they're [ __ ] disabled.
Obsessed every day.
It's mad, isn't it?
Let me see.
I hate this [ __ ] internet, man. I hate it.
Wow, look at that belly button. Jeez.
Look at that belly button.
I bet you tried getting in there
knick-knocks a few times though, didn't you, LT?
Bet you tried getting in there knick-knocks.
You can't lie to me, bro. You can't kill
a killer, son.
I bet you was trying to get in there knickknacks.
Don't lie, mate. I know you. You're a crafty [ __ ]
You're a crafty [ __ ] You are. Can't
fool me, mate. You're a crafty [ __ ]
You're a proper crafty [ __ ] You are.
So, Nicolo. Yeah. Did So, did LT try to
get into USA? Is these knickknocks?
What was What was happening there?
What was happen? What happened there?
Now, you tried to get into mad people's nickn
I don't trust you, mate.
about that, bro.
So why was So why was LT messaging USA?
Izzy, Nick, I know. Sorry, my [ __ ]
internet [ __ ] there, man. Why was he messaging her?
No, I'm not talking [ __ ] bro.
Down for the brown. I like that one.
Yeah, cuz I told you about some of her little exes
and obviously they were all off they
were all of color. So LT was like, you
know what, I'm going to see LT's not
dumb. You know, a lot of people think
he's dumb, but he picks his moment. He's
like, been with a lot of black men, you
know. I know. I can uh
I can um
I can I can I can I can sit my way in
here. You know what I mean? Yeah. I can
sit my way in here, mate. I've got a
good reference. I got a good reference point. Yeah.
You know, I see always sat there in the
background, aren't you? picking your moment,
you know, picking your moment. I don't
blame you though.
You was FaceTiming, bro.
Nah, you was you was FaceTiming it. Yeah,
you was facetiming it.
I would say you was you was
No, bro. You was you was you was
involved in all that, bro. You was very much involved.
And that was all from a cold approach,
Nicolo. Look at all of that [ __ ] I
caused. Yeah. From a cold approach.
I've got to be loved on here.
Got to be loved on here, bro. You know
what I'm saying? Yeah. I've got to be
loved on here.
Yeah. You should try and get some um
some nudes, mate. Yeah.
Yeah. He that LJ was trying to get into
that J. He's such a simp.
That L is such a simp. Cheers.
Such a simp, bro.
He actually is a s.
That's for sure, bro. Mhm.
He's on benefits, bro. He's skinn as [ __ ]
So, what if he buys the newest pair of
trainers? What are they like? What?
£300? 400? That don't mean nothing, bro.
I could go out right now and buy a
[ __ ] four, five, 600 pair of
trainers. Does that mean I'm rich? No.
You think about it, bro.
You ain't got nothing, bro.
You think you think on benefits you
can't Well, obviously not on 300 pound
month, but you think you was getting
six, seven bills a month and you can't
buy the latest pair of trainers. Of
course you could.
250, 350, 450. I could buy a new pair of
trainers right now if I wanted to. So nah,
I didn't say I was going to I didn't say
I was going to kill anyone. When When
did I ever say I was going to kill anyone?
I said I was going to go and see what a
[ __ ] is about face to face.
Oh, bless you then NLT. I swear I swear
haven't checked that plan. I didn't say
I was going to kill her actually. So,
get it right.
Aquarium. I swear haven't checked that
place out. I was thinking of going
Birmingham today just to piss up for the
London and that but I need to really
start saving now, bro. I don't want to
be skinn like Virgin boy.
Can't live be living these lives
anymore, mate. So, I'm just going to go cinema.
Yeah, I was just going to go Birmingham,
me just an all nighter.
I was just going to do an all nighter,
mate. [ __ ] in Birmingham.
[ __ ] cheapest ships now. I just
can't be [ __ ] mate. Go cinema. Yeah.
You all you to me, mate. All of you to me. Yeah.
Let's go. Cinema, eat some popcorn.
Chill, man. I went out three times this
week. Like, you know, in a week. Like on Thursday,
Saturday, and then on last Thursday.
[ __ ] that. I don't feel like he's a dude today, bro. Yeah,
bless you then. LT if it's your little
pal's birthday. Bless you.
Bless you in life.
Bless you in life. Then [ __ ]
down the highway.
All right. In the cinema, you don't have
that popcorn and that coke. It's lush, man.
Popcorn and coke.
When the cinema is [ __ ] lush,
I'm so tired from the drinking on
Thursday. I'm just going cinema today,
bro. Can't be bothered going out
drinking. [ __ ] that.
supposed to be meeting somewhere next
week anyway. So,
I'm saving up. I'm going to go on
holiday, I think. But I'm going to go on holiday.
UK's finished. I mean, Grey, if you want
me to go Birmingham, I'll go to
Birmingham today and do an all nighter,
but I'd have to run it by Grey first.
Is that okay with you, boss?
I'd have to run it by you first, boss.
Is it okay with you, boss?
No, I'm not going. Um, no.
Just been watching Resistance GB in
London and a woman was shouting, "Help,
help, help." Even though she came up to him.
Yeah, they are entitled in this country,
bro. They're [ __ ] in this country.
No, she'll be watching. LG I'm not
messaging her, bro. I'm not involved.
She She'll be watching.
Yeah, they are entitled. They're
[ __ ] in this country.
They're entitled [ __ ] in this country, bro.
Yeah, they're [ __ ] here, bro.
Why do you think Adman [ __ ] living in Thailand now?
You still get the odd good one. Maybe from like Ukraine or
maybe Russia or
I'll tell you a story, right? LT's here now.
LT LT is here. So I approached this person.
They they had a boyfriend. I didn't
realize that a boyfriend. It was some
black guy. You know this, but LG don't
know this. This is how [ __ ] up they
are. They all the same in London, bro.
So obviously she had a black boyfriend,
which is Oh, okay. I didn't know she had
a boyfriend. Then I'm going over
speaking to other people cuz I can do
what I want. It's a free country and I'm
single. What the [ __ ] I was drunk. And
she calls my friend over saying, "Oh,
he's talking." So I said, "Why have you
gone over to them?" Cuz I thought, "Why
has he gone over speaking to them for
what reason? I'm getting us some drinks
here." And apparently he was called
over. I was like, "Why are you calling
him over? Call me over, bro. I'll tell
you to mind your own [ __ ] business in
front of your [ __ ] boyfriend. I don't
care who the [ __ ] you're with. I have
told her to mind your own [ __ ]
business. You're with your guy drinking.
[ __ ] mind your own business. Go with
your own [ __ ] life.
But they know they couldn't say anything
to me, bro, because I would have just
told him straight. You know what I mean?
But welcome to England anyways, Grezy.
It's not going to get worse. It's not
going to get any better. It's just going
to get worse, bro. So, what is it? See,
I learned that. You see, I I learned
that with like my own like thoughts like
that. I don't even moan about it anymore
cuz it's just the same old same old
England. Nothing to moan about anymore.
And there's nothing to moan about
really. Just how it is. It will never
change. That's it.
Yeah, they do start [ __ ]
They do start [ __ ] here. They start
They start [ __ ] and then they can't
finish it. It's like what I was telling
you about when I was doing that delivery job.
Yeah. They do. They start it cuz they're
entitled and then then they can't finish
it. That's what they do here. Not about
any other city, but they do it here.
Uh, country's full of [ __ ]
What do you think would have happened
right that day when that kid was trying
to steal my bike? Right.
If I put my hands on him, what do you
think he would have done? What do you
think that kid would have done, bro?
He'd have been like, "Oh, I'm a child.
You're putting your hand on a child."
That's what he would have said, bro.
That's why I just I just got the
security to deal with him. I know it
seems a bit [ __ ] but yeah, he would
have been like, "Oh, I'm a child. I'm a child."
Yeah. Entitled [ __ ] in this country, bro.
He's playing some Franklin Grezy. I like
Franklin Franklin. He's such a He's such
a nice little character, isn't he?
I do like Franklin. Franklin.
But the thing is is that back in the
day, right, we wouldn't do that. We were
getting our We were getting our our
bikes stolen at his age.
10, 11. We were getting our bikes
stolen. Well, a lot of people was. Now
you got them trying to steal people's
bikes. It's mad.
They're just not brought up properly.
They're all [ __ ] in this country
cuz there's no discipline, bro.
That's why they're all [ __ ]
That's why, bro. That's why I don't even
go out Saturdays anymore. There's too many [ __ ]
That's why I just stick That's why I
normally just do Thursdays. Me, there's
too many [ __ ] on Saturdays.
Uncle Bad Touch has retired. Yeah, sadly.
What's your plans today, Greasy?
I'm just playing some Franklin passing time then.
cinema. Yeah. A new horror film come
out. I was like, "Ah, now I know what I
can do today instead of being sat bored.
Do you know what?
Hey, Grooves, I've got a question. Are
you still there?
Yeah, it's out next May.
I'll answer that quickly for you. So, I
said to Laney, right? How do people save
and not go out and drink? Um,
bro, these people are [ __ ] disabled,
bro. One second. And she's like, "Oh,
well, you you have to pick one or the
other." I said, "How are people that are
saving for like a car or holiday not get
tempted to go out?" And she said, "It's
because it's either one or the other
when you're saving in it. You either go
out or you save and do what you want to
do with the savings." True, it
have I done any approaches this weekend.
Are you [ __ ] disabled? I literally
told you that I went out, bro, there's
no point. These people are disabled.
There there's there's no point even even
answering. They're disabled, bro.
M I'm going to be indoors as well. I
bought a new [ __ ] TV. It was450.
Well, I sold the other one and then
bought another one cuz I was moving. So,
yeah. I'm not going to be in. I'm going
to I'm going to buy a PS5 and Yeah.
No, I went out on Thursday. I got going
out. I went out last I went out last
Thursday, last Saturday, and last Thursday.
I got 13 numbers and if I'm lucky I will
get one date if I'm very lucky next week. But yeah, man. Oh [ __ ] Yep.
So yeah, it's out next May anyways. So
should have come out in the winter to be
fair. It would have made more sense
coming out in the winter.
Yeah, but most of them aren't
interested. So, it just goes to show how
much of a waste of time it really is in this country.
Thank you, Tik Tok. Thank you,
Instagram, for [ __ ] it up for for us,
most people. Anyways,
thanks Instagram. Thanks, Tik Tok.
We can we can find Tik Tok and Instagram. But yeah,
anyways, we're not talking about this anymore anyways.
Yeah, it's good. Except from the whole
none of them are probably going to be
interested. Did you seem to forget about that part?
Uh, did I get I think I got about four
replies. Three or four maybe. One was
supposed to meet me last week and they
ghosted. One's supposed to meet me next
week. We'll see if they actually do.
No, you're just wasting your time here.
That's why I'm just going cinema today.
I just got chill today, bro. [ __ ] this.
But yeah, it is it is impossible really.
Well, almost it is almost impossible. That's Franklin.
The picture is Franklin from DJ.
So yeah, man. I got 30 numbers. I think
like three or four replies,
but nothing will come out of it. That's
actually [ __ ] up when you think about
it. Like you can go out, right? Well,
there were between two days. Two days.
No, it was three days. Three days.
That's mad how you can be good-looking.
Yeah. And you can go out. Oh, [ __ ]
and accumulate numbers, right? And you
can't even so much as get as a date. So
much as even get a date. It's a madness, isn't it?
It's a proper madness, isn't it?
[ __ ] I should understand if she was fat
and ugly, then I be able to understand it. Yeah.
But anyways, no point talking about
something we can't change. So yeah,
the only thing I like about drinking is
drinking and then coming home.
It feels good. You know, grievy, you
drink and you're just about to go sleep
it feels good, isn't it?
I don't know how to explain it.
Oh. Um, it's a horror film.
It's a horror film, bro. So, Oh, I
didn't even read that. Yeah, it's a
horror film, bro. My bad.
I might as well go cinema, spend £25
instead of spending 70 80 pound
drinking. And I don't even want to go
out drinking today. So,
I like horror films. It's an Australian one.
No, I'm not keen on kebabs. I don't know
what the hype is about him. You know,
these kebabs, people love them. I I I
don't really I'm not really asked about them. Me?
Don't know about you, um, Grezy, but
I don't really care about [ __ ]
kebabs. You see people going mad for
them had a drink. I could easily live
without them, bro. I don't even like
them like that. And the only kebabs that
are good is like shish kebabs.
I don't know. I don't get the hype, bro,
with these kebabs.
No. Either no Chinese or Indian or
I had a kebab for [ __ ] ages.
I don't see the hype of me. I've had
like German kebab and it's nice. It is
nice, but I just find kebabs overrated.
I think they're over I think they're definitely overrated.
German dollar kebabs nice, but it's just overrated.
But the shish the shish kebabs are nice.
The the the lamb shish ones and
lamb shish and lamb uh but they're more
expensive. But they're they're nice.
They are nice, but I wouldn't think, oh
yeah, let me go get a kebab.
No, I just get a nice Chinese
or an Indian or I don't know.
I think they're overrated, man. You know,
last time I had was maybe 3 months ago
when I was at my sister's and that's
only cuz she ordered it. Nah,
but yeah, the dating thing is [ __ ]
The dating thing is really [ __ ]
But it will never change in this
country. So, best get used to it. Hey, Grezy
must get let's get used to it, bro.
and it's only going to get worse.
So if you're complaining now and it's
bothering you now,
then what are you going to be like in
another year or two years when it gets
worse? Can't be doing them things, bro. You know Yeah, it's bad.
Oh, Frankly, you ever go to the pictures, Greasy?
Now, Superman might be a nice thing to
watch as well. A little I prefer
Spider-Man. I don't really like Superman.
Well, not not as good as uh Spider I like Spider-Man,
but I might just watch the Superman one next week.
Why would you go to single? Yeah, no,
I've not tried single events. I need to
try these single events because you got
nothing to lose by trying it. But my
guess would be why would any woman need
to go to a single event
when she can literally cuz I need to
save money now Greavesy you know like I
don't want to go below a certain amount
of money cuz I want to start doing stuff you know
and not just going out getting drunk. So
maybe I'll just see just I'll go cinema
today and then maybe go cinema next
Saturday just like a plan something to
do. So save a bit of money in it. It's
good, isn't it? Um, so with the single
events, why would any woman need to go
to a singles event when she can just go
and get a man on Instagram or dating
apps? They've got all of these options.
Why would they want to
I don't say boyfriend, I say boyfriend.
So yeah, say it properly cuz I don't say
boyfriend, I say boyfriend. Yeah.
But yeah, why would a woman need to go
to a dating
a dating event? Just doesn't make sense.
Just none of it makes any sense whatsoever.
Unless they're like in their 40s or 50s.
They're the only people that you
probably get there. Is bad. Superman.
Yeah, I might I might watch that. It's weak. Yeah,
if she had anxiety, she wouldn't be
going to a singles event.
You wouldn't be going to a singles event
if you had anxiety, mate.
They don't know where to start. Well,
they can get any man they want on a
[ __ ] dating app. You remember I done
that thing with USA Izzy? I put I made a
profile of her at like 3:00 4 in the
morning and in an hour she had thousands
and thousands of likes. It goes to show
it tells you everything you need to know, man.
Dating is rigged against men. It's the
way that's just the way it is now.
Well, no they don't. They they they
exist for men.
So they exist for men. So yeah,
they mostly exist for [ __ ] men and
women in their 40s and 50s. So,
oh, really fat, ugly people. That's the
only thing you're going to see there. I'm guessing
I already ate. I had some pork. I've got
I have some roast pork. I'll just eat that later. Yeah, man.
Same. He's motivating.
So, yeah. I mean, I could try it, but
I mean, they exist for men. The reason
they are they were invented is mainly
for men. The only people you're going to
get there is [ __ ]
And I think if you was to go one of them
places, I wouldn't want to do it in London either.
I'd want to go to maybe like a smaller
a smaller city. So,
any luck with Fanny? Stop asking stupid
questions and you get stupid answers.
Why do you ask the same questions when
you know it's the same thing in this
country? That's what makes me think that
they the people in here have brain damage
cuz they ask the thing same thing like
it's it's never going to change.
30 numbers is a lot as well, bro. In
three days. Yeah. In the space of three
days. But it's still like over four
numbers a day, is it?
Yeah. It's bad, is it?
[ __ ] really bad.
Some of the replies you got from like
years ago as well, like two, three years ago.
Like you'll always get one saying like
they're seeing someone and [ __ ]
Same old, bro. It's been the same old
for years, but worse.
It's [ __ ] hot. Why has it got hot all
of a sudden? [ __ ]
That would be that pork greasy.
Oh, did you do your food shopping,
Grezy? I done my little food shopping.
I done my little food shopping. Did you do yours?
It comes to £41.
I actually done a video of it as well,
but I bought some washing stuff as well.
But probably spent about 60 one. Yeah.
Oh, bless you. So, what are you doing?
Just one takeaway a week now.
One takeaway a week.
Is that what you have?
So, you've given up with the takeaways
now. But how are you going to live
without McDonald's, Greasy?
How are you going to live without
McDonald's? You love McDonald's.
I'm just going an hour and a bit.
You're not going to be able to live
without So you're telling me you're
going to go a month without McDonald's?
So you're going to Wait, wait, wait,
wait. You're going to go a whole month without McDonald's?
Oh, you don't. Hey, LT, remember that
time? Yeah. You come to the house? How
can you forget that time that we came close?
That's the closest we've been for a
couple of years.
So, no takeaways now. No,
that's what I need to do, bro. I'm
[ __ ] I've done my food shopping. No
more takeaways for me. For me, bro. Okay.
I can't I can't afford him.
I can't afford him, mate. I won't be
able to save money if I do it.
So, you're going to go a long time
without takeaways. Yeah, Grezy,
I think you're lying, bro.
I can't imagine it. Nah.
What's a special occasion? H
imagine me, LT, and USA Izzy all holding hands.
Cuz imagine that LT, me, you, and USA is
the all holding hands. Walking king.
Oh, what a lovely site.
USA. Is he in the middle? You on the
end, I'm at the other end. Walking King. Oh, another
How about this LT? How about
How about this?
Me, you, USA, Izzy, James, and Mark
Hamilton all holding hands. Could you
imagine how that would look?
Bezy, could you imagine how that would
actually look? That would look [ __ ] mad.
That would look [ __ ] mad. That would broy.
That would look mad, wouldn't it? [Laughter] Oh,
I said it to you earlier. Al, you think
the Jane thing is funny, is it? And you
like, why do I think I'm funny? Yeah.
You think everything's funny, LC?
You think everything's funny, mate. Mom,
they just ain't interested in this country.
Can't wait to have a nice drink and
popcorn. Oh, lovely. Greavves are
It's a lovely site, matey.
Bless you, Grazy. Imagine King at the cinema.
Imagine King at the cinema, bro.
Oh, you're going to buy it. Pleasure.
Hold it again. Oh, Franklin,
you look very Franklin.
Franklin, you've got a bruise on your face. [Music]
Oh, Greasy. He's got a very bloody face. Hud.
I like Franklin. He keeps me entertained.
It's a lovely little character.
He's a lovely little character.
No, you need to be stupid. Stop. Stop
it, Nikolai, man. You'll meet someone.
You'll beat someone when you least expect it.
That's what my mommy always used to tell
me. So, [ __ ] you, bud.
Yeah, and man.
Yeah, sorry. I was just talking to
Antman. He says that when you're out
there, you don't want a girlfriend.
No. One second. L2, you still there?
Don't you remember when we came close?
Do you remember when we came close?
Are you remembering me and you come close?
You remember, don't you, Greasy?
Me out in USA. Is he holding hands?
Yeah. Be lovely sight. That would be a
lovely sight. All holding hands, eh?
Oh, bless you. Yeah.
Do you remember the other day um you
said people in the pub thought that I
escaped from a mental asylum? Bless you.
How am I being gay, bro? I said we're holding hands.
We can share her
in the middle. We can share her.
That's funny as [ __ ] bro. They thought
I escaped from a Hey LT. Yeah, I was
going mad in the pub the other day and
Greg's like, "Everyone thinks that I've
escaped from a mental asylum."
Yeah, people was looking in it. [Music]
Yeah. [ __ ] annoying, bro. I'll do
that [ __ ] again. Yeah. When I leave
London again, I go to a proper club.
Yeah. Where people don't know me and
that. I would I would do it, boyfriend. Yeah, bro.
We'll do a mad weekend, bro. When one
time, trust me.
Yeah, I was thinking of doing it, bro.
You know what? Yeah, I was going to do
it on Weather Spoons, but they knew me
in there, but they bothered me anyway.
So, what I might do is just get a drink
there. I told Antman I was going to do
it and just go on the table and be like, "Ah, boyfriend.
I don't want to be in the pub where
they've all got Polish friends.
You know what I'm saying? What fun is that? Yeah.
Yeah, bro. It's [ __ ] isn't it?
I love your little projecting comment, bro.
Yeah, nice projecting comment, bro.
You're probably still a virgin.
Oh, no. I thought he was getting near
the airport, man. Like,
yeah, you're talking about yourself.
You're probably still a virgin. Oh,
all the self. Do you go on this LJ's channel? Greasy.
Nah, I don't really go on at me, bro.
Too many self projectors.
Repeaters. Nah, I don't go on me.
Repeating people. Same repeating people.
Why don't you go on it? Oh [ __ ]
But yeah, you know that at least you
know now that women are entitled here.
They are entitled to deatho.
Do you reckon they have a Weather Spoons?
Don't know. Don't care. We don't talk
about that virgin on my channel.
So, take it somewhere else. Anyways,
Grey, do you reckon they'll have a Weber
Spoons in Birmingham?
I haven't been to Birmingham for about
[ __ ] two and a half years.
I wonder if they ever Weather Spoons there.
You reckon I'll serve Guinness or you
reckon it will be different?
Reckon they've got Weather Spoons there or
Not anymore cuz I need to save money. I
don't have food. No, I bought some food today, Nick.
Now I am cooking. I have to cook.
I need to save money. I am going to Thailand.
But I wanted to give another place one
more well before I do
a little world.
Yeah, I bought some burgers, some lamb,
bought some stuff today. We're not all
rich like grievy anymore.
But we're not at the same time, we're
not like the virgin. So I got to go
soon. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, I'll do Superman next week.
Why Superman? Why not Spider-Man?
That's like £50 in two weeks you'll
spend instead of [ __ ] 160 170. So,
you're still saving money.
Yeah, I was I had I had McDonald's and
Chinese yesterday, but I can't do it
anymore cuz I want to be saving some
money, bro. I'm never going to get out of here.
You might be like the [ __ ] virgin.
Only little benefit money, Nicolo. I
don't want to be like that, you know.
But it must be hard to be disciplined, man.
No takeaways for a month. I don't know
if I can do that, but we can try.
Uh, I bought a McDonald's Big Mac from
um the shop, bro. It was like£1 something.
It's like a microwave version. So, you
put it in the microwave. It's like a
replica of McDonald's when I was doing
my food shop. So, I'll try that later.
See what it's like. Probably a load of [ __ ] but
so I need to like Yeah. Imagine
I went out approaching every day for a month.
Every day for a month, Nicolo, [ __ ] hell.
Every day for a month. Jeez.
Yeah, it probably will be ranked, but
we'll give it a while. Every day for a
month. Oh, [ __ ] bro.
You probably end up killing yourself.
The first day, you'd probably end up killing yourself
every day for a month. [ __ ] hell. If you imagine
that would be mad.
I used That's how I met that
19-year-old. I used to do it Wednesday.
I used to as a job grieves. I used to do
it Monday to
maybe Monday to Saturday.
No. No, I used to do Tuesday. No, I used
to do Monday, Tuesday, Thursday, Saturday.
I used to do the approaches.
That's how I used to go and do the approaches.
No, just on the street. And that's the
square on the street. Yeah. So,
no, it was outside the Eminem shop basically.
Outside the Eminem shop. Yeah, man. Yeah, bro.
He is [ __ ] bro.
Wouldn't suck my willie the first time.
That's when I went on a date. I spent
£700 that day, bro. That ain't happening
again. That ain't never happening again, mate.
I won't be able to afford to do that
now. I can spend £700 on my boat. Nah.
Nah, bro. I actually spent £700, but I
went in the casino with 300 and got to 900.
So many fun times, bro. So many fun times.
I just about to go to the pictures.
Yeah, I was just saying to LT,
"Oh, yeah, mate. That me and that
Virgin, we we we met quite a few times,
me and the virgin." My mama even calls
him that as well, virgin boy. That's
that's my little nickname for him, Pet
Boy, cuz he is one. He is a virgin. Oh, [ __ ]
It's a horror film. Yeah.
Yeah. I used to be able to spend £700
and not worry about it.
[ __ ] hell. I was rich back there, matey.
I missed going to the casino. Oh, I
gambled yesterday, Nicolo. 150 on 150 on
a roulette. I didn't win anything.
These casinos are [ __ ] as well, bro.
You know these ones that aren't on on
GameStop. Yeah. You try to ban you you
try to close your account down, they
don't let you close your account down.
They make you email them and then they never reply.
Yeah. They make you email them and then
they never reply. Yeah.
Then then and then they never reply.
I think it's called Bring Her Back.
That's the horror film it's called. And
then and then you you try to contact
them then they don't reply.
I used to bro
I used to love going to them casinos man.
[ __ ] I used to love it bro.
I remember I got a back payment of
[ __ ] £4,000 before.
Then I went in to see 300. I got to a,000.
I had to wait for the payment cuz they
banned me and that in it.
Good times e good times.
You remember them little£50 notes they
used to give me. Nicola [ __ ] sake.
It's [ __ ] madness, isn't it?
Always hitting that number 11 e
in the casinos. Run a
what's the horror film called? [ __ ] sake.
show you. I tell you right now,
I remember that time I won that four
grand like it was like it was yesterday.
It's called Bring Her Back. That's what
the whole film called. That's what the
whole film is called.
Yeah. if they weren't going to pay back,
I was going to smash the whole casino
up, bro. They just said, "Oh, yeah, you
need to email them." And
then when I went back, they literally
didn't pay me out. It was [ __ ] bro. I
lost £500 because they didn't they
didn't. Basically, I was trying to get
my money back. Long story, bro. They
[ __ ] me over in the end. But I I got
the last laugh with all of them casinos,
bro. They got rinsed. That that that
strip of casinos, I used to rinse them, bro. Oh [ __ ]
I'll never forget that day, bro. £4,000
in [ __ ] wallet.
Yeah, if they didn't pay me, I would
have, bro. If they didn't pay me, I
would have. Yeah.
If they didn't pay me, I would have.
That be It was so hard to get that money
as well. They were making it so [ __ ]
hard. I had to email them and they said,
"Oh, give your bank details and we'll
send it to you.
Then they sent a thousand." So, yeah,
what they owed me.
Yeah, they're all the same, but it's
better than nothing.
God bless you then, Greasy,
with you in your little condition.
But yeah, Nicolo, I don't think you can
win anymore, bro. I don't think you can
win anymore online. I tried yesterday.
[ __ ] same old next door [ __ ]
You can't really make money nowadays, bro.
[ __ ] knows. Little dodgy in it.
It was fun though. That four grand. It
was fun. It's fun to have.
Yeah, it was £4,000 in wallets.
Then I turned 60 into a,000.
60 into a,000. Yeah.
In the patty power.
I don't think you can win nowadays though, bro.
Like that. Well, unless you can go to them casinos. No, not
it's No, if you've got no outgoings,
you can you can easily live off it. But
If you ain't got no outgoings, like none
at all. You can live off it, especially
if you've already got some sort of savings.
But like I said, it didn't really hit me
that much cuz I'd already lived the
life, the casino, the escorts, the
traveling stuff. Obviously, it's still
[ __ ] but I just put down to what's
going to happen. I've still got savings. So, yeah.
So, it was the worst thing to happen
because I had already had it for 3
years. I've already done the escorts,
the traveling, the [ __ ] so to have
had something left from it and still get money. But
no, you can. It's still not the worst.
What? Yeah. If you ain't got no outgoings, then
It's only temporarily anyways until I
find something. So,
what my plan is, I'm going to win try
and win a football bet,
£80 with a football bet and then that
pays about 250 300
200 300 and obviously with that two 200
300 that will pay for some drinks and
food and [ __ ] Then you can save. So,
I need to try and win a football back somehow.
Did you get a few nights out with £300?
One, two, three maybe. And then
obviously you just save the Yeah,
something something like that I'll have
to do for the time being.
But I didn't really care so much about
the house cuz I was just happy doing the
Uber. 1.5 1.8 that's enough for a month.
1.8 8 1.7 uh 1.5. I just didn't want the
house. I just didn't want the
responsibility of the house anymore. Got
my savings from it and I was just happy doing that.
So, as mad as that sounds, but is what it is.
It is bad. Oh, yeah. It is.
But the only thing I'm doing now is
saving and leaving. So I'm not really
off. It was going to happen anyways. So
I'm just saving and leaving now anyway.
So it doesn't really matter.
Yeah, man. Yeah, I got some I had some
pork today, bro. It's pork.
But yeah, you can't win gambling
anymore, Nicolo. Not online. Nah.
All the roulette rigged now, bro. Like I
said, I done it yesterday. That was the
first time in two months.
That was the first time in two months, bro.
And nothing changed. Nothing changes with that.
Well, I used to live off 700 5050 5050.
So, yeah, 1,100 you can you can do it.
I think I've already probably spent
about 700 to be fair. Yeah.
What it is, it
no more cooking videos, matey.
Yeah, I just can't do them anymore. It
is what it is. It's not like ah, bro.
Like I said, the way I saw it in my head
is I had already lived the life for
years. I got savings from it and yeah,
it's all good things come to an end anyways. So,
so, but obviously I won't be able to I
just won't be able to do that if I'm
saving, would I? Well, unless I win a
football bet. That's the whole point of
that as well. But it's fun though. It's
a good thing, man. That is a good thing, you know.
Now it's a challenge to more make more
money. It's good, man. That house thing
just got annoying, man. It just got
annoying. Your responsibility, the
tenants, it was getting annoying. The
house is [ __ ] always falling apart. So, yeah.
Just want to do the escort is it.
You think if I approached every day for
a month, Nicolo, I'd find someone if I
approached every day for a month. Nah,
I don't think so, bro.
with a hot banana.
Would have happened by now, is it?
The only thing I'm going to do, bro,
is try another city one more time.
At least any city but London.
One more time, right?
And then see what happens.
What do you think, Nicolo?
Hit up Birmingham one more time, maybe. Yeah, somewhere. Yeah, man.
Got slow it
does well when the pump.
Still haven't heard anything from these
jobs, mate. Oh my god.
I still haven't heard anything from
these [ __ ] jobs. I'd be doing Uber
right now. I'd be doing Uber today, bro.
If I could do Uber, I'd be doing it
today. I could make £100.
That's if there's no [ __ ] protest on.
I like the Uber thing, man. Like keeping
up keeping busy. And it was good, bro.
There was nothing better greasy than
coming home from a hard day's work black as s.
Oh, mate. I used to come back black as
sit, mate. Blacker than king. Cuz
obviously I was on the bike all day, wasn't I? Yeah.
It kept taking me to where I met my mama though, Nikolai.
[ __ ] kept taking me to where I met my mama.
No, I don't remember his, bro. I don't watch him.
It was like he was trying to like torment me.
Kept taking me to where I met my mama.
Boy, is this some kind of sick joke? you know. Yeah.
Remember when I tried to message my
mommy on Snapchat, Nicolola, and she
didn't want to know?
Straight up abandoned, in it.
Straight up abandoned.
Yeah, that fish owner syndrome. Yeah.
I just don't know how somebody could
abandon their baby.
Do you understand that, Nicola? How they
could abandon their baby? Pet B
can't get a tax anymore because he's
already found his mama.
Do you remember that one? Do you
remember that one? Greasy.
He's already found his mama. Yeah,
that was funny, bro. [Music]
Grezy will never work. He ain't got it in him.
He ain't got it in him, mate. How come? [ __ ]
Just before my shorts are dry.
Got really warm outside, isn't it?
One second. I need to talk to someone.
When do you reckon he will actually lose that V? Really?
When do you think
nonslegs will actually lose that B card?
I don't think ever. I think he'll die one.
I'm I'm I'm the [ __ ]
of the real bro. I want to wear these
shorts, but they're kind of damp.
They're a bit damp.
Let me sort of try and dry them on a on
a fan thing.
I think I think you will [ __ ] die a virgin, mate.
You try and dry them on a fan in it.
I want to wear these shorts. I don't
want to wear any other shorts. Grievy. I
want to wear these ones and these ones only.
You know what I mean? Grezy. Only these ones.
These ones and these ones only.
Isn't that a clever thing to do? Hey,
Greasy. Put the shorts in front of the fan.
Is that a clever idea?
That's a clever idea, isn't it?
You're going to [ __ ] die. [ __ ] virgin.
You're going to die. [ __ ]
Hi, Steven Alvin.
Why do you think Virgin boy always used
to go on about virgins?
Sounds like what a virgin would say.
Sounds like what a virgin would do.
Why do you think he he he used to say
all of these things?
you know, cuz he'd know all the signs
obviously being the biggest one himself.
So, he knew exactly what a virgin was
was like. He know all about something
that he is the biggest one going. Do you understand?
They're all stuck up in this country.
I I somebody on Reddit said to me, "I
don't know what your problem is. Your
approaches seem fine. You got some good messages."
They said maybe too many stick up. He
said there was like too many. They said
maybe there's too many
stuck up [ __ ] in your country.
You reckon they were right, Greavvesy?
Yeah, they were like too many stuck up
[ __ ] in your country. Maybe
that's what they said to me. Nah. Nah. Yeah.
There's a lot of stuck up [ __ ] here in England. Stuck up.
Right. I need to go picture soon everybody. [ __ ]
So, Grezy, you're going to be living on
what? 4050 pound a week now. Yeah.
You're going to be living on 4050 pound
a week now. Yeah.
Is that right, Bezy?
I don't think you can do it. I don't
think you can stomach it.
I don't think you can do it. Hey,
how how much do you think you'll be
living on a week now?
How much do you think you're going to be
spending a week?
It's hard trying to hustle through a
month, isn't it, Greasy?
It's hard trying to hustle through a month.
So, what are you going to do?
You probably spend about 100 a week, don't you?
Well, you you spend about 100 a week,
you fat [ __ ]
My money is probably just going to be
the same to be honest. I don't think I
can save anything.
Can't say I don't think I can save anything.
Wigs and dresses? What the [ __ ] you silly goose?
Why? Why are you spending money on wigs
and dresses, you silly goose?
Why the [ __ ] would you spend money on
wigs and wigs and dresses? You silly goose.
Who spends money on wigs and dresses?
You're a silly goose.
That doesn't make sense. Wigs and
dresses. Oh, where my my cup should be
here soon. My little cups. What?
I need to go to I need to go to the cinema.
Catch your [ __ ] Oh,
catch your [ __ ]