Oh [ __ ]
Where's my bloody thingies gone?
I think I lost them.
That's a bit odd.
I've lost my head once.
Oh, I lost my ears.
Love it all. Yeah.
All you and this J need to pack it in.
If anyone would ask me, I think you're
both a pair of tants.
You two need to pack it in. Seriously,
how long are you two going to keep [ __ ]
doing this for?
You know, I spoke to [ __ ] Britney um
yesterday and I was going to mention it,
but I'll use it as a [ __ ] example. I
spoke to Britney. Yep.
Yep. Spoke to Britney, mate.
Yeah, I spoke to Britney.
Yeah, I spoke to Britney, man. We'll see. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, man. I spoke to [ __ ] Britney
and she basically said that
she's not interested in skin virgins,
which is why um yeah, she rejected him
all these years.
Oh, I got powder here.
Not going to say anything, but yeah,
she's not interested in skin virgins, unfortunately.
that's never had a j
that's never had a little j.
So yeah, a jab, not a go o b j a w b.
You're not interested in lanky skin
little virgins. Yeah,
I've got a football bet for next week.
Haven't done it yet, but I already know
the two teams I'm picking.
Oh, dear me. Dear Oh [ __ ]
Why is it saying that?
Your appeal was denied. [ __ ] what? My
god, they're [ __ ] wankers, mate. Oh, they're wankers.
They're [ __ ] wankers, man. But yeah,
>> it was all right speaking to Britney yesterday.
I ain't spoke to that Canadian in a long time. Nah. [ __ ]
Yep. Here we go. GTA Cross.
She's good this game, man.
But yeah, she's not interested in skin
virgins. I ain't got a job.
Well, I have one next week
hopefully. Hey, bro, you should have saw
how many couples I saw in the cinema yesterday.
But to be fair, there was this black
guy, right? And he was with like a four
out of 10.
And it's mad because it's like I've been
with better than that before. And I and
I felt like, bro, I weren't even happy
with them. And then that's how bad it's
got now. People having to [ __ ] lower
their [ __ ] standards. It's [ __ ]
bro. It's so [ __ ] They have to get
what they can because
Yeah, it was like some five out of 10 wearing glasses.
It's mad what people have to That's not
even bad to be honest. I've seen even
worse what people have to settle with.
It's mad, isn't it? It's mad.
I should have this date next week. Well,
this week really, but we will see. E,
probably not. It is. It is bad. It's
proper bad. It's so bad, bro.
People seem to make it sound like it's
easy when there's nothing easy about it.
Honestly, I'm I am leaving, bro.
No, it's not horrible. Did you not just
listen to what I just said? And the guy
wasn't African either. Did you just
listen to what I just said? I just
explained it for like 2 minutes. I swear
some of you on here have actually got
like [ __ ] brain damage, bro.
You really really got brain damage. You
don't listen to anything anyone says, do you?
Yeah. There's no point me even talking
about anyway. I'm not talking about this
dating anyways. So,
cuz you clearly have brain damage. You
don't listen to what anyone says. So, it's pointless.
It's pointless, bro.
I think you need to get a life and stop
[ __ ] coming on YouTube and mocking people
if you're not even going to listen to
what anyone says. So, it's pointless,
but I don't give a [ __ ]
But it ain't my problem cuz I'm leaving
anyway. So it ain't my [ __ ] problem.
It's not my problem cuz I'm not leaving.
I'm leaving. So it's not my problem.
End the [ __ ] story. It ain't my problem. Simple.
It's your problem, matey. Not mine. [Music]
Well, I like your trolling, man. It's funny.
Your trolling is funny. I like it. Yeah.
I spoke to Britney yesterday, man, and
she weren't interested interested in
Virgin Boy because he's a virgin. He's
skinned and he's never had a job.
That's why she's she's she's not he
wasn't interested in him.
She's not interested in skin virgins.
Yeah. I was speaking to Britney. You
know Britney from Canada? Yeah, man.
What I find depressing is there's no
ways to [ __ ] make [ __ ] money.
That's what I find [ __ ] depressing.
That's That's what I find [ __ ] up, bro. Um,
I'm just saying I went to the cinema
yesterday. Good horror film by the way.
If you ain't watched it, the Australians
seem to come out with good horror films.
Even though they've only made two,
they're really good to be honest with
you. I was just saying I just saw saying
how I see like couples in the cinema and
how a lot of the women that they're with
are like very very but average. Four out
of 10. I see this black guy with like a
four out of 10 with glasses and it's
weird cuz I had better than that before
and even I was unhappy.
It's mad to see how like people actually
lowering their standards nowadays.
But I saw this fat guy, but I never used
to see this in my area. Just I don't
know used to tell me about this, but I
never used to see this in my area. I see
this fat guy, right?
And he was with like a [ __ ] seven,
eight out of 10. He was some fat guy,
bro. He must be selling crack to [ __ ]
kids or some [ __ ] Must be a drug dealer
or got a million followers.
Oh, and I was playing the grabbing machines yesterday.
Yeah, I need to I need to accept
reality, bro. I need to leave.
Maybe I I I The reality is you need to
leave this country. That's the reality.
I'm supposed to be going on this date
next week, but if they're who knows if
they're actually going to come out,
I'm trying to prepare for the worst cuz
I don't want to put all my eggs in one
basket. Just say that they're not going
to come out. So, when they don't come
out, you're not cuz they've done this a
million times now. So, it's like, yeah, you know,
so that's the reality. You need to leave
the country. That's the reality. Oh
[ __ ] How the [ __ ] did he get in that car?
Yeah, I was tempted, man. No,
it's mad how like I've been all over the
country. To be fair, I would never go on
a date to a cinema, but it's mad how
I've gone all over the country. And it's
not even that I've gone over the It's
not You know, you you know what? Yeah.
It's not even that I've been all over the country.
It's also what I've tried recently. It's
not even about like going Wales and
Scotland. It's about recently I went out
in three days, right? I got 13 numbers,
right? Think of this. Yeah, 13 numbers
and I probably don't even have a date. I
should have one next week, but I
probably won't even get that. So, think
of that like say you approach 13 people
in 3 days, which was more than that. It
must have been about 40 or 50. It's
[ __ ] disgusting, bro. It's also about
more recently as well. [ __ ] all of that.
It's bad, is it? It's so bad, bro.
I think that some people are just not
meant to find anyone in this country
cuz it would have happened by now. Straight.
Straight, bro. Straight. It would have
happened by now. [ __ ]
Yeah, I was playing these grabbing
machines yesterday, but I wanted to
smash the whole arcade up. I put £10 in. Yeah.
Yeah. They would always say no in this
country. It's mad. Anyways, I was in
this arcade. Yeah. Trying to catch Nemo.
I actually done a video of trying to get
a Nemo toy and I grabbed the [ __ ]
Perfect cut. Bro, I don't I tried 20
times. It was 50p ago and the [ __ ] kept
slipping. I wanted to smash the [ __ ]
whole place up, bro. It's [ __ ]
annoying, man. cuz I was a bit early to
the cinema. So, I thought, let me just
try the grabbers.
I wanted to smash the whole arcade up,
bro. They were perfect grabs as well.
And he kept slipping and slipping and
slipping. How does it keep slipping? Well,
I told you about a million times I don't
gamble anymore. So, uh, none.
I think you you people have got brain
damage on here cuz people people tell
you [ __ ] Yeah. And and then you forget
it. I mean, yeah, I gambled the other
day, the first time in two months, but
you know, I don't gamble. So why are you
asking that when you know I literally don't gamble? So, so no,
I will be gambling from next Saturday
though on the football. I've already got
my bet sorted as well. So, I'm going to
put £100 on these two teams.
Fingers crossed it [ __ ] wins.
No, but why are you making conversation
when you know that I don't gamble? It
doesn't make sense. You're saying any
luck on a gambling when you know that I
don't gamble. So, how does that make any sense?
cuz you you know that I don't gamble.
Yesterday, uh the other day was a one off.
So why would you ask that stupid?
Nah, I was getting urges yesterday cuz I
was buy like loads of betting shops, but
I was like, nah, there's no point
playing something that's rigged.
There's no point playing a slot that's rigged. Right, Grezy,
so I just went to the cinema. [ __ ] it.
But yeah, it is disgusting. 30 numbers,
no dates. How we doing, man? I I got 13
numbers, bro. And I think I've got a
date next week. Maybe. I've not heard
from her in a couple of days. She's in abroad, but
so yeah, man.
She could just be busy abroad, but we
scheduled something next week. But I got
13 numbers in three days. Notorious.
It's bad, ain't it, bro? It's [ __ ] bad.
13 numbers. Wow. It's a lot in it. It's
a lot in three days, bro.
I just wonder when it's ever going to end, yo.
I don't think it will ever end in this
country. I don't think it has no ending.
Generally don't think it has any ending
in this country. Doesn't stop, does it?
The [ __ ] don't stop. Jesus Christ.
Just playing some GTA. It'll never stop here. Never.
You'll always see the same stuck up
people, the same attitude.
You'll always see the same thing. I
didn't go out drinking uh yesterday. I'm
not going to go out this week either
cuz there's no way to make money now. So
I can't be wasting it.
So what I'm saying?
Must be. It must be.
So yeah, it's bad, isn't it? It is bad
life. It is a bad life.
The only thing you can do is leave.
That's literally only thing you can do
is leave, bro.
I think the truth, bro. The only thing
you can do is leave this country.
Not forever like what Ant-Man's doing.
But you need to keep thinking about
Ant-Man. Cuz think of Ant-Man. Yeah. He
never he hasn't dealt with half the [ __ ]
I've dealt with. Not even quarter of the
[ __ ] that I've dealt with
in the way I've dealt with it. In the
way I've dealt with it. And he's he's
not here. You don't need to [ __ ] live
there. But I mean,
you don't have to. No one's saying
[ __ ] move there. even though he's a
better life, but you know, it's like you
need to really think about that, you know, like
he ain't tried nowhere near as much as you have
and he left, you know. So, it's that's
what you really got to think about doing
even but my my but the way I see it
though is that I shouldn't have to
the way I'm seeing it is I shouldn't
have to leave my own country.
It doesn't matter where the [ __ ] it is,
how far it is. I should have to leave
where I'm born and bred to to to find someone.
You know what I'm saying? I think it's
I think it's disgusting me
about anyone else.
If he was fat and ugly then Yeah. You know,
cuz you know, people have been going
Thailand for years, you know, but it
used to just be the fat old people saying,
but this woman who's supposed to be
meeting me next week, she's from the
Ukraine and she's [ __ ] sexy, bro. I
was going to [ __ ] and I'm trying to
not let it piss me off because I know
there is a chance she's not going to
come out next week, but I'm just trying
to not let it piss me off.
But how can you not let it piss you off,
bro? It's like, what the [ __ ]
You're human at the end of the day. Um,
it's [ __ ] up, bro. It's It's [ __ ]
up. It is [ __ ] up.
It's not normal. Anyways, Jane was
showing me some uh videos.
Sorry. Jane was showing me some messages
of what LT was sending her. You're a
dirty dirty boy, aren't you, LT?
I knew you was trying to get in there little nickn little knicknacks.
I knew you was trying to get there a
little bit, but
I don't say [ __ ]
I knew you was trying to get that little knicknacks.
No, I I I know you weren't like trying
with [ __ ] USA, is he, boy? But I I
even said to you, you can have the
[ __ ] You can have the [ __ ] [ __ ]
You can go to America and have the [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] You can have that [ __ ] bro.
And I got a phone now. I can't afford it, mate.
1.8K on a phone, mate. Sorry, man.
That would be all my money. I can't afford it.
Nah, I can't afford it, mate.
And for some reason, it's letting me get
a contract out as well. So, yep.
I can't afford two grand on the phone, matey.
I don't even think I could even then.
That's [ __ ] ridiculous. Let's say two
grand. And it's And I tried to get a
contract out as well, even though I pay
my phone bill every month on time. I pay
all my bills on time and it doesn't let
me uh it doesn't let me get a contract.
I just got my old phone back uh my old
the the Fold six, but it's almost packed up.
Yeah, it's almost packed up. The
screen's almost [ __ ] on it.
Even though I pay my bills on time,
every single bill on time, my credit
still doesn't seem to go up. That's
funny, isn't it? And they were asking
for £500 up front. So, when I tried
ordering it, when I tried pre-ordering
it the other day, I was like, "Oh,
they're asking for £500 because your
credit's a bit shit." So, I was like,
"Okay, I'll pay the £500." Um,
I need an upgrade. I guess you just
didn't listen to what I just said again.
Brain damaged. A lot of you got brain
damage. So, then when I tried to order it, um,
they didn't let me. So, yeah.
So, I'm just using this phone now, and
then when it breaks, I'll just buy like
a four 500 pound one. Simple.
I can't pay 1.7K on a phone, bro. So,
I can't pay 1.7K on a phone. That's
ridiculous, bro. That's a holiday to
America. I can't justify it.
more than happy to pay the contract. But
that doesn't make any sense cuz I pay
I've been paying that that that bill for
month and I've even gone over and I've
paid it. Nah, I'm good, bro.
I'm not spending 1.7K on a phone. You
can [ __ ] right off.
That is not happening.
This phone has probably still got a
couple of months left on it.
So, I can't pay that for a phone. That's ridiculous.
To be honest, I'm I'm using that as an
excuse not having it, not being able to.
I still wouldn't do it. Even if I had
5K, I still wouldn't do it. It's
ridiculous. But a phone and a new one
comes out every [ __ ] year. Every year
a new one comes out.
I paid a contract, but I'm not buying
it. I'm I can't pay I can't pay that,
bro. That's ridiculous.
That is That is ridiculous, bro.
You need to stop trolling, bro. It's
You're really bad at it.
You need to stop trolling. You You
You're either trolling or you're generally disabled.
This guy is either trolling, bro, or he
is generally a [ __ ] [ __ ]
Really? Really? I think a bit of both,
to be honest. [ __ ] disabled. Oh, [ __ ]
You still there, Grey? Let me Let's ask
what Greavvesy thinks. 1.7K on a phone.
What do you think, Nicolo? 1.7K on a
phone? Nah. Nah, mate. There's a few
reasons. A, there's always a chance of
your phone getting robbed. B, a new
phone comes out every [ __ ] year. And
with 1.7K, you could [ __ ] go to
America. Why the [ __ ] would you pay that
on a phone? I, bro, it's ridiculous.
It generally is ridiculous, bro.
It's the new Samsung Fold and they bring
out a new Fold every um every year as
well. It's ridiculous, bro. Would
you pay 1.7K for a phone? I wouldn't. I
wouldn't, bro. Even if I had it spare, I
still wouldn't do it. It's ridiculous.
Yeah, I tried getting a contract out,
Grezy. You know how I've got like a pay
monthly sim and I pay it every month. I
pay all my bills every month. Um um
I pay I pay um I pay my phone every month.
Yeah. You show Yeah. Yeah, man. You show
me that 10 grand I've been waiting for
for a year and then come back to me.
Yeah. Yeah. You show me that 10 grand
and then come back to me. Um anyways,
and I tried getting a um tried getting a
phone and they wouldn't let me.
which doesn't make any sense cuz I pay
my bills every month. So
yeah, 1.7K that's the cheapest. It's
more like 1.8K.
So I can't uh if it was like8 900 even a,000
bro come back to me when you've got 10 grand. Bye-bye.
Let me state this clear right. I'm not
playing the money game with anyone until
I'm shown 10 grand. I'm eliminated.
I'm eliminated from that game cuz I'm
yet to be beaten. Anyways, yeah, Grezy,
as I was saying. So, I pay this monthly
um SIM bill every month
and it's about and I've been paying it
for months and months and months and
months. I don't ever It's a direct debit.
Um, and I tried to get this the contract
out with the fold
and they're asking for like 500 up
front. They seem to do that when your
credit is a bit low, which I don't know
what mine is cuz I pay my bills every
month. And then when I tried to get it
out, they didn't let me.
So I'm thinking, well, I'm [ __ ] then
because I'm not paying 1.7,000 for a
phone. So I'm [ __ ] I won't be able to
get it. It's as simple as that. So,
you know, my phone days are done by by
the looks of it,
which there's no reason why they didn't
give me it, cuz I pay my bill every I
pay my bills every month, but they
didn't give me it. So,
yeah, I can't justify 1.7 1.8K for a
phone, bro. You can go to America with
that money. Just use that as an example
because it's like one of the most
expensive holidays. So, you can't you
can't justify it, bro.
I've already got the model before the
new one. You [ __ ] I just told you
I've got Samsung Galaxy F 6. Oh, you are [ __ ] [ __ ]
Sorry about my language, but you really
seem like you're [ __ ] disabled. Why
is there so many disabled moles on this
community, bro? What the [ __ ] I already
told you I've got the six. I'm using the
could probably just get the screen fixed
to be fair if it's cheap enough. But the
phone is blocked. But yeah, the phone is Yeah,
but I'll never pay that for phone.
Even a thousand you could kind of Yeah.
Yeah. I'm skinn. I've got more money
than you'll ever have, bro.
More money than you'll ever have. I
don't see you showing 10 grand.
I don't see you selling 10 grand
and you're gone. Bye-bye, [ __ ]
Bro, let me ask you this question. Yeah.
How long are you going to keep doing this for
like year in year out year in year out
year in year out? It's got to be some
autism in it with with these spastics on
this community. It's got to be some autism, bro.
I think Greavves is like the only normal one
and that Joe
in terms of like
actually have a conversation. How long
are you [ __ ] is going to keep doing
this? I was I was going to do this
little challenge with um Lord J um yesterday
that you say that I can't live without
YouTube and everyone's skitting all
this. So I was going to do this, right?
I was going to say, how about this? I
won't come on YouTube for a week and you
won't come on YouTube for a week.
Saturday to Saturday. And I will come
back on Saturday and we'll see who's
been on YouTube and then we'll see who's
the ones that can't live without
YouTube. And it will be the same mongos
every single day. Yeah.
Get [ __ ] spastics on here, bro.
I'll be watching Superman next week.
Maybe that's where I'll take that date
if they want to meet. We can actually go
watch some Superman.
Just never been on a date to a cinema. I just never
just never saw the point of it.
But try something different. Is it
on a date towards Superman Grezy? Ah, bless you.
But yeah, I'd recommend a horror film,
but just make sure that uh you don't
[ __ ] your pants because it's quite uh
it's quite scary.
Good horror film though. Quite scary.
I'd give it an eight out of 10.
Yeah, I just go on a date and watch Superman.
[ __ ] it, it
give it a whirl. What's that? Maybe you
you probably share the popcorn I'm
guessing, right? Only drink. What's it 3540? Maybe 45 cinema. Well,
I might say let's go and watch the new Superman. Yeah.
Yeah. I thought I probably was the only
one in that cinema by myself yesterday.
You do see people.
But I didn't like yesterday, bro. It was too busy.
Uh I don't like Saturdays, but they're
too busy in the cinema. I don't like it
when it's busy like that.
To be fair, the people are quiet. But
the thing is, Greg, they always seem to
come out on Fridays. So
that's the thing.
I hate this. You know, I was walking
around Grezy, like the area, this
different area, and I was going I was
looking in some of the clubs and the
pubs, and no one really goes out
anymore. Like, obviously, if you go
central London, you'll get some people
out. Obviously, central London, but if
you've noticed, right, you don't see
many people out.
That's how you know just people just
don't have the money anymore.
you you know
these people don't really have the money
anymore bro cuz obviously you do see the
odd there must have been in one place
maybe about seven eight people
just don't have the money anymore you know
to go out I guess
it's strange isn't it and you know what
I've got a feeling I've got a feeling
these cine boys are going to go bust
I got a feeling these cinemas are going
to go bust one day. Why don't you tell
us what you think, Greenley?
I've got a feeling these these cinemas
will go bust
cuz there's a lot of people that go
there, but it's not like there's
there's so many I don't know how they
make a profit with all like the
electrics and [ __ ] You know what I mean?
Bye-bye, [ __ ] Not reading that.
You just wasted your time writing that
paragraph and you just got blocked. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye, Virgin Legs. Uh,
yeah, but I think one day it will go
bust, bro. Do you remember Blockbuster?
Grezy that went bust.
Blockbuster were the days, bro. What the
[ __ ] days? He's not reading that. Go
on another account.
Bye-bye, Virgin. Another account, please.
Not reading that. Yeah. Do you remember Blockbuster Greezy?
It's mad that they waste their time
making accounts just to get blocked.
What a loser.
And to answer your question, no, going
up to somebody and complimenting them is
not sing. to actually answer the last
bit I actually read. That's not what
simp means. No, that's not what simp
means. Do I sit there all day sticking
up for women? No. No, bro. Anyone can go
up and and and compliment someone and
not be a s. I don't think you understand
the definition of sing.
And there's no such thing as sing in
real life either. It's all done on
social media. So, try again. Virgin by
I need to try the Odon next time.
No, but seriously, what do you think
about going on a date to the cinema to watch Superman?
I think that's that's not a bad uh date
to be honest.
I might message all of these numbers,
see if they want to go and watch some Superman.
Yeah. What do you think, bro?
I'll do some drinks and some Superman.
I'm trying to think if it would come off
as weird. I don't think so,
cuz Superman's not a kid thing, is it?
It's It's like the same as Spongebob.
You know, Spongebob come out in the
cinema, you could go and watch it
because you've been you've been watching
it since you was a kid, you see. Same
thing with Stitch,
you know, so you you know, you can watch
stuff like that. It doesn't matter how
old you are. I still like Spongebob. Greasy.
I'll always love Spongebob. He's my little friend.
Yeah, I love Spongebob, bro.
Don't know if you still like it, but I still do. Spongebob.
But yeah, that [ __ ] Cherry needs to
pack it up, bro. You can't troll like
me, bro. You can't troll me.
Why do these people sit on here and do
this every day, Grezy? It's so
concerning, isn't it? You not think it's so weird
sitting on here every day talking about
themselves, trying to troll. Do you not think it's,
you know, she not creeping around me?
She was just showing me messages from
LT. I just ignore her, bro. I don't talk
to her. She can't reel me in. And I know
what she does.
No, she's just sending sending me stuff
that LT was sending. It [ __ ]
I'm not interested. Yeah, man.
All Lisa, can I ask you a question? Why
do you think these people make me
insecure? These people on YouTube never
make me insecure. these fat ugly skinned
people. I don't know why you always say
that. Like whenever I go drinking, I go
live. Yeah. You always like make you
insecure. Make you insecure. These
[ __ ] losers can never make me
insecure. They can never make me stop
showing my face. Lisa, you need to get
that in your head. I don't think you'll
ever get it in your head. These fat
lossers that can't live without YouTube
are living their worst life.
They're [ __ ] mongos.
You think they affect me?
I do not. Yeah, but I'm not trolling
about the women and like getting a
woman. No, that isn't possible. I'm not trolling.
But um it is [ __ ] up. Dating in this
country is [ __ ] up. I'm being serious.
But yeah, I do laugh at them.
They're [ __ ] mongos. They can't live
without YouTube. They're [ __ ] They
are something to laugh at. They really
are. But no, with the women thing, I'm
actually being I'm being dead serious.
It is [ __ ] up the dating in this
country. It is [ __ ] up.
It's not normal. But yeah,
listen, Lisa, how many times are you are
you going to say that you're not badl
looking? I know that I'm not bad looking.
I I'm not insecure. You don't need to
keep compliment complimenting me.
You don't need to start complimenting
me. Uh Lisa, I know what I am. I know
these people self-project.
You know, they are stinking, they are
skint, they are fat, they are ugly, they
can't live without YouTube. They are all
of these things. Look, Lisa, you you
should know yourself. You follow this
law, J. Listen, listen. Let me let me
tell you something. What What the [ __ ]
do they call people every day skin? If
if they if everyone's skin, why are they
sat on YouTube every day?
Talking to each other? If they've got
all of these friends and all of this
money, why are they sat on YouTube every
day talking to each other?
It makes it makes no sense.
Because they are skin, they are loners.
They are fat. They are ugly. They're
everything that they try to call other
people. Everyone knows this man with
these people and they
fat ugly losers.
Yeah. Look at I'm younger than them. I'm
better looking than them. I've got more
money than them.
Even though I don't have loads and loads
of money, but yeah,
they're [ __ ] They're all talking
about themselves. Bless him. So,
um, yeah, Lisa,
do you know where Kitty Minister is?
I got a friend that lives there. Kitty Minister.
Yeah, I got a little mate that lives there, Lisa.
Yeah, he he he has a black country accent. Uh
yeah, I'm pissed up. Yeah, man. Yep.
[ __ ] hell, man.
I'm just chilling playing some GTA. Lisa,
just playing some Grand Theft Auto.
I want to watch the new um Superman.
Lisa, do you want to come with me and
and watch the new Superman?
We can go to the cinema together.
Oh, I had my dinner. I had a full English.
I'm going to have some pork chops today.
Or maybe some burgers. Not sure.
Maybe make some burgers.
Yeah, I had a full English. I woke up at
10:00. I'm a lazy bastard nowadays.
No, I don't like Jane.
That's LT's woman.
I don't know why she's involved with me.
Leave me alone.
They don't leave me alone. These
bastards, Lisa, they're always trying to
[ __ ] get me involved with their [ __ ] [ __ ] off. You know,
but Lisa, they're all weirdos on here, man.
I'm going to come off here soon and live my life.
Yeah. Well, she ain't getting it.
She ain't getting it, mate.
I don't know why she's emailing me. I
don't give a [ __ ] bro. Stop involving
me in your [ __ ] [ __ ] annoying, man.
If he doesn't stop, I'm going to go to
Cardiff and go in a D.
I'm coming off this [ __ ] and living my
life, bro. It's [ __ ] weird, bro.
It's [ __ ] proper weird.
All a bunch of self-reflectors.
They're [ __ ] mongos. Yeah,
I don't know why you entertain that
[ __ ] L. He's a [ __ ] idiot, man.
He ain't got a life. He says that I
can't live without YouTube, bro. He He
gets himself He gets himself himself
confused with other people.
Why don't you go meet Timmy? Lisa,
you should go meet Timmy.
There's this woman on [ __ ]
She's trying to get She's like in her
40s and she's still trying to get attention.
It's [ __ ] weird. She's on Instagram.
She's trying to get attention messaging
me. It's mad how these [ __ ] don't
stop like even in their 40s.
I think they might stop in their 50s,
but that's it.
Who do you hate the most on here, Lisa?
I [ __ ] hate that little virgin. I'd
love to get my hands on that [ __ ]
I'd love to get my hands on that lanky prick.
Oh, it's just some idiot, man. Who do
you hate the most on? I hate that [ __ ] virgin.
Oh my god, bro. So much. I'd love to get
my hands on that [ __ ] lanky skin
[ __ ] Like, I can't even tell you how much.
Yeah. You don't even know, bro.
I hate the Virgin and I hate Lord J. Yeah.
Now, if it wasn't for me knowing what
these people are like on here, Lisa, I
would have been to Bare Force by now and
slap the [ __ ] [ __ ] out of him. But I
know what they do on here because like
I've traveled all around and they don't
meet up and then they pretend like
nothing's happened. That's why no one
You don't waste your time. You don't
waste your money, you know? You don't
waste your time. You don't waste your money. So,
you know what I mean, bro? So,
I love to slap that egg, bro. You don't understand. Yeah.
Who do you think would have won Lisa
that day when Lord J come to England?
And I think I would have battered him, bro.
I think I would have I think I would
have battered him.
What do you think?
That would have actually been a good
That would actually been a That would
have actually been [ __ ] entertaining,
is it? Like say I wasn't standing in
front of my mom and I actually went out.
That would have been funny, isn't it? Yeah,
that would have been funny, in it. Yeah,
the neighbors would be looking. I wonder
what the neighbors think of me, man. Honestly,
yes, I did. Yes, I did, Lisa. Yes, I
did. If you actually if you actually
watched all of it, you would actually
see what happened. Yeah. He didn't get
me down. He slipped. I slipped. Yeah.
And as soon as I got back up, I punched
him in his jaw. He fell down the [ __ ]
You see the video. And then after that,
he didn't want no anymore. He didn't
want none anymore, bro. I slipped.
That's what happened. I slipped. And
then as soon as I got back up,
I punched him and he didn't want no more.
And then [ __ ] Timmy kept running up the road.
He was running away. Timmy was running
He kept running away, man.
Like Tiger would even tell you himself
that I beat him.
Like Tiger will tell you himself that I
beat him. He would even tell you himself
that I beat him. So yeah,
it will tell you if you ask him. He'll
actually tell you cuz he told um he told
Mike, so he'll tell you. He'll tell you
himself if you ask him.
You know what? I might go Birmingham
next week, Lisa.
Yeah, I might go Birmingham next week. I
was thinking of going this week, but I
just went cinema, man.
I might go I might go Birmingham. Maybe
Monty doesn't live in Birmingham anymore
and I wouldn't meet Monty. I want to
call out that prime, bro.
I want to call out that [ __ ] prime.
No, I'm not meeting Monty. And Monty
doesn't even live in Birmingham anymore.
I think the only one I'd actually call
out is that Prime to be honest. Yeah.
Yep. They moved. I spoke to him
yesterday. He said that he moved.
He said that he lives in Manchester now. So,
how the [ __ ] do they get rehoused? Oh,
no. Yeah, they don't live there anymore
and I wouldn't meet them anyways.
Yeah, he's not. I spoke to him
yesterday. That's just a rumor. Just one
of these silly stupid rumors these
stupid people make up on here.
Yeah, it's just a rumor.
Yeah, they make up rumors, man.
Yeah, they make up Yeah, I spoke to
them. I spoke to M yesterday,
but that's what they do on here. They
just make up stupid rumors. They're immature, man. Oh, [ __ ]
So why don't you like Monty anyways, Lisa? Huh? [Music]
They're [ __ ] retards, man. Yeah, they do.
How much money do you have right now, Lisa?
How much money do you have right now?
What? 300 400 500.
Yeah, it's just like everyone really.
Most people are struggling nowadays.
I think I've got about 2K me, which is
quite bad to be honest. I should have a
lot more than that at my age.
Should have a lot more than that.
[ __ ] 2K. I don't have the [ __ ]
income coming in anymore as well. So,
it's [ __ ] man. I need to get myself a job, matey.
suffering for a job, matey.
Oh, bless you then, Lisa. If you done a
little shop, £200 shopping. What the
[ __ ] did you get, you silly goose? £200.
I know. There's no way to make money nowadays either.
There's There's no ways to make money
nowadays either. That's the maddest thing.
It is a joke. It's a [ __ ] joke, man.
How the [ __ ] did you spend £200 on food?
Is that for the month or what? 3 weeks.
I done a food shopping yesterday.
I spent like 61
food washing stuff.
61, but the food was 41.
What the [ __ ] That must be for the
month though, is it?
But that must have been for the month, right? 200.
You must have got a lot of [ __ ]
How much How much do you get a month?
Bye-bye. Stop calling yourself a Manta.
Uh, how much do you get a month?
That doesn't make sense. How have you spent
so much on food? That doesn't make sense.
250 on food for 2 weeks.
Where the [ __ ] are you shopping, man?
You can easily do a week shopping for
like 50 quid, £55.
You're [ __ ] man.
That doesn't even make sense.
But it shouldn't be that much. It
shouldn't be more than about 50 60 a week.
Shouldn't be more than that.
I'll show you. I don't know food shop. I
have recorded it actually. One sec.
This is a food shop I done yesterday.
I used to do it every Saturday as well.
It come to 41. See 4041
probably last about near enough a week
to be honest.
But yeah, 55 60 should easily last you a
week. Man, you're mad.
It has gone up but [ __ ] yeah
that was Audi but it's the same anywhere Morrison's
[ __ ] wherever you go it's the same
it's not [ __ ] £100 like Joe saying oh
yeah two then it's different
yeah then yeah then that makes sense but
I'm saying as a single person this Joe
guy is talking shite I didn't put a
video up about £100 a week. It's not
£100 a week cuz that what I just
shopped. And yeah, it might be Aldi, but
it's Aldi is just as expensive nowadays.
Aldi, [ __ ] little, [ __ ]
sainsburries, [ __ ] Morrison's. It's
all the same [ __ ] you know?
But 100 a week. Nah, that is [ __ ]
bro. That is, bro, that is [ __ ]
But yeah, two people
still a lot though. 250. But what does
it last two weeks? So yeah, then that's
just about right.
But not 100. That is bollocks. That is [ __ ]
Especially they probably don't drink
Coke the way I do as well. I drink a lot
of Coke. So
the maximum a week you'd probably spend
on food is probably about 80.
I'd say maximum. What do you think,
Greg? I'd say 80 is the maximum,
but not 100, bro. And that's eating like
proper like butcher [ __ ]
I had a full English today.
I'm going to make some burgers.
I got some pork chops. So
yeah, we're not all um we're not all
rich like Grezy, are we?
Isn't that right, Grezy? [Music]
Yeah, I got four for about £3 something.
Do you remember the burgers on the
George Farm in um Greasy? It's nice,
isn't it? Them burgers.
They're [ __ ] lush, man. But yeah, I
just bought I just done some food
shopping cuz I need to start saving now.
My biggest fear is going broke and I
don't want to be broke like that [ __ ] virgin.
I don't want to be skin like him.
And obviously if I went out drinking
twice a week and keep eating out
eventually I'll be skinn like that virgin
skin [ __ ] skin flint.
I want to keep my money around like
[ __ ] 2k then I can say you know you
got like a little bit there to make it
last you know. So 2k like no out going
and [ __ ] it's it's all right in it. So,
well, I'm trying to find ways to make
other income, Lisa, which is not what
not like what these people are doing.
They're just happy to sit on [ __ ] money
for the rest of their life.
I'm like [ __ ]
trying to find ways to
make more money, but it's not as easy as that. So,
yeah, I don't want to be [ __ ] skinn
like that. Virgin Greasy
skin a [ __ ]
I'll play house shoot. Huh?
I'll take you there if you give me a [ __ ]
That's nice, isn't it, Grezy? That's a
nice little offer.
No, I'm only joking. Well, Baltic place.
What the [ __ ] you on about? Baltic house.
What the [ __ ] are you on about?
I have no clue what you're talking about.
I don't know what you're on about.
Curry. Oh, yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I used to eat a lot of curry. Yeah.
Yeah. I love Indian.
I don't get as much nowadays though.
I like piggies, Lisa. Like a nice bit of roast pork.
Let me ask you if you have any P.
Yeah, I bet it did. Lisa,
but these little virgins can't afford it, can they?
Virgin boy can't afford that. Virgin boy
can't afford that, mate. Bye-bye. Virgin boy,
I spoke to Britney yesterday. Virgin
boy, she's not interested in skin
virgins. That's never worked. Sorry,
mate. Try up with someone else, mate.
She's not [ __ ] interested in [ __ ] skin flints.
Skint flint virgins.
Sorry, mate. She's not interested in
people like you, mate.
Nah, mate. No, mate. Not interested in you, mate.
Lisa, I was having I was having a little
um masturbate this morning. You know,
sometimes when you Yeah. He's obsessed
with me, man.
Yeah, that's what happens when you're
better looking and you got more money.
People become obsessed with you. And you
know the thing is Lisa, this is one of
the reasons like we're all laughing
about it now why I'm actually coming off
this. They never stop. They literally
literally never stop. That's how you
know they're disabled.
Like it's not even about, you know, you
think how many years these mongos have
been doing this now.
How many years these [ __ ] mongos have
been doing this on this community?
It's mad, isn't it?
How many years that they've been doing
it? That's why I'm [ __ ] leaving, bro.
[ __ ] that. You know, to be fair, if you
even go on my channel, you can see where
I've not been on it for like two weeks,
three weeks. [ __ ] know what I mean?
You can see
He say he needs to get laid. I' I've
been saying it for [ __ ] donkeys
years, mate. I don't know how many
[ __ ] times I've had to say this. He
just needs to get laid.
I think once he loses that V play, that
V card, I think he'd be all right.
Cuz you you must know as well like when
you was a virgin when you was younger. I
I know for sure. When you finally lose it.
Yeah. He's with a dwarf that doesn't
give him any sex. That's that's that's
the whole point. When you finally lose
your virginity, you you must know. It's
like it's completely
I don't know. You feel you feel
different, you know. I can't explain it.
No, he's a big virgin. He is, bro. Big [ __ ] virgin.
He is a [ __ ] big virgin, bro. Big virgin.
Yeah, bro. It is. It is. It is, bro. Cuz
they're they're disabled, so they don't
even understand anything you say. Yeah,
it is. And they'll never ever stop.
That's why I'm leaving, bro. Like, you
don't even see me on there sometimes for
like two, three weeks, bro. Cuz it's
just the same [ __ ]
It's just the same repeating disabled people.
Yeah, it is.
It is literally that cuz they don't understand it.
They're [ __ ] weirdos.
And I know that I'm better than them
because they're obsessed with me.
They're obsessed with me. So, I must be
better than them. Lisa,
it's like I said on that video to Jo,
you wouldn't waste your time on somebody
that is all of these negative things,
but they do. So, yes. Oh, [ __ ]
How are you anyways, that boy?
Yeah, I'm just hoping this woman meets
me next week.
Mate, they ain't got a No, they're
[ __ ] Come on, bro. They're disabled.
They ain't got a life. What do you expect?
They're [ __ ] disabled. They ain't got a life.
Yeah, I actually thought it was that
[ __ ] in America.
I actually thought it was at first. Some
of it look believable, but yeah, it just
go ain't got a lie.
They ain't got a life, mate. I have
people emailing me. [ __ ] Jamie
Thompson stalking me. They ain't got a life.
I was 17. I was
Yeah, they [ __ ] Yeah, man.
Yeah, you are so awkward. Stop talking about yourself.
That's why you're sat on YouTube all day
every day cuz you are socially awkward.
You got no friends. Stop talking about yourself. Self projectors.
That's what I'm saying. Everything is about themselves.
Skin socially awkward. [ __ ] virgin.
Ugly. Everything is themselves.
Talking about themselves.
You can be on here Friday, Saturday. You
go a lot of days, it's the same mongos
talking to each other. And that's how
you know they're all skin.
Skin ain't got a life.
Skint and ain't got a life. But YouTube
Yeah, they proper stalk me, bro. They've
been doing it for years. I get emails.
I get [ __ ] They actually stalk me,
though. That's the difference is what I
was trying to explain to Joe. That's how
you know it's jealousy, bro. We're not
going to get into it again, but yeah, we
just know that they're just jealous low lives
that they never stop.
I couldn't imagine doing it for years
every day stalking and being jealous of
someone. I I couldn't imagine it every
day. Imagine Imagine waking up one day
and then you're like, "Oh, who can I
stalk today? Who can I pester today?"
And they do it years and years. That's
how you know they're disabled as well
because they don't stop. They do it for
years and years and years and years and
years and years and years.
They're proper bully victims, bro.
Proper proper bully victims as well. Yeah. Yeah, man.
How the [ __ ] did I even get in here? I
shall never know, mate. Yeah, I'm
leaving, bro. 100%. To be fair, I was I
was only coming on every like 2 3 weeks.
It's same It's just just the same
repeating people. Same stalkers. Well, I
say I'm leaving. I'm just going to go on
my other channel. I've got some new
videos to put up on there. Some more
approaching videos I done the other day.
I done some approaching videos the other
day and I'm going to put them on there.
I don't want these people watching me
anymore, but I hate them.
So, I hate these little weird creepy
little bastards. So, I'm just going to
go on my new channel. I've got about 20
videos on there anyways to be honest. So,
I might come back every 3 weeks when I'm
drunk or something, but
these people are [ __ ] weirdos, man. I don't
I just come online to just rant about
women and rant about [ __ ] dating and Yeah. Yeah, man.
I I recorded a few approaches um the other day
and then Yeah, I'll just put it on my new channel.
these people will never have the balls
to approach a woman sober. Never.
Their anxiety won't let them. Just like
Virgin Legs. That's why he's jealous cuz
I've had more women than him and he's
still a virgin. He's been like just for
years and years and years this [ __ ] weirdo
years and years and years just [ __ ]
ver and you know back then bro like I
was young so I didn't really understand
it when I was like [ __ ] 17. But then
I I and then as I got older, I kind of
understood like why the [ __ ] does this
[ __ ] weirdo keep calling me the
[ __ ] virgin when I've literally told
him stories of me having sex and then
it's all because he was one himself. But
I didn't I didn't realize that.
I just thought, oh, like he just
generally doesn't believe it. But yeah,
he it all made sense because he is the
virgin. The biggest one going. the
biggest one going, bro.
And that story about them the them black
guys throwing water, that was actually
the truth as well. They actually did
throw water on him. Come on, bro.
[ __ ] hell. Like, you're walking
around Stratford, people can spot a
[ __ ] lanky, creepy virgin when when
they see one or possibly even smell one,
you know? No wonder, bro. The [ __ ]
virgin [ __ ] walking around, you're
going to get [ __ ] with. Happens in a
lot of [ __ ] cities now. You [ __ ] virgin.
He's a big [ __ ] virgin, bro. The
biggest one I've ever come across. Literally. Yeah.
Should get laid, mate.
Do you even have some good if you
actually got laid? Oh no. Died. [ __ ] Franklin.
Proper virgin, bro.
Do you think it's weird how they never stop?
I think that I think that's what the
weirdest thing I I think about.
That's what I find strange. They never
ever ever ever stop.
Imagine that routine every day, bro.
[ __ ] hell. They're jealous of
something in life.
They're jealous of something, matey. Yep.
They can't take one day off of YouTube.
This is their life, bro.
These people only have YouTube. Like
Lord J, the people that follow them,
they they only have YouTube, bro.
YouTube is their whole life.
That's about Yeah, man. Yeah, about Yeah. Oh,
yeah. But it's weird. I think I think
they're deep down they are jealous of
me. But definitely jealousy.
Jealousy is a horrible horrible horrible thing.
I've never been jealous of anyone.
Cuz that's the only thing that would
explain why they waste their whole life
reacting to you.
The only thing it would be is jealousy.
There's no other There's no other bars
it could be. You understand?
I don't even think people do that when
they're in love to be honest with you.
I think No, I think they're in love with
you and they're jealous of you. Jealous
of you at the same time. And they hate
the fact that they can't be you better
looking, more money than them, more of a
life than them. I think that's what it
comes down to.
And they probably do love you as well.
But it can't just be just love because
I'm sure people in love don't do this stuff. So
they hate the fact they're at they're
basically angry with themselves that
they're fat and ugly and they ain't got
a life. They ain't got nothing. So they
hate that. So they just come on YouTube
and project that anger and they're too
old to change it as well. That's what it
is. They're [ __ ] bro. Most of these
people don't even leave their [ __ ] house. >> Yeah.
I used to say they're [ __ ] um
so yeah, [ __ ] Um,
[ __ ] hungry. Why am I hungry again,
bro? What the [ __ ]
No, no, no. [ __ ]
I think it kills virgin boy that he can
ever do it.
I want to make some burgers.
Some burgers. Some burgers. Some
burgers, bro. Some burgers.
window also eat 10. Uh
well, I say it's a weekly shop. Yeah,
it's probably maybe like Yeah, five, seven days.
But I it was 61 all in all cuz I had to
buy some washing stuff.
Better start getting used to this life
now, mate, cuz this is my new life.
Could have been a lot worse. I could not
have two I could not have 2K, but yeah. Yeah.
Uh yeah. I was speaking to uh Britney yesterday, Joe.
And the reason she's not interested in
virgin legs is cuz he's a skinned virgin
and he's never had a jel.
That's what she said.
Well, I'm going to have I'm going to
make some burgers in a minute. I had a full English.
So, I'm going to have some burgers now,
then have some pork later. Yeah. Uh,
I got lasagna, I've got pizza, I've got
bonets, I've got meatballs,
I got some more burgers,
bacon. So, yeah.
Well, we'll see how many days it lasts. Anyways,
yeah, that's why Britney's not
interested in nonsakes.
No, not ready meals. None of them are ready meals,
mate. I'm not rich anymore, mate. I
can't be eating out every [ __ ] day.
You want me to be [ __ ] skinned like
virgin boy? [ __ ] that.
You must want me to be skinned or something.
Well, bro, even if it lasts 4 days,
you're talking [ __ ] about it.
I can tell you exactly how many days it
will last. Actually, if I go downstairs
and it doesn't matter because even if it
lasted 4 days,
that's You said it's 100 in a week. That
doesn't make sense.
It's not 100 a week, bro. And then you
got LT saying he spends a,000 a month.
That's [ __ ] bro. That is absolute So So
that is bollocks, bro.
That is actually [ __ ]
You don't spend £100 a week.
Doesn't matter. Even if you have three
meals a day, I can do it. I can do it.
I can tell you exactly how many days it
will it will last.
Let me actually go downstairs.
So, I'm putting some burgers on now. Porky chops. Let's see. M
I can actually see actually
we got some pork here as well. So one
one two three.
Should we throw some stuff as well? One, two,
probably another five days.
I got mints as well, which is two. So,
let me calculate this. Yeah, one
probably about five more days maybe.
I just hate shopping. But yeah, is what
it is. I'm actually going to put some
burgers on now. I'm actually hungry.
Oh, there it is. Still not.
I think you're tripping.
No, you said [ __ ] You said £1,000 a month.
I think a lot of you are fantasist. I thought that
I actually do think a lot of you are fantasist.
That's a lot, £1,000 a month. You know,
you can actually believe £100 a week.
You can you can believe £1,000 a week.
Uh, sorry, £100 a week if you're having
like really good stakes.
Yeah, but I mean,
yeah, but you shouldn't. But listen, the
problem with this is Yeah. is that James
a [ __ ] sto
a [ __ ] Like the thing is with Jane, I
don't like Jane. So I don't like Jay because she's
I don't like Jane because uh
just for burgers. I don't like Jane
because she doesn't admit that what that Mark does.
She has very bad words to say about
Mark, but he's just a [ __ ] [ __ ] Was it So yeah.
Yeah. Just putting this uh just putting
these burgers on. Two burgers.
You're trying to get me [ __ ] skin. You are
You're trying to get me skinned by lunch.
You organizes. I know your game.
You're trying to get me skinned, aren't you?
That's why you're telling me to keep
gambling, eh? Yeah. You're trying to get
me skinned like a virgin. You think I I
don't know what you're trying to do.
Everyone knows what you're doing, mate.
You're trying to get me skinned in that
[ __ ] virgin tongue.
Yeah. See how I've got no selfawareness
about you trying to say that he's not a
virgin. He's the biggest [ __ ] virgin.
If I don't let any
You're just trying to get me scared.
That's what you're trying to do. I know
what you're trying to do. It's not going
to work. It's not going to work.
It's not going to work, mate. They're
trying to get me by that virgin.
What am I going to do if I sens?
What will I do then?
I will be [ __ ]
Oh, I need burgers. Why?
One second. Why is it sticking,
bro? The [ __ ]
Sorry about that, man.
One second, please.
You're trying to get me to skip out that
burger. [ __ ] you, Joe. You [ __ ]
My dad. They're trying to get me to skip the volume. Yeah. Anyway,
I don't understand why she trying to get
me involved with all of this [ __ ] I'm
not involved in your your stupid drama, man. You know,
I need to stop getting stop, man. That's [ __ ] stinking.
So what? You've got no opinion on me
speaking to Britney, Joe?
You've got no opinion to me. You got no
opinion of me speaking to [ __ ] um Britney.
It's still sticking.
Why does that burger keep [ __ ]
sticking, bro? It's stinking the [ __ ]
over the cup with [ __ ] god knows that
much butter. It's still sticking.
Why? It just sticks. It literally just
Let me put my maybe horrible man.
I'm just cooking up some beef right over there. So yeah.
Oh [ __ ] Where are they?
Where are these [ __ ]
Where are these [ __ ] bies, man?
You should come out for some burgers. [Music]
Oh, I got four. Oh man. Yeah.
But she ain't never But the difference
is she will never admit um what that mark does.
She will never admit what that M does
cuz she's in denial. Now she knows the
truth, but she's just in denial, you see. So
she's just um Yeah, denial.
Uh one second, mate. Hold on.
Yeah, it's so nice, you know, like
sometimes I get my mom cook for me like
a a nice roast dinner
and it's so bad to think that the virgins
the virgin's mom used to starve them. I
have my my mom cooks for me all the time.
I go around and stuff. Never let my mom starve me.
He hates anyone with a mom that doesn't
abuse it. Yeah, I'm cooking some ice
burgers on here. Just cutting the cheese
now. It's like
he's angry at the world because his mom
used to starve him.
Used to starve him, mate.
I think that's why he's so hurt. if you
ever move back with your mom
because of um cuz your mom used to starve him.
I mean it's not ideal, you know, people
to live with their parents, but people
do live with their parents in London.
They even live in a box room,
[ __ ] They live with their
parents. They even live in a box room or
they live with their parents.
[ __ ] keep sticking
even either one. You don't even do
either one, you know.
And that's where the jealousy come from
cuz his mom used to starve him. Yeah.
You don't understand. If I ever see that
virgin, I'm going to smash that in the
face. You know that little smiling that
he does on YouTube. Yeah. I will smack
that [ __ ] show that he will never come
back on you again with that ugly face.
And I I'll be even the winner. Yeah,
I would, bro. I would do a little [ __ ]
prime. Oh, say sorry. No, no, no, no.
There'd be no sorry, bro.
He would get humid. He would never even
he would never come back on the internet
ever again. Like, not even Facebook or anything.
I would literally slap that bird so
[ __ ] hard. Oh bro, it wouldn't even
be a lovely sight. Yeah,
one there. One there.
Oh, [ __ ] That burning up.
You've got almost done.
We'll see what they're looking like. Lisa,
look at them.
They're cooking with butter. I need to
put the bun in them.
Hopefully these ones will actually cut.
I think they're working there.
Mel bit cheese. Oh,
they're going to be nice, man.
They're going to be nice.
Fancy with this. Cheers. Yeah. Yeah, man.
It's just a shame about the dating in
this country, is it?
A shame about the dating so hard.
Why is the dating got to be so hard in this country? Huh?
Why is the day going to be so hard in
this country, mate?
Stuck again. I don't know how they get stuck.
To be fair, it is quite an old thing.
Yeah, it's sad. Is it Johnny? This
country know it's so hard.
Should just be easy, matey.
Should just be straight up easy.
But no, it can't be.
Nope. I put the cheese here.
Then we put in the microwave.
I don't want to do the bacon to be fair.
I just want it with cheese. [Music]
I can actually tip it now.
There we go.
Nah, it's not that. It's the simps.
Especially in London.
Especially in London. It's not that.
It's the simps. The simps [ __ ] it. Tik
Tok and the simps [ __ ] it.
They ruined the whole dating game, bro.
You can't even find someone here now.
But I was thinking one more time, you
know, go somewhere Joe, just one more
time out of London. Just one more time
and do a full send.
Just one more time maybe. I don't know
when. And then I'm I'm looking. I'm
gone. Simple. [ __ ] that. You know,
good idea, is it?
I I I you know what it is? It's not It's
not that I I will ever learn. It's I I I
don't think I I'm stubborn. I don't feel
like I should have to leave my own
country, especially when you're not fat
and ugly. There there's no reason you
can't find someone. So, you might think
it's, oh, you will never learn, but it's
the fact that you should find someone.
You're not fat and ugly. And I feel like
I'm different than Mac. I don't feel
like I'm better than him, but I feel
like I don't know. I feel like we're two
different people, so should we should
have to gone down the same avenue?
It's [ __ ] up. See, it is [ __ ] up.
You can't even find me when you're in
country. It's [ __ ]
Yeah, it's [ __ ] up.
Well, you're watching me, bro. So, if
you don't like it, stop watching me in it.
And listen, bro, I'm not interested in
yours and James drama. I don't know why
she's emailing me. I don't give a [ __ ]
Cuz if you if you two keep winding me
up, I'm just going to get myself involved.
I'll just get myself involved. Like if
you if you two keep winding me up, bro,
and winding me up and winding I'll just
get myself involved, bro, and just start
calling you all again. I don't give a [ __ ]
I don't care what you said. I don't care
what she said. Why the [ __ ] are you
emailing me, bro, about what? I don't
give a [ __ ] bro.
Leave me the [ __ ] alone.
I'm trying to turn this bastard microwave on.
trying to cook some [ __ ] burgers.
Yeah. Why is she emailing me?
I swear to God, if you two don't stop,
I'll come down and I'll [ __ ] you both
hard. I'll come down and [ __ ] you hard
if you don't stop.
I'll [ __ ] you both hard. Yeah.
I'm just trying to enjoy my little
burgies in peace.
But I don't know why she's emailing me.
Why is she actually emailing me? It
doesn't make any sense. Is already
Just whipping up some tasty burgers here
cuz you want my opinion. I think you two
are a pair of [ __ ]
Ah, you know, I didn't say anything, but
I think you two are generally a pair of [ __ ]
No, I don't even think I just think
you're both a pair of [ __ ] Yeah,
I'll just go I'll just go to Wales and
go on her door and just end the whole
thing. No, but no, really on on a real
though. Yeah, let's be real. How long
are you going to keep doing this for,
bro? How long are you going to keep
doing this [ __ ] man? Mark J. [ __ ] How
long are you going to keep doing this?
I only brought Virgin Boy up cuz I spoke
to Britney yesterday.
That's the only reason I brought it up
because uh I spoke to Britney yesterday.
She doesn't want She's not interested in
a skin virgin
that's never had a job, which is only
the only reason why I brought the [ __ ]
up. She's not interested in in a skimp
virgin that don't that's never had a job ever.
That's why I brought it up, bro. Oh,
these burgers are t they look tasty. Oh
jeez, these burgers. They look like how
they made it in Spongebob. Oh, [ __ ]
hell. They look delish.
They are delicious as well.
M. What's up?
Yeah, I told you to jump. Yeah, cuz she
keeps emailing me, bro. It's [ __ ] annoying. YouTube YouTube
[ __ ] need to pack it in. No, honestly,
YouTube and you're telling me that I
need to pack it in. What pack what in? I
do. I thought he's getting emailed.
When is this [ __ ] going to stop like? Yeah.
And I don't know why. I think this is a booby trap.
I think you two are trying to set me up
for a booby trap.
I think this is all a booby trap.
Yeah, you were saying about how you
wanted her to show you the lead. LT,
you're a naughty, naughty boy. You're a
naughty boy. You are. [ __ ] naughty
No, you're a naughty boy. You are. You naughty,
naughty, naughty boy.
Don't think I ain't seen your messages, mate.
You're a dirty boy, mate.
It's not for me to say any I'm not
saying anything, mate. You know,
don't think I ain't seen your little messages.
Don't worry, Alie. It's our little secret.
Don't worry, bro.
It's our little secret. Bro,
I'm 30. I'm nowhere near 30. Stop
projecting. You people in your 40s,
mate. You wish I was 30, bro. Cuz if I
was 30. Yeah. If I was 30. Yeah. Let me
tell you this. If I was 30, that would
make you better about being 40, bro. You
people are 40 on YouTube every day. You
ain't got a [ __ ] life. You spastics
[ __ ] 30. You wish I was 30.
You're in your 40s, bro. Even if I was
30, you [ __ ] selfjector.
You don't need to know how old I am. But
I'm not 30.
You don't need to know that.
No. I never said I was 30, mate. No.
Oh, another thing is out here. Yeah, I
write poems, bro. I told you. Everyone
knows that I write poems, bro.
I'll put the poem up, bro.
I've never said I was funny, bro.
You must have missed some that me.
Listen, I said I wrote poems as well. I
put the poem up. I don't give a [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
But I like your little um
instead of sitting on YouTube cuz I'm
not cuz I've not got anything better to
do today. Bro,
why are you sitting on YouTube? Why are
you on YouTube? Same question goes to
you. I went to the cinema yesterday,
bro. I'm just chilling.
I'm straight chilling, bro. Since
somebody wanted to involve me in drama.
Why are you sat on YouTube? Same
question goes to you. Maybe you should
you should be sat on YouTube. What projectile?
I'm sat here chilling, bro. It's a Sunday, man.
Yeah, you are chilling alone. Stop
talking about yourself. sat on YouTube
alone. Yeah. Yeah, that is you, bro.
Yeah, you're sat there chilling alone on
YouTube. Yeah, you are. Stop talking about yourself.
You people know all about being lonely.
I got brought into drama.
So, I'm here. Yeah.
Can I ask you this question though? I've
got a question for you. Yeah.
And I I promise you I'm not trying to
troll you yet.
I'm not trying to get a rise. Let me
just start by saying that until um
I'll ask you this question.
Hopefully you don't take no offense to it.
So here's the thing. Yeah.
Listen, you right. You say you get all
of these women. Yeah. And I don't get
all of these women, bro. I don't I don't
sit there and say, "Oh, well, I get
numbers and most of the time they don't
reply or they [ __ ] me around or no, no,
no, no, no." But think about it, bro.
Why would you bother with any woman on
this community when you know that
they're just going to expose your ass?
It doesn't make sense. It does not make
sense. Why would you even want to meet
anyone on here, bro? Even if you met
someone on here, they're just going to
expose you. That's why I would never
meet anyone on here, bro.
So you see how it makes no sense, bro.
Then you know
that there's no exposure. You understand?
It doesn't matter, bro. She's in she's
she's contacting me all the time
and I'm ignoring it because I know
what's going to happen, bro. I know what
she's trying to do.
She trying to play games with me to get
me to want her to put my messages up. I
got it, bro.
I don't need to bother with some woman
on YouTube. I can go out today and talk
to someone if I wanted to. Technically
talk to someone if I wanted to. Not date
someone, not [ __ ] [ __ ] them, but I
could talk to someone. I know what she's
trying to do. So
that's why I ignore it cuz I know you
[ __ ] with anyone on here, bro. Natalie
G, Jane, it could be anyone, bro. You
know what's coming. You know yourself. So why?
That's why I just love me.
Lord Lord J does it because he's
desperate and he has no life of he has
no life outside of YouTube. YouTube is
literally his whole life. Simple Belfast.
Yeah, but it is though on this community
it is because you're going to Yeah, but
it is though.
But the thing it is because they're
going to expose you. Anyone in this
community is going to expose what you
write. Anything you write to them,
they're going to expose. So there is a
problem with it. It's the same with any
of them. Why do you think I don't [ __ ]
with all of them? See how many times
she's been emailing me?
Why would I need to speak to her, bro,
when I can just go out and try to speak
to someone? Cuz I know that she's just
going to put up everything that I say.
That's that's the problem. There is a
there is a problem when it's this
community. There is. Cuz look, you see
what happened again and again and again.
So there is no problem getting off the
internet, but on this community there is
because you know what's going to happen.
They're just going to try and Yeah.
She must email me every month and I
always ignore it.
I always ignore it. I don't
want to fight for with her. So I put it
on the internet.
It's like what Oxo used to do with Tiger.
Tiger. But she couldn't do that to me
because I already admitted everything
that I had said. So there'd be no point
There'd be no point um
there'd be no point um putting my stuff up.
But yeah, bro, the point I'm trying to
say is, yeah,
yeah, to be honest with you, I keep it
real with you. I never bother with women
on the internet. No Instagram, no
Facebook, no none of that [ __ ] bro. Cuz
there's a few different reasons. I don't
know who I'm speaking to. I just I just
meet people in real life. I talk to
people in real life. That's all I do. I
know it's not the in thing now and it's
a bit out of fashion, but I just prefer
it for various different reasons. Um,
so I I don't even speak to people online
except like people that I'd already know
like Yeah. cuz it's like you don't even
get anything out of it. So yeah.
No. What does it mean?
But you get my point.
I don't speak because bro listen. Yeah.
You know sometimes when I get these
numbers and I'm not going like I get
[ __ ] bro cuz I [ __ ] don't. Yeah.
You know when I get in combos right
and little dates or messages back. I
wouldn't get that online bro. I wouldn't
get that online if I started trying to
message someone on Facebook yet or I
tried [ __ ] tried messaging
people on [ __ ] It's hard enough in
real life now as well, you know,
Facebook or Twitter or whatever, bro.
They ain't [ __ ] replying back. No
way. So, I just do real life now. I like
to know who I'm actually talking to.
You're a naughty boy. You are LT. You're
a naughty boy, bro. Naughty boy.
You're very naughty.
Very very naughty.
And another thing, bro. Yeah. You say
that you go to these festivals.
You not [ __ ]
You're not chatting things up, bro. When
you're going to these festivals now,
you're single, though. Come on, man. Load these festivals
about these festivals. You
these burgers are very good, bro.
Yeah. So, surely you meet people in
festivals. So, if you're single, surely
you're getting numbers some some social
places you're going. So, why would you
have to bother with anyone on here?
That's why I never bother anyone in here
cuz I could just go out and try with someone.
So that's my my logic, bro. Like
I just go out and find someone.
Look at what happened with N.
Look at N. I look at Monty. Yeah.
Imagine no one knew Natalie G and she
was off this community. Imagine, bro.
No one would be able to get involved
with anything. You understand?
What? Anyways, she's always going to do
the same thing. But
I don't know why she's emailing to me.
Like, what the [ __ ] am I supposed to do
about it, bro?
It's like what I told you about that
Lord J, bro. Like, there's certain
things that don't make sense. And I'll
keep it real with you. There certain
It's like him, right? I told you this on
when I spoke to you the last time. I
said to you like he does not make any
sense. He claims he gets all this money.
He has it for life. Yeah. They sat on
YouTube begging losers for money. It
doesn't add up. Do you understand?
Some people they don't make they don't
make sense on here.
You understand, bro? Yeah.
He doesn't make any sense.
And he's simp. Bro,
no, no, no. I What he's doing does not
make no sense, bro.
I It doesn't make sense because if it
made sense, I would understand it. Think
about it, bro. You're getting all of
this money a month, right? Three grand,
three half grand. Say you're getting
that money a month. Why would you
swallow up your pride and beg for an
extra £150 a month? It doesn't make
sense. That's why I don't understand it.
It doesn't make sense, bro. I would
never take I would never take money from
anyone on this community. I'll never beg
anyone for money. I don't want no one's
[ __ ] money. The only reason you would
be doing that, bro, is if you're skin.
That's the only logical thing it would
it would be. Yeah.
So he doesn't that doesn't makes no
sense what he does.
But like that's on you, bro. But I don't
speak to anyone online.
I don't speak to anyone online, bro. I
keep it real with you. No Instagram. I
don't speak to anyone because it would
just annoy me, bro. Like when I used to
go on these dating apps, it used to
annoy me that like
what if they don't reply back? You can't
really stand out. They've got so many
options. I don't [ __ ] with it, bro. I
tell you, the last time I went on these
dating apps, I'll be honest with you,
was back in January when people was like
too skinned to go out. But
no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no. The difference
is the difference is right he probably
made millions and millions and millions
from them donations. Lord J is not
making millions and millions and
millions a month. So to swallow your f
pride and to beg for an extra tiny bit
of money. Sorry, I should have rephrased
that as well. Right? If you're making
loads and loads and loads and loads and
loads listen, let me let me explain this
to you, right?
You know this merch [ __ ] what these
YouTubers do, KSI, a lot of them, right?
They are making millions and millions
and millions and millions and millions
and millions from it. So, it does make
sense for them to do it. But he is
making which is why I said £150 extra a
month. It does not make sense.
Yeah. When Donald Trump is asking for
donations, he's going to make millions
and billions. Lord J is not making
millions and billions. It all points to
being skin. That's this is what I'm
saying to you.
Okay. Put it this way. Right.
You know my circumstances now. Do you
think I would start begging for an extra
£200 a month?
Listen. Okay. Okay. Okay, let let me let
me let me let me put this let me put
this to you now. Right. Do you think I
would need to be begging on YouTube for
an extra £200 a month? No. So, if I'm
putting myself in that position and it's
not a business because all of the people
that follow him or skin, so he doesn't
even make anything from it. So, that's
another thing. It's it's not even a
business because all of the people that
are watching him are not donating
because they've got nothing.
So that it's not even a business. It's
literally like he is scraping
and doing anything for an extra bit of
income. Not that he's doing it as a
business. So yes, I do understand
business, but that's not what he's doing it for.
That's what I'm trying to say, but I
don't think you understand it, my man.
So, so you get three grand a month,
right? And you'll beg for an extra £200
a month. That makes sense, isn't it?
Yeah, that makes sense.
That makes a lot of sense, don't it? Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. Yeah. Because cuz if you get
three grand a month, Yeah. you would beg
for an extra £200 a month, but it
wouldn't be worth my time.
I wouldn't be doing Uber if I stole
three grand a month. It doesn't add up to anything.
So you would swallow your Yeah, but it's
not for free though. But the difference
is it's not for free. It's It's not for
free. He's begging. He is literally
begging for money. So it's not for free.
That's the whole point is it it's not for free.
You understand? It all points to him
being about £400 a month. I'm telling
you, bro. I've done business. I know
these things. It all points to him being
on that skid benefit money a month.
Every month. That's all it points to. It
It's all it points to, bro. It don't
point to no three grand a month.
It doesn't It doesn't point to anything.
But he skinned. That's the only thing it
points to, bro. Sorry you don't like to
hear it, but
cuz you won't be begging.
He's not even
He's not even begging. See, with the big
YouTubers, they knew they'd make money from it.
They knew. Listen, listen. Right. If I
was getting three grand a month. Yeah.
And they said, "Oh, yeah. If you bring
out some merch, we'll give you an extra
five grand a month." I'll be like, "Fuck
yeah, bro. An extra five grand a month."
The whole point is these people knew
they would make billions. These people
knew they would make millions just like
the prime drinks. They knew that they
would actually make money
and whatever they say people would do
cuz they're big YouTubers. That's the
difference. That's that's the difference
that you're not getting. You know,
why would you need to risk your pride
for £200 a month? You're You're
literally putting your pride on the line.
It all points to being skin, bro.
It all literally points to being skinn. Really does.
It really really [ __ ] does. Yeah.
I only had that Uber thing cuz I went on
the same money every month. So,
but all we know is he's [ __ ] scared, mate.
But yeah, you do you, bro. If you want
to speak to [ __ ] online, that's you,
bro. I'll never speak to any [ __ ] on
the internet, bro. [ __ ] that. I don't
speak to [ __ ] on the internet.
None of them. It's straight up number
message dub. You know, it's so bad. I
don't even have like
I don't even have Instagrams. It's only
Snapchat and numbers. I don't even [ __ ]
with that, bro. I like something that's
like proper encrypted. You know what I
mean? Something that's proper encrypted. Oh, [ __ ]
So yeah, man.
But you need to you you need to pack all
this [ __ ] in, bro.
Like I said, it's been going on for
years with you lot. Yeah.
When's it going to end, bro?
When is it going to end? Huh?
Well, why don't you join the hangouts,
LT, and put your camera on?
Jane does it. I'll do it. [ __ ] I don't
give a [ __ ] bro.
They're not going to find you from your face, man.
They ain't going to find you from your face.
Think about it, bro. They're not going
to find you from your face, man. Come on. Yeah.
They're going to find you from your
face, bro. Come on. Yeah.
You know what, Alie? You're just a
[ __ ] troll, bro. I can't even take
you serious. You're just a troll, bro.
Yeah, you're just a troll in it. You're
You're just a troll in it.
Yeah, you're just trolling, bro. Stop it, man.
Stop trolling, bro.
You're a [ __ ] troll, bro.
All right. Why are you such a troll metal?
Huh? Oh, [ __ ]
No, I wouldn't I wouldn't I wouldn't
[ __ ] I don't [ __ ] with me. I wouldn't
[ __ ] with me, bro, if I was you out
here. I'm not the one, bro.
Don't even try it with me, bro. I'm not the one.
I'm not the one, bro.
I'm not the one, bro. Yeah,
I'm not the one. Imagine saying that to someone
because I want to, bro.
Is that any of your business?
Why are you flirting with people on
[ __ ] Why are you flirting with people on [ __ ] YouTube, bro? Huh?
I like Peppa Pig.
I'm not breaking the law. I can watch
what I want,
you know. I like Peppa.
I like all the little characters. What's
that got to do with you?
You dirty [ __ ] Oh [ __ ] Yeah.
So, yeah, man. Anyways,
how long ago was these messages as well?
How long ago was these messages?
That's what we need to know. How long
ago was these messages, bro? And there's
a reason I'm asking. Hold on. Hold on.
How long ago was these messages?
Yeah. So, bro, at the end of the day,
Yeah. So, you were still talking about
meeting even though you knew she was
clapped. Remember? Yeah. She's a
catfish. Yeah. And you were still trying
to meet her. It doesn't make sense, bro.
You would have still met her. You were
still going along with it. So, at the
end of the day, in You knew she was clapped.
One, hold on a minute. But you knew she was clapped. So
that doesn't really make any sense, bro.
You like the thing is now last month.
Yeah. You can't even come on here now
and start saying, "Oh, she's this, she's that, bro."
If it's been after because then you'll
just contradict yourself.
Can't you just block the [ __ ]
Just block the [ __ ] and just don't talk
to her again. End of
Bless you, LT.
You'd do anything for the pun, wouldn't you?
You would do anything for the pun tang. Bless you.
Yeah, they email me as well. Yes, they
Ley you just sat there picking your moment. Uh
yeah, I'll tell you about this over
there. Yeah, but you find it funny.
That's why I don't even That's why I
don't even give this is why I don't give
this LT advice anymore.
I don't give this LT advice anymore because
he just um he just finds everything funny.
He just finds everything funny. Yeah. Yep.
I think you don't need to pack it in. That's
I think you lot need to [ __ ] pack it in now
before I call the old bill. If you two
don't stop it, I'm going to call the
boys in blue. H
I'm going to call a poison player. Yeah, mom.
A proper mail.
That's funny. That is
It's the football next week, Nicolo.
Yeah, football next week, mate.
Football next week.
What a joke. E,
but L2 just thinks it's all funny.
LT just thinks it's all funny. Don't you?
Yeah. Ali thinks it's all funny, don't you?