There you go.
only going live cuz Monty wanted me to go live.
Don't have time for this [ __ ]
[ __ ] place anymore for the repeating people.
See one is coming on. What the
[ __ ] Sorry, dude.
Why are you coming on? Yo
>> yo, one minute. Let me go outside. Yeah,
>> I'm leaving this place. Going to walk
home. Can't be waiting around now. >> Yeah. [ __ ]
>> Yeah, I just can't be bothered anymore
with this, bro.
>> No, but I can't either.
>> I just just don't see the point in it anymore, bro. >> Yeah,
>> you stop coming on. You stop coming on
as well, is it?
>> I can't be asking YouTube anymore.
Hang on. I'll be right back. I'll be
You hear me? Yes. Yeah. Yeah. I'd be
Yeah. money go live. So, [ __ ] it.
I don't have time for this
[ __ ] place anymore
with these repeating [ __ ]
Yeah, Monty man's in hospital.
He was going to um he was trying to get himself sectioned.
That's the only reason I'm on it at
least. So I don't come on here anymore.
I'm not interested in shitty YouTube anymore.
It's only cuz money man wanted me to go
live cuz he's having issues with
Natalie. I thought [ __ ] it. I'll just go
go live. But I'm not interested in this
place anymore, Lisa.
Because I I go by evidence, right?
He'll tell you when he when he comes on.
I I go by evidence, right, Lisa? Like
these people sit here all day saying
that you're this, you're that, but
they're the ones sat on YouTube all day.
So, it must be them talking about
themselves. That's all I need to say,
bro. And carry on living my life.
Apparently, uh, she split up with him,
so he he's been cutting himself.
He said I was allowed to say it. So, yeah.
I don't know. Money man. Yeah. >> Yeah. Blood pressure.
>> Say again.
>> Just let them take my blood and that
>> this is the sport workers fault. All
this. No one knows nothing. Not even
Lisa knows anything. I'm not saying
nothing as well cuz
>> Yeah. Yeah. I know. I know.
I can tell Lisa cuz it's her daughter,
but Lisa will have to ring me. But this
better not get put on YouTube.
>> Yeah, I give Lisa my number so I can
ring and tell Lisa what's going on cuz
it's her daughter.
One sec. Be right back. Yeah. My man.
She said that she's got your number.
You're crazy about the over woman, bro.
No woman could ever get me like that,
bro. You're mad.
Not now. I mean, not now, obviously. You know, [ __ ]
You're crazy, Monty. You're crazy, mate.
I always knew you was a big softy.
I always knew you was a big softy, lad.
But yeah, Lisa, that's the evidence that
I go by. Like they sit here every day
call you skin.
Well, they're the ones sat on YouTube
all day, so they must be skin.
You know what I mean, Lisa? That's my
logic. That's my logic.
Uh, I just went live because Monty man
wants me to go live cuz he's having some problems.
I don't have time for this place anymore, bro.
Just repeating place. I'm done with it.
It's the same people every day. Same
repeating people every day. Same atmosphere.
I bought uh Call of Duty Black Ops 2. It
was on sale.
Can't beat Black Ops 2, bro.
I'm [ __ ] constantly hungry, man. All
I do is eat, you know. Lisa, eat, eat,
eat, eat, eat.
I'm not back, mate. I've only gone live
cuz Monty man wanted me to go live. He's
having some um home troubles. So
yeah, I'm not back. [ __ ] Am I [ __ ]
back? [ __ ] that. [ __ ] repeating
people in it, Lisa. [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] you doing this eater, man.
I'm about to go Thailand
early, Lisa. The flights cost me £770.
I'm [ __ ] off.
I was watching these videos on Instagram
in America where they're like
approaching women and [ __ ]
Oh, I hate it, man. I hate watching it.
It's [ __ ] annoying, bro. Even when
it's not happening to me, it's gotten
worse. I thought, "Fuck this. I'm leaving."
>> What else do I need doing?
>> What else do you need to do?
>> [ __ ] that.
>> Excuse me.
I'm going to walk home in a minute. I'll
be out of
>> I'm on an office of [ __ ] Birmingham, mate. in Birmingham. >> Yeah.
>> [ __ ] Monty, bro.
Can't be doing that over a woman, lad.
You think a [ __ ] woman would ever get
me like that? Never, bro. Not again.
I I wouldn't care how much I like them
or how much I love them, bro.
[ __ ] that. No way, bro. You're mad.
I had someone [ __ ] with me a few
times over there. I don't give a [ __ ]
about them, bro. No way.
This This must be Monty's um Monty's first love.
Got to be, bro. It has to be, isn't it?
cuz it can't have happened before cuz
you would know.
cuz I know what they're about. They're
[ __ ] just predictable [ __ ] time
wasters, which is the whole point of me
leaving this country.
Wanted to leave. You know what I mean,
bro? So, I kind of expect the [ __ ] they
do now. You know,
>> it wasn't Natalie's fault. It wasn't
Natalie's fault. So, now it's totally different.
>> No, no, no. I'm not saying it is. I'm
not. I'm just saying
fault. Not Natalie. No,
>> not interested. Ste, I'm not interested.
this country. I ain't interested
anymore. We're beyond that now.
I didn't go out yesterday. I didn't go
out last week. We're beyond this. We
We're beyond We're beyond that now.
Beyond that. I was watching this guy in
America approach. I was watching like a
few of these guys approaching Lisa and
it's really bad in America as well.
Lisa, I'm not saying nothing to you to
be honest with you because you do your
own daughter's address. This is
partially your fault, Lisa. Remember
that. This is partly your fault because
you do your own daughter's address out there. So
if you didn't do Natalie's address
leaves there, then none of this would have happened.
Money, if you don't come off this [ __ ]
you're gonna you're gonna die, bro.
>> I am coming off a P. It's not worth it.
It's not worth it. Really not.
>> So, what happened? Was she was on
YouTube? I I still don't actually
understand it, bro.
>> Lisa, you are to blame. You're the one
who blocks your daughter's address.
You're the one who gave all these people
on YouTube your daughter's address to
send these videos out to these sport
workers and everything else off your own
daughter. This is your fault.
Yo, make sure someone clips it. Lisa, it
is your fault. You're the one who put
your daughter's address all over
YouTube. You're the one who destroyed
your own daughter's life by doing that.
And then you sitting there saying, "No,
me. It's my fault." Yeah, it's your
This is why I'm not saying nothing to
you, Lisa. Nothing to you at all. What's
happened with me and Natalie? Yeah,
you you you've messed your daughter's
head up and you messed my head up, too, Lisa.
>> Madness, bro. It's really mad.
>> Lisa is not allowed at the property. Oh,
these all your clothes are going as
well. And the
>> No, no, no.
>> Yeah. So, we're kind of beyond that now.
Stephen Howard, as I was saying, in
America, it seems really bad there now.
Lisa, as well, in America,
America seeming really bad for it as
well. Not likely Lisa. You makes me feel
suicidal, you know. All it's your fault.
All of it.
Don't worry, Monty.
Just come to London and and um spend a
few nights with me. Monty,
why don't you come down come down and
spend a few nights with me, bro? You
like it down here?
>> No, I won't, bro. I need to save money
now. I booked to go. I've booked to go.
I can't afford it. I I need to save. I
won't, bro. I won't.
>> Especially after seeing that [ __ ] in
America, bro. [ __ ] that.
>> No, you know what? Yeah, GT's [ __ ] my
life up. Yeah, it's [ __ ] everything
>> address body. And it's not [ __ ] my
life up either. >> What?
>> It's [ __ ] my life up, too.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I know. Not that. Um, the
thing is they even want to talk to Lisa about it.
>> Lisa wants to come in. Lisa wants to
>> If she comes in, I'm going. I can't be
out with her, man. You're not knowing
anything from me. Nothing.
>> Well, you don't want to talk to her now.
>> No, I don't [ __ ] want to talk to her.
No, do I?
>> Well, you try and bury the hat [ __ ] bro.
>> I buried the hat [ __ ] She docked her
own daughter's address. She's ruined
basically my relationship because of
YouTube by doxing her address.
She doesn't even understand what she's
actually done to her young daughter. She really doesn't.
You see his f daughter up truly.
No one even knows what's going on. I'm
not saying nothing. It's nothing to do with anybody.
>> I'm not even telling because
>> what can you just be civil with each other?
>> I'm not being civil with Lisa. No, man.
Not what she's done to her daughter. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> No, I'm going to walk on.
>> Yeah, I booked Thailand Slim. It cost me
£770. I booked it yesterday, bro. I
thought, "Fuck this." Who's this?
Someone a clown. What the [ __ ] is that, bro?
>> Yeah, Lisa can go live all she wants.
And she doesn't know what's going on.
She has no idea what's happening.
>> What the [ __ ] going on? I'm I'm I'm
[ __ ] joker. I'm here to suck your
dicks. [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Weirdo. Bye-bye.
>> Yeah. Same. I booked it, bro. [ __ ] Sorry, bro.
>> [ __ ] I'm not getting myself sectioned.
At least in mine. I'm a [ __ ] I'm going
to win. I'm not getting myself sectioned.
>> It was always going to come to that
money though, ain't it? Someone's going
to get hurt or section. It was always
going to come to that though if you
stayed on it. You knew it.
>> What PDF?
>> You knew it was going to come to it
though. It like hurt or sectioned.
>> I knew that me and that weren't going to
last anyways to be honest with you. I
knew that from the start to be honest.
>> Slim, I had to do it for a better life,
bro. It's I can't continue like going
around in circles all my life. I had to
do it, bro. That's why I booked it, you
know, cuz I was watching this guy in
America, a few a few guys in America
doing these whizzes on Instagram and
they were getting the same [ __ ] in
America as well, bro. And it was just
pissing me off just watching it. It just
annoys me watching it. Even when it's
not happening to me, I thought, "Fuck
this. I'm out of here." So,
yeah, it gets to a point where you're
like, "Fuck me, bro." Like, this has got
to stop, you know?
Why don't you come on YouTube?
>> Money, why don't you come and meet me, man?
>> I'm going on. I'm working on
you like it down here, son. You never
have to go out. Yeah, I'm just going to
go out for a sig. My phone's charging in
my bag. I'm going to take my bag outside
and have a sigy outside going on. >> Yeah.
>> Black Ops 2. I was I was playing Black
Ops 2 on Xbox One. >> What?
>> I was playing Black Ops 2 on Xbox One.
You know, Black Ops 2.
>> Well, yeah.
>> Yeah. It cost me $11.99. I was playing
it online, bro. I love [ __ ] I love
Black Ops 2. It's my favorite one.
>> What was your What was your favorite
Call of Duty?
>> Call of Duty World of War Five.
>> Yeah, I like Black Ops 2. That was my
favorite, bro. Nuke Town.
>> Nuke Town. Yeah. [ __ ] it. I'm
not You're getting for [ __ ] this,
man. I'm a [ __ ]
What the [ __ ] am I playing at?
>> You're money. You're going to end up
dead if you don't come off YouTube.
>> I am. I'm a stupid [ __ ] I'm a stupid bastard.
Natalie, I mean, Lisa, I don't know why
you give out your daughter's [ __ ] on
YouTube. This is all your fault. Literally.
>> All right, Morty. I want you to know
you [ __ ] Sort yourself. Who is it?
>> Rose in it. >> Yeah,
>> I'm walking. I've got an hour and 35
minute walk. An hour and a 35 minute
>> Bless your body if you're in love.
>> I am. I love Natalie. I [ __ ] love her, man.
>> She doesn't understand how much I love
her. Even though I am a [ __ ] up and I am
a [ __ ] up, you know.
>> God bless you.
>> No, I'm just saying I do [ __ ] up. Men do [ __ ] up,
you know. I I didn't
This would have happened if the address
didn't get docked.
>> You know what I mean? Cuz no one knew
where no one knew where we was living.
>> Lisa opened her [ __ ] mouth.
>> Don't matter how much me and Lisa was
arguing that day. That was Lisa's fault.
Why that happened is because Lisa went
live started slagging me off live when
she's supposed to like me and when she
went live she's slagging me off and me
and Natalie seen it and then fell out
>> just come to just come to London buddy
I'll make you a piggy sandwich bro it's
hard to get laid over there >> huh
>> it's hard to get laid
>> yeah but [ __ ] who gives a [ __ ] about
that bro we'll go to Thailand ever.
>> No, I'm happy with Natalie. Even though
Natalie, I'm still trying with N.
>> Yeah, London's for
>> I do love her. I'm not just saying that.
I've never ever felt like this for
anybody in my life.
>> God bless you then.
>> Never. Not even for Kayie. I I even told
my mom today I've never loved anyone
like I I bet I I I bet I can make you
fall in love with my piggy sandwiches though.
>> Money, bro. >> Yeah,
I'm sneaking off. Oh, me on big PJ. Put
>> money. Me and you eating piggy
sandwiches. Do you know what piggy sandwich is?
>> I'm going the wrong way.
>> You know what it is? It's a bacon sandwich.
>> Yeah. Some pigs in a blanket in it.
>> I can get arrested for this, you know.
>> Well, bless you then, Monty.
>> I couldn't believe you was crying earlier. Bless.
>> Of course. Of course. I've been crying
all week. I've been crying.
>> Don't worry, Peter. Peter Belly's here
for you. I'll be your shoulder to cry on.
>> It's not that. And the sport workers the
sport workers are going mad. They asking
for Lisa's numbers. It's not like Lisa.
Yeah. If PJ stays live, wait till I get
back home. Yeah. Lisa, I'll show you the
front room. All your clothes are being
packed up in the front room getting
ready to go to [ __ ] a charity shop.
Monty. So, bro, listen. So, the reason I
don't go with him anymore yet, I'll tell
you the real reason. Yeah. So, you know
when these people call me Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> when they say your skin, you're this,
you're that. I'm I'm not saying that
they're this. I'm not saying they're
that. I'm showing everyone that they're
the ones that can't get off of YouTube.
So, then it must be them. Do you get it?
>> No. At least can't get off YouTube. I
I'm I'm a fake bastard for coming back on YouTube.
>> Yeah, I am. But only way I come back on
YouTube is cuz I was angry.
I was angry because
I'm sick of getting kicked out of places
>> over women. I don't like being shouted at
>> the women.
>> It's because of what I was going through
with Kaye, the abuse with her. >> Yeah.
>> And plus getting kicked out included
of the hotel and because I got kicked
out of Kis all the time.
>> It just brings it all back,
>> you know. Why?
>> That's why I went live and I told
everybody that me and Natalie was in the
hotel, but we didn't say where we were.
I told everybody that that we was in Manchester.
>> Bless you then, bro. Bless you.
>> I'm going to get in [ __ ] for this. I'm
walking home. I just walked out of the hospital.
>> Hey, Monty, I remember when you was with
Yeah. You was with Kaye and then Natalie
used to want to meet me. Do you
remember? But I never met her in it.
>> Yeah. Then then Lisa wanted to meet me.
>> Yeah, it's weird, isn't it?
>> Yeah, Lisa wanted to meet me. You wanted
to meet Natalie.
>> O you, [ __ ] you prick.
>> Timmy, I'll [ __ ] meet you now, you
little sad little man. Walk to me now,
you little [ __ ] sad man. Walk to me
now. I'm out of the streets, you sad
man. You [ __ ] fle
your face for [ __ ] you [ __ ] head. Oh, [ __ ] >> look. Kick him.
>> Yeah. Well, yeah. I didn't know. I
didn't even know it was him. I didn't
even know it was him. I didn't even know
it was him, bro.
>> I didn't even know it was him, bro. He
didn't come in his real account, bro.
>> Okay. Meet me now, Timmy.
I'm [ __ ] I'll turn my camera around
so you can see why.
>> Oh, [ __ ] I didn't even know it was him.
He come on a different account, bro.
Yeah. Keep it on big ear. Kick,
put me on. Yeah, kick me on big yard.
Turn my camera.
>> You saw that screenshot I showed you
earlier. It was the same [ __ ] in it.
>> It's all the same [ __ ] in here.
>> You [ __ ] with it, bro.
>> You want to meet me? Yeah. I show you
where I am. I just need to keep
following the S now. Oh, here you here's
the street sign for you, Timmy. So, I'm
so right here, Timmy.
So, I'm here.
>> Be careful, Monty. They don't call it
old be it.
>> No, they can't. They can. They really
They really can. I don't have nothing on
me anyways. I've quit weed. I don't
smoke weed no more.
>> I don't have nothing on me. Just roll up.
[ __ ] idiots. Like I need to grow up.
I need to get my ass off YouTube.
>> That's why I stop coming on it, bro. I'm
only on it now cuz you you said to go
live. I wouldn't be on it, bro.
>> Live still.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. [ __ ]
>> But I need to I need to grow up. I need
to sort myself out because at the end of
the day, yeah, I'm [ __ ] my whole life up.
>> Yeah. Like going on YouTube. I can't
help it. It's my disability. Yeah. I've
got a [ __ ] mental disability. I've
got HD spectrum of autism where I get
angry and I can't help myself to do things.
>> Yeah. I mean, it's hard for me.
>> And like I said, bro, we'll get our own
we can find another community. We could
start our own community, bro. I was
saying this to you earlier. Like, we
don't need to be on this [ __ ]
>> It doesn't matter if you're in a new
community or not. It's not you, it's these people.
>> They can't find me. They haven't found
Monty. I've got another channel that
they don't know about that I go on.
Do you get me?
>> Yeah. Yeah, I do get you. I do get you.
But is it worth it, PJ? It's social media.
>> I hate these people, money. That's why I
stopped coming on it. I hate these people.
>> Yeah, I do as well. I I can't stand
them. They're [ __ ] They ain't got no
lives. None of them have.
>> That's why I don't bother with it. >> Yeah.
>> [ __ ] her own daughter's life up and that
>> like literally she [ __ ] her own
daughter's life up.
>> You don't watch RJ anymore, is it? I
don't watch anybody on this community anymore.
I don't like anyone on here. This is why
>> I don't I don't I don't The only one I
like on here is unworthy clock.
>> I did like Kisa. I really did like Kisa.
You know, I'm looking right to Lisa as well.
>> Tell them how much I do love Natalie
because I do love her.
>> But obviously I [ __ ] up. Like
obviously you do in relationships, you
[ __ ] up. Obviously, relationships they do fix.
>> They're not coming in.
>> What do these people actually know about
Natalie? Nothing. Because they haven't
told him nothing. You know what I mean?
Only what these people know. Is
Natalie's at home.
>> All right. Monty on Worthy Clock's a good guy.
>> Who's that?
>> It's Timmy's friend, but he doesn't get
involved with any drama. He doesn't get
involved with anything, bro. He's
>> ringing. I'm ringing. I'm ringing. Hang
on. It's the It's the doctors. Hello. >> Hey.
>> Yeah. Speaking.
>> Hi, Jamie. It's one of the nurses
calling from good home.
>> Yeah, I've I've gone. I've walked off. I
can't do it. I I just can't do it. And
>> can't do what, darling.
>> Talk about my dis talk about my stuff.
>> Someone's going to get sexy, bro. I can
see it. I can actually see it, bro.
Who Who's that you with?
>> Oh, just I'm talking to a mate on the phone.
>> Okay. Um, so the only problem I've got,
are you going to come back?
>> I don't want to come back to be honest
cuz I don't really want to get set.
>> How long will I be there? Cuz I've also
got to walk back home as well.
>> Madness. I got mad.
>> I got someone else is ringing me.
>> Someone else keep talking.
>> Yeah. P. Yeah, someone keeps ringing me
as well. I've got two phones.
>> The only problem that I've got is I'll
probably have to phone the police for you. >> Why? >> Yeah.
>> Because you haven't been seen by the
doctor or anything yet. And because of
what you've come in with come back
not to talk to you.
I might get session
back. We'll get the doctor to have a
word with you.
>> I'm coming back now.
>> I've got in a minute. >> Hello.
>> Yeah. Yeah, it's Jeremy.
>> I'm calling from home. >> Yeah.
>> Wondering where you are.
>> Oh, I walked out. I walked out. I got to
go back. They told me to go back.
>> Who told you to go back?
>> The doctors because they said they're
going to get the police if I don't go back.
>> What do you mean?
>> I don't Who's they speaking? Sorry.
>> The about the um
>> Oh, just one of the nurses rung me cuz I
was just going to walk home cuz I don't
really want to go through this like talk
about my my elf and stuff like that. I
don't really want to, but I have no choice
or else I'm just going to get arrested.
>> Are you coming back?
>> Yeah, I'm coming back.
>> Okay. Where are you?
>> Um, I'm around the corner on the street.
>> Please come back cuz Yeah, we will have
to call the police to bring you back.
>> Yeah, I'm on my way back now.
>> All right, give me 15 minutes.
>> All right, then.
>> Thank you. Bye. Bye. >> Bye.
For [ __ ] sake, like
>> you need to [ __ ] hack this in, bro.
>> I do. Don't know. This is [ __ ]
remember when we used to make jokes about it.
>> Monty, do you remember when we used to
make jokes of it? About it?
>> What about us getting sectioned? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Look what's happening.
This is gay as [ __ ]
>> You think it's funny?
>> I don't think anything's funny. I don't
even know where the doctor is now. I'm
[ __ ] lost. You know what? I might
They can get the police. I might just
keep I might just walk just keep walking.
>> Yeah, but you know if the police come,
the police will section you. That That's
who section you. You know that is the
police. If they call the police, they
they section you. You know that it.
>> Oh man, this is [ __ ] Lisa's fault. This man.
Why did she [ __ ] dox her own
daughter's aggress? Why?
Cuz she's anable old [ __ ]
Oh my god.
I don't police at least now.
>> I remember being in love Steven Howard.
You remember? Uh
>> I am in love. I'm in love with Natalie.
Completely in love with her.
You know Natalie's got a good lad. I
just make mistakes.
That's it. Like every [ __ ] is good.
Do you remember Stephen Hardwood when I was uh
>> I don't know whether you ought to be too late.
>> Sad times.
>> For [ __ ] sake.
>> No, Tim, you're not getting a link. Timothy,
[ __ ] off. Timothy Aldridge.
This is gay as [ __ ]
Why have you
saying he's going to make my life hell, Monty?
Timmy's life's already like hell.
>> [ __ ] hell.
>> Jimmy ain't even got a [ __ ] life.
All the big man on YouTube acting as
[ __ ] knows where I am. Come and meet
me now to me.
>> Then it would be bad, wouldn't it,
Stephen? How would it be [ __ ] bad?
>> Bring more money Mike too if you want to me.
This is getting as [ __ ] There's the hospital
for [ __ ] sake.
>> Yeah, I had to book it, Slim, cuz I just
realized it's never going to change here.
So, I had to do it, bro. I had to. I
can't I couldn't I couldn't live
depressed forever here. I want to do
what Ant-Man done. You know, Ant-Man
Ant-Man's motivated me.
>> Can't believe they [ __ ] threatened me
with the police to go back.
>> There's never going to change here,
Slim. It's obvious.
>> PJ, stay alive. Yeah. And it'll be back on. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, man.
>> I tell you from what goes on now
[ __ ] shitty hospital.
Let me know how it goes. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Stay alive. Stay alive with the back.
I'm [ __ ] getting there first.
>> Yeah, man.
>> [ __ ] you now.
>> Yeah. So, I had to book him.
>> I've had enough.
I'm scared now. Like lally scared about this [ __ ]
>> Don't be scared.
>> I'm getting sectioned, lad.
I'm being self [ __ ] aring.
>> Does anyone know about that Charlie Vel?
>> I'll be back in a bit. Yeah, PJ. Stay
alive, buddy. Stay alive.
>> Yeah, man.
>> Yeah, I had to book the Thailand thing, bro, because
it's just obvious it's never going to
change here. And [ __ ]
I was, like I said, I was watching this
guy in America, Monty, interrupting me
and he was doing these approaches and he
was getting the same thing. I've got a
boyfriend. I was like, "Fuck this, bro.
This is annoying me just like listening to it."
So, um, I just booked Thailand for [ __ ]
this. You only live once. I can't live
like this. It's [ __ ] depressing.
Yeah, that YouTuber. Yeah.
I I went by the logic, right? I went I
went by a few things. cuz I was like,
listen, if anything was going to change,
it would have changed by now. This has
been going on for years.
You got 13 numbers last week. You don't
have a date. It's still It's been
happening for years. It's only getting
worse and it continues to happen. So
then I was like, "Fuck, I'm I'm out of
it. I got nothing to lose."
So, and obviously I'm in the 1% who
tried. So, if anything was going to
change, it would have already changed by
now. It's [ __ ] depressing, mate. You
know, so I was like, "Fuck this. I'm
looking. I'm I'm looking. I'm going out
of there, bro.
Not staying in this country deal with
this [ __ ] I've already dealt with this
[ __ ] from enough enough years, you know,
and and to be fair,
Antman motivated me as well. So,
how many more years are you going to
keep dealing with that shit?" You know
what I'm saying? Slim
and that's Yeah, I ain't been out for a
while, bro. I ain't been out for a
while, to be honest.
Think I'll ever go out again, bro.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] boring, bro.
You got that to look forward to now. Yeah.
Black Ops 2.
I should have went years ago to be
honest. Two, three years ago.
Nah, I'm going Philippines as well. I'll
be going Philippines. And they're actual
people that actually want relationships as well.
You can't be here all your life dealing
with this [ __ ] bro. There has to be a
cut off point where you think to
yourself like, "Nah, man. This is ridiculous.
These games, these just attitude like
it's never going to change in this country.
You know what it makes? It makes me
laugh when people think it's going to
change when it's never going to change.
It's laughable, bro.
They're only lying to themselves. Really?
Hope money man's okay. Yeah.
Timmy, you're [ __ ] I was just going
to give you the link, but you're [ __ ] Yeah.
You don't know what women like. You've
never had a woman. Stop being a s. You
would know what women like. You've never had one.
Wow. It makes me laugh, right? How you
get these people on YouTube don't know
anything about women. They're just in denial.
They're lying to themselves. I mean, no.
No, they're not in denial cuz they know
the truth. They're just lying. Oh,
you're engaged. Oh, Kusha. Uh, you don't
know anything about women, bro. I was
watching this guy in America and he was
doing approaches and he was get the same
old [ __ ] I have a boyfriend. I have a
boyfriend. You know, the thing is, yeah,
I I actually thought, yeah, if you went
to America, I actually thought it'd be easier,
like somewhat easier, but it just seems
worse over there. I was like, oh [ __ ]
they play they do the same [ __ ] as they do here.
any westernized country for you. It's
never going to change. You stay in a
westernized country, it will be the same forever.
They're all the same, bro. Yanks,
[ __ ] English, Australian.
Yeah. You don't know how to get no
woman, bro. You've never had a woman in your life.
I don't care about women either, bro.
I'm I'm not as I'm going Thailand. I
don't give a [ __ ] bro. which made me laugh with
Monty man being like suicidal over
Natalie. Do you think a woman could ever
make me suicidal, bro? And you know,
it's like he's clearly not been in that
situation before. If it's affecting him
now, bro, I know what they're like. I
know the [ __ ] that they do.
Like when I got in 30 numbers and
nothing come of it, I was just like,
"Oh, just England like same old."
Yeah. They just like, "Oh, well, just
England. Same old [ __ ] It never never
going to change."
You know, you didn't see me getting all
pissed off about it. And there was
somebody that I was meeting like several
times. No woman could ever make me like
that, bro. Cuz I know what they do. Once
you know what they do and how they act,
you'd be more surprised if they didn't do that.
You'd be more surprised if they didn't do that.
I'd be more surprised if they didn't.
That's how bad it is. The ghosting, the
[ __ ] around or any anything it is.
Even if you was with them, right? How
long has you been with this Natalie? What? Uh
what? A few months. Like if I was with
someone for a few months, I Oh yeah,
just just England. Like that's I
literally I would expect it. I wouldn't
expect anything anything less from them.
That's like honest. Yeah.
Yeah. You know what they do.
I wouldn't say it's necessarily you
don't feel it fall in love again or you
can't fall in love again. It's more you
know what they do. So you it you expect
that the [ __ ] that these women do
and it will never change. So yeah, man.
And I said, I was saying to Antman as
well, I said the only way it will ever
change is if they ban social media,
which they're not going to do. You go to
Asia or you go to South America.
Unless any of them three things happen,
you're going to constantly be living in a cycle.
And have you ever heard of breaking? I
realized I was in a cycle.
Realize it without realizing it. That
you go out in England, you expect it to
change. It's been going on for years.
It's actually gotten worse. And it's
like, how long are you going to keep
going out and complaining? You, you
know, you can go, you can leave the
country. There are other options.
So yeah, and I was like, I've done the
right thing, I think. So yeah,
so I don't give a [ __ ] about women
anyways. I'm just saying
it would never change in this country ever.
Even itself 13 numbers are not one day.
This trolling is taking it will never
stop. Never ever ever stop.
And we don't deserve it. So, let's go to
another country where we're treated better.
That's that's the thing I went by. So,
Oh, you don't need to you don't need to
give me tips, bro. I've had more women
than you'll ever have. I'm just not in denial.
That's the difference. I'm just not in
denial. You don't need to give me tips.
I already know the tips. Ban social
media. Go to Thailand. go to South America.
I'm not in denial. Just because I'm
stating facts doesn't mean I've never
had a woman. I'm just not in denial.
I've had plenty of women. I'm just not in denial.
That's the That's the difference.
I'm not in denial. You know,
I've had way more women than you have
had sunshine, more than you ever have.
I'm just not in denial.
There's a difference, bro.
You know, you get these guys that lie to themselves.
It's always guys I've never had women
who get women. They they lie to
themselves thinking, "Oh, nah, women
aren't the problem." Nah, no. They're
actually lying to themselves.
Um, they're just lying to themselves.
I mean, Stephen, they're lying to themselves.
Yeah, you're talking about yourself
again, bro. I've had way more women than
you have ever had and will ever have.
I'm just not a simp. I'm not in denial.
That's the difference. Yeah, you're the
one sing. If you really got women, you
would be resorting to sing,
which is basically what you're doing.
Sticking up for women.
I don't get these guys, Steven Howard. I
really never never got him.
Never never did. Never did.
They get no women. They've never had a
woman. Some of them never had a woman.
Some of them don't get women anymore.
They fail with women and they still
defend them. Never. Never got them kind
of guys, bro. Never got them kind of guys.
They're in the situation because of
women, but yet they still defend women.
But deep down they're just lying to themselves.
You know what I'm saying? Yeah. Like I
said, I'll say it for the fourth time
again. I've had more women than you
would ever have and will ever have.
You're a simp. If you was really
engaged, you wouldn't be sat here
defending women. The only people that do
that are people that don't get women.
They defend women. It's [ __ ] madness, bro.
And the only thing is Steven Alard is
when you see these guys approaching,
they're always getting the same [ __ ] It
doesn't matter what guy it is, they get
the same [ __ ] as I as I got when I used
to do it. Same game, same It's literally
like, right, you're talking to an NPC
when when you approach a woman, right?
It's like you're literally talking to a non-playing character.
Once you've met one, you've met them all
because of Tik Tok. There's literally
like not even a point in even trying to
speak to anyone, bro.
Antman got the right idea, bro. He is
very very motivating. Hate him or loathe
him, you know. He's got the He had the
right idea, bro.
Big up Antman. Big up Ant. Big up
Yep. They get the same [ __ ] as well.
And like I said, I don't even like
watching it. It annoys me. Even watching
it annoys me.
The boyfriend [ __ ] it's annoying as [ __ ] bro.
Even when it's happening to other
people, it bores me, bro. Bye-bye.
This is exactly why I don't come on
YouTube anymore as well. Um,
I only went on because Monty Man wanted
me to go on, so I thought [ __ ] it, let
him talk. I won't be on him again, bro.
I can't be bothered with these stealth
projecting weirdos, low lives. you get
to a certain point, you get to a certain age,
um, they just ain't got a life.
There's no point being on here talking
to [ __ ] no lives.
No life [ __ ] baths, you know?
That's why you don't see me on here no more.
Have you noticed you don't see me on
here no more?
Can't be off of it.
They're all [ __ ] idiots. Yeah.
Do you know what Monty man's going through? Yeah.
You reminded me of the whole USA Izzy
thing all over again. Steven Howard. Jesus Christ.
Reminded me of the whole USA thing. Well,
I could be with someone now. I could love them.
And if they love me, I wouldn't care.
I expect it. Sorry.
cuz I know what they do. I was supposed
to meet somebody this Thursday. Was it
this Thursday? Yeah.
Supposed to meet England. Same old
Nothing ever changes here. So, I mean, I
kind of expected it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, man.
Same old England. Yeah.
But yeah, no one could ever make me like that again.
Not after that comfort cuz
it's all about life experience. You see,
back when I was younger,
I didn't expect these things to happen.
And then as you get older, you expect it
to happen because you you realize what they do.
They're all the same. They're all this
Tik Tok [ __ ] Obviously,
that's why it doesn't bother you because
you know what they're about. You know
what they do. But
if I if I went out yet today, for
example, I'd know what would happen,
which makes the whole run out just
pointless. You know what I mean? So, yeah.
Good old USA is he
and he doesn't understand that all of
this crying and all of this they don't
care. They're so sick in their head that
these women don't even care. So
that can't be the first time was Oh Jesus.
That's crazy, bro.
I can't wait to leave now, Lisa.
I honestly can't wait.
I really can't wait. sick. Leave England.
I think it's like I was thinking of
Antman. as I look out for.
Look how far Antman's come
coming off YouTube going Thailand four
times and he's not even put up with half
the [ __ ] I have.
And then I just used him as an example and yeah like
keep doing this [ __ ] you know
cool guy though.
Oh I had to buy a new after shave by the
way. I had to buy new after shave intensive.
Yeah I started on the tenants me
bro. You don't know what I said to the
tenant steel and I said listen [ __ ]
but all you can do is steal people that
have to say behind their back but let me
tell you you'll never steal to my face
two [ __ ] bunchs of [ __ ] I said,
"Listen, I bought a new one. I bought a
brand new one.
A brand new smelly one. Come and steal
to my face. Come and take the piss to my
face. They all shut up then."
Yeah. [ __ ] stuck it on all of them,
bro. And the [ __ ] girl as well. Yeah.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
Yeah, I stuck it on there, bro. I don't
like dirty little beefs.
dirty stinking little [ __ ] thieves, bro. Yeah,
but they go on about black people.
They go on about black people, right? But they're
their religion. They're not supposed to
[ __ ] steal. And then they I hate
people that steal, bro. Like an
aftershave that's that's run its smell.
It was just annoying, bro. And then
someone told this girl and I was like,
"Who's told her?" Cuz someone sold her.
I said, "There's no point starting all
this [ __ ] if you're not going to finish it."
Then they just shut their mouth.
I have to buy a new after save, bro. But
the one that they stole didn't even
smell anymore. It's pointless.
And she was trying to be like, "Um,
we were trying to be funny and shit."
Long story. And I told her, "Get your,"
she said she's going to get her ex on
me. said, "Get your ex on me. I'm not I
don't give a [ __ ] bro." Not scared of your ex.
I'm not scared of your ex, bro. Are you
mad? Bring your ex anytime. I don't give a [ __ ]
I'm so glad I don't have that house
anymore, bro. In many ways, I am. You know,
yeah, you might not get as much money,
but I get enough money. I'm lucky. I
want I hate them, bro.
caused a lot of problems. >> Hello. >> Yo.
>> [ __ ] Yeah, man.
>> What's up?
>> Man, I'm never feeling suicidal again
over a woman, man. I'm not [ __ ]
>> God bless you.
>> Bless you in life.
>> Monty, Lisa and Timmy trying to get in.
Oh, Timmy, [ __ ] up. You [ __ ]
spasticated little [ __ ] Yeah, meet me.
I'm [ __ ] halfway. I'm [ __ ] near
you now, man. You know what hospital I'm at?
So, you're not far from me, mate. So, go
running in your mouth on YouTube like a
little fat old [ __ ] Mr. Tumble you
are and get alive. Did
>> you want to speak to Lisa?
>> No, I do. I thought going to speak to Lisa.
You can if you want.
Let me see what she has to say. Well,
>> [ __ ] toys.
>> I don't give a [ __ ] about you, Lisa. To
be honest with you. Yeah, you got
>> I'm not I'm not in here to speak to I'm
in here to speak to PJ.
>> DJ, go and get a life instead of sitting
on YouTube, please. Sir, I'm [ __ ] 50. Literally. YouTube.
>> How about you get a job?
>> How about what? Get a job. Have you ever
had a lot of people for Saturday, Steven?
Honorable [ __ ] You're the honorable
[ __ ] when you're dodging your own
daughter's address, Lisa.
What these people do, Lisa? You [ __ ]
your own daughter's life up.
>> Yeah, really. So why have you cut yourself? >> Really?
>> Why did you cut yourself up for? Why? >> What?
>> Why have you cut yourself up? Why?
>> That's only your business, Lisa. Why you
so hungry? Hang on. Why did you ask to
speak to me?
>> I didn't I didn't ask to speak to you at
all. I didn't mind. I changed my mind. I
said, "Oh, yeah. Yeah, I said Oh, I told
you. I'm not telling you, sir.
>> I'm not telling you nothing about versus
Lucy. Yeah. At the end of the day
for your daughter.
>> It's almost 300 pound return for 80
pound. Not bad. Sorry.
>> You don't know what's going on.
>> Listen, [ __ ] She's my daughter.
Crackhead. Listen. You're little dirty
crackhead sat on YouTube.
[ __ ] your own paying you rent for you.
>> You can't even pay. >> What?
>> 40 quid a month. You didn't even pay
that, did you, Lisa?
>> What? For the last three months. I don't
even want to be there. And I No, no.
Your daughter paid for all that [ __ ]
>> and then you took your daughter under the bus
will do me good.
>> You're a [ __ ] mom, Lisa. And then you go
around sleeping with your daughter's boyfriends. >> Wow.
>> You can hear it in your voice. You can
hear it in your voice. You're
>> Yeah, of course you not.
>> You slept with
>> her boyfriends will tell you different, will they?
>> Oh, no. No. Because Natalie's
boyfriend's already told Natalie latest
in the argument.
>> Hang on. And have they spoke to her like
since she's accused him? Have they?
>> Listen. Listen, Natalie. Accusing.
Listen. You know what you've done. Police
has said [ __ ] that she doesn't know what
she's on about her brain.
Yeah, just kick her. Yeah,
>> shut the [ __ ] up. Kick her. Get rid of
her. All what she wants to do is talk
about her daughter. What? Who she
doesn't even care about?
>> Yeah. I'm only the one who actually
cares about your daughter, Lisa. What
did say? Do
>> you go back? Yeah,
>> I'm going back now. No,
>> I'm out of the hospital now. Yeah, I'm
[ __ ] out of there now, mate.
>> You know what, Monty? Yeah, there's one
thing I I regret about meeting you.
>> Go on. What's that?
>> [ __ ] introducing me to that nons legs, bro.
>> I never [ __ ] introduced you to Sha
[ __ ] long legs. Don't blaming me for
sha long legs cuz I weren't even his
mate when you met him.
I won't even see any longleged mate back
clip. I I [ __ ] him off a long time ago.
>> Don't know who, but it went through me.
>> [ __ ] weird, bro. It's too weird.
>> This community is [ __ ] weird. You know,
>> that's another reason I That's another
reason because they That's another
reason I left, bro. Cuz they don't leave
you alone. They just don't stop, do they?
>> No. No. I'm not giving these anything
about my life anymore. Nothing.
>> Nothing at all. They don't even know
what's going on. Lisa doesn't even know
what's going on. And this is what what
what I try telling Natalie. No one knows.
>> Hey. Hey, Monty. Monty. Yeah. One
second. Yeah. Um.
>> So, you know when I met you?
>> Yeah. Go on.
>> How long ago was it when you met that [ __ ] virgin?
>> It was Sean. M
>> I think I was about 20.
>> So that was like 5 years ago. That was
like 5 years before you met me.
>> I like in my 20ies. It was early 20s. >> Jeez.
>> Cuz I didn't know you then when I was about 20.
I knew you when I was a little bit older. >> Yeah.
>> Yes. that he's going out with underage
girls on PlayStation, man.
>> Yeah, bro.
>> Yeah. No, man. It's [ __ ]
>> I think a holiday would do you good, man.
>> I think that me and Natalie need to go
another day, a good holiday that. And I
need to stop giving people [ __ ] on
YouTube. In fact, I'm not after least
live. I'm not coming back live ever again. Ever again.
Not at the end of the day. Yeah.
This community is [ __ ] my life up and it's [ __ ] It's just
>> Yeah, but you basically grown up on here.
>> It's no one grow. Yeah, I'm more grown
up than these little clowns either way.
>> No, but I mean like you've basically
grown up on here. Like you was quite you
was a lot younger when you was on here.
when you first come on here like me, we
basically we basically grew up on here.
>> I don't even know how old they were when
they started YouTube. I was only what
I've been on here four, five years.
Five years. Six years I've been on here for.
>> Yeah, man.
>> You know, and there's only one woman who
I do [ __ ] fancy off here, and that's
Natalie. Always will do. Always. I will
always be there for Natalie. Always be
there for her.
Yeah, I can tell you didn't love Kaye
because when you when you broke up, you
didn't care in it.
>> No, I didn't care about it. No, no, no.
I didn't care. I didn't cry. I just
laugh. But Natalie,
>> [ __ ] my eyes out.
>> Bless you.
>> I'm being See, I'm not lying on this
[ __ ] I cried and I've never cried off.
>> I saw you crying. >> Never.
>> You cry. >> Never.
You know, and obviously Natalie
has been in some [ __ ] up relationship.
I've been in some [ __ ] up relationships.
We both been through the basically same.
>> So, I know why Natalie
>> doesn't really have to rust
either way because of the relationships
what she's recently been in. So, I do
understand that. But Natalie can trust me 100%.
I'm not a cheater. I do make mistakes
like every [ __ ] does,
>> you know. >> Yeah, >> mistakes.
>> Mistakes are fixable. I've even quit
weed. I don't smoke weed anymore.
>> This is why I'm probably losing myself
first. Well, because I've quit the weed.
I quit the weed yesterday. I had an
ounce of weed. No lie, a [ __ ] full
ounce of weed. Went down the toilet.
Went down the toilet yesterday.
>> Do you miss it? What? Weed
>> to be honest. No, PJ. I actually don't.
I'm not I'm not getting it.
>> It's not that weed. Weed's [ __ ] up as
well. You know, when you
>> when you smoke weed, you don't have that
brain cells. It [ __ ] your brain cells
up. So, so you can't think straight
>> or you just do what your brain says.
Like my brain told me to go on YouTube
to tell people that we in the hotel and
that cuz Natalie kicked me out the hotel
arguing. Obviously I put that on YouTube
anyways, but I shouldn't have put it up on YouTube, you know. >> Yeah,
>> but I'm sick of getting shouted at both
women. I can't I can't handle it. I
can't I can't do it.
It's because of the the abuse what I
went through with Kaye.
>> Does Kayie still come on YouTube?
>> I don't give a [ __ ] to be honest with
you. She does or doesn't.
>> I don't watch her, so that's what I mean.
I GTA San Andreas is such a good game,
bro. There I've been discovering
glitches on it, you know.
>> Yeah, there is. There is.
What do you want? Xbox.
>> You're on Xbox.
>> You're on Xbox One. San Andreas is a
legendary game, bro.
>> You You played You played all the GTA's.
>> If Lisa wants her claws back, she needs
to hurry up and get her claws back
before they end up going. I'm not
telling her to come and get him, but
they are going to go.
>> So, so money, you can understand why I
was Now you can understand why I was
pissed off when I wanted to go America
over that [ __ ] Now you understand it.
>> Yeah, but I don't threaten women. No,
PG. I'm not threatening Lisa.
>> No, I wasn't threatening. I just wanted
the [ __ ] to come out and say
to my face, bro.
>> No, the thing about women, they do not
understand men. They think, "Oh, believe
me, I understand women completely." So,
Lisa, I know what what you're like 100%.
I know what all women are like. >> Yeah.
>> I'm kind of lost, you know.
Listen, my whole thing is Yeah. If
you're big enough to chat [ __ ] online,
big enough to come out and say to my
face. That's my whole thing, isn't it?
>> You can't be doing that [ __ ] and then
play victim. You know what I'm saying?
You can't be doing that, bro. You know
what I mean?
What do you What do you think?
>> These people won't meet you anyways, PJ.
You're not like 100% yourself, you know.
>> No, I'm speak I'm speaking about that
[ __ ] in in America, Monty. If you're if you're,
you know, making up stuff, then say it
to my [ __ ] face, bro. It won't.
>> Yeah. Yeah. No. No. It's true. It's
[ __ ] go blush. Yeah.
>> Then that's what these [ __ ] do. Then
they play victim on it. You know,
>> they play victim.
>> Yeah. You know what that means? >> Uh >> yeah.
>> No. No. Natalie's different. Natalie
doesn't play a victim. M
think I'm not even talking about it to
be honest with you because that's no
good for me.
>> But when I'll just say it either way,
but when when women get in argue well
some women when they get in argue argue
with you like have like a little
discussion with you or whatever.
Some women can argue with you and not
split up with you.
You know what I mean? Where some women
they argue with you and they can't
handle the arguments. So they they end
it. They just end it. >> Yeah.
>> Get back with you. And then when you
have another argument, they end it
again. It's over. It's end.
>> Yeah. But Mon, you think that's funny
going to another country to confront
someone in it? Yeah. Hey,
>> to be honest with you,
>> I wouldn't I would never ever date
anyone from a from a different country.
>> You think it's funny, though? It
>> I don't think it's funny. No.
>> Well, go to another country to confront someone.
>> No, I don't know. I don't know. I don't
>> You think it's a bit OTT?
It's very OTT.
People valid their money. I'm sure
people have in it.
>> What? Yeah. Obviously people are being
over country center to get a quick old dip away. >> What's
funny as [ __ ] it?
>> Ronnie, when is this [ __ ] Timmy going to stop?
onto Holland Road.
>> I don't know. Same me. He will never
stop. He don't matter if you kick [ __ ]
out the lad or what? He will never stop.
>> He's a bastard in it.
>> Yeah. There's a lot of them in this
community, though. A lot of them. I'm
not in this community. I'm only
>> No, I'm not in it. I'm not in it, Mon. I
only went live for you, bro.
>> Yeah. No, of course. C. [ __ ] I can't
be [ __ ] with it anymore. It's just
repeaters in it.
>> Yeah. Well, Lisa is still there, is she? Ah,
>> no. She's gone now.
>> You used to like Lo J at the start in it.
>> Let Lisa back up if she comes over. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I will.
>> You used to like Lord J it.
>> I've never liked Lord J
>> before like the whole [ __ ] you know.
>> No, no, no. I've never ever like never
liked her. Never ever liked her.
I never liked any of these PJ to be
honest. Once they started, it's not like
Yeah. I shouldn't have joined this
community. It's [ __ ]
I I've never been like this. I quit all this [ __ ] >> Yeah.
>> Obviously, this community got me with
Natalie. Yeah. But when Natalie told me
not to go back on YouTube, I should have
listened to her.
Lisa's Lisa's live apparently.
>> Yeah, leave it to it then.
>> Yeah, you should have listened to her,
bro. Cuz obviously Yeah, you know what
they do it?
>> Yeah. Yeah, I know what they do. But I was angry.
>> I was just angry all that time because
>> my little bones are aching, Steven
Howard. My little arms are aching. My little bones.
>> Have you seen my new form, PJ?
>> No. What is it? a phone.
>> No, it's called um nothing.
>> What do you mean?
>> The phone is called nothing. It's a nothing phone.
>> You never heard of it?
>> Right here. I'll show you there quick. I
jump on this. One sec. I show you now.
>> My little arms are aching. My little
bones. Steen Howard. Oh,
let me back up.
Come on on my phone and you
[ __ ] I'm playing GTA.
>> Put another link up. PJ
>> Steven Howard, is it possible
to win on roulette nowadays?
I don't think you can win on that
anymore, bro. Riged. I hope this
football bet [ __ ] I can do with an
extra [ __ ] £300.
I could do that right now, matey.
Not that I need it, but maybe I might
want to go for a drink. It helps me
cuz it's like [ __ ] £300, isn't it?
I don't need it. I still got my own
money and [ __ ] but still.
Yeah, but online is all bent in it,
Stephen. now with online is all bent.
So you can't even win online. It's all
bent in it.
>> Go me. There you go.
>> They're all bent now, bro.
>> Yeah. This is my phone. Yeah. Watch what
it does when you go on YouTube. It's [ __ ] mint.
>> How much was it?
>> DJ, start talking. >> Yo,
>> start talking. >> Hello.
>> Go on. >> Hello.
See the lights?
>> Yeah. How much was it? >> 500.
>> Yeah. Stephen Hen, I could do this
football bet winning mate cuz I could do the £300
to be honest.
me 500 for some drinks and it all out and that
>> see look when I put music on PG does it
look see it's not happening now talk
>> it's not happening now cuz I've got I've
got you post on
>> pause you let me unpause you right talk >> hello
see there's a
got a phone, isn't it? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. So, it goes by um
So, it goes by um basically if I put a
tune on, I won't put a tune on for long.
It goes with Ste.
>> One second. Steven
is all online rigged now. Or I think all
online roulette is rigged now, is it?
100%. Yeah. Go on, Monty.
>> Yeah. So, if I put a song on
>> I play I play it low so you don't get [ __ ] copyrighted.
So, I put a song on.
>> M go with the beat. >> Okay.
>> So, the lights go with the beat of the music.
>> So, one sec. So, you know I'm So, you
know I'm not on camera. >> Yeah. river.
>> I show you what it look like. It's
proper. I need light. I need light.
>> Let's see if we can see it like this.
There you go. Look at the back of it.
>> Yeah, I see.
>> See? Yeah. Gorgeous phone.
>> Do you want to hang out?
>> Hang out? What do you mean hang out?
Hang out. It
don't know what that means.
>> Yeah, I know what hang out means. Yeah,
I'm going to jump back on this one.
Yeah, cuz I need this one first now to
get me home.
>> Okay, can't
one. Yeah, cuz I need this one now to
get me home.
I'm getting back on now.
It's very rigged online with a it
is very rigged isn't it? Very rigged [ __ ] win. Hello [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm on Google maps me.
>> Hello Monty. That's where I am on Google Maps.
>> Monty, you're rich in it.
>> Rich is not not rich. Rich rich, but got
money. Got a long way to walk. Anyways,
>> you got a lot of money, won't you?
>> A lot of money. I've come up with quite
a bit of money.
>> You have 1,400.
Someone get Lisa. Go and tell Lisa to
come back over here on PGX. On PJ?
>> Yeah. Come and tell her. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Go and get her. Go and tell her.
>> You got You got 1,400.
>> No, I got I come out with just over
Yeah, I come out with just over Well,
just over 2,000.
Yeah, but how though? That's ridiculous.
>> What do you mean? How's it ridiculous?
>> Yeah, but you have to pay housing
benefit in it.
>> No, I don't pay pay housing benefit. Nor
do a [ __ ]
>> Yeah, but there's no benefit that pays over 2,000.
>> Oh, I I get um 700
and something on 700 700 90 on my
>> I get 700
I get 790
on my universal credit.
So up. Yeah.
>> Yeah. So it's about 1.5 1. Yeah. Yeah. 2,000.
>> No, it's 1.5.
Yeah, you Yeah, you're the same as a lot
of people. Yeah, but you not There's no
way it's 2,000, bro. I was about to say,
what the [ __ ]
>> 1.5 or something. No, it's still
>> It's still good anyways. It's still
good, bro. Yeah, it's good, man, bro.
You don't work, so
I get like I get like 1,200, I think.
It's not as good as yours, but it's what it is.
Well, it's not as good as mine, is it? >> No. >> Yeah.
>> Is what it is, don't it? I don't care. It's
>> not that I've got mental disabilities and I >> Yeah.
>> I told the hospital to [ __ ] off, you
know, when I went back in. >> Yeah.
>> Told him I want to go home.
I r him. Obviously, I felt suicidal.
Well, I did ring them cuz I did feel suicidal.
To be honest with you, I'm just going to
leave Natalie alone and let her talk to
me when she's ready
cuz she will talk to me.
>> So, is Le not coming back in? Tell Lisa.
I tell her tell Lisa I tell her what's happened. Obviously I'm not.
No. My fault telling Lisa anything. Nothing. PJ
PJ's left the building. I think he's
going to end his life. I'm not too sure.
Yeah, sorry, bro. I got disconnected.
>> Oh, [ __ ] No, no, you're right.
>> Yeah, I was just saying I probably won't
do it again after Steven. I hate
gambling, so if this one loses, I'll
probably give up if it more. Buddy,
but you used to be a prolific gambler. Did you?
>> I've never gambled in my life.
>> A prolific gambler. You know what that means?
>> Yeah. Like [ __ ] No. Go on. What does it mean?
>> Someone that does it a lot.
>> Yeah. I don't even do it a lot.
I don't even gamble at all.
>> I wonder when these people will leave YouTube, buddy.
YouTube channels that
>> No, I'm just saying when will the day
where they just don't stop coming on it?
>> Don't know. One second. Stay here. One
second. I'm pressing this link, seeing
what it is. I'm coming right back. >> Stop.
I'm playing GTA.
>> It's Lisa.
It's Lisa's channel.
>> Money would ever stop.
>> None of these can stop.
>> Is their life there?
>> Yeah, but don't they get bored?
No, these people would never get bored.
I'm just to say, Miss Lisa,
I need to I need to stop being Lisa and
get off YouTube completely off it, to be honest.
>> Yeah, it will kill you. It will kill you
if you don't get off it.
>> It's killing me already.
It's already [ __ ] up my relationship.
You know what I mean? It's already
[ __ ] up that. But I actually do blame
Lisa for that. I'm not even I'm not even
joking on that either.
>> I do blame Lisa, but I mean
>> No, it wasn't Swanage. It was cold
chest, Trema, and Wall and Swindon.
>> I do blame Lisa for it all.
>> Imagine you die, Monty, and I go to your funeral.
>> My funeral? You won't be invited.
>> It'll be over YouTube. It'll be over
YouTube, isn't it?
I want to get stuffed, mate.
I might be dead in a couple of days
anyways. I haven't been eating.
>> I have to come to a funeral.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I can do it live.
>> And it'll be over YouTube.
>> Yeah. The hospital was asking me if I
got children and that. I said that. I
said, "Yeah." I said, "I've got two daughters."
>> Oh, bless you.
No, not bless you. They was asking for
the names and that. I told her I'm not
giving you my kids names.
>> My kids.
>> Yeah. I said, "What? What? What? What
have my kids got anything to do with this?" Nothing.
I said, "My kids don't even live with
me." I said, "My kids live with my mom, so [ __ ]
nothing to do with me." You should get
off YouTube and live your life. Man,
>> I need I am getting off YouTube and
living my life. I just need Natalie to
understand. I have not told anyone
anything about Natalie. I've only
mentioned about the hotel. But I didn't
even mention what hotel we were in. I
said that we were in [ __ ]
>> How much did you put on it, Steven
Howard? How much did you put on it?
It's put 2 pound50 on it.
>> This is all [ __ ] le's faultless.
If if Lisa didn't do Natalie dress,
>> you put 20 on it. I put 80 on it. What?
What? What does yours return? >> 40.
>> Steven Howard, what does yours return? You
>> know, you're good. They're going to pay
somebody who said 40. return 40.
>> I'm guessing it returns 60 70
>> 80 90 F. >> Nah, I put >> Huh?
>> I said I'm [ __ ] Natalie's at home and
I'm [ __ ] I'm missing her, man. I need
to get back home to her.
Unless you then you sound like a You
sound like a fool in love.
>> I am, PJ. I am in love. I am, but I'm
also a prick as well.
>> Oh, bless you.
>> I'm a prick.
I blame I blame Lisa for doxing the address,
>> but I blame myself for coming on
YouTube. And I promise N that I will
never come back on YouTube. Yeah,
>> I'm only back on YouTube so I can get
Natalie's attention and tell Natalie. I
have not told these people nothing
cuz she thought I told him everything
what's going on but no one knows.
>> Can't return 100. It can't return 100
off 20 Stephen Howard. That don't make sense
of a double both teams to score. How can
it return 100? I put 80 pound on two
teams. It returns 285.
I'm not bothered about it to be honest
with you. That mean that broke up. I'm
not ass to be honest.
But I I do love the woman.
Do you love me?
>> I mean, you're all right, PJ. You just got
>> No, but no, but I mean like love. Yeah.
>> I love you as a friend, PG. I like you
as a friend.
>> Nah, bro. You don't come to see me, bro.
>> Don't come to see you. You live all the
way in [ __ ] London.
>> And you backstabbed me with You
backstabbed me with the bomb and [ __ ]
>> [ __ ] off, man. You backstabbed me B times,
>> bro. You backstabbed me in that Discord
group, you [ __ ]
>> I've never was on this. Never been on.
>> Yeah, you was with that [ __ ] trauma
>> When were that? Oh, that were ages ago. That volcan.
>> Yeah, they turned on you in it. No, they
they they they only wanted me on Discord.
>> Yeah, they they wanted you on there to
try and take the piss out of you and
then you come crying back to Peter Belly.
>> No, no, they wanted me to go around.
They said that like I can show them and
all that lot and then troll all these
people. So, I were trolling them for the
but I weren't doing it for them
cuz I knew what was going on. I was just
playing back me seeing what Discord was
like. Only what they do is send pictures
of kids around and that [ __ ]
>> USA is Steven.
>> That went on for two years, isn't it?
>> You're a good [ __ ] Monty.
You know, I've got to walk from the park
[ __ ] hanging now. This is this is a
hanging walk. I've walked this walk
before. It's a park. It's got a pond
around it. It's got like woodlands there
and all that lot
was up there. I walked from here to It
>> took me miles, [ __ ] miles.
Your anxietyy's kicking in.
>> My anxiety never kicks in. It only kicks
in when a woman breaks up with me.
>> Oh, bless
you. That place [ __ ] sound.
>> Bless you.
>> Hey, taxi for your pe. Yeah, >> taxi.
You and Terry can be friends. What?
>> You and Timmy can be friends.
>> I never be Timmyy's friend.
Then people who fought Natalie over,
then people who fought me over, never be
their friends again. Never. Starting from now,
>> never. And I will never ever forgive
Lisa what she's done. >> Never.
Why did you and Mon, how did you and
Lisa even fall out? Like you was when
you was together, you was all right.
Like, you know.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I know. I know.
Um it was Lisa
um talking [ __ ] about me on um Bingy's
channel, started talking [ __ ] about me.
>> And me and Natalie, me and Natalie,
>> we were watching, we saw the video where
she were chatting [ __ ] about me and all
that lot online and that. Oh,
>> so the name we questioned it to her and
she started arguing with her and then
she said, "Oh, I'm going to do your
address. I'm going to do your address."
I said, "You're not doxing my address.
You're doxing your daughter's address."
But then then she ended up giving
everybody Natalie's address out.
>> Yeah. No.
>> And only what I'm going to say is
Natalie's got into a lot of serious
trouble for it.
>> That's only what I'm saying. Nothing
more. But she she's in a lot of serious trouble. >> Yeah.
>> Say it's not no one's business and I'm
not putting it up on her and that. But
if Lisa didn't give out Natalie's
address, these little clowns won't even
have Natalie's address and me and
Natalie would have been stood together now. >> Now,
you know, cuz she would have had our address.
>> Yeah, it's weird. She don't know.
>> Yeah, it is. It is. Well, it's my fault
as well for going live and telling
everybody that we in the hotel, but I
didn't do us. I told everybody like that
was in the hotel in Manchester and we
wasn't in Manchester. We was in talking
in a totally different city completely.
>> But Natalie,
but I was telling everybody everything.
I haven't told no no one nothing.
I only what only what I said is that
there is what what what I said is only
why she's angry is cuz I mentioned the
hotel like that we at the hotel cuz
we're [ __ ] ballistic cuz she we got
kicked out of one hotel already and she
didn't want to get kicked out of another one.
That's why this is going on now. Um,
but yeah, so [ __ ] I ended up turning
around. I haven't been to sleep for
days. I don't know what's up with me.
I've been waking up at the o'lock in the
morning. It's like it's like being
normal again where when I was in a tent
waking up at 5 4:00 in the morning and
all that lot. You know what I mean?
That's what it's been like. Like being
homeless. But obviously we're not
homeless. Obviously me and I live we've
got a roof over our heads. There's that
uh [ __ ] I use that as a word now that
cuz it's a [ __ ]
you know what I mean cuz they're being
normless and when they can't sleep he
always brings that word up [ __ ]
my little it's my little word now PJ
it's my little Bed.