Yeah, I can't be bothered to repeat
myself. I thought we
[ __ ] Oh my stars, stop. Oh, stop
calling me. [ __ ] off, you
know. [ __ ] off,
man. What me? You
know what you [ __ ]
[ __ ] I'm done for a month. I going out
for a month, man. [ __ ] that.
Yeah, I'm done, bro. I'm gone for a
month. You haven't seen me for a month. All right.
How often do you call anyone a skin big
nose rat face when I literally showed
you over £1,000 yesterday and you
couldn't show me nothing? Well, so going
by your logic, you are the one that is skint
uh and got £1,000 a week. When did I say
that I get £1,000 a week? That's never
come out of my
mouth. Oh my god, this guy is such a
[ __ ] Oh my god. He said the only way
you can get a grand a week is by sending
cracking her. I never said I get a grand
a week. When did that come out of my
mouth when I said I get a grand a week?
You little rat
face. One grand. One grand. When did I
say one grand? Rat boy, you're diagnosed
with autism. Don't try to tell anybody
how to speak. Yeah. Do not try to tell
anybody how to [ __ ] speak.
Oh my god, this guy is a [ __ ] How can
I be that? This guy, these people on
here are so stupid. When did I say that
I get a grand a
week? I never ever said that I get a
grand a week. I'm not on no [ __ ]
grand a month like you. You little rat
face. You little poverty. Living in
poverty, mate. That's living in poverty.
is projection. I literally showed you
over £1,000 yesterday, rat face. What do
you mean projection? Bro, stop it. I'm
just going to end up doing posters of
you again and I'm just going to start
owning you in real life again and just
start the madness again, you know?
When did I say When did I say that I get
a grand a week? That's never come out of
my mouth. You little virgin. You little
virgin on a grand a month. When did I
say I get £1,000 a week? That's never
come out of my mouth. That has never
come out of my [ __ ] mouth.
One grand. No one says one grand like
one grand autism boy. So I don't know
why with your rat face you keep
pronouncing it like that. Must be your severe disabilities.
No, it's not projection. It's me telling
you that you're on £1,000 a month and
that you're skint and how I showed you
over £1,000 yesterday and you couldn't
show me nothing. No, that wasn't
projection. That was me telling you
about your rat face life. That was me
showing you over £1,000 and you not
being able to show me anything cuz
you're a skin [ __ ] You know, why didn't
you get your money out yesterday? Cuz
you ain't got no money.
How could I get a grand a month and show
you over a grand in this society, mate?
I spent £500 yesterday. What? Oh
w is like get more money than him. Oh my
god. Like he actually done a whole video
it. Oh my
god. God, he's so jealous that people
get more money than him. [ __ ] hell.
It's crazy, isn't it? It is
crazy. No, that's not be projecting.
That's me. Look at this. Right. I went
out yesterday. I bought a round that
cost over 23 quid. You saw a round over
23 quid, right? My passport. How could I
be on a grind a month? That doesn't even
make any sense. That means I'd be skimp
right now. No. Oh, and I lost £200. So,
I lost £280. Got my passport. Spent £300
yesterday, but I want to grind them up.
H. Yeah, I don't think so. Huh? Uh
uh. Stop talking about yourself. Stop
self-reflecting. Yeah, but it wouldn't
be possible, you
know. Would not be possible, mate.
imagine. Imagine a story.
Yeah, you saw me out yesterday. [ __ ]
sake. I must have spent
about 300 pound on booze. 250 maybe [ __ ] a
bit rat faces on the ground up. Not me, mate. Yeah,
bro. Yeah, I'm proud to be on benefits.
How can I be on benefits when I
literally told you how much money I get?
I give up with you retards. Yeah,
because somebody on benefits can lose
200 pound and show you over a
grand and go out spending money in it.
Yeah, because I'm on benefits. That must
be a great life on benefits, isn't it?
That must be a great life on benefits,
mate. If you can lose £300, show over a
grand and spend £500 at the same time.
You must be on a lot of benefits, mate.
Yeah. Yeah. It's a great life,
bro. How are you on benefits anyways?
Getting £300 a month on benefits.
M because we all know by this at this
point, bro, at 2025, all you losers do is
self-reflect. All you do is literally
talk about your own lives. So like you
should ask yourself that question. How
is it like you being on benefits? You
know, that's what you should be asking
because it's your own life that you're
talking about. It's your own life that
you are talking about, no one else's. I
just I just gave you three examples, you
know. Yeah. Someone on benefits can lose
£300, show over a grand, and spend
£500. Yeah. Okay, bro. I'm on benefits.
Yeah. Good for you in it. If I'm on
benefits. Yeah, I'm on benefits. I'm on
£300 a month. Sucks to be me, eh?
Yeah, I'm on pip, bro. Okay. So, you're
you're on pip as well.
Yeah, you're on pip as
well. Yeah. So are you. You're on
pip. Yeah. Go self-reflect on another
channel. Yeah. Go self-reflect on
another channel, dear.
Yeah. Sleep in a bit, I reckon. [ __ ] like it. [Music] There we
go. Never you mind how much money I've
got left. That's none of your business.
Worry about how much money you've
got. Worry about how much you've got.
I'm [ __ ] going to bed soon, man. I'm
[ __ ] knackered after that curry. I'm
tired, bro. We went out. We spent
[ __ ] hundreds on booze for no reason.
Eh, uh, when did I ever say that I was
on a grand a week, rat face? You done a
whole video trying to say how much money
I get, but you don't know how much money
I get. You just got showed over a grand
yesterday. You couldn't show nothing. Rat
face. You know rat
face. Oh, [ __ ] This rat face is really obsessed.
Really? That face is really upset. I'm
projecting by saying that you're on a
grand a month. No, you literally are on
a grand a month. I just showed you over
a grand yesterday.
Yeah. You know what I'm saying, bro?
Yeah, I'm tired,
bro. Rap face is on a grand a month.
Slim, I never said I got £1,000 a week.
I've never said I got £1,000 a week
ever. Yeah. I never I just said I'm not
on a grand a month. [ __ ] grand a month, mate.
Yeah, I literally spent about5 600 pound
the past two
days, but I won't be going out for a
month now anyways. I'm just going to
wait for my passport to come back and
then have a
book. Have a good old book. Yeah, just
waiting for that
passport. I can't believe [ __ ] that
that they let me down, bro. [ __ ]
knocked counties. God [ __ ] the whole
bet up. cost me 150 quid. Eh, I could
have done with that, mate. Could have
done with it,
lad. Yeah, it was
nice. I'm sleepy
now. Yeah, I'm sleepy now,
bro. Going to go sleep in a
bit. Mhm. Tired. Knocked out. Yeah.
Just pull a [ __ ] on [ __ ] damn
trip. Yeah, they they they scored on the
in the 90th minute. [ __ ] my whole bet,
man. Yeah, you keep telling yourself
that through cave. You don't know how
much I have. It's none of your business
how much I have. You can try and work
out and think you know how much people
have whatever. You don't know nothing
and you will never know nothing.
Yeah, I already told you how much I got
to be fair. So there you
are. 400 left. Well, I'm not on a grand
a month. So why would I have £500 left
if I'm not on a grand a
month? Grand a
month. I'm not like that rat faced
virgin, you know, isn't it? I'm not like
that [ __ ] virgin, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Find the power for the month
it no cinema. Nothing in the cinema now
for like a month. [ __ ] with that as well.
Uh hopefully we can go to sleep and not
wake up. That will be ideal for
us. That would be ideal, man.
Yeah. We must change the number. Yep.
I got I got a Muslim woman to me
again. It's annoying,
bro. [ __ ] right off. I told her I'm not
going out for about 3 weeks
cuz I'm going out. Keep wasting money
like that, bro. I told her,
"Yeah, you won't see me for a little bit."
Oh, no. Simmons. No
simmons. Nice to meet.
Yep. Can't believe I lost my ass bit yesterday. Steven
Howard. That's why I could live on a
grand a month cuz one night out in
London cost you a good couple of hundred
quid, you know?
So, I'm not on that little rat face
income with his little rat face [ __ ]
doing videos on me. He's so
obsessed. Oh, you're so obsessed, you
little virgin. Just cuz Peter Belly has
more money than you, matey. You
know, you're trying to say that I'm
projecting by saying that you get a
grand a month. How could I be projecting
when I showed you over a grand? I lost
300 pound and I went out and spent
[ __ ] three, four, 500 yesterday.
Probably 600 including the passable.
That's me telling you about your income.
That's me telling you about your own
life. You know, virgin. Yeah.
ratfaced virgin. Is that clear enough
for you? Rat boy. You bald and rat. [ __ ] ugly rat, you
know. No, I'm living. You don't know how
much money I've got. How much money do I
have? Yeah, I need to start living
within my means. That's a good That's
good. Let me ask you this question. How
much money do I have exactly? You don't
know. That's it.
So think what I'm
saying. Yeah, I'm living I'm living beyond my means. Nope. Keep
guessing. Would you reckon I'd be
spending 600 pound in two days if I
wasn't living beyond my means? Again,
don't talk about people that you don't
know. Timmy learned that lesson
yesterday. You know, I to be honest, I
only showed them money because I was
drunk. I I would never show these people nothing
again cuz they just self-reflect their
own lives. But I was drunk and I
thought, "Fuck it. It'll be funny in it
to get some cash out." Rat Boy couldn't
show nothing. Steven Howard, the rat
face virgin, he went into hide
him. Rat face is
nons. No, I don't like Tom Woods.
Oh, did you watch the uh burger video, Stephen
Howard? Did you watch it?
Yeah. Did you watch it? I linked it. Might got
removed. T got more than that. Try
again. Try again. more than
that. That's what I
showed. And you shouldn't talk about
people that you don't know,
bro. Yeah. Yeah. It was It was It
[ __ ] almost killed me. How about that one for
be, you know? That almost killed me,
bro. I was vomiting on the street and
everything. [ __ ] hell, bro. I don't
know how. So he said three out of 10
people can finish it. Mate, I couldn't
finish that, mate. It was like [ __ ] a
lighter to my [ __ ] tongue. That was bad,
bro. Would I eat it again?
Nah. No, I couldn't finish that, mate.
No, if if I had like milk. Yeah, I was
eating honey as well. They were giving
me honey and that. I was down in honey
and [ __ ] It was [ __ ] hot. I've had a
pow curry. Yes. once when I had um
co I had to sign a form to basically say
that if anything happens to me it's not
the restaurant's responsibility and it's
my responsibility a bit like when you go
skydiving you have to sign something cuz
you could die from eating that and then
you could end up in hospital eating
something that hot so just
yeah something like that Oh,
no. Who's losers? Don't know. But I
don't care. They're
obsessed. Probably the same fat little
virgins that's been doing it for years on
YouTube. Yeah. Probably the same fat
little virgins that ain't got a life
that self-reflect their misery on here
every day. They've been doing this for years
now. Yeah. I had a foul once. Yeah, I
had one. I had it once. Yep. I done a
football bet and I lost. I had a both
teams to score no draw. It was winning
and then more um more um not county
scored on the 90th minute making it a
draw and it [ __ ] my whole bet
up. But that women [ __ ] is is bad, bro.
Like even though I went out just to have
fun and that Yeah. Like I spent hundreds, bro.
And I don't have a date next week. I
don't have a date this week. That's crazy, bro.
Jeez, that is crazy. Like, imagine a normal person,
bro. Like, that's mad. A normal person
on a normal income. That's what they
have to go through every week to try and
get a woman in this country. I'm not
[ __ ] doing it, bro. I sent my
passport off today. I should get it back
next week renewed and I'm out of here.
I'm out of here,
lad. Not playing these silly games
anymore. And And it's not even that. It
costs so much money to go out,
too. So much money, so much time.
And then you just got stinking hangover for 3
days. Like I said, I only went out cuz I
was renewing my
passport. Because I was renewing my
passport. So, I thought I'm going to get
my hair done, so I might as well just go
out. But I'll be done now for a month.
100%. I'll be done for a month
now. Yeah, because I see no point in
keep wasting money in this
country like that. Like I see no
point. Why do I drink? Um to have fun
and try to get women. Something to do.
But I woke up the press today because of
the drinking as well. That's another thing.
Yeah, I done balls in. No, nowhere
near. I thought you was going to show me
money, but obviously you have to live
within your means. If I was just on a
grand a month, I couldn't do
that. probably back to America and
Thailand. Yeah, I should have got
something yesterday. I got four numbers
in that, but I just got
trolled. Yep. Not County [ __ ] my bet up for
£150. I didn't need the £150, but I
could have done with it. You know what I'm
saying? [ __ ] the bet up, bro. I was so
I was like 3 minutes away from winning
150 from [ __ ]
But that's what I'm saying, bro. It's
like if you had done a See, that's what
I don't like about them bets because
they can [ __ ] you up at any minute.
Whereas both teams to score, once you've
won, you've won. There's no it can [ __ ]
you up. That's the good thing about just
the both teams to
score. Probably go to Miami to be
fair. They almost killed me, mate.
ain't even a joke, bro. But yeah,
probably go Miami or something. I'm done
in this country,
bro. Um cuz well for like a month
anyways cuz it's just [ __ ] dead, bro.
It's the same [ __ ]
man. You go out, they pretend they got
boyfriends, they give you attitude, they
give you their number, they play games
and this same old
[ __ ] And it was somebody I liked
yesterday and I got her number. We was
talking for a bit and she didn't [ __ ] reply,
bro. It was [ __ ] [ __ ] The bartender
replied, but then she kind of stopped
replying. I can't be bothered with it,
bro. I can't be [ __ ] But I got a
brand new passport coming soon anyway.
So, and it is because you live in
London. It is because you live in
London. They're all [ __ ] here, man.
You won't be I bet you any money. Yeah.
If you lived in Glasgow, you wouldn't
have these problems. Not for as long as
you've had them. What's happening? Just
went out yesterday
drinking. Yeah, it was a good night and
that. It was a good night and I I spent
what I could afford to what I could
afford. It's just the women [ __ ] just
ruin it. It just ruins it,
lad. It just ruins it, bro. Like, it was
fun. But the way I see it is, yeah, you
should have to I bet on AC
Aington and um Fleetwood. Two separate
games. Yeah, two separate
games. Yep. I know about I knew the
teams to pick cuz I studied it for a
little bit. I should have got that
today. [ __ ] bollocks, man. But yeah,
I was having a good time with him.
Yeah, but it is [ __ ]
you live somewhere else, you wouldn't
have these problems for as long as you
have. I know you
wouldn't. There's just too many stuck up
[ __ ] in in in this country. Well,
like especially London, is it? That's
That's literally what it is, bro. That's
is. Trolls and just [ __ ] [ __ ] I
got a hooker at the end of the night.
Yeah, but I couldn't even come cuz I
drunk too much.
Yep. She stopped my deck and I couldn't
even come. Yeah, I know. I know they
were. They just needed to stay like that
as well. But
nope. And if you don't go out looking,
you still won't find anything. So yeah.
Anyways, I'm done. I don't care about it
anymore. Anyways, I know what I need to
do. Leave this country. So that's
it. Yeah, I know what I need to do, bro.
So, it is what it is,
bro. I see. I I just want to watch this
horror film, but it doesn't come out until the
28th. But I am actually done on them
machines. I'm done with them machines. I
only played it the other
day. No, I'm not going
Australia. I approached an Australian
woman yesterday. She had a boyfriend, apparently. So they
say all got boyfriends. Um the woman in
yard. I'm thinking that I should just do
Blackpool and Glasgow
though. I reckon I should just go
Blackpool and I reckon you're not going
to have these problems over there. Even
if you lived in Edinburgh, I swear to
God, I don't think you're going to have these
problems. It's London. It is London.
Yeah. It's It's the country. Yes, but more so especially
London. It is, bro. They're all stuck up
[ __ ] here. Everyone with a brain would know
that. [ __ ] London, bro. They're all the same MPC
[ __ ] You know, that's that's
literally what they
are. Um, I don't think it's in the West
Millions. Have you ever heard of
sarcasm? I was taking the
piss. You really believe that? I think
it's in the West Midlands, bro. I've
been all over the country. I know every
county, every town, every
city. Yeah. Well, it's something to do
it. Would I move to Bristol? No, because
they sound like armies, right? No, mate.
You're No. [ __ ] that, bro.
No, I'd probably move abroad to be fair, but not
Australia. [ __ ] that. Why do you go to
Australia when it's just going to be the same [ __ ]
there? You're westernized [ __ ]
No. Why would I move to Bristol? That
doesn't make any
sense. I do like London. It's just very hard to
get. I've already been. I'm going
back. But you're not going to get any
more success there with the
women. No way are you. This time I will
vlog it because I'm not going for beef.
So I will vlog it this time. Yeah.
But yeah, you should just be able
to we got you should be able to just go
out and meet a woman normally,
but don't work in these westernized
countries. I went to um New York and Massachusetts. I
went I need to go get a drink, bro. I'm thirsty again.
I get over three grand a month and it's
lush. Did I get any linkups? Nope. I
went out last Friday as well. I kissed a
Scottish woman, but them numbers didn't
reply, I don't think. Yes. Uh the
numbers I got yesterday, two of them
replied. and then one randomly blocked
me and then one just went quiet and then
the other two just didn't reply. So,
it's just the same
[ __ ] I was drinking uh rum and
coke. Was a blast. It was a
blast. I can afford to go out every
week. Doesn't matter what I do. That's
for me to know and you to never find
out. That would be 10 a
minute. But yeah, if you was on a grind
a month, you'd be finished. Just think
about it, right? Say you get PIP, right,
which is £620. Haircut, passport, food,
drink. You're done. You'll be lucky to
have £100 left. You can't do it on a
grind a month. This is what I'm trying
to say. You can't do it on a grand a
month. I could go out every I used to go
out every two weeks because I still used
to like to save money. I used to do like
every two weeks.
every two weeks. I'd go out every two
weeks. I still never used to do it every
week. Every two
weeks. But I could do every week easy.
But why why would I, bro? But
yeah, waste a lot of money [ __ ]
drinking and [ __ ] women and [ __ ] in it.
Would you like to see Peter Belly in Glasgow, Steven
Howard? Now, I can't go to Glasgow, bro.
It would remind me of time too much.
Just knowing that he's in that city and
I can't find
him. That's what would piss me
off knowing that I'm in his city and
I'll never find
him. That's I don't think I
could. That's quite scary.
Yeah, I would want to
find So if I was in Glasgow, I can find
him. I'm my dealer. Yeah, totally, bro.
I I sell cocaine. Yeah, totally. I'm a drug
dealer. Yeah, bro. Every day I go on the
streets and drugs. Yeah, I totally do that. Yeah.
Yeah, I know what you're saying about
Blackpool, but I don't really want to
waste any more money in this country. I
want to get out of it, bro. I'm 27. I'm
not getting any younger. I'm just
waiting for my passport now. So, I just
want to get out of it, bro, to be fair.
Yeah, I have had women though. Um,
Harry, I've had more women than you,
haven't I? I'm the only one here that's
been seen with
women. Yeah, I've had more women than
you, though. if you go by
YouTube, but it's a bit dead. Yeah, it's
a bit dead now, but I've had more than
you. And no, and nobody pretend to
laugh. I'm just I'm just saying what
people are scared to
say. Like, you're trying to make fun out
of me, bro, but at the end of the day,
I'm only saying what people are scared to
say. Like, look at me, Harry, bro. If I
can't get women, you're not getting
women. I'm just saying what people are
scared or or scared to say.
Have I ever gone to Newcastle? Bro, why
are you asking stupid
questions? You know, yeah, but it would
happen to you as well, though. Yeah, but
that's the day and age that we live in,
Harry. It would happen to you as well.
It would happen to 90 95% of people.
Yeah, it would happen to you as well,
just like 95% of other people it would happen
to. But yeah, why are you asking if I've
been to Newcastle, bro? Stop asking silly
questions and actually watch videos that
I put on my
channel. [ __ ] hell, I've got a whole
channel based on what I do with my life.
You ask me if I've been to
Newcastle. Yes, Newcastle's way easier.
But I've always got something. Every
time I've been to Newcastle, I've got
something every time I've been there.
I've been to Bristol, but not on a night
out. Nah, I don't want to go back. I
don't want to waste money in this country anymore,
bro. Like that. Nah.
Nah. No, but obviously you would know if
I went to Newcastle if you watch my videos.
Yeah, it makes
sense. Come on now, man. What's
the G shot? All right, I'm going shop. Yeah,
I Oh [ __ ] Yeah, back. Go shop. I'm back.
Hey. Oh, is this all virgin on here? It's not bad. Virgin. No virgin.
Yeah, Peter's never had a
girlfriend. Oh boy, more projection.
Yeah, I b that little rat face version.
He's too irrelevant for my
channel, bro. Few people in here. I've got
[ __ ] serious autism. How they can
come on YouTube every day?
Yeah. Bothering people and they don't
stop. That's serious autism, bro. Like
the fact that they can do this for years
and years and years and years and
years. You know what I mean,
Fred? It's mad how they can do this for
years and years and they don't get bored
of it. It's mad.
He said it's lust he lives with his
bird, mate. You can have your dis you.
Yeah, you you live with your bird. But
guess what? My sloppy seconds live in
your head. Rent free. That's why you
can't shut up about them. Morgan, Izzy,
like the women that I've had are women
that Sean wishes he had. So he can't
accept the fact that Peter Belly has had
them. So he tells himself every single
day that like I've not slept with them
and [ __ ] because he wishes he has been
with these women that I have been with.
But because he
hasn't, he gets jealous and he tells
himself every day that I've not slept
with him because Yeah. He's he's jealous
that he has to he can only get a disabled disabled girl.
Yeah. Start doing it.
Does anyone get depressed the next day
when they drink alcohol? I
do. I get depressed. Do
you? Then I fall asleep and
then that's not the real Monty, man. If it
is, I've got a bone to pick with you,
lad. But the thing is is the drinking is
really bad for you, bro. Like, it
causes after I drink I'm like two
days. Like, yeah, just depressed and [ __ ] Let's
see. That's not a real money, man, is
it? Would you ever? No, I wouldn't.
She's too disabled and too [Music]
ugly. He's so jealous that I got with
Morgan. He's so jealous that I got with
Izzy. He kills him every day. His
jealousy towards me kills him every
day. Do you reckon if I go to go I'll pull Steven Howard? Yeah.
Yeah. No, I don't know. Actually, I went
to Edinburgh to be fair. Edinburgh was
just sort of
like it was
like it gave me London vibes but it was
really cheap and it was nice and stuff
but it gave me London vibes with the
people. I should have went to Glasgow
instead. Yeah. He's mad I've had Morgan.
He's mad I have had Izzy. He's mad I can
just go and get a normal woman's number
even if I don't [ __ ]
her. Yeah. But that's what we want.
Yeah. You're laughing
at you're laughing at
yourself. Yeah. All you're doing is
laughing at yourself, lad. Go
self-reflect on another
channel. My favorite takeaway is
probably Indian, but I like a Chinese
sometimes. Like a nice chicken fried rice.
I do like a nice chicken fried rice sometimes. That's
bad. But probably
Indian. Can't beat an
Indian. Yeah, I'm not really keen on
kebabs to be
fair. I've never really been big on
kebabs. And if it if it was kebabs, it'd
have to be sh. It couldn't be Donna. Too
greasy. No, I'm not really one for them,
bro. I think the last time I have a
proper one was when I was in
Wales. I just don't see the f about
kebabs. I like them. It's not I don't
just Yeah, I like pizza and jalapo.
Yo, this woman yesterday I got her
number in a club. I was hoping she would have
replied. Yeah, I like
pizza. Man, she was split as
well. But I think in terms of trying to
find someone in London, I don't think
it's going to happen,
buddy. I don't think it's going to
happen. Too many stuck up.
And trust me, I sent it yesterday. I
mean, I got four numbers. My friend
didn't get any numbers,
but yeah, he's jealous. I got you, is he?
Um, I've got a certain amount of money
that I want to save and I'm not dipping
into my saving.
So, even if I have to live off
£100, KFC, McDonald's is
[ __ ] KFC any day of the week.
every day of the [ __ ] week. But
yeah, so even though I got to live off
like 100 pound, I live off 100 pound.
I'm not dipping into my savings. That's
over a grand. I'm not doing it. I'm not
dipping into over a grand, bro. [ __ ]
that. That's money for like the future
and that, you know. My
own two, two middle breast, two leg.
Yeah. I thought would have been a
candidate for baby. I actually know
where she works. By the way, if you
don't reply, I'm going to go to where she works.
I actually know she works. She told me
worked and I will make her be a
candidate for baby
Peter. I'll make you love
me. I will make you [ __ ] love me,
brother. Yeah, we could
do How about this? Yeah, we'll do we'll
Blackpool Thursday. No, we can't because
we're going to be too [ __ ] by
Saturday. I was going to say we could do
Blackpool Thursday, Friday, and then do
Glasgow on the
Saturday and then back to London on the
Monday. How much do you reckon that will
cost us? A lot.
That would be
mad. That be
longer. Yeah. Those are% have good
boyfriends, baby. That's about it.
There's loads of totty in London, but
they've all got boyfriends,
apparently. The simps have gone to their heads, I
think. Yeah. Loads of women with invisible boyfriends.
Uh just eating
popcorn. What do you think,
Greasy? So, do Blackpool in Glasgow or just
Blackpool? I love it as well, Harry. I
love it as well. I reckon we should do Blackpool and Glasgow. Just
What do you reckon? I'll be able to find
Tam if I go to
Glasgow, my mate Tam, who I lost contact with.
Pam said to me in good faith, "I think
you need to talk some things through with a
psychiatrist." No, I've not seen it. But
Tammy said to me, "In good faith, I
think you need to talk some things
through with a
psychiatrist." I was dead, bro. I was
dead. No, I don't know who it is.
Yeah, him and his little Scottish
mate. All right. I don't know who it Oh,
yeah. I think I do know who you're talking about,
actually. Yeah, I think I do. The little
skinny one with a [ __ ] up teeth that
used to go around
Liverpool. Yeah, that one.
Yeah. Yeah, I think I do know you're
talking about. Yeah, that little
[ __ ] Yeah, he's talking
about T from Scotland I met last year.
I've been trying to track him down,
but yeah, I know who it is,
but no popcorn for
one. Popcorn for one, mate.
I don't give a [ __ ] where he's going,
man. To be
fair, I already had a curry. Yeah, it
was nice. It filled me up. But I'm just
having some popcorn now and snack. I love
popcorn. Nothing better than eating
popcorn in the
cinema, watching a nice film, putting
your feet up. Can't beat it. Especially
when you're the only one in the cinema. Doesn't matter whether
it but yeah I I
mean yeah like I said I'm not find out
for a month because I'm not dipping into
my saving and if I go out it will be me
dipping into my savings at must point
cuz it's just going to be the same [ __ ] anyways.
I got a boyfriend.
[ __ ] same [ __ ] they do.
So, even though they're in a nightclub in it,
madness. Oh, did he That's nice for him.
You can keep calling me out cuz I don't give a [ __ ]
Yeah, these women say they've got
boyfriends, then they go
away. Then they go away. They say they
got boyfriends even though they're in a
nightclub which cost £20 to come in.
That's crazy, bro. I just can't imagine
like loads of their boyfriends just
allowing their women to go out to the early
hours. I just I just can't imagine them
men that many doing
it. I mean, yeah, some but no
way. No way.
Dude, bro, literally the women that say
they've got boyfriends, about three out
of 10 actually
do. There's no way, bro, these guys cuz
when when they actually have
boyfriends Oh, this woman replied, "Hold
on. When women actually have boyfriends,
Yeah, she replied, but she's back now,
so it's no
good. If they actually had boyfriends,
they're with their
boyfriends. Trust me, bro. I've got
sisters and they do not go out club
until early hours in the
morning. There was this woman I was
speaking to. She's So, I got a few
numbers yesterday and they were the same
age as me. Some was 18, some was 34,
some was my age,
27. Yeah, she liked me, but I'm not I'm
not getting with her, bro. I knew her from before.
Anyways, I bought her some drinks
yesterday cuz I had the money to burn, bro.
So, asylum. Nope.
No, I'd get with an 18y old. [ __ ] damn right. Uh-uh,
mate. This woman, well, whatever you
want to call her, she's 18 and she
actually works near me and she's got big
tits and she's got braces. Do you think
I'm going to say no to her if she wants to [ __ ]
me? Do you really think I'm going to say
no? Hell no, bro. Hell no. Am I saying
no? Sorry, you're too young for me.
You're 18. [ __ ] that, bro. I'll bang the
[ __ ] out of
her. I don't give a [ __ ] if she's
18. You know, you're old enough to come
in the club, you're old enough to drink.
Yeah. You stop going after certain age.
[ __ ] yeah. I'd get with an 18y old. I
don't know. When I was 26, I don't give [ __ ] You
know, not 16. That's pedoish. But 18, I
would. In the situation I'm in, I would. Yeah.
Like think about it. If some [ __ ]
girl who's 18 shows you a bit of
attention and she wants to get with
you and you have no other options, you
be stupid not to. It's way past the
legal age. She's an adult. You know, you
be stupid. 17.
Nah, I don't think so by now. But 18, I
would see this is how you know Sean's a
nons. I'll explain it
because whenever I said, "Oh yeah, she's
16. She's too young." He would really
get defensive about it and say, "Oh,
this is not certain states in America.
It's legal here." Now, a normal person
with normal morals would know that it's too
young. But he would always fuss up that
argument because he's a
pedophile. Like, I'm going two years
above the [ __ ] legal age. You know
what I'm saying? Would I fight Sean?
Stop asking stupid questions. You know,
every time I go to the Virgin's area, he
doesn't show up and he hides under his
bed. He's a keyboard warrior. So, the
answer to your answer to your question, no, I
wouldn't because he's a keyboard warrior
that would never meet me. So, no, I wouldn't fight
him. Okay. She reply back what she's saying. Yeah.
You know, just some little keyboard
warrior. You think I've got anxiety, Steven Howard?
Nah. Nah. You actually think so? Nah.
No, I've never seen
him. I don't know. Do I see the Howard?
Not really. I just got
depressed. I don't have anxiety.
But what I have anxiety
over Well, well, no, not
really. I just got some popcorn and tic tac. You get
tick. I'm going to do a video. Yeah. I
don't know when I'm going to do it, but
literally really I'm going to start like this.
Yeah. Wherever Peter Belly's little legs
taken. Yeah. I got some tic
tacs. You have ticks. What the [ __ ]
Yeah. Wherever Peter Belly's little legs
taken. Greasy. Would you like that little
series? Wherever Peter Bennett's little legs take
him. Is that cute?
I cost £60, but I couldn't even come
cuz I couldn't come because of
uh I was too
drunk. Answer me this question, Walter.
Um, how many women that say they've got
boyfriends in clubs actually do? I think
it's about three out of
10. I think three out of 10 actually
do. Three out of 10 was good.
Yeah, I'd say three out of 10 actually
do. Yeah, everyone's different. I
dropped too much and I couldn't come.
So, how many out of 10 do you reckon
actually have boyfriends? I think three
out of 10 have
boyfriends. Answer me. Wait, how many
out of 10 women that say they got boyfriends actually
do? I'd say three out of
10. What about
you? There's no way boyfriend's birth.
No [ __ ] way, bro. I'd say about
three. It's just what they say in
England. They're just
[ __ ] Yeah, three or four, I'd say.
Yeah, I think some
do, but normally you would see it on
their phone if they actually had a boyfriend.
But yeah, it's [ __ ] bro. We hear we
hear that like a million times about
make money boyfriends. It's so
[ __ ] You know what? I'd rather
somebody just say to me, "Oh, I wish
you'd done this different. I wish you'd
done that different or you look this way
or you look that way." And then actually be
honest. I'd actually respect that more
than a make believe boyfriend cuz how
can I respect something that don't even exist?
Yeah. Do you reckon I'll ever find Tam
from Glasgow? Greavvesy. Well, he said
he went to Ed He said he went to university in Edinburgh.
So, I was thinking of going on Facebook,
going on to Edinburgh University and
trying to find
him. Nah, you're not finding it,
mate. That was my
little do you find attractive?
You find car
attractive. You're [ __ ] gay. You
don't find shovel car attractive. You're
[ __ ] gay. Homo. Everybody grieves is
homo. He doesn't find shovel car
attractive. Homo. You're [ __ ] gay.
I'm copying somebody who can hear me,
guys. The Orton
copycat. I'm copying the
copycat. The little virgin trying to fit in.
Remember, I actually don't think she actually looks
good. But apparently I'm gay. Greavvesy.
I didn't know I was gay. I actually
didn't know I was gay until Virgin Sea told
me. I don't get what's attractive about
her. What is
so What is Okay, let me put it this way.
What is so attractive about
her that if you don't find her
attractive that makes you gay?
What is so attractive about
her where if you don't find her
attractive, you're gay? I can't see it,
Greasy. I actually can't see
it. And that's how you know Sean's just a copycat.
Because in a normal environment, right,
if you say that you don't find a woman attractive,
Greezy. Yeah. What do people say? Oh,
okay. Whatever. you like this type, you
like that type. But when it's to do with
Cheryl Cole, apparently you're gay. It's
because it's trend. He's a copycat. He's
copying. Do you understand? He has to he
has to try to fit
in because what happened was he used to
get Well, he never used to get bullied,
but people in his college used to think
he was gay. He used to study gardening.
Yeah. So people used to think he was gay
because of how he dresses, how he talks,
the fact that he's still a virgin and
he'll die a virgin. So people used to
think he was gay greasy. So he was like,
I'm sick of
this. So then he found out a trend where people
um would find cheer car attractive and
they would say that if you don't find
cheerful car attractive, you're gay. And
he wanted in on the
trend. I'm looking at her and I
literally do not find her
attractive. No tits, no ass, average
face. I don't see the the attraction,
lad. I don't see what's
so special about this shovel cole. I
really really don't.
Sh a even got any tits for [ __ ]
sake. Is Sean gay? Yeah, he's gay.
Yeah. Yeah. I think he's a closeted
homosexual. Yeah. But people in his
college used to think he was gay.
Yeah. People in his college used to
think he was
gay. So that's why he started saying
about Shem Cole. Fit in.
I don't find
attractive one little bit,
mate. But somehow that makes you a
homosexual. But that doesn't make sense
because there's gay people that find her
attractive. Just copy
it. He's just copying. Little
copycat. Why you little copycat? Oh
yeah. Do copy that. One sec.
Yeah. Sorry, bro. I was just on the
phone. Yeah, I was on the phone.
Yeah. So, if I go to Glasgow, Greavves,
and I put a woman, are you going to get
jealous? Are you going to get
jealous? You're going to get jealous, aren't
you? Are you going to get
jealous? Yeah. You're not a fan of Come,
bro. Oh, Chinese text me today. She's
like, "Hey, how are you?" And she gave
me a postcode. She said, "Is that near
you?" I said, "It's not near me. It's in [ __ ]
Manchester." It was like the outskirts
of Manchester. I think Chinese is he
still likes Peter Benny. Yeah.
I don't get that sexy frustrated anymore
though where I'm having to keep getting
[ __ ] escorts and that I don't really
have. It's calmed down a lot, Grezy. Is that good?
No, there's a few different Izzies. Yes, she
is. Nope. I'm white.
USA. Oh, there you
go. USA. Who was your favorite Izzy
Greasy? Oh, you you know the normal
Izzy. She put on her Twitter that she
Does anybody know about me and that I
harassed her? Izzy was one of my
victims. Why did I block them? Because
they're repeating little bastards. I
don't want little repeaters on my
channel. I don't want repeaters on my
channel. Yeah, [ __ ] repeaters. I
don't want repeaters on my
channel. Is that right, Steven
Howard? [ __ ] repeat bastards. Yeah.
Stop asking stupid questions, bro.
Get asking stupid [ __ ] questions, bro.
[ __ ] What did Monty say? YouTube is
banned from his house. How did Monty's
life Yeah. get ruined over YouTube,
though? That's mad.
His life got ruined over YouTube.
Yeah. Yeah. I never said I got a grand a
week. Ever. Long flex. I've never said I
got a grand a
week. God, he's such a little keyboard.
I'd love to just get his little rat face
and just squeeze it. [ __ ] ugly
[ __ ] Monty's life got ruined over the
same website you can watch KSI on. Imagine
that. The same
website you can watch [ __ ] KSI on.
Let that sink in. That's mad.
Guys, I see this
madness. That's so [ __ ] bad.
You're you're in a grand a
month. Is that a funny amount? Stephen
Howard with a grand a month on £750 a month. Bless
him. I'd probably spend that in the past few days.
Grey, not bragging or anything.
Greedy, but yeah. Bless you and life. 750. Bless
you. [ __ ] bless you in life. Bless
you. Bye-bye, [ __ ]
Um, there we
go. And you got my subleting stopped.
How would you get my sublet stopped?
stop stopped. Are you a [ __ ] baiff?
How would have you got someone sublet
and stopped when you're not a baiff and
you can't make the baiffs come and buy
you glass them? See the thing is right
when you don't work for someone here's
the thing these people can't [ __ ]
anything up. If you don't work for someone,
right? These people can't [ __ ] anything
up. Like if you sell merch, if you
sublet, if you sell [ __ ] bagels or
whatever the [ __ ] you do, these people
can't ruin anything. Whereas if you work
for someone, then they can, you know,
they can get you sacked and stuff,
whatever. But if you don't work for
someone, you got brand deals, adverts,
sublet, what the [ __ ] whatever the [ __ ]
you do. These people literally can't ruin
anything. And that's the good thing
about not working for
someone. You know what I'm saying?
crazy. Like when you work for when you
don't work for someone, they can't ruin
nothing, you know? Definitely if you're
working like [ __ ] football
stuff and that's it, bro. Yeah.
You know what's so funny is that he goes
on like these this in these videos
Stephen Howard, but when you go in his
when you go on his area, he runs to the
police screaming he's not a
fighter. And trust me, I've had a big
mouth, bro. He's a big man on YouTube.
doing these little gay videos, but when
someone's in his area, he's the first
one to run to the
police. But remember it being every day, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. It's always on point,
bro. You know how jealous you sound in
that video. S you know when you're doing
that video where you're saying about I'm
Nintendo, I got a gag, bro.
You do realize you just sound so
jealous. Like I'm not I'm not even to
say that because you know that you are
the one that gets a grand a month. Not
me. Not me,
lad. That's the
thing. You sound so jealous. You done a
whole video talking about me not getting
a grand a
week. You are [ __ ] [ __ ] mate.
He needs to get out of
line. No job, no woman, no money in a
bed. You're talking about yourself,
mate. What have I told you about talking
about yourself, Red Star? It's very
unhealthy, lad. Come on here and talk
about yourself. No job. I don't need a
job. Had more women than you. Got more
money than you. Like I said, I played a
money game yesterday. You was nowhere to
be seen. You're talking about yourself,
lad. Stop self-reflecting. It's bad for
your mental health.
Delayed. Stop self-reflecting. It's no
good for the mental health. No job, no
woman, no money. That's you. Stop
talking about yourself. It's very
unhealthy to talk about yourself, isn't it, Steven
Howard? You ain't got a life. Look at
what I was doing yesterday. I was out
with a couple of pals living it up,
drinking, showed money. You was on
YouTube obsessed over
me. So, who's the one that's
winning? These people are all they do is
talk about their own lives, their own existence. Yeah.
Yeah. He's just a weirdo,
mate. That's all he
is. You said I've got no money. I just
showed you money yesterday for [ __ ]
sake. Over a grand
[ __ ] It's just self-reflective. Like
think of it like this. Yeah. You can
show that you're married. You can show
[ __ ] a million pound and they'll
still tell you you don't have these
things that they don't
have because they just
self-relect. They've been doing it for
years. [ __ ] years that these people
have been doing this now. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah,
man. It's called a Carolina
Reaper. Carolina being South Carolina in
the state and Reaper being like a grim
reaper. It's the hottest uh burger in
the world. Hottest
jalapeno. And what? It almost [ __ ] killed
me. No, bro. It almost killed me, bro. I
can't remember the
shop. Nah, bro. It almost killed me. I
think it was £9 with a drink, which
ain't too bad for central London. It
almost almost [ __ ] killed
me. It's not funny, but
yeah, I had to go to a coat machine like three
times. Yeah, you regret greasy.
I don't know what it's called. It's
called bed. Wherever Peter Benny's
little legs take him. Yeah, I was
burping as well, mate. I was I was Yeah,
I would. Remember that? I would give it
whirl. It's not that bad. Bye-bye
now. So many bongo on this YouTube
man. Sean's jealous of me,
man. Why is this Sean so jealous of me,
Fred? He done a video saying about how I
pretend I get a grand a month. I never
said I get a grand a month. I said I get
more than you. And you're on a grand a
month. He's so jealous. Like [ __ ]
hell. His whole life is obsessing over
me. The jealousy is unreal. Fred, the
jealousy and and the autism is very
strong. He's a greeneyed monster little
virgin. If we spent less time stalking
me every single day on YouTube, he might
actually lose his
virginity and he wouldn't be such a
bitter little virgin on YouTube with
there. Isn't that right, Fred? [ __ ]
virgin. I'm not let that virgin on. I'll
let him on when he meets me. Tell the
little [ __ ] lanky string a piss. And
stop calling him Shorty. His name's
Shan. Don't even try to give him a nice
name. He's a [ __ ] little virgin
[ __ ] We get so Yeah.
What day is tomorrow?
Sunday. Sunday roast tomorrow. Me thinks
n. Yeah. Don't call him shorty. Call him
short. He's a virgin. [ __ ] shorty, mate. [ __ ]
Yeah. Do I miss Laney? Not at all, mate.
I ain't been there for [ __ ] ages.
No, I ain't been there for ages, man.
Maybe I'll go back at some point on
Earth. Could give it a whirl. This
lady I wanted that 80 to be a candidate
for baby Peter Red. Not a prime
candidate for baby
Peter. Yeah. Not a prime candidate for baby Peter though.
It not a prime candidate for baby Peter.
No, I have to satisfy Peter Billy's
needs. We such a weirdo,
man. You've been saying things like
that. Who on the earth to satisfy Peter B's needs?
Yeah, I spent £23 on um some drinks
yesterday around a drink, Steven Howard.
And you know why I spent that and you
know how I was able to spend that? Dude,
I'm not on a grind a
month. That simple. I'm not I'm not on a
grind a month,
mate. Not on a grind a month. Grind them
up. [ __ ] ground up. [ __ ] grind them
up. Not anymore. I don't,
bro. No, I followed
everyone. I unfollowed most people. Not
now. I don't, bro.
Yeah, I hated that problem alone. He's a [ __ ] [ __ ] Oh my
team. Shut the [ __ ] up, you stupid
little grummy mug. I remember
that. I said, "Mate, you you sound like
a cat being
strangled, you know. cookies.
That That has got to be the worst accent in
England. That has got to be I think
that's got to be the worst
accent. Worst accent's definitely Birmingham.
Yeah. You're the [ __ ]
prick. You're the [ __ ]
prick. [ __ ] hell.
I think the scale accent is the most
easiest to do in
it. Yeah, but Fred, you'll meet somebody
when when you least expect it,
lad. When you least expect it, mate.
Yeah, I can do
it. You're the [ __ ] prick. You're a
prick. Very easy, lad.
Yeah, came on my live stream yesterday.
I was doing his
accent. Yeah, I was doing his accent. He
come on my live stream. [ __ ] sad old
man. [ __ ] a sheep shagging
[ __ ] Yeah. Shut your [ __ ] mouth when
I was in W, didn't you? You
[ __ ] Shut your mouth then, didn't you?
Don't shut your [ __ ] mouth then you [ __ ] Yeah.
Get in the caravan. I can't do a W
accent. [ __ ] That's my attempt.
Yeah, I can't,
mate. I can do a Sean. I can do a Sean
one. So, my name is
Sean. I was diagnosed with autism. I
live in but I say that it's London to
try and make myself sound better so
people think I'm much better than I
actually than I actually am.
So yeah, I met PJ
um about 10 years ago and um he started
getting more women than me
and having more
sex than me.
So I um I got really jealous and and and stuff. So
yeah, they don't he sounds nothing like
London. He sounds nothing like [ __ ]
London. He doesn't even sound like us.
The [ __ ] virgin. He doesn't sound
nothing like London cuz he's not from
London. And even Gromley is not
London. Bro, I don't even know why we're
talking about this [ __ ] rat face
virgin. He's not even worth talking
about. Let's Let's change the
subject. [ __ ] hell. But they that
Yeah, they don't
Yeah, they don't sound nothing like that
emerging [ __ ] Southeast London. [ __ ]
off. Southeast London. Even Brmley's not London, you
idiot. See, people sometimes say they
think I'm from Manchester. They never
get my accent right because they say
that I don't sound like a cockney. Yeah,
cuz I'm not a
cockney. Do you remember that black
cockney guy um
Fred that stuck up for the Asian nons
and he ended up getting nicked as well.
He was like, "Leave him
alone. Leave him alone then. [ __ ] off.
You're bullying him. [ __ ] off." I love
that. [ __ ] off. You're a bully,
mate. Yeah, that's prop. That's proper
cockney. Yeah, that's a proper cockney.
That is You never wanted your
shell. You will never know what it's
like to be inside USA. Izzy or is he?
They didn't want to know. Yeah. Not even
for one night,
mate. I love that.
No. Oh, yeah. Apparently, I'm from
Essics. This little virgin tries to say
I'm from Essex, even though I was born
in Leighton Stone. lived in Leon 13
years and then lived in Stratford 14
years. But apparently I'm
Essex. Okay. No, you are literally from
Kent. Born and bred a Kent wanker.
You're a Kent [ __ ] You're a Kent
virgin. That's what you are. How can I
be from Essics when I'm the other way? You [ __ ]
[ __ ] No, I don't have an Essex
twang. I'm just very well
spoken. You are for Londoner. But yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. How said um women are stuck up in
Liverpool. You should try coming to
London. You should try coming to London, mate.
mate. You all know all about [ __ ] up
people. It doesn't matter where you
really go in the west. It's the same
people. It's the same men, the same
women, the same people with attitude,
you know. It doesn't It's the same everywhere you go. Yeah.
Chester. How do you work that one out?
No, the worst for stuck up women is actually London.
Yeah. And then the most picky in London
as well because it's the biggest city.
It's the capital of England. So, you
know, maybe the places where they're not stuck up
is maybe like a village in Wales, maybe.
But yeah, London is they're all [ __ ]
they're all stuck up in
London. I don't think I've ever met
stuck up woman from Glasgow. Nah, don't think
so. No, I don't think so,
Dad. Nah. No, I don't think so.
No. Yeah. Me and Harry will go Liverpool
City Center. Me and Harry will go on the pool together.
It What do you reckon will happen if we
went on the pool together, Harry? Me and
you. Me and you in Liverpool doing
approaches. What do you reckon the women will
say? Me and you just sending it in the
nightclubs. What do you reckon they'll say?
Antman said to me that they're just not
interested in this country. I think he
was right though. As mad as it sounds. Yeah.