That's the level. Sorry, mate.
But trips canled.
Trips cancelled. Sorry, lads.
Oh, [ __ ] this. I've done all of this
before and then done a U-turn. Oh, [ __ ]
But I haven't really done so much for three years. Oh. Oh [ __ ]
So I'll be mad. I can't be mad. It's so
bad. I'm not even going out. I think I
truly That's when you know you're truly
done. Truly done now.
Yeah, I can't be. [ __ ] this. London say
I can't be bothered. I definitely can't be [ __ ]
What happens when you've done so much in three years? be
I won't even drink to be honest.
Like I said,
that's what happens when you've done so
much that um
a young age. Um
>> yeah, that's what happens when you learn
so much at a young age.
>> [ __ ] Lord Jacob anxiety. He's the
only one that's got anxiety here. Many
to self projectors. They sit in all day.
>> Yeah, man. We let them just embarrass
themselves on YouTube every day.
We don't be happy with them. No reaction.
Yeah, bro. I'm not going to I can't be
bothered, man. You know,
two stops. I like [ __ ] this. Can't be
bothered going home. This is what
happens when you you've done so much in
in three years traveling, [ __ ]
[ __ ] going drinking. You just don't
want to do it anymore, bro. I'm not even
going to go out in London today. Even if
the football bet wins, I'm probably just
going to get a to be honest. Can't be
[ __ ] That's what happens when you've
done so much, you know. Yeah,
I see uh LJ's followers are um
embarrassing themselves again on YouTube.
I let them just embarrass themselves,
show themselves up. It's the best way to be honest. But
yeah, even if it's not about money at
all, it's not about money in the slightest.
I'd rather just chill, man. What happens
when you do when you've done so much in
three years? I was telling Antman as
well. I was like, "You don't
understand." I was telling Antman about
this on on Snapchat. It's like even with
the gambling, you don't even get the
same buzz cuz you've done so much of it.
So much drinking, so much gambling.
You just get bored of it, bro. Like, I can't
I can't explain it, bro.
Like you just get so bored when you've
done it all.
So yeah, I can't be I literally can't be asked, bro.
Yeah, I feel sorry for Monty, but I just
can't be [ __ ]
I just generally can't be asked. What
happens when you have to work for 3
years? You get loads of money. Yeah.
No. Do you know what it was, Greasy?
Yeah. I'll be honest with you. Yeah. I
got in a bus. I was two stops away and I
thought, "Fuck this for a game of
soldiers. I've done this all before." I
was going to meet Monty today, but I
couldn't be bothered. I got on a bus
literally two stops. Yeah. Had I can't
be asked, man. I generally can't be
[ __ ] It's not about money. It's not
about any of that [ __ ] bro. Just can't
be bothered. And then I was like, "Oh,
well, you've dressed up now. You're on
your way to barbers. Maybe you can go
out in London." No, I'm not interested.
That's what happens when you live the
life for three, four years, bro. You get
bored of it. Yeah.
Yeah. I was going to meet Monty today,
but I just couldn't be bothered.
And to Laur, you're the only one that's
got crippling anxiety. That's why you
know all the telltale signs cuz you're
the one that has the condition. You're
sat on YouTube [ __ ] skin talking to a
lot of [ __ ] mongos. Bro, I just can't
be bothered. I I'm too tired for the
traveling nowadays, bro. I don't know
how I used to do it, you know? I don't
know how the [ __ ] I used to do it.
Looking back on it, I don't know how I
used to do it, bro.
So, yeah, I was going to go big and get pissed,
but then I realized like, what's the
point? Like, you're not going to meet
anyone. And even and it's not even nice.
Even if you do meet someone, what am I
going to do? just keep going back to
[ __ ] Birmingham, then I just don't
see the actual point in it.
Then I just got some chicken and coke
and then come home. Yeah,
after save me as well. [ __ ]
Yeah, it would have been a laugh, but
bro, I can't be [ __ ] to be honest with
you. If I had already had my haircut,
then maybe. And why does LJ make it an
anxiety? When is this L going to stop
projecting his life onto people? He's
anxiety and [ __ ] When When is he going
to stop projecting his skinnness and his anxiety, bro?
But is he really going to stop doing
like bro, you know, I would I'm actually
considering going there and just
slapping the [ __ ] up, bro. You know that
I'm actually really really really
considering going there, which I know
like it's immature and [ __ ] but I'm
actually really thinking of just going
there and just slapping him up, bro.
Like I'm I'm sick of this little [ __ ]
Like he's starting to annoy me now more
than anybody on there. You know what I'm
saying? Any any anyone on here, bro?
I really want to slap this [ __ ] up, bro.
Like, I'm not even joking.
[ __ ] me, bro. Then I'm going to have to
sit waiting to get my hair done. I can't
be asked for all that.
I'm not getting my haircut. I can't be bothered.
I would love to slap that slap that Lavy
up, bro. Really love to slap that cut
up. Like, no. No one understands, bro. I
was telling L2 about this and he just
thinks it's funny, but it ain't funny,
bro. It really, really isn't funny. I
would love to slap that [ __ ] up. The way
he's just a coward, the way he just
avoids people. Like, I hate him, bro.
Like, you don't understand. I hate these
people on here. Really? Really, bro.
Serious serious [ __ ]
I hate these people on here, bro. I
wouldn't I wouldn't care if they [ __ ]
drop dead. Like, I'm not even like just
saying it, bro. Like I'm being serious
with you, you know?
I wouldn't give a [ __ ] bro. I'd have a
party. They drop dead. I' I'd have a
party at their funeral, bro. I hate
them, bro. You don't understand how much
I hate these people.
I'm being deadly serious, bro. I might
have not said it before, but I generally
do, you know. Yeah, bro.
But yeah, that's what happens when you
just [ __ ] do too much, bro. [ __ ]
in three, four years, man.
Yeah, I was going to go Birmingham today
in Nicolo. Yeah. To go see Monty
and then I was two stops away. I was
like, "Oh, [ __ ] bro. We've done all
this before. All of this traveling
around England and drinking and [ __ ] like
I can't be asked with it anymore, bro.
That's how you know you live the life,
bro. That's how you know you live the life
in in them three, four years if you're
if you're bored of it.
You don't like I ain't got money. I've
got money, bro. I've got more than
enough money. I can do what I want. I
[ __ ] I've got more than enough money
to do what I want, bro. That's how you
know you're you're bored of it, bro.
Even if I am in the 1%, you know,
it's like it's all long like going train
station and get to get a train. It is so long, bro.
It's very very very long, bro.
It just seems It just the whole thing
pointless. You know what I mean?
No, I was No, I was two stops away on the bus.
from that from where I am and I just
walk back home 5 minutes away.
Obviously, obviously I weren't on the
train. I wouldn't get the train to
Birmingham then come pack, would I?
No, I was on the bus away from the house
to the barber shop. I like [ __ ] I've
done all this before.
Yeah. No, obviously not, bro. The [ __ ]
I would have got on the train and then
just got off. You know what I mean?
No, I need to get the bus to the
barbers. So, I need to get the train st
a train to the train station. The the
train station that goes to Birmingham is
[ __ ] long, bro.
That's how you know you're just [ __ ]
bored of it all, bro. You know what I
mean? And getting your haircut is
boring. It's so boring being sat there
for an hour.
It's so boring, bro. And no, I don't
have anxiety like L J and L J's
followers. They're the only one that's
got that condition, which is why they go
on about it and sit on YouTube all day.
But, you know, like I just can't be
bothered. It's just long.
Like I said, if id had my hair done
maybe nah, I still don't think I would have.
That's what happens when you do it so
much. You know, it sounds ridiculous.
It's like when people come on here and
talk about gambling. Oh, yeah. And they
talk about their wins. It don't even
trigger me because I've done so much of everything, bro.
Now I'm just looking at like new hobbies
and ways to make money and then leaving.
That's all you do at my age. Well,
at my age now, you know, so it's like
if I win that football bet, I don't even
know what the [ __ ] I'm going to do, bro.
I ain't going out drinking. No way. So
maybe I don't know what I'm doing, bro.
Maybe go a restaurant or something. I
don't [ __ ] know. I'm just uh
I feel like I've got no nothing left to
prove. I've proved my point in this
country time and time again.
You'll wake up one day, bro. Everyone
everyone's different, you know, at
different times. But I woke up and I was
like, I proved my point more than enough
now. I've got nothing left to prove, you know? So,
it's like what Antman said. He said,
"One day you're going to wake up old and
you think, oh, there's people in
Thailand enjoying Thailand right now and
you're there." And it's true. People are
there enjoying it, you know.
Yeah. I've done it multiple times. I
remember the first time I the first time
I left London by myself was when I went
to Birmingham when I was 19 and it was
like a big thing. I was like, "Oh." I
said, "I hope I can make it." Cuz
obviously I was a [ __ ] anxious
[ __ ] child when I was 19. And I and I
went all by myself, so it was fun.
But yeah, it's like
ah I just can't be bothered with it,
bro. I'm just happy chilling, man.
I'll tell you what, I'll buy the
football bet wins. I'll just buy buy U
but even that wouldn't motivate me to
go, bro. Like it's just long. It's just
boring, bro. I ain't even going out of
London. I can't be asked. Go out, get
numbers. Numbers [ __ ] you around. We've
been through it before, bro.
Like, yeah. So, that's it. [ __ ]
football better [ __ ] window.
Might just get with it. Yep.
You got a good memory, huh?
Probably just getting escort to be honest. Yeah,
escorting a big McDonald's.
[ __ ] hell, the football's starting in
like an hour.
LJ's followers are a bunch of [ __ ] losers.
I really want to go there and slap them
up. Michel, bro, I really want to do it.
I really want to slap that [ __ ] like
like cuz you got this channel. Yeah,
where he lies to all of these people and
he thinks that he's big. I just want to
go there and just slap the [ __ ] out of
him. Oh, and if I went to Birmingham
today, I would be calling out that Prime
as well. That's another thing. I'd be
calling out that [ __ ] Like I
wouldn't be I wouldn't be able to help myself.
Yeah, that's another thing that will
happen as well. There's no way I'm not
calling out that [ __ ] if I was to go
there or if I go there, maybe I'll go
there next week. I'm definitely calling
out that [ __ ]
There's no way cuz the amount of times
I've heard this [ __ ] and heard this [ __ ]
be mentioned time and time, it's just
going to it's going to go really sour,
bro. Trust me.
you know, cuz then I'm not going to have
it. Yeah. Where then I come all the way
back to London and then these people
start again like they always do. Um,
so yeah, I'd be calling out that prime
definitely, bro. So
yeah, it will just it will just turn really bad. Yeah, man.
Where he actually lives. I hate them,
bro. That prime lord. I hate them, bro.
I hate these people on here, bro. You
don't understand how much.
I hate them, bro. Seriously.
And that's what I would do. I would call
them out, bro. There's no way I'll go
all that way and not, you know. So,
which you could do on the Sunday to be honest.
But then what's going to happen is
they're going to say, "Oh, too short of
notice." Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Well, I'll just stay in Birmingham.
That's done. and then I'll just end up
staying there. That's the thing.
That's what they will do. If you went
out with that um if you went out to call
that crime today, they're going to say,
"Oh, it's too short notice. We're doing
stuff with our family." No, no, no, no,
no. Then what's going to happen is then
when you go back to London, they will start again.
You know, Birmingham was actually a good
place to be honest, bro. I could stay
with Monty for a few days as well to
just went and I'll just call I'll just
put them all to shame. Every single one
of them prime Timmy that oh that
provident loans as well. There's a few
of them that live there that I [ __ ]
hate, bro. There's a few of them that go
on that little J. Yeah, bro.
Yeah, there's a few of them on there,
bro. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. There is. Mhm.
Trust me, it won't look it won't be
good. Trust me, it won't be good.
Yeah, it won't be good, bro.
That's mad. Why are these people not out
with their friends today,
Nicolola? Why are they not out with
their little mates on LJ's channel? But
why are these people sat on YouTube now
with their little friends?
They've got all this money, all these friends.
Doesn't add up, does it?
Doesn't add up, does it? Really?
All these friends, all this money, but
can't get off of YouTube to save their life,
man. Does it? Something doesn't look
right there, does it, bro?
Something doesn't look right, does it?
Something really does not look right there.
I don't know about you.
Yeah, they are skin. They're skinn.
They're [ __ ] ugly. They got no
friends. Sat on YouTube every day. Oh,
listen to this. Nicolo, right? I know I
shouldn't like care cuz I don't care
what people have. But this this goes to
show the lies on here.
LJ was trying to say how after expenses
he gets three and a half grand a month,
but last week it was two and a half
grand a month. So you get over four
grand a month living in Belfast. Yeah.
Keep lying to yourself.
Keep lying to yourself. You don't get
even you barely get £300 a month. You skid Flynn. Yeah.
Not even Bro, believe that bro. Believe
that. You can't just get into
properties. People don't just get into
Like, do you understand? Nope.
Anxietyy's not got to me, mate. Don't
suffer with anxiety.
Not in the slightest.
Because I'm not going out in London, so
am I scared to go out in London. Why
would anxiety get to me? I don't suffer
with anxiety like you people.
No, not in the slightest. Don't have
anxiety. Okay, Greasy.
If you give me £200, I'll go.
You send me £200. You Yeah.
Yeah. I was going to say £700 to be
honest. I was going to say that to be
honest with you. I was actually going to
say that as well cuz you need to put the
pieces together, Nicolo.
You need to put the pieces together, right?
Think of it, bro.
Three and a half grand a month but sat
on YouTube begging every day. It's quite
a lot of money, is it to have left over?
Three and a half grand a month after
expenses in Belfast but you're sat on
YouTube begging every day. Why would it
be in someone's interest to beg? See, he
doesn't. Yeah, I would say about 700. I
think 300's too low. Even a,000 is too
much. Even £1,100, you can you can still
go out and drink and you can still go
out with £1,100 a month.
But I I think you're right, bro. Yeah. I
think about I think you're right to be honest.
Trust me, people in London barely get [ __ ]
four grand a month. Like I said, unless
they work anyways, it doesn't matter anyways. Sorry, bro. Yeah, man.
Yeah, I sent body voice. I can't be
bothered to go to that. I generally
can't be [ __ ]
Now that Now what will happen is the
football bet will win
and it will make you have to go. Yeah. Yo,
>> can you hear me?
>> What's going on?
>> [ __ ] all, man. I'm just chilling now. I
thought I'd be [ __ ] Oh,
>> I'm bleeding. >> What? Why?
>> Look, put me on big. >> Yeah,
>> money, you should have saved, bro. You
look [ __ ] ill. You should have kept your beard.
>> I am ill, man. I am ill. That's the
thing. I am ill.
>> You look [ __ ] You look like a [ __ ] cancer patient.
>> You should have kept your beard, bro.
>> Bless you.
J deep or not.
>> [ __ ] hell, bro.
>> Are you penny razor?
>> Did you? >> Yeah.
>> Bless you.
>> Then you use the penny razor.
No, I don't need it to win, but I'd like
it to win.
You're a good [ __ ] in it, Monty.
Uh uh uh uh.
Yeah, I was going to go. Yeah.
I'm just so tired nowadays, bro.
So, Greasy, do you want to do that bet?
Yeah. You send it and I'll go. Yeah. Tom.
>> Yeah. Look, PJ, look. I use that Spanish razor.
>> God bless you.
Okay, now we got
>> No, is that serious? She said I can't go
cuz of anxiety greasy. Yeah.
>> Yeah. So, if you if you think that's right, then
bro, I don't have anxiety.
Why the [ __ ] would I have anxiety, bro?
What the [ __ ] about what? I'm not even
going out in London.
Yeah, they're just idiot idiots. Jimmy,
>> because you're trying to say that I I
can't go cuz I have anxiety, bro. Why
would I have anxiety, bro? I'm not even
going out in London.
>> My [ __ ] shit's [ __ ] H.
But I do want to go. I want to cheer
Monty up. You know,
I feel like Monty's in a bad place.
That's the only reason I feel bad.
But bro, I ain't got anxiety, bro. You
know, I I've done it quite a few times,
you know, where I've walked to go
somewhere and I'll make it like 10
minutes up the road and I'll be like,
"Fuck this. I've done this before."
Yeah. I don't I don't have the whole um
like the whole [ __ ] energy and [ __ ]
to do it anymore, bro.
And even if I had anxiety, I'd still go
cuz back in the time there there'd be
the odd time I had and I'd still go.
That's the That's the thing. So, it's like
Yeah, bro. I don't know if I drunk too
much, but I'd still go either way.
whether I was scared or I wasn't scared.
You know what I'm saying? Which I'm not
scared obviously. You know, Monty
Monty even shaved.
I think I should probably go, man.
Then this football bet just [ __ ] win. [ __ ] sake. Um,
oh bless you. Um,
oh Monty, bless you.
>> [ __ ] patience. Don't [ __ ] believe it. Oh, bless.
>> We're still with the [ __ ] bless, man.
>> You don't like it?
>> [ __ ] [ __ ] >> huh? >> Scare. >> Really? >> Yeah.
Oh, I done a song for Natalie and I
[ __ ] I'm crying on a video. So, I
done a video.
>> Oh, bless.
>> Yeah, of course. Course. I'm a [ __ ] sweetheart.
Do you want me just to come? Do you want
me to Do you want me to just come to your house? >> Oh,
>> go out. Unless you want to come here and
go downtown for a bit and come back.
>> You know,
one second. I'm just playing some pranklin. Monty,
>> why you still sitting there? PJ, why you
not getting a move on?
I'm [ __ ] lazy, bro.
>> Are you coming or not? >> Yeah, mate. >> Huh?
>> I'm getting ready to set up in a minute
soon as my face stops bleeding.
>> Well, Monty, I'm a bit sleepy.
>> A bit sleepy. I've not been sleep for
[ __ ] four or five days, man.
>> Why am I scared, bro? Scared of who? Why
would I be scared?
>> For real, man. cuz I want to go and kick
puck out of Jimmy Eldridge. He said he
wants to meet me today.
>> So come on, man. >> Really?
>> Yeah. I'm going to kick [ __ ] out of him
today in town. I'm not asked anymore.
>> What the [ __ ]
>> I shouldn't get charged.
And that's going to be an embarrassment
for him on YouTube.
>> No, I done a U-turn, Joe. I was on the
bus and done a U-turn. I felt sleepy. No,
I felt really sleepy. I was on the way
to the barbers and I felt sleepy.
Then I felt sleepy, Joe. And I came back.
>> That's what happened. So bad.
>> Look how bad my face is bleeding. >> Yeah.
It's just not [ __ ] stoping.
>> So what? You're going into town even if
I don't come.
>> Why you not coming? I might as well just
stay here then.
>> I'm a bit tired, man. I was going to
come, but I'm tired.
>> Oh, so you [ __ ] up the day. I can't be
asked PJ then. Yeah.
>> No, don't leave, man. I don't I [ __ ]
up the day. No, no, no, no. I'll be
honest with you, Joe. Yeah. No, no. I'll be serious.
I was on the bus to go to the barber
shop, right? And then I was on the bus
to go to the barber shop and then I was
like, I've done all of this before, you
know, traveling to different cities. I
was like, well, now you're dressed.
Well, you could just still go out in
London. I was like, nope. Done it all
before. Going out in London, drinking.
I'm fed up with it all, man.
I'm [ __ ] fed up with it all, you know.
No, I'm not messing people around. I'm
Yeah, but that means getting a haircut
and I can't be bothered sitting on the
[ __ ] chair for [ __ ] an hour. It's boring.
Sitting on the chair for an hour is
boring, bro. Nope. I've got plenty of money.
Nope. No money issue. Got more than enough money.
Nope. Doesn't sound like it to me cuz
I've got more than enough money to do
what I want. So, you're wrong there,
buddy. And the whole thing would
probably cost about 100 150. Nope.
Definitely not a money issue.
Definitely definitely not. You got that wrong.
You do realize that I live um
you know why do I need my haircut? Cuz
I'm not going out unless I've had my
haircut. Obviously, I look like a [ __ ] terrorist.
I'm not meeting you, PJ. [ __ ] it. Even
if you ask me to meet you again on your
turn off, I'm not going to meet you
anymore. Can't be asked with it. You
asked me to come and meet you last
night. What? PJ, you're going to be
wearing a hat. For [ __ ] sake.
>> Do I need a haircut?
Okay. Okay. After the Okay. After the
football, I'm going to come then.
>> I'm not getting a haircut. I'm not
getting a haircut though. I'm not
getting a haircut.
>> Okay. Now, look, I'm just saying why
make [ __ ] plans up all night.
>> I'm coming. Okay, I'll come. I'll come.
>> But I'm not wear I'm not wear I'm not
I'm not getting my haircut though.
>> You don't get You don't have to get your
haircut done. If you want a haircut, you
can get it done. Don't mind.
>> Yeah. Okay, fine. I'll come.
>> I'll make my way at 4. Yeah.
>> Okay. Hell, man. I got all dressed up
and all that.
>> Yeah, I'm coming.
>> Are you coming? Yes.
>> Yeah, but I'm just not getting my haircut
>> cuz it's just going to take too long and
I can't be [ __ ] with it, you know.
>> Still [ __ ] bleeding up.
>> Oh, we have we have we have to call that
Primeat as well. >> Prime?
>> Yeah, we have to call them all out in
Birmingham cuz I've had enough of them.
Yeah, we call every single one of these
little clowns out in Birmingham. Call
them all out. All of them if you want [ __ ] everyone.
>> Yeah, shout that loud back out who
grabbed all of your PJ. Yeah.
>> Yeah, that's prime. Yeah, that's crime.
>> Shout him out to come. I [ __ ] [ __ ]
out of here.
>> That's prime. Yeah.
>> Yeah. The guy who grabbed all the PG PJ
come to my town. I be together.
And I'm going to be like, I'm in your
city now. Move me. I'm actually in your
city now. Why don't you come and move me
a little bit to his city? He's going to
b you in it.
>> Yeah, I'm going to be in it and and
Yeah, I'm going to be there.
>> Yeah, come.
>> Yeah, I'm going to And I'm going to call
that money mic out as well. All of them,
bro. All of them.
>> Yeah. Call them all out. Every single
one of them.
>> Call the lot out in it.
>> Call them all out.
I am. I'm going to call out them all.
Leave away money. Mike, Tim Ale, King
Tiger, that lad who wanted you a fight.
I shot them all out.
>> Yeah, we'll defeat them, won't we? >> What?
>> We'll defeat them in it. [Music]
>> Yeah, but you like them. You like them people.
>> [ __ ] bleeding. [ __ ]
>> Bless you. Unless you then. Okay, now
>> using a [ __ ] vanish, man.
>> And what will we get up to tomorrow? >> What?
>> What will we get up to tomorrow?
>> [ __ ] noise.
>> [ __ ] One sec.
>> [ __ ] noise. [ __ ] noise. [ __ ] noise.
[ __ ] know. I'm going to be setting up
in a minute. I'm just waiting for my
phone to charge up. I mean, I'm setting
up for the baby.
>> Yeah, I'm coming, bro. I'm I'm leaving at 4.
>> You're leaving at 4? >> Yeah.
>> Why 4? >> Huh?
>> Why 4:00?
>> Because that because that's when
basically the football was like on
Halime, isn't it?
Well, what time is football at?
>> Starts at 3.
>> Time isn't >> 21 210. >> Yeah,
Grey likes this community in it.
>> I don't like this community to be honest
with you. It's [ __ ] everything up for
me. This is why I'm back on it. So why
am I It's already [ __ ] everything up for me.
>> Yeah, but you like
I don't like it, PJ. I really don't like it.
If I knew if I knew he will [ __ ] me and
Natalie up, I would have gone back on
it. But I haven't gi anything about
Natalie. I haven't told him nothing
about Natalie. Absolutely nothing.
>> Only what I said to Le get me out the
hotel and we in Manchester. I didn't
even tell him where we were,
>> you know. But he only went live cuz I
was [ __ ] angry at her cuz I keep
getting kicked out of [ __ ] hotels and
[ __ ] keep getting kicked out of
[ __ ] houses and I just lost it.
>> You know, you don't understand. Women
don't understand though what men go through.
>> They don't care.
[ __ ] is gay. PJ, he's going to bomb
you. Definitely not gay.
>> Why? Why do these people call you gay?
>> Oh, no.
>> Did you see the Did you Didn't you see
that? Why didn't you find it funny the
picture I sent you earlier?
>> What picture?
>> With LJ sitting down
>> with a
wait till comes to Birmingham again. I'm
going to snap East the little fat ginger little freak. >> Yeah,
they're live now, buddy. Is it?
>> Have you noticed that with the Lord?
>> You know, you know they're live now, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Yeah. But have you noticed that
with Lord Yeah, whatever town I'm in.
When he says he's going to
>> He never turns up when I'm in that town.
>> because he said he's coming come back to Birmingham.
Soon as he found out I was living in
Birmingham, he's he hasn't turned up. He hasn't come.
>> He's pull it off.
>> What do you What do you think they're
talking about right now on the live?
>> Probably like always. >> Yeah.
>> Mongo's reading to
pull pull up. Multi's ready to pull up.
ready to pull up. I'm not pulling
anybody. Listen, peeps. I'm happy with
Natalie. Obviously, I'm not with
Natalie, but I'm happy with I'm going to
get PJ laid. That's what I'm going to do.
>> We're going to get you laid.
>> I'm going to be PJ's wingman.
>> No, I'll be yours.
>> PJ and a wingman.
I can't believe you find this community
funny, bro. You're [ __ ]
Trust me, Natalie. If Natalie does that,
then I would never ever go back out with
Natalie. I will never forgive Natalie
again if she [ __ ] does anything like that.
>> Hey, buddy. Do you know what I think you
do? Yeah. I think before you go to sleep
every night, Yeah. you laugh at this
community, is it?
>> No. In fact, in fact, Lord will have my
sloppy seconds. So, he's right. >> Yeah.
But why do you laugh at this community?
I don't laugh at this community. They're
pathetic. I shouldn't even be reading their comment.
Really, I'm not even reading their
comments now. Actually, they can [ __ ]
off. I don't like I don't know why
they're talking to me when I don't like them. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? If I li
>> I don't know why I'm reacting to the
comments and I don't like them. Yeah,
[ __ ] had money m sloppy seconds. So,
>> oh [ __ ] Actually, I didn't have money m
sloppy seconds actually cuz money m's
got a little small dick. He couldn't
even get it up.
>> Natalie has even told me he couldn't
>> That's funny.
>> He doesn't get it up. Oh, money couldn't
even get it up. He couldn't even reach
his spot on.
>> Has she messaged you? Like, money, has
she messaged you at all? >> No.
>> But she read your messages. >> No.
>> It's weird, isn't it?
>> Yeah, it is weird
cuz how can she be out with me for one
minute the name just go at the second
minute? I don't get it.
>> Yeah. I never do this to anybody. Never.
If I broke up with a woman and that
woman wanted five minutes to talk to me
about things, I give her five minutes to
talk about [ __ ]
>> I wouldn't just completely blanket because
if you love someone,
you know, you don't ignore them. Even if
it's over, if you got feelings for
someone, you at least give that person a
chance to explain why the [ __ ] did you do it?
>> But it's different
with Natalie. She doesn't she doesn't
let you explain. >> Yeah.
>> So, [ __ ] it. Only why I went live on
YouTube anyways cuz I got kicked out the
hotel cuz I [ __ ]
I'm getting I'm sick of getting shouted at. >> Sure.
>> What you
[ __ ] shouting in it. I can't handle shouting. >> Yeah.
>> What is that? I woke N up in the hotel.
It was by accident. I I went and saw it.
I woke up needing a piss. Went and saw
it. Picked up me energy drink off the
side in it. put it back down. Nat woke
up and started going mad at me. Then she
[ __ ] told me to get out the hotel. So
I did. I went out the hotel. I was angry
because I wanted to go back to bed
again. And then he ended up going
outside going live.
Soon as I went live, I thought, "Fuck
sake, what am I doing? [ __ ] it now. I
might as well." Soon as I went,
>> have you stopped bleeding yet?
>> Yeah. Yeah, I've stopped bleeding.
>> Well, bless.
>> No, no, no. just started talking [ __ ] about that.
>> What I should have [ __ ] said, I
shouldn't have said anything about that.
But I haven't told any of these what's
what's going on or anything like that.
No one knows what what's going on. And
that's good. And these people will never
know what what's going on with Natalie
and myself cuz I'm not giving at them.
I'm not telling [ __ ] about it. >> Yeah.
You know only what I said to these
people. Yeah. Is that me and Natalie's
in a hotel in Manchester that I said and
that I walk her up and it's like being
homeless again. Waking up at 4 5:00 in the morning. >> Yeah.
>> Only what I said.
That's only what I said. And she come out like
>> Well, did you use a fanny razor?
>> Yeah, I used a fanny razor. >> D.
>> Yeah, you bastard.
>> You're a dirty [ __ ] You >> Why
>> use a fanny razor? >> Yeah.
>> [ __ ] hell. Why
>> would you not use a funny eraser?
>> Huh? Would
you not use the funny? >> No.
>> Would you not? Oh,
>> you know, you and Timmyy's been arguing
for like 5 years, isn't it? >> Uhhuh.
>> That's your fault.
>> Five years, isn't it?
>> Yeah, but that's your fault.
>> Yeah, but you like it.
>> Don't like it. That's your fault for
getting him on a [ __ ] channel. Huh?
>> That was your fault for getting to me on [ __ ] um
what's it called? What was that with me
and you for me to call him through [ __ ] lockdown?
>> You know what PJ was actually normal for
coming to this community before you got
me into I had my life going for me. I
had everything in life and I come on you
start trolling again and [ __ ] my life
up. This is why you stopped trolling. Is
this why you stopped it back on PlayStation 3?
>> You know PlayStation? Yeah. How comes
everyone eventually stopped going on it
and moved on with their life? But people
here were on it every day. That's weird. No,
>> but most of these people in this
community are off PlayStation 3. They
come off PlayStation on to you.
>> No, not everyone.
>> No, not everyone, but most of them. >> Yeah.
Will Lord J ever get off YouTube?
>> I'm getting off YouTube to be honest
with you. I can't be honest with it. I'm
already here trying to trying to make
remains with N.
>> What if Natalie says, "Oh, she'll meet
you. She'll get back with you, but you
can never go back on YouTube.
>> I will never go back on YouTube. Never.
Never. Ever. Ever. Never." And she if
Natalie gives me a chance and we argued
or whatever else like that and she kic
me out another hotel I will never go
live again. I will never tell anything
ever J's dad are watching us. Yeah cuz
they ain't got no life in it Monty.
>> Yeah. He ain't got nothing better to do
except to watch us and talk about us. That's it.
>> That's it.
Cuz they ain't got that long content. So
they want to make content through other
people on YouTube. That's it. Yeah,
>> they ain't got content. So, we are learn
content and that's it. If you don't get
it, we are learn content.
>> They haven't got content.
>> They've got to make mine and PJ's
content or other people's content.
That's it. It's not your own content
what you're putting up there.
>> It's my content, PJ's content, and
everyone else's content what you only
can put up on your own channels.
>> Yeah, there's a lot.
then you rise. Put yourself out. Yeah.
Granny bash you.
>> How do you know who? How do you know it
was him straight away?
>> What? Rise. >> Yeah.
>> What? The Granny Basher who's already
had one woman in his life.
>> Yeah. How do you know it was him?
>> One woman.
>> So easy name.
Right. It's a Granny Bash. Yeah. I'm
gonna make a song up about rise shagging granny's actually.
That's what I'm gonna do. I'm gonna make
a sexy song up about rice shagging Mary
and my granny and him poo fingering his
brother. That's what I'm going to do. A
video of him pooping his brother and
shagging a granny.
>> Well, it tickles.
>> Ask I just want to ask Monty something. PJ,
>> you're not asking me [ __ ] Kicking PJ.
No questions. Kicking.
>> Who is it? Who is it? Oh my god. Why?
>> I'm not giving you all.
>> Don't know, but I'm not giving him no questions anyways.
>> Griezy, you know, if you show people the
middle finger in GTA 5, they they come
out and beat you up in it.
I've been showing my middle finger and
this guy keeps coming and trying to beat me up.
I love GTA 5, man.
>> Yo, Rise. Rise, you can go out with
Kayie. Literally, you can go out. Kay's
not my ex, you [ __ ] Natalie's my
ex. Kay's my ex X.
Kay's not anymore.
>> Natalie's my ex, not Kayie. So, you can
do what the [ __ ] you want with Kayie,
but I don't think Kayie will go out with
your eyes cuz your eye ugly mug.
Man, she's even slapped your flowers
across the [ __ ] gate, lad. It just shows
that K doesn't want you. And the funny
thing is, right, I've already been with
Kayie. I've already been with Natalie. >> Yeah,
>> I'm not bothered. I'm not bothered. At
least I've been with N.
So, I don't have to cry about that.
>> Yeah, that's something you can't do, guys.
I've seen her flower. What does that mean?
>> He hasn't seen a flower cuz K doesn't
show [ __ ] or send [ __ ]
>> I know
>> flower. It means a funny.
>> I never heard that saying before, bro.
>> Oh, I know.
I know. Right. You've never seen Kay's
funny cuz Kayie never shows anything anything.
All she does is send pictures.
So I know that's [ __ ] lad.
>> God bless you.
>> Not asked about Kelly Rice. I'm asked
about Natalie, not Kelly.
Yeah. So that's the difference one.
I'm asked about Natalie. No one else. No
one else. So if Kayie wants to go out
with you, right, she's more than welcome
to because I don't fancy Kaye.
>> I do not love Kaye. I do not fancy her.
I I I I despise her. I I can't stand >> Yeah,
>> I really can't stand her. Natalie,
I will walk to the moon and back for
that woman. Leon and back.
No [ __ ] That's only one woman who
I've actually fell in love with. Who
I've cried for. I've never cried for Kayla.
>> Never cried for. I laughed at Kay. Go
and ask your rise if I laughed at her. I
always laugh at her. She's a country.
>> Yeah. If you show your middle finger,
they come out trying to fight you.
That's funny, isn't it?
>> On YouTube.
>> No. on GTA um 5.
>> No, I didn't know that.
>> Money, would these people on YouTube ever stop?
>> I don't know. What they thought? You got no life.
>> Oh, middle finger.
God bless you.
>> Rice, listen. If you think you are a big
gangster, Yeah. like you think you are.
Yeah. If you want a real If you want to
meet a real gangster
or whatever else, more than welcome to
come and meet me, lad. I will I will get
a gun. I'll put my gun to your go. Bye-bye. Up left. PJ,
>> can I get all the Can I get all the
guns? Yeah. Or not. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Thank you.
>> You know, if the police, Do you know if
the police catches you with a gun, they
let you go in it?
>> I've already been arrested for a for a
gun. Before I got arrested for a knife,
knife and gun.
I can even get my mom to tell you that
as well. I can even get a video. My mom
even telling you that I got arrested for
a knife and gun.
Even can get a video.
>> That's why my mom when when I was with
Natalie, my mom said, "Stop acting like
a gangster and just get on with your
shit." But R, if you want to meet an
actual gangster, fair enough. We should
do after we meet today. I think we
should go to Belfast and beat and get Lord J.
>> I'm not threatening anyone. Me really,
but I can get all that [ __ ] Rice, I can
get all of that stuff.
>> You want to go to Belfast?
>> Well, you want to go to Belfast? Yeah.
>> Yeah. After we meet today.
>> Yeah. If you want to go to Belfast and
go to Belfast if you want.
>> I might have. I've been live all this
time. Bro, you're on YouTube all this
time. You can't get off of YouTube.
Who said that?
>> That's what makes me laugh about these
people. They ask me if I'm still live,
but they're on YouTube, isn't it?
>> They're on YouTube more times than
anybody else. They're on YouTube 24/7
off the live. These are the [ __ ] who
haven't got a live and tell people to go
and get one. >> Yeah,
>> that's crazy. That's [ __ ] up. The [ __ ]
do I want to go and get a live when I've
got a live? Well, I did have a life. I
[ __ ] it up.
Oh well. Oh well.
Okay, I might get laid today. I can't be asked.
>> [ __ ] what you getting jealous over me for?
>> Getting jealous over you, you ugly rat.
Have you seen a state of
>> [ __ ] [ __ ] Why you still fantasly
bastard? Look at that off that. Wow. The
man who shags for
>> I can't even
>> [ __ ] you can't even keep a relationship
going. It's too now you [ __ ] up
>> I am going down.
I'm going down to your location and I'm
going to [ __ ] Natalie like tomorrow.
>> I am going to split you open like an Adam's apple.
>> Oh, just give me
rise. Is that supposed to make me
jealous or something? Definitely not
lad. Natalie won't go nowhere near you.
So that's all mouth to you and it' be no
action there. That's it. Mouth, no action.
I show you action today, right? I show
you a proper gangster today with about four men.
I'll be there as well.
>> I show you. I show you.
Monty never got owned.
These people get olded every day in it, Monty.
>> I didn't get olded. What? Over a lot of
rat man who who just said he's going to
come down here and shag Natalie. The man
can't even leave his front door.
>> Greavves. I'm still playing Franklin
Birmingham. Actually, I'm I'm just going
to stay in Birmingham for Natalie.
That's what I'm going to do. I'm not
leaving Birmingham. I'm staying here for
Natalie. Are we going to go back?
>> Oh, no. There's no point. I'm staying
here for Natalie to prove to Natalie I'm
here for her cuz I'm here for Natalie.
>> I'm [ __ ] here for her.
>> Franklin's cute in it. Grezy. I like
Franklin. He's a cute.
>> So when Natalie does need me, I will be here
for anything or anything. I do anything
for that woman.
>> [ __ ] anything.
>> Bless you.
>> Bless you. She knows it. She knows.
>> So I'm not going. I'm staying for her.
She got me.
>> I don't want you. So
>> yeah, I'm not bothered if Natalie
doesn't want me. I'm not bothered. I'm
still staying here.
I'm not bothered. I'm still here forever.
>> At least you're not like [ __ ] At
least you're not like Virgin Boy over
Britney. Do you remember?
>> Oh [ __ ] Long age. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] to be honest
with you now. She's me and that I don't
give a [ __ ] I care about her. I love
>> that Britney thing was that Rice wants
to come in. Monty,
>> no. Leave him out. Leave him out. He
just wants to [ __ ]
>> Let's just all meet up today. All Rice,
come to Birmingham.
>> Rice won't leave his front door.
Rice can even bring a knife. We've been
moving once to. You can bring a knife.
I'm done with these on here. I'm going
Timmy's offered to be out of fight
today. Told me to go to Birmingham City
today. So, I'm going to go today. I'm
going to go in a minute.
And Jimmy's going to get his head
smashed into there, pig. It's not going
to be a [ __ ] a cuddle fight.
He's getting destroyed.
No, I don't think Monty. Yeah. Listen, I
don't think you really done anything
wrong with like, yeah, okay, you was on
YouTube, but listen, bro. Yeah, you and
Natalie, like you met on YouTube. It's not like
>> she wasn't on YouTube and then you put
her on YouTube. She's from YouTube like
you. Do you know what I mean, bro?
>> Yeah, of course. Of course.
>> She should have understood that like
[ __ ] you know?
>> Yeah. Oh, yeah. Of course. Of course.
But it still weren't the point of me
coming on this [ __ ] community when me
and Natalie were supposed to quit and we
we told each other we're quitting and I
[ __ ] up by coming back on. You know
what I mean? I'm appreciate that.
>> You're not coming in. Rice.
>> Only what you're talking about Rice is
the women I slept with. Your channel's little [ __ ]
Do you reckon Rice has ever had a [ __ ]
Rice. Well, of
a granny. Yeah, that's it.
He had a [ __ ] blow job of of his own
age, you know. Of a granny. Yeah, that
that's about it. >> Yeah.
>> Rise. Rise. Why are you coming on to me
when you've already get more women than
both of you? I've had more women than
you would ever have.
>> Rice can't get a woman. He can only get
granny's. That's not a woman you'll ever have, son.
>> [ __ ] hell,
she's granny's. That's it. >> Yeah,
>> I can make it all.
>> So, what you're going to You're going to
come to Birmingham today, Rice. Yeah,
>> they're right.
>> Um, why am I always moaning? Cuz I'm not
in the No, I'm not moaning about not
getting women. I'm not in denial.
>> The difference is I'm not One second,
Monty. I'm not in denial like you simps.
I'm not scared to say how it is. Because
I'm not in denial.
Just cuz I don't lick women's asses like
you do, it doesn't mean I've never had a
woman. Do you know what I'm saying?
>> Yeah. Of course. Of course. That's what
the That's what guys does, Lloyd.
women's asses. He kind He bullies women.
Have you seen it? He bullies them. When
he can't get his own way with them.
>> When he can't get his own way with a
woman, he tries bullying them.
>> Yeah, man.
>> When he can't get
>> Jimmy Eldridge. Timmy Eldridge owns the
dregs. What? Because I say, "Yeah, they
don't they don't count." But I've had
I've had people that weren't escorts as
you've been shown a million times. But
what I'm saying is like, yeah, I just
say, oh, like it's annoying. They waste
people's time. They say they got
boyfriends and they're evil. Yeah. What?
Does that mean I've never had one? Come on, bro.
I'm just not a th.
And escorts actually do count. And I've
had loads of people that weren't escorts.
>> You can't even get an escort. You're too
ugly. Even if you tried to pay, they'd
still reject you. >> Rise.
Just all of them on here. Rice wants to
come in. He said he's going to come Birmingham.
>> Oh, let him in then if he's going to
come Birmingham. If he's just going to
shout and rave and [ __ ] like that and
then he's not going to come either way.
But let him up then cuz I know he's not
going to come Birmingham today. He only
wants to come up to talk about the women
I slept with and say how good he sit
with. I'm going to sleep with her. Oh my
god. Let him up. Let him up cuz I know
100% right in coming. He can bring bring
Mr. Wilson with him for [ __ ] sake.
Mr. Listen, listen. Sid lookalike [ __ ]
Listen carefully. Yeah. Stop bringing
the women up who I slept with. You are
so jealous of me. You talk about me
daily. D daily on your channel. Won't go
this. Won't go that. Oh my god. Stop
getting jealous of the women I slept
with. You [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] If you
want to come to Birmingham, stop sitting
there and get to Birmingham. I'm I'm
really really jealous that uh you you
had two relationships and you [ __ ]
them up like you know it's not like I'm
actually right I didn't [ __ ] up relationship with >> listen
>> I'm happy I mean Kay split up I wanted
to split with anyway
>> why you why you happy because you split
up with um why is she so bad
>> because Kay is a child abuser she kick
[ __ ] out of my own hat you [ __ ]
>> Well, if you're lucky in Scotland, you are
>> a [ __ ] child abuser, lad.
>> You should be You should be privileged
that I live so far away from you.
>> Oh, so you're not coming now, guys. So,
you're not coming?
>> I tell you something. I will do it. You
>> Oh, just get rid of him. Get rid of him.
He's not coming. You're not
I told you he's not coming.
>> Well, he said he was.
>> Yeah. No, he only wanted to come up on a hangout.
>> Why didn't you come to Birmingham today? Um, Rice,
it's not too far from Glasgow.
>> Yeah, we're doing laps from my room to
the bathroom to the toilet.
Oh, these people are idiots, isn't it?
>> Yeah, but listen, I only I'm only I only
[ __ ] argue with people who actually
meet me like Jimmy Aldridge. Like today,
Timmy Aldridge said he was going to meet
me today with PJ and that was a promise
he was saying. >> Yeah.
>> So, so if Timmy don't turn up today in
Birmingham, I'm done. Timy's now getting
another shout out again. I'm done on
YouTube completely after I met PJ. I'm
not coming back live. >> Yeah,
>> I'm off. I'm not coming back.
>> I'm not I'm not back now. You don't see
me live. I'm on PJs.
>> I'm not.
>> Okay. Now,
>> I hope no one rings the police though.
>> No, no one will bring the police cuz
it's it's only it's getting recorded.
He's not going live.
>> Only a person who will love what the pleas. >> Yeah.
>> Right. And I'm not being funny yet, but
Kay's already [ __ ] up for herself
from seeing Lauder and Prim anyways by
taking the piss out of me. For [ __ ]
sake, I've got recordings and [ __ ]
pictures of her what I'm waiting to send
to my mom. What my mom wants to stop
Kayie from seeing them kids cuz my mom
said she she take Kaye to court. That's
what my mom said. She will take Kaye to court. We
>> should beat Kaye up.
No, I'm not beating no woman up. I'm not
a woman. I'm not a woman abuser.
>> She's an abuser.
>> I don't whack women. I don't I don't
beat women up.
>> Yeah, but she's an abuser.
>> Yeah, she's abuser. But I still don't
batter a woman. Even if she abuser,
leave her to it. If she wants to abuse
her abuse, I'm not an abuser.
>> Who Who do you think would win in a
fight? Me or Kayie?
>> Obviously you. Kay's not even out. It's
not it's not obvious. How it's not not necessarily obvious.
>> I [ __ ] I I've teleported Kay. I've
literally teleported her from one side
of the room to the other side of the
room in one second. Flat properly teleported her
when she's attacked me. And that [ __ ]
I grabbed her on a [ __ ] throw her
teleported across the room. >> Yeah,
>> that's always the That was
>> like a friendly fight off of YouTube. Is it?
>> I think Kay still [ __ ] loves me to be
honest with you cuz she can't stop
talking about me. But I don't love her. I love
>> Nat later. Yeah.
>> What time is it now? Actually, I'm going
to start setting off in a minute. It's >> 2:41.
>> Yeah, the 3:00. So, you'll be setting up
in a minute.
Yeah. You said you set enough at 3, didn't you?
>> No. 4.
>> Oh, 4:00. So, another nowhere. >> Yeah.
>> Katie, you're more than welcome to come as well.
>> [ __ ] off. She can stay where the [ __ ]
she is. Literally, she can stay where
What she is is a [ __ ] bully. A bully.
You used to think
you used to think Rice was funny, is it?
>> To be honest with you, I liked Rice at
first and then he just he's just a
weirdo. It's just a freak to be honest with you. >> Yeah.
Disabled bastard. No, he isn't.
Who said that?
>> Just a count.
>> What account? Sorry, I weren't looking. Sorry.
>> You know what? You're sitting there,
right? Saying I'm a [ __ ] abusive you
my local squat. Sort yourself out there.
Go and shave your beard. You
>> shave your ass. Go shake your back. You
[ __ ] sad woman. You [ __ ] man off
the line. Take your wig off.
>> [ __ ] hit me. You know what? Slide the
wig off every day on other people's
panels. You dirty lag. >> Yeah.
You s bullying your kids. Bullying your
kids. Why did you smack in the face? Why
did you Why did you chuck Lola on the
bed? Why did you smack Lola? Why did you
chuck water all over Lola as well? Why
did you do that, Kay?
>> You're abuser. I know. You know what?
All this [ __ ] I'm sending to my mom,
Kayie. All this [ __ ] what you've doing
to me on YouTube hanging around with 420.
My mom knows about 420. You're not
seeing them kids again. I'm going to put
a stop to it.
>> You see the kids tomorrow?
>> You see the kids on the phone tomorrow? >> Yeah.
>> Oh, okay. But but you put load and p all
over YouTube going live. Oh, look at me.
I'm on a train going and see my kids.
My mom My mom don't like you. My mom
loves Natalie. She adors Natalie. You My
mom can't stand you. She hates you. Yeah. Yeah.
>> My mom can't stand you.
>> Guess what? Didn't you just get banned
recently from senior kids because of the
coke you were taking, [ __ ]
>> Oh, actually, no, you didn't, actually, Kay.
>> Yes, you did. Cuz your mom told me.
>> No, I didn't. Yeah, my mom didn't b me.
I'm seeing my kids today. You did. I'm
seeing them today. Not tomorrow. Today.
when you see them tomorrow.
>> That is true. >> Whe
you hang out with the people who bullied
you, who bullied your kids as well. Go on.
Go on. You corner.
Well, when you have used diesel, you're [ __ ] using
>> Stop making stuff up, Katie. Stop making
>> a PJ.
>> No one asked the police to strip search
your kids. Shout out.
Okay, you go PJ for that. You go PJ for
that. But you don't go out for putting
our kids up on the wall. I forgive you,
Philly. I forgive you. Yeah, you're
[ __ ] great to speak to
all these old who on your kids and
you're entertaining them. You sad [ __ ] Get alive. >> Yeah.
Pathetic. You are pathetic.
>> It makes perfect sense. You s You s with
actual pedophiles, Kay. [ __ ]
pedophiles entertaining on you sad [ __ ]
get l on YouTube listen my sloppy
seconds who wants my sloppy seconds
you're not anymore you're my eggs you're
not my ex anymore
you know what can I tell you something
I've never loved you I've never ever loved you.
>> And that's good. And that's [ __ ]
good. To be honest with you, when I
first met Natalie, I fell in love with her.
>> I fell in love with you.
>> [ __ ] fell in love with her from the
first day I saw her on YouTube.
>> I fell in love with
you. I've never you
>> I only wanted to leave down south. I
only wanted to shag you so I can have a
couple of kids. Oh, now you can't have
kids anymore, can you? No, you can't
have kids, can you? It's a risk. Give
me, it's a risk for you.
>> I can have kids. You can't.
>> You should. You know when you're
supposed to slick your wrist and that
should have done a better job.
>> Actually, actually, Natalie, I went for my wrist.
>> Kayie, I'm going to Birmingham
Birmingham to give Monty some support.
You should be doing that.
>> Kelly can't do that. Kill never gay
prick and bullied me.
>> You know what I mean? She get she got
bullied off her mom and dad. Her mom and
dad fought her off and then she to her own partner.
>> Her mom fought her off. Her mom fought
her off. [ __ ] another abuser. Your
mom look like your autistic cuntable.
>> End of story.
>> Yeah, you are. End of story. You are end
of story. You think I get back with you?
Yeah. All right.
Don't want you. Never wanted you.
>> If you think that hurts me.
>> I don't give a [ __ ] if it does or
doesn't. I've never wanted you. Never.
She started abusing me.
>> She started abusing me.
>> I love Natalie. I love Natalie.
>> My heart is yours.
>> I do not give a [ __ ] I'm currently awake.
>> You give a [ __ ] Of course you do. You
can even hear it in your voice. You give
a [ __ ] You can even hear it in your voice. Back [ __ ]
>> You do give a [ __ ]
PJ, get rid of it now. Yeah.
>> Haley thinks all this YouTube thing is
funny, isn't it?
>> Yeah, she does. She thinks it's
hilarious and whatever else. Leave her
to it. She's just a [ __ ] prick. That's why
>> that's why I have so much respect for Natalie.
>> I've got so much respect for that woman.
Even though that woman, you know, that
woman's done nothing to me. Nothing.
Even though me and Nataly have had our arguments and
diesel, that's old. That diesel thing.
>> Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] about diesel.
Well, I do. He's my dog. But these
people bringing diesel up. I'm not a G.
I don't get cough for that. I got rid of
diesel because I had to get rid of him.
Not by choice, but I'm not going to cry about it.
>> How long have you been with Nanny? Two months.
>> No, longer than two months. >> Three.
>> Longer than three months.
>> Four. Is it
>> longer than four months?
>> It can't be longer than four months.
>> About four or five months.
>> Yeah. Four or five months. Yeah.
I don't read the comments. Hey dear,
>> you people are proper pedos in this community.
>> [ __ ] idiots.
>> Creepsy. Creepsy.
They are aren't they? Yeah,
>> they're [ __ ] weird. They are proper
freaks with ages and that. They talk about [ __ ] >> weirdos.
>> [ __ ] weirdos. You think it affects me
what you people say? You people are [ __ ] weirdos. Yeah.
>> Okay. No.
>> Jesus Christ.
>> What do you think this community is funny?
>> I know. I think I think they [ __ ]
disabled CS to be honest with you, PJ.
>> Oh, [ __ ] sake.
Listen, I know why you people call
people mongos. is cuz you look in the
mirror at yourselves and you say what
[ __ ] monger I am. I go and go YouTube.
>> You [ __ ] ugly bastard.
>> Get McDonald's today. Um, Grezy.
>> No, actually, you got that wrong. It
wasn't Emma Mitchell with the banana. It
was Kirsty Mitchell actually with the
banana. It was
>> So that's wrong, lad. You got that
wrong. It wasn't Emma with the banana. with Christie >> Mitchell
>> and I've only I've I've only done things
with Christie Mitchell not Emma Mitchell
I've not dated or done anything
>> I do like Franklin I love Franklin he's
cute he's a lovely character
>> I'm not going live anymore peeps I'm not
on YouTube no more I'm all here to meet
PJ in Birmingham I'm not coming back on YouTube tomorrow.
You know what I mean? I'm off. I'm off
here tomorrow. I'm only meeting PJ.
>> Oh, Franklin, go left.
You like Franklin, Monty?
>> It's all right.
>> Who is it then?
>> It's all DJ 5.
>> Yeah, he's a cute He's a lovely P.
No, I like Trevor, mate.
>> Oh, I like Franklin. Franklin's back.
>> No, Trevor's Trevor's a psycho. I like
Trevor, mate. He's me and Trevor.
>> They're proper [ __ ] nons on this
community, is it?
>> [ __ ] is nons on this community. He is
now. I can't be I can't be ass with
women anymore. Me. Like, I can't. If
women are like that, like [ __ ] Kay
abuser, didn't Natalie. Oh, I [ __ ]
love her. What if she finish me when
when [ __ ] get stuff? I don't want to go
out with women like that.
>> You know what? If she doesn't get back
with you, just buy another dog and just
stay with a dog in it.
>> I'm not getting another dog, PJ. It's
too much heartbreak, mate.
>> But they're very easy. All you do is
walk them three times a day, feed them
three times a day. It's quite easy.
>> I've I've already been out with one dog.
I don't want to go out with another dog. I'm about
>> people making fake accounts, man.
>> Of what?
>> Just silly accounts of other people.
>> Yeah, the idiot. That's why
>> it'll never stop.
>> Yes, we
just give me another chance.
No, I'm just saying if she does give me
a chance, I never come back here again.
Never. I [ __ ] I stick to my word.
>> These people are [ __ ] weirdos, bro.
What? Diesel was Lola and Prim's dad.
They're [ __ ] freaks, aren't they?
>> Yeah, they are [ __ ] right?
>> What the [ __ ]
>> I'm sure you are all pedophiles. Only
what you do in this community is talk
about teenagers and my kids. Yeah, that's it.
>> That's it. That's a bit freaky on my behalf.
I'm not being funny. What you talking about?
>> Yeah, but Grey likes it. Grezy likes
this talk. He's [ __ ] weird, bro.
>> Well, that's [ __ ] weird. Like, it is
weird. This is why I reacted to these
people. I'm not reacting to them
anymore. They [ __ ] weirdos. >> Yeah,
>> these people have got a problem. Come
[ __ ] meet me.
That's a problem solved in it.
Okay, now Matt. >> Yeah.
>> Oh, look at your little picture, Grezy.
You love Stitch, don't you? Yeah. Monty
used to like Stitch, >> huh? >> Stitch.
>> Yeah. You know, you know Stitch. >> Stitch.
Yeah. Do you like him? >> Him? >> Stitch.
>> Yeah. Oh, Stitch. He's cute. >> Stitch.
>> It's Natalie.
>> I want it.
>> I want it. Natalie. It's Natalie. Stitch.
>> Can I have it?
>> No, it's Natalie's.
>> Well, can you get me one?
>> I want it. Do you know how in in Blackpool?
Oh, they grab the claw machines.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> They're [ __ ] [ __ ] trying to win on
that. Yeah. Do you know when I went to
the cinema last week, I was trying to
win the Find the Nemo and no matter how
>> good you grab it, it just slips. Just kept slipping.
>> Yeah, I know. No, I'm good at the
machine. I'm really very good.
>> Haley will even tell you how good I am
with the claw machines. I've never lost on a
>> How much was it a go? How much was it a
go? One pound
>> a quid? Yeah. On the first go. one
stitch on my first go. I've never lost
>> I've never lost on them titty machines.
I've always grabbed about three titties
in one go or two titties or one. The
most titties are grab
>> the most titties I grabbed out of one
with one go is about three titties with one go.
>> Bless you.
>> Three titties. What?
>> Bless you. What's happening? No, I'm
just going to um I'm just waiting for
the football to start. I got a football
bet on and I'm meeting Monty, man. Um
I'm leaving at 4:00. I'm going to
Birmingham to meet Monty.
>> Natalie, if you're listening, yeah, why
don't you come Birmingham with us and
come and have a drink and let's sort
[ __ ] out naturally.
>> Yeah, we can have a We can have a free.
>> [ __ ] off.
>> I'm joking. I'm only joking, bro. You know,
>> I ain't been Birmingham for about 3
years, Ghost. I ain't been there for
three years. Me.
>> So, Natalie, if you if you are watching
PJ's channel and you're watching me,
please come to Birmingham.
>> I haven't been out for a couple of
weeks. I don't really bother anymore,
ghost, I can't be asked, bro,
>> in this country anymore. I'm past it all
>> to going out and I'm over it all now, bro.
I want to go in Birmingham to see Monty,
you know. So,
I'm not a cheat. I'm not new in I'll
come here. I I'm not I'm not shagging.
No one. I'm not getting off with anybody.
>> Yeah, I've been to Birmingham. I've been
to Birmingham like five times. Ghost Goston.
>> Natalie's in the bedroom.
>> Natalie's in her bedroom. She don't even
want to talk to me still. She's all
[ __ ] quiet. Her headphones in. She just what?
>> Yeah, I'm bored of the going out now.
Going. I've been doing it for like four
years, bro. Like [ __ ] multiple times
a week. Once you've done it for so many
years, you just get bored of it.
Bored. Same women, same
[ __ ] It's same [ __ ] isn't it? [ __ ]
I don't really I just stay in there now
and chill on GTA.
Lots more fun. Yeah,
I just I gave up with the women thing. I
got 30 numbers two weeks ago ghosting
and I ain't even got a date. Two people
were supposed to meet me, they ghosted.
I got like four replies out of the 13
numbers. I got 13 numbers in three days.
I just can't be bothered anymore.
That's what happens when you've gone out
for 3, four years, bro. Trying and
[ __ ] traveling and [ __ ] I just can't
be bothered with this country anymore,
bro. To be fair, I don't think I'll ever
try here again.
It will never change. You know what
makes me laugh ghosting is when people
think it's going to change. You're not
going to wake up one day and suddenly
it's going to change
when it's only getting worse. It's not.
It will never change.
It will never change unless you The only
way it's going to change, bro, is if they
ban social media.
You go to Asia, you go to South America.
That's the only way. It will never
change, bro. Ever in this country
with these women.
Never, bro. It will never change. The
football's starting now, ain't it? Yay. Yeah. Houston.
Yeah. So, what I was saying is um Yeah,
I got an 80 double both teams to score. Returns 285.
Nice profit, ain't it? Yeah, man.
But yeah, I can't be asked with the
women [ __ ] anymore, bro.
I can't be asked at my age. Yeah, I
don't I I think ghosting I think it's
because I've done it so much, you know, 4 years, not working.
Um, getting all that money every month.
You've been there, done it, it worn a t-shirt.
You know, I've done it for so long.
Yeah, sports the g it's like gambling
now. I'm only doing gambling now just
for a bit of extra money on the
football. It doesn't even trigger me
gambling wins anymore because I've
gambled so much. I've drunk so much.
I've done so much for so much long in
four years, bro. Three, three, four years.
So that's why I've done it all, bro. I'm
just ready to like leave now, find
hobbies, and leave.
Which is ridiculous as that sounds. Like,
think about it. 3 years. You're getting
over three grand a month for 3 years and
you're not working. Think of what I done
in that time, bro. So much [ __ ]
So much [ __ ] drinking.
That's what happens. Anyways,
who the [ __ ] got the police? Who the >> What?
Do you understand what I mean? Ghost them.
So much drinking, so much gambling,
so much trying.
It's like this whole Monty thing is sad
over Natalie G. No woman can make me sad
now cuz I know what they do. Been there, done it.
I think I've got more life experience
than I should have for my age. Does that make sense?
Yeah. and he was with he was with a
woman and she's like I think she's broke
up with him and he's kind of sad
but I know what these women do. I know
what they're like. So it it I would be
surprised if they done anything other than that.
Yeah, man. I'm just I just can't be bothered anymore
with the women thing, bro.
It will never change. Ghosting never
never changed. You just get yourself to Thailand.
I don't I don't believe it, bro. I don't
believe it, Ghosting. Because how could
I? If you've been trying for [ __ ]
years and years and years and you're
still single and it's continuous and
it's continuously going to get worse,
how is it going to change? I mean, you
you can I'm trying to see it from a
realistic point of view. You can't even
barely get a conversation out of someone.
It's not changed in years. Why all of a
sudden is it going to change? How could it? So,
no, it's not going to happen because if
it's not happened in years, it's not
going to happen now. That's my logic
that I go by
that. Why do you think I don't even go
out? I I I know if I went out today
exactly what's going to happen, I know
exactly what will happen with these
women. I could tell you exactly what
will happen and bet money on it because
it's I was watching this guy in America
do it video after video after video and
he was getting the same [ __ ] Boyfriend,
you're too old for me. You're too young
for me. And it was just pissing me off
watching it. It's not going to change.
It will never change.
>> Maybe when you're 50 will change.
on the ambulance here.
>> What happened?
>> Yeah, they got the [ __ ] police to my
door. They little pricks.
>> The [ __ ]
>> Saying that I'm [ __ ] suicidal and all
that. Lord, the police and the ambulance
and all that. They'll just come out.
What the [ __ ]
>> But it's not going to change though. Um
ghosting because it would have changed by now.
>> Sorry, bro. The police have just seen
the chat and all that but as well. I'm
just going to the police chat what they
talk about on this chat. >> Wow.
>> Yeah, they just please come asking me if
I'm suicidal and all that lot. And then
the ambulance crew I'm not suicidal.
I only hurt myself. It's cuz I wanted to
get the pain. I wanted to get rid of the
pain. God bless.
>> The pain,
>> the pain's not going.
The pain is not going. That's how much I
love N. You know what I mean? I love her.
>> I told them to be
>> And this is why I need to get off
YouTube to be honest with you, cuz of that [ __ ] >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Guys, I got Wel and Swindon and
Colchester and Tremier. They just need
to both score and
Yeah, I get a lot of people [ __ ]
troll me, bro.
>> You're not even trolls. You're [ __ ] idiots, PJ.
>> Yeah, but you know.
>> Anyway, I'll make you anyways. I'm done
with YouTube. It's up to Natalie what
she wants to do from here now.
>> If she wants to talk to me and forgive
me or not,
>> entirely up to her to be honest with
you. I don't give a [ __ ] but I do give
a [ __ ] But also, I don't give a [ __ ]
But I do give a [ __ ] You know what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> I give a [ __ ] but I'm starting to not
>> Just [ __ ] her. Is it?
>> What do you mean [ __ ] her?
>> Like to like get get like just to [ __ ]
with her. Like don't don't worry about
it. You know what I mean?
>> I [ __ ] I love her, mate. I love her.
And she needs to understand I love her.
>> Blessing her. Well, I'm going to stop
about that, man. I'm getting too [ __ ] cling on. >> Bless.
>> What time is it, PJ? >> 3:07.
>> I don't smoke weed anymore, people. I've
quit the weed. I want to put my weight
on. I want to get big again. I haven't
had weed for like two to three days, and
that's no [ __ ] I've not had weed
for for three days. [ __ ] quick weed.
>> You been on that roulette. You've been
on roulette ghosting.
>> Oh, PJ, when you get here. Yeah.
>> Might have to [ __ ] put 50 quid in
your bank to get out. I don't have my
bank card. My bank card at my m
I've been trying to throw this [ __ ]
50 quid out all [ __ ] night and all
day. I can't get a house. Monty's skin.
Nah, Monty's not skint, man. I'm skinty's not skin.
I just want Natalie to ring me something
at least explain to her, but I don't
think she anymore. I really don't think she is
cuz I am a big [ __ ] up, mate. I am a big [ __ ] up.
>> But I told Natalie Lee before she even
got with me. I will make mistakes.
I've told Natalie Le, I will make
mistakes. I mean, coming on YouTube, but
it was a mistake.
>> Okay, we've already got one goal from
Warsaw. Let's go, son.
>> Come on, man. We need this to come in.
But yeah, see that?
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Is Where is she now? Monty,
>> she's in her room. She's ignoring me, Lord.
just [ __ ] go on the door in it.
>> I'm not doing that. That's just [ __ ]
harassing her, mate.
I'm not doing that [ __ ] I'm going out
you and Natalie can come with us if she
wants or not. I would like
>> she going to come.
>> She She won't answer me. Look, watch now.
See, I knock on the door. Natalie,
>> what is she doing in there? Just don't
she leave the room?
>> Yeah, she leaves the room, but we're now
[ __ ] in my bedroom while I'm out.
I pissed her right off, mate. She won't
come out of the bedroom.
>> Wind ghosting. This better [ __ ] win, bro. >> Send.
>> You think it will?
Set send not under.
I've been trying to get
me. I'm not doing it no more.
>> She might be dead.
>> She's not dead. She can't. She's not
>> Yeah, obviously. Of course I'm still
going, bro. The [ __ ]
Travel to Birmingham. Why won't I travel
to Birmingham? I've been all over the
country. Why would I travel to Birmingham?
>> I've been all over the country by
myself. I've been out the country by
>> I do want Natalie to come Birmingham
with us for a drink.
>> I really do. >> Yeah,
>> that's what I want. I want Natalie to
come with us to come and have a drink.
Let's come and sort this [ __ ] out.
Swindon will score definitely. I always
bet on Swindon. It's just the other
match is quite um concerning, isn't it?
Yeah, Swindon. I always bet on Swindon
by myself. What? By myself. Go to
Birmingham by myself. Yeah, I did go I
went everywhere by myself.
Why is that surprising?
I learn everywhere about myself.
>> Yeah, Monty, that person just gave you
some good advice there. >> What?
>> He said, "Jamie, just get off YouTube
and focus on Natalie." I think that's
good advice now.
>> It is good advice and and that's what I
am going to do. I am going to do that. I
need to And this is why I'm trying to
get Natalie's attention, you know, and I
take that advice. I I I'm I'm listening
and I need to listen to people like
>> why why why does that surprise you that
I've been everywhere by myself?
>> Am I disabled? Not not as not as
disabled as you and uh
>> yeah Swindon. I always I always bet on Swindon. Um
[ __ ] what's your name? Ghosting. I
always do Swindon and I always do Oxford
United as well when they play cuz
there's always way they always score.
>> It takes two people to care about each
other, not just one. You know what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> If I was going to jump off YouTube, I
need Natalie to understand and willing
willingly to to stay off YouTube. I
don't want to come back on YouTube.
I just need Natalie to understand I'm
here for her. No one else. I'm on YouTube.
>> Why did it surprise you that I've been
everywhere by myself? Timmy Eldridge.
What's surprising about it?
>> He's Timmy there. Is he? >> No.
>> Oh, okay. It's a fake one. >> Yeah.
>> Natalie knows where I am. She can pick
up the phone. Soon as she picks up, soon
as she rings me, I'll be off YouTube. I
get off YouTube. Or as soon as she comes
out of her room and talks to me, I get off YouTube.
>> Yeah. Give it a whirl.
>> Only what I said. This is only what what
I said. PJ. Yeah. Obviously, you've
heard what what I said. This is what I
said. I tell you what I said about
>> why. I tell you. Yeah. When you when did
you kick me out the hotel? When I went
live, I started saying B [ __ ] Started
saying I don't know why I moved to
Birmingham on that. Like all what she
does is kick me out of hotel rooms
[ __ ] when I wake up. It's like this is what
>> this guy said. This guy said I won't
travel to Birmingham. Why won't I travel to Birmingham?
>> I actually feel sorry for Monty.
No, I don't want to freeze him. I was only joking.
>> Who do you hate the most on here?
>> Who do I get the most?
>> I hate L and yeah,
I don't think it's coming in matey.
Hopefully it does. But
>> well, PJ, do you know when you talk to
women, do women not reply back to you?
>> Yep. All the time.
>> So, why do women reply back to me when I
talk to women?
>> No, some do, but a lot of them don't if
I just met them.
>> Yeah. Well, say that. Natalie's not even
replying to me.
>> I don't [ __ ]
>> Natalie will ride me like a sea biscuit.
No, she's not. She's She's not as exper
she hasn't got more sex experience than
me. Do you know how many escorts I've
banged? Do you know how many people I've
banged and escorts? She ain't got more
experience than me, son.
>> Maybe more than one. >> Yeah.
>> Uh, hang on. Hang on a minute. PJ
Natalie is very experted in bed.
>> Do you know? Yeah, but I've slept with
more people than she has technically.
>> If you want to be technical about it,
>> she is the best I've ever had. And I'm
not just saying that she is the best
I've ever had.
>> Yeah. I'm not saying that she's not, but
I'm saying that obviously I've I've
banged [ __ ] god knows how many
escorts, bro. Jesus.
>> I'm the best liquor. I'm the best liquor
outer she's ever had. I've let her out
that much. She makes I make it come and
everything just with my tongue.
>> I bet it tastes nasty, is it?
>> No, actually. No, it doesn't. I don't
eat [ __ ] me.
>> I eat [ __ ]
>> It's [ __ ] disgusting.
>> Oh, okay. Yeah, just
Yeah, Tra is about to score. Come on
now. Come on. Yes.
>> Just two more goals now. Come on. We
just need two more. We just need two
more goals, [ __ ]
We just need two more goals, [ __ ]
>> Only what I'm going to say. I'm going to
drop it. It's Natalie. I love you and
I'm sorry. I'd never go back on YouTube.
>> No, this bet's coming in, bro. This
bet's coming in.
>> Are you really PGA?
>> If we get two more goals. Yeah. Oh, I
should have bet on that Selfford [ __ ]
game. They've already scored. I just
need two more, bro. It's only been 40
minutes as well. They should they should score, bro.
>> I'm going to set off later if it's 40
minutes cuz coming out three for
>> Oh, yeah.
>> I'm going to set off now.
>> I'm going to keep everything on for a minute. >> Yeah.
I just need Swindon and Colchester to
score. They've got to score, man.
chest is playing home as well. So,
>> how much will you win, PJ?
>> Uh, I put £80 on it. It gets 285. So,
it's quite nice profit, isn't it?
>> £200. 205.
>> It's good, isn't it?
>> You know what, PJ? If Natalie rings me
now, Yeah. I'll be off YouTube. I'll be
off it. I just talk to you on Facebook.
>> That's good, isn't it? 205 pound profit. Yeah.
>> Going on.
I need to stop going on about
>> someone just give me a slap. Yeah, I
need a slap.
Do need a slap.
>> I reckon another one's going to score by
the time. Yeah, we're on the [ __ ]
17th minute. We just need them. Imagine
they just both got penalties now.
[ __ ] Imagine. there.
It's not even been 20 minutes. Jesus,
it's horrible when it ends nil nil.
I [ __ ] hate that, bro. When it's nil,
when they're both They're both early.
You got some early ones there.
No, I wouldn't.
Monty likes it
in wings. What's that say?
>> PJ, would you bomb that?
>> No. Why you winging PJ? I said about
Kaye. The bottom one, not Natalie.
>> Oh, Kay wigs.
>> Any comments like that? I don't read
read them out. I don't give it what they
say. I don't reading them. What did you
What did it say?
>> They said K in wigs. >> K
>> K in wigs. Yeah.
>> What? What? What does that mean?
Got a wig.
>> Ask him what he means by K wears wigs.
If Nat single, I'm moving in. Good luck with that.
It's got reading in that in that one out there.
>> They're the ones writing it, isn't it?
>> Yeah, I know. But don't read them out.
They only doing it to piss me off.
>> Why? Why would they want to do that?
>> Because they know I [ __ ] Cuz they
know that I love Nap.
I'm going to have a big McDonald's today.
Come on, matey. We need this bet to win,
>> Otherwise, we're poor, matey.
We're going to go casino as well, Monty, today. Yeah.
>> Monty, we're going casino today as well. Oh yeah. >> Well,
>> is that okay with you, boss? >> What?
>> We're going casino today as well. >> Casino. >> Yeah.
>> I don't gamble PGA.
>> You will when you're with me.
Who? I'm not I'm not answering that
question. Stop asking me weird questions.
I would just like to come on YouTube one
day and these people don't come on, you know. >> Huh?
>> What? PG?
>> I said I just hope one day I can just
come on YouTube, right? And Oh, w got a
red card. Um, I just want to come on
YouTube one day and these people not be
on here. You know,
would it happen? >> What?
>> Well, I can just I just come on here one
day and these people don't they're not on here.
>> The these will never get off YouTube,
PG. They stay on here every You know,
>> maybe one day it'll come off.
I think one day they'll come off.
>> No, they only come off when you're in
the grave, mate. Like,
>> but and then even then they won't in it. >> Yeah.
Yeah, bro. Come on, Swindon. Come on, Colchester. score.
You [ __ ] wankers. We also got a red
card as well. They've got Swinn's got a score, man.
I think I've got this one, bro.
There's some nice early goals there, bro.
One second, bro. I'm coming back. Yeah.
Just getting a drink.
making a tea,
bro. We should have that one, man.
We should have this one
in the [ __ ] bag, bro. They got a
[ __ ] They already got a red card in it.
Oh, that one got postponed.
This has got more chance than any of
them. I think >> Yeah,
>> come on.
Just both score.
All they got to do is score. You're
getting emotional, man.
>> God bless you then. >> Look,
you're getting [ __ ] emotional.
>> Oh, bless.
>> No, it's not even funny, mate. It's not
even funny. I've never felt like anyone
in my life, Mark. Never.
>> I've never felt like this for anybody. Anybody.
I'm [ __ ] so in love, man. One side.
>> Oh, PG.
>> One second, bro.
Just make one second. I'll be right
back. Yeah, I'm just muting my mic.
>> Yeah, go for it. Sorry.
>> I miss any money. >> What
>> do you think? Do you think nons legs
will ever lose his virginity? >> Who? >> Nons.
>> I don't give a [ __ ] about Sean. [ __ ] non
obsession with him.
>> No, but I'm saying just do you reckon Do
you reckon he's going to die? One shastics. [Laughter]
Oh, bless you.
>> Oh, he's not forgive me that
>> we just need Colchester and Swindon to
score. What do you What do you think the
chances are, Steven? It's the 26th
minute. I think they're going to score.
Both of them me. They better do
otherwise I'm going to go and beat them up.
>> I needed to forgive me, man. I really
[ __ ] do. Huh? Natalie need Natalie to forgive me. >> Then >> what?
>> Yeah, they've got a red card. That's
good. So then we just we just need Come
on, man. We need to win this [ __ ]
It's looking good, bro. It's not looked
this good for a very long time.
It's not looked this good for a very
long time, man.
To be fair.
>> [ __ ] women. I'm I'm kind of related
with women no more
>> and all the others are like nil nil as
well. So if anyone's going to do it,
it's got to be this game, bro.
I need that £200. That's going to pay
for my number one cocaine.
>> Cocaine. What is that? What you want?
Some coke. Is it?
>> No, I'm only playing.
I'm going to make a cute little video.
I'm going to make a cute video. It's
going to be so cute. >> I'm right.
>> How do you get a woman to be gay for your man?
go to America and beat the man. >> No,
>> that's what I was going to do.
>> That's not really giving, is it?
>> Yeah, she she led me on and used me. Monty,
>> which I think is pretty low. What do you think?
>> Some I don't get women why women are
like this to be honest with you, man.
Only what a man wants is a is a woman to
love him. for his mistakes and for who he is.
>> No, that's a load of bullets.
>> It is a load of bullets cuz a man loves
a woman for anything. What they If a
woman [ __ ] up in a relationship, a man
doesn't finish any [ __ ] A man want
the police for threatening to batter me.
>> Oh, what you a grass, Kaye?
>> Oh, Kayie, do you want I have never even
threatened to battle you. You [ __ ]
parade. So, so you be getting done there
for lying. You correct?
>> She's a grass, isn't it?
>> No, she's going to get in [ __ ] for false allegation
>> because the video's right here with her
shouting and screaming. So, she's the
one who's going to get [ __ ] Don't
delete this video, PJ.
It's not because Kay is going to get
[ __ ] for lying about me threatening
her and that cuz I ain't even threatened
her. So if Kay's rung with the police
saying that frightening day, Kay's going
to get in a lot of [ __ ] a lot of [ __ ]
for making the postation.
>> So that's all right.
>> Only what I have to do anyway is show
the police on my head and tell her that
tell the police how she put a cup over
my head and everything else like that.
I've already told the police that that
she abused me when she when the police
just come to the door. That abusive
relationship my misses you used to abuse me.
>> You know what I was gonna do? I was
going to pick Cambridge and Chelton him.
You know Steven Howard. Luckily I
didn't. Is it Cambridge and shouting
him? I was I was going to pick them but
I never Good thing I didn't. It
>> really PJ's got the full video with you
up here. I haven't even threatened you.
You sad woman. Go and lose your wig. [Laughter]
Yeah, that's the good thing, isn't it?
>> If I pick that [ __ ] Cambridge and
chat with him.
>> You know what, K? I'm going to get I'm
going to get the video up actually on my
phone now if the police do come so I can
show the police like that you're
actually chatting [ __ ] to get you arrested myself.
>> Oh, bless you.
>> No, I'm going to get her arrested, mate,
for chatting [ __ ]
When did you come in?
>> Yeah, I think I think my one's got the
best chance in it. Steven Howard, mine's
I think mine's the best chance of
winning. I think if any of them are
going to win. Come on.
Really? You're the one who's going to
get n false allegation.
This is what I'm on about. You're going
to, in fact, I'm going to ring up the
police now. I just tell them what you
doing, Kelly. [ __ ] it. I'm going to ring
them up now and give them your address,
you thick [ __ ] Yeah, watch. I do it on
loudspeaker at 1299.
There you go. Ringing. I do on
loudspeaker, you stupid win, bro.
>> So, what do you get? 220, I get 280.
Please can I have the police, please?
>> Police emergency. What's the location?
>> Um, I'm home in Birmingham and what it
is is my misses, my ex Mrs. She keeps
ringing the police up saying that um I
threatening to batter her and stuff like
that. I've got the video here proving
that I haven't threatened or anything
like that. She keeps trying to send the
police to me house with false
allegations and stuff like that. Um, and
I want to and I want to press charges
now. I want to do something about it
because this has been going on now for a
while now with her. If you want a name,
her name is called
>> Grezy's loving this, isn't it?
Grezy is just loving this.
So that I've got the text is here as
well writing on my mate's channel saying
that she's getting the police for like
I'm threatening her and all that look.
>> Okay. What's your name?
>> My name is Jam Hey.
>> She's already put a cup over my head as
well back in her time back ago. She put
you can watch in a big blue house
the same website
>> cuz I lied to the police it was someone
else so I basically stood up for her. Um
I also on this as well she smacked my
daughter in her face and she put my
daughter on the bed at me. My daughter
was new as well. Um, I didn't even tell
social services this either, but I
thought I might as well just get it out
in the open now.
>> Okay, that's fine. Let me get these bits
down for you.
>> Thank you.
>> Monty likes this.
>> Uh, what's your home address, please?
Uh, it's um 71.
Is this bet going to win? Um,
is this bet going to win? Steven Howard,
it better [ __ ] win.
I was going to do Akring and
Chillingham. It's good thing I changed
my bets in it. The ones I was going to
do was still nil nil.
Still [ __ ] nil nil.
It's good thing I
sat in the chat room saying prove it.
Laughing saying prove it. Prove it.
So just stand here now on the chat room
saying I prove it with a lad >> chat. >> Yeah,
that's um on YouTube. I can give you a
YouTube channel as well if you want that.
>> Is it going to win? Do you think
>> you as well? So I give you
a YouTube channel. Now, um I I can't
exactly read it to you, but I will spell
it out letter to letter.
>> Yeah, that's fine. Thank you.
>> Um so, it is X. >> Yeah.
>> So, X dash >> Yeah. >> K. >> H.
>> A for apple. >> Yeah.
>> O for orange. >> Yeah.
T for tag. >> Yeah.
>> A for igloo. >> Yeah.
>> For cat. >> Yeah.
>> Dash x.
>> So many nil nils.
>> Yeah. The YouTube name.
>> Yeah. The YouTube name. Yeah.
>> Okay. Thank you.
>> No, you're right.
cuz she said that that she run the
police on me for threatening her. I've
not threatened her. That's why I run you
up putting false claims on me. But what
I'm doing is not false. I need to get
the truth out there about this woman,
what she has done and what she's doing
to me now.
Okay. I'll get
>> Come on.
>> Okay. So, you know, you said about the the mug. >> Yeah.
>> When did that happen? Um that happened
uh about three three year ago I imagine.
>> And what was it that happened?
>> Um I was talking to a woman um on
YouTube but we weren't going out. We
were just close friends
>> and um
>> I wanted to come in but it needs to ex
out and then
>> but I don't think it will.
>> Obviously I never cheated on I've never done anything.
>> Swindon and Coldchester. Swindon and
Coldchester need to score, man. Come on.
>> And that's how it all started with the
mug. She end up slamming the mug off of my head.
>> And they need to score.
>> The SC is on my right side of my head.
Um above my here. The side of my back.
This side of my back of my head. >> Yeah.
>> Hope it wins, bro.
They should have got the best chance of
winning anyway initially, but you said
that um it wasn't her that that caused
>> Look at all them nil nils. She got a cop
off my head.
>> Look at all these nil nils.
>> That's what I mean. But you said that
you covered that up for her. So when you
reported, but you told them she didn't do it.
>> Yeah. Yeah,
>> I covered that up for her. >> Okay.
And that's it really. >> Yeah.
>> Okay. And then what did you say happened
with um was it your daughter when she was newborn?
>> My new newborn daughter. She chopped her
I was I was um upstairs in the bedroom
on the bedrooms
playing with me and daughter.
Um come upstairs with my youngest
daughter and she was all a newborn at
this time and she said you can have her
now and then just ch
>> he ended up going underneath the crook cover.
>> I think it's got like
>> so I ended up picking her up. I went mad
at her but I didn't report it. I should
have done really
>> I just need another before the [ __ ]
half time bro. And then there was one
more incident where my oldest daughter
was playing around at night time when
she weren't going to bed. So I picked
her up about to bedroom like I had a
flat like Superman
>> and then she come running upstairs
and then went [ __ ] off right into her
face when cuz right into her face. Flat
on into her face.
>> I'm just looking at this.
>> I mean from her eye from her face not
not from the back of her head. was in
front of her face, slapped her right
dead on on her face.
>> Come on, man.
>> And she would have been about
>> right now.
>> But the rest are nil nil. What the [ __ ]
Lucky I didn't do any of the others.
Swindon need to score. I don't know why
Swindon ain't scored now.
>> I need to get this out instead of
keeping it. I think I need a gate cuz
it's stuck in my head what she's done to
me, what she's done to my kids. And
>> I can't let it I can't let it slide. Do
you know what I mean? It's
>> No, of course.
>> My daughter will even tell you as well.
My oldest daughter, she's se seven. She
will even tell you six.
>> So, she will tell you as well. She She
even she even knows.
>> Swindon, come on.
>> [ __ ] Why have they got a penalty?
You just all this for you. If I go
quiet, I am still here.
>> No, no, no. That's bad. That's
>> need to get a penalty.
>> Did you actually put 60 on the same bit
as me, Steven or you just trolling?
>> You are just [ __ ] taking a piss in
it. YouTube and that calls me names and
that calls me [ __ ] cuz I've got
disabilities. I've got HD and spectral
myism and she sits there and takes piss
out of my disability as well.
>> Is this on that um chat room? >> Yeah.
>> You reckon it's going it should win is
it? It should win it.
>> It's live on YouTube. You reckon it's
going to win
on my mate's panel. cheesy and now
riding away laughing and
>> Oh, come on, man.
>> If you need her address, I can ring my
mom up and get her address.
>> [ __ ] it. Look how many nil nails there are.
>> Okay, bear with me. >> Nails.
What the [ __ ]
Yeah, Colchester needs to [ __ ] score as well.
>> I think it's um is is Linton Drive in Leicester?
>> Yeah, Colchester needs to [ __ ] score, too.
>> I think it's Linton Drive. She lives at
Leicester. Linton Drive. Do
>> you think Colchester will score?
>> It's um the block block of flats at the side.
I can give you the door number and the actual address.
>> Yeah, if you've got that for you.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I'll get that for you now.
Just got to get on the phone now quickly
to my mom and get that for you. Sorry about that.
>> PJ, I'll be right back.
>> Oh, Chucky,
how are you, Chucky? I haven't watched
you in ages, Charles Lee Ray. A Ah. A bless. Come on.
Come on. Slow. Chucky. Yeah, Chucky.
What's the chance of this bet actually
winning Steven Howard? Like 70%. Come on.
We just need Colchester to score and
then we can basically say one swing going score.
It'd be nice to win the first the first
season, you know, the first the start of the season.
I don't think it's going to win, matey.
Still no goals.
Come on. Score. Score. [ __ ] score, man.
Cuz all the others are nil nil.
That's the thing, bro. Cuz all the
others are nil nil, you see.
So if it any is going to win, it's going
to be these two. [Music] Come on.
They're not going to score.
Colchester is not going to score, bro.
No, I think they'll score.
I think I think they will. I think
they'll both score.
If any's going to win, it's going to be them.
If any is going to win, it's going to be
that. It's going to be them.
Yeah. 80 nothing to me, son.
So, yeah. Stop trying to troll me
because you can never troll someone like me, bro.
80 nothing to me. So, I don't give a [ __ ]
It was a good start though.
But there's loads of load there's loads
of nil nils.
Loads of nil nils in it, bro. Loads of
nil nils. [ __ ]
Yeah, I know there is. But it would have
been nice to have got a 1-1 in the
[ __ ] first half, you know.
Yeah, it would have been nice.
But my picks were still good even if it
does lose because look at all the other
teams. They're [ __ ] nil nil. Imagine
you put £4,000 on two teams
and then they won.
Oh, could you imagine?
Could you imagine? Yeah,
that'll be a lot of money, bro. Oh [ __ ]
So, you think there's an 80% chance? Yeah. Oh, no.
It's good I didn't do a and chilling. I
would have been [ __ ]
I would have been [ __ ] if I done them too. Yeah.
Yeah. I would have been [ __ ] bro. I
actually would have been
I actually would have been [ __ ]
There has to be, bro, cuz they're the
only ones that have been scoring. One sec. the uh
why is there so many uh
why is there so many nil nils?
Why is there so many [ __ ] nil nils, bro?
It's weird, isn't it?
So many nil nils.
So many nil nils, isn't it?
What the [ __ ] Why is there so many Neil Nils, bro?
I think we picked the right teams. I
think we actually picked the right
teams, bro. I think this is our best chance. Really?
Yeah, this is our best chance, I think.
cuz I was like I said I was going to do
Aquinon and Chilling
and I was going to do Bristol and
they're and they're both nil nil.
So I think I always pick like Colchester
and Swindon. I pick Oxford United as well.
or Oxford United's playing
Swindon I think next week or another
team. I might put like a 100 pound on
it. Who knows?
But this is the best. I think I think we
picked him all right to be honest.
It's hard to win football bets, in it, Steven Howard.
Yeah, it's very hard.
It's hard, bro.
It is a mugs game, bro.
It is a Mug's game. I'm only gambling to
try to get some extra money, bro, to be
fair. But it is a Mugs game. All of it.
Do you think roulette is a Mug's game as well? Yep.
You better [ __ ] score, you
Go collect the money. Go to Birmingham.
Give Monty his little hat.
A bless. We'll have £300 to spend.
Do you think that will be enough? Train,
hotel, drinks, £300. Yeah,
it's more than enough, man.
Go to the little coral, pick up the winnings,
and off we trod. Oh, bless.
Yeah, I'm lucky I didn't pick them two
[ __ ] teams. I would have been fat.
I've won a few of them before. 60 pound
200. I've won a lot of these both teams
to score, bro. A lot of them.
Like lots of them.
Yeah. I've got
I've done a fewund pound ones before.
They've never won. Yeah.
I done I remember I was on a date in
Birmingham. I won one in Birmingham.
I've won a few of them, bro. Um,
going to Manchester, I've won them. I've
won I won like four times in a week before.
I have won a lot of them.
So you think there's a
So you think right that there's a
80% chance of winning this bet.
Colchester has got a score, man. [ __ ]
hell. and Swindon.
What about a Arending and uh Crystal? Nah.
No chance, mate. Nah.
Nah, they're not. That's not happening, bro.
It [ __ ] better do, mate.
It [ __ ] better do, son.
Anyways, I'll be gone. They'll come
back. Yeah. When