Make your move. [Music]
>> Oh, I know. I know you know planet. [Applause] [Music]
>> Come on.
>> You're supposed to beat me today. >> Yes. [Music] [Applause] Any
of you want me to fight? Let's go for
it. Any views of YouTube, let's go for
If you think I'm sorry, let's go for it. [Applause] [Music]
Come on, Shimmy.
Come on. You push it all. I'm in your city, boy.
They won't beat me regardless. They're [ __ ]
>> They won't be.
>> They won't get [ __ ] [Applause]
[ __ ] [ __ ] Oh, it is
classic. Come on.
You know the shot. Come on. You [ __ ]
>> you. Come on.
>> You want us
on [ __ ] YouTube every day.
>> No life. New people's got no life.
>> They all [ __ ] on YouTube.
>> New people are classic. [Applause]
Hey, darling. Come on. [Music]
We ruin Bingington. We ruin it. We
[ __ ] ruin B.
We are the Birming. >> Yeah. [Music] [Applause] It's your man.
I'm not I'm not [ __ ]
Wait, there you [Music] want. in here. All women soldiers.
>> What shimmy [Music] soldiers?
>> We want it.
I fell in [ __ ] Jimmy.
Remember that snow? >> Yeah. [Music]
>> Tell them
the natural war is [ __ ] off. [ __ ] off.
Naturally, I love you, Nar. Oh, wait. They're [ __ ] [ __ ] 10. >> Yeah. [Music]
It's not even Timmy.
>> You're Timmy.
>> No one. No one will cover me. No one feel like never
I am not going live anymore.
I love Natalie. I'm not going live no more.
>> I finished YouTube. YouTube. I finished. I'm done.
>> End now. Get some pictures. Are they