[ __ ]
got so [ __ ] prolific. Prolific hiccups. [ __ ] me.
Too much drinking last night. Oh my god.
That's an understatement. Oh
[ __ ] One sec, bro. Hold up.
You get back. Okay. [ __ ]
Oh, bro. I'm [ __ ] I ain't even slept
yet. I had to go on three trains, you
know, cuz the [ __ ] ticket to [ __ ]
It was being a [ __ ] I had to go and
then one of the trains got Oh, I had to
get three trains. It was so long, bro.
Oh, I'm so glad to be back. [ __ ] bro. What? Oh, hiccups.
Oh my god. Monty, bro.
>> Yes, PJ.
>> What are you doing?
>> [ __ ] chilling, bro.
That one mental,
>> huh? It was good, is it?
>> That one mental. >> Yeah.
>> Did you like it?
>> [ __ ] up, >> huh?
>> Them two birds. Them two [ __ ] birds last night.
>> Yeah, I got a hand job.
>> That [ __ ] bouncer.
>> That bouncer. Do you know what? Yeah.
Even though I weren't involved yet, it
was I got involved because it was
annoying me, bro. that bouncer.
>> Yeah, it was annoying me. That's why I got involved.
>> I was going to drop him, was I? I was
going to chop him.
>> Yeah, he's a [ __ ] bro. He's only acting
big cuz there's police there.
>> Yeah, they cuz the police are like the B.
>> In London, they're not [ __ ] in
London. They're not [ __ ] like that,
bro. You don't get them like that in London, bro.
>> Yeah. No [ __ ] hell.
>> I don't really like Birmingham, bro.
>> Birmingham's good. It's good. It's all
right. It was a midnight last night.
It's not that. Don't forget I didn't
have my ID on me, did I?
>> I left my
>> I think London's better, though.
>> I've never been clubbing. That was my
first ever going out doing that, man.
>> I've never ever done that in my entire life.
>> Well, you owe me £200. I'm only joking.
Only joking, bro. You owe me £2152.
>> I'm joking. We had a blast.
They [ __ ] did.
>> We had a nice blast, bro.
That breakfast. That breakfast was nice.
>> It will, wasn't it?
>> Yeah, we had a nice omelette. >> Yeah. >> [ __ ]
what? I I can't remember my name, but I
[ __ ] last night, mate.
>> Uh, what?
>> I got I got free numbers on the Facebook.
Yeah. I w I weren't even called approaching me.
>> I got hand job.
>> Yeah. Got a hand job, PJ. That's it.
>> Yeah. Got a hand job off that girl.
>> But I wanted more.
>> Me. I couldn't do it to Natalie. Peeps.
The girl was trying it on with me. I
couldn't do it.
>> Ah, bro.
I need a nice coffee today. What are you
going to carry out?
>> Yeah, the bet come in it, bro.
The bet come in.
>> The bet come in did it.
>> Yeah, I told Stephen Howard what bet to
do. It was a good bet in it, bro.
>> I still my winnings yet. I still yet.
>> The funny thing is, yeah,
>> BJ is a funny bastard.
>> He picks up the wrong bank card and
comes to Birmingham with the wrong bank
card. when he tried his bank card, it said decline.
>> Oh, bro, it's not funny, bro. If my
sister didn't let me, I would have been [ __ ]
>> Yeah, I know. I know.
>> We would have actually been [ __ ] bro.
>> I I just paid it back when I come back.
>> Yeah. I can't believe you done that on
an empty stomach. None of us ate. We didn't eat.
>> I'm still not eating except for that
breakfast from this morning.
Yeah, I bro I I didn't eat. I basically
didn't even eat.
Yeah, that prime's a puss [ __ ] and that
to me. Don't if they ever try calling
you out again.
>> I know they never did this [ __ ] back.
>> Don't Don't respond to them.
>> No, I'm not. I'm not. I've done it now.
I went to Birmingham.
>> They had their shots. Well, Timmy did.
Timmy was there. He had his shots.
>> Of course he did. I spent about I think 160
>> with uh maybe Yeah. including a train.
Including a train 160 man.
>> Oh PJ
don't say nothing but um I sent you a
text. Did you see it?
>> Yeah, I see it. We'll talk about it later. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. But can you say your own or
do you still want it? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. But it Well, it's there anyways.
>> Yeah. We'll talk about it later. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Cuz of these [ __ ]
>> Call on here. I'm not giving up nothing.
Nothing at all.
>> Hey, Monty can be my witness. I I even
done a sober one in front of you, didn't I?
>> Yeah. He did a sober one. I as well
sober when I did one. Yeah.
>> Orchard Road.
>> I couldn't do it, PG. I couldn't do the
pulled approaching. I couldn't [ __ ]
my penis, man.
>> Oh, yeah. I was I asked for that stitch
and you wouldn't give me it. >> What?
>> I I asked you for that stitch you didn't
give me. Remember >> Stitch?
>> I'm not going to give you Stitch.
>> I wanted Stitch. I told you.
>> But to be honest with you, Birmingham is
worse than London though.
>> The statute mine
>> London all the way. There. So I
Notorious. Me and Monty went to
Birmingham and the thing is with
Birmingham. Yeah. There's so many stuck
up women there. But I got a um snug hand
job. But there I approached a lot of
people, bro. And there it seemed like it
was even worse than London.
I only had my name is [ __ ] I think it
was hard two girls until we got to that
[ __ ] club. The last
>> you're I got three numbers on the
Facebook but bro it was hard and the
bouncers are [ __ ] in Birmingham. Ask
Monty. They're proper [ __ ]
>> Yeah, one of the bounces taught me to
move. I didn't He told me to move three times.
>> I weren't moving.
>> So I told him to [ __ ] off. Don't tell me
to move. Yeah. Let me let me tell
everyone what they said. Yeah. They said
me and Monty can't go into one club
unless we're with a group of girls. I
was like, "Bro, you're a s." And he
started getting all aggy and that.
>> I was like, "Bro, you're a [ __ ] I
said to him, you're a s." Because let me
tell you something, bro. I live in
London yet and I've never heard of that
rule in my life. Ever.
>> Well, because it was with girls.
>> Oh, there's so many men in there,
>> bro. But it was only it was only two of us.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I know. I know. And then I
told him, "Right, okay then. I tell you
what, then when he said that no more men
allowed in because there's too many men
in there." So I said, "Okay, I'm gonna
stand here then." Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> I said I said, "I'm going to stand here.
I'm going to watch how many men you let
in the public." Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. That
>> Yeah. He was a [ __ ] would he? I told
him I snap his jaw. We just stood there,
couldn't do [ __ ]
>> Orchard Road and a big [ __ ] guy come.
I [ __ ] t pushing me away. I told him
to basically do one.
>> I'm not bothered. >> Yeah,
>> you need to um next time something like
that happens, Monty. Yeah. You know what
you need to do? Don't um don't go close
to them. Do this. Yeah. Stand a bit away
from them and say, "Come by yourself,
big man." Around the corner. And if they
don't do it because the thing is the
thing is right if you get close to them
all that's going to happen is the other
B is just going to try and push you
away. So it's pointless.
>> I'm lost still.
>> You get me?
>> Yeah, I get you.
>> And obviously if he doesn't move then
he's a [ __ ] Simple.
Yeah. Prime was nowhere to be seen.
Timmy was nowhere to be seen. That's funny. E.
>> Yeah. Primal meet. That's the thing.
the same as [ __ ] Lord. Yeah.
>> Monty's natural Monty's an actual strong
[ __ ] You know,
>> what do you mean PJ?
>> Peter Belly had to come to Birmingham to
pick up the pieces, didn't I? Monty
near you though, didn't I? Huh? Did
nearly break your fingers.
Yeah, you did, bro. I was telling my mom. >> What?
>> I was telling my mom.
>> How' you [ __ ] get your name?
>> Yeah, Kayie, you are a nons.
>> You are a [ __ ] weirdo, Kay. You know
what, Kayie? I want to ask you a little
question. Why you a [ __ ] bully? Why?
Why do you bully your kid's dad?
Your your children's, you know, why why
why what's wrong with you? You say that.
Oh, she says that I do this yet to your
[ __ ] kids and that, but I was the I'm
the only one recently that's been that's
been there for you, you know.
>> Yeah, I know. Natalie's been there for
me. Kelly ass [ __ ]
you know what I mean? I
>> She's skinn and she she can't afford to
drink like us.
I get women, man. I get women.
>> You know what I mean?
>> I do. But my mom is a woman.
I have a mama.
>> Yeah, I've got a great mama. I've got a fantastic mom.
The best thing about my mom is that she loves Natalie.
>> We were both crying over our mommies yesterday, bro.
What a night PJ. Two birds. Two [ __ ]
birds. You know what? I should have got
>> I should have got off with you on camera.
>> [ __ ] man.
>> [ __ ] it.
>> Yeah, I should have. No. Respect, isn't it?
I'm getting pissed through, are you, man?
>> You're going to want to do it every Saturday now.
>> I am. Oh, I am [ __ ] doing it, mate.
>> I don't know how I Bro, do you know I
was getting the train back today? Yeah.
>> I don't know how I used to do it. Every
week go Newcastle, drink, come back. I
don't know how I used to do it. I don't
know how I used to do it, bro.
>> [ __ ] no, PJ.
>> I don't know how I used to do that, bro.
I didn't think I was going to make it
back today. I was so tired.
>> Oh, yeah. PJ is right. Anyways, because
um I've got a police call coming up
anyways as [ __ ] the police are getting
back in contact with me. Anyways, they
run they run me up last night if I could
do a video call with them about Kelly
when she's done what she done to Lord and Prim. >> Yeah,
>> cuz I haven't told anyone about it.
>> I haven't told the police about it. I
haven't told even social services about
it. But now I have
>> What are you going to eat today, bro? I
>> get a crisp, mate. Huh? A
>> packet of Chris?
I'm going to have a nice Indian
cuz I'm [ __ ] starving, bro.
We spoke to so many women though in it.
Well, what I did?
>> Yeah, we did. We did. We It's not that I
I was going to PJ. You were pushing me.
Come on. Go and call the pro [ __ ]
>> We were [ __ ] bro.
>> Weren't we? I'm still counting the [ __ ]
>> We had shots. We had
[ __ ] We had shots. We had
uh we had Guinness, we had um rum.
>> Yeah, Monty didn't think I was going to come.
>> They were taking a piss. It was that [ __ ]
>> I have to come because
if I didn't come, you would have cried
so I had to come. With you time with me
>> and the football bet won. So I had no
excuse not to really go and I had
nothing better to do. So,
>> I'm just sick. I know I'm just getting
sick of getting time wasted.
>> It was long though. It was long. >> Longer.
>> Uh, I think it depends what time you go
at to be honest with you.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
No, I'm not having I'm not like [ __ ]
legs. I have vindaloo.
>> A binding?
Is that what you had? Is it?
>> That's what I'm going to have. Oh, I
just put £80 on it. Returned 285. So,
just quick £25 and it's all right in it
>> for the first first game of the season.
>> You man, you're
you're going to have to sleep today in it.
>> Have I been sleep for [ __ ] a while,
mate? I've been awake.
I just been awake just chilling in the
bedroom on my phone and I know I just
got out. I can't be asked in
>> Yeah, Timothy Eldridge. Yeah, we called
Timmy out. We called Prime.
>> It's pretty funny. Yeah, because Timmy
was saying um he meet me in Birmingham.
He meet me in Birmingham yesterday. He
was supposed to meet me, never shown up.
But when Timmy shouts me out again,
I'm not showing up. >> Yeah,
>> I'm not just going to say [ __ ] off. I'm
not doing I'm not meeting him.
>> Turn right on road.
>> What the [ __ ] are you doing? >> Me? >> Yeah. >> Walking.
>> I got to use the satnav to work.
>> No, Monty didn't rape you, Katie. Shut up.
What the [ __ ]
Le I'm going to be telling the police
all this. Don't worry about it. Saying
that I'm raping you now. Don't worry.
Let the police know that the false
allegations you had, [ __ ]
>> I met K in person.
>> Yeah, she's a [ __ ] three.
She is a three
to be honest with you.
Yeah. What? [ __ ] sid.
>> Yeah, bro.
>> Early in case.
>> No, I just done an all nighter. I didn't
stay over. I just done an all nighter.
I got a train back at 11. Monty.
>> Yeah, cuz PJ Cuz PJ's not allowed back
at like a dress or anything. So, I had
to go back home.
>> Yeah, we just I just done an all nighter. Yeah.
Yeah, I did. I've done the all night as
well, mate. You're not the only one. I
got banging headache.
>> I haven't I think it was two years I
last went Birmingham. It's still the
same old [ __ ] hole.
>> I didn't I didn't run off nowhere, did I, Monty?
>> I met a couple of friends last night
before you turned up. Couple of lives and that.
>> I am shy. I am shy, but now I think I'm
over tired. It's and I had to get I had
to get on free trains as well. I had to
get on free trains. So, you know, I paid
um and it only applies to certain rails.
So, the ticket inspector come and he
kicked me off. He said, "You have to go
on this train." Then I went on that
train and that train got um
[ __ ] what happened? It terminated in
Northampton. So then I had to get off at
Northampton and then get another train.
I had to get on three [ __ ] different
trains. He was a [ __ ] He was as well.
He could have easily let me stay on that
[ __ ] train. [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> [ __ ] that ticket inspector maybe got
[ __ ] three [ __ ] trains, bro, to get back.
Um, I got a hand job and a snog.
But apart from that, it's it was
Birmingham's very hard, Joe.
Nah, I don't hate them, bro. It's a job
at the end of the day, but he was being
a [ __ ] He could have easily let me
stay on that train. and I had to go on
three [ __ ] trains. But yeah, I don't
like Birmingham, Joe. I don't like um
Yeah, the women are really stuck up
there. And the bouncers are [ __ ]
>> Me and problems with the bounces.
>> Yeah. Yeah, it is.
>> They're proper [ __ ] No, bro.
>> Two [ __ ] bouncers.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> The bouncer was all right. They were but
they were but they were stuck but they
were stuck up though. The women are
definitely stuck up in Birmingham. 100%.
100 million%. Birmingham is not easy bro.
>> Some of you might think.
I think it's like it anywhere now.
America, England. I think it's like that anywhere now. What is
>> just like how some of these women be and
that but yeah that ticket inspector was
a [ __ ] anyway.
Yeah, Joe. I thought there was no excuse
for me not to go. You know, if I didn't
if I didn't go, Monty would cry. I won
the football bet. Oh, I won my football
bet, by the way. So, I had no excuse not
to really go.
>> There's a few times I was going to do a U-turn.
I'd get to the train station say, "Can I
be bothered?" But I just went. I
thought, "Fuck it."
>> I'm actually shattered. I didn't even sleep. So
>> I been sleep either.
They won't p
>> No, he didn't.
>> Yeah, but I [ __ ] traveled from
[ __ ] London, bro. It was long
a long train as well. It weren't even a
fast one. Well,
>> you're back. Okay, you're back home now, are you?
>> Yeah, it's good to be back home.
When I always used to go traveling,
that's one thing I used to miss is that
is my bed in the room and that your own
house. I don't know
staying in alone.
Yeah, but I won't be out now for like
two three weeks.
Yeah, it was. I won't be out for like a
few weeks now cuz I I only went out
really cuz Monty wanted to go out and I
thought why not?
But it going to be every week, bro.
>> No, not every week. [ __ ] off.
>> The curry the curry place opens at 5, so
I have to wait until 5. I'm >> tell
>> Yeah, bro. I need a curry, man.
>> We're getting tonight. Is it?
>> You know what, Joe? I I I I was thinking
to myself, yeah, on that train back to
Birmingham, all hung over and [ __ ] How
did I used to [ __ ] do it? Like do it,
go to Scotland, get pissed, and come
back. I don't know how I used to do it.
I don't know how I used to do some of
them journeys. I It'd kill me now. I think
>> I saying you got it. You got from Birmingham safe,
you know, Birmingham to you got you come
to Birmingham safe and you got back.
>> No, no, no. But what I mean is the
travel the travel the traveling and
coming back hung over. It's not about it
being safe. I don't know how I used to
do it. I don't know how I used to do it,
bro. I went to Scotland, bro, for a
piss. Listen, I went to Scotland.
I flew to Scotland, went on a piss up
and come back in like 7 hours,
but I was I was falling asleep on the train though.
>> 7 hours?
>> Yeah, I was I was in Scotland for 8
hours and I just come back. Yeah, I used
to do bad things.
>> bad things I used to do. Bro,
>> I was going to drink some milk last
night, but I thought to myself cuz I was
drinking just gle sick. So, I didn't
>> No, I did have a hotel. I did. I did
have a hotel, but sometimes
Yeah, I've been Amsterdam. But yeah, I
did. I did. But what I done in es while
I done in Scotland I try drunk I tried
to pull couldn't pull got an escort and
then come back. So I went all the way
there just to basically
>> escort and come back.
>> That was mad bro. I can't believe I done
that. I was [ __ ]
I've gone to Manchester come back the
same day as well. I was [ __ ] bro like
three days after that. Wait, you a football? Yeah.
>> Yeah, I was [ __ ] bro.
That's how I tried to meet Bomb.
Yeah, I used to be wild and then I
realized that this country is a waste of
time. Like I said, I went to I wanted to
meet Monty cuz I hadn't drunk for two
weeks and he wanted to meet. So, I
thought, "Fuck it, bro."
>> Good night, little
>> You can tell we had a good night on all them videos.
Yeah, it was good, bro. >> Yeah,
>> that were [ __ ] awesome. Sorry about my
>> to a lot of places. When am I meeting
Monty again? I'm not sure.
>> Don't tell him nothing. PJ,
>> I think you
>> I think me, you and Longlegs should meet. >> What?
>> I think me, you, and Longlegs should go
for a beer.
>> Oh, long legs. Why do I keep bringing him up?
>> I never go for a drink with Sean on PE
on long on legs. Never.
>> Yeah. So that's what I was saying, bro. Um
Mont Monty should travel to me. Yeah,
Monty. I used to like going out with
Ant-Man as well. He used to he used to be fun. What year?
>> Oh, I had a friend called Antman. He
lives in Thailand now.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah.
>> I might have to stop meeting you. You're
quite you're quite heavy-handed.
>> What do you mean I'm heavy-handed?
>> Like you're a bit rough. A bit vicious.
>> What do you mean?
>> I don't know. He was a bit rough with me.
>> What is that?
>> Yeah. And it really hurt. No, seriously.
>> What? PJ, I'm not a strong PJ.
>> You hurt my hand. It made me bleed as well. Remember?
>> Well, yeah. Yeah, I made you bleed, didn't I?
>> Yeah, Monty's not to be [ __ ] with.
I mean, I'm delicate. Monty,
>> you're delicate.
>> I thought you was going to try and beat me up.
No, PJ, the thing is, yeah, you
apologized long before anyone else apologized.
>> Yeah, but Fraser tried to beat me up.
>> Fraser lives in Birmingham, don't he?
>> No, no, no, no, no. It was someone else.
No, no, no. Fraser, the one that lives near London,
>> he tried to beat me up. He lured me and
tried beating me up.
>> That's what I thought. See the thing is
money m you got understand when you meet
people right you need to think of if
you've ever had any past with them
>> that's what I mean with me and Natalie
me and Natalie's got a past on YouTube
and Natalie needs to understand that we
both come off YouTube
>> you know what I mean and Natalie
>> so obviously me and Natalie's got
history there with that because I used
to go in that
>> why are you so rough
>> what do you mean
>> like vicious
>> I'm not vicious She is.
>> Yeah, you are.
>> [ __ ] no. [ __ ] no. I don't know, mate. I don't know.
>> You was You were saying for me to punch
your abs. I didn't want to do that.
>> Yeah, you punched me abs, didn't you?
>> Yeah, but I didn't want to. You forced me.
>> [ __ ] solid, isn't it?
>> Yeah, but you you I I come for a drink,
not to punch people. Well, except private.
>> Yeah, people. But I let PJ punch me in
the belly hard as he could.
>> He did it.
>> I think Monty I think Monty might beat
me in a fight. >> What?
>> I said I think Monty might beat me in a
fight, you know.
I think you know, maybe. Yeah. Should
>> we have a fight PJ if he wins?
>> Yeah, but maybe it be 50/50. What?
>> Maybe it be 50/50.
I'll pick you up.
>> I'll pick you up.
>> You're stronger than everyone, is it?
>> No, it's just
strength, Pet. Yeah.
>> I think I think you could beat The Rock.
>> The Rock. >> Yeah. >> No.
>> Really? No.
[ __ ] the rock's a [ __ ] wrestler.
He used to be a wrestler. He was like,
"Oh, let me let me squeeze your hand."
And I was like, "Ow, stop. That hurts."
>> See, when I used to be a mad man, he
never used to do that stuff. Be heavy-handed.
>> Did he not?
>> No, he was quite gentle.
>> That was a PJ with me. I'm not I'm not
gentle. Also, you was doing you spilled
the [ __ ] drink all over us, you silly
[ __ ] It's lucky we was wearing black.
>> No. Yeah, I punched the table. The be
>> If we weren't wearing black, we would
have been [ __ ]
>> Yeah, be went everywhere. PJ's be went
everywhere. I punched the table. When I
punched the table,
>> you're a loose cannon.
>> When I punched the table,
>> I know what I thought you was going to
do, I think. I thought Yeah, I thought
before me going to the train station, I
thought you was going to try and hit me.
>> Did you?
>> Yeah, I'm prepared. Dude, look at things
that's happened before, bro.
>> PJ, I'll tell you if I'm going to whack
you or not. And if I say I'm not going
to whack you, I'm not going to whack
you. If I say I'm going to whack you,
I'm going to whack you. That was me.
>> Yeah, but look what Prime did.
Yeah, just little weasel. They all
little weasels in this community. All developing weasels.
>> This person this person says yet you
dress like a [ __ ]
>> Better dressed than you, you [ __ ]
>> Yeah, that's what they say.
>> Yeah. And so you call in the claws what
Natalie gets me. Trumpy. Yeah, [ __ ]
Hey everybody, do you like my little cap? >> What?
>> Do you like my little cap?
>> Yeah, you just said a good half on you, bastard.
>> I forgot to bring it. Legit forgot, bro.
>> That girl n my off me.
>> That girl n my off me and tried out in my baldness.
>> You couldn't wear uh That's the thing.
You couldn't wear um a hat in the club.
So when you couldn't wear your hat and
you showed everyone you're a bald head in it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I'm not ask about my baldness.
Look at that woman though. PJ who wanted
to talk me head all night stroking me at
the pub at the bar.
>> Oh yeah. What? She was stroke. She
didn't want me cuz I had hair.
>> Yeah. Yeah. She she didn't want PJ cuz
she had her she wanted me cuz I didn't
have her. She was stroking me head and
everything. And another ball man next to me.
touch your mind on his head.
>> [ __ ] hell.
We was crying over our mommies, weren't we?
>> I crying over my grandma. >> Yeah.
>> No, I keep crying off, not me, mate.
>> What do you What did you say you think
of the Birmingham? It's It's [ __ ]
hanging, isn't it?
>> I like the Birmingham good. I like it,
mate. Let me back.
>> You were taking your homeless friend for
a night out.
>> I'm not homeless. You [ __ ]
>> Yeah. You say he's is my mommy.
That's my mom. Hey, Grooy.
>> Oh, Timmy, if you go in town, Timmy, if
you're watching Yeah. Just look at the
grids. Yeah, there was wet cement on the
grid. So, so I I wrote my full name and his name.
>> I wish I had someone stroke my head. I want attention.
>> Yeah, you got you got attention. You got
>> I mean like I mean like all the time
obviously, but I mean like all the time, you know.
>> Yeah, but you're not going to get
attention all the time and hugged. Grezy,
I like to be kissed and hugged. What do you think?
>> I wanted Monty Stitch type a Stitch toy,
but he wouldn't give me it. I like
>> not my Stitch.
>> It's not my Stitch. >> Yeah,
I like Stitch. He's cute.
I like Do you like attention, Monty?
Like kisses and hugs
>> all the time. All the [ __ ] time.
>> I like as well. What?
>> I like holding hands too.
>> Yeah, I never really got attention off
Kelly with that. Not really.
>> USA gave me so much attention. Greasy,
>> is it?
>> No. Someone else then I stopped getting
the attention and I've became sad.
>> That's what That's what women do. Give
you a little bit attention and [ __ ] off
and [ __ ] Women are [ __ ] sad as
well. Head [ __ ] More head [ __ ] and a manise.
>> More head [ __ ] than a fanny.
>> No, I said more head [ __ ] than a
manise. Meaning a man has meaning a man
has full respect for his woman. That that basically
he doesn't think about anyone else.
>> I wasn't going to go to Birmingham, Lord
J, because of my anxiety.
Lord Jerry, when are you coming
Birmingham, you little fat little ginger three,
you know? Yeah.
>> Lord J, you little nons.
>> Why do you put your kid all over YouTube?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Timmy got owned, bro.
>> He weren't even trying to come in. He Lord,
>> just don't be as Just don't be just
don't be as fishes next time.
>> What do you mean as fishes? >> Heavyhanded.
>> I want to meet that lad. We're taking
piss of the traffic light. Lord Yeah. I
want to meet that lad today if he wants
to meet me. Lord Yeah.
>> When they try finding out where we're
living, taking pictures of local shops
and it was a lad in Birmingham saying,
"Come here. come here and
I'll put my camera on on the way when I go back
then let them see where I am.
>> What? Did I get any I've got a boyfriend yesterday? Yeah.
>> did I get? I've got a boyfriend yesterday. Yeah. As well.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You're going to get that.
>> You're always going to get that. It's to be expected.
>> This woman This woman tried selling me
flowers. She said it one rose for £3. I
told her to [ __ ] off. I said I can get
them for a quing.
But the women the women in Birmingham
were all very stuck up as well. And the
bouncers are [ __ ] We had bad
experience with um the bouncers which
never happens. Yeah, bro. I think I prefer London.
But yeah, it was good. Like I like
meeting up with Monty and getting drunk
and [ __ ] but I don't know. I prefer London, bro.
>> Did I give you a good night? And and the
women just seem
I don't know, bro. They're just stuck up
there. Yo PJ,
>> what in Birmingham?
>> I've never been to
>> that girl. That girl who who you sat
down next to got to her mom and dad and
that and she was shy because of her mom
and dad and that and now we're telling
her why you that you thought it was just
a friend or something. I like no it's a mom.
I've done so many approaches.
>> It will go on a night out with the mom. Little PJ
>> ghosting. It will never change in this
country though. Long term. You know that.
That was my first time in Birmingham in
a few years. I think two I think it was
two years. Yeah, two years. No, two or
three years. Uh,
one second. But I think it might have been
a few years, bro.
Yeah, I approached her. She said she had
a boyfriend ghosting.
I done two approaches.
>> I done a couple approaches because PJ
>> I got I got a boyfriend ghosting it. I
got that a few times.
What's your opinion on that ghosting?
Same old England eh. Yeah, Monty done some approaches.
>> Not not like PJ. I was just watching him really being
>> Monty was a bit shy though.
>> I'm not shy. It's just that I got full
respect for that in that way. I never do
that to you know.
>> It's the same old in England, bro. What
do you mean big cities? What do you
You're just going to go into a town and
suddenly you're not going to get that.
Yeah, I got three numbers anyways,
Ghost. Three numbers in the Facebook,
but I only wanted to have fun with
Monty, but I still wanted some numbers to text.
Cuz if you ain't even got any numbers to
even text the next day, what's the point?
>> No. No, he's not. >> What?
>> That's what I I tried telling him.
That's what I That's what I told him. George, >> what?
>> I gave him the same advice.
>> Hey, me.
>> Uh, Monty should just let Natty do the
chase and forget about her. If she comes
back, take it from there. Don't Don't
chase her obsess over her. That's what I
basically said to you, is it? >> Yeah.
>> Which is is the best advice. I I gave
him the same one.
>> I was saying, "Okay,
>> it's hard. It is hard when these
feelings I've got with my disabilities
as well. Like I obviously I'm going to let you
>> I'm just going to let you understand me
a little bit more better. Yeah. My disabilities
and special of autism. If people tell me
not to do something, I'm going to do it.
Do you know what I mean? Yeah,
>> I I just don't use my brain and I need
to start using 100% of my brain instead
of um 12% of my brain. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? Like now people
have quit weed. I'm off the weed. Literally quit.
>> Did I have any we did I have any joy
last night? No, but I had a cigarette.
>> Yeah. Yeah, you did. You had a cigarette. Yeah,
>> I've quit me, peeps. I don't smoke weed anymore.
>> We just go in his bedroom. Just go in
the bedroom and sort it out with
Natalie. I don't [ __ ] know, bro.
>> I'm not going No, listen. I'm not I'm
not that man. Yeah, you're going to
Natalie's bedroom. Natalie,
I'm leaving Natalie alone. Natalie's in
her bedroom. I'm leaving Nally alone in
You know what I mean?
I'm not I'm not a bag. Yeah. Little cigarette.
>> But yeah, Monty, you need to stop being so vicious.
>> What do you mean so vicious?
>> When you you almost squeeze my you
almost broke my hand.
I almost broke you. You made my hand bleed.
>> How did you manage to make your hand bleed?
>> Yeah, Monty was like, "Oh, this this is
how strong I am." Yeah. And he started
squeezing my hand and it [ __ ] hurt.
>> Is actually strong, you know? I'm not
even taking a piss.
>> He is actually strong, bro. You hurt my
[ __ ] hand, you [ __ ]
I don't know where you got that
>> from, bro.
>> You don't know where I got that stroke from. >> Yeah,
>> that's why I'm not scared of anybody.
PJ, that's why he's standing the ground.
You see how close was to the
>> We called out that Tim. We called out
that Tim Elders. He didn't come out. We
called him out. He didn't come out.
>> We called them all out. Money m We was
calling them all out.
>> Okay. Whoever else it were prime.
>> They weren't having it for toffee ghost.
>> You're prime. You want to meet me prime?
Yeah. I'll literally meet you prime.
I'll meet you today if you want. Prime.
No skin off my nose. Lad.
You say miss L. L J wants to meet me.
Peep. I'll meet Lord J. If he thinks
that I'm going to run off or whatever, I
am bot len snap his nose in two person.
>> I spent about I spent about £200
ghosting all in all probably about
almost 200. But the train there and back
was only £29 which wasn't too bad.
>> £29 back
there and back. No dare and back. It's
not that bad actually. >> Yeah.
I had to get three I had to get three
trains back. Oh, don't ask me why. It
was a nightmare, man. The ticket
inspector was being a [ __ ] Long story,
but yeah, I had to get free trains back
in the end. H was long, mate. I still ain't slept.
>> Yo, do you know what? Yeah, I should
wear this, but I'm going to say it
anyways. Okay, Natalie.
>> Long story.
>> I need to talk about it, but I'm going
to say this about once
to as well. This is to carry as well.
Yeah. K's not going to like this. >> Yeah.
>> Basically goes, "One second, Monty. Let
me just explain this to this." Go.
>> Basically, bro, that the ticket I had
the return, it's only valid on certain
trains. So when the ticket inspector
come, he says, "Oh, you have to get off
at Coventry and get the um train that's
coming in half an hour." The train comes
in half an hour, then it terminates in
[ __ ] Northampton. So then I had to
get another train from Northampton. So
it ended up being three [ __ ] trains.
He was being a [ __ ] He could have
easily let me stay on that train, bro. I
paid. Not like I didn't pay. He was just
being an awkward [ __ ]
>> Oh, I hear what he said. Yeah. He said,
"Oh, cuz obviously I was going to go in
the toilet and shut the door and cuz I
was I'm not getting off at Coventry."
And he was like, "What are you wandering
around for? You're getting off in a
minute." I said, "Excuse me." I said to
him, "What did you I said to him, what
didn't you just say?" And then and then
and then I said, "I'll go where I want."
And then he started like backtracking
what he said. I was like, "No, we heard
what you said, mate."
He was just being a he was being a [ __ ]
but he was just being a [ __ ] bro.
There's a bouncer. Get in, fellas.
>> Ticket inspector.
>> Get in the land.
>> All right, Triple H. I don't know what
why you come on YouTube. [ __ ] sting,
bro. You're the one that doesn't listen.
Listen, you little [ __ ] weasel. Yeah.
Instead of [ __ ] sting on YouTube. Why
don't we actually mate? You know what
you're about, you little [ __ ]
>> Instead of going on YouTube calling
people, you little clown.
>> So why don't you do that? Why don't you
come and do that?
You know where I am. You know my You
know my address. No, you listen to me.
You little special needed little [ __ ]
ugly little [ __ ] Just meld.
>> Go and shake your face for the biggest
[ __ ] You ugly bastard.
>> Get this out here.
>> Listen Triple H. Yeah.
Timmy Eldridge doesn't meet people just
like you don't meet people. Just like
your little nons.
>> Triple H if you're about just like you.
Just like you never come out of
Newcastle three times.
>> That's what I mean. Please [ __ ]
weasled in here and they come on like
like the hard as [ __ ] It's time to meet you.
>> Bye-bye, Triple H. I don't like this
Triple H, bro.
>> I don't know.
>> I see what he does. I see what he does,
bro. And it And it's silly.
>> They all silly PJ. They all [ __ ] we
all mate. That's why I'm not
entertaining them. No, I'm stupid for
coming on here. >> Yeah.
>> I just want to sort out with Natal and
I'm getting off here. I'm not getting
I'm not coming back on to sort of [ __ ]
with Natalie. I'm never coming back on
to YouTube again. I'm already here just
so me to see what I'm doing. That's it. >> Yeah.
>> You know,
>> we we got pro. That must have been the
most drunk you've ever been in it.
>> Yeah. I know what a night law.
See what I mean? When I said it's no
point drinking when you're depressed cuz
when you drink you're happy for you're
happy for the day. Well, for the night
and then after the night you're back to depressed again. >> Yeah. Literally.
>> You know what I mean? How did you
collect your Did you collect your
football winnings yet?
Yeah, bro. I am tired ghosting think
about this. I haven't even slept.
>> All that drinking.
>> Oh, mate.
>> You've got that thingy. Anyways, PJ,
you've got it
>> anyway. So, that's good. You've got it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I I know, bro. I know.
>> I talk to you in a bit about it anyway.
So, we're not putting up on YouTube.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Anyway, so we'll talk about that in a bit.
>> Yeah. Well, I got there at What time did
I get there, Monty? Quart 9. >> 9.
>> I got the train back at I got the train
back at 11 and I didn't sleep.
We getting [ __ ]
>> You got a train back at 11:00 in the morning.
>> Yeah. But you was waiting around
Birmingham still when I was on my way
home till 11:00.
>> It was 11:00. Yeah. Yeah.
>> You should have told me I would have
stayed with you. Oh no, I couldn't get
through the gate. Could I could I
go on Facebook a second? Um,
>> a second. Yeah, bro. So, >> yeah.
>> Oh, the traveling kills you. Could you
imagine doing new an all nighter in Newcastle?
No, they shot at 3:00 a.m. You imagine
doing an all nighter in Newcastle
and then coming back. Oh, you would be
dead, bro. I think you'd be dead. >> Yeah.
Know, I don't know.
You just play on the train, don't you? Huh?
You sleep on the trains, Lord. Don't
you? You just fall asleep on the trains and that.
>> Yeah, but I can't I I I I'm paranoid
about falling asleep on the train of my
phone and that is it. >> Yeah.
>> Like even though you put it in your
pocket, I know. Yeah. But I'm just
paranoid. I I just can't I I just can't
sleep on the train because of that reason.
Unless I'm literally on top of like a
duffel bag, but still I wouldn't fall
asleep cuz I'm
I don't know. I'm funny, bro. You know, like that.
>> Are you obsessed with women?
>> No, I'm not obsessed with women. I'm a [ __ ]
>> I just like being kissed by them.
>> No, if I was obsessed by them, then I
would have got off with that bird last
night who both way through. You want to
the You know what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> I told them, "No, me. I'm I'm happy with Natalie. me.
So, I could have got off with her, but I
didn't. I told her no. She started
stroking my leg and everything. I told
>> people just keep saying that. These
people keep these people just keep
saying Nat doesn't want you.
>> N doesn't want us. That's only what they can say.
>> But that doesn't want them either. >> No.
That doesn't bother me.
You know what I mean? I'm done. I'm
done. She doesn't want me.
>> Yeah, but look at me, George William and
Steven Howard. Look what happened with
me in that USA. Is it? I was still out pulling birds.
I didn't give a [ __ ] bro. I didn't give
a [ __ ] mate. I still do it, mate. I
don't give a [ __ ]
>> That doesn't hurt me. >> Yeah.
>> When they say that they don't want you
don't want you. I don't know.
>> I'm going to say one thing, Natalie.
>> Just think of all the good times we
have. Just put the good times with the
bad times. Just put it all in one. Think
about all the good times we've had and
think about all the bad times we've had. Natalie,
I remember when I used to like kiss
other women. Yeah. After meeting her and
it was like, "Yuck, yuck. It tastes
disgusting. Doesn't taste the same.
That is the way you kissed me, mama.
>> That's fair.
>> You know what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> Yuck. You're not my mama. Yuck.
You're a fraud.
I know who you're not my mommy.
You don't kiss me the same way. Yeah.
Yeah, he usually would love a night out
with money and PJ with a steak. Yeah,
well, she can kiss goodbye to that. He's
blew that because she makes people cry,
writes them poem, makes them write poems.
Yep, I got a hand job, Mr. B yesterday.
It was nice.
I like to be hugged. posting.
All of these other women after Grezy
after USA was trying to act like that
they were my mommy. They're not my mama.
You think I was born yesterday?
I know who my mommy is. You know,
they were trying to pretend that they
were my mom. You're not my mommy. Yuck.
Your kisses don't even taste the same. Yeah. A
Yeah. No, I just wanted to get back
home, but I was [ __ ] shattered.
Oh, I gave a woman some flowers today.
Ghosting. And she said she had a boyfriend.
Yeah, I gave her some flowers. Um, they
cost me a pound.
Somebody was selling them in Birmingham
and she said that she had a boyfriend. Um,
and she said, "You want us did you want
them back?" I says, "No, you can keep them."
But I ain't going to lie, bro. Apart
from that though, Birmingham does seem
pretty hard, bro.
I think, bro, give it another give it another year,
um, it will be impossible.
You give it another year, it would be impossible.
Uh yeah, I went to Broad Street. Me and
Monty tried to come in. They said, "Oh,
you can't come in unless you got a group of girls."
I was like, "What?" Bear in mind, I'm in
London. I've never heard anything like
this. I've heard that you can't come in by yourself.
Um, I've I've even heard like if there's
three guys, there's too many guys for
the ratio. But I've never heard
something so simpy in my life.
And then the bouncer started trying to
get rude. I said, "Listen, bro. Save it
for when you're not got police behind
you. It's cowardly. Stop acting up in
front of the police. We all know how the
how this goes now. You know, if you
about that life, I was starting on him.
I was it was annoying me, you know. It
was just annoying me um
like listening to it, you know what I
mean? Which is why I kind of got
involved as well.
But them kind Yeah. You don't get
[ __ ] bounces in London really.
Everyone's just sound, bro.
[ __ ] you have to go with a group of girls.
You're going in to meet girls.
What the [ __ ] Why the [ __ ] would you be
going to a club with a load of girls?
We just got breakfast, got pissed, and then
Yeah, I just we just No, we just stayed
stayed round the city center.
Yeah, they are [ __ ] bro. That ticket
inspector was a [ __ ] as well. He could
have easily let me stay on that train
and he made sure I left as well.
Yeah, he made sure.
But it does defeat the point. Yeah,
because you're going in to meet women
with a friend to meet women,
but they're telling you
that you need a group of women to go in,
which defeats the whole point
because defeats the whole Yeah, it
defeats the whole Yeah, they're just
[ __ ] [ __ ] Them bounces in
Birmingham are proper [ __ ] bro.
They act all big when they know there's
police around, but they won't come
around the corner. They won't go away
from police. They won't go away from the other bouncers.
You know what I mean? They they actually
get rude about that. They don't know who
they're [ __ ] [ __ ] with cuz I'll
just tell them about themselves back, bro.
And it's not a regular thing really to
get a negative experience from bouncers.
It's quite rare to be honest, but
when you go out of London like Leeds and
Birmingham, it seems that
Yeah. I don't know. It's negative, bro.
Yeah. But anyways, [ __ ] them.
I am knackered, lad. I am knackered.
I'm having KFC. I can't have greasy
[ __ ] I can't have greasy [ __ ] bro.
I can't have greasy [ __ ] when I've been
out drinking. I need to have nice curry.
A nice curry with some chicken ticker. I
can't have greasy [ __ ] after I've ate.
It makes me feel sick.
I want to be hugged again. I love huggles.
I want USA to hug me again and kiss me.
I just miss them little kisses, you know.
But I felt something in my toodger
when she done that. Yeah. I started to
feel something in my toger. Yeah,
I remember that one. But I didn't feel
anything in my toger.
Uh, no. I've never followed anyone home.
But yeah, them bouncers. I think they're
simps, bro. I can't lie to you.
Oh, they're just weirdos that want to
prey on drunk women because why why are
they telling people to go with a group of women?
The ratio should be men and women.
Why do they want group a group of women
in a club? It should be uh even, you know,
I miss them kisses.
Yeah, but I don't know, man. I don't
know if I can meet Monty again. He might
break my hand this time.
You know, I was very rough. Very, very,
Why is he so vicious? Ant-Man never used
to be vicious to me.
He was quite gentle.
Yeah. I said to Monty Man, "You're quite
vicious." He said, "What do you mean vicious?"
Why? I like Monty man.
He's just a bit heavy-handed, that's all.
I said, "Ow, that hurt."
He said, "I can squeeze your hand." And
I said, "Ow, that hurts. Let go."
Yeah. Yeah. That don't make sense. I've
never But then again, Birmingham is backwards.
Yeah. Birmingham is backwards, bro. I've
never heard that in London,
bro. I've never heard that in London.
I've never heard that in London, bro.
Never. Never heard it anywhere.
Just that you can't go in by yourself,
which is just like a standard thing they
say, but I've never heard that. That's ridiculous.
They are [ __ ] simps.
They act bad, but they know that there's police there,
but they act bad. That's what makes me laugh.
Police everywhere, bro. [ __ ] everywhere.
But I've never heard of that. I've never Yeah.
Who the [ __ ] were going somewhere with a
group of girls?
That is so dumb.
Yeah, I got a boyfriend. I got a
boyfriend a few times. I got I got a
boyfriend a few times. Like I said, I
only went to go see Monty, but
I did still want some numbers to at
least text, you know, cuz
what's the point you got no one to text
next day, you know?
Oh, I'm [ __ ] tired, bro. Oh man,
it's all that traveling, bro.
Oh my god.
Oh, I'm going to have little snooze.
I'm fat. My eyes are fat.
I wish USA Izzy was here to look after me. Grezy
to rub me with her little crumbling sausage fingers.
They were like cumbling sausages.
Make me a cup of soup,
you know, when I'm under the weather.
Yeah. Go where my little legs take me.
Maybe you didn't think I was going to
go, did you? Yeah.
I just want somebody just to come and kiss me.
That's why I said to the girl tenant. I
said I come home from work one day. I
said, "Listen," her name was Maya. I
said, "Maya, can you come and rub my
feet and give me kisses and huggles?
I'm really tired.
Can you come and look after me?" She never replied.
No, I wasn't messing him around. It was
more like should I go? Is there point of going?
Um, I even got to the train station, oh,
should I just do a U-turn? I was in two
minds. I didn't know what to do.
Yeah. USA is he needs to look after me.
Yeah. I want her to look after me, you know.
I still remember the way she kissed me.
It was cute.
Very cute, wasn't it, Grezy?
I just like kisses and stuff.
Yeah, feeling. But
I just like to be, like I said, kissed.
Kissed and hugged.
I'm going to watch Superman this week,
Steven Howard. And I've got no one to go
to the pictures with.
I've got no one to go with. Oh man. Oh, Franklin.
Yeah, I'm going to watch Superman. Yeah.
Maybe that 19 year old
meet me again. 20 year old. Sorry. No,
she's she's 20 now, isn't it?
I used to say to her, "Every time you
give me a [ __ ] you have to swallow
it." And she did do it a few times.
It's hard to get people to actually want
to swallow it, you know.
Yeah. She's one of my bubbers.
And then we had a Chinese after.
Had a Chinese takeaway.
Yeah, I used to invite around to give me a [ __ ]
She used to hate sucking dick as well.
She used to hate it, but she still does it anyways. Yeah,
she hated it. She hated it, bro.
But I don't want that. I just want
kisses and huggles. Yeah,
I'll be back later. Yeah, I'm [ __ ]