Yo yo. Oh.
Oh, [ __ ] Who said go live? Monty go.
Oh [ __ ] man.
Yeah, I put £50 on the Frankie and nothing.
You can't take a day off. You're here now, boss.
I've already took days off, weeks off.
You're the ones that can't take a day off YouTube.
Yeah, I done 50 pound on Frankie. Yeah, nothing.
Well, I tell you the truth, I put 100 pound in
and I played it down to 50 and I was
like, "Fuck that. I'm not putting no
more money through this rig [ __ ]
I'm not YouTube dependent. No, I'm [ __ ] not.
I've come off YouTube for [ __ ] days
and weeks. Something that you people
can't do. I'm not [ __ ] YouTube
dependent. I'll stick to my bet. I bet
you 100 I bet you all my money.
No, he didn't. I I I bet you all the
money I can take a week off YouTube, but you can't.
I'm not a [ __ ] YouTube [ __ ]
dependent. I'm my [ __ ]
Money kind of got me back on this [ __ ]
No, I put £100 in and I took 50. There's
no way I was going to give that another 50.
[ __ ] that, bro. You mad.
No, that them slots. Hey, I was get I
got really mad when I lost that 50 as well.
I got back. They paid 285
and I got 50 note as well. So
yeah, it's [ __ ] so [ __ ] fixed. Oh.
Oh my god, bro. It is so fixed. It's
unbelievable. Yeah, I only put 50 on it
though. Well, I put £100 in and I took
50 out. There's no way I could justify
losing 100 pound on that, bro. No way.
Not a bonus to save your life.
I was doing one pound spins. Can't even
get a [ __ ] bonus, bro.
So, I just took 50. So, I only lost 50.
I just banked the 235.
Yeah, I had 235.
Obviously, I didn't get a feature. I
just told you I didn't get a feature.
You [ __ ] brain dead.
So, I just took the 23 and I just So,
then I got 235.
It is a [ __ ] enough, mate. Cuz I kept
getting base game wins. It is enough cuz
I kept getting base game wins.
But somehow I kept losing. Strange, eh?
I got base game wins though.
I'm not getting into it again, bro. New
day. Move on.
I'm absolutely skinn. You wish I was
skin. You're the one who's skinn. That's
why you call me skin. Yeah, I'm skin,
bro. I went to Birmingham and I spent
£200 and I've still got loads left. How
the [ __ ] am I skin again? You're talking
about yourself. All of the people that
call other people skin or skin
themselves. That's why they bring it up.
These people aren't your [ __ ]
personal bank accounts.
Figure it out, bro. They call people
skint cuz they're skint themselves. I
don't need to prove. I've already proved
to you millions of times I'm not skin.
You prove that you're not skint.
I'll put the link up for you, man.
Right. Hold on.
They call people skin
because they're skinn.
Look at what me and Monty was doing on
Saturday. Well, he he actually is
skinned. But I mean, like, no, I'm going
to Thursday, but I mean, he actually is
skinned. Think of it, bro. Went to
Birmingham, spent money.
Yeah. Let's see all your money. Come on.
They call people skint cuz they're skint themselves.
It's just self projection.
I ain't [ __ ] skinny. You mad. Yeah, man.
Yeah. Anyways, after that £50, I weren't
going to put any more in it.
Well, I'm not putting no more money in
that rig [ __ ] [ __ ] that.
Talking about yourself. Hey, no self
projection on my channel.
I haven't got a pot to piss in, bro. The
link's up there. Come on, let's play the
money game. Come on.
Talking about yourself again.
I think these people's disabilities get them confused.
Um, they get they get themselves
confused with you. I proved them wrong
many many times and they still call me
skin. They're talking about themselves.
That's why it doesn't matter how many
times you prove yourself to these little
mongos. They're talking about themselves.
So, it doesn't matter what you prove
because they they've got you confused with themselves.
Their brains don't work properly. D lad,
>> you can ask Monty man what I done what
we done in Birmingham.
>> One second, bro.
>> Listen, come in and show us your money.
You started something. Now finish it.
Come in and show us your money.
Come on. You You just come in. You just
say that I was skin. Come in and show us
your money. I want to see what money looks like.
There's no point coming on YouTube like
a [ __ ] every day starting [ __ ] you
can't finish. Don't start something you
can't finish. Don't be a London cyclist.
Show me your money. You come on here.
You started on me. Are you coming in or not? Simple.
Simple. Are you coming in or not? Skin.
Are you coming in or not? Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay. Hey, come in and show us your money.
Nothing, man. I just lost £50 frenzy. Yeah,
I actually showed six grand actually in
cash, but yeah, there you go.
One second, bro. Hold on.
One second. Yeah, Joe. I put £100 in and
I just took 50.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. We've done this before and every
single time I show you something, you
run away. You call me skin, show me your
money. You started coming on here
calling me skin. Let's see your money.
jump on. I want to see your money.
Otherwise, I'm banning you. Come on. Are
you coming in or not?
I put 100 pound in. I took 50. So, I
only lost 50. There's no way I was
putting the last 50 in. [ __ ] that, bro.
I don't even know why I put 100 pound
in. I just took 50 out. There's no way I
can justify losing more than 50 on that [ __ ]
And you're gone. Bye-bye. You got chance
after chance after chance after chance. After
chance. After chance. So, bye-bye now.
Go self-reflect on another channel. You
started something and I was prepared to
finish it and you won't join.
So, bye-bye now. Go call yourself skint
somewhere else. Bye-bye now.
They bring money up because they're
skint themselves. That's why they call
people skin cuz they are skint. Where do
they get the idea skint from? Went to
Birmingham, met Monty, go out all the time.
They must be Skint themselves.
Well, okay. Your show money. Okay. How
much is that?
Let's count it. Okay. Well, someone's
coming in. Show money. Nice, man. How
much is that? >> 8K. >> Okay.
It's 8K. There you go. 8 8.5 or something.
>> There we go. So, why couldn't that other
guy come in and show money then?
>> There you go, man.
>> Three log.
>> Wow. See, it's not that hard, is it?
It's not that hard, is it, man?
Yeah, I was at a food bank. I've never
been in a food bank ever. But yeah, I
didn't even get a bonus. Anyways, I've
already shown mine. And that weren't a
guy calling me skin. I've already shown mine.
I've already shown you money time and
time and time and time and time and time
and time and time again.
What do I think of that? I don't care
because I'm not obsessed with money.
That's I I generally don't care.
I've got more than enough money to do
what I need to do. I don't give a [ __ ]
Good for whoever has that. Good for
them, bro. I don't give a [ __ ]
So yeah, man.
Money is not everything. Unless you're
like [ __ ] Monty.
So I mean, unless you unless you're like
Monty at the minute, doesn't really matter.
No, I'm not showing you [ __ ] nothing.
I'm not showing you nothing
about me showing my 50. I ain't showing you nothing.
And that guy didn't even beat me either.
I asked to be shown 10 grand. That
that's not even 10 grand. So like I
said, I'm still yet to be beaten. Unless
you're like Monty, then then it matters.
So yeah, it's actually 10 grand that has
to be shown to me. But yeah,
why are these people? So anyways,
Richie, like where do they get the idea
from, bro? Like people of skin. I went
to Birmingham, went on the piss with
Monty. Where the [ __ ] do they get this
idea of skin from? There's no lifestyle
that supports what they're saying. And
then the only thing that can make sense
is that they're talking about themselves.
You understand, Richie?
It's because they're talking about their
own skin selves.
You know what I mean?
I'm on 2x. You don't know how much I have.
You don't know how much I get. Exactly. But yeah.
Yeah. They're [ __ ] disabled, bro.
They proper are disabled.
Yeah. It doesn't matter how much I get.
It's none of your [ __ ] business. Just
like it's none of your business how much I have.
>> Money. What is it with these people and money, bro?
>> Stop mentioning me like like multi skin.
I'm not asking ask if I'm skiing. Money
is just [ __ ]
>> I'm using it as an I'm using as an example.
>> Yeah, but the example is it's what is
money? Money is nothing. What's more in
what's more what cost more money or a
house over you? What or a book? Yeah.
>> Why do why? Hey, why do you not keep
bringing up money anyways, bro?
>> Cuz money is nothing. You spend money,
you lose money. Money comes and goes.
>> That's what money, you know what I mean?
It's these people are [ __ ] idiots.
Paper. It's [ __ ] paper [ __ ]
money's for nothing. It's no [ __ ] I
can't even say that word. There's
nothing to money. Yeah. Just say just
say if you went to a snow. Yeah. And got
a a marble comic book or something like that.
>> Oh, by the way, sorry to cut you off
money. Yeah. It's lucky that it was
only50 because I was getting them severe
mood swings again. Then I went to Gregs
and got some sausage rolls and calm down
after like 10 minutes. It's not a good
idea. I play these things, bro. It was
giving me really bad mood swings again. Sorry, Monty.
>> Yeah. So, so if you go to Aston, buy
yourself a Marvel comic book. Yeah. Or
just a normal regular book. Yeah. That
book inside will go up in price. Money
doesn't. Money drops.
do goes up in price. Money is for call.
You come with money, you lose money.
Items are worth more than what money is
because you can get more for items in
the future times to come. You know what I'm saying?
>> Yeah, but how do you get it? Yeah, but
how do you get items?
>> Basically from Tesco's houses, these
books like comic books, stuff like that
because in time all that will cost
money. You know, you know what I'm saying?
>> Like money's [ __ ] money. You you you
you spend your money. You don't see that
>> Money's nothing. Money's just anymore, Joe.
>> That's why I don't do it. Do you do you
reckon I win another football bet this
season, Joe? Maybe not in it.
>> I'm jumping up anyway. Yeah. >> Why?
>> Because I'm not on YouTube no more. I
just come up and said I'm off this [ __ ]
I'm off it. There's nothing here. Big
weirdos, mate. But um yeah, I've got
Natalie TV now anyway. So Natalie TV's
come now anyway. So, look, I show you.
>> Did you un Did you unbox it?
>> No, it's I'm not going to unbox it. It's
staying in this box. It's not my TV.
>> It's here.
>> Not my TV. It's Nice. >> Yeah.
>> Nice TV. Like I said, I always keep to
my word. Always keep to my word. Never
lie. When I say when I say I get it, I
get it. That's what I'm talking. Do you
know what? You know what I mean? I can
still get so it doesn't matter. I've got
a lamb shank for dinner in it today, Joe.
>> Good. I'm jumping up. Yeah.
>> Can I see that? Can you unbox it?
>> No, I'm not unboxing it. It's not of
this TV. I'm not opening it. It's not
this TV. I'm not going to open that.
This [ __ ] gift. [Music]
>> I'm just going to sell it.
I'm going to jump off. Yeah. In a bit.
>> Yeah, man. Going to be here. But yeah,
remember that money's for call.
>> It comes and goes in a bit. Yeah.
>> Yeah, bro.
about that, bro. I was doing something.
Right. Let me try to get money back on. Sorry, bro. Yeah, man.
Oh, [ __ ] Yeah, £50 in Frankie, not even
a bonus. And it wasn't it was more than
enough because it had it had base game
wins as well. It had a couple of base
game wins. So, obviously, you're talking
maybe like a hundred with the base game
wins. I thought, "Fuck that. I'm not
putting any more in.
[ __ ] that, bro. That's madness.
Nah, bro. [ __ ] that. I just took 50.
It's mad, isn't it?
I think that's how you know when you're
done with them, is it?
So, like I said, I just put the 2385 in the bank. I'm bum.
One second. I'm doing something. Hold on.
[ __ ] I probably been [ __ ] around with
to be honest with you, Joe. I might not
meet any of these people, but do you
think I give a [ __ ] No. Why? Cuz I know
what they do.
So I don't give a [ __ ] bro. Mom was
just pissed me off just now. I don't
give a [ __ ] I know what they what they
do, bro. You don't see me crying about it. It's [ __ ] sustainable [ __ ]
Don't see me crying, bro. Even if I was
with them, I don't give a [ __ ] bro.
But losing 50 pound on them machines,
that was annoying, bro.
I hate it, bro. SW shouldn't shouldn't play Yeah, man.
Yeah, man. It's like me, bro. Like, I
was just talking to one as well. I just
had one randomly block me, Nicolo. But
it doesn't bother me because it's the
same old England.
So, it's like you don't see me getting
pissed off about it, bro.
because it will never change is is what
I've been saying for ages.
It will never change in this country.
There's nothing to get pissed off about. No.
All of the numbers replied. One just
randomly blocked me. So, no. It's got
worse and worse and worse since I last
went there. It will never ever ever
change in this country. Like you when I
go out, bro. Bye-bye, [ __ ]
No one cares about you, you coward.
Keyboard warrior coward.
Go react to me on your channel. Um, so
like it's never going to change, so
there's nothing to be pissed off about. Uh, three.
Yeah, three. And they all replied, but
one just randomly blocked me. So,
you know what I find so mad yet? I
wouldn't say I'm even like young
anymore. It's not like I'm like 18, 19,
you know, where, you know, you expect
people to act immature.
No, you didn't get anything. Like, we're
almost 28 and we still deal with people playing games.
It's all very well and good talking to
people, bro. But when it comes to
actually meeting, they [ __ ] themselves.
They [ __ ] themselves.
When [ __ ] gets real and it's time to
actually meet and hang out, they [ __ ]
themselves, you know.
It will never change in this country, bro. Never.
Oh, I feel a bit run down from the
drinking, bro. [ __ ]
But no, Monty got no numbers. You're not
getting a mod. [ __ ] off.
Well, Monty's single now as well.
So, yeah. What I know with Birmingham is
uh the numbers reply.
There's no problem getting replies.
No, I'm having a lamb shank later.
There's no It's not a problem getting replies.
The problem is is um getting them to
actually meet you. But in London, you
can't even get replies to be fair,
but in Birmingham I got some replies. Um
but trying to get like someone
interested or stay interested or
actually meet you, it's next to impossible, bro.
And then when I go back out in London,
it's just a shot of Guinness. It's just
an alcohol shot. It tastes really nice as well,
but it's going to be even worse now back in London.
I I went to Birmingham for Monty, bro.
Deep down, I just went for Monty and
because I hadn't been out in two weeks,
I won money. There was nothing else to
do, you know? So, I wouldn't have done
it by myself. I wouldn't have just went
like, "No, it's not strong. It tastes a
bit like coffee.
If it I would have just went to got up
and went to Birmingham
like just to go to Birmingham or Wales
or out of London or even in London, bro.
Like I can't be asked with all that anymore. You know,
stop asking stupid questions, man.
Yeah, it's very hard to just try to find
people that don't play games, which I
think is crazy at this age, Grebsy, how
you have people still playing games at
our age. Obviously, I expect it cuz it's
England, but like
I mean, we're getting like it's not like
we're [ __ ] 18, 19, you know, we're
like adults. We're adults adults.
It's crazy, ain't it, bro? I think women
stop playing games when they're 50. Maybe.
Maybe when they're 50.
But I I just went for Monty in cuz there
was nothing else to do cuz my logic still stands.
You know, if something was going to
change, it would have changed by now.
That's why I broke the cycle.
And then Monty walked to the station and
then [ __ ] oh I had to I felt obliged
to then go and
you still get these people playing mind games
and it's like every nationality woman
would do the same thing like how do I
explain it like
French will do the same Romanian will do the American
would do the same. If you notice, right,
every woman from the from the same nationality,
I don't give a [ __ ] You can come and
say to my face.
What I was saying is uh
that's how you know that they're all the same because
Yeah. And so they're not so they're not
interested in you then, seller.
Yeah. Interested in millionaires. So
they they're interested in people that
don't even want them. Yeah. They're
interested in men that don't even want them.
But that sounds about right. But then I
guess they're not interested in you
because you're none of them things.
But yeah, they're interested in men that
don't want them.
And who the [ __ ] are they to be
interested in millionaires? They work at
[ __ ] McDonald's. How can a low status
woman want a high stat status men?
status men. But that is what it is. You
get these low status women wanting high status men.
What the [ __ ] It doesn't even make sense.
They aren't interested in them. It's
weird, isn't it?
But um yeah.
No, there's not wanting the Yeah, but
there's being there's being realistic.
Oh, you've got a misses. Of course you
do. Isn't it funny how all of you on
here claim that you've got a misses?
No, bro. You don't. No, you don't have a
misses. Cuz all of you people on here
claim that you've got a misses. Well,
bro, how about you [ __ ] spend time
with your misses and stop coming on
YouTube every day then and then it at
least would look a bit more believable.
They've all got misses, but they're all
on YouTube all [ __ ] day. Doesn't make
any [ __ ] sense, bro. Why? Why do you
lie anyways? And there wanting the best.
Okay. So, what how would you feel if I
only wanted a millionaire woman? That
was a 10 out of 10. What would your
opinion be then? Okay, if you're going
by that logic, then okay. Okay, so I
want a woman who's a millionaire, who's
famous, that's good-look,
does that sound realistic to you? Let's
just say that we use that as an example.
That comment doesn't even make any sense.
How can they want the best when they're
not the best themselves?
Here's an article. Anyways, end of conversation. Anyway,
yeah, just like what the the men that
these women want is close to impossible. So, yeah,
there's like 1 billion on the planet is
Yes, it is hard to get a miss. Yes, it [ __ ] is.
Yes, it [ __ ] is. It doesn't matter
who you [ __ ] go for. You think every
single woman that I approach is a slag?
No, it is impossible because of [ __ ]
Tik Tok and because of [ __ ] Instagram.
Everyone's got [ __ ] Tik Tok brains, bro.
I only went to [ __ ] Birmingham for
Monty, bro. And cuz I won that football
bet. Even though I didn't need to win
the football bet, I just went, "Fuck it."
Where they lower their standards. Yeah,
maybe in their 40s.
It doesn't matter who the [ __ ] woman
is, bro. where the [ __ ] woman's from.
You're still going to get the same old.
You go out and you try to start a
conversation, you're you're still going
to get the same old, bro. It doesn't bother me.
I'm I'm over it. I'm past it. I'm over
I'm done with it, bro. Monty Monty
wanted me to come.
The football bet won. I had to kind of
go. And in the process, I approached
women when I was there. Simple. I
wouldn't have went by myself, bro, for no reason
cuz it will never change here.
I would I weren't even going to go out in London.
So I I'm not asked, bro.
Like it will never change. Never.
The games, the [ __ ] It will never
change, bro. And I don't expect it to.
How could it?
That's that's my whole logic is how I
actually could it.
Yeah, I did have a good time. That's why
I went I went there for a good time.
But the women thing is still a bit
[ __ ] up. You expect it, but at the
same time it is still [ __ ] up.
It is. It is still [ __ ] up.
So it is still [ __ ] up though.
And some of the rules is [ __ ] up too. Yeah, bro.
It does annoy me a little bit. I'm not
going to I'm not going to pretend that
it doesn't annoy me. It does annoy me a
little bit, but
I think it would annoy anyone a little
bit. It is It is a bit annoying, but at
the same time, you expect it, but it is still annoying, you know.
It is. It is still annoying
cuz it shouldn't like it shouldn't be
that but it is that way. So, and it's
been that way for a long time and it
will never and it will always be that
way until you leave. So,
yeah, that's where we at. That's where
we're at, unfortunately.
That's where we're at, unfortunately.
Cuz you know, every single time you do this, right,
you're proving people wrong every time.
You know, all of these people that tell
you year in year out, "Oh, keep
hustling. It will change." You're
proving them wrong every time you go
out. Every single time. And I don't even
get a lot of money now like I used to.
And I still managed to do it.
Football bet whatever, you know, like
it's that is the only way this is going
to end. I I said to I said to Monty man,
right? Not Monty Man. Um Ant-Man, I
said, "Listen, bro, the only way this is
going to end is if they ban social
media. You go to Brazil or you go to
Thailand. End of. If you don't do any of
these things, bro, this is going to
continuously keep happening."
And I didn't say him because obviously he's there.
It's not ever going to change. It
doesn't matter who they are. Like I was
speaking to someone today randomly.
They've just randomly blocked my ass.
What the [ __ ] Why waste your time? Why
Why waste my time? It's [ __ ] bro. But
the thing I did notice different about
Birmingham is, like I said, all of the
numbers replied with enthusiasm,
which is which don't happen in London,
and it would never happen in London.
You you go you go to [ __ ] you get
three, four numbers in London, you'll
get lucky if one of them replies. And if
they do reply, they're not going to be
enthusiastic. So, I mean, that's the
only difference there there was. But yeah,
anyways, end the conversation now. Let's
just move on from it, bro.
You can't get Why? Why? Okay, one
second. One second. One second. Let's
Let's Let's go by this logic, right?
Why would you get laid in Birmingham if
you can't get laid in London?
I can show the whole conversation if you
want. I can show the whole conversation.
It's been going since yesterday.
Okay. Why Birmingham specifically? What is Birmingham?
It's a city in England full of English
women which go on Tik Tok, which goes on
Instagram. Why would you suddenly get
laid in Birmingham but not London?
They're all addicted to [ __ ] Tik Tok.
They're all addicted to Instagram. They
all base their status on [ __ ] based
on social media. It's um
I can show you the whole conversation if you want.
We can all have our say. Uh I'll put the
conversation on YouTube if you want.
Yeah. And and I guarantee you there's
nothing you can say about it. And and I
mean at this point you shouldn't even be
questioning me. Like I shouldn't have to do that.
I shouldn't have to do that to be honest
with you. I shouldn't have to even put
my conversation out there because you
shouldn't be you shouldn't be doubting
me. I will do it. But you shouldn't be doubting me.
I didn't I didn't go wrong. No. No. No,
That's the whole thing. I didn't go
wrong. So, I feel a bit offensive when
you're like doubting me.
Why would I go wrong? I didn't go wrong.
That's the whole point. And I don't like
it when people are doubting me. But I'll
put the conversation up, you know. Do
you want me to read the whole I will
actually read the whole conversation if
you want. It's not too long.
One sec. It's not too long. Uh,
do you want me to read it out? I can.
Oh, it's not even too long to be fair.
Do you want me to read all of it from
top to bottom? It's not that long, actually.
You're You're not even going to believe me, though.
Okay, I'll read it out, right?
Okay. Hi. Hey, it was lovely meeting you
last night. How's the hangover?
Hi them. Hi. I only just woke up
properly. I didn't drink that much to be
fair. I was only tired. You okay? I
replied, "Ah, fair enough. Yeah, I'm
good. I'm back in London now." They
replied, "Oh, okay. Did you get a train
back?" I said, "Yeah, train back to
Houston. You should come sometime. I
knew I know a few nice cocktail bars we
could go. I might smiley face. Maybe in
a weekend would be nice." I said, "Yeah,
it would be nice. just let me know when
you decide to come. She said, "Sure.
Which part of London are you from?" So,
she's asking me questions now. Though I
said, "Oh, I live in East London, the
place in East London. Have you heard of
it?" "Yes, I did hear about it. Never
been, so it would be nice." I said,
"When was the last time you came to
London?" They wrote, "Two years ago."
I wrote I wrote, "Fair enough. It was my
first time in Birmingham last night." In
2 years, also, she said, "Did you come
with work or just to go out?" I said, "I
just went out to meet my friend." She
said, "That's nice. I hope you did enjoy
it." I said, "I did enjoy it and meeting
you was a bonus as well." smiley face.
She said, "Haha, that's cute. Was nice
meeting you as well." I didn't even want
to go out, but my friend really wanted
me to go, so I went out. Then I I
replied, "How often do you go out
drinking?" "Not very often," she said. "Once every
one every two months, probably you."
Bye-bye. I said probably the same to be
honest, but yeah, I went out because of
my friend and so did you. So, it's good
we went out else we wouldn't have met
each other. She replied, "Haha, yes,
that's true." I said, "What's your plans
for today?" She said, "I am working. How
about you?" I said, "Oh, fair enough.
I'm just going to get something to eat
in a bit and chill today."
Uh, she wrote, "That's good. Not working
today?" I said, "Not today. Do you work
every day then?" "You should come to
London next Saturday." She wrote, "Oh,
I'm away in Belgium." I said, "Oh, fair enough.
How about the week after?" She's like,
"Not sure yet." I said, "Oh, whatever.
It's fine. We'll just arrange the time
closer to the
closer to the time anyways. Not a problem."
She said, "Yes." With a kiss. And I said
to her, "Anyways, what are you going to
Belgium for?" She said, "Friends."
I said, "Ah, see, you'll like it there.
I've been there before." literally blocked me.
That's the whole conversation, bro. So,
it wasn't that long, but there was a few
replies. So, as soon as I said, "Oh,
you'll like it there. I've been there
before." Which I have been there before.
She blocked me. So, yeah.
And from what I can see, there's nothing
wrong in that conversation.
And that's how it all went. So when
you're doubting me, I don't like it cuz
you shouldn't doubt me, bro.
You shouldn't doubt me. That's literally
how it went. She blocked me when I said,
"Oh, I've been before. It's nice."
No, she didn't ask me no question.
No, she didn't.
No, she didn't. Stop making excuses. No,
she didn't. She doesn't know my name and
she doesn't know my last name.
Yeah. I said, "Oh, I" I said, "Oh, I see
you'll like it. I've been before. It's
nice." Cuz I have been to Belgium before
and it was nice. Well, Brussels anyways.
And then she just blocked me. No, I
didn't avoid a question. She said, "Am I
working today?" I said, "No,
I'm too forward." Oh, I'm too forward.
Okay. So, you want me to speak to people
for weeks and weeks and weeks when
they're going to lose interest anyways?
I give up, bro. I I I can't get through
to you people.
I give up, bro. If you're just going to
keep making excuses time and time again,
it's not my problem anymore. Like, I'm
going to Thailand. There's nothing too
pushy about that. You talk to someone,
you get their number, you speak to
someone, you want to meet them. How the
[ __ ] is that too [ __ ] What the
[ __ ] And even if you speak to them,
they're going to lose interest anyways.
Even if Yeah. Even if you speak to someone, right?
Yeah. They're going to lose interest anyways. So
anyways, I'm done. You're just going to
make excuses no matter what I say. Don't
But anyways, so it doesn't matter. Yeah.
You're just going to make excuses
anyways. So there's no point.
And who the [ __ ] goes to Belgium to see their friends,
you know? But nah, it don't work like
that because even if even if right, you
text them, right, they're going to just
stop replying anyways.
So what? Good luck trying to [ __ ]
Yeah. Anyway, Yep. You keep telling
yourself that, S. You keep telling
yourself that. Anyways, I've had more
women than you. So, you're you're wrong.
So, you're [ __ ] wrong
because I've had more women than you.
So, how can that be true?
Anyways, moving on now. I don't want to
talk about this no more. I didn't book
Thailand to start having the same
conversation and getting into it. You
know, I'm done with this now. It's not
my problem anymore. It's the same as
what I said to Ant-Man. I went out cuz I
wanted to go out and meet Monty and
that's the side effects from it. And
that's exactly why I booked to go to Thailand. So
yeah. No, I didn't want to. Anyways,
it's not my problem anymore.
It's not my problem anymore. This is
exactly why I booked Thailand.
So because to get away from all this,
but Monty was in a bad place. So yeah.
So you're just going to make excuses no
matter what. So there's no point because
if it was speaking longer, you're going
to say, "Oh, you should have asked her."
Like, "Whatever I do, you're going to
tell me to do the opposite." So it
doesn't it doesn't matter, bro. Whatever
I do, right?
You know, you're just going to tell me
to do the opposite. Now, I believe in
the talking thing for longer if you've
met them online, but you've not met this
person online. You've met this person in
person. So, it's different.
It's literally different. Like, you've
not met them on a dating app. You've met them approaching.
Like, that's completely different. Like,
you were speaking for about 10 minutes.
You've met in person. If it was a dating
app, I'd say, "Yeah, talk for like 2
weeks to a month. This is not a dating
app. This is approaching, which makes
the whole thing completely different."
No, no, no, no. You don't understand.
This is not a dating app.
And again, you're just going to tell me
to do the opposite anyways. So, whatever
I do, you're going to tell me to do the opposite.
So, if I'm not too forward, you'll tell
me that I need to be more forward. So,
whatever I do, you're just going to tell
me to do the opposite.
And no, she didn't. Now, again, you're
just making excuses. Now, you're just
looking for excuses.
But this is not from a dating app.
So it's completely [ __ ] different, you know.
Yeah. Yeah. You're talking about
yourself again. Bye-bye. Stop talking
about yourself on my channel. But
anyways, I'm not having this
conversation anymore. You wanted a
conversation. You wanted the um you
wanted a conversation. I showed you a
completely normal conversation
with nothing wrong with it and they're
randomly blocked. I'm done with this
conversation. I'm not having it no more.
I didn't pay [ __ ] £700 for flights to
to stay having the same conversation.
I'm not having this conversation. I
think I've wasted enough time and I'
I've showed you the conversation.
There's nothing wrong with the conversation.
Um because there literally is nothing
wrong with that convers and I'm not
having this conversation anymore. I
booked Thailand to get away from this
[ __ ] you know, to get away from this
stupid [ __ ] in this country. I went to I
went to Birmingham because of Monty.
Yeah. And because I had literally [ __ ]
all better to do. I don't care anymore, bro.
You know, you're always going to make excuses.
You're always going to make [ __ ]
excuses cuz then what I always say is
that, okay, if it's this thing, what
about that thing? You know,
okay, whatever. I'm desperate. Yeah,
it's all my fault. Get over yourself.
Yes, it's all my fault. I'm desperate
for not wanting to waste my time. Yes,
because I didn't want to waste my time
like all the other times. Yes, I'm very,
very, very, very desperate. Oh, well,
I'm just going to agree with you, bro,
because unless someone agrees with you,
you're not going to [ __ ] You know
what I'm saying?
Anyways, I'm not having this
conversation anymore. You're just going
to make excuses. What? Oh, did they see
the Twitter post? Oh, what if they heard
Monty say that you love Morgan? You just
make excuses. So what's the point of
even having a conversation, bro?
You know, he's
Yeah. But no, but you're not giving But
you're not giving opinions. You're just
looking for excuses. That's the
difference. It's not about an opinion
because you're looking for excuses.
Because if I done something wrong there,
then I done something right there.
That's the difference. If I done
something wrong there, then the other
conversation I would have done it right.
So that's how you don't have no
argument. You know,
you will defend them no matter what. No
matter what, whether I'm wrong, whether
I'm right, you're still going to defend
them, bro. Like look at the things
you're saying. Oh, what if Monty man
said [ __ ] you?
I don't [ __ ] love him. I was pissed.
I don't love that [ __ ] bro. I don't
love that [ __ ] bro. I said it like
she's my mom as a joke. I don't love the
[ __ ] bro. I was with Monty and I kept
thinking of it because because where
Monty was talking about Natalie, it was
bringing it all up again. Do you understand?
Cuz Monty was bringing it up like he
situation. It was reminding me and I was
pissed. I don't [ __ ] like her, bro. I
don't [ __ ] like the [ __ ] Otherwise,
I'd admit it. No, I don't anymore.
[ __ ] me, bro. Monty kept bringing it up
and I thought, "Fuck, one second. Monty
wants to come in."
>> I don't love, bro. [ __ ] off.
>> Who sent Who sent me 25 [ __ ] quid?
>> Don't know, bro.
>> Yeah, [ __ ] hell. Someone sent me 25
quid. I just thought in the bank 25 [ __ ] quid.
>> Yeah, no. [ __ ] I'm forgetting about
Natalie now anyways. I'm forgetting
about it. I can't be honest with it.
Believe me now on this like
>> I'm not playing games with women
anymore. You you seen
I'm just going to come out with it
either way peeps. I've been talking to some bird
have I been talking to some bird.
>> Yeah. They've been having some sexy
chats on the phone.
>> Sexy on the phone.
>> Yeah. No, I've been talking to some bird
um up um Mansfield Warop area. So yeah.
So, I'm going back up there because I
rung my place up last night and asked if
there's any rooms. I can put the video
up there if you want me to. So, I'm
leaving this place. So, I've been
talking to some next it what what would
you rate that?
>> Who emailed? Who do you reckon emailed?
Was it definitely people from YouTube?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> See, they'd have me homeless if they had
it their way.
>> Yeah. Lucky enough, last night I got
onto the phones cuz they know about
YouTube anyway. or
they know how malicious they are. So now
I'm going back really [ __ ] you up there.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. >> Huh?
>> I'm going back to my old place anyways in WhatsApp.
I'm going there. They can't get me out
of that place anyways cuz they know
about YouTube anyway. So they can't
start trying to get me out or that place
anyways. So I'm leaving this place. I'm
going to that woman me who I was talking
to last night. me.
>> Someone said money is a skinned bastard.
Yeah, it's all you.
>> I am a skin [ __ ] Stop repeating
yourselves. That's not a skit on my
behalf. I just got you your behalf. >> Yeah,
>> I get paid in 13 days and not whoever
give me that paying 25 quid, they're
getting it back when I get paid. I'm not
like that. I give money back. So that
person who g 25 quid, they're getting it
back. I'm all these scheme people. It's
because I was in a tent with Natalie and
I had to go and help Natalie out with
food and myself out with taxes on food as well.
>> So, what are you supposed to do then?
Just start just just keep talking to
people for like a month.
>> Like, is that what you want? Is that
like just to keep talking to people for
a month and then they just lose
interest? Anyways, you're an idiot, bro.
>> You asking I'm comming more money in
you. Kay, you stupid [ __ ]
I can't you asking you're more skinn
than me. Kay
with more money than you. You sad [ __ ]
I get paid twice in the same week basically.
>> Yeah, but they're going to lose interest
anyways, Joe. But they're going to lose
interest anyways cuz they're just going
to stop replying anyways.
Have you ever had it before where
someone's really interested in meeting
you never met and now they've lost
interest? Have you ever heard Have you
ever Have you ever heard the saying,
"Grab them by the grabbing something by
the [ __ ] horns while someone's still
by the bullet."
>> It's It's the smart thing to do.
It's literally the smart thing to [ __ ] do.
Well, it doesn't happen actually, mate,
because eventually they'll just lose interest. So,
>> yeah, these thoughts anyways, PJ, I've
been on the phone to the police ring me
today. I can even screenshot it all and
send it you. Kay's actually [ __ ] I've
got to go to the police station and sit
down and get interviewed. Not
interviewed, but talk about what Kelly's
done to Lord and Prim. That's what I've
got to do now. I've got to go back to
the police station, sit down with him,
and talk about the old days.
>> No, no, no, no, no. Joe, Joe. No, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no. You don't
understand that it's them. The problem
is them. Once you're out of this
country, once I
>> I'm not going to the police. Yeah, I'm
>> Yeah, let me kick you. Once you're out
of this country, you're not going to
have these problems. It is literally
them. Otherwise, I would not be wasting
over £700 on [ __ ] flights. It is them
not being interested. One second, Monty.
I'll let you back in. It's them not
being interested. It doesn't matter what
you do, what you say, they just aren't
interested in this country. End of. No
matter how you try to beat around the
bush or have different haircuts or try,
it's them not being interested due to
social media. [ __ ] hell, bro. Sorry, Monty.
Let you back in,
bro. Well, are you going to have this?
Are you going to have these problems in
a different country? No, you're not.
>> No, you're not. Sorry.
>> Yes, PJ. >> Yeah.
>> Yes. Ger,
I heard you talking about me, you know.
>> Not me, mate.
>> Well, someone said you said to him, "Oh,
there's this guy called Lemon or Lemls."
>> How you doing, PJ? I'm good, man. Are
you still housebound?
>> Yeah, I got schizophrenia. They call
that psychosis these days. I was in a
psych ward for 3 months and it changed my life.
>> You live You live in Milton Kees, don't you?
>> Yeah, I do.
>> Yeah, I went past there um Saturday.
>> All right. What was you doing? Can I ask?
>> Just going to Birmingham.
>> Oh, bro. Yeah, that's not too far.
That's not too far, is it? It's It's
like 30 pound It's like 30 for you. It's
probably £40 on a train, right? Return ticket. >> What? >> Yeah.
>> No, it cost me 29.
>> Exactly. That's what I mean. Like it it doesn't
>> It's like It's like 3 hours work.
>> So, you never go out? No. >> No.
I used to walk my dog, but
I don't know if you've seen the video,
but I was actually threatened with a
machete on live stream.
>> What the [ __ ] >> Yeah.
Yeah, that's my
>> um Yeah, I like you LMS, man. At least
you like admit your problems and [ __ ]
You know, you get so many people in law
J. Yeah. They don't admit that a lot of people
>> don't even don't even give him an
honorable mention. Don't even say his
name cuz he's not worth it.
>> They don't even No, I know. But they
don't they they try to make it seem like
they're a lot of people in the same
position as you, you know, like [ __ ]
got anxiety and [ __ ] but they don't
they don't admit it, you know.
>> If Lord Jay comes around here, I'm
chasing him down the street with a frying pan. >> Yeah.
>> How old are you now, Lim?
We're on 36 next month, Giza.
>> It's getting on, isn't it? Getting on, bro.
>> Yeah. The the worst side of 40, you
know, 30. I mean,
>> yeah, it is what it is, isn't it? >> So, what's [Music]
what's your biggest win on uh slots or whatever? Gambling.
>> I I haven't won that much on slots to be
honest. Only roulette.
You have to actually you need to make a
big win and then just go to Thailand and
live your life.
>> Yeah, that's what I've already booked
Thailand, bro. Yeah, for Yeah. Yeah,
I've already booked Thailand.
>> I want to go to Thailand. How much was the flight?
>> Uh 770 return though. >> Yeah.
Yeah. But how are you going to Yeah, but
how are you going to go to Thailand if
you can't leave the house?
As soon as I'm out of my area, I'm fine.
>> Yeah, Thailand is good, man. Yeah,
>> my friend lives there now.
>> Yeah. So, what does he do?
>> He just teaches English.
>> He keeps it English.
>> No, he teaches English.
>> He teaches English. Why? Okay.
>> Does he Does he know like what's it?
What's the language called? Taiwanese.
Taiwanese or something.
>> I don't even know the language to be fair.
>> I learned a little bit of Indian
language and then I lost it through brain damage.
>> Through brain damage. >> Yeah.
I've been damaging myself with loads of
chemically siders lately and I've
already I'm already got I've already got
mild [ __ ] damage. And I'm [ __ ] man. >> Yeah, >> PJ.
>> Yeah, bro.
>> You should come to MK and we'll go to a
drum and bass night where there's loads
of MC's and they will be sick.
>> Sure, why not?
>> We could take some ecstasy.
>> Nah, that.
>> All right. Okay. You're not invited.
>> Wait. Have you ever Have you ever done cocaine? >> Yeah.
>> What? A lot.
I don't know. A little bit.
I mean, I bought an eighth before. I
>> How How much money do you get a month? A
lot in it.
>> Um, I'm actually on minimum I'm on minimum pip.
>> So, what do you get a month? >> Um, 900.
It changes though. Sometimes it's 1,200. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. But that thing you were saying
about that drum and bass, how much is
that? That that that's got to be like
300 for a night out, is it?
>> No, I'm going to take my own drugs in
with me. And the alcohol is really
expensive. I'm not going to take
alcohol. I'm just going to buy bottles of water. >> Yeah. Bless you.
>> Last time I went there, I met Nikki
Black Market and he got me he he got me
he got he stopped me from getting me
kicked out. He stopped
>> when did you when did you last when did
you last come to um London? >> Um Tenacious D.
I went to afterwards when I was high on
Molly. I was high on Molly went to
London. I I wanted to meet loads of golf
ladies, but it didn't work out that way.
I went home. I was in I was in Canada
for like two hours. >> Jesus.
>> I was waiting. I was like, "Yeah, where
am I going to go now?" I didn't know
where to go and I had no money left. I I
had a I I had enough to get a couple of
pints and then go home.
>> What's the point? What's the point, Joe?
>> So, what do they call people for Milton Kings?
What do you mean?
>> Like what are you last like? Londoners
are known as Lond Londoners. Rumies are
rums. Manchesterers on Mans. So what are
people for Milton Kings?
>> You know what? I don't know.
>> Cuz you're not a Londoner, are you?
>> I'm a Southern Jordy.
Uh, PC was born.
>> I was born in the UK, PJ.
>> So, I'm not actually
>> Come back in, PC. Come back in, PC. Stop
making excuses for women. You simp.
Stop being a s.
No wonder women aren't interested. One
second. I let me kick Glems out. Yeah,
like when you go up and you start a
conversation and they give you attitude
as well, is it? Yeah, that's the reason,
bro. Because I didn't let you in the hangouts.
Yeah, man. Yeah. Like when you try to
speak to them and they just don't even
give you a chance to begin with. Yeah.
It's probably because I don't let you in
the hangouts, isn't it, bro? Yeah. What
a [ __ ] simp.
What a simpy thing to say.
Madness, isn't it? And why do you want
to know when Lem's misses? Sorry, Le. I
had to kick you there. One sec. conversations.
Yeah, that PC guy is a simp. I think
they're lying to themselves.
No, no, no, no, no. I don't think that
they're s I think that they're just
lying to themselves
by not thinking that women are the
problem and stuff. I think they're lying
to themselves deep down because they
don't want to get called called out for it.
If I do that to women and friends, what
about the approaching videos that you've
seen? What was the excuse that time?
What was the See, that's what I'm
saying. You don't even like
acknowledge things that you're shown.
You're that in denial. Well, I guess you
are in denial cuz that you're still
lying to yourself. Really? You You don't
even acknowledge videos like that you're
actually shown. It's crazy. It's like
that doesn't suit me because they're so
scared of the truth that they just
pretend it doesn't exist. It's madness.
It's actually [ __ ] madness. I think I
I mean I think most people have seen my approaching videos.
Yeah, but they just pretend like
nothing's happened. It's weird.
It's so mad.
They don't admit women are the problem.
It's madness, bro. Madness.
It's crazy, lad.
It's bad, is it? It's really bad, bro.
I don't love that. USA, is he? It's cuz
Monty, man. Think of it. Yeah. You're
drinking. Monty keeps talking about
Natalie. Yeah. You was in a similar
position [ __ ] two [ __ ] years ago.
And And it's like he's bringing it back
up every time he keeps talking about it
when someone keeps bringing it up,
bringing it up, bringing it up, bringing
it up, bringing it up. Like, you know
what I'm saying, bro? So, I thought,
"Fuck it. Let me just join Monty, man,
and say I love someone when I [ __ ] don't, bro.
I don't love that [ __ ] bro. be [ __ ] mad.
Yeah, she's my mom and whatever, but
[ __ ] that's all. She's just a useless
mom. That's all she is. Just a useless mother. Yeah.
That abandoned her son.
Yeah. That's why I would never meet a
woman from YouTube.
Yeah, I know, Mark. That's why I never
met Natalie G. That's why I would never meet anyone. Yeah,
that's why I I would never meet a woman
off YouTube, bro. you know.
So, yeah, man. But yeah, so let's just
go by Joe's logic, right? So, you get
someone's number, right? And then, well,
firstly, Joe, you need to get them to reply.
So, you think you should keep talking to
them for a while before meeting. But the
problem is is a lot of the time they
don't even reply.
I mean that B in Birmingham they did. I
mean that was a one-off. You don't you
can't even get a conversation out of
them. Well, normally like let's say
normally that Birmingham thing was a
one-off. So I mean it all stems from
them, you know. It takes two to to tango,
you know. So if someone's not interested
then it's like yeah it's
you're it seems like a lot of people are
scared of the truth. That's what I think it is. Madness, bro.
You're in denial. Yeah, man.
That's where it is.
Here you go. You're not talking to me
like that, Lisa.
You [ __ ] [ __ ]
You're not talking to me like that, you old [ __ ]
So, yeah, that's that's it. Yeah.
But yeah, Joe, it seems that you pretty
much make excuses for them.
You make excuses for them. It's strange, bro.
Oh, did she did she did she hear you say
you love USA, Izzy? Uh, did they type
your name up? All of these are just excuses.
It's just excuses.
And I think the best thing to do is when
you approach someone, try and meet them
as soon as possible.
That's what I think. You try and meet
them as soon as possible.
Like Well, not like literally like
didn't say, but yeah, I think so. Yeah, man.
Hi, you're muted.
>> All right, I'm all muted.
Wait, don't come on. Hang on.
>> Yeah, what's up?
>> Hey. Right, what what did you just say about me?
>> I said that you're old.
>> How old am I, PJ? >> Yeah.
>> How old am I?
Well, you're getting on a bit, love, aren't you?
>> Well, I am a little bit. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. What's up? >> Points.
>> Well, I don't know. Are you picking on me? No. >> No.
>> Okay. Right. So, don't know.
Did you just say you ain't talking to me like that?
>> Yeah. Are you calling me gay?
>> When did I call you gay?
>> Just read back what you just said. You
said Pay and I said you're not talking
to me like that. You old [ __ ]
>> I always call you that. I always say PJ like don't.
>> No, you [ __ ] don't.
>> Yes, I do.
>> No, you don't. Anyway, right. What's happening? >> Anyways,
>> just chilling, man. What about you?
>> I'm just chilling.
>> Just playing some GTA. >> Um,
all right. Okay.
>> I'm not happy. I'm not happy with um the
[ __ ] This situation clearly.
>> You think it's funny, is it? Right. Why do I
>> I don't know. You just do it.
>> No, you do. You're making me laugh now.
>> I don't think I think
>> I think that um is a [ __ ] and he said
what he said on here and I think that
Nat Lee, you know, don't know as is
practically the same.
>> I think they should get back together.
I don't know. Don't see it happening to you. >> No.
>> Hey, that Natalie wants to join your
chat, but I think that you don't like her.
>> What's Natalie? What?
>> No, the other. Do you know that Nat
Nyaps? That one?
>> What? From Nottingham.
>> From where?
>> The one from Nottingham.
>> Yeah. Do you know her?
>> Yeah, she's come on before. I don't have
a problem with her.
Oh, she thinks she got a problem with
her, right? She's probably watching. I
said, "Come up then."
>> No, I don't know.
>> I told her we said, "If you're all right
with him, he's all right with you." I
told her that, but she don't believe me.
>> Yeah. I was in Birmingham Saturday.
>> No. Yeah.
>> With Monty. It was a good laugh.
>> I thought you listen though. Um, I don't
know why Monty's being the way that he
is towards me.
He's not me and my daughter speaking,
does he? Why
>> is Is
going to get back with him?
>> I don't know. She talking to me. She She
thinks I've tried it on with everybody
cuz Monty has turned around and and he
said to you, he said that I tried to
send her to the shop
to try and try on with him. What the
[ __ ] is on about saying that [ __ ] to my daughter?
>> [ __ ] knows.
>> You know that's weird, right? Yeah,
>> my [ __ ] lights ain't working. Is
Natie in your chat? >> No.
I send her a message cuz I said I'd go live.
But she says that she um think it's
here, but she's scared to come in here.
>> She can come in here.
>> think she going to have a go with her? >> No.
Why would I?
>> I don't know. But well, you know what
everybody else is bloody like, so don't know.
>> Yeah, I'm all right.
>> Hopefully she'll speak in a minute if
she's watching. N say he's okay. We are coming in
and she's all right for panels and [ __ ]
PJ, she's a nice girl. I like her.
>> What is actually a cool dude?
Listen, I don't really say [ __ ] wrong
about him. All I said is that the same
thing, right? I was called out about his
[ __ ] app on his phone, right? And I
had to agree with it.
He had a [ __ ] teen dating app on,
right? What was wrong with admitting the
truth about it? He did have it though.
You know, he did and I do.
>> So, what you want me to do? sit there
and go have it. He did have it
>> that day.
>> I don't know.
>> Your daughter were watching you slag me
off and your daughter off. You'd be
stick up for your own daughter-in-law
here. Was slagging her off.
Lisa Lisa the sport is me
that chat giving it big didn't you
>> making lies up again are you Lisa
Natalie even knows what Natalie even I was off ugly [ __ ]
>> What about your false teeth?
>> He's a true [ __ ] He's a true [ __ ] >> Listen,
>> you got a fantastic daughter. Look at
the state of you.
>> You know, how the [ __ ] did you erase
that girl? for two months.
>> Did you mother offer?
Did Did you Didn't you even got the spot
worker today saying you were going
Natalie? Cuz you won't do that to this
[ __ ] will you? Lisa, sort yourself
out. Yeah. Get off YouTube, you old
wrinkly [ __ ] Before I get my mom to
knock you out. Yeah. Simples.
Yeah. Wrinkly assa
you ugly fat ugly ass
wreck or inky you ugly
>> you you two pack it in
>> so he's supposed to be coming today to
get a close you sport worker on me up today
nobody said I'm coming you [ __ ] >> But coming today,
you're not coming today. >> Okay.
>> Who said
you work? You [ __ ]
>> Well, there's a worker. Oh, no. Nothing.
in your own [Applause]
said you were coming to doing [ __ ]
house leaves sir
thinking the house
>> I don't like
why can't everybody just listen to
listen to le yeah when me and
No, you allowing this. You're allowing
this wearing it. Listen, listen. Listen to this
me when they were cleaning out your
bedroom. Why was a picture of your
daughter behind the unit? Not even even
a flame. You was more bothered about what you >> just
one piece. He was bothered about one.
cuz it just fell down the back had it
>> you [ __ ] m
it was creamled up. It were crinkled up
and it looked like it being chopped down
the side. It's plenty funny.
>> I ask you about that.
>> Why did it look like that? I
>> did ask you
when you break when you show proof about
I don't need to show proof. I don't need
to show proof to you. I don't need to
show proof to anyone in this community. Never.
>> I believe you.
>> You're a [ __ ] [ __ ]
to me on PJ in the chat room with in
front of your daughter back in the day.
>> I'm going to say that.
You talking about your vagina to me and PJ
that then did that. Did I chat?
Yeah. Did you PJ when back in the day
when it was me?
>> What bloke does this? Answer me a
question. What does this picking up for
your [ __ ] daughter? You're a [ __ ] mom
to her. In fact, you say you blown your
son up, didn't you? Where's your son
living? Where's your son living? You
didn't bring your son up, did you? No. I
like my son. You never blown your son
up. Your son lives here with your
[ __ ] mom, didn't he? And none.
No dad's mother.
So why did you say you liked him better
than your own daughter? Mother actually
you said you'd like him better. You you
talk about your son more than what you
do about your own daughter. You slide
your own daughter off completely in this
community but not your own son who you
never [ __ ] see.
>> I've got nothing.
>> What are you talking about?
I'm getting all the truth out on you. Yeah.
Yeah. And you're just going to sit back
and watch what you
brick up a month away. Yeah. What about
when you attack her with a chair and all that?
>> My children. [ __ ] Did I my children
came up? No.
>> Oh, no. No. Cuz you idiot. You got other
people to bring your kids up.
>> My kids. How did I get other people to
>> I'm not muted.
>> You know what I mean? Lisa, you're
bringing that up. Look how she turned
out. Wonderful. Yeah.
>> You remember
Tam's your d. And you everything
you blame for money going mission and everything
she's watching this. I hope she's money.
>> Where did where did your mom's money go
for the hotel?
>> My opinion is they all red money about
your mom the hotel.
>> The hotel your mom's your mom and dad's
hotel. Where did her money go to?
>> What do you want about how the [ __ ]
What are you on about you [ __ ]
>> You spending your mom's hotel money and
blame it all on
>> Yeah, for yeah. Is that what she told
you? That what she told you?
>> That what she told me. So why did you do
that then? Why did you bring her? Carry
on with carry on with it. Go on. Go on.
This is interesting what she's told.
Anyone who's on YouTube slagging your
own so why not Lisa?
Okay. I can all day with this.
What else? What else do you want to say?
>> Mom to that girl.
>> That girl serves so much [ __ ] you.
No, I tell you what.
Want to know you're a [ __ ] dead.
Your mother is a door.
Your mother is a cracking mondo
when you met me. My mom don't touch
drugs. You do
when I met you that your mother is the
next smackage. A [ __ ] lawyer now. What?
>> She's the next crackhead.
The [ __ ] are you pulling a crackhead?
>> You tingling [ __ ] crack tablets. You
you crackhead. You your mother is a
>> You [ __ ] m you.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You're [ __ ] what? How the
[ __ ] is she?
Why are you not getting over?
>> Why you not getting over
here? Is that is she that's shutting the [ __ ]
Okay. Who's my dad? Grezy. Grezy. Who's
>> Why did you blame Natalie for the death
of of the granddad or something? For the
fight. Why did you blame?
>> Who blamed her?
>> You blamed her.
>> Oh my god. This is all coming out today. Go ahead.
>> It's all coming out, is it?
>> Yeah. So, you blame your own daughter, didn't you? I dad
wanted to look after you then you blame
blame not me blamed not me get it right okay okay
I apologize on that one
>> leather being spartic
I swear to God, never beat me again.
>> I I mean this I am done. I am done with
you. You [ __ ] horrible little [ __ ]
putting [ __ ] into this mongo's head.
>> Mong head. You put [ __ ] in your head.
>> I'll tell you what. I'm going in here
and I'll put Roy and I'll tell Roy.
>> Yeah. Get the kids out of Royy's house.
Go and get him.
>> I'll tell you what
I'll get from that
and I'll get Aaron down here to cap his
knees cuz that's what he needs.
>> Come on, get him. Again, >> [ __ ]
right. You [ __ ] big [ __ ] If you
see what you can do, [ __ ] Let's see.
>> Yeah, Lisa thinks I'm soft.
>> No, M's quite strong to be fair.
>> You want to Yeah.
>> What are you going at me for? >> [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Mother's number.
>> Yeah. Monty's quite vicious.
>> That's already
worked as it
>> cross anywhere. Anyway,
>> how many times How many times do you
have a bath, Lisa?
>> I have a bath enough mondo.
Another one. Another one. Another one.
Why did you Why did you shout out Natalie?
>> Why did you say Natalie was poisoning
you a couple of days after you set with her boyfriend?
Here we are.
>> You can get it all your own
shades. Feeling guilty. Feeling guilty.
>> What else? Feeling guilty.
>> Which one? Which one did I shag [ __ ] Cuz apparent one.
>> Oh, I saw you basically. Which one? You said two.
>> I'm a leader.
>> You said two, you le
what [ __ ] one.
>> You know which ones. You know which
ones? You hear me? You know which ones you have.
>> Do you want me to boot your face off or what?
I get my [ __ ] off.
>> I get my mom to knock you down. I
[ __ ] get my mom to break your person.
Nothing is an exe
got two kids.
>> Your mother is a mother.
>> I get me auntie to buy you then. No problem.
>> Yeah, I'll do this. I'll And I'll get
people to b you, mom. Come here. I'll
get his son to kneecap the [ __ ] out of
you. Come on then, [ __ ] >> Look,
>> come on then, [ __ ] That's not about
him then. Come on.
I dare you.
>> I dare you, [ __ ] Come on.
I'm [ __ ] Come on, Natly. Bring [ __ ]
here. Go on. If you're arguing,
you you know is crackheads.
>> Do you know? Do you know after this
Natalie, this is going to be I swear to
God, I messaged you earlier, right? This
is me and you done for [ __ ] good. for
[ __ ] good after your [ __ ]
>> No, no, this is your [ __ ]
>> This is all your [ __ ] Lisa.
>> This is my [ __ ] Where's your [ __ ] You
[ __ ] me. So why you flipping hell so bad?
>> Where the [ __ ] is
as a looney [ __ ] head and as a
mecking [ __ ] up [ __ ]
Maybe the ex
even told he slept with you.
>> Which one?
>> Yeah, they've been in the house.
Listen to this. PJ PJ, listen to this.
>> Listen to this PJ. One second. Listen to
this. Do you know Lisa?
in my house for me.
>> Somebody record Monty.
>> Yo, go for it, PJ.
>> I still want to move in, bro.
>> Yeah, you're not allowed. I'm leaving
out of this [ __ ] all anyway.
>> Yeah, because of these people on YouTube they email.
They're watching you. I give you >> I'm see
give everybody this address on YouTube.
What you've done?
>> Did you not tell me to give it give it?
Did you not meastard
one of you email the house guard me you
[ __ ] and know you think you're in
control of the house burn my [ __ ] [ __ ] go ahead
let's see what happens to you [ __ ] go ahead
I'm not going to be trying. Your [ __ ] is
actually smells. It smells like sweat
[ __ ] I'm pissed.
>> Who's in my bed? You m
>> Natalie's bed. I'm actually sleeping in
Natalie's bed. You thick [ __ ]
>> In my bedroom for weeks, you [ __ ]
That's the only one with the [ __ ]
>> I actually uses my bedding.
>> Why don't you?
>> Yeah, my bed.
>> It's been washed. So why didn't you take
it with you then?
>> So why did you use it again?
>> You left it.
>> So hang on. It was washed. But it stinks me making
wash it. Not only had to wash it cuz it
stunk a fish.
>> Yeah. She washed it the damn day, didn't
she? Yeah, good.
>> Now the answer to the question is you [ __ ]
>> and I believe everything that Kaye said about you.
>> You wrecked that girl's life. You did.
>> She ruined her own life. >> You
haven't done nothing but
like you're talking about me again.
You're the one s you're talking about.
>> You have done everything to break that
girl's life and she's young as well. Horrible.
You put your own daughter's life up. You might
put your own homeless.
>> You're the one who put you on D
homeless. You're the one who's got now
put on the streets by giving out this address.
>> Did you not keep guarding me to get the
address out, Mondo? I didn't know you did.
>> Listen, what about answer? Why you got
your own daughter kicked out this house?
>> Why did you give out elite
>> every address?
Every address you
>> Why did you put your own dog up?
>> Cuz you kept asking me to guard to guard
no. You turn me on and say I'm going to dox. Did
>> you not say that kept shifting all over
the toilet seat?
So I said do it.
>> You say to me you keep shifting all over
the toilet seat. You ain't worthy of
being around your daughter. You're
>> I see my kids.
>> You ain't got nothing on me with my
children. My daughter talks about me
daily every day. She talks she never
my daughter talks about me every [ __ ]
day. Yeah. She never brings up Kayie. My
daughter talks about me and Natalie.
Yeah. Not Kayie.
My daughter likes your daughter. My mom
would My mom likes your daughter. This
is what you've created. This little monster. >> Monster.
How do I care when we're
as well? You go for younger Io.
But no one's giving you attention, you sweaty [ __ ]
>> What is it? You can't get on your own.
>> How old's among you have to come on? You
have to come on YouTube and flash your teach
at least I've got respect for my body.
>> Do you Lisa
patient [ __ ] Listen, listen. I'm fit
and healthy. I quit the weed. See how
easy it is for me to quit the weed? It says piss.
>> I don't drugs. I don't do anything. I don't drink.
>> Is this how you turned on Kylie before and
we haven't even turned on Natalie? Do
you know what? Natalie's amazing [ __ ]
woman. Do you see me slagging Natalie
off even though Natalie's finished, man?
No. Cuz Natalie's done [ __ ] all wrong.
I'm not going to set you a lie, am I?
That is a [ __ ] She's amazing. >> [ __ ]
>> If it's a child abuse and your
daughter's unstable, [ __ ] So I hope she cut
you unstable. You made your own daughter
unstable. Yeah. Yeah. You made you
unstable the way you leaving in the
bedroom on her own. Not even talking to
her. D is spitting in to kill you by
food poisoning. You're bringing up
costic kids to get police and ambulance.
[ __ ] you said completely right
though. Going out shagging the partners
for the [ __ ] rent money and all that [ __ ] Yeah,
>> it's rent money as well. Wait there,
[ __ ] I have to pay rent money for me
for Go on. Oh yeah. And then and then
you said that Ry wasn't
even wasn't even you kicked Roy out didn't you?
>> Didn't you keep kicking out? Yeah.
Didn't you kick him out? Didn't you Roy
had to go homeless? What are you on about?
You kicked Roy out and Roy had to go
homeless. That's why he's got his own
place now in Birmingham. And you said um
like he moved to Blackpool with you.
>> No, [ __ ] What happened?
Yeah, you're full of [ __ ] You ghosted.
I got ghosted. Anyway, PG. See you
later. Yeah, I finished with this whole
bag. Anyways, yeah.
>> See you later.
>> Yeah, ghosting, man. I was talking to um
the numbers replied
um from uh Saturday. Yeah. And we was
talking and um said, "Oh, you should
come to London sometime." Proper reply
and like. And then today she said, "Oh,
she's going Belg. She said she's going
Belgium. I said, "Oh, Belgium's good.
I've um I've been You'll like it." And
then she just randomly blocked me. It
will never change in this c in this
country, ghosting. Never.
My autism is bad. Never had autism in my
life. You're talking about yourself
again. You've got me mixed up with
yourself, bro. The only one that's got
autism is yourselves. Just like you all skin.
Yeah, bro. It never changes ghosting. I
only went to Birmingham to go see Monty,
bro, and because I won the football bet
in it. So, I thought, [ __ ] it. I got
nothing better to do. I didn't go for
women. But yeah, there you go. Just an
example that it doesn't change anyways.
So, it's madness, isn't it? It literally
never changes in this country, does it?
>> It's a ma, bro.
It's a madness.
You never had autism in my life. You're
talking about yourself.
The only one that's got autism is you. Uh
they're abusing each other to be honest
with you, Ghosting. They're abusing each other.
Yeah. They just need to move on from um
NI Gina, I think.
Nah, you've already got autism.
You've already got autism. That's why
you go on about autism because you've
got it yourself. You've got autism. You
are autistic. That's why you know all
the telltale signs. Oh, [ __ ] Well, yeah.
Yeah, man. Anyways, I'm blocking this
account as well. Yeah, man.
But yeah, it doesn't change this country ghosting.
Never, lad. It will never change.
And you don't expect it to change either.
I'm trying to find a car here, bro.
[ __ ] battery's going to die again.
Yeah, I lost £50 on fishing frenzy
today. Go. I went to collect the winnings
and I lost 50. So, collected 235. Yeah, man.
I've never admitted to having autism
because I don't have autism.
You people have autism. That's why you
go on about it because you've got it
yourselves. Takes one to no one. Um, no,
I didn't get a bonus. I put £100 in. I
just took 50.
But I've never admit having autism
because I don't have autism. You people
are the ones with autism. You people are
the ones that come on YouTube every day
repeating yourselves for year in year
out. Year in year out. You people have
been coming on here repeating yourselves.
So you must have autism yourselves to be doing that.
So yeah, not even a bonus anyways. Ghost.
No, I didn't get a bonus. I put £100 in,
but I just took the 50 cuz I didn't want
to give it any more money, you know. Yeah,
that's why I don't play it anymore, bro.
It's pissing me off. I just got the 50.
Don't even know why I went on it to be honest. Yeah. Yeah, man.
Yeah, it will never change in this
country. Ghost in the dating scene. Never.
Cuz it's been happening for years, which
is one of the reasons why I booked
Thailand. I only, like I keep saying, I
only went to Birmingham to see Monty.
Hadn't been out in two weeks, won some
money, so why not in it? I had nothing
to lose. So,
but yeah, that's where we're at basically, bro.
They all reply to numbers.
It will never change. I don't know why
ghosting you think it's going to change
though. If it's not changed in years,
why would it all of a sudden change?
You know, it won't because of the the
time frame it's been happening for. You
know what I'm saying? And it's like when
I got them numbers. Yeah. I was like
maybe but then realistically I'm
thinking well think of it right. You've
done it for years and years before like
going to different cities. I don't think
it's going to be different this time.
And it wasn't different this time and it
will never change which is why we're
going to Thailand.
Well, we other places but there as well
but cuz of the time frame you see. It's
it's the actual time frame that's been
happening for and how long it's been
happening for. You see, all the evidence
suggests that it will stay that way.
Yeah, I know, bro. I know. But I'm just
saying, is it?
I know, bro. I know. I'm not I'm not
moaning. I'm just saying, you know. Yeah, man. [Music]
it was fun in Birmingham though. It was
a good good night out. It's mad.
It's not even just a relationship. You
can't even get laid.
Even get laid either.
No, I'm not going back there, bro. You
mad? What the [ __ ]
Why am I going to Why am I going to go
back up there, bro?
Why would I go back up there?
Why the [ __ ] would I go all the way back
up there, bro? Because Huh?
Yes, she did.
We've already been over that.
We've already been over this.
Yeah, it doesn't matter. I'm not going
to go out and waste another [ __ ] £200.
[ __ ] that, bro. That was a That just
reminds me why I don't go out in London anymore.
That just that just tells me that just
explains why I don't try anymore.
That that weekend. Yeah. Just just just
that tells you why I don't even try
anymore, bro. If it wasn't for Monty,
I don't know why he's I've already
explained this, bro. I'm not going over this again.
That's autism right there. You're asking
the same thing over and over again,
which I've already explained. That's autism.
No, it's not about the cheaper. I I
can't be bothered, bro. Going up there,
wasting money. I can't be asked with it.
That's why I don't try in this country
anymore, bro. If it wasn't for money, I
weren't even going to go out in London this week.
I weren't even going to go out in London
to be fair. It's pointless. It's It's
the same [ __ ]
That's why I don't I can't be bothered.
It's the same old, bro.
It's the same [ __ ] That's why I don't
even try, bro.
I don't even try anymore. Me, bro. I
can't be asked now.
It's just the same trolling, same games,
same [ __ ] [ __ ] in it.
Yeah, man. See you.
And then people are trying to blame, oh,
you're asking them to meet too fast.
You're asking them to meet too fast.
It's just excuse after excuse after excuse.
And then if you take it slow, they're
going to say, "Oh, well, you should have
asked her to meet you. You're boring
her." It's always going to be these excuses
until one day like somebody actually
wakes up and smells the coffee,
but they won't because they're just
lying to themselves. So that probably
would never happen to be honest.
You need to meet people ASAP, bro. What the [ __ ]
But yeah, they never blame them. They
always blame you. It's they're in denial.
No, it is an excuse. No, no, no, no, no.
It is an excuse. You was coming up with
things. Oh, she might have heard you say
this. She might have looked your name
up. Like, no, it it is an excuse because
if I had done the opposite, you would
tell me to do the opposite. And I'm
telling you it is an excuse
because I know exactly what you would
say if I done it the way that you told me. So
yeah. Yeah. Talking about yourself
again. I'm not even going to block you.
I'm just going to let you stay on and
embarrass yourself. Yeah. You get a job.
Yeah. Same same back to you. You get a job.
So you are you are using it as an excuse.
It is literally an excuse. It takes two to tango. So
it takes two to tango.
You would say you're boring her. You
should have asked her to meet. That's
exactly what you would say.
It literally is an excuse. What do you
want somebody to to speak to someone for
a thousand years?
Nope. That never happened,
you know. Well, she didn't. She could
have, but she didn't. Again, it's just
another excuse. I've heard loads of
different excuses. I've heard that you
don't have a job, you live with your
mom, maybe they've seen you recording,
maybe they've seen you speaking to a
camera. You're literally just looking for excuses.
That's why no one really cares what
anyone says because it's just excuses.
I've heard so many excuses in my life
that [ __ ] hell, bro.
Yeah. And I didn't say it 10 times. I
just thought I'd join in with Monty.
I don't love that [ __ ] Otherwise, I
would tell you I do. I don't [ __ ]
love that [ __ ]
Monty kept [ __ ] bringing up Natalie
in the same situation. So I thought,
"Fuck it. I'll just join him." So yeah, man.
But yeah, all of these are excuses. Oh,
like you live with your mom or you don't work or
no no no.
No, I won't because I've took your um
I've took your advice
and it doesn't work.
It's not constructive criticism. It's
just excuses. I've worked. I've lived by
myself. I've gone through the gym. Nothing changed.
So, if you go through all of the excuses
you've you've made over the years, it's mad.
There's no helping. It's there's too
many stuck up [ __ ] in this country
and they think that they're better than
they are because of social media. That's
the truth that no one will tell you.
That honestly is the God's honest truth.
Like no one will sit right here yet and
tell you, "Oh, maybe that woman was
[ __ ] with your head or maybe that
woman was trolling you or maybe I don't
know, maybe that woman was leading you
on." Nobody would ever say that. They
will just blame you and make excuses.
That's the That's the funny thing about it.
Yeah. But we're not talking about
cooking. We're talking about suckup
[ __ ] that think they're better than
they are because of social media.
It's like you're scared of the truth.
That's what I think most people are.
They're scared of the truth.
It's they are stuck up [ __ ] due to
social media. There's no helping.
You know, you don't have success with
women because I've had more women than you have.
But I've had more women than you will
ever have. So why would I take your advice?
I've had more women than you. Just
because I don't simp and and [ __ ]
lick their asses, that doesn't mean I've
not had women. I I'm just not scared of the truth.
I'm just not scared of the truth. I'm
not in denial.
That's the difference. I'm not in
denial. And I'm not going to sit here
and lick women's asses. Straight up.
Kieran, how are you doing, bro? Like,
yeah, I got I got three numbers
yesterday uh on Saturday.
Still feels like Sunday, man. Shining. I
was speaking to this person, Kieran.
Yeah. Like nonstop.
Um, and then I suggested like meeting
another time. And then they were like, um,
and then they r and then I said to them,
they said they were going to Belgium.
Yeah. And then when I went when when I
went to uh then I was like, "Oh, you'll
like it there. I've been there before."
He literally just randomly blocked me,
bro. And then I read the whole
conversation on YouTube and these people
just make excuses for women all the
time. It's ridiculous.
They literally just will look for
excuses. It's not even It's not even
constructive criticism, bro. Because
then my whole thing is, so what what
you're supposed to talk to a woman for a
thousand years before asking them,
right? Asking them to [ __ ] meet.
Like, it's always an excuse.
It's literally always an excuse. No, I
don't think texting a woman that I
approached the night before counts as
having more women. I think having more
women is being on more dates, seeing
somebody for 2 years, [ __ ] with loads
and loads of women. That's more than
you've ever had. I'm just not in denial.
I'm not going to sit here and keep
defending them when I know they're in
the wrong. Simple.
But I think me sleeping with more women
than you, going on more dates with you,
being in more relationships than you,
cuz I have been in a relationship, I
know more about women than you. You
can't help me.
only I can help myself and that's
leaving the country.
No, but here's the thing though, Kieran.
Even when you're up their asses, they're
not interested. Think of it, bro. How
long have these guys been singing for,
right? How long I haven't seen anyone
for 2 years. You keep telling yourself
that, bro. No. No. But here's the thing,
Kieran. They think by sing it's going to
get whipped, but it doesn't get them
laid. Women don't sleep with simps.
That's the thing. The women do not like
simps. These simps, right,
have had less women than me and you,
right? And they still sit there and
defend them. Like, women don't like them
and they still sit there and [ __ ]
defend them. Bro, it's embarrassing.
If they got women in the first place,
they wouldn't resort to tin.
I've had more women than these people
that stick up for women. And I'm talking
generally. That's the That's the [ __ ]
up thing about it.
They're just in denial, you know.
Yes, I have that 19year-old. Yes, I have
that 19year-old. Try again.
But yeah, Kieran, like what do they want
you to do? Sit there and speak to
somebody for 10 years before asking to
meet? That is that what you want someone
to do? They always make excuses for
women. It's embarrassing, bro. When no,
the truth is that there's just too many
stuck up [ __ ] in this country due due
to social media. That's the truth.
No, never paid a 19year-old. And I'm not
having this conversation again. Like, I
I want a conversation with somebody that
can give constructive criticism, right?
Do you understand? Not somebody that's
just going to defend women like these
people do. I'm not interested in that.
It's pointless. It's a waste of my time.
Oh, I lost £50,
you know, and you're banned. I told you
I'm not having this conversation. Simple. Bye-bye.
Simple. Anyways, Kieran,
um, yeah, I lost 50 on Fish and Frenzy.
A brass. You You're just going to get
kicked for even saying that.
Yeah. And then she just blocked me
randomly, bro. And then these people are
making excuses. Oh, you shouldn't have
asked her to meet. So what the [ __ ] did
you want me to [ __ ] do? Sit there and
speak to someone for [ __ ] 10 years.
They always make excuses for these
females. This is exactly why I booked
Thailand to get out of here, bro. This
is Listen, I had fun with Monty on
Saturday. But this is why I want to get
out of here, bro. This is exactly why I
booked them tickets to get out of it. To
get away from this [ __ ] Just like
Ant-Man did. Just like Ant-Man did. To
get away from this [ __ ] Yeah.
I put my conversation up there. Yeah, I
put my conversation up there because I
know I hadn't wrote anything wrong.
Obviously, bro, I'm a [ __ ] adult. Yeah, man.
Yeah, I got three responses, Kieran, but
I was talking to one constantly, bro.
And they do it on purpose. Here's They
They do do it on purpose, bro. Like, no.
Oh, I've never done anything bad
anytime. It's not just this time, it's anytime. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. Like, what do you want me to
do? Sit there and speak to someone for
[ __ ] 10 years?
Like, I I don't understand what what
what these people are getting at and
they do it. And the thing is, Kieran is
they do it on purpose. A lot of these
people do what they do on purpose. The
[ __ ] this Yes, they [ __ ] do, bro.
Yes, they [ __ ] do do it on purpose.
And then you get all of these people
defending them like it they're not the problem
a lot of the time. Let's put it that way.
I'll read out the conversation if you
want. Again, Kieran, it's annoying, bro.
They give their number, they reply, they
agree to meeting him, then they waste
your time. This is why I don't go out
anymore, bro. I went out because I felt
sorry for Monty. Simple.
So, I thought, "Fuck it. I've got
nothing better to [ __ ] do. Wow, bro.
Yeah, exactly. That's what it is. It is social media.
And I said to Antman, the only way this
will change and if they if they ban
social media, you go to South America,
you go to Asia, and they're never going
to ban social media. So, they're the three options.
They're the three options, lad. You
either they either ban social media
here, which they're never going to do.
They go or you go to Brazil, you go to
South America, or you go to Asia.
They're your only options. But the first
one is never going to happen. But I
mean, in terms of it like changing,
you understand? So
yeah, man. I got three replies.
They all replied to be fair with
enthusiasm. They did reply but [ __ ]
then I replied and then we was talking
and we're talking today as well.
It's [ __ ] bro.
Okay, Kieran, let me read the
conversation to you. Yeah. And you can
tell me if I done something wrong cuz I
know we've been speaking for years. Let
me read the conversation. Yeah.
It's going to take like 3 minutes. I'll
read it to you, bro. And it's just [ __ ]
like this that annoys me, bro.
It's bro, you didn't tell me nothing. I
knew this, bro. Kieran, you didn't need
to tell me this, bro. I knew all of this [ __ ]
But the reason I don't have I don't have
hope. Even when they replied back, you
know why, Kieran? Because it's been
going on for years. So even when they
were applying deep down I'm like ah like
this is going to happen again because
it's it's been happening for years. So
what's the odds here Kieran? Think about
it like this realistically bro. What's
the chance that you've just gone out in
Birmingham? Bear in mind I've gone to
Birmingham seven times. You have just
gone out this time in three and a half
years and suddenly now it's going to
change. It doesn't even sound
believable. It doesn't matter who texts
back, you know. It doesn't matter who
text back or whatever.
It's been going on literally for years.
So, the odds are not looking good.
It's been happening before there was
even Tik Tok, but it wasn't as bad to be
fair. But the thing is, Kieran, and the
thing I've noticed, Kieran, yeah, is
it's very based on nationality.
So, this one was from Romania and she done
she done what a um
Huh? Get a get a You need to mug off and
settle for one night bangs. Ha. And how
you going to get one night one night
bang? One night bangs then. One night bangs.
Yeah, that's what Adman says. It's dead.
The dating game is dead in this country.
Yeah, but where you going to get one night bangs?
Where you where where you where where
the [ __ ] you going to?
They never all blocked me.
They didn't all block me. Just that one blocked me.
You know, like these people don't seem
to think that it's women.
Like they still they don't seem to think
that it's women doing it on purpose.
They don't seem to ever say that. It's weird.
But yeah, a one night bang. Where are
you going to get a one night bang from,
bro? When all of these people in clubs
apparently have boyfriends. Where you
getting a one night bang, bro?
What's so weird is that you're
good-looking like me. I don't know how
you look like. And you still can't even
get anything. It's [ __ ] wild, bro. I
would understand if you was fat and ugly
and skinn. I could actually understand
it then. It's crazy, bro.
And you know the worst thing about it is
when this stuff happens, you're drinking
and obviously you're depressed for the
next couple of days because of the
drinking. So you've got the depression
from the drinking and then you got this
[ __ ] on top of it. It's bad, bro. Bad.
It's really bad.
What I don't understand is why they give
their numbers and reply and then stop
replying. That's how you know it is then.
Yeah. Well, one did. Yep. Yeah. Well,
one did. Yeah.
But then then they're like, "Oh, well,
maybe he was too pushy with the
meeting." Okay, I'll speak to somebody
for 10 years then. Okay, next time,
right, when I get a number, I'm not
going to ask them to meet and we'll see
how far that gets me then.
Huh? You can't do right for doing wrong, lad.
You can't do right for doing wrong. You
need to get people when they're
interested or when you think they're
interested. You need to get them
straight away, you know.
Yeah, maybe, bro. Maybe. Maybe, lad.
It's [ __ ] up, is it?
It's weird, bro. It's weird.
I had hiccups all day yesterday, bro.
They've only just got better.
Had horrible hiccups. They were hurting me, bro. Horrible, lad. Yeah, man.
Yeah, I can't live with Monty now
because someone's been emailing the [ __ ] house,
the housing thing. And this is how you
know that most of these people on here,
Kier, have got autism because they're
still obsessed with things you said
about women and kids. That's how you
know they've got autism on here. You
know, I was talking about Mont I was
telling this to Monty the other day
like, you know, all of this [ __ ] Yeah.
Um, you know, um, I was telling Monty
about this about with like the kids and
[ __ ] Um, like obviously loads of people
have said different things, but with me
I forget. These people can't.
That's what makes that's how you know
they've got autism. The way like they forget nothing.
Um, you know. So,
but yeah, maybe it will change when I'm
in my 30s. It's definitely not going to
change in my 20s. Not in this country. But yeah,
that's how you know they've got autism
cuz they obsess over like things people
have said like in anger. It's so weird.
Yeah. If you if you chat up women in their 30s,
um they'll just say that you're too
young for them. All right. Here's
another thing as well is that um
uh another thing as well is that um
it's the same in America as well,
Kieran. I was watching this guy in
America and he was getting the same old
I've got a boyfriend. You're too old for
me, you're too young for me. It's the
same over there as well.
So, good luck to anyone, bro, trying to
date in these westernized countries. And
he was more confident than me as well.
And he I was like, "Oh [ __ ] it's even
bad." I had to stop watching it cuz it
was annoying me.
It was annoying me. And the maddest
thing is you're not ugly. Like if you if
you like I keep saying, bro, I don't
want to keep sounding like I'm a repeat
and all that, but if you look like
Timmy, you're better than these women.
Like you're probably more better off
than these men women. You probably got
more money than them. You're probably
better looking than them or if you're
not better than them, you're in the same
like they're not better than you.
So, it's wrong how you need to put them
on a pedestal when they're not even
better than you and you're not even
ugly. Like, you don't look like [ __ ]
Timmy Aldridge. You know what I mean?
But then there's people that are better
than me that still can't get anything.
So, it's [ __ ] It is all weird, isn't it, lad? Yeah.
I had a one night that stand with a New
Zealander. She was 31 or 32.
And her [ __ ] was really smelly, bro.
She had a smelly [ __ ]
She had a smelly ass, bro. It was really bad.
Like, it was really bad. But yeah,
but yeah, all the numbers replied
while I was speaking to she's a bit fat.
She hasn't blocked me. I just messaged
her. When did you last come to London? No reply.
Hey, nice to meet you, too. I I wasn't
too bad, actually. Just had a family
day. Don't come back to Brum all that
often. Did you make it back to London?
She lives in Liverpool, by the way. I
replied, this was another one. Same. It
was my first time there in 2 years. And
yeah, I'm back in London now. Did you
make it back to Liverpool? No reply.
I mean, I don't understand like I
understand given your number because
people make excuses like oh um they
might have felt scared or all of these
silly excuses that they make. Who the
[ __ ] is that? But what I don't
understand is why they give their number
to reply if they do reply and then stop
replying. That's the weird thing.
This guy was trying to scam me by the
way. That's how you know they're doing
it on purpose because
they will reply
but then stop replying. So, they're
obviously doing it on purpose.
Like, obviously they're doing it on
purpose, bro. It's so weird.
Social media's really [ __ ] us up, bro. It
It's really bad, isn't it?
That was another number. That was one of
the numbers from Birmingham. She said
she lives in Liverpool.
But yeah, this one says she's going to
Belgium to see her friends. I mean, that
doesn't even make sense.
Oh, mate, I've already done them
experiments a million times.
Yeah, they reply straight away to negativity.
Well, I've just messaged her again and she's
Well, she hasn't blocked me.
So, where where's our picture gone then? That's strange.
Thought she has blocked me.
No, she did. She must have and then
she'd unblocked me. What the [ __ ] bro?
What What the [ __ ] is this [ __ ] doing?
What the [ __ ] is this [ __ ] doing, bro?
I just type Wu2
one tick. So I got blocked. Then it said
they're online. So I typed it again.
Bro, these [ __ ] are playing some mad
games, bro. What the [ __ ]
Mad games. These [ __ ] playing it.
What you you two? It went through that time.
So why has it gone back to two ticks,
bro? These [ __ ] are [ __ ] [ __ ]
man. Anyways, I'm going to go eat my
food. I'll be back later. Yeah.