[Laughter] Yeah,
I never said I was getting a courage today.
You just made that up.
I think a lot of you on here are proper
proper proper [ __ ] disabled, man. I can't lie.
R said I was getting a curry today.
Yeah, I didn't say I was getting a copy
today. What the [ __ ]
Nah, not with me, mate.
You got the wrong person.
I had a lamb shank.
I had a curry yesterday. Yeah. Not today.
No, not really.
All right. Should we do this little bet? Yeah.
Everyone come off of YouTube from
tomorrow for one week and whoever goes
on it like types and stuff, they have to
give they have to give £100
so we can see who's the real people that
that ain't got no life but YouTube. See,
we do it starting from tomorrow.
And anyone who goes on YouTube has to
give me £100.
And if not, I will give a,000 pound.
Yeah, I will give £1,000 if none of
these people type.
Let's see if they can live without YouTube.
It'll be it'll be a fun challenge, is
it? Just for a week. And I'll come back
on Tuesday, next Tuesday, and see who's
been on YouTube.
Then I can say these skinned people have
got no life but your job.
Yeah, of course you are, bro.
Yeah, of course you are.
Yeah, she unblocked me. Maybe she didn't
block me. Maybe she just turned her phone off.
Yeah, you definitely get more replies
with the in Birmingham. You definitely get more.
Yeah, you definitely get more replies.
Yeah. Oh well, doesn't matter. Anyways,
I'll try and meet them eventually. I
want to go. I'm going to invite some of
these numbers to the cinema with me.
Nope. No interest.
Never been to Greece. I've got no interest. [ __ ]
No, I'm not a meanie. I'm not giving you
a [ __ ] mod.
Why am I going to waste my money in this
country when I'm leaving in November?
I'm not interested.
Why am I going to waste my money in this
country? I only went out to Birmingham
Ste Monty cuz he was in a bad place and
I won a football bet.
That ain't happening again, bro. Why am
I going to go Brighton?
I told you I'm going Thailand. Have you
got brain damage or something?
I'm sure some of you people got brain damage, bro.
No, no, no. Some of you have got brain
damage. The lads telling you
why the [ __ ] am I going to go to Brighton?
What the [ __ ]
Like, I'm going to go somewhere and
waste [ __ ] £300. What the [ __ ]
[ __ ] Brighton. Jesus Christ.
Why would I go back there? I've been
there like seven times.
No, I just told you I'm going to
Thailand, you [ __ ]
While he's in Indonesia, are you a
[ __ ] [ __ ] lad? [ __ ] hell, bro.
They call me [ __ ] disabled.
Barley's not in Thailand.
Marley's in Indonesia, lad.
[ __ ] hell, mate.
Well, there's one from Birmingham might
meet me. So,
yeah, you definitely get a better
response in Birmingham. Like the numbers.
I'm trying to think what it was like
before when I got numbers. I can't remember.
Um, probably. Yeah.
Monty's my friend.
Monty's a cool guy, man.
He's like, "Oh, I'll give you the money
back." I said, "I want the money back.
I don't care about money, matey.
Who give [ __ ] about
I'm not going to do a football bet this
Saturday. I don't like the teams, man.
No, not really. no, no.
Don't think money man will get off
YouTube now hopefully.
Oh, she's unblocked me now, which is
strange, Joe. And messaging me like
nothing happened. I swear these [ __ ]
have got mental health.
Yeah, I was just saying Monty said, "Oh,
I'll give you some money back when I get
paid." But I said, "I don't want money
back. I don't care about money, bro."
And I looked at the football and there's
nothing exciting for Saturday. So, give
it a miss this week, I think.
Yeah, that Frankie thing pissed me off
losing 50 pound, bro.
Yeah, I'm playing it clever. I left her
right in the last message. I'll message
her again in a week. See if she wants to meet
and then the other one lives soon in
[ __ ] Liverpool. So I ain't going
Do you know Do you know a fun fact, Joe?
Newcastle is twice twice the distance as uh Birmingham.
It's twice the distance.
That's [ __ ] mad. It's over twice the
distance. How mad is that?
That is madness, man.
No, I'm not texting her every day cuz
that's how they lose interest.
I've text her enough now. I'll invite
her out next week. I'm not going to text
every day, bro. That's how people lose
interest. That's how people get bored.
That's why you're supposed to meet
someone on Thursday in London and and
meet them by the Saturday. That's the
whole point of trying to meet when
you're in London.
You're supposed to meet. Yeah, photo
went. She did block me, but she
unblocked me. She is using a work phone.
Maybe she didn't want to see
Maybe she didn't want to um people at
work seem that she was texting someone.
Anyways, it doesn't matter. But um
that's why you're supposed to meet
people on Wednesday.
That's why you meet people on Wednesday. Thursday.
No, you don't need to keep it regular
because that's how they lose interest.
It's not going to work. They'll lose interest.
It's not going to work. Simple.
If you message them every day, they're
going to lose interest. Trust me, I
know, bro. I've been doing this for years.
I've been doing this for [ __ ] years, mate.
like so I know what happens.
So, but anyways, that's why you're
supposed to meet somebody on Wednesday
and meet them on the Saturday. That's
the whole point. You're supposed to meet
when you go out on Thursday, right?
You're supposed to meet somebody by the
Saturday or Sunday. That's that's how it
works. Or even the next week after or
the next or the next week.
It's supposed to be casual. Yeah. for a
couple of days, two or three days, and
then you're supposed to meet. But
obviously, she lives in Birmingham and
she's away, so
you're you're supposed to keep it casual
for not too long, and then actually meet. So,
she says she's in Belgium next week. So,
this week, so,
but yeah, like I said, they they do
reply. They did reply all of them
and they actually replied with
enthusiasm which is strange cuz like I
said sorry to keep repeating but in
London you rarely even get a reply.
Strange that though isn't it?
It is strange.
I didn't get one ignore me. Well, I got
one on Facebook that ignore me. But
three numbers, three repliers, mate. If
you had that every single time you went
out in London, you'd be laughing.
You'd actually be laughing. But yeah,
it's nice to just get replies. It's madness.
Maybe Birmingham is a little bit easier
than London, maybe.
But I think England's just England. I
think it's just the same everywhere.
I don't know, man.
But the last time I went to Birmingham,
I had a date, so I don't know.
I'm not sure.
Why am I going to get out of London,
bro? I don't I don't like Birmingham.
I like London.
Why would I Why would I go to B Why
would I live in Birmingham, bro?
doesn't make sense.
It's too far, bro.
And I need to see my mom time to time.
So, I can't do that.
I don't feel I could get used to Birmingham, bro.
Cuz I'm from London and they want to be London.
They try too hard. Yeah, but
yeah, I could have probably met her
Sunday if I stayed. What I was going to
do is I was going to stay Sunday. Yeah.
And text some of the numbers. I probably
could have got a meet Sunday to be
honest, but I just wanted to get back
home. I was getting homesick.
Yeah, she's all right.
Yeah, she's all right, man.
Yeah, but I think it is.
I don't know, bro. Like I said, you need
to do it monthto month.
Nah, that inspector was a [ __ ] bro. He
made sure I got off as well. He's a
bastard, bro. He's a wanker. Then I had
to end up getting on [ __ ] three
[ __ ] trains. He's a [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
He was a [ __ ] as well. He was a proper
[ __ ] man. Proper [ __ ] He was
had to get off another train and then
get a train and it terminated at
Northampton and had to get another train to London.
No. How? Well,
yeah, but maybe he saw cuz I paid for
the ticket in it. He was a [ __ ]
though. He was a [ __ ] He said, "If
you pay £23, you can stay on this
train." I said, "I'm not paying that."
If he had said like £10. Yeah.
If he said like um
uh you know £10, then maybe I'd consider
if I could stay on that chair. But £23,
[ __ ] that, bro.
just to stay on a train there. [ __ ] that.
Or get off. Simple.
£23. That's too much, bro.
Why don't they just have one train?
There's two trains to B. There's a fast
one that's an hour and 20 and then
there's a long one that's
No, there's a long one that's like 2
hours. But on that 2hour one, you can't
get food. Like there's no food, there's
no nothing. It's [ __ ] bro. But I just
got the cheapest one because as long as
I get there, I get there in it.
But next time because I didn't plan it.
You see, I didn't plan it. So I just got
like ended the cheapest ticket going
there cuz I didn't plan it. So
like I said, I don't know how I used to
do them Newcastle ones, matey. [ __ ]
hell. You imagine doing it in Newcastle
an all nighter.
You would be [ __ ] bro. Really [ __ ]
You would be really really [ __ ] up.
Yeah, man. No. No. Never.
Monty's my friend. Huh?
No, Newcastle's long, man. I remember
when I used to do them Newcastle ones
and you always know when you're near
London again cuz you go through a tunnel
and that's when you're back in London
cuz you go through a tunnel.
No, I like I like Monty Man, bro. What
the [ __ ] Monty man's just a bit of a
ruffian. He's a bit vicious.
I said you're a bit vicious.
Ow, that hurts. Let go. I said it hurts. You meanie? Yeah, man.
Move to Birmingham for funny. Nah.
Nah. [ __ ] that. [ __ ] Birmingham.
I hate Birmingham, bro.
No. Do you know what he don't know? He
tried to give an attitude. Yeah. I swear
to God, this is what actually happened.
But if I didn't get off, he was just
going to call the police, lad.
No, I don't bring it on myself. I paid
for the service. I didn't try to bump
the train or anything. So, I did I do
follow the rules. I didn't even know I
was on the [ __ ] wrong train. Yeah.
So, at the end of the day, I do follow
the rules. And also, no, no, no. I was
sat on the standard premium and he said,
"I'll get off at Coventry, right?"
And then he went and saw someone else.
They paid for their ticket. And then I
was like, "Oh, I need I'm going to go in
the toilet here. I'm not getting off
that commentary. [ __ ] that." And he
says, "Oh." And then I get up walking.
He says, "Oh, don't you go wandering
around." I said, "What did you say?" No,
no, no. Then I said to him, "No, no.
What did you just say?" I said to him,
"I will go where I want." He says, "Oh,
um, yeah, I was only," he made up like
some excuse to try to backtrack,
you know? I was like, "What?"
I was like, "What did he say? Am I Am I
hearing things right?"
Jesus Christ, you're bloody lucky I'm
[ __ ] getting off the [ __ ] train to
be honest. He would have just called the police
um and then they would have just got you
off. Yeah, they do it with buses as well.
There's a lot of bus drivers that have attitude problems.
So yeah, he was just a dick. You're
saying following the rules? Like I
didn't pay for the train. Anyone would
think I didn't pay for it.
I didn't bring it on myself. I paid £29
for a return just because it wasn't
[ __ ] West Midland's Rails. I still
paid for it.
I still paid for it.
You're talking like I didn't pay for the
[ __ ] service. Just a [ __ ] clown.
Being a [ __ ] because I remember before. Yeah.
Yes. I did follow the rules. I paid for service.
Yes, I did. I've got the ticket right
here. I paid for the train. I I paid for
the train. So I I I I I did follow the
rules cuz I paid for the train, you
know. So yeah,
stupid rules. A train's a [ __ ] train,
bro. The [ __ ] So I mean, yeah, I did.
And also another thing is what happened
before? And he was being a [ __ ] as
well because I remember before, yeah, my
rail card expired. I can't remember
exactly what happened. The rail card
expired and this G ticket inspector come
on. He said, "You can either pay the
£100 fine or just renew the rail card."
And I just renew the rail card. See,
that's what you call being. He said,
"You can either pay the pay a fine,
right? Or you can just renew the rail
card." I was like, "Fuck it. I'll just
renew the rail card."
Makes more sense, doesn't it? So, he was
actually being fair, but he was just
being a [ __ ]
Yeah. Well, that's on them, isn't it?
That's on them.
That is on them, bro. Why isn't it
funny? Why do I have to get on a
complete different train?
Stop being a [ __ ] bro. That's not
even fair dodging. That's literally not
That's You know what I'm saying? You're
still paying to [ __ ] the service.
It's not even fair dodging.
You know what I mean? Jesus.
But yeah, he was a prick, man. He said
pay £23. Fucking£23 [ __ ] pound. What?
I could have just said, "Yeah, I'll pay
I could have just said, I'll pay the
fine and then just give him fake details in it."
I could have just said that.
I could have just said that I'll just
pay a fine and then just give him a fake
name like I did before, but I couldn't
be [ __ ] bro. Yeah, man.
They sometimes don't come on a train,
but they always come on a train. Um when
it's um when you go Manchester, they're
always on that [ __ ] train, mate.
When you go Manchester, to be honest, I
don't think I've ever had one going to Wales, though.
You know what I'm saying?
Um, well, if you had done that, then
they would let you do that.
Yes, I did get a return, but I I can't
remember ever being stopped in in Wales.
No, I don't think I ever have.
No, it was a valid ticket. It was an
anytime return. Listen, [ __ ] I got
a train. Yeah, with anytime return, but
because it wasn't a specific line on the
train that he was trying to say that, oh
yeah, you need to get off and and wait
for the other one. It was just a
different um company. Same train,
different company. It was an anytime
return. It was just a different [ __ ]
rail um railway line.
So, it wasn't No, it was an anytime
return. It was just a different [ __ ] line,
which is stupid cuz you're still paying
for a [ __ ] service, but it doesn't matter anyways.
No, when I went to Birmingham, there
weren't none on the train,
but it was coming back.
Yeah, but it doesn't matter, bro. But in
in Cardiff, I've never had it.
No, I've never had it in Cardiff.
Yeah, I used to have a rail card. I used
to follow all the rules, but I don't go
traveling anymore, so I don't have a
rail card. And he says, "Oh, can I see
your rail card?" I said, "I can't show
you." He says, "It's because you don't
have it in it." I said, "I do have it."
He says, "Yeah." I said, I said, "I
don't have it." But I don't do things by
the rules now cuz I don't go traveling anymore. So,
there's no reason for me to have a rail card.
But I said I had a rail card.
I just say that I've got a rail card cuz
you get discount. It's only £30 for the
year. But how many times I'm going to
use it in a year?
It's good the rail car though if you was
going back and forth somewhere and [ __ ]
Yeah, man. 30 for the year or 70 for 3 years. Yeah.
But yeah, I've never had it in Wales. I
don't think I've ever had it in Wales.
No, I've never had it in Wales.
He says, "Because you don't have it." Yeah.
Do Do you know what I want to get? I
want to get one of them Dyson fans, but
they're about 300 quid. Do you know them Dyson fans?
I want one of them Dyson fans.
Yeah, I want to get one of them Dyson's, man.
But it's pointless because um
it's going to be winter soon. Like £400
hopefully. Monty man. Monty man sorts
himself out soon. Yeah, man.
So, Joe, you think online roulette is rigged then?
Online roulette is rigged when you're
putting like 3040 pound on a number. Yeah, 100%.
Yeah, it is, bro. Yep.
I can't believe I won that football bet,
man. I wish I had like [ __ ] £300 on it.
That was good odds as well. 80 to 285.
That's actually good odds. If you look
up next week, 80 will get you about 230, 240.
So, they were actually really good odds as well.
Yeah, they were good odds them on the
football, bro. That was actually good
odds. Maybe because it was the start of the season.
But the thing is, I don't like
I said, man, the thing I hate about
gambling is it's not guaranteed. I need
guaranteed money, which is why I'm
trying to find a job, cuz I need guaranteed money.
I don't like something that's not
guaranteed, you know, not guaranteed
you're going to win a [ __ ] football bet, lad.
So, I need something that's guaranteed, you know.
I probably won't win a football now for a while.
Yeah, cash it out. Coal.
Then I put the 235 in my bank,
which will pay for some bills and [ __ ] So,
I have two bank accounts. So, yeah.
But I actually done really good this
month considering I'm not getting that
income anymore. went out, pissed it up, you know, [ __ ]
I think I done good this month, you
know. Bought nice after shave, went out
a couple of times, left London. I think
I done good with, you know, considering
I don't get all that money anymore. I
think I'd managed quite well.
Like I said, I went out a couple of
times as well drinking. So, I think I'm
done pretty good to be honest,
considering I don't get [ __ ] three
grand a month anymore.
Yeah, delivery jobs. Well, I'm trying
for some delivery jobs, but they still
not got back in touch with me.
So, I have nothing for now, you know, to do.
I need deliver to hire me, bro. I'll
make 150 a day on that. Easy. [ __ ] man.
There's realistically only two ways
you're going to get money. Yeah.
You either gamble and try and win, and
that's a risk, or you you just have to
save your benefits and live off like £80 a week.
Like if you was actually really trying
to go somewhere, bro. Like that's the
only thing you could do, live off like
£80 a week. Oh, you could gamble, but
obviously that's a risk. That's the only
thing. Can barely even get any job
anymore, bro. I [ __ ] apply for like
three or four. I'm still waiting, bro.
I'm waiting for delivery three years later.
Nah, even they're hard to get them
cleaning jobs. And I wouldn't do that. I
I want to do the delivery thing.
So 3 years I even signed up with a different address.
So I have nothing but football bets and
waiting now really. So
it's mad how there's not really a way to
get money nowadays. Is it strange?
How much do electricians get a week?
How much do they get a week? Electricians.
No, it's not going to make a difference.
You [ __ ] idiot. I made a new account
using her address. It doesn't make a
difference. And it doesn't work cuz you
need to verify who you are. every time
you um My sister's boyfriend's an
electrician, but he doesn't seem to have
loads and loads and loads of money.
They don't seem to have loads and loads
of money for the job that he has,
which is strange.
He's electrician, but he doesn't seem to
he doesn't seem to have loads and loads
and loads of money.
But yeah, I can't use her account
because I've already made an account
using her address.
Um, using her address. I made a new
application using her address and
they're still saying they've got too many drivers.
So, the last resort
must be I have to maybe
use an address in like Wales or something.
And if they're still saying they've got
too many drivers, [ __ ] off. Simple.
It's not as easy as that, bro.
I'm on a waiting list. It's been 3
years. That delivery you will make money
with as well. I mean, you can rent
accounts, but it's a risk, you know,
cuz what if they don't give you your money?
So, if they don't give you your money,
then you're [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying?
>> You can work 10 hours for one day and
they don't give you your money. So, um
yeah, look, I'm I'm getting these women
still message me from Birmingham, bro.
The messages are not dead.
You don't get this in London, bro. You
really don't get this in London.
It's actually nice, you know.
But if I can get that delivery, bro, you
can make 150 in a day.
You could probably make a grand in a week.
Cuz I remember when I done it in
Stratford, I made £40 in a few hours.
And that was that was in Statford. That
wasn't even central London. That was C
that was Stratford. If that was central
London, you could easily make a lot of
money, bro, in there, you know. Yeah. Second, bro.
Yeah, at least they're replying it.
I need that deliver account, mate.
I need that [ __ ] deliver account.
You be laughing.
I've been thinking sometime to put 500
pound, you know,
or like for both teams to score, but I
don't think I could want I don't think
I'd want to lose 500 pound like that, bro.
It would be horrible, would it?
No. I think the most I'd put on a
football bet is maybe 100. The maximum
I think the maximum I put on it is about 120,
but I don't like the teams for this
week. So, I'm going to wait next week.
I was tempted to put that 285 on two teams.
Nah, I can't do that, bro. I'm not
losing 500. [ __ ] that.
Jesus. Could you imagine? Nah, [ __ ] that, bro.
No. [ __ ] that.
Could you imagine?
Imagine I had £500 on that 75 to1 that
come in years ago. Nicolola,
I'd be retired at [ __ ] 27.
that I'd be good for a couple of years, wouldn't I?
That pound better bet I done with 16s
when I was 19 and it come in. Imagine I
had £500 on that. Jesus,
I'd be retired, bro, for a couple of
years at least.
Couple of years, three years, two years, three years.
Yeah, probably, bro.
Yeah, I'd be good for I'd be set for a
couple of years, would it?
Yeah, but you're not going to put 10
grand on a football bet, are you?
I can't believe it coming when I only
had a [ __ ] quid on it, bro. I never
thought he was ever going to win six
teams, man. What the [ __ ]
Yeah, but if you had £500 on it,
you would be set for a couple of years, isn't it? Yeah. Mhm.
Why Nicola? Why did you say virgin boy
calls me skint?
Is it because he's skint himself? Yeah,
he's skinnier than a fing skin.£500.
Both teams and score would return about. Yeah.
So, you'd be set for maybe two years. Yeah, man.
Yeah. But you're not going to obviously
put [ __ ] What would they pay you in
cash if you won that much, Nikolai? What
will they pay you in cash?
They pay you in cash in it.
No, they wouldn't pay you in cash. How
would they pay you? Would they pay you?
Yeah, but how easy would it be to get the money?
Um well um actually there's a reason why
I didn't get um a hotel and an escort.
Because I brought the wrong card with
me, you [ __ ] No, I had to get my
sister to send me money on the car that
I brought with me cuz I brought the
wrong card. You spacker.
So, mate, skin. If I was skint, I
wouldn't have even been able to went to
Birmingham and spent [ __ ] 150. Well,
I spent £200 cuz I had some on my
account. Yeah, that's how skint I am. Yeah.
And why would I get a hotel if I was
staying at Monty's?
Why the [ __ ] would I get a hotel, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
Why would I get a
Yeah, but how Yeah, but how easy do you
reckon it' be for them to actually
actually pay you, bro? Um, save money.
But no, I brought my wrong card. I
brought the wrong card. I've got so one
card expired. I bought two cards with
me. I had one I had like £50 in one
account and then I had the rest of my
money on the other account.
But the other account was the wrong
card. So I had to tell my sister to send
me money. I'll give it back to you when
I get home. So
you people go on about skin so much cuz
you skint yourselves. You're obsessed
with money. It's madness. Like you sit
on YouTube all day. Yeah. Calling other
people what you are. It's a sad life.
When are you going to grow up? When are
you actually going to [ __ ] grow up, man?
It's like what Monty man says, even
though he words it in a [ __ ] way.
Money comes and goes, you know,
and like you have if you have enough
money to do [ __ ] Why do you people keep
going on about money when you're the
ones that are sat on YouTube every
single day? It's so autistic.
That's what makes me think that these
people are autistic, bro. Cuz all they
do is go on about money. It's weird.
But Money's right. Even though he he he
words it in the wrong way.
So what? So so
yeah, you have to prove your source
source of wealth. Yeah. So what if you like
why is the light not working? Oh, what
if um So what if you don't prove your
source of wealth,
Nicolo? Then what happens? What? Like
what if I mean like what if your source
of wealth is low? They won't pay you
then, I'm guessing.
I'm guessing then what? They wouldn't
pay you. Say he was on benefits or
something like he was getting I don't
know. What? They just wouldn't pay you.
I'm guessing. No.
I read about that thing that happened in
William Hill where it took the guy like
three weeks to get his money. Yeah, man.
So, what's the most they will pay you in
cast you reckon? Like 10k. What if you
want like 10k? Then what?
Maybe they pay you 10k and capture that.
Yeah, this guy on YouTube, Nicolo, said
he was getting £40,000 a month at one
point. You believe that? 40k a month on
YouTube. Imagine, bro.
Do you believe do you believe that
[ __ ] 40k a [ __ ] month? What the
He said he used to get 40 grand a month from YouTube.
They're like a million subscribers.
That's a lot of wa matey.
40k a [ __ ] n.
And he has no savings as well.
But he has no savings, which is mad cuz
I was only on three grand a month and
I've got somewhat savings.
But the thing is, when you're getting
that kind of money, you're living your
life and you don't [ __ ] know when
it's going to end, you know? So, they
think that the money's never going to end. Yeah, man. KSI Kel Freezy.
Yeah, man. I don't know how YouTube can
afford to pay that much. Have you ever
wondered how YouTube
affords to pay like how they can pay
millions? How the [ __ ] does YouTube even
afford to pay people millions?
It's mad, isn't it?
How the [ __ ] does an app want to pay
people millions like different channels?
That's crazy, isn't it? Yep.
Well, obviously I'm more mature cuz he's
got disabilities. Obviously,
I'm not mature, bro. I'm not [ __ ]
mature at all. I laugh at any I laugh at everything.
KSI can be as rich as he wants, but
guess what? He's [ __ ] ugly. And
there's no amount of money that's going
to change the fact that he's an ugly bastard.
You have to admit he is an ugly bastard.
You know how you get like some black
people that look decent or some mixed race people?
He is [ __ ] stinking, son.
He's an ugly bastard. Doesn't matter if
he's black. It's not that he's black.
He's just ugly.
He is actually ugly, bro.
You like the side men in it, Nicolo?
No, I used to watch the side men, but no,
I can't stand some of them, bro.
I like channels like with three, four,
like thousand subscribers.
I like the smaller channels. They seem
more genuine. You know what I mean,
Grezy? Like the smaller channels
like I don't know. They seem more
I don't know, man.
They seem like they've got more of a
point to prove cuz they they they all
start off like that and then they become
famous and then then they just become [ __ ] Like
but that Charlie Vel is getting big. He
never used to be big.
He never used to be big.
big as in like um yeah, I watch Billy
Mo. I watch um I don't watch that
Charlie. I know who he is. I watch
Wendle. They're smaller channels.
They're all they're they're they're
smaller channels, but they're more genuine. So,
I like people you could actually type to
and they could actually see your
comment. Else it's just pointless.
I tried making money from YouTube for
years, but they were asking for [ __ ] crazy um
to become eligible, bro. They were
asking for like 10 million public short
views, and I think I only had about
can't remember. They were asking someone
ridiculous. I think I had about 10K or something.
And they were asking
ridiculous like um um requirements is the word.
Yeah, that Charlie was always like, "Oh,
I tell you why Manchester is cooler than
London." It's not cooler than London.
London's the best. It's just the people
in London are [ __ ] That's the only
thing that that lets London down.
But London's London's the best in terms
of a city. It's the best in the whole of England
cuz there's so much to do. you know,
it's got its pros, but
no, I don't like that. Um, Ed Matthews,
he's a [ __ ]
No, I don't like him. He's a [ __ ]
bro. If he ever came trying to troll me,
I'd slap him in front of his camera. I
hate that guy, bro.
He's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
No, I don't like him, bro. He's a [ __ ] proper [ __ ]
Did you ever watch Jack, mate?
Again, these are smaller channels. You
might have not ever heard of him, but he
used to call out YouTubers. It was quite funny.
Yeah, you might have not heard of him.
Again, like I said, he's a smaller one.
No, I used to like some of these videos
on um that Alfie Days. Again, you might
not know who Alfie, you should know who
Alfie Days is. Everyone knows Alfie Days.
So, his boyfriend,
you must know him. I'm sure you've heard of him.
and he used to do videos on him.
Um, do you remember? Yeah.
Yeah. I've got I mean, I've got another
channel. I'm trying to build it, but I'm
trying to build it.
Yeah, I hate that Ed Matthews though,
bro. I hate that guy. I'd slap him, bro,
if he ever come trying to take the piss.
Stop talking about yourself. Yeah, man.
Who else do I like?
I used to like that Simon Wilson, but I
think some of these videos are fake.
There's no way you can do them no money
challenges, bro. And you got like help from subscribers.
So, I don't believe I don't I don't
trust all of his videos, you know.
But if you ever watched him or
I used to be good at editing videos and stuff.
See, I like Hyperlinks. When I used to
um do gambling, I used to watch
Hyperlinks cuz he seemed to be the only genuine one.
Um you know, hyperlinks. But at the same
time, I know that he uses real money,
but what I don't understand is how he
used to hit these numbers with 40,50 on
it. Like, trust me, man. I've gambled a
lot of money online and I've never hit
numbers like that. And I'm thinking, how
the [ __ ] is this guy putting 40, 50, 60
on numbers and hitting cuz I have
gambled a lot of money online and I've
done some 300 spins [ __ ] and I've
never hit that way.
But it's it's I don't understand how he
does it. It doesn't make sense, bro.
So, when I used to watch gambling
videos, he's the only one I could. And
Rock and Roller used to be okay again
when he was a smaller channel, but like
me and Grey was saying, when they get
too big, it goes to their head.
So, and then they just become [ __ ]
I What do you What channels do you
watch, Greavves? I just watch these
police ones in America really where they
stop the people. That's all I really
watch on YouTube nowadays. Just body cam videos. Franklin,
what are you doing? And yeah,
it's all I really watch and travel
[ __ ] videos. But yeah,
what about you, son?
Oh, I can't stand that [ __ ]
Oh, [ __ ] bro. Not that Jack Jones. Yeah. M.
Oh, not that [ __ ] bro.
Oh, I [ __ ] hate him. I hate him. His
videos are staged. What's the point of staged videos?
No, I can't stand that [ __ ] He's been
going for years in, bro.
And the videos are so staged.
They're so [ __ ] staged these videos
as well. If they were actually real, I
could give him some credit, you know?
Okay, he puts himself in some mad
situations, but they're all fake.
You do realize these videos are fake, right?
I used to like that Aaron Crash scale. I
tell you, there was one that made me
laugh, right? When he was singing on the
train and everyone just looks at him
like where he listens to the earphones,
then he sings along and everyone just
looks at him. It to be honest, it did
make me laugh to be honest, bro. That
was funny as [ __ ]
Yeah, he made me laugh. I was dead.
Yeah. like he listens to some of it and
then he says the red the other half like
just shouted and everyone just looks at him
but there are some good people on YouTube. Yeah, man.
You know that Sorella when she was scamming people
Yeah, that's so
scamming people with the calendar. Yep.
I'm sure she was all right at one point
as well, but yeah. Yeah, man. Yeah.
Who else is there? Yep.
That's what you get when you [ __ ] around in Asia.
Have you seen the [ __ ] prisons in
[ __ ] Norway? They look better than
[ __ ] houses, mate. I wouldn't mind
going prison in [ __ ] Norway.
Have you seen the prisons in Norway,
bro? They don't even look like prisons.
They look like normal houses, bro. Like
a normal like accommodation.
Have we seen them in Norway? They're [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. I hate that Jack Jones. Yeah, I
can't stand that [ __ ] bro. [ __ ] he's annoying, bro.
Grezy likes him.
There was this cold approach that he
used to be called Johnny Barber. Don't
know if you ever heard of a Nicolo, but
he killed himself.
You remember when I met that John off
YouTube? Me and him, we used to like watch him.
I used to watch the Hodge Twins. Do you
know the Hodge Twins?
Yeah. Tickle wiggle wiggle.
Do you remember that guy Barber? Maybe.
Maybe you don't know, but he killed himself. Anyways,
he was a dating coach, trolling.
Nah, bro. I tell you, I can't stand that
chunks. Oh, I hate that [ __ ] bro.
Oh, he's so fat and [ __ ] annoying,
bro. Do you know who he is?
He's not even funny, bro.
You remember the hod swims?
You might not know them. Yeah. I can't
stand that chunks, bro. God, he's
[ __ ] annoying, bro.
I used to watch like Ali Law and stuff,
but he doesn't do YouTube anymore. Ali law.
He got a girlfriend and he had a kid.
All because he's a big YouTuber. Just
like what Ant-Man was saying.
Yeah. Ali law, bro. He's ginger, but he
doesn't do YouTube anymore.
He's got like 60 convictions when he
used to get caught with [ __ ] caught
with the police and [ __ ] But yeah, man.
If you're a big YouTuber, like you got
millions of followers, then you can you
can get a girlfriend. But if not, you're
going to struggle in this country.
It's all about followers nowadays.
Greasy and status.
Yeah, I don't like that chunks, bro.
He's [ __ ] annoying, man.
But we shouldn't hate on you shouldn't
hate black people, man. You shouldn't
hate African people, man. Don't forget,
Acon's African and Acon's a [ __ ]
legend, man. I like Acon, man. I think
if he actually come back, I'd actually
go to one of his concert. I'd actually
go to one of his concerts.
I like Acon, man. He's like proper like
I think I would actually go, bro. I'm
not even joking. I don't think I've ever
been to a concert, but I would go to see
Acon definitely if you come here.
And he's African. He's got like [ __ ]
seven words to his [ __ ] name.
Yeah, Acon was good, man.
You remember AON Nicolola?
Bless you then.
You know Aon, don't you agree?
I said to my mom, "Yeah, do you reckon
Taylor Swift would get with me?" And she
said, "You could try." I said, "I want
to get with Taylor Swift. I want her money.
I want her money." Hey, she says you can
try, but I don't think Taylor Swift will
get with me.
I could have some of her billions.
Oh, mate. You'd be [ __ ] laughing, ain't it?
That'll make YouTube [ __ ] jealous,
would it, Grezy?
Yeah, I think you like her as well,
don't you? Like Taylor Swift, Grezy,
Maybe I'll message her on Instagram. see
if she'll meet up with me.
>> Yeah. Good luck with that, bro. Nah, mate.
Oh, Franklin's gone back in the car.
Why don't we make a cartoon, Grezy? If
you want to make loads of money,
if you um if you want to make money,
bro, we should maybe make a cartoon. You
know how like Matt Groon made the Simpsons,
cuz I think we've got quite good personalities.
So, I think maybe we could make a
cartoon, me and you. Obviously, it might
take a couple of years and that, but I
think we could make a cartoon.
What do you think? Like we can make it
like [ __ ] Spongebob or something?
Yeah, we can make something like the
Simpsons and Spongebob.
We'd be [ __ ] rich, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. Oh, [ __ ]
Oh, bless you. if you wanted to get in a
little relationship with Erden Grezy.
Bless you if you fancy Taylor Swift.
Yeah, I used to like that Ariana Grande,
but then I realized she has literally no
body. No ass, no boobs. She looks [ __ ] ill.
I used to like her, but I don't like her body.
It's a bit [ __ ] isn't it?
Like it's really bad. Like she looks ill, bro.
>> Yeah, I used to love South Park.
We were talking in terms of thing that's
that's the most populous. Yeah. I used
to watch South Park 9:00 Comedy Central. Yeah.
It was good, bro.
This guy in America is getting the same
excuses that I get in London. Oh, I'm
talking to someone. Bro, you know this
[ __ ] Yeah, these approaching videos,
they actually they are actually starting
to look like NPCs.
Like, I'm not saying about what they're
saying and that. If you look at some of
these women, right? Yeah. And you see
the ones that he's approaching, they
actually look like robots. Some of them
look like they're being programmed.
Like their eyes just seem I can't I
can't explain it, bro. Like they
actually look like they're being they're being controlled. Obviously NPCs.
Can't explain it, bro. I can't explain it.
It's like if you look in their eyes,
right, they look like they've got the same attitude.
Ant-Man says it will never change. Never
change. He said they all look like
they're literally all It's like they're
programmed by Tik Tok.
I'm not even I'm not even joking, bro. I
was watching these earlier. Yeah.
And they look so
I can't explain it, bro. Like you can't
It's like they look so brainwashed
by It's like they've Tik Tok brains.
It's like Tik Tok is inside of their bodies.
That's why they don't know how to
communicate and socialize cuz of Tik Tok and Instagram.
They're literally non-playing characters.
That's They're literally all non-playing characters, bro.
They just have that look in it. I can't
explain it, bro. I can't explain it.
They just look like robots.
And man said it will never change.
Nicolo Monty Man said to me, "How is it
going to change?
Yeah. Monty man said, "How is it going
to change? It will never change."
Yeah, I have a boyfriend. I got in
Birmingham as well.
I got it in Birmingham as well, bro.
But at least with the numbers you get in
Birmingham, at least they replied and
one might actually meet you.
Well, at least they actually replied.
It wouldn't be too bad if you got if you
had to deal with [ __ ] but then
you'd actually get numbers that would
reply and meet you.
Then it's not bad, is it really?
No, I don't want any of Natalie G's friends.
But listen, how do they No, but all
jokes aside though,
um, Nicolo, how is it going to change?
It's like what what Ant-Man said, it
will never change.
That's not even a real Monty, man.
They're all NPCs.
It will never change. He says, "I'm
surprised of all people you think one
day it's going to change. How's it going to change?"
I do you know this woman? Yeah. She
approached this man. She said, "I want
to do rejection therapy and she looks
decent." Yeah. She approached this man
and do you know what he said? He said,
um, he said, um, to be honest with you,
you're not really my type. I said, my
guy, now they know how it feels, eh?
Yes. She was being serious. She
approached him and she's like, um, to be
honest with you, you're not really my
type. And and there was nothing wrong
with the way she looked either. She was
actually good-looking. He says,
"Unfortunately, you're not really my
type." I was like, "Get in there, son.
Give them [ __ ] a [ __ ] taste of their own medicine."
You know, now they know what it feels
like. Get up there, son. You know,
they [ __ ] reject us.
One second. Is that really Monty?
Yeah. I'm glad he rejected her. Good. Yeah,
>> that's a real money.
>> Yeah, my ears were burning.
>> Yeah, my ears were burning. They were
talking about me.
>> I said my ears were burning. I said my >> Oh,
>> meaning someone talking about me. Yeah,
we was calling you a bit of a [ __ ]
>> You could. No, you said you were saying
something about No, we're watching. Yo,
we're watching. You said multi said
something about [ __ ] what?
>> These people never change.
>> How you say,
>> how you say people how you say these
people obsessed with money because money
comes and goes. It's true though, is it?
What? Yeah. What you said is true, isn't it?
>> Money comes and goes. Yeah,
>> we just talk about money on here all the
time. Of course, money comes and it goes.
But you never rarely see these rarely
out the house. So these are stupid [ __ ] bastards.
>> No, but I can't say that. I can't say
that because someone actually sent me 25 quid today.
>> I I I spent a lot more than£25 on you
yesterday on Saturday, mate.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I know. I know. Today.
>> When I was up on your panel today when
you were just saying that Yeah. That was
skin though. Someone sent me 25 quid.
>> What did you buy with it?
>> I've still got it. >> Yeah,
>> still got it. Yeah, still got it.
Whoever sent it that Thank you. Didn't
really have to like But yeah,
>> the breakfast we got was good though, is it? Yeah.
>> Yeah. Well,
>> that was actually quite nice, bro.
>> Yeah, way were nice. It went nice with a
gorgeous breakfast. I wish they had that
in London, but I've never seen it. Never.
>> What was it called?
>> It was something in Canada.
>> Canada? Yeah. Where was it? >> Yeah.
>> Google it. See if this anywhere near
you. Canada [ __ ] food shop.
>> Yeah, but I need to know the name of it.
>> I didn't know you ate pork, Monty. I
thought you would have ate pork. >> What?
>> I was surprised when you ate pork, to be honest. Did you?
>> I thought you would eat pork.
>> I thought you wasn't into pork, mush pork.
>> Yeah, but
you don't eat a lot though, do you?
>> What you doing on YouTube anyways? You
need to get off your pier.
>> I'm just talking to Greby, my little
friend. Won't he?
>> Why don't you give Grimsby your [ __ ]
Facebook and talk to him on Facebook?
>> He's got Grimsy. Make a new Instagram.
>> On Instagram or something. Talk to him
on Instagram, not YouTube.
>> You don't like YouTube, do you?
>> It's [ __ ] your life up, lad. It is.
The This place is not worth it. It's not
>> How is it [ __ ] my life?
>> Is it?
>> It's [ __ ] my life up. It's not like
Yeah. With Natalie. Yeah. I've done call
to her. I didn't even cheat on her.
Yeah. They mentioned how we was in the
hotel but we was at Manchester. Didn't do Yeah.
I just get off YouTube. YouTube pop my relationship up.
>> I just Yeah. Yeah.
>> Know what I mean? I would I won't I
won't just sit here and just stay with
these little clowns. I wouldn't see I
never even done anything to nothing. I
even cheated on
Has it ruined mine? Like it's ruined my
life as well though, is it Nicolola?
>> Yeah, I see. It has ruined your life. It's ruined,
you know. I wouldn't sit here with the
people who's ruined your life or tried
to ruin your life.
Entertain the people who you want to
entertain, but I wouldn't entertain the
people on here.
>> Would you say my Would you Would you say
it's ruined my life, Grezy and Nicolo?
Is it really? Um,
it has, but not as bad as you, I don't
think. Is it? Of course.
>> PJ, we both had the same [ __ ] done to
each other. You've had sent there as I
have. We've had the same [ __ ] sent to
We've had the same [ __ ] done.
>> I know that. No. Yeah, but the posters
are not the issue now though. That's
what I'm saying. With your issue, it's
the whole Natalie G thing. The whole the
whole K thing and the whole the kids
[ __ ] You know what I mean?
>> To be honest with you. To be honest with
you, it's not to be honest with you.
He's not even Kayie. He's not Kayie.
Kay's just a clean gun who keeps
hollering me around whatever chat room
I'm in. That's it. I've got nothing to do with
>> my family.
>> Nicolo has it ruined my life. Let let
Nicolo answer it.
>> But he already said, "Yeah, let him answer."
Well, it made me Well, I wasn't
homeless, but I was sleeping on the
stairs for like two nights
and a dog. Yeah, there you go. I lost
the dog. I lost everything on YouTube.
Do you know what I mean?
>> I've lost
So's PJ. PJ's lost his dog.
>> Yeah, YouTube.
>> Yeah, you let your dog out for him.
[ __ ] ran off. Yeah. Answer
me, Nicol. I ask you a question,
Nikolai. Not your mic.
>> Nicolo, do you think that YouTube has
put PJ's Live up?
>> It caused me inconveniences. Monty killed.
Monty killed him.
>> Monty, let me Monty, let me ask you.
Monty, listen, bro. Yeah. This is what
we mean with you. Yeah. When you come on
YouTube, this is what I was saying to
you earlier, bro. Yeah. You come on like
with Kaye with a dog in a house. Yeah.
Now you're by yourself. >> So,
you got like, how do I explain it? Long time.
>> But this is what I've actually been
thinking. This is [ __ ] just think
about it. Yeah. Log logically. Think
about it. Yeah. This is [ __ ] up. Now,
um Natalie's left the house. Yeah. Now
I'm living in Natalie's house. Natalie's
off YouTube now. I'm in a YouTuber's house.
>> That's [ __ ] up.
>> What do you mean?
>> I'm Don't worry. Don't worry. You're not seeing it. >> Okay.
But multi is
still here. Exactly. Exactly. We still
leave with a smile on my face. Exactly.
>> I wouldn't be smiling if I was you though, bro.
>> I am smiling now. I'm off. I'm done with
it now. I'm done. I'm done playing these
old mind games with women, mate. They
[ __ ] mind gamers. You tell them you
tell them you haven't done [ __ ] all
wrong and you just play games.
>> It's not.
Stop saying bless you for [ __ ] sake.
If a woman loves you. Yeah.
If a woman right if a woman gets with you. Yeah.
>> And a woman and a woman finishes you. Yeah.
>> So what what was the point of that woman
even getting with you knowing that she's
going to finish you with you and not get
back with you?
>> What's the point?
>> You want my opinion?
They all [ __ ] [ __ ] I'm saying it.
>> They're all [ __ ]
You remember it? The old [ __ ] Is that right?
Yeah. But me and we're friends now. Is it? Yeah.
Are we? Are we? >> Huh?
>> Yeah. I'm on you, mate. You're all
right. You're not bad. Not bad enough. Mhm.
You need to stop the aggression when you hit again.
>> Yeah, you need to get off YouTube. You
>> need to stop the aggression, mate. It
was very painful.
What I was saying? Yeah.
Cuz when I come on YouTube, I have nothing. I find
by the time like when I start on YouTube
now then until now I I've lost nothing.
I've been linked a few times. Yeah. To
sleep in the stairs twice.
Um but I have no long-term damage.
That's what I'm trying to say.
And when I got picked out my moms, I was
already having problems with like the
neighbors and [ __ ] with the gambling and
that I got longterm
effects. Does that make sense?
Whereas YouTube actually [ __ ] bro.
You need to get off YouTube, bro.
I'm making myself some super noodles. I
love super noodles.
Because when my mom kicked me cuz when
my mom kicked me out, I went back to the
rooms, the house that I was renting.
Obviously, I couldn't stay in the room
because of um I couldn't stay in the
room because of um they were all rented
out. I had to stay on the stairs and
then one of the guys let me sleep in the
room with him like on the floor.
So, I had to sleep on the stairs in the
house and it was horrible, bro. Almost
froze to almost froze to death. Yeah,
it was [ __ ] up, man. Almost. I
actually almost froze to death, bro. It's [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Do you want to see the TV I got
now? I' see what it was like.
>> Yeah. Go on.
TV. I know. But I'm not asking someone.
>> It even got a to it. It doesn't even
have a TV a
new ones. You don't need an
>> No, you don't. Yeah, you got you don't
need the for >> No,
that's Natalie's TV. It's light as a feather.
>> Natalie wants it. Can come and get it.
I'm not bothered.
>> Let me see it. Let me see it.
>> It's not bad.
>> It's not. She gets all that as well.
She gets all them.
>> Yeah. Smart TV. Yeah. You don't need an
air nowadays. But
>> it's it's Natalie. I got it. If you
don't want it, you don't want it. You
know, it's the same as this chair. I've
got I've ordered that as well. That' be
coming soon as well this year. >> Yeah.
>> [ __ ] hell.
I'm not getting played by anymore.
Anyways, I get out of here [ __ ] and I'm
done. I'm done with it. I can't be asked. >> Yeah.
>> That was cute. It was cute. Me and you
having a bagel together. It was quite
cute, isn't it? >> What?
>> Me and you having a not a a bagel, an
omelette together. It was cute, isn't it?
>> Oh, it was all right.
>> No, it was cute. It was a lovely sight
having some piggy omelets.
>> Piggy omelets. Bro, I still don't know
how that I don't know how we done that
drinking with an empty stomach. I still
don't know how we done it, bro.
>> We done it, didn't we?
>> Yeah, I was mad. That was [ __ ]
>> We weren't even
surprised you wasn't sick. You did eat
in 5 days. Yeah. And you went on the And
it was r It weren't like you was just
drinking beer. We was drinking
everything, could it?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And I didn't eat for 5 days.
>> That's mad.
>> My body was gone. I I had no [ __ ]
food in my belly. I just had water. I
just had energy drinks inside of me.
Piece of [ __ ]
>> I was living on [ __ ] pieces of [ __ ]
for five to six days. >> Yeah,
>> I w I eating [ __ ] all nothing at all.
>> I was even sleeping, man.
>> I couldn't even have a wank. I couldn't
even have a [ __ ] wank. That's
she made the wrong choice anyway. She's
[ __ ] up anyway. She made the wrong
choice. I've done nothing for her,
peeps. I'm telling you now. I'm going to
show up about her anyways, but I'm going
to say this. I've not done [ __ ] off to her. Nothing.
But [ __ ] it.
I don't want a woman in one. You know
what I mean?
Yeah, it's hard going off.
>> Listen, this is what I said to these
people. Yeah, I'm going to prove how
these people have got no life. I said
today, yeah, after tomorrow, after
today, I'm not going to be on YouTube
until next Tuesday. I'll come back on
Look what's been histen.
Unless they're still on YouTube every If
they've been on YouTube every day in
that week, then they're the ones that
ain't got a life, is it? >> Yeah.
It's a good idea, is it?
>> Yeah. Yeah. One minute. One minute. One
minute. You You people think that they
listen the funny thing about me. Yeah.
If a woman [ __ ] choks me away. Yeah.
The funny thing about me, peeps, PJ will
even tell you.
I I show you, peeps, I show you. I show
you. I just show you.
We went for a kiss up, didn't we?
>> What do you think about that bird that
sent you? The picture of that bird who
I'm talking to.
>> He's nice.
>> Yeah, nice. >> What?
>> He's well nice.
>> Yeah. Can you Can you put the piece up a
small voice? I can't [ __ ] stick.
>> Yeah. sticking the piece off her
>> offer. Yeah, the woman who I'm talking to
the one who got my phone number
see me on quit me. I'm a quick mover on
I don't stay around for too long, mate.
Woman [ __ ] me up
like get off YouTube for a week and see
if they're still on there every day in it. >> What
>> is that? That's how I do that. Monty,
get off your YouTube or we can come
back. See who's still on there.
>> There she is. That's the bird I'm talking to.
>> Did you see what I sent you earlier in the chat?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> What was it?
>> That's who I'm talking to.
>> Yeah. What was the chat?
>> What about Yeah, she sent me some
[ __ ] proper badass pictures last night.
What was the chat though? Like what was
the chat like?
>> Uh what chat
>> I showed you earlier? The screenshot.
The YouTube one.
>> Oh, I don't I don't look out there yet.
I just look at it for a second and [ __ ] off. >> Why?
>> Why don't you ever see I get the
picture? Get rid of the patient. Please
take it off now. Take it. Take it off.
Yes. Get off.
>> One second, mate. One second, mate.
>> What I'm saying is, yeah, is that a good
idea? Me to come off YouTube for a week
and then go back and see every day if
they've been on there.
>> Yeah, I'm waiting until she text me. I
met her last night, me outside last night.
>> Seriously, Monty, is it a good idea
though or not?
>> What? I'm going to come off of YouTube
tomorrow for a week and when I come back,
>> trust me, if I knew Natalie was going to
be likely scared, if I knew Natalie were
going to get me into Birmingham and [ __ ]
me off, I wouldn't move to Birmingham.
Do you know what I mean? I wouldn't have
done it. But to be honest with you, I'm
[ __ ] pulling left, right, and center
up here. See, I'm pulling left, right,
and center. No [ __ ] Left, right,
center. I'm pulling birds.
>> What is it? Why is it a good idea what I
told you then?
>> [ __ ] community PJ some good people in here
listen listen what I'm saying is yeah
I'm going to come off of YouTube
tomorrow Tuesday until next Tuesday
right and I'm going to look what's been
happening in that week and if they're
still on YouTube then they're the ones
that are skid then it it has to be in it for me.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
I show my dick to me, man. I show my
dick to her. Just dropped to the floor
last night. Money think money. Do you
not think it's been mad how in six years
it's been the same [ __ ] Really? It's
>> Yeah. I'm done with them anyway. They [ __ ]
put you down. Yeah, they put you down
because you're bettering them and they
know you probably can get more birds in
there. I put you down and call you
whatever you look at me. Look at me.
Jay was my ex. Now she's my ex X.
Natalie my ex. Now I'm with Now I'm with
another woman basically. I supposed to
be going to her house tonight. I'm
waiting for the taxes. That's I'm all dressed up.
>> That's how I got my jeans back on.
>> I supposed to be going home tonight, meeting her. >> Nice.
So, we're just waiting for text me to
>> I was just waiting for me, man.
>> PJ gets nothing and multi gets what? Birds.
Multi gets the birds. Hey, I get the
The birds birds. I do, don't I? I [ __ ] do.
No, they are not going to be honest with
you. I'm [ __ ]
winding up Natalie.
They're well nice.
I think I think Natalie got some of
them. Not too sure. They're nice. I like them. Yeah.
Yeah, I like them. I don't like pot noodles.
I prefer um you trying to come in.
Someone trying to come in with your
[ __ ] dog picture. What a weirdo, man.
>> Yeah, they are weirdos. It don't bother
me anyways. It bothers them. It bothers me.
>> Look people. Diesel. Diesel. Diesel.
It's gone to a [ __ ] dog shelter,
boys. He's going to have the injection pot, boys.
So, it don't bother me. You can keep
mentioning diesel all you want, peeps.
>> Me, me and you. Me and you get on like a
house on fire. Do you know what that means?
>> House on fire. Yeah. That we get on.
>> Well, they were scared when we was in
Birmingham in it. Proper scared. >> Who?
>> What are them?
>> They're scared either way. Even when I'm
on my own, they still [ __ ] scared.
They watch people
now. They know where I live and [ __ ]
but not for long because I may back up.
>> I don't even think these people are
human. I don't think these people are
human. I think they're robots.
>> Cuz I'm moving back up north in two
days, three days. Me peas. I'm not going
to be here no more.
>> I've already run my place up and it's a
[ __ ] a room left so I can go there.
>> Don't go on Don't go on [ __ ] YouTube, man.
>> I'm not going on YouTube. Soon as I
leave this place and go back, I'm not
coming back on YouTube ever again.
>> It causes too much trouble, you know.
>> It does. It's [ __ ] bollocks. It's gay as [ __ ]
It's a weasel. It's a It's a community
for the weasels, isn't it?
>> It is. Don't listen. I'm happy. I'm
happy to meet any of these out of this
community. I swear they've been meeting
a rust enemy.
>> I [ __ ] 10 ft underground. MP
the best way to pull. Yeah. Tell you how >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. You don't go see I was watching
you. I'm first thing you did. You went
straight for the number. >> No.
>> Yeah. You had like a little conversation
and then went for the number.
>> Conversation like five like three five minutes.
>> Three. I for three five minutes and then
you ask for the number. You don't do
that at all. What you do Yeah. It's like your propag
you got nice you'll
I'll come back Saturday.
>> Yeah just
you got [ __ ] nice you [ __ ] hell. I
bet you got a nice
to come back Saturday. >> Huh?
>> Yeah. You want to come back? Yeah. Come
back if you want.
>> Will you come out?
>> Look at a girl. Yeah. And if you can see
her cleavage, don't look at eye contact. Eye contact.
>> One minute. One minute. That's another
thing. Why do you little [ __ ] email the house?
>> Oh, just drop it, PJ. Leave it. Leave
>> No. No. Cuz I wanted to move in with
you. What the [ __ ]
>> I'm not leaving it. It's bad. It's
[ __ ] bad that.
>> You know what I mean?
Yeah, they're [ __ ] cowards.
All these little clowns email them.
>> Yeah, I'm out of this house anyways
two days. Anyways,
>> so you think it's weird?
>> Yeah, email that.
>> Yeah, the weirdos, you know. Anyways,
>> you done it to me as well, not just you.
>> That's why I'm going.
I am being I kicked out now. I'm just
going anyways cuz there's nothing else
in here for me.
Know what I mean? That is [ __ ] put me
off for nothing.
>> Yeah, I ain't got no one. I ain't got no
one in Birmingham. Who have I got really?
>> You got Timmy?
>> [ __ ] Timmy.
[ __ ] Timmy. This bastic.
Is there a boss that goes city center from yours? Yeah.
Have you took it yet?
>> No, I I walk me PJ. You don't know that.
I walk everywhere. I don't jump buses if
you think I am.
>> That's That's a long
>> Do you think I'm a bus wanker or something?
>> That dream might come back. Monty. Yeah.
>> I hope she does come back. I hope she
does come back. I'm not cheating on her.
I'm just talking to people. Keeping my
hooks in open. That's what I'm doing. So
that's what I'm doing. I'm not cheating
on no one. I'm single. I'm a free man. I
can do what the [ __ ] I want to.
>> If he comes back and then I'm going to
tell her if he gets out, don't run off.
>> Don't [ __ ] run.
>> Talk. Don't shout. Talk. Because if
you're going to shout, that's going to
[ __ ] up the relationship. And then
that's it. You don't shout, you talk.
And um and if you have disagreements,
agree around people. Agree. When you get
home, disagree all you like, but when
you're around people, agree
>> with that Uber that you've been talking
to. I would look nice.
>> I don't know. I'm too in love with now,
mate. And I do love her a lot. You know,
>> she's well nice, Monty.
She's got a nice [ __ ] punani too,
mate. I sell you now. I can send you that.
Give it a w.
>> You want me to send you that pier? >> Nah.
>> Oh, you'd be having a one car for that. You
>> trust me, you would you um
I hate this community, man.
Multi new bird looks nice. What? Multi
new bird looks okay.
>> Why do these people are here stalk? It's weird.
>> I don't know. Let me [ __ ] text her
anyway. So you if you don't believe me
anyways that that I'm talking to. I assure you.
>> Why do these people stalk?
>> Cuz they do.
>> Yeah. You like it though?
>> Yeah, that's a tit. I catch you that. Hey peeps.
>> Oh, there you go peeps.
>> You're a nice cl you are. I'm a nice it
loving Natalie didn't last long.
I know we didn't last long. I know we
didn't. But you know what? Me and N did
make a perfect couple. We really [ __ ]
did. I'm not just saying that. We really
did make a perfect couple. James
couldn't handle couples and come into
arguments and disagreements.
>> Monty, people say that I'm more mature
than you. No, I'm not. I'm immature. I'm
quite immature. Is it?
>> I'm No. No. will tell you I'm a clever
bastard. I'm a very clever clever clever
>> But Monty, when I met you, Monty, when I
met you, I didn't laugh once, did I?
>> Yeah, we were laughing all night. You
[ __ ] Oh, now both of us were
screaming and laughing. Screaming and
>> Yeah, but I wasn't laughing at YouTube, was I? >> No,
I was just talking prop.
You find YouTube funny
PJ to be honest with you.
>> I don't know how I don't know how I do
it. I don't know how we get these women
straight after one and the other.
I haven't lining up. Please believe me.
I haven't lining up. You know, it's kind
of got 50 at the front door now waiting.
>> You love YouTube in it. >> What?
>> You love YouTube, is it?
when you to get
I don't want to pull anyone to be honest
with you. I'm happy with [ __ ]
Natalie, but if she's one of these woman
who [ __ ] off when it gets I can't be asked.
Boom. She's blocked me on everything,
man. I still can text her, but I'm not
texting her anymore. I'm not doing the
chasing anymore. Yeah.
>> You know what I mean?
>> And I don't know why [ __ ]
Lord J was asking how good I was in bed
and all that lot to Natalie who were
better than me. Yeah, that is weird.
Obviously [ __ ] me, man. Have you seen
the size of my [ __ ] knob? No
[ __ ] Have you seen the size of my dick?
>> That's not [ __ ] isn't it? That's not.
>> Yeah, it's quite small.
>> It is quite small. It is. It's [ __ ]
tiny, mate. Tiny Tim. Why do you think
that girls [ __ ] jumped on me? Y man.
Natalie was short anyways when she first
saw it. were [ __ ] furry shots because
she thought it was going to be small. PJ
cuz of Kay
said my dick small
I'm being jumped on GTA here.
>> You're getting jumped at you.
>> You know what that means?
>> Getting battered. >> Yeah,
there's free [ __ ] on me, mate.
>> What? What? What? Is he better than one?
Is he better? What do you mean?
>> Have you never paid you? Have you never
played GTA 5? Did you say? Yeah.
>> Yeah, of course you have.
>> It's good, isn't it?
>> I know every single glitch gener.
>> Did you play as soon as it um as soon as
it come out?
>> Yeah. PS3.
>> Yeah. Okay. What month did it come out then?
>> I was talking. I remember coming out near Christmas.
It was October, was it? Um
not too sure. It was years ago. Go to
>> You found USA is attractive, didn't you,
Grezy? You found her attractive.
>> Yeah. Monty, >> what?
>> Monty, you know when I told you I
messaged that girl's dad in America, you
did laugh at some of it, in it. >> No,
>> a little bit.
>> No, cuz you could get a bullet through your head.
>> Yeah. Why do you You don't find nothing
funny in it.
No, not really. I'm not a funny guy.
>> Yeah, but I thought that was quite funny.
>> I love making people laugh.
>> You remember the dad texting me back at the museum?
>> They're all at the at the table in
Thanksgiving talking about me at Thanksgiving.
Imagine the conversation here. Yeah, man.
I've pulled more birds than you, Steven Howard.
>> Yo, people people, the funny thing is
Yeah. This bird who I'm actually talking
to. Yeah. I did not called approach her.
She called approached me.
She come to me.
So give me a number.
>> Do you want to go? Do you want to go to
leads on Saturday? >> Leads? >> Yeah.
>> Should I get paid like in 15 days?
>> You want to go to leads or do you want
to go leads then?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Wait till I get paid then.
>> Well, you'll come to leads.
>> Yeah, we got leads. Yeah, we got leads.
>> We're going to pull in leads.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. We will do. We will
do. We're going to put the [ __ ] off.
He's using me now as a [ __ ] wingman.
I'm just clicking on here.
>> You You scared you scared you scare the
birds away with a shitty stick. Is it?
>> No. The birds come running when I when I'm out.
You like it in it?
>> Imagine you. Imagine you and Longlegs on the pool.
>> [ __ ] off. Never go out with him anywhere.
>> Imagine on the pool though, huh? That
would be funny, in it.
>> Yeah. No. No. [ __ ] off. I don't mate.
I kill him.
Timy's gone quiet.
I mean, I'm just bringing in quiet.
>> Yeah. Yeah. It's gone quiet.
>> This community is a [ __ ] community, isn't it?
Funny. This community is embarrassing,
isn't it? Every Oh, man. And and these
people on YouTube said they ruined my
life, man. They're helping me out peeps.
They're helping me out. I'm a PJ now.
I'm a [ __ ] PJ. >> Yeah,
>> I can go out and get as much as [ __ ]
remember to remember we was talking to
them 18y old girls body.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
We should have We should They should
have come back with us instead of giving
me Listen, 18 is too young for me, lad.
>> It's too young for me.
>> For [ __ ] sake, man.
I was only looking too young for me, lad.
>> Nah, it's legal, man. It's above legal, actually.
>> Yeah, obviously. Obviously, obviously I
can book her. Obviously, of course I
can. But to me, she's a teenager.
>> Did she ask how old she was?
>> She asked me how old I was. I said I was 31, 35. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Obviously, I'm going to tell the
truth how old I am. I'm not going to
[ __ ] sit there lie. I'm not being
paid or I'm 35.
You know what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> That's why I didn't [ __ ] do anything.
That's why I didn't talk [ __ ] on me or
nothing. Nothing. I just kept myself to
myself. I talked to her. That's as far
as it went.
>> No kiss. Nothing.
>> You like this YouTube? You like this
>> I don't like YouTube. No. [ __ ] You're [ __ ] angry.
>> You're addicted, aren't you? >> Addicted.
I'm not really addicted to it. I'm just
on here telling you what you're doing on
here. Like, you shouldn't even be on
>> Money. I just I you know why I come on
here? I just to see if it's the same
people on every day.
>> See this text me one sec.
>> I just want to see if it's the same
people every day. Monty, do you understand?
>> It is the same people every day.
>> Yeah, but forever
money. Look at that picture.
>> One sec.
Keep it up.
I can make you laugh at that picture.
>> Oh my days, please. Yeah. >> Huh?
>> How's that going to make me laugh?
>> Two siding in bed together.
>> How's it How's it be the fault?
>> Two penos lying together.
>> What the [ __ ] How?
Now look at them both coloring each
other coming each day.
>> Yeah. One's a
>> Oh, do you remember money? Do you
remember the voice over I showed you and
he was like, "Oh, oh, faster, faster."
That made you laugh, didn't it?
>> Yeah. It didn't make me laugh. No.
>> Oh, faster. Bungle faster. Do you
remember Grezy? Yeah.
>> I can't even read these comments. One
sec. One sec, please.
One say don't talk. Just say let me read
this comment. Won't say
what she's saying. Nothing. She I'm
supposed to be going to her house in a bit.
She said I can go to her house. She liv.
>> Yeah. Go to go to her house and go live in it.
>> [ __ ] off, man. You want to go live? Yeah.
>> Huh? You don't want me to. We're going
to go live when I get there. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Give it a while. I would
>> I go live when I get there then? Yeah.
>> Yeah. I will do. I will do.
>> You think everything's funny?
>> I don't like doing this tonight. Do you
know what I mean? But I'm single.
You just find everything funny.
>> No, I just start pissing women off. >> Nasty.
>> I just start pissing women off who piss
me off. That's it. >> Yeah,
>> I'm not pissing that off. I don't even
want to do this to be honest with you.
But [ __ ] it. Ny's playing games. I'm going
I'm going I'm going [ __ ] skip dip in
the bath, mate.
>> Well, bless you.
>> Yeah, I will do. I will do stick. I need
a stick hit.
This is going to hurt though. This is
going to proper hurt and I don't want to hurt. >> Yeah,
>> but I'm not. She doesn't She doesn't
care if she was hurting you.
>> No. True, true, true. And see, I'm still
letting down some kind of way. You know,
I'm telling her that I miss her. I know
all that cuz I do miss her. I do miss
>> She don't give a monkey. And she don't
give a monkeys [ __ ] does she?
>> No, she don't. She don't. That's what I
say, what I do, or whatever.
>> Yep. It's bad, isn't it?
face in a sink. No, man. I wash my dick
I wash my dick in the sink. I make sure
this has got all the plates and cups
there, though. It's well in it.
>> Oh, you dirty [ __ ]
You're a dirty [ __ ] You
>> You have to be careful with your money
next time, Monty, so you don't end up in this position.
>> No, listen. I was happy. I'm happy that
I spent that money. Listen, I'm so
happy. Yeah, because making sure that
Natalie had some food down her neck and
biking, keeping her warm and you know,
that's what I'm happy for doing that for
Natalie. I'm not being funny, but
Natalie were there for me when I was in
a tent. Obviously, Natalie was only in a
tent with me for three nights and then
she went back home and I was in a tent.
I was with Natalie from the day she was
homeless from the day she got a new place.
>> So Natalie really
>> Natalie wasn't on her own. Not on her
>> I know why she was so angry and stressed
out. It's cuz she got kicked out of this
place. So I know that it's cuz of these
little clowns on here sending videos and
all that to them. But I'm leaving this.
Why do why do you people on YouTube do
that as well?
>> The idiots PJ the [ __ ] mongos. I'm
lucky that I've run my place up
actually. I'll put the video up anyway
so you can hear him on the phone. In fact,
>> ask Baldi if he still speaks to Kay.
Listen, listen. If you want to go out
with K, go out with K. Yeah. Go and give
her a [ __ ] ass like Yeah. But I bet
you any money Yeah. you end up with a
[ __ ] big dirty black area in the end
of your teeth.
So go for it, L. She's got one hair ass.
I want her back. She's even grow a
bigger beard than me.
>> Monty, you get paid in 13 days.
>> 13 days. I get paid on the 17th.
>> Yeah. 13 days.
>> Not that long.
I'm only eating burgers though. That's
only what I've been eating. Burgers. I
got to eat burgers for 13 [ __ ] days,
mate. Is that good?
>> Is it good? Is it [ __ ] good?
Is it [ __ ] I have to go shop early on
because I found like a little bit of
money on the floor here from last time.
>> I should have done I should have stayed
over another night and we could have had
like a barbecue.
>> Yeah. No PJ M. You're not allowed to stay here.
So that would be
>> Yeah, I would have anyway, isn't it? >> No.
>> Yeah, but they want to see it, isn't it? >> No,
>> I want to stay.
>> PJ, no. You're not allowed to stay. One
second. One second, PJ. Yeah,
for [ __ ] sake. What?
This guy so stupid, man. One sec.
Move your [ __ ] mic, PJ. Yeah. Listen
to that [ __ ] voice or I send you PJ.
Okay, bro. Yeah. Yeah, I got it, man. I got it. Yeah, bro.
Yeah, man. So,
[ __ ] hot today, isn't it?
>> I'm not bossing P around. I'm not
bossing them around.
>> It's boiling, bro. It
>> It is boiling.
I'm going to try and get this girl's
attention anyways. Yeah. By shaking my
doing a windmill. Look, sending a video
off of me doing a windmill.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
>> Just stay off YouTube. Yeah,
>> you need to stay off YouTube.
>> You need to get off YouTube,
>> I might get McDonald's.
Oh, I don't
>> Yeah, Greensby is still here. >> Who? >> Green.
>> Gy, where are you?
>> Yeah, I met PJ's Ambble. I met his Amber lead.
>> Yeah, nasty. Yeah.
>> Almost snapped his po.
I've got a bad ass.
>> You're just a nasty cannon.
>> I'm a nasty [ __ ]
>> Yeah, I've got a
Oh, what? I got a powerful grip. >> Yeah.
>> Oh, you're an alcoholic, Monty. I'm You
get I am I'm I'm turning into what? I'm
turning into what, man? I might as well
turn into a crackhead. When I say crack,
I mean funny head. That's what I'm on about. >> Alcoholic.
>> Oh, we're going out in a minute.
>> What drink you [ __ ] Let me try minga.
>> Well, bless you then.
>> No, no. Shut up. Shut up. Shut up. Be quiet.
All right. I can.
>> Sure. Sure. Sure. Yeah. Bless you. Not yet.
>> Bless you then.
>> Oh [ __ ] >> Monty. >> Yes.
>> I can only meet you again if you convert
to Muslim to Islam.
I am not converting to no Muslim and I
am not converting to know Islam. >> Please.
>> I am completely [ __ ] atheist.
I'm staying atheist. That is the best
religion in town. You believe?
>> No, I'm I'm a Muslim.
>> I'm going to buy you when you come down
PG then. Yeah. Why? >> What? >> Why?
>> Why won't you Why would you convert to
Why would you convert to Islam?
Because I never convert to Islam.
I like Islam.
No, I never turn Islam PJ. Never. Never.
Ever. Ever. I won't even turn Christian
or Catholic or nothing.
I'm atheist and that's it. I don't
believe in anything or anyone or I just
believe in myself and my legs and that's it.
Me and my legs.
>> God bless.
>> This girl taking a piss, man. She just
wanted to send me a couple of [ __ ]
funny pictures on me just to send my
dick to her. Oh, bless.
>> Do you want to see your tit?
>> Oh, bless you. Yeah.
>> You want to Yeah. Do you want to say P? >> Yeah.
>> [ __ ] off.
You know what I'm saying? No bad t mate. >> Why?
>> All in my eyes to see. PJ, you got to go
and get your own titties. PG.
I am a daddy. I'm going to make this
now. I swear to God. Yeah. I'm going to
make If she If I do go to a house
tonight, Yeah. I'm going to make her
squirt me. She's going to be pissing all over me. I swear.
It's all over me. Check out my name bird.
is [ __ ] banging.
>> She's banging.
>> Is that the real K? >> Yeah.
>> You sure?
>> Yeah. Come on, P. You can't say You
can't say that now. She's [ __ ] banging.
>> That Katie is a nasty c.
>> Oh, she's [ __ ]
meeting her today in a minute. Come on,
man. New York. Text me. Yeah. Look,
look, look. I'm not going to let me get
rid of that. Oh, I can't go. You can't
see that. That's 30. That's dirty.
>> I decided to get with Kaye. Yeah. Good
luck with your get with Kaye.
>> Yeah. Look, look, I'm not going to go up
any more, but they send pictures.
>> That's not That's not the real Kayie, Monty,
>> is it?
>> That's good.
>> Why do these people make fake accounts? >> Huh?
>> Cuz they're pricks. I don't know what
follow we're talking. I got two phones
and I don't know which phone we're
talking to on. This phone,
this phone or that this phone I'm on now.
>> Mr. B, are you doing it? Mr. B, are you
doing any football bets this week?
>> I'm going to jump anyway.
>> Monty, Monty, do you like Mr. B's cool, isn't it?
>> Mr. B's
a little bit too fast. Really?
>> Mr. I haven't seen him talk about us.
>> Yeah, he has. He has. He has. He's not
He's not as worse as the rest of them.
>> But he he asked old.
>> What has he said about me?
>> Oh, he called you the [ __ ] biggest
[ __ ] in his community.
>> Oh, is that right, Mr. B? You called me that.
>> Yeah, that's what he said. Really?
>> Yeah. He said you're a bigger monger
than I am. >> Wow.
>> Yeah. I swear. I swear.
>> I'm going to have to come down there and
beat you up, Mr. B.
>> You're going to have to
Why do you keep making [ __ ] accounts
with Katie? You weirdos, man.
>> I know. It freaks in it.
Why do they just get off YouTube and get a job?
>> Weirdos. What do you peeps? I know why
you put that picture up of Kayie cuz you
think I still fancy Kay's, don't you? Do
you all think I still fancy Kayie?
Do you all really think that I fancy
that woman? Look at my face now. I do
not fancy Kay one little bit.
For [ __ ] sake.
K is a [ __ ] abusing little fat why
these people need to get off YouTube.
>> If I could get birds like that I
wouldn't even got with K. I would have
got a lot more birds pregnant. I'm going
to be a [ __ ] I'm going to get B
pregnant me. I'm getting no
relationships. I'm just going to shag a
bird. Squirt right up. Get pregnant and [ __ ] off.
>> Let's go.
>> That's what I'm going to do.
I'm going to have about 50,000 kids
around the UK by the end of next week.
>> You're still hung over, isn't it?
>> No. Well, the next morning no more was [ __ ]
>> You was hung over. Yeah. The next
morning, isn't it?
>> A little bit. Yeah. Without
>> Yeah. Yeah. It's the drinking, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Don't forget we was in town all
night. All night till morning. Then we
got the breakfast.
>> Yeah. We was on a piss, bro. Oh, wait.
How long did it take you to walk back? Exactly.
>> An hour.
>> Look how [ __ ] you're mad you are.
>> An hour. Took me an hour to get al back.
But don't forget, I was on my feet all
night and all day and then walking back
there. That's how energetic I am.
>> Your legs must have hurt the next day, aren't they?
Yeah, Monty's my friend.
I'm going to be texting this bird
getting away. So, I'll be back in a bit.
Yeah, please. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, man.
>> I'm going to get my dick s. I'm getting
my dick sucked. Me, mate. I'm going to
go down on that [ __ ] I'm I'm going to
eat it like it's a lettuce. Complete leg.
Oh, you're a dirty [ __ ] Oh [ __ ]
>> Yeah, me and Monty's met twice now.
I'm going to show you. Yeah, I'm going
to get some [ __ ] bit. Yeah.
>> All right, mate.
>> [ __ ] hell. Every time I move, the
comments jump up. Wow. Wow. No, not wow.
Not wow. Why am I going to stand around
and wait for a woman who don't love me?
So, it's not a wow. I'm doing what I
need to do. I'm not waiting for Natalie
until she's ready.
I I don't play them games with women.
They leave. If a woman if if a woman
wants want to play them kind of games,
that's when I jump.
I don't play them games with women.
>> You don't pull Steven Howard. Steven
Howard, how comes you never poor? >> What?
>> I'm asking this Steven Howard. How come
he never psy?
I can't believe you was in a tent.
That's bad, is it?
>> I am being power fish.
>> Molly, I can't believe you was actually
I can't believe you was in a tent.
That's [ __ ] mad, isn't it?
>> I've been in a tent race. One one on me
on and one with Natalie.
>> Yeah, but that's mad like staying in a
tent, isn't it,
>> PJ? That is my life.
That is the best life you could ever
live. No [ __ ]
>> What a tent.
>> Obviously not in a tent, but if you make
your own little cabin house out of
[ __ ] pellets and put like a little
fireplace in there, then you're buzzing.
Who needs a [ __ ] break out?
>> Would you say you ended up in a tent
because of YouTube? Yeah. Was it?
>> Yeah. No. >> No.
>> Still, no. It won't YouTube.
It weren't. It weren't YouTube. It was
Natalie's mom, Lisa. If Lisa's If Lisa
didn't do his address, Natalie Bishia.
>> Yeah. So, it is still YouTube though if
you think about it.
>> Yeah, but Lisa give everybody this address.
>> No, I'm saying before that when you was
on the when you was in the tent. >> What?
in the tent.
>> Oh, on my own. When it was on my own. >> Yeah.
>> No, that weren't YouTube
>> at all. That was K. No, that was Kaye
sticking up for her [ __ ] abuser mother.
Her mom didn't Her mom don't even love her.
Her mom Her mom and dad treated her like
a prick and all that. Okay,
>> if you weren't on YouTube, it probably
would have happened that way, is it?
That's what I mean.
>> Oh, yeah. It would have happened that
way. She's just a [ __ ] She's a prick.
I choose a 10 any day. I've got a
[ __ ] tent. Literally, man. I've got
my lives. Have you seen my [ __ ] My survival [ __ ]
Look at it all, mate. Listen, if you
say, "Oh, how the [ __ ] how the [ __ ] are
you going to wash yourself outside,
[ __ ] How the [ __ ] are you going to get
a shower, Mongo?" Listen, people, I know
it's coming peeps. It's gone.
>> It's gone terribly wrong for Jamie.
We got a shower. I was We got a shower.
This is a hold shower. Literally.
I see what you p You don't believe?
Yeah. Door shower.
Watch this bad boy. PJ, this is a bad boy. This
It's a shower. I'm not even [ __ ] So,
what you do, you grab that. You put that on there.
What's this? Yeah.
[ __ ] banging, mate.
>> Yeah. Let's get our sh. Yeah.
>> This website's going to kill you one day.
>> I've got two of these. Look, I've got
two of these. We've got lace here.
And then we've got actual sha head itself.
Yeah. So, let's take this into the
bathroom. Come on. Let's go into the
>> What? I hope this website don't kill you, bro.
>> I hope it doesn't.
All right. So, what you do?
>> Is it Kelly? Yeah,
>> it's a fake Kayie. Yeah.
>> Yeah. So, what you do just just let me
run the bath. I'm not running the bath
all the way up.
Let me show you what this does.
So, what you do with this, you just pour
it in water like that.
So, that goes there in water. Turn my
camera around. Sorry, Pia.
>> Well, bless you then.
>> Yeah. So that's in the water.
It's not plugged into anything. It's
just there. Nothing.
It's a shower p. No change here. You put
in any kind of water form or whatever. I
can live all this life. Most people
can't in this community. I can live that life.
Now he can live that life. She can do
it. She's done it.
She's lived in a tent for a couple of days.
Not as long as me though.
That is where you store
>> you to get off YouTube here.
>> Monty, would you meet?
Would you meet belly?
>> That's my shower. Sick. See, I can wash.
>> What? Would you meet?
>> I meet. Of course I meet.
Of course I would.
>> Who would you meet?
>> You could you could have a beer with her
in it. I never die. Never.
>> By's a good guy. It
>> didn't a good guy. By's a good guy.
>> Bell is a pedo.
>> Yeah, but not really.
>> Really? He's a pedo when he's got like
kids up on his wall and that.
>> There's loads of people. Oh, another
man's case up on the wall.
>> There's loads of PE on this room in it.
>> Yeah, is
>> I'm going to jump anyway. Yeah, cuz I'm
going to talk to this bird now. >> Okay. [ __ ] interested.
>> And it hasn't been 4 days, people. It's
been longer than 4 days when Natalie
spilled with me.
It's been longer than 4 days.
I think you're I think you're getting
over her now. Anyways, I think
>> I am getting over her. I am getting over
her. Of course I am. I was sick of
getting played by [ __ ] women.
>> Natalie. Natalie. You know what?
Natalie's better than Kayie. 10 times
100% better than Kayie. I'm saying that
now. 100 times better. And
all I do what Kelly does is he stalk me
around YouTube. Stalk me.
>> It's K who still pes the [ __ ] out of me.
You know what I mean? It's K who still p
with me by stalking me.
>> You should you should me.
>> [ __ ] off, man. You end up trying to shag
me the dirty bastard.
>> You and Timmy rented the house together. That's
>> doesn't even know that the police are
going to a house soon.
>> When is this YouTube thing going to stop?
You've never even had a bird [ __ ]
You had a granny.
And I'm not being funny, R. Just look in
the mirror. You really can't say
anything about anyone.
You one, you can't even get with Kayie. Two,
you can't even get with anybody on
YouTube or it's over 50.
>> Do you like it though?
>> He likes his granny's. He likes his
[ __ ] cobwebs. He does. He likes his
tried [ __ ] walkers crisps. He does bastard.
>> Keep getting me out of the car in GTA,
bro. It's [ __ ] annoying.
>> Go on. I'll let you into 10 little
[ __ ] disabled ones who ain't got no
friends in this community. Yeah. >> Okay.
>> I see him. PJ's G.
Mr. Lee. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Oh [ __ ] I could call you again. I
thought I would left.
>> No, I'm only
>> You think this community is funny?
>> Guys, it's not a disabled run. Have you
seen the state of his fingers? GT finger
dead long [ __ ]
>> well. I've got about six people trying
to kick the [ __ ] out of me on GTA.
>> That's good.
>> All right. See you later. Yeah.
>> Yeah, man.
All right. Rice. I can get more [ __ ]
You rise. I'm going get [ __ ] now, lad.
In a bit.
>> I love GTA 5, man.
I love running the people over and killing them.
You want some more, do you [ __ ]
I love running the people over, bro.
It's fun, is it?
It's fun in it, Monty.
Yeah. One second. Oh,
one second. Rice.
Oh, why? Rice, why do you never message
me anymore on WhatsApp?
What's up, bro? Why you never message me on WhatsApp?
You have my number? Glasgow. [ __ ] Glasgow.
>> Yo, PJ, how you doing, my friend? Yo,
Mong, I got a message for [ __ ] I have
Yeah, because I need to tell him this,
right? That little daff cake, right? [ __ ]
Let's let's let's speak adult PJ, right?
[ __ ] up two relationships. One woman
at one, right? And he's going around
saying, "I can't get any woman I want."
Yeah. Fine. Let him think what he wants
to think. I don't give a [ __ ] The guy
is a lost cause. Yeah. He [ __ ] his own
family up, his own kids, right? The guy
is a [ __ ] up in society. Do you know you
got a better life than PJ? Yeah. That
man, right, put a camera That man put a
camera in his two girlfriends' face,
right? And you know who he blimped for
that? The cocking community. He blimped
the community for the actual [ __ ] as
he is. He, you know, he's not even
allowed to see his own [ __ ] kids cuz
his mom hates his [ __ ] guts. For
[ __ ] sake. He's a drug addict. He's a
smackhead. And then he goes around
accusing me of this and that. [ __ ]
[ __ ] Trust me, mate. Not one person on
this internet knows nothing about me.
And I got a private life. Yeah. And I
swear, mate, you're wrong about me. I
can get whoever I want on this internet
and it's lush. And I mean lush. I'm
going to [ __ ] you up, [ __ ] It's just a
matter of time. I will come to your
location eventually cuz I'm going to
take out every little bit of anger I've
got for you out on your [ __ ] face.
I'm not scared of you. Never have, never
will. I'm going to put you to sleep
quick. Yeah. And I promise you are, PJ.
I will. I put him to sleep. I'm an odd
little [ __ ] I'm going to make our boy
cry my name and apology. He's going to
say sorry for me for everything. He
thinks he's an odd little [ __ ] PJ,
I'm a gangster. I I'll make him
disappear, bro. Honestly, I will let him
that hard. He go thinks that he's [ __ ]
Honestly, I'll kill that.
>> But would you ever go to Birmingham?
>> Yeah, I'm just I'm just waiting on
something at the moment. Yeah, I got
something planned. Right. There's
something in the in the in the
waterworks, right? Well, let me tell you
something, PJ. Right. I will be going
down there, right? Eventually, right?
And I will be I'll be rinsing him like a
a [ __ ] flannel, mate. I'm going to
meet up with him, right?
>> No broadcasting, no cameraing faces, and
I'm going to put him to sleep.
>> So, are you with are you are you with Kaye now?
>> Well, no, I'm with Mongo's mom. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Me and his mom, like, it's [ __ ]
hard. Like, she's, you know, she's got a
good [ __ ] on her. You know what I mean?
>> Wait, but have you met Have you met Kaye yet?
>> No. Kayie hates me.
>> Why? I thought you two was trying to go
and get together.
>> No, Kayie hates me.
>> Why do you try?
>> Anyway, if I tried anyway, I probably
could [ __ ] Hay, too. I bet she's a
better [ __ ] Natalie. Anyway, I'm
actually I've decided something. I'm
going to go down and [ __ ] Natalie first.
Yeah. No, I'm going to [ __ ] Kaye first
and then I'm going to go down and [ __ ]
Natalie and then I'm going to basically
record me [ __ ] Kay first. put that on
the internet and then I'm gonna put I'll
record myself [ __ ] atly the same time
after. So I'll [ __ ] both of them so I
can say that I [ __ ] his uh exes and
[ __ ] That's lush. That's lush. And I'm
going to be a daddy to his little kids
too. A sweat god. I'm be a better daddy
than he'll ever have been.
>> Have you ever been to Birmingham?
>> No, I will be. I I'm excited. I'm
excited to go to his location because I
I can't wait cuz I'm going to [ __ ] him
up big time.
>> Yeah, you have to get the train. Oh,
it's all right. Sorry. I'll sort the cont.
>> No, you have to get the train in it.
>> No, I'll get I I'll get there, mate.
Trust me. If I have to [ __ ] teleport
all the way down there like he tried to
teleport [ __ ] Kaye. Yeah, that's what
he said, didn't he? You know, he was on
your panel. Uh uh PJ, and he said he hit
the woman. He hit the woman, mate. How
[ __ ] up is that?
>> He's a [ __ ] up in society, mate. You see
him 20 years down the line, mate. Right.
and he be in the same position as he is
right now. You know, it's Why can't he
settle down and just get himself a
girlfriend and just be happy?
>> How old are you? How old are you now again?
>> Me? I'm 38.
>> Oh, so you're right about the same age, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Yeah, mate. I swear, mate. I'm
going to put him to sleep. I swear I'm
just It's a matter of time. I'm not
worried about anybody else.
>> Yeah. Yo yo yo, I'm deceiving. Yeah, I'm
a cute little [ __ ] in real life. Yeah,
and I swear, mate, I'm going to make him
look like [ __ ] uh a car crash when I meet him. He
>> Well, you should just try and make up.
>> Nah. All right, I'm going to make up.
All right, I'm going to make up. I'm
going to smash his face and my hand is
going to meet his face, mate.
>> I don't do drugs. Never do I've done
drugs in my life. When did you last drink?
>> I haven't drunk for ages, man. I' I'm in
a new relationship now, bro. I got
responsibilities. I'm not even on I
don't even [ __ ] broadcast anymore, you know? >> Yeah.
>> I've stopped all the social media. It's
called being responsible. PJ, I said to
the community when I get myself
girlfriend, I'm not coming back on his
social media. Here he is. Look,
I'll focus on your
even you. Oh, you the only thing you
could do is whack women around. All you
could do is swim women around your f.
Look at that. Oh, you well you are in a
woman about my life. You manatch rape.
>> Why did you rape?
>> Think about you boy.
>> Why did you You don't [ __ ] about me.
You know about me, Rice.
>> Oh, I [ __ ] Kelly two times yesterday.
Listen one little bit.
>> I [ __ ] you.
>> Listen, Rice. Rice, you haven't [ __ ]
>> Oh, I haven't [ __ ] listen. I'm not allowed.
I'm not vulnerable. You can sh
your face looking like you got your
face. The union kids got better looks
than you. You [ __ ]
>> Mongo's getting.
Does anyone know the kid? That kid with
the P face. He's even got a better look.
I think he would raian kid on him.
>> Oh yeah. Like cool.
>> Google kid. Yeah. Google him.
>> Look at this.
>> Meet up with you, mate. And I got [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] Why don't you come here?
>> Can you fight? You never come here. >> Wait,
>> you never come here.
>> Can you fight?
>> Can you fight? Yes or no?
>> Pete, can I fight?
>> Well, it's not a [ __ ] odd question, is it?
>> Can I fight?
>> What? What?
>> What are you do? What are you doing?
>> What are you doing?
>> Do it. Mate, fight.
>> What is that?
>> I'm not even What is that? I'm not even trying.
>> I'm not even trying, guys. That's the
thing. Let me try it. Anyway, why don't
you come to me and show you the fight?
>> Well, I I will Okay. Okay. Okay. Who's
good to leave the front door? Rice.
Who's good to open a door to when
someone's knocking on his door? Rice. >> Rice.
>> Rice can't do this, people. Rice can't
do this. It's called being a
little boy. I don't
>> you have a little boy rice.
>> Anyways, preacher, I'm getting ready to
go and meet a bird. I'm going to
actually shag him. So, don't send me
pisses off him in your chat again.
>> Why are you shagging? Why you underage?
>> I'm going to shag a gorgeous woman. I'm
getting ready, mate, to go. She's underage.
>> I'm getting ready to go.
Entertaining rice. She's 15 years old.
>> Look at that.
>> Show your body. Rice. Show me your body.
>> I show your body.
>> I show you right there.
>> Show me your body.
>> I show my body.
>> Show me your body. Rice.
>> You love the body.
>> Show me your body.
>> I show your body. Katie was all over.
>> Show me your body. K loves my body. >> Yeah.
>> Show me your body. Come on. No.
>> Get your body out. Right. >> No.
>> Get your body out. Come on. Chop. Chop.
>> My body is only for one eyes only. And that's Kayie.
>> Kay doesn't fancy. Kay doesn't want you guys.
>> Oh, that's
>> Kay doesn't want you.
>> I know.
>> She's already smashed your flowers up, you [ __ ]
>> Mango mango.
>> See, I'm off.
>> See you later, you ugly man. See you
>> [ __ ] your mom. I'm [ __ ] your mom. [Laughter]
He is an absolute [ __ ] PJ, how'd you
put up with him?
>> Fun. Man,
>> he don't like me one bit there. Trust
me. Anyway, I got to go. I just want to
speak to that. Anyway, you enjoy your
night. Yeah. Bye, man. Yeah.
Yeah, just me now.
That's fake K by the way.
That's fake al. Yeah.
Which one's the real one?
No, they're all fake.
All the Kies are fake.
Yeah, you're all fake. All fake tailies, bro.
Oh [ __ ] man. I'm playing some Franklin.
Monty needs to get off YouTube in it.
I'll be coming off soon. So
little mongos on it. No. Yeah. One second.
Well, it's cute, isn't it?
So, you having a football bet on um
Saturday, Mr. Be,
you having a little football bet? Bless you. Nah, bro.
I can't afford to lose 300 pound.
Yeah, that that returns like what? A,000 maybe?
Yeah, like a thousand in it. But it's
too expensive, bro. I can't [ __ ] water £300
like that, man. What the [ __ ]
Have you ever done £300 on two teams?
Well, have you done 300 on two teams?
I wish I put £300 on that bet the other day, mate.
I wish I put £300 on it.
I wish I [ __ ] did now.
I would have returned
over a thousand, I reckon, isn't it?
Yeah, but what if it loses, Mr. B? Then
you are [ __ ] aren't you?
Yeah, then you're [ __ ] If it doesn't
win, you're [ __ ] aren't you?
Then you'll be [ __ ] if it loses it.
Imagine that 300 pound down the drain on
two teams. [ __ ] that.
Yeah, there's one here. If you put £300
on these two teams, it returns 896.
That's not worth it for 300 risk, is it?
That's 500. And
it's like almost 600 profit in it.
It's not a good return though, is it? Yeah.
Why don't you play slots anymore? Yeah. Hear
If you put £500 on it, you get 1494 back. 1 £1,494
[ __ ] Losing £500 on two teams.
Oh, [ __ ] that, bro. SL
[ __ ] that bro on two teams. [Music]
must up 500 pound on them two [ __ ]
teams last Saturday, mate.
I would have been [ __ ] laughing.
I would have been laughing, mate. Right.
I'm going. Yeah.