Yo, I'm just on Mon's [ __ ] live
stream. Yeah, bro. That person's [ __ ]
talking [ __ ] Trying to blame me. Oh, PJ
got youring kid strip
search. Who's the one that got social
services involved? Who's the one that
sent letters to people's neighbors?
Who's the ones that got [ __ ] Monty
banned from the [ __ ] soft play? Don't
[ __ ] blame me, bro. about the about
the the it lands on me. What? Because I
called the police saying that Monty and
Kaye was arguing and then they decided
to strip search these kids. I didn't
even know they could [ __ ] do that.
Don't [ __ ] go in your [ __ ] chat
[ __ ] blaming me, bro. Are you [ __ ]
mad? You know what I'm
saying about the blame lands on me? Look
up. Wait, who's the one that sent
letters to people's neighbors? Who's the
one that got somebody banned from
software? Who's the one that got social
services involved? Who is the one that
got social services involved? Answer that. Yeah.
Listen, let me ask you this question.
Who's the one that got social services
involved? Who's the one that sent
letters to your neighbors? Who's the one
that got you banned from soft play? I
called the police saying that you was
arguing with Kaye and they decided to
strip search your kid. That's not my
[ __ ] fault. I didn't even know they
could [ __ ] do that. I didn't even
know they could even [ __ ] do that. I
I wouldn't even know if they would have
come out, let alone [ __ ] strip search
someone's kid. So, don't [ __ ] blame
me, you know, cuz let me tell you
something, right? If it was just me, let
me ask you this
question. If it was just me doing that
one thing, social services wouldn't have
been involved and you wouldn't have lost
your kids. Yeah. Simple. If it was just
that one thing, no traumad, no one else,
you wouldn't have lost your kids. Yeah.
Your kids would have not been lost if it
was just me.
Yeah. Yeah. No, I I I do feel bad like,
you know, bringing you on this
community. That's my fault. I do feel
bad. But don't blame me, mate. Cuz one
one thing Yeah. one thing would have not
made you lost your kids. It wouldn't
have even got social services involved.
I didn't even know they could strip
search your [ __ ] kids. How the [ __ ]
would I know that? Huh? You know,
Traumador was the one that caused all of
this [ __ ] Yeah. No, you're blaming me,
you little [ __ ] I've seen your
comment. Don't come on my channel trying
to be [ __ ] two-faced about it's me to
blame, you little [ __ ] Get the [ __ ]
out of here, you little [ __ ] You
know, you stupid little [ __ ] fat
loser [ __ ] Yeah. Don't [ __ ] go on
Monty Man's talking [ __ ] trying to blame
me, you [ __ ] virgin [ __ ] Little
weirdo. and then come on my channel
trying to [ __ ] play trying to [ __ ]
trying to play um trying to um play two
sides. You little [ __ ] I'm jealous of
Monty's kids. Don't be so [ __ ]
stupid, you little [ __ ] Yeah, you're
the ones that talk about kids every
single day. But anyways, yeah, let's
let's get back on to this. Yeah. What's
it? Your [ __ ] kids. Yeah, I sound
triggered. Stop repeating yourself, you
little [ __ ] Yeah. And you And you're
a fat ugly [ __ ] Stop repeating
yourself, you little [ __ ] You little
spacker with autism. Yeah. So, don't try
and [ __ ] blame me. Yeah. Get Monty
man on here now. Get Monty man on here
Yeah. These are the people that made you
lose your [ __ ] kids. Not me. Not
[ __ ] me, bro. Hell no.
Yeah. Yeah. Don't come on my channel,
Cam Joel. Like, I don't know what you're
doing, you little [ __ ] Get a life.
Get off of YouTube, you little
[ __ ] You little [ __ ] downy, you
know. Yeah. Come on here and I'll
explain this to you again. Yeah. I'll
Yeah. [ __ ] sake, bro.
Yeah. How can anyone um grass into social
services? Grass into social
services. Traumad was grass into social
services. That's what got his kids took
taken away. Not me. Not [ __ ] me. Cuz
let me tell you something now. If it was
just me, you would still have your kids
and there'd be no social services. If it
was just me, if it was just me, there'd
be no social services and you'd still have your
kids. So, you can't blame me, man. I
know it's easier to blame someone else,
but you can't blame me. Sorry, you
can't, man. No, you can't.
Yeah, they can't take kids without Okay,
so what was the reason then? What was
the reason then? What was the reason then? Go
on. I smell nice, bro. I smell like the
plug. Plugins are nice. Have you ever
had them plugins for your house? Them
adapting plugins? Oh, they're [ __ ] lush,
man. Oh, it smells so good. It goes all
over your clothes and that.
Well, mate, it wasn't
me. You know, the only thing I done bad
was bring him on to this community, but
I didn't know they were going to target
him like that. You know, I do kind of
feel bad. Yeah, but I mean,
yeah, it wasn't me, mate, that made you
lose your kids. Why don't you come on
here? Why don't you come on here,
Monty? I mean, but yeah, you're right
about people being fat, ugly virgins.
Yeah. Like these ugly fat people that
can't get [ __ ] laid. Yeah, that's
actually true, man. It's like it's like
when they tell me that I'm 27, I've
never been in a relationship. These
people are 47 and they've never been and
they can't get laid. They've never been
laid. They're fat and ugly. You know
what I'm saying, bro?
Yeah, we had music beaming. Hey,
Natalie, you okay? I went out on Friday.
I got four numbers. They didn't go
anywhere. Yeah, I'm feeling rough today.
I went to Greg's this morning. Got a
piggy and cheese wrap and I fell
straight to sleep. I fell asleep until
[ __ ] 12:00, bro. I was up
early. Drinking gets to Peter Belly,
Natalie. Yeah, I got a few numbers, but
they didn't really go anywhere. I spent
£500 last week, Natalie.
Yeah. Got told about her. Yeah, I went
to the clubs. Natalie, guess what they
said when I approached? Yeah, I went out
Friday. I got four numbers and some of
them replied, but they didn't really go
anywhere. But yeah, I got loads of uh
I've got a boyfriend's last
Friday. Yep. Loads of uh I have a boyfriend,
man. Yeah. Oh, yeah. I went to I spent
like500 on Friday. Had to get my
passport renewed and stuff, didn't I, Natalie? So,
yeah. Detox for a month. coming on strongly, lad.
Yep. I smell so nice, man. Like them
plugins. It's just the same old [ __ ] in this country,
Natalie. Same old. It's like wherever
you go in England, it's the same. You
get the same men, the same women with
attitude, the same people, you know.
Yeah, it's better than staying in, but I
can't do it every week because I need to
save now. I need to leave this country.
So, I can go out every week if I wanted
to, but I'm not going to,
obviously. What's my plans? Just
chilling, bro. I'm just going to get a
Chinese and chill. I'm I'm having a
quiet month. I've decided I'm on I'm
having a quiet month. But yeah, I did do
the approaches anyways, Natalie. I did
try. Somebody was like, "Oh, at least
you tried." And I was thinking in my
head, "Bro, man's been trying for the
past three [ __ ] years about at least
I've tried." Man's been trying.
Uh Monty's blaming me as to why he lost
these kids as usual when it literally
had nothing really to do with me because
who's the one that got social services
involved? These people, you
know, you know what's so mad is if
anyone ever made me lose my kid over
YouTube, I would literally get one of
these people. I wouldn't be I'd get one
of these people, then I'd come off. But
yet, he's still on here. It doesn't make
any sense. He, you know, and he blames
me if it what, bro. He blames me. It's
mad. I can't even get a bite. Stop self
stop self projecting. Oh [ __ ] My
bad. Like, you lost your kids and you're
still, bro. All this community consists
of is just fat, ugly bongos that ain't
got a life that just self-reflect.
That's that's all they do, bro. Like I
don't even know why you're still on it
after you lost your [ __ ] kids. And
that's literally what they are. Just
fat, ugly little mongos that's got
nothing in their
lives. They got [ __ ] all in their life but
self-reflecting. Think of it. I was out
on Friday getting pissed. These people
was on the
YouTube. Do you know what? I was looking
up flights to Dubai. Yeah, you can
actually go to buy this month. Yeah. For
a week for 800 quid with the hotel. I'm
not even joking.
go to Dubai. But why would you go to Dubai,
bro? You've got no chance in that
country. But I'm surprised it was so
cheap. I looked it up. I'm not going to
tell you the airline and that because of
grasses, but I actually looked it up.
Yeah, I looked up, bro. was legit for
[ __ ] Dubai, bro. But I
wouldn't I wouldn't go Dubai
cuz there's no point in going to a
Muslim country that's strict. It's
stupid. It doesn't make any sense. But I
mean, for that price, I
mean, I'd rather do that than go out in
London again, to be
honest. Oh, and I could I could get rid
of this phone. If I went to Dubai, I
could get rid of this phone as well cuz
if you go to the buy, they can unblock
it in it. Imagine that. That'd be a good
little vlog, is it? Stephen Howard,
Peter Belly goes to
Dubai. What a lovely site. And then get
this phone unlocked and then come back.
That'll get [ __ ] nonslegs [ __ ]
raging with his fat ugly girlfriend. I
don't know how much, but you can sell it
in Dubai because they can unlock it there.
Yeah. Yeah. These people would be
raging. But I don't have my I think I'll
get my passport on Friday. Maybe. I had
to renew my passport, Mr.
B. I had to renew my passport.
Oh, so yeah, Natalie, every time you go
out in England, it's just the same
old they got boyfriends. But the one
that I actually like, she didn't reply.
I got an Italian number. She was talking
and then she just stopped.
Um, then the bartender stopped when I
asked her out. And then one blocked me
and then one didn't reply. So,
uh, they're just not interested in this country,
Natalie. As Antman
said, they're just not interested in
this country. But in Dubai, right? I
think if you went to Dubai.
Um, oh, did you watch my burger video,
Natalie? Did you like
it? It was really hot. Well, it almost [ __ ] killed
me. It almost [ __ ] killed me,
Natalie. It almost killed me,
Natalie. But yeah, they're just not
interested in this country,
Natalie. I think it's because I don't
look like I'm white. That's what I think
it is. I think it's because I don't look
like I'm white.
I got this woman's number from [ __ ]
Romania. But they just they're just they
just I I just think that they're all
evil. I just think these women are just
evil and they just like playing people
for fun. That's the conclusion that I've
actually come to is that they're just
evil and they just like playing men for
fun. That's what I actually
think. Yeah, it was a Reaper
burger. I couldn't handle the heat. It
almost killed me, bro. I was throwing up
on the [ __ ] street.
I couldn't handle the [ __ ] heat. He
almost [ __ ] killed
me. Funny enough, I didn't get the shits
the next day, but I think that's because
I sked it all out. I was being sick on
the pavement and [Laughter]
everything. I was being sick on the pavement and
everything. It was mad. I swear down.
Yeah. He almost killed me. Yeah.
How much money do you get a month now
Natalie? I get over 3k so I could afford
to that £500 for the passport and that in
it. I approached this woman and when I
asked her out the other day she's like I
only love black guys. I was like oh my
god bro I'm not hearing this am I?
That's literally what she said m I'm not
even joking. She was from Switzerland.
She says that she only loves black
guys. I've got my ways, Natalie. I've
ways. Peter, he's got his
So, could say that. Yeah.
How much do you
get? 500 pound on
Friday. Yeah. She said she loves black
guys. You get 1k a month. See, 1k enough
is not enough for Peter Betty's lifestyle.
That's not enough for because you know
say I did get really lucky and I met
someone and then like I had a baby.
Who's going to pay for the baby Stone Island baby
grows? Who's going to pay for the Stone
Island baby grows and
stuff? 1K just won't do it. I just told
you I spent 500 quid. I had to get my
passport renewed. I got my hair done. I
went on the pier. Got some food. £500
done. Well, realistically was £450.
Yeah. Well, relisted he was 450, but you get the
point. Yeah, lad. It's
still No, cuz Yeah. And obviously if you
want to go approaching, you need money.
So, it's like, yeah, who's going to pay
for the little stone islands and
stuff? You know what I'm saying? Steven
Howard, who's going to pay for them
things? Let me
see that because there's no link up.
There's no link
up. So yeah, Natalie, I've got my uh
passport renewed, but I should just go
to Dubai for the 850 quid. Think about
it. Would you rather go to Dubai for a
week somewhere you've never been or
spend money in this country? And
realistically, when you go out drinking,
you're probably going to spend about 300 quid.
You're probably going to spend about 300
[ __ ] quid. But just see it as as
that, you know, going out drinking,
hearing that they have boyfriends when
they don't, you know, same old
[ __ ] I'm not living lush though, man.
Because I'm still having the same problems with
women. So I'm still having the same problems.
Yeah. I asked for you. Yeah. We'll tell
them to put the link up
then age this [ __ ] [ __ ] one more time. But
yeah, but yeah, they've all got
boyfriends, Natalie. But I think I done
good getting F. I I started off in my
area. I got a bartender's number, then I
got free when I went out. But I did a
lot of approaches.
I did do a lot of approaches, bro. I
did. Trust me, I
did. Yeah. I had a I had a bacon and
cheese wrap from Greg's this morning.
Oh, it was [ __ ] lush. I had two of
them. They just come out. Oh, it sent me to
sleep. Yeah. You know,
bro, that is what we
need. That is what we [ __ ] need, mate.
Yeah, it's actually called Peter Belly's
It's actually called Peter Belly's Pork Chops.
Yeah, but yeah, Natalie, they all have boyfriends
apparently. At least you don't have a boyfriend.
Uh, can't I get a ride off that? We're
not talking about that on here, are we?
And I don't like rides. I just like
[ __ ] I had a I had an escort. I had
a [ __ ] from an escort, but I couldn't
come on um Friday, Natalie, cuz I drunk too
much. I drunk too much. Sean was like,
"Oh, if you drink too much, it doesn't
affect you." Yes, it does. I have no
problem coming and have no problem
having sex. I just can't do it when I've
drunk too much. Does he not understand
that when I go out and drink, I don't
stop. Yeah. I do not
stop. Yeah. I don't stop until I
physically can't no more. I don't go out
and have one, two, three drinks. I'm on it all
night. So Sean, that's a bit different
than you having two, three drinks, you little virgin.
know. Yeah. I don't have wide rides. I
just like [ __ ] I don't really care
about the women anymore, but and that
it's just it just pissed me off on
Friday cuz even though I went out to
have fun and
that it's just annoying hearing, "Oh,
I've got a boyfriend." Like, it's
[ __ ] annoying as [ __ ]
bro. So annoying. Even though I didn't
really just go out for that, you know?
It is annoying,
man. Living that day life.
Yeah, Natalie, you would have you would
have gave me you would have gave me a
blow. No, they didn't all say they had
boyfriends, but a lot of them did. Some
of them gave their number. Some of them
said they had boyfriends when they
didn't. Some of them said that they don't like
men. Um, some of them just showed no interest, but
mainly it was it was I've got a
boyfriend. It was it was quite a few few
of them that said that from what I could
remember. But it's normally all different. It's normally.
Yeah. I I remember I went out one
Friday. Yeah. And two of them said they
had a boyfriend. I was like I thought
that was a good day, bro. I only got I
got a boyfriend I got a boyfriend twice.
I was like, "Yes." Because when you hear
it like a few times, Yeah. you need to
like you need to um you need to um stop
being a white knight. Um, you need to
stop like when they when they say like
they've got a boyfriend twice or three
times, I'll be like, "Okay, cool. That's
fine." They I just assume that they do.
But when you constantly hear it at like
1:00, 2:00 in the morning, there's no
way. Because people that actually have
boyfriends, they go out with their
boyfriends. That's the difference. They
do. They do. Maybe the odd one doesn't,
but they they don't. Because think of
it, right? Most women would cheat.
That's not even me generalizing. They
would. Women are not loyal. Men are not
loyal. We live in 2025. So even if they
actually did have a
boyfriend, what's the chances that
they're actually loyal? Like there's so
many things to go by, but of course they
don't have boyfriends. They're full of
[ __ ] Yeah. I I think we have
not tried to interrupt me. Literally
Natalie, I was in a club uh three I
think it was about 3 weeks ago and this
woman was giving me attitude. Yeah. I I
was trying to talk to a friend and she
was giving me attitude. Bro, I stuck it
on everyone in that club, bro. I will
say I'll say it to a woman when I want,
how I want. And I said, "No man's going
to [ __ ] stop me." And there was like
somebody that was about 6' 3, 6'4. I
weren't going to I weren't going to
stop, bro. Cuz I said, "You know what,
mate? Guess what? If I get battered, I
win." cuz it had to took more than one
of you. Yeah. I was I was having it,
bro. [ __ ] that. You know what I'm
saying? And I say I'll say he said, "Oh,
you don't speak to girls." Like I said,
I talk to you the [ __ ] I want like that.
You know, and I was and I was I was I
was sure as well. I'm not going to let
some little white knight Yeah. [ __ ]
tell me what I can and can't [ __ ]
say, bro. You know, cuz if you get
jumped, you're the winner, bro. Think
about it. Because it took more than
that. It took more than one of them to
get you down, bro.
So, I don't like to talk about them
things, bro, cuz it's just negative.
Yeah. But yeah, it's impossible in this
country, man. I need to get myself to
Thailand. Bye-bye, Sean. [ __ ] off, you little
virgin. [ __ ] ratfaced virgin. That's
another reason, you know, he's a virgin
because he's on YouTube every day
stalking me. He says he's been with this
woman for three years, but he's on
YouTube every day stalking me cuz he
wants to be me. [ __ ] virgin. [ __ ]
ugly virgin. I don't know most women. I
know more women than you, mate. You've
never been with a normal woman. I have.
Hence why you're obsessed with my sloppy
seconds. You weirdo
virgin. You're not a fighter. I don't
care if I'm a fighter or not, mate. I'm
not going to let somebody talk to me
like I'm a prick.
Did my mate get laid in Thailand?
Um, he gets laid about 10 times a
day and my mate my mate is Ant-Man. Yes.
Guess what? He gets laid 10 times a day
and he never hears that I've got a
boyfriend. Huh? Isn't that funny? Yeah.
He gets laid 10 times a day. Five to 10
times a day. No exaggeration, bro. He
puts on his Snapchat and you never hear
about boyfriends there.
Never. Yeah, that virgin's always
watching me. I think he wants to be me.
I think he's jealous of me, man. I've
got a few stalkers, to be fair. Jamie
Thompson. Um, yeah, really. Yeah,
really. He said he's never heard it
there about boyfriends. You don't hear
it over there. You hear it here. Trust
me, you [ __ ] hear it here, mate. I
tell you that for nothing. You
definitely hear it in
England. Yeah, he's always watching me.
I think he wants to be me. Na na n n n n
n n n n n n n n n n n n n n n n n n n n
n n n n n n n n n n n n n n n n. Even that Jamie
Thompson, I think they want to be
me. I think they want to be me. I think
they're jealous of me, bro. They won't leave me alone. [ __ ] weirdos. But
yeah, no, I wouldn't have sex with you in that
energy. Nope. Not all of them are prostitutes.
prostitutes. I don't know, man. But have
you noticed on this community, all of
these people, they're e they're all old
or fat and ugly. Have you noticed that?
I've noticed that with this community
that they're either fat and ugly or
they're very old. That's why they they
they say to me, "Oh, you're 27. You've
never been in a relationship." These
people are 47 and they've never been
laid and they're still virgins and
they're fat and ugly.
Everything that they say, they
self-reflect. It's just their own lives
they're talking about, you know? They
they're miserable, fat, ugly people
that's got nothing going for themselves.
Can't even leave their house. So that's
why they come here and do what they do
every day. And they've been doing it for
years as well. You can ask Natalie.
Natalie will even tell you. They've been
doing it for years, man. Projecting
years. They've been doing it for years.
Fat, ugly people that's got nothing
going for themselves. you know. Yeah.
Um yeah, I said the women that say
they've got boyfriends, only three out
of 10 actually have
boyfriends. Only about three out of 10
actually have boyfriends. He tells me
that I don't know most women, but I've
been with more women than him. He's
jealous of the women that I've been
with, but I don't know most women
apparently. Apparently I don't know most
women. na na. Yeah. All of the women
that I've been with, he's jealous of.
Morgan, Izzy, [ __ ] There was another
one. I forget. I forget the name. Sig.
Sig. But I don't know most women. Even
though I've been with more women than
him. And I don't care if I've not been
in a relationship for three years with a
[ __ ] [ __ ] That doesn't mean
anything. I don't know most women
apparently. Yeah. All of the women that
I've been with have been normal. Huh.
It's mad, ain't it?
But I don't know most women apparently.
Um I do know most women because they're
pretty much all the same. Same attitude
just like men are the same. It's the
same in London. Same [ __ ] same
[ __ ] that women go for. Same women,
same attitude. They've all got Oh yeah,
that one in in London as
well, you know. Uh who am I to question
it? I am who I am. [ __ ] virgin boy. Bye-bye
now. go and meet
that. Like I said, if you come to
London, I'll meet
you. But I'm not traveling anymore. I don't travel
anymore. No, it's not that you're not my
It's not that you're my No, no, no, no,
no. It's not that you're not my cup of
tea at all. No, no, no, no, no, no. You
know what it is? It's I don't I'm not
like Laura Jay. I'm not a s. I don't
simp women on YouTube. Let me Let me Let
me explain this to you. You're going to
believe this or you're not going to
believe this. I don't speak to any woman
unless I've met them. Nat can pop my
cherry. I've had more sex than you will
ever have. You little virgin. Go
self-reflect on another channel. Like I
said, you people are the only ones that
are fat, ugly virgins on this community.
No one else. That's why you can't get
off of YouTube and get a life. Anyways,
um I don't speak to any women that I've
not met. Natalie, believe it or don't
believe it. All of the women that I
speak to are people that I've met
personally and I don't speak to them on
Instagram. It's only
WhatsApp because I'm not a simp like
Lord Jay. Yeah. A simp little [ __ ]
weirdo. So, yeah. So, I'm not going to
say, "Oh, oh, Natalie, meet me. Meet me.
I want to bang you. Oh, meet me. Oh, I
don't speak to no one, bro, that that I
haven't met in real life." Like I said,
if you come to London, come to London.
Simple. That's all I'm saying. I'm not
here to simp over people, bro. That's not
me. Yeah, of course you will. Yeah, of
course you will, Virgin. You know, the
thing is, Tiger, I was going to come on
your door that day. You know that? You
know, when I was last in Birmingham, I
was going to come on your door, but you
lived in some awkward place and I had to
spend like £30 for an Uber. So, I
thought, nah, [ __ ] it. I was actually
going to go on your door. If you lived
in the city center, that was the last
time I went to Birmingham when I had
that day. I was going to come on your
[ __ ] door. I was actually going to
come on your door. You know, you had to
get about four buses to get to where you
were. I looked it up. I was like, "Let
me go in this [ __ ] store." Yeah. Let me
knock on this little faggot's door.
Weirdo. Yeah. But I was like, I had a
date that day. Do you remember the date
I went on? It's still on my channel. So,
I thought, [ __ ] it in it. I'm not
spending 30 pound for it.
Yeah. And I wouldn't have needed backup
either, so I just allowed it. So, yeah.
Natalie, why don't you come to London
anyways? You ain't been to London for a long
time. To be fair, I like to go out with
someone else now, you know, cuz it's
easier to get in
places. I prefer going out by myself
approaching, but it's good to have
somebody with you because
like, you know, it helps you get in
places and stuff. That's the only
thing. But I like
um But I don't bang people anyways. I
don't I don't bang people. I just get
[ __ ] You can't get no one laid.
You're a virgin. How can How can the two
virgins of YouTube get me laid? How can
two virgins get me laid? Tiger, that
doesn't even make
sense. Who's that Py, mate? Uh he's not
PY firstly. Um, and just some guy and
he's not a
packy. And why would it matter if he
was, but he's not. So,
yeah. Um, yeah. The two virgins of
Birmingham that's never been seen with
women are going to get me laid. That' be
some good content, is it? That would be
some great content. The two Virgin
Marys, the Spackers, are going to get me
laid, but they can't even get laid
themselves. I think I I'd be charging
for that, bro. I'd be charging5 pound a
ticket for anyone that wants to see
that. That'd be some good content, is it,
Natie? You know, we will get your ride.
Don't you sick of getting I've never
been rejected as much as you ugly
people, mate. I've never been rejected
as much as you ugly people on YouTube.
Trust me, not as much as you ugly
people. Remember, Tiger, I'm out on the
road. I'm out on the road.
That is a desperate virgin that's never
had nothing. Bro, do you think I would
ever send a woman me putting f two
fingers in between my mouth licking?
That is some desperate virgin birth. I'm
telling you right there. Never ever ever
have I ever had to resort to anything so
desperate like that. [ __ ] hell. You
really are a virgin, mate.
You really, really, really are [ __ ]
Could you imagine Tiger in London approaching someone? [ __ ]
hell. It's crazy,
bro. It's crazy, isn't
it? I'm going to come off this community
for a bit after today, I reckon. What's
the day? Tomorrow, Monday. Call it a
weekend. Yeah. Yeah, you can stay on
this community for a couple of days, but
you can't stay on it every day, bro.
It's because it's just the same
spastics, same atmosphere. They start
frying your [ __ ] brain, bro. These
people start frying your [ __ ] brain,
lad, the longer you stay on talking to
these spastics. I swear to
God. But you know what's so mad is that
I'm not scared to say what I I I I think
about women and I don't lick I don't
lick women's asses. And you and you and
you give me [ __ ] about it. Yeah. But
I've still had more women than any of
you. And that's not even me just saying
it to say, "Oh, like what?" So, because
I don't lick women's asses, that means
I've never had a woman. Bro, there's
women on my channel, on my main channel
that I have been
with. But because I'm not scared of
saying what I think, you think like it
it's mad, bro. Then what does that say
about you then? If I'm looking the way I
am and I'm getting rejected and I've had
more women than you, what does that say about you
people? That's what I'm
saying. Just cuz I'm not a [ __ ] s
that licks women's asses, [ __ ]
embarrassing. Arrison as [ __ ]
Yeah, maybe I get KFC today. Actually, I don't know.
I was thinking Chinese,
but probably get KFC to be
fair. Good old
KFC. Good old
KFC. How does this person know this
woman? I'm thinking I can find this Tam
guy, but it's it's too hard, bro.
It's too hard to find this. How does
this person know this person? Right. If
anyone can find this tab in Glasgow, I
will give away
£500. You're never going to find a
[ __ ] So, I know there's some proper stalkers on
here. Yeah, I know, right? Yeah. Yeah.
Self-reflection doesn't get you anywhere, David.
Listen, Dave. Who's the one that's been
seen with women and who's the one that hasn't? Remember
that. And your life is YouTube. Who's
the one that's been seen with women and
who's the one that's not been seen with
women? Tam is a guy that I met last year from
Glasgow. We had a bit of an argument and
because I got my phone robbed and I lost
his number, I don't know where to find
him. But I know he I know he's from
Glasgow. He's a Celtic
fan. Dave Everett, who's the one that's
been seen with women and who
hasn't? So if any Yeah, I've been trying
to find him, but I can't find him.
Steven Howard, I don't think I'd ever
find him. I hate that, man. I hate
people that get away. I hate it, man. I
hate [ __ ] like that. [ __ ] Scottish prick. Yeah. God,
if No, I just want to find him, man.
Just to be his
friend. He didn't do anything. I just
want to be his mate.
Yeah, I'm a nasty little virgin. That's
not nice to talk about yourself like
that. It's not nice to call yourself a virgin,
Ev. That's not nice to call yourself a
virgin. You see, these people don't
bother me, Steven Howard, because they
just talk about
themselves. That's why they don't bother
me, man. Because they seem to have this
they have a habit of coming on YouTube
every day talking about themselves.
talking about their own
lives. You're incredibly skinn. You said
you get 3K. You are not on 700 a freak
seekers. I talk behavior because you
hate people getting away. Uh Sean, I
showed you over a grand on Friday and
you you ran away. Remember in the pub I
showed £1,100 bum change and you went running
away. Uh I don't have £500. I just
showed you £1,100.
Stop calling yourself skimp. It's not
nice. It's not nice to call yourself
skimp, buddy, because you got showed
£1,100 and you went running away when I
was night clubbing in London. The only
skin one is
yourself. The only skint one is you rat
face. I know, bro. Bro, I even said
that. No, no, no, no, no, no. I even
said that. No, I am obsessed with you,
Sean. Yeah, I'm very obsessed with you,
man. Of course I'm obsessed with you.
It's not like you've got a whole channel
dedicated to me. You can't go one day
without posting about me. Yeah, I know.
Yeah, you have never showed £14,000 ever
in your life. No, you [ __ ] have not.
You've shown £14,000. Go and show it now
then. Show it now then. No, you have.
Listen, Sean, you got shown £6,000 and
you went running away. You got shown
over £1,000 yesterday. You went running
away. Why do you pretend that you've got
money? You are the skinniest person I
know. Okay, let's go through some
things. No designer clothes. You live in
a bedsit. You got no bed. You shop in a
charity shop. You got no passport.
You've never been abroad. You've never
left England. Mate, everything about you
screams skin. Nothing in your house is worth over
£1,000. You're a skint flint on a grand
a month. You're a skint flint on a grand
a month. But somehow you expect us to
believe that you're some billionaire. Oh,
okay. Yeah, I have a girlfriend. Yeah,
guess what? Sean's jealous of all of the
women that I've been with. Morgan and
Izzy. Jennis that he's got a disabled
girlfriend. No, thank you. All of the
women I've been with are not flat like
he's ugly disabled girlfriend. He's
jealous of all of the women that I've
been with. The jealousy. Every single
day he talks about Morgan and Izzy.
Yeah. Dave Everett, stop reflecting. You
and Sha are both virgins that can't get
nothing. Stop self-reflecting your fat
virgin lives onto me, mate. Yeah, I'm
jealous that he's got an ugly
girlfriend, mate. I've been had more
women than him. Women that he can't get
out of his head. I don't care about his
fat, ugly girlfriend who he's never
shagged. Okay, go and do it then.
£3,000. Go and do it, mate. Show us his
£3,000. Go on. Show us his £3,000. Guess
what? Do you know the difference between
you and Do you know the the same thing
Dave and and Sean? You're both virgins.
You're both ugly and you're all skin.
You're self-reflectctors. Everything you
type is about your own life. You do not
have no free grand. Show us it. Show us
your money, rat boy. I've been asking
you since Friday to show us your money.
You're skint. Listen, that money rat
face, that little bum change that you
showed the other day was your housing
benefit that you got from the government
that you need to pay your rent. You are
a sad, lonely virgin. We know you are.
Stop talking about yourself. Yep. Stop
talking about yourself, fat boy. Fat
virgin. We know you are. You cannot
amount. You cannot withdraw that amount
from a cash machine. Oh, well, go to the
bank tomorrow then. Go to the bank
tomorrow and show us your free grand.
You ain't got no free grand, you little
skin fin. And Dave, stop calling
yourself a lonely virgin. It's not doing
your mental health any good. You talking
about yourself, it's affecting your
mental health talking about yourself
every day. You know, it's not nice to
talk about yourself like
that. O rat face, where's your money,
rat face? You and your fat ugly
girlfriend. I got more money than you
and your fat ugly
girlfriend. Come on. Come on. Show us
your money. Anyways, you're boring now.
Go self-reflect on another
channel. Come on. No. Come on. I want to
see the color of your money, rat face.
Come on, rat boy. Come on, rat boy. With
no teeth. You and your fat ugly
girlfriend who don't give you no sex.
You got erectile dysfunction. You've
never shag Shar, bro. Why do you think
you're on YouTube every day stalking me?
Cuz Sarah don't give you no sex. You're
still a [ __ ] virgin. I I was watching
your video. Yeah. where you was talking
about erectile dysfunction. Mate, you've
had it your whole life. It's why you'll
die a virgin. I've been saying this to
you for [ __ ] ages. You and your fat
ugly girlfriend. I got more money than
both of you. I get more money combined
than you and your fat ugly girlfriend.
Your fat ugly girlfriend. Woo. How's
that? How's that one? Hello. Come on,
rat boy. Okay. Can I ask you this
question then? If you've got all of this
money, why have you got why? Oh, this is
not even on. Why have you got no
passport? Why have you never been
abroad? Why have you never left England?
And why do you live in a bedsit? If
you've got all of this money, why are
you living in poverty? Let me ask you
this question. Okay. Okay. You've got
all this money. All jokes aside now,
right? You don't have sex. I don't think
I know. Three years, bro. You're on
YouTube every single day. Um, you was on
you you're on YouTube every single day
stalking me. Yes, you've been with a
[ __ ] for three years and you're still
a virgin. Yes, that's exactly what I'm
saying. And you will die a virgin. Yes,
that is exactly what I am saying. I'm in
a shared accommodation. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. You say that you have
got all this money. You got no designer
clothes. You've got no assets. You've
got no savings. You live in poverty.
Nope. You got a [ __ ] clothes, no
passport, you've never been abroad, and
you got no assets. Sounds like a grand a
month to me. That sounds like a grand a
month to me. Now, me, I can tell you
what I've got. Just renew my passport.
I've got about £10,000 worth in clothes.
I've got savings. I've been abroad. I've
been all over England. I go out almost
every week pissing it up. See the
difference? £1,000 a month, boy. £1,000
a month, boy. Do you see the difference?
It doesn't matter if you It doesn't
matter about designer clothes or not.
I'm I'm using that as an example. You know, you
know, I'm using it as an example. All
the food I've ate, I've had 100 pound
steaks. You literally live in a bedsit
in your virgin area of Orington. You sit
on that virgin bedsit and you got
nothing. You literally have [ __ ] all.
You literally have nothing. You've got
nothing. You know what I'm saying? You
got nothing but a virgin [ __ ] bed sit
with no [ __ ] bed in it. You [ __ ]
virgin [ __ ] on a grand a month. That's
literally all you have. Because if
somebody had all this money, they'd have
they'd have something to show for it.
Would wouldn't they have something to
show for it? Look at my channel. Look at
all of what I have done. But this [ __ ]
on a grand a month sits in his virgin
bed sit all day with his fat ugly
girlfriend, not getting no sex. No sex. No [ __ ]
sex. You don't have money. Okay. How
much money do you get a month? Okay.
Okay. How much money do you get a
month? How much money do you get a month? Come
on. Tell us how much money you get a month. Come
on. And you was trying to say that I
said I get a grand a month. I've
literally never said I've got a grand a
month. Never said I got a grand a month.
I said I get over three grand a month,
which is not a grand a week. Sorry.
Sorry. I said I never get I I've never
said that I had a grand a week. But I
know I got more money than you and it
kills you. Woohoo. That's what somebody
said to me before. They said to me,
"You're better looking than them. You
got more money and it kills them." Yeah.
Come on. for the longest time as well.
You don't have more money than me, mate.
I showed you,00 bum chains on Friday,
rodent face, you [ __ ] ugly [ __ ] And
you couldn't show me nothing. You don't
have more money than me. You don't have
more money than me. Not in the past and
you still don't now. You have got no
money, bro. Shut the [ __ ] up. Yeah. How
much do you get a month? I get more than
you, mate. And I'm not a skinned little
virgin in living in Kent. Living in
Kent. And I've got Listen, I've been
abroad. I've got a passport. Yeah. I'm
not some [ __ ] Kent virgin in a
bedsit. You see the difference? You see
the difference? Am I a Kent virgin in a
bedsit like you with no passport? Never
left the country. Never left the
country. Your skin. How the [ __ ] can you
be 30 years of age? Still a [ __ ]
virgin. Never left the country, no
passport, no assets, but you've got all
this money. But the virgin claims that
he's got all this money. Something is
not adding up. Something is not adding
up. This little lanky string of piss
little virgin claims that he's got all
this money yet he's never been abroad.
No assets. Lives in a
bedset, no teeth, but he's got all this
money. [ __ ] hell, mate. Well, let me
tell you something. If you've got all
this money, you might as well be living
in [ __ ] poverty cuz you're still a
[ __ ] virgin and you'll die one.
You'll [ __ ] die a virgin, mate. You
could be married to a [ __ ] You could
be married to a [ __ ] for 5 years and
you would still die a virgin. You will
still be a virgin because you can't get
it up. Do you not understand? Your
little dick, your little autistic dick
don't go up. Nothing. If you go on this
morning, there's a guy with no penis.
There's a guy with no penis and he's got
a woman. Does he have sex? He lost his
penis due to penis cancer. You're going
to die a virgin. You're going to do
what? Do you do you think I want to see
you 30 years of age die and still being
a virgin? Still having no woman. Do you
really? Come on, Sean. I used to meet
you all the time, I don't want you to
die a virgin. As much as I hate you, I
don't want you to die a virgin. And no
one cares about this plastic ugly
girlfriend that you've had for 3 years.
Yeah, you're going to die a [ __ ]
virgin. Isn't there more important
things than that? Yeah, you've got a
woman, but you've got a woman, but but
you're on YouTube every day stalking me.
You're on a YouTube, you're on YouTube
every day stalking me. So, she's not
doing anything for you. She's not giving
you sex. That's why you can't get Morgan
out your head. That's why you can't get
Izzy out your head. Because I shagged
him and no one's ever shagged you,
Virgin. Mate, let me tell you something.
Yeah. The only the only reason she's
with you is because she's too vulnerable
to leave you because she's not like a
normal woman that needs needs. You know,
she's not like a normal a man that has
needs. She's a [ __ ] So, it's not
like she's going to leave you anytime
soon. Even though you're not [ __ ]
her, you think I'd be with someone I
don't sleep with. Sean, you don't have a
choice. You can't get a normal woman.
So, yes, you would be with somebody that
you don't sleep with because you can't
get a normal woman. You have no choice. You've got
autism. So you would have no choice but
to stay with a woman whether she's
giving you something or not. You can't
Sean, you don't even have normal
friends. You don't even have normal
friends, virgin boy. You know, that's
why you go about Morgan and Izzy cuz
you're a jealous [ __ ] who's never had it
yourself. So yes, you would be with
somebody that that don't sleep with you
cuz your virgin ass can't function in
normal environments. So, who else are
you going to get
with? Who else are you going to get
with? Who else you going to be with? You
can't get a normal woman. You little
virgin. Anyways, you're block, buddy.
You're boring me
now. You know. Yeah. I'm not letting
that virgin on. So, stop telling me to
let that little [ __ ] virgin on. I'm
not letting him on. [ __ ] off. Tell him
to meet me in real life and then I'll let him on. Yeah.
[ __ ] let that [ __ ] virgin on. I'm
not letting that [ __ ] virgin on. [ __ ] off. Oh
[ __ ] No, I've done it enough times
where he's not even worth it. He's not
entertaining. The [ __ ] little [ __ ]
I I don't even know why I was talking
about him. He's not even worth talking
about, bro. Yeah, I'm done with him anyways. [ __ ]
virgin. Little keyboard warrior, bro.
[ __ ] that. Nah, I'm good,
bro. [ __ ] hell. That's stupid to
these people's levels. Jesus Christ.
[ __ ] what I was doing for 10 minutes.
But I made my point anyways. You get what I'm
saying? You asked me that yesterday.
Brain damaged. I think you got brain
damage, bro. Cuz I already told you
yesterday. I think you've got brain
damage. You asked me the same question
yesterday and I answered
it. I literally I've already answered your
question. I think you got brain damage
delayed. But anyways, I'm going to I'm
going to be live today anyways a bit
later than I've done for um a little
while, bro. Because yeah, same spastics.
You can only stay on here for like two
days maximum. Then you start losing
brain cells like these spastics, these
[ __ ] mongos. I can't get off of YouTube. Little
self-reflectors. But I'll definitely be
live again later. And then tomorrow is a
new week and then I'm done for a few
weeks. You won't see me for a couple of
delayed. You have to take breaks of this
[ __ ] bro, because you end up like these
spastics if you don't. Same [ __ ] repeating bastards.
me. How much I get a [ __ ] mouth? Oh
[ __ ] You've never shown £14,000 in your [ __ ] life, mate.
Yeah. Nothing ever changes on it ever, does it?
Yeah, I know what I need to do. I think
that's the I think that's the most I
think that's the most sensible thing you actually
said. Of course, I need to [ __ ] off to
Thailand, bro. No [ __ ]
Sherlock. Yeah, no [ __ ] Sherlock.
[ __ ] hell, bro. Why do you think I
got my passport
me? You don't need to wait until you're
30, 31, bro. You know what this country
is like. You know what this shit's about. you
know, like I think I'll be meeting
Ant-Man soon in a couple weeks when he
comes back. But
yeah, yeah, Thailand's the place, bro.
And it's not even just about the women.
It's, do you know, you know, places like
Thailand, it's not even just about the
women. It's the whole culture. Damn's
banned. The weather's nice. Everything's
cheap. Cheaper. Well, cheaper than
England. It's not as cheap as it used to
be, though. Right.
It's in England. It's just I find with
this country. Yeah. It's just it's just
all a double negative. [ __ ] weather,
[ __ ] women, gambling. Gambling's legal.
Um [ __ ] government. Like it's just
everything in this country. I hate this
country. The only good thing about this
country, yeah, I'll tell you the only
good thing about this country, I tell
you now, is the sentences are lenient.
Like when you get caught by police and
that like the sentences are lenient. But
mate, this country sucks dick. The women
are [ __ ] They've all got attitude
problems. Even when you're not trying to
pursue them, the weather [ __ ] [ __ ]
Gambon should be banned or at least not
have that many bookies in one place.
It's just all a negative. It's not even
just women, bro. It's amalgamation of
things. This country sucks dick.
What I'm probably going to do is I'm
probably going to give it one last hurra on a
Saturday and then I'm out of it, bro. I
still have my passport by then as well.
Maybe a few weeks, a month,
whatever. And then I will have one last
one one last hurrah, you
know, and then that's me. I'm done,
bro. Could you imagine that? Sending it
all day on a Saturday. [ __ ] you now.
Well, we're in March now anyway. So,
what's it what we second of March? Yeah.
Give it one last hurrah.
Lols. Just give it one last
hurrah. What do you think of that? One
last hurrah. Yeah.
Yeah, one last.
No, Benador is not okay because Benadorm
is just full of English people.
Nope. No, it's not okay cuz it's just
full of English people, westernized
[ __ ] So, it's not it's not
good. It's not good, bro.
I might fly to get this phone
unlocked. It isn't, mate. It's full of
English people. I remember Ant-Man told
me he went to Benador and they said they
had boyfriends there,
too. They said that they had boyfriends
there, too, in Benador cuz they're obviously
English. So, it's Thailand you need to
go. I think we'll do a few countries. I
think we'll do that by We'll do
Thailand. We'll do America again.
Doesn't matter if there's fitties in
Benador, mate. They've all got
boyfriends, so they
say. They've all got boyfriends, apparently.
Yeah. Yeah. They're all up for it. What?
In Spain or they Yeah, right. Oh, they
[ __ ] all up for it in Spain, mate. Is
that before or after they tell you that
they got a boyfriend? [ __ ] out of here,
mate. There's only one place that works
and that's Asia. And I know that for a
fact cuz I've seen people go there. I've
I don't like how Thai girls looks, but
in time in terms of the only place
working is Thailand. Well, Asia, it
could be anywhere in Asia. It don't even
need to be Thailand. The only continent
that works is Asia. Nothing else
works. So, there's no Spain, there's no
Italy, there's no no Sweden. They're all
[ __ ] Oh, South America is good as
well. Yeah, Brazil. Brazil. Brazil's
good. Yeah, but it's Yeah, Brazil.
Brazil's good. I've been with some
Brazilian women. That's easier. Yeah.
Nope. Not Australia. It's a westernized
country. Nope. Australia doesn't work. It's
westernized. South America does.
Yeah. Uh, it's a lot easier. Yeah. South
America, Asia, that's the only place
that work. Australia doesn't work. It's
westernized. Why would Australia work?
Australia is the same the same women
here. You get the same women in
Australia. I approached an Australian last
week. These westernized countries do not
work. It doesn't matter what country it is. [ __ ]
Australia. Right. Tell me in these
hangouts. Yeah. I'm going to join these
hangouts. Can you tell them to let me in?
doesn't let anyone talk. He just blocks
people. Yep. He doesn't let anyone talk.
He won't even let anyone talk. He's a
[ __ ] [ __ ] He's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
He doesn't let no one talk. See, there's no point.
There's no [ __ ] point. Yeah, there's
no [ __ ] point,
lad. He just doesn't let anyone talk.
What's the point of letting somebody in
when you're just going to kick them?
It's stupid as [ __ ] bro. You
know? Yeah. But you know what's so funny
is that the people that you're talking
to are the same people that got social
services involved. They're the same
people that got social services
involved. Isn't that funny? Yeah, yeah,
yeah. Apparently, I'm a pedo. I didn't
know I was a pedo. That's interesting. But yeah,
Romania, I don't know where, but these
westernized countries don't
work. None of these westernized
countries work. I said to Ant-Man, go to
Dubai and do some approaches in Dubai.
He said that you know it's not going to
work. He said that you know Dubai is not
going to work. That's what he said. I
said no man you go to
Dubai. Go to Dubai
man. Yeah go to the
buy. He's like yeah I told him to go to Dubai bro. [Laughter]
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I told him to go to
Dubai. Yeah, he's weird, bro. He does.
He just keeps kicking
me. Yeah, [ __ ] Monty. He's by himself
now. Anyways, I don't give a [ __ ] man.
Anyways, I'm gone. I'll be back later.
Yeah. Peace. I'm out of here.