Yo yo
I don't think these skinny little bongos
will ever get off the YouTuber.
Think it's all they have
to have their little YouTube.
[ __ ] hell though. These people
[ __ ] asleep for YouTube
again that sub. They ain't got nothing
but yelp. So all these little mongos
have that in their little lives. It's YouTube.
Guess they skip ones all along. Yeah.
You can't get off of YouTube.
Can't get off of YouTube.
That's all they have.
Best them then if they've only got YouTube.
I can't be YouTube.
these people be able to get off of
YouTube if they weren't skinned in a
line. They then tried to call other people
with their little self little self projectors.
The little self-reflectors that can't
get off of YouTube.
Oh my god, Timmy's bad. It's just the
same [ __ ] on here.
Same [ __ ] every day, is it?
Same [ __ ] same people every day. Yeah, man.
So why can't you
So why can't you people get off of your job?
Why can't you little mongos get off of your job?
Just a little question from Peter Belly.
Why can't you get off YouTube?
I see the same people every day.
Every [ __ ] day, mate. Yeah, man.
So, why can't you people get off of YouTube?
imagine you just walked into that whole thing.
[ __ ] me, bro. Could you imagine you just
walked into that whole thing? That would be jokes.
They'd probably all like jump you or something.
That'd be funny, man.
That would be [ __ ] hilarious. No sh.
No, it's cinema day. I was thinking
about my mommy yesterday, Nicola. I was
talking to LT
and Yeah, man. It got brought up.
Mommy's not on YouTube anymore. I was
thinking about my mama.
Look at my mama put a new picture up
with all her um uni
um uni colleagues
and I was just thinking imagine you just
walked into that place like imagine
randomly you just walked into that place
where she's there with like 15 other
people. How awkward would that be, Nicolo?
How [ __ ] awkward would that be? Huh?
That would be like so that would be like
so awkward, isn't it? I found my nick and I nothing m
quite late last night.
I was thinking of my mama Joe and I see
that she's put um up a new picture. I
was speaking on the phone to LT
and my mama come up
and um yeah, she put a new picture up
with her little colleagues and I was
just saying to Nicolo, "What would have
happened if you walked in?" Like, say
you you just randomly walked in and
they're there with all of them colleagues.
They would have got their ass whipped.
Yeah, it' be funny, wouldn't it?
That's why I I couldn't listen to Monty
for too long because it's like it's
bringing it all back. You know, the
other day, right, when Monty was um
when Monty was uh talking No, he wasn't,
man. He's all right. He's a pretty good [ __ ]
And um when me and Monty was um when we
met and he kept going on about it, it's
not good, you know, man, cuz it's like
it's like you're reliving it. your, you
know, your problems.
Yeah. They be like, "What the [ __ ] is
going on, is it?" You'd probably get ambushed,
wouldn't you, Nicolo? You'd probably get ambushed.
Nah, not today. I would have called my
mama a couple of weeks ago. A couple of Nah,
she's a [ __ ] horrible old [ __ ] She is.
She's a [ __ ] horrible old [ __ ]
That Indonesian guy messaged me
yesterday asking me if he was ugly. I
said, "What the [ __ ] you asking me
stupid questions for, dickhead?"
I said, "Are you insecure?
Have I done dating in this country?
Pretty much. Yeah, man. I mean, none of
their numbers reply back from London, so
I've only got the Birmingham numbers
now. But after that, yeah, I'm pretty
much done, bro. I didn't I mean, like I
keep saying, I only met Monty um last week because
he was crying. I said I was going to go.
I won a football bet. I would have hit
the last of it. So, yeah, bro. I pretty
much I pretty much am done to be fair.
What's the point of staying in a country
where people are not interested?
No, they [ __ ] won't put out. I was
there last [ __ ] week. They said they
had [ __ ] boyfriends.
No, they [ __ ] don't. And another
thing is um but I got some nummies that
replied, so I'll try one I'll try with
them. And if that doesn't work, then
yeah, why am I going to stay in a
country where people aren't interested?
When you can go [ __ ] Cambodia,
[ __ ] Thailand, Philippines, and you
can just go on a dating app and find
someone. Why am I going to stay in a
country where people aren't interested?
I've more than proved my point.
Obviously, I've still got them Brummy
numbers, but in terms of the London
ones, none of them reply back.
So what's the point of staying in a
country where people aren't interested
when you can actually go to a country
like Ant-Man where they are interested
and you don't have to deal with none of this [ __ ]
It's a no-brainer really.
Even that USA thing, I was thinking
about that yesterday, bro. It was
[ __ ] pissing me off again
before I went to sleep. It's annoying,
bro. It is. It is annoying, man. Proper
proper [ __ ] annoying. Just something
to add on, you know.
Nah, I'm good, bro. I don't need new
numbers. I've proved my point more than
enough. I'm going to cinema today
anyways. And I need to go walk the dog.
So, bro, I'm not interested.
I'm done. We're beyond that now. We are
We are far beyond it. You know, I've
I've I've proved my point multiple
times. I didn't even want to talk to
women last week. It's only because I
went to Birmingham to see Monty. Bro,
we're beyond that now. That we're beyond that. Seriously.
So yeah, basically what I was saying is
that we're beyond that.
We're beyond that, lad.
Look at USA Izzy's new picture.
That's my mama. The first one's my mama.
Look at my mama. Yeah, I would have
probably got [ __ ] ambushed.
Well, like I said, no one no one should
feel sorry for her, though. To be
honest, I was saying this to LT on the
phone yesterday. You play with fire, you
get burnt. You know that that that's
what happens. You know, it happens to everyone.
You know that, you know, eventually they
meet their match and [ __ ] So, it's like
people shouldn't feel bad. You want to
be a [ __ ] even though it's life. Yeah,
we get it's life. But don't don't cry
when you know when when someone stands
up for themselves.
Do you know what I'm saying, bro?
You'd probably get [ __ ] ambushed.
That's how I That's how I see it, bro. Yeah, man.
No, she's not. She's moving to Miami.
No, that was the last picture. She's in Miami now.
[ __ ] my eye, bro.
Actually, she's actually moved. Oh, the
[ __ ] Virgin went live about me
yesterday, Nicolo. I swear to God, but I
was watching some of it and I was
laughing my [ __ ] ass off. I was
messaging I was messaging Monty about
it. Yeah, I was laughing my [ __ ] ass
off, bro. I think all the neighbors
heard me. I said, "Shit, is this
supposed to trigger me or something?"
It was actually hilarious. Some little
ratfaced [ __ ] balded lanky smelly
[ __ ] is going on about me. I was pissing
myself laughing. I was like, "What the
fuck?" Yeah, I was laughing my ass off,
bro. Is that Was that supposed to get me
angry or something? It was [ __ ] hilarious.
He's something to laugh at. Like him him
reacting to me like he does on his
channel is is is something to laugh at.
His hairline's getting worse as well.
Have you noticed? Jesus Christ.
Have you noticed his [ __ ] hairline's
getting worse? He's [ __ ] He's almost bald ears. [ __ ] virgin.
How do you How are you so skinny but got
a double chin? I don't understand that.
I really don't understand that.
Jeez. Yeah. Yeah. And guess what? It's
the same cash that he's been sewing for
like a year. I want to see 10 grand, not
some shitty £1,000.
I literally want to see £10,000
which I've literally been asking for
now, Nicolo, for the past [ __ ]
um year and a half. That's not flashing
the cash. What's showing £1,000?
You think I can't go and [ __ ] show
over £1,000 right now? That ain't
flashing no cash. What's showing you
benefit money that you've been showing
for about a month, about a year? That
ain't no [ __ ] cash, mate.
I want to see 10 [ __ ] grand what I've
been [ __ ] asking for [ __ ] year.
[ __ ] no one cares about a shitty,000, bro.
Believe that. So everything he done
yesterday just made me laugh. It's
actually quite funny.
You think showing £1,000 is flashing the cash?
Where it stands? I've I've won the money
game. See, this is what these people do.
Nicolo, right? They say this is how what
they do. Yeah. Let's play the money
game. Let's play the money game. Let's
play the money game. So then what what
happens is you show them money. Then
they don't show you anything. Like say
you have say you've won, I don't know.
I don't know. Let's just say that you
won £3,000 right now. Let's play the
money game. Let's play the money game.
You show them £3,000.
None of them show anything cuz it's all
skin. And then in a month you think,
"Oh, maybe I want to book a holiday.
Maybe I want to spend some money." So we
got a whole month, a whole two months of
them not showing nothing. And then after
they'll show you half of what you've
shown and act like they've won. They do
it every single time, bro. They all like
I have beat them in the money game
multiple multiple multiple times. And
all they do is show nothing. And as soon
as you book a holiday or you put money
in a bank or you buy some garments, you
don't have the cash, they'll show you
half. That's what they do, bro. It's the
same [ __ ] with these people. They've
been doing it for [ __ ] They've been
doing it for [ __ ] donkeys years,
mate, on here, you know?
I'm still I've still not been beaten.
I've still not been beaten at the money game.
Oh, look. My mommy put a new picture up
um yesterday. Grezy,
look at my mama.
She's about to go to Miami. My mama.
No, it's a little picture. It's my mama.
Yeah, that is that's his housing
benefit. Why does he keep showing the same £1,1200?
It's weird, isn't it? Jesus Christ. He's [ __ ] skinting flint.
You skinted in the [ __ ] skint flint, Nicolo.
He's [ __ ] skint. Yeah, that's my mama
bey. Do you like my mama? So, yeah.
Good night, my mama.
Yeah. And then packed it up in it. And
then she packed the chat up. She says, "You motherfucker."
I said to LT, "Could you possibly get us
back together?" He said that ship has
sailed. I said, "No, go on. I'll give
you a I'll do a football bet for you and
I'll give you a football bet that we'll win."
I said, "If you can get us back talking
again." And he was like, "I think that
ship has sailed.
There's no going back now."
He said, "You messaged her dad.
You know, you messaged the old Syrian."
And he doesn't he doesn't need that kind
of [ __ ] in his life at that age. Grezy,
he wants peace, you know. Oh, the old
Syrian man wants some peace. You know,
that's what people want at that age. A
bit of peace.
You know what I mean?
He said, I think that ship has sailed.
Yeah. Has that ship sailed, Gregy? I
don't think so. [Laughter] Oh, mate.
You know what I should do? Yeah. I
should I should wear that Chucky costume
and then go to Miami and go to the university. Nikolai. Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] No. No. It's not sinking
battleship. It's I'll light up your
I'll [ __ ] go there and light up her
battleship. I wear the Chucky costume in
it. Imagine that.
Want to play. [Laughter]
Bless you. No, he never said sinking
battleship. He said I'll light up your
All right. That Indonesian guy is such a
coward. He said, "Oh, I didn't approach
when I was with you." "Yeah, you done an
approach when you was with me over a month ago."
Then he's asking me if he's ugly. What the [ __ ]
This guy's a coward, bro. He's a [ __ ] coward. Yep. Yeah.
Yeah. The Miami Uni. Yeah.
You like it down here, son. You never
have to grow up.
What do you think of the Chucky um outfit?
Easy. Should I get it? £22. Yeah,
I'm thinking of getting it, bro. I'm going there with it.
Yeah, but she's going to call the police on me.
Yeah, she's going to call the police on me, though.
Yeah, but my mommy's going to get me
arrested. I'm thinking of going like this.
Yeah, she's still under that number, by
the way, because I called it a couple of
weeks ago and she's like, "Hello." I
said, "Go and suck your mother."
Go and suck your mother. That's what I said. Yeah. Ah.
Yeah. Go on, Halloween.
Yeah, but my mommy doesn't want to speak
to me anymore, Nicolo.
So why would I?
I've already got Sig as well, Nicolo. I
can Sig's my mommy, isn't she? Yeah.
It's your lucky day.
You got to go to the university with the
do like a video of it in it. Yeah. Yeah.
But I I can I've got a new mama. Nicolo Sig.
What about Sig? Sig's my mommy, isn't she? Yeah.
Stigler was never.
Yeah. Yeah, but Sig breastfed me.
Yeah, but Sig Yeah, but Sig breastfed
me, so she had to be s not Peter Belly's mother.
You're not my mommy.
Yuck. Yuck. You're not my mama. Yuck.
Yuck. You're my mommy. Ain't it?
Peter belly can't get attached anymore
because he's already found his mama.
It was never your mother.
That was you that said that. Is it?
Yeah, that was you that said that.
But why would I go there though? Cuz my
mommy's not going to speak to me, Nicolo.
If my mommy back, my mommy went back to
get away from me.
I know this is you. No, she said, I know
this is you because I have your number
saved. You are sick. You are sick and
twisted, [ __ ] Get some help.
Yeah, I will be blocking you again. Yeah.
I know. She know. She said, "Oh my god,
get a life. I know this is you."
It's funny, isn't it? Yeah. Yeah, man. Jesus, bro.
Yeah, I was thinking about the one night
stand I had with her yesterday. It was quite nice.
It's so nice to have someone give you attention,
even if it's just for a couple of hours. Nikolai,
she's bad, man.
You know, actually, Miami is actually
cheaper to go to,
but that is actually a place I would
actually be scared of going. Bro, you
get shot there, bro. You would get shot there.
Maybe I'll write the poem in person, Nick. Nic,
it's not like I want to be with a person
or I want to do anything with them
again. I just I just need my mommy back.
It's like, you know, have you ever
watched long-lost families where they go
and they find their mama? Boring.
Boring. Bro, you just killed the vibe, man.
No jokes. That's so boring.
Oh, you killed it.
You killed it, man. You just literally
killed the vibe.
Same jokes. Boring.
Boring. My nose ain't even big, bro.
Come and come and show your face. You
can't. You're an ugly [ __ ]
I noticed that. Yeah. You people that
try to talk about my nose, you're all [ __ ] rotten.
like [ __ ] nons legs. He's a [ __ ]
ugly bastard. Ugly rat [ __ ] rodent
face. Skinny. He talks about my [ __ ] doggy.
But no, I'm just trying to get my mummy
back. But that is actually a state that
I'm actually scared. Well, a city in
this in the state that I'm actually
scared of getting killed in, bro.
Cuz they'll just [ __ ] shoot you
there, mate. And they won't give a [ __ ]
But I guess it'll be worth it if I find
if I find my mama Nol. I'm saying
never be your mama.
Yeah. Step mama in it. Yeah.
I tell you about you people keep coming
on trolling me. No,
but I don't think my mommy wants to see me again
because she put me up for adoption
obviously for a reason.
So you don't put a child up, you don't
abandon a child and then want to see the
child again, you know, you want to get
rid of the baby. All right. Yeah.
Oh, you're still talking about that,
bro. But listen, listen, listen, listen.
You can't even use that anymore, bro.
Because guess what? I called that guy
out last week and he was nowhere to be
seen. So bro, you can't even use that
anymore. Cuz I was in his actual city
last week calling his [ __ ] ass out and
he was nowhere to be seen. So bro, you
can't even use that anymore. That's why
people don't even bring it up anymore.
He showed his true colors when I was
actually in his city and he did not come
out. Same as Timmy, same as Prime. So
like that, you can't even use that
anymore. Yeah, someone caught me off
guard two years ago. Two and a half
years ago, someone caught me off guard.
Oh, whipped [ __ ] woo, bro. But have
you ever heard of something called a re
match, a rematch, which was last week,
and he didn't come out. So you can't
even you can't even use that anymore,
bro. It's embarrassing at this point
because he didn't come out last week.
And why do I have no chance in the USA?
Bro, the Americans are weak. Without
[ __ ] weapons, they're weak. Why would
I have no chance in the US?
I mean, yeah, if they [ __ ] they'd kill
me with a with a weapon. But they're not
strong. They're weak. They used to get
[ __ ] up every week in the [ __ ]
O'Neals. from Americans. They used to
get [ __ ] up every week by people in
the [ __ ] army. They're weak.
Americans are weak.
They only kill people with [ __ ]
weapons. They ain't strong.
Not at all.
They're [ __ ] They're not strong. They're weak.
Where do you think the strongest people
come from? It's not America.
Yeah. So that guy didn't even come out
last week. So I mean it's embarrassing now, bro.
And that tell and that that explains why
I don't go out to try and meet these
little mongos in this community anymore.
These spasticated people,
but she would actually call the police.
That's the thing. She would actually
call the police. That's the thing.
Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ]
Someone's blocked me a link.
Someone blocked me on LinkedIn. You university Jesus.
You can't even use that prime thing anymore.
You repeating bastard.
This community is full of [ __ ] repeaters.
Full of [ __ ] repeaters, lad. Feeling
a bit hungry now.
I need to go to that thing at night. Oh,
watch that [ __ ] cinema and watch that film.
I might go out next week. Yeah, maybe.
Doubt it though.
There's no point, bro. The [ __ ]
the [ __ ] dating game is dead in this country, lad.
[ __ ] It's dead in this country, bro.
So yeah, can't be asked.
Who the [ __ ] is that? That
We are going out today. It's pointless.
[ __ ] pointless, lad.
Go out to get new numbers that do the
same thing. It's pointless. Yeah.
What's up, bro?
It's funny when you say you've got no
chance in the US because they're not
even strong. They're actually weak over there.
It's like when her [ __ ] ex was trying
to [ __ ] mouth off, bro. He'd get
[ __ ] slapped up. some [ __ ] short
chubby [ __ ] some short chubby [ __ ]
mixed race guy, bro. He's [ __ ] taller
than him and he's and he's and he's [ __ ]
Bro, it doesn't it doesn't really
matter, does it?
Because I've got money and I get enough
money so I don't need to go on your post, bro.
I don't really give a [ __ ] You're obsessed.
I don't understand. And you're upset
like on this on this community, right?
You're obsessed with
what people have, what people don't
have. But the thing is, none of you
people, let's let's get to it again.
None of you people have shown me this 10
grand. I've been asking
for over a year now to be shown this 10
grand, and no one has shown me it. I'm
I'm still waiting. I think I need I need
I need to keep asking. I want to see
this [ __ ] 10 grand.
When people say I'm skin, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. Let let me let me let me
give you the definition of skin. Skin is
what you people are unable to show
anything. So, no, no, no, no, no. You,
you people are skinned. That's why
you're on YouTube every day. That's the
definition. When people show you money
time and time and time again and you
can't show nothing, that is what you
are. Skint. Okay. Okay. Okay. Who's
shown the most money on this community?
I have. Who has probably the most money
on this community? I do. So, yeah. If
you people weren't skinn, you wouldn't
be on YouTube every day. Simple. That's
what I'm saying. It it it's straight,
you know. So, you are wrong cuz you're
skinn yourselves. Cuz you wouldn't be on
here. I'm sticking to my guns. If you
had all this money, you wouldn't be on
YouTube. Remember what I told you about
your YouTube activity gives you away.
You people are skinting anyone. You've
been asked to show money for over a year
and every single time I ask you, you
change the subject because you're
talking about your skin selves. That's
why I don't react to any of you people
anymore because it's just classic self-p
projection. So, I'm not bothered about
what you say about people being skinn.
Well, guess what, Joe? I've shown the
most money on this community and no one
can show me this 10 grand. So, read into
that what you will. Yeah, read into that
And I'm not below the poverty line. And
we're not talking about this anyways.
Until you show me 10 grand, I'm not
having this conversation. If you've got
all of this money, show me my 10 grand
that I've been asking for [ __ ] a
year. I want to see 10 grand. Oh, I'm
not having this conversation. Simple. I
want to see this £10,000
that I've been asking for [ __ ] a
year. Doesn't matter if I've lost all
the money, I've still got the money. I
want to see my 10 grand. And if you do
not show me it, you're skinned. Simple.
That's it. You are skinned. If you do
not show me £10,000, you are skint.
Simple. That's my definition of skint.
Me showing amount of money and you can't
show me anything back. Sorry to say,
you're skint. And that's not even
double, bro. Double is 12 grand. But I
said, okay, if you show me 10 grand. So
until you show me 10 grand, my I think
you're skin. How about that one? Simple. That's it.
You know, if you if you had £600 on this
community, Yeah. say you had £600 in
your bank account, you've got more than
most people on here. Who who really has
money on this community? Like let's keep
it real. Timmy don't have money. Lo
don't have no money. [ __ ] you don't
have no money. [ __ ] Most of the
people that comment, you ain't even I
would say you've probably got about 2030
in your bank account. I would say
majority of the people on here don't
even have £500. Like that's that's
literally how bad it is.
You know, you don't have anything
really. Like it's you don't need to be
sorry, bro. You need to be sorry to
yourself that you ain't been able to
show this 10 grand.
Go put up your bank account right now
and let's see how much you got in your
bank account since you don't carry all
of this in cash and we'll see the real
definition of skin. Come on, you can't do it.
And no one cares about Virgin boy
showing the same,000 that he's been
showing for years. You haven't beat me.
That's not the way the money game works.
I want to see £10,000.
Well, I need to stop asking because no
one's obviously ever going to show it.
So, that's it.
Skin is when you can't Skin is like
Monty, man. You can't even afford food.
That's what skin is. That's what [ __ ]
And why are we even talking about this any anyways?
Why is it always about money? If you
people have got all of this money, why
are you on YouTube all day every day? If
you've got all of this money and
everyone else's skin, why do you spend
your life on YouTube? See, you can't
answer anything. It's pointless, bro.
There's no point starting [ __ ] you can't
finish. Stop being a London cyclist, you know?
Think about it, right? Let's just say
that I'm wrong and you've got all of
this money. What are you doing with all
of this money? You're spending all your
life on YouTube. So why would you care
who has less than you? You know what I'm
saying? It's mad.
It's been the same for years now, bro.
Like you call people skint cuz you're skintselves.
I It's It's No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
One second. One second. You people come
on YouTube every day saying that people
are skin, people got no friends, people
are alone. If you weren't any of these
things, you wouldn't be on YouTube every
day. It's it's it's facts. If you had
all of this money, all of these friends,
you wouldn't even be on YouTube. And
yes, it does mean that they are skid. It
does mean that they are [ __ ] skids.
Cuz I used to go on L's all the time,
right? Friday, Saturday, and it would be
the same people, the same low lives all alone.
It would be the same people that
couldn't get off of YouTube.
But no, that ain't skin. And again, so
you're not going to show me this 10
grand, then? So, you're not going to
show me this 10 grand then,
bro. You really don't know the
definition of skin. Like, you really,
really, really don't know the definition
of skin. The definition of skin is like
[ __ ] virgin boy showing his housing
benefit off that he has to put back in
the [ __ ] bank,
you know. And you know the maddest thing
is he doesn't have more money than me.
I've got more money than him. But let's
just say that he had more money than me.
But guess what, bro? Here's the thing.
I've got more life experience. I'm
better looking than him. I I have more
hair than him. I've been to more places
than him. I've had more women than him.
And I've I've just lived a better life
all around. So I mean, bro, if you've
got all of this money, time to start
living your life.
I mean, I done a lot this month, you
know, even though I don't get that
income anymore that I used to get, I
done a lot. I went to Birmingham. I went
out [ __ ] three times. I [ __ ] done
quite good this month to be honest. And
I didn't really And you know, and I've
still got some money, you know.
So, I mean it also goes depends on what
you do in your life as well, you know.
I done pretty good this month to be honest. So, yeah. But
you people will never show me 10 grand.
So, what do you think, man? pulling up
to uh pulling up to um USA Izzy's [ __ ]
university Joe. Oh,
why would I stand a chance in the USA,
bro? Yeah, I wouldn't stand a chance if
they [ __ ] use weapons,
but they're not strong. They're not strong people.
They never been strong, bro. They're [ __ ] weaklings.
Think of who's the world's strongest
man. They've never been American.
They're [ __ ] weak, bro.
They're [ __ ] weak.
They're [ __ ] weak. The world's
strongest man before, I think he was
Polish, then it went I think like
Eastern European. They're not [ __ ]
strong. Do you think that Damon would
ever speak to me like that to my face?
And we can keep talking about Prime, but
guess what? Prime was nowhere to be seen
on Saturday when he was being called out
a million times. Timmy was nowhere to be
seen when he was being called out a
million times. And Timmy was on the
chat. So, I mean, bro, you can't even
use that anymore.
I was having this conversation with
London Taylor um yesterday that just
London and Birmingham alone. How many of
these people do you think live in these
places like that go on J's um you know
Birmingham, London. I'd say quite a lot
live in Birmingham and London. You know
them two cities alone. God knows how
many people in this community live there
and they don't ever meet anyone. They're [ __ ]
Like don't don't think into it too deep.
Oh, they don't say where they are. You
don't know where they are. Trust me,
some of them are in Birmingham and some
of them are in London.
Um cuz they know too much.
They know too much about certain places.
So obviously they're never going to say
where they are um on LJ's, oh I'm in
East London. Oh, I'm in I'm in South
London. And they're never going to say
that because if one of these people said
that then people just going to go there
and go live and then they're just going
to be shown up and then as soon as they
go back on L Js they're just going to
get bullied for being the coward that
they are. But believe you me some of
them do live in London and some of them
do live in Birmingham as well.
Them two places though cuz obviously
they're big they're the biggest cities.
I think that good vibes only is London you know. Jesus Christ.
Let's just have you running about. They
don't have me running about. I went to
meet Monty Man. They don't have me running about.
They used to. Yeah. When I used to go to
different cities, but at the end of like
it's like, you know, that time Bomb made
me go to Manchester. Yeah. That time.
And I thought he was going to meet me.
Bro, he got me laid. If I didn't go, I
wouldn't have got that. I wouldn't have
got sex in Manchester if I if I didn't
go that day. So, in a way, he he
actually got me laid
cuz he would have wound me up on that
Good Friday and then I wouldn't have
went up there. He actually got me laid. He did. Yeah.
Yeah. He actually got me laid. He did, man.
But yeah, I know all of this. I know all
of this, bro. That's why I don't go and
meet anyone anymore.
But if you notice, they'll never say
where they are. Like I'm in London, I'm
in Manchester, I'm in Newcastle. And um
cuz they know that you can just go there
and call them out, you know.
That's why they never say where they are
cuz they're [ __ ] cowards.
You know what I mean?
So yeah. So anyway, show back to this Miami thing.
How how will it plan out?
How will it plan out, matey?
You know what? I might actually go, bro.
I'm not even joking. It's not even as
expensive as you think.
It's going to be a lot harder to afford
things now, matey.
But still doable.
You can You just won't be able to [ __ ]
go out every week. That's the only thing.
Yeah, man. I think I've I've got about 2K. So,
which is just normal, is it?
This is why I need to really come off
YouTube. I need to start thinking of
ways to make money now, bro. This is actually serious.
So, this is actually serious, bro.
I could easily book this holiday £900 to £1,100,
£1,500 spending money. It'll be enough.
Really could actually really do this, bro.
I could actually do this, bro. I'm not even joking.
But I do really need to come off this
[ __ ] soon, bro. Cuz I need to do I need
to actually um
see what I'm actually doing, bro. Cuz
Yeah, I need to be rich, matey. I don't
want to be skint like [ __ ] nons legs.
You know what I'm saying? [ __ ] hell.
Right. Let me look at let me look this up again.
So, I can't really go on my birthday because
it's too cold.
That's the problem.
And then it's just [ __ ] you know,
I need to try and win a football bet,
man, or something. I swear to God.
But if you go to Miami, it's not as
expensive as um the other one.
Greavves lives off £1,200 a month.
How is £1,100 just above poverty if you
got no outgoings?
That's not above That's not just above
poverty. How could that be just above
poverty? That doesn't even make sense.
Oh, see, look. There's one here. £827.
There's one here. 600. And that's a
flight and a hotel. Must be cuz it's in um September.
That one's a fourstar as well.
So that's 827.
It's not bad, is it?
Looks like a nice hotel as well. It's
got to be cuz it's cold. That's why.
What do you think, Grezy? £827 to see my mama.
What do you think, bro?
To see my mama, Grezy.
Is it worth it to Is it worth it to see my mama?
Why is it Why is it a waste, Grezy?
What? To see my mama? How is that a waste? £827
flight, hotel. What? How is it a waste
when I'm going to see my mama? Grievy.
And I can also find a new mama.
Why is that? That's actually really cheap, man.
Oh, this one's nice as well.
But she has to want me though. Greavvesy
because I'm her sunny.
I'm her sunny. She has to want her
Her sunny matey
is messaging me on her.
But she has to want her sunny. Grey,
why is it so cheap? It's got to be cuz
it's cold, isn't it?
Yeah, it's got to be cuz it's cold, is it? Grievy. Yeah, man.
But £1,100 is not poverty, bro.
It's not poverty.
Think of it. I That's how much I got
paid this month. I done Birmingham. I
went out a couple of times and but I
didn't win a football bet. So maybe it
was like 1,300 but still
it's not poverty lad. Yeah,
she will call old Bill in it. Greasy. Yeah.
Yeah, definitely. That was cool old bill. Man,
you couldn't stay for [ __ ] You
couldn't stay for 4 months, Grezy. You
couldn't stay for 4 months. You think
you could actually stay?
Well, it's not poverty. Well, the
country is wrong, bro. Because if you
had £1,100 a month and you've got no
outgoings, that ain't poverty. That's
literally what most people are left with
after they pay rent. It's like if
someone gets two grand, 2 and a half
grand a month, right? That's what
they're probably left with after their
outgoings. So, the country is wrong. And
also, they they don't know what people's
outgoings are. That's another thing.
They don't know what people's outgoings
are. See, you get these people that are
on like 2 grand a month, 2.2K 2K a month
and they say, "Oh, uh, I can't live off,
uh, £1,200 a month. I can't live off
£1,100 a month." Yet, when it by the
time they've paid everything, they're on
probably less than that.
That's how [ __ ] they are because
they they see as they they think
everyone's got the same outgoings as them,
you know, and then they but once they
once they deduct their outgoings,
they're left with probably less than you
or the same as you. But that's how
[ __ ] they are.
Well, mate, no one in London has two,
three grand spare after housing costs.
No, they do not. No, they [ __ ] do
not. So, anyways, I don't know even know
why we're talking about this anyways.
It's [ __ ] irrelevant. I get my money.
I have enough money. That's all I need.
That's all I need to know. Simple. Why
are we so obsessed with money as well?
Why are we even talking about this? Huh?
Like it doesn't really matter, bro. I
mean, like you people can win the
lottery and you still wouldn't get off
of YouTube. So, it's just a pointless
conversation. It's a pointless topic
because if you people had all the money
in the world, you still wouldn't get off
of YouTube. So, why does it matter what
I have and what you have and what it's just pointless?
I could go out today getting pissed and
I'd be all right.
It's It's just pointless talking about
it though, really. in it,
you know. So, what what what is even the
point of it? I don't understand.
Uh but no, no, but the people that are
saying I'm skin, I've got more than
them. So, they're talking about themselves.
So, no, I'm not to them because if I was
skinned to them, they would show me
their 10 grand. Then I'm not skin to
them because I've got more money than
them, which is why they can't show me
this 10 grand.
So no, they can call me what they want,
but they're just talking about
themselves. Just like L, he's skin. Just
like Virgin Boy, he's skin. We They've
been proven to be skin multiple multiple
times. I mean, for [ __ ] sake, bro. You
could be sat here with [ __ ] £20,000
cash. They still call you skint because
they are talking about themselves. They
are skint. That's the point. It's not
you are skint them. They are skint
themselves. This is why they call you
skint cuz they're self projecting.
That's the whole point. It's their own
lives they're talking about. OJ skint.
Timmy skin. Virginite skint. They're all
skint themselves, which is why they talk
about other people being skinn
cuz this is a self-reflection and a
self-p projection of their own life
they're living. They know all the
telltale signs about being skinned. I
would say 90% of these people couldn't
even afford to go out today drinking.
That's how bad it is. I don't even think 90%
people could have go out today drinking.
And part of the reason they're addicted
to YouTube is because they got no money
to go out. It's because they've
generally got no money to go out, you know?
So, I've got more money than them. I've
always had more money than them and I
still have more money than them. And
they still call you skin because they're
talking about themselves. Go don't go
work it out, bro. It's like when they
call people ugly, they're ugly themselves. Simple.
L J is skinned. I don't know why he
tries to act like he's got money when he
doesn't have money, but but L.
Yeah, I'm skinn, bro. I got two grand
and I'm skinn. Yeah. Yeah. I'm I'm
dying, bro. I'm I'm dying of starvation.
Yeah, you're right, bro. I'm starving.
I'm completely skinned, bro. Yep.
Completely skinned. I've got two grand
and I'm completely skinn. I'm probably
going to die within the next couple of
days. I know, bro. Yeah, I'm skinn.
Yeah, I'm properly skinned. Oh, man. It
sucks to be me, bro. It sucks to be me. Yeah, bro.
It sucks to be me, bro. You're right.
I'm probably going to die in a couple of
days. Damn. Sucks to be me.
Sucks to be me. Grievesy, can you donate? Oh,
sucks to be me.
£1,100 a month is not pittance. If you
got no outgoings,
can you donate to me, Greavves? I'm skint bro.
Skint is what bodybad is. That's what
you call skint.
Skint is literally nothing. Not 500, not
600. It is literally nothing. That is
that is what skin is. And again, I don't
know why we're talking about this until
you show me this 10 grand. Stop talking
about money. If you've got all of this
money and I'm so skint, show me this 10
grand I've been begging for. And if you
can't, then you're in no room to talk
about anyone. You got no room to talk
See, it's the whole thing, right? If I
was to put my PayPal link up, that would
be because I'm skinn. It's like L J. He
is skin. He tries to say that he gets
three and a half grand a month. He does
not get no [ __ ] three and a half
grand a month. You wouldn't be begging
on YouTube. You see what I'm saying is
people's YouTube activity gives them
away. It It's literally like somebody
snaking them. It's like somebody giving
them away when they're on YouTube every
day. Hold on a minute. They've got all
of this money. They've got all of these
friends, but they're on YouTube every
day. That doesn't add up. Hold on a
minute. Someone gets three and a half
grand a month after outgoings,
but they're begging on YouTube every
day. You see, when you when you actually
think about this, it makes literally no sense.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. You
people started the money game with me.
You got shown 5.7 grand and I I asked
you to show me [ __ ] 10 grand and you
can't do it. So, at the end of the day, like, it's pointless.
can't even show [ __ ] 10 grand, bro.
Yeah, that large they tried saying he
was on three and a half grand a month.
Is he [ __ ] on three and a half grand a
month? He's never been on three and a
half grand a month and he's [ __ ] old.
I didn't even used to get that when I
was renting them houses
now. He's he he is on like him for
example, he's on benefits, I would say.
No, no, no. He doesn't get £300 a month,
but that's a bit less. I would say he's
on about £700 a month.
Yeah, man. 700 a month. Definitely, bro.
Definitely £700 a month. I don't think
£300. He gets He's definitely on benefits.
Definitely on benefits.
Like I said, people's YouTube activity
gives them away. What they do on YouTube
snakes them. It gives them away.
Yeah, it gives them away. And no, not
really. You can get you if you get
£1,100 a month, right? You can go to
Thailand in three or four months. You
can go to America in three three or four months.
You know what I'm saying? You could
still save. It just take [ __ ] long.
You know, you're talking like it's £300
a month or it's like £200 a month. You
could easily [ __ ] do it. You know
what I'm saying?
But I mean, it's nowhere near as bad as
you're making it out to be.
It's nowhere near as bad as you're
making it out to be, lad. Trust me. Nowhere near.
You I probably get more than most people
in this [ __ ] community, to be honest.
Oh my god. Listen, [ __ ] how many
times have I had to explain to you that
I've got no outgoings? Listen,
[ __ ] let me explain it again to you
because you obviously keep comparing
your your situation to me. I don't have
no outgoing [ __ ] I don't know how
many times I've had to explain this to
you. I have no outgoings. It's all mine.
So, the only thing that I have to pay
for is food. That goes very [ __ ] far. Yeah,
bro. I bro, why would I like the word
poverty? You people are the one in
poverty. You can't even show me money,
bro. 1.1k after no outgoings goes it.
I've probably got more than you at the
end of the month again. Until you show
me this 10 grand, I'm not having this
conversation. Go. Okay. You like to put
up stuff on your channel, right? Time
and time and time and time again. Show
me this 10 grand, right? I'm in poverty.
Okay. Okay. Show me this 10 grand.
Otherwise, you're living in poverty
then, right? You claim that you get this
four or five grand a month. Okay, show
me this 10 grand. Shut me up once and
for all. Shut me up once and for all and
show me this £10,000. Yes, I'm skinn.
I've got nothing. I'm literally on the
bones of my ass, bro. Show me this
£10,000. Stop typing and show me this
You get all this money. You're rich. I'm
poor. Yep. I'm starving. I'm literally
starving. I want to see 10 grand. I
don't want nothing else. And if you
can't show me this 10 grand, well,
you're skinned. Simple. That's it,
right? Cuz if someone's getting three,
four grand a month and they can't show
me 10 grand, they must be skinned.
That's the definition of skint, right?
You like to post things on your channel
time and time and time and time and time
again. Yeah, you are broke as a joke.
Yeah, you're talking about yourself,
right? You're talking about yourself.
Yeah, you are broke as a joke. That's
why you people can't get off YouTube.
Okay, show me your bank account. No, no,
no. [ __ ] the cash, bro. Show me your
bank account. Yeah, bro. Cuz a joke.
I've got more money than you will ever
have sat on YouTube on benefits. You
people are sat on YouTube on benefits
talking about your skin selves for a
living. Listen, bro. If you people,
right, really had money, right, you
would have bro, show you 1K. Listen,
bro. I've already shown you thousands
and thousands and thousands. I don't
need to go to my bank and withdraw any
more money. You show me that 10 grand.
You show me that 10 grand and I'll come
and then come back to me. You don't You
don't have 30 fucking,000. You skin
flint. Right. Let me put the link up.
This is what I mean with these people on
YouTube every single day. They start
[ __ ] and they can't finish it. Right.
Show me this 10 grand. Show me the 10
grand. Bro, you've been shown thousands
and thousands and thousands. Show me
your savings. Come on. Come on, Skint
Flynn. You've come on here and you've
started. I will go to the [ __ ] I will
go to the bank and I'll go to the post
office right now if you show me your
money. Come on, skin boy. Stop typing
skin flip. Show me, bro. Show me all
your money. Come on, Skint Boy. You've
come on here and you've started with me.
A typical [ __ ] YouTube bong. Starting
something they can't finish. Come on.
You broke as a joke, Skint Flynn. Come
on. What you waiting for? The link is
up. I'll do it again. One second. Come
in and show us your money.
Come in and show us your money.
Exactly. Cuz you ain't got nothing. See,
you see the thing is right. If I had an
account to show right now and all this
money like this person, I wouldn't be
avoiding the question. He's running away
again. He's running away. He's running
away again. Exactly what I'm talking
about. They're all skint. They got
nothing. Bro, listen. And if they had
all of this money, right? Yeah, you are
disabled. You are disabled. Why are you
not joining? You disabled Skint [ __ ]
You disabled [ __ ] You're coming on
YouTube every day. You skint benefit
life. Calling other people skint. And
you can't show nothing. Stop
embarrassing yourself. Stop embarrassing
yourself. The link is up there. Why are
you embarrassing yourself?
Stop embarrassing yourself, you little
skint. Come and show us your buddy. What
you Why do you keep typing? Why do you
Why are you keep typing? Cuz you ain't
got nothing. Showing yourself up on
YouTube again because you ain't got
nothing. This is what they do every
single time. Grezy. Yeah. They come on
here and they start something that they
can't finish. Every single [ __ ] time.
I will go to the bank and take out two
grand and show you. When you show me
this 10 grand I've been asking for, all
I want is these people to show me this
10 grand and they keep avoiding me every
single time. It's cuz they ain't got it.
They're skint. This is what I'm saying
to you, bro. They are the definition of
skint. You know,
you know, think about it, Grezy. You
show money. The whole game is you show
money and they double it. You show
money, they double it, right? And then
what they show, you double it. That's
that's literally how it goes.
You show£10, they show 20, you show 40,
they show 80. You You understand? That's
the whole point of the game. But with
these people, they get shown money and
then they run away and then they come
back like 2 3 months later showing half
the amount you just shown. Well, less
than half the amount you just shown.
They just embarrass themselves. That's
all they do, bro. They they they
literally just embarrass themselves
every day. If they had all of this
money, well, put it this way. If they've
got all of this money and they want
YouTube, shame on them. Shame on them.
That's all I've got to say, bro. Shame
on them. If they've got all of this
money and they choose to waste [ __ ]
all their life on YouTube, shame on them
then, isn't it? It's a big shame on
them. That's all I got to say, bro.
Yeah, it's a shame on them, is it? Really?
Cuz you need to ask yourself this
question, Greasy. If they've got all of
this ridiculous amount of money, why
would they be traveling the world or
I don't know, going on nights out or
going on a cruise like with all of this
money? Why would they be sat on YouTube
every day? They're [ __ ] lives. I
think I make a valid point. Got a Donald
cap on today. Because they ain't got no
money. They're skimplings. They're little self-reflectors.
They ain't even got a They ain't even
got £500 in their account, bro.
They ain't even got £500 [ __ ] pound
in their account. You know, the maddest
thing is, you know, when I was on that
[ __ ] £700 a month, bro, I still had
more of a life than them.
They're just little fat little ugly
people on benefits that talk about
themselves every day embarrassing
themselves on YouTube. They just They
don't realize, bro, like when when they
do this this whole typing [ __ ] they
just they just embarrass themselves.
They literally just embarrass
themselves. Why start something you
can't finish? Don't be a [ __ ] Don't
be a London cyclist.
We have it with these people. We have it with [ __ ]
USA Izzy. We have it with so many
people. They're starting [ __ ] they can't
finish. It's embarrassing, bro. It's
embarrassing as [ __ ]
you know. But anyways, I still ain't
been showing this 10 grand. So, what do
you want people to do, right? Keep
showing you the same amount of money for a year.
Is that what it is? You want people to
keep showing you the same amount of
money for one year, like just have six
grand sat there for a whole year. Well,
you know, maybe you want to book a
holiday. Maybe you wanted to buy
garments. And as soon as you put money
back in the account, which No, no, no,
no, no. Hold on a minute. You actually
can still show your [ __ ] because you
actually bought garments, which is part
of where the money went. So, the money
is still very present. It's just an assets now.
It's actually just It's actually just an
assets. So actually it's still there but
it's just in assets which is which is
the same as it actually being there to
be honest to be to be honest with you.
So the money actually is still very
there. It's actually in the same [ __ ] room.
So you know what I'm saying?
And then they'll sit there and wait and
then they'll show you then like maybe
£800 or £1,000. They're [ __ ]
embarrassing, bro. It's the whole thing
of it is [ __ ] because think of it, they
if even if these people had all the
money in the world, they'd still be
skinn and ugly on YouTube. So why what
what what would what would be the point
of them even having anything?
They'd still be skinn ugly on YouTube.
Skin and ugly on YouTube. I've got about
[ __ ] 131,400 in jumpers. So if you
wanted to ask where some of that money
went, it went on jumpers. It went on
clothes. Clothes that I've still got. So
the money was spent. It's still the same
as assets. I want to see my 10 grand. I
don't know why you keep changing the subject.
Because you're skintselves. End of
story. That's what it is. You call
people skint cuz you skint yourselves.
Simple. That's it.
There you go. That's 12 1300 pound in jumpers.
Yeah. It's a madness, bro.
They'll all skin their [ __ ] selves.
Why they go on about it? And if they've
got all of this money, what are they
doing with all of this money? Let's say
they've got all of this money. What are
they doing with it? Sat on YouTube every
day calling people skin.
It's mad, isn't it? They're just fat,
ugly people on benefits. If they had all
this money, they wouldn't be on here.
Simple. They'd be living their life,
enjoying their life. Be like what I was doing.
Yeah. When you show me my 10 grand.
Um, excuse me. No, one second. One
second. Back to the 10 grand again.
You're changing the subject. Are you
going to show me this £10,000 or not? If
you're not going to show it, I'm going
to block you because you've been
bringing this up all day. I've been
asking you to show me 10 grand and you
keep ignoring me. Show me my 10 grand
and I'll show you anything that you
want. Simple. It's your turn. It's your
turn. I'm putting the link up. [ __ ] it.
I'm putting the link up. I want to see
£10,000, right? These people are working
people. I don't know how much. They
probably get £45,000 a month, whatever.
I'm all skin. Let's see what 10 grand
looks like cuz I've never had it in
cash. And I'm going to go I'm going to
be quiet now for 5 minutes. I'm not
going to respond to any messages. They
people's got bank accounts, people have
got cash, whatever. I want to see this
£10,000. I want to see what it looks
like. I'm not saying anything else now.
Just wait patiently.
We're going to give it a little bit
because I need to go out in a bit. So,
there's the links there. Everyone else
is skin, but these people, they've got
all of this money. I mean, 10 grand is
not a lot if you're getting three, four,
[ __ ] £5,000 a month. So, I'm just
going to sit here and wait.
Everyone else is skin. These people have
got all of this money, yet they sit on
YouTube every day. Let me put another
link out there.
I've noticed you're very touchy about
showing 10 grand. I've noticed that.
Must be because you don't have it.
You're very touchy about this £10,000 kn.
And then you'll ask me where my £5.7k
went and then I'll explain it again. But
it doesn't matter.
You have been shown £5.7,000
and there's still assets to be shown. I
want to see this £10,000.
But everyone's running away. I don't
know why everyone's running away now.
And again, what is the point of this
whole money game? Because none of you,
even if you had a million pounds, would
get off YouTube. You all skid little low
vibes. Is it Is it autism or Cuz you
call people You call people like
disabled every single day and that,
whatever. I don't know why you do it,
but it's got to be part of your autism.
Think about it, bro. I could show
[ __ ] £2,000 right now and you could
have £30,000, but who's going to have
the better life? I'm going to have the
better life cuz you people are stuck on
YouTube every day. It's not like you do
anything. You know what I'm saying?
Oh, you don't. Okay. Well, you can show
us your bank account then. Okay. Well,
then show us your bank account.
Show us your bank account. Show us your
bank account, then.
Show us your bank account.
I'm asking everyone. But why does it
matter? Because if you had 30 times what
I have, I'm still better looking. I've
still got a better life than you. Really? So yeah.
What is this whole why? Who who the [ __ ]
invented this whole money game thing, by
the way? I think it might have been Timmy.
But as it stands, I've shown the most
money on this community, and I've got
assets to prove it. So, I'm the winner. So, yeah.
Yeah. You wouldn't be on YouTube if you
had all of this money. I know that for a
fact. You'd be out there living your life.
Think of it. What is M, bro? It's
freedom. It gives people freedom.
You wouldn't be on YouTube if you had
all of this money. What?
And then you're saying, "Oh, well, why
are you on YouTube? What the [ __ ] did I
do last Saturday, bro? I [ __ ]
traveled. God knows [ __ ] how many
miles across the [ __ ] country. So if
you had all of this money, you wouldn't
be on YouTube the way you're on YouTube.
Simple. You'd be out there living the
life, but you're not. You on YouTube
every day. So red flags all over, isn't
it? To be honest with you. Anyways, I
need to go anyways. So yeah, put it on
your channel by the way cuz I'm going
now. I'll be back later. Yeah, put it on
your channel. Don't forget to put it on
your channel. I want to see this £10,000.
Anyone who's watching this as well, I
want to I want to see it as well. Yeah.
So, put it put it put it on your
channel. Yeah. And um Yeah. Simple.