[ __ ] hell, bro.
Typical Timmy, eh? Acting the big man
when it's all over. You see what I mean
with these people, man? These people are
this this shitty community will never
[ __ ] change. Honestly, it's it's m
The only thing is, yeah, it's so
predictable as well.
It's so predictable as well.
What what he does.
We was [ __ ] in Birmingham last
[ __ ] week and [ __ ] he was in the
chat and he didn't want to meet any of
us and then he's on YouTube acting big again.
Bro, this is what I mean with these
people in this community, bro. What the [ __ ]
Madness. [ __ ] madness.
[ __ ] Ain't it, bro?
Yeah. Yeah. You're talking about
yourself again, you little self-reflector.
I don't sit on YouTube all day like you
people. I was out all day, mate, for 9
hours. You are the ones that sat on
YouTube every day calling people what
you [ __ ] are.
skin [ __ ] fat ugly mongos. Bro,
you're the ones that do it. You're the
clear example. Sat on YouTube all day
every day. That's you, mate. You get
yourself a job. Yeah. Give that advice
to your [ __ ] self, you [ __ ] repeating bastard.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
You know what? Yeah. I'm not going to
bring anything up until someone I was
going to bring something up today,
right? Yeah. But I'm not going to bring
it up until someone says something.
Then, you know, we'll see if it's still
going on. But I was actually thinking
about this today. You know,
you know what I'm saying?
[ __ ] madness, bro.
[ __ ] repeating bastards.
I couldn't even leave for one day, bro.
You can't even leave for 10 minutes.
Leave for one day, bro. I've left for
weeks. You people can't even take one
hour off of YouTube. Go self-reflect on another channel.
[ __ ] self-reflecting bastards.
Self-reflecting little [ __ ] bastards
on YouTube. Little no lives. Yeah, I
I've been out all day, mate. I've only
just got back. The [ __ ]
[ __ ] One sec.
You're a loser. Yeah, you are a loser.
Stop talking about yourself.
Yeah, you are a loser. You can't live
without YouTube. Yeah, you are a loser.
Yeah, stop talking about yourself like
that. It's not good for your mental
health. Just like you call people skintselves.
Yeah, you talk about yourselves every
[ __ ] day, year in year out for a
living. All you do pe all you people do
is talk about yourselves.
You're something to laugh at.
You're literally something to laugh at.
You call people skint every day. Yet
none of you have any [ __ ] money. And
here's the thing. Yeah. Let let me bring
that up as well. Yeah. You all call
people skint every day, right? Yeah.
You've literally lost the money game
time and time and time and time again.
You've lost the money game time and time
and time and time again and you will
continue to keep losing it. But listen,
here's the thing. You say you got all of
this money. Why do you spend all of your
life on YouTube? Sorry, I had to
rephrase this. Yeah, I actually had to
rephrase this. Not coming on YouTube.
You spend every second of your day on
YouTube, yet you claim that you've got
all of this money. Ha. Isn't that so
funny, bro? It's because you then go to
the cold half truth hold cold hard truth
that all you're doing is talking about
your own lives which brings you on
YouTube all day every day
cuz I guess [ __ ] someone could just
go on YouTube and just laugh.
Um that could [ __ ] you know someone
could come on YouTube and just [ __ ]
laugh at you [ __ ] spastics for like
an hour a day. So I kind of had to
rephrase what I said. You spend every
single second of every day on YouTube.
Nah, something ain't adding up, mate.
Something ain't adding up. Something is
really, really not adding up there, bro.
It's because you're talking about yourselves,
bro. I could have £500 in my bank. £500
only. £400 only. I literally could lose
£1,500 right now. £1,600 right now. I have £400 left
and I'd still have a better life than
all of you.
That's the saddest thing about it. You know,
you people can't get off of YouTube.
It's your life. It's your livelihood.
Without YouTube and projecting, you'd be [ __ ]
So, what made me come back? Um, to talk to Monty.
Why are you on YouTube every day, all
day, every day?
Why can't you people get off of YouTube
for a couple of weeks like I have?
The [ __ ] You literally spend all your
life on YouTube all day every day. The
[ __ ] You people literally can't live
without YouTube. Don't [ __ ] ask me
why I'm on still [ __ ] YouTube. [ __ ]
off, bro. None of you [ __ ] work.
And here's the thing. You do realize,
right, that it it's a couple of
different things. Do you like Anyways,
I'm I'm blocking you spastics. Anyways,
bro, one second. You're gone. You're
Bye-bye. Don't entertain spastics. Yeah, man.
You go on about that's what I don't
understand is they go on about money all
day but none of them have got a life.
The [ __ ] bro? You don't know what is the
meaning of money?
>> Yeah. They talk about themselves every
[ __ ] day on YouTube.
It must suck to be It must suck to be
them, bro. Really? It must really suck
to be them.
It must really suck to be them.
How the [ __ ] do these people become so
disabled? I think they got brain damage or something.
Really? I was trying to think. I was I
was actually thinking about this
earlier, Grezy, is that even if these
people had way more money than me, think
of it, bro. I'm better looking than
them. I've got a better life than them.
I have more life experience than them. I
actually leave my [ __ ] house.
You know, it's Think about it, bro. Like
I said, even if I only had 400 I if I
got £400 a month. Yeah. Let's say I got
£400 a month, I would still have a
better life than all of them. Do you
understand? Like they that's why they
want people to show them money because
they want to be shown things that they
don't have themselves because they don't
have money which is why they go on about
money every single day is because they
ain't got no money. Do you understand?
That's why they're sat on YouTube all
day every day.
See how I rephrase what I said there?
They're literally on here all day every
day. What life do they have, bro? Come on.
Cuz it's not just about money. It's
about multiple different things. What
life you have, what you look like. It's
not all just about money.
You know what I mean?
That's the thing, bro.
But yeah, I knew Timmy was going to do
this. I knew he was going to do this,
bro. He does it all the time.
And he's going to tell Monty to not
respond to him. We all saw the real
Timmy when we was in Birmingham.
Something one day you people [ __ ] get life, bro. Yeah, bro. Middle thing.
Yeah. Now, are we going back to
Birmingham tomorrow, Greavvesy?
Hopefully not, though. I don't want to
go all the way back there to be honest. But maybe,
maybe, maybe. I don't know yet.
But yeah, these people are [ __ ] weird, bro.
You said like they say they've got all
of this money, right? And everyone else
is skin. So why they got a life then?
Why are they sat all day every day on
YouTube? That's that's the bit I don't
get. That's the only thing that I don't
understand. If they've got all of this
money and everyone else's skin, why are
they the ones with no life? It doesn't
make sense and it just does not make,
you know, to make someone jealous, you
need a life. Money without anything
else, it means very less.
You know what I mean? It doesn't it
doesn't mean anything. You need to be
good-looking. You need money. You need
to have a life. None of these people
have any of these things,
you know? It's hard to try to explain
what I mean. So, like, yeah.
Oh, what's that? Weapons, by the way, bro.
Reeves, it was no good.
[ __ ] [ __ ] horror film. I caught it,
bro. Uh, yeah.
I went cinema today.
[ __ ] went out. Had some Nandos.
These people sat on YouTube all alone,
let me guess. Yeah, man. Yeah.
But instead of showing this money,
right, that these people think that
they've got, why don't you start doing
something with some of this money,
traveling the world, buying garments, be
like what I spent that five grand on if
you surely to go have all of this money.
But that's the that's the whole point is
that they don't have money.
That's the whole point and they ain't
got a life.
So it's like it just doesn't make any sense. Yeah, man.
I used to have a bro I had a better life
than these people when I was on [ __ ]
£700 a month.
I don't give a [ __ ] about money, bro.
You think I give a [ __ ] No, I don't
give a [ __ ] bro.
These people obsess over it. It is weird.
It is very, very, very, very, very
weird. They obsess over money, but they
ain't got a life. So, even if they were
to get money or have money, what are
they doing with it, bro? They ain't even
got a life. So, the [ __ ] Oh [ __ ] Yeah.
Anyways, bro, moving on.
And I've spent weeks off of YouTube, weeks.
Cuz here's the thing, right? If everyone
else is skin and you people got all of
this money, you don't need to hate on
YouTube, bro. live your life.
But the fact that you come on YouTube
every day calling it other people when
with all of that money you should be
living your own life. It tells everyone
what they need to know, bro. You know,
just doesn't make it don't make any sense.
Like I said, I was thinking about this
quite a bit today actually. I said
they're going on about money. Who has
money? Who has no money? This person has
this. But none of these people have got a life.
Think about it, bro. That's that's
actually the main thing.
All old people sat on YouTube every
[ __ ] day. Anyway,
Bam. Oh, hi, bro.
So, they were supposed to go Belgium
this week, but apparently they didn't go
Belgium this week. Nah, it's not even
addicting at all. It's just for the
spastics. I've been out all day. I've
literally just come back. Nah, it's not
even It's not even addictive.
It's just spasticated.
Not even addictive at all. It's just
funny to laugh at [ __ ] Timmy. He's a [ __ ] pratt.
So, you're supposed to go to Belgium
this week and now all of a sudden you
haven't gone to Belgium.
Oh, no. That's not good, is it? I go
live every day. Listen, mate. I've been
off of YouTube for weeks. Like, bro, do
you really want to play that game again?
Well, I don't come on YouTube for weeks
and new people come on here every single
day. Do you really want to play that game again?
Bro, I can play the game again. If you
really want to go down that avenue and I
can show you again who ain't got a life,
I am more than happy to do it, bro. New
people come on YouTube from the time you
wake up to the time you go to bed, day
in day out.
Yeah. every single day, every moment of
every day, you're on here. So, if you
really want to play that game, who can
sell off YouTube the longest, bro? I'm
more than happy to. If you want to play
that game, just say it.
If you want to play that game, just say it. You know,
but you people are on YouTube all day,
every day. You've never took weeks off of YouTube.
So yeah, you can't get off of YouTube.
YouTube's your life.
I've just come here to speak to Monty if
he comes on.
And it's not so much about like going
live. It's actually what you do on
YouTube as well. It's actually what you
people do on here. Like writing comments
all day, every day, hating. It's not
even about It's actually what you do on YouTube.
If you had all of this money in this
life, you wouldn't be doing it. It's
It's self-explanatory. You wouldn't be doing it.
You actually wouldn't be doing it, but
you are doing it. So, something's not
right there. So, yeah.
It's what you do, bro. I can I can I can
[ __ ] put on a live stream and just
[ __ ] talk [ __ ] for hours. Doesn't
mean anything. I'm not going out today. So what? So yeah.
Yeah. You don't you haven't completed
life. If you completed life and you had
a family, you wouldn't be on here doing
what you do every day. Yeah, bro. You
wouldn't be on here doing what you do
every day. Simple.
Yeah. Okay. You keep telling yourself that, bro.
You keep telling yourself that. Retired
at what? 40. 40 years of age. What? You
retire in your 40s?
I don't think so, bud. I think the age
has actually gone up to be honest. Nah,
you ain't retired. What? 40 years of
age, mate. You people in your 40s, 50
maybe, you ain't retired. So, don't even
try and say that you [ __ ]
retired because you [ __ ] ain't. So,
you can't even say that either.
You're sat on YouTube every day because
you ain't got a life. Simple. That's it.
You ain't retired.
How the [ __ ] do you retire at [ __ ] 40
years of age? Retired at 40 years of
age. Not possible.
How do you retire at 40 years of age, bro? Strange. Madness.
Um, how do I come back the next day?
Again, I'll repeat myself cuz you got
brain damage. I've literally took weeks
off of YouTube. I think it's strange
that you people call other people's skin
yet you're sat on YouTube every day
writing comments. That's what I find strange.
>> Yeah, I find that very strange that you
you call other people's skin, right? And
that you got all this money yet you're
skintselves and you ain't got no money.
And bro, like I keep saying, I could
have £400 to my name and I'd still have
a better life than all of yours. So yeah,
you don't really make any sense, do you? You know, yeah, man.
Yeah, I was using £300 as an example.
Yeah, it was it was an example,
but you know what I'm saying? And I'd
have more of a life than you. It was an
example, dick weed. But you people claim
you got all this money, but you're sat
on YouTube every day. It's mad, isn't
it? Mad that. Calling other people for
what you are. That's mad that, bro. Bye-bye now.
Nice, man. I'm just chilling.
I'm just chilling. Playing GTA.
Yeah, I'm just playing GTA, bro. [ __ ]
just Well, not long come back from the cinema. Yeah, mom. Yeah.
Got to put one on it. Yeah, man.
They don't want to go all that way if
they don't meet.
Oh, it's long, bro.
Then that's going to be another probably two300 pound.
It's bad, is it, bro? [ __ ] bad.
got some simp comments so I had to delete it. Yeah.
It's bad, bro.
Here we go with the [ __ ] [ __ ] hell.
Oh, bro. No. I was trying with this
person in Birmingham.
Oh, bro. They're they're they're [ __ ]
me around proper.
Just goes to show that this country will
never ever change. I really need to
start looking into plan B, bro. Well, we
know what plan B already is, but this
another thing I was thinking cuz I had a
lot of free time that you you need plan
B now, bro. We're beyond all of this.
Even though like we were trying, we
giving up. I don't know how many times
until you get the point, it is not going
to change in this country till you learn, bro.
It is never ever going to change. If
anything now, it's just going to get worse. So
I've got 189 numbers and to be honest
I'd say about 80% of them are women from cold bridges
and then it's not even that then I've
got to go all the way back there anyway.
So it's mad.
It's just like I'm the thing is bro I'm
27. Yeah. And you know I'm going to be
28 in two months and I'm still playing
these games with people bro. I'm still
playing these [ __ ] games with people.
It's [ __ ] annoying, bro. Like, you'd
expect it from a [ __ ] 18, 19, [ __ ]
20 year [ __ ] old, bro. Not somebody
at the same age as you.
It's just the same old, bro. It's boring
as [ __ ] Boring as hell. It will never
[ __ ] change. It is so annoying.
And I shouldn't even be laughing at it.
You know them times when I laugh at it,
bro. To be fair, I shouldn't even be
laughing, bro. Why? There's nothing to laugh at.
There's nothing to laugh. There's
nothing to laugh at
really, bro. Like, I've tried more than
anyone in the world. Why? Why the [ __ ]
am I even laughing at it, bro? It's not
even something to laugh at, really.
We'll give them to next week anyways.
It's It will never change, bro. Unless
you've got a million subscribers on
YouTube or Instagram, they ain't
interested in this country. End of.
Unless you got some sort of status or
some sort of following, you're [ __ ]
Simple. That's how it is, bro.
You know, and I was thinking about this
when I was in the cinema earlier as
well. It's bad. It's bad, bro. It is
bad, man. Well, we weren't even Well, we
were not even certain that would work,
but it would get their attention.
It definitely get their attention.
Unless you're something like that, bro,
you've got no chance. If you didn't meet anyone before um
social like before Tik Tok become big or
this whole Instagram or you didn't get
lucky at work, you're [ __ ] You are
[ __ ] now. Simple. It's it's it's
simple as that, bro. You're Scrooge
McGood. You're [ __ ] You know,
it's bad. It's bad. It's [ __ ] bad, bro.
And you know, the maddest thing about
it, bro, is I wouldn't mind if you was
fat and ugly or you hadn't tried as much
as you did or then I would understand it
kind of thing. Or like I said, if it's
been going on for 6 months to a year,
then I'd be like, "Okay." But bro, this
has been going on for years now.
Like, it's [ __ ] it's depressing, bro.
Like, it is really really depressing. Yeah.
It's bad. Unless you got a million
subscribers on YouTube
or a million Instagram followers, it's a
waste of time even trying.
Like it is a waste of time you even
trying to even speak to someone. No.
Like all serious like all jokes aside
now I know we laugh about this, you know.
So unless you got a million subscribers
or a million followers, you're [ __ ] basically.
Like you were supposed to be going to
Belgium, you said this week. How are you
not going now?
That doesn't make no sense. You said
that you was going Belgium. See, I'm
still playing these games as a 27 year
old man. You said that you was going to Belgium.
Then you're saying you're not going to
Belgium. And then you said you're tired.
You want to stay in Birmingham. Then I
turned around and said, "Oh, okay. What
if I come to Birmingham tomorrow? Didn't
really think it through then. Oh, well,
it's my friend's birthday. No, no, no.
It's just the same old same old, bro.
You know, I've actually done it before
when I've actually gone to Nottingham
and I don't It's not even It's not even
a W, bro. Like, do you really think I
want to go all the way [ __ ] back
there? It's [ __ ] long.
But it's good to know that even Oh, [ __ ]
She didn't have an excuse. She just blocked me. Oh, [ __ ]
It will never change, bro. Never ever ever change.
It will How could it? That's That's
That's the question, bro. Is how the
[ __ ] could it?
Well, we'll give them till next week anyways.
If they're still making excuses, then
[ __ ] B them off in it.
So they didn't give an excuse. They just blocked randomly.
It will never change. And and you know
the thing is you know people like Joe.
Yeah. He says, "Oh, you should speak to
them." Oh, you should speak to them. Oh,
yeah. Keep somebody entertained for a
month, bro. Is it? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Cuz they're totally
right in interested stuff, aren't they?
It's like these people don't get it, bro.
It's [ __ ] winding me up today, bro.
I'm not even joking. It's annoying.
It's [ __ ] dead ass winding me up,
bro. I'm not even joking with you. It's
[ __ ] annoying. It's just the same
old, bro. And you know these people
recently, they've actually been the same
age as me as well, you know?
They're the same age as me.
Why? I don't go out anymore, bro. It's
why I don't bother no more. Oh [ __ ]
This is why I don't bother no more, bro.
I went to B him cuz Monty was crying and
I won that football bet. Else I wouldn't
bother doing anything, bro. They They
will never change. They're all the same. They're NPCs.
They're [ __ ] It's like It's like what
Antman said. You can see the westernity
in their eyes. Yeah.
You can see the westernity in their
eyes. It will never change. Think like
let me let me let me explain this. Say
you meet a French woman and she does
something, right? Every single other
French woman you will meet will do
exactly the same thing. If you met a
Romanian woman, every single Romanian
woman you meet would do exactly the same
thing. If you met an American, every
single American would do exact. They're
all the same. Depending on where they're
from, like nationality wise, they will
always do exactly the same thing
depending on where they're from. That's
what my experience is. I had that with
six French people. It never ever
changes, bro. But it took it took me a
long [ __ ] time to wake up and and and
finally give up here, bro.
Just looking for plan B now, bro. Well,
we know what plan B is. Like it took cuz
I was always thinking that it was going to change.
You know what I'm saying, bro? I I was
always like under the impression that
like it was going to change.
So, but I've noticed that no matter
depending on where they're from, once
you've meet one, once you meet one,
you've basically met all of them.
They literally are all the same. Like, I
I used to make, bro, I used to make
jokes about this before, like, oh, maybe
it's the wrong ones. And but no, they
they generally are the table. Am I out
tonight? Um, well, considering I've said
about a million times, I'm not going out
anymore. Uh, no.
And I and I dead ass mean it. I went out
last week because of Monty and I won a
football bet. So I had no excuse to go.
I didn't go for [ __ ] women because I
knew it was just going to be the same
old. It would always be the same old.
You stay here. It's always going to be
the same old. That That's it, bro. I'm
used to it now. So,
like I said, there's only a few ways
this is ever going to change. You become
a famous YouTuber,
which is not going to happen. They ban
social media, which is not going to
happen, or you go to or you use escorts
for the rest of your life, or you go to
Thailand, or you go anywhere in Asia, or
you go to South America. That's the only
way it's going to change, you know.
Like, think of think of just the amount
of numbers I've got on my phone so far.
188. A lot of [ __ ] numbers, bro. 189,
actually. That's a lot of [ __ ]
numbers, bro. And they're just they're
they're just WhatsApp contacts.
If you didn't meet anyone a few years
ago, you've had it, bro. That's just the
way it is, you know?
because like how the [ __ ] are you
supposed to go to Belgium, right?
And then um all of a sudden now you're
not in Belgium.
That doesn't even make sense.
Nah, it's not even that. No, no, it's
not even that at all. What annoys me is
because I've tried more than anyone in
the world and I'm not fat and ugly.
That's the thing that annoys me. That's
that's actually what annoys me, bro.
And it will never change.
Like you say to someone now, you [ __ ]
mean it now, bro. It's is what it is.
Nah, it's not even that, bro. If I
didn't have a trying history, I wouldn't
I wouldn't mind it. I'd be like, "Oh,
well, I didn't try much." Or, "Oh, it's
only been happening for a year." Then I
could be like, "Okay, whatever.
But it's because you tried more than
anybody in the whole wide world.
And I've not met any everyone in the
world, but I know no one tried more than me. So
yeah, that's the thing that's annoying,
bro. And even when you give up, it's still happening.
Unless you've got a million subscribers,
bro, that's the way it's always going to be.
You can't even get attention without followers. It's bad.
Try and try and don't change your
situation. You need to leave the country.
You need to leave the West. It's that's
it, bro. We're We're beyond everything
else now. Like, it's,
you know, there's nothing else. Um,
it's bad. It is really really bad, though.
It shouldn't be how many followers
someone has or whatever. But
unfortunately, that's the way it is, you know?
It's madness, isn't it?
And we're still getting these excuses.
We're still getting this [ __ ]
It's not funny. It's It's [ __ ]
annoying, especially when it's people
your age as well. Like when it's people
like round about your age.
It's so [ __ ] bastard [ __ ] annoying,
you know? And I didn't even speak to
anyone even earlier to be honest with
you, bro. I just It's just annoying. The
whole thing just annoys me.
Where did my other airport go?
You used to get them people on Reddit
that say, "Oh, keep trying. Keep trying.
Keep trying." Like, you need to make a
decision now, bro. At 27. Like, it's now
or never. You can't keep doing this the
rest of your life, bro. You know, you
try another [ __ ] let's say, bro, look
at this. How many years we been doing
this? You try another [ __ ] seven
years, 8 years, you'll be almost
middleaged and you're still going to be
in the same position. Like, bro, you
can't waste another seven, eight years,
you know, doing this. It's time now to
really think about like what what you're doing, bro,
in terms of another plan because it's
like you prove you got nothing left to
prove. There's nothing left to prove
now. It's [ __ ] The dating game in
this country is is absolutely
Scrooge McGood's [ __ ]
You're not going to change it, bro. What
there's nothing the only thing you can
do is like I said, leave. So, it's like
that's the only thing that's in your
control is leave is leaving him.
So, that's it, bro. It's [ __ ] bad,
bro. It is really bad.
Think about it today, bro. I went out
today. Let's just say, for example, I
went out today. It would be the same [ __ ]
It would be the same [ __ ] old [ __ ]
It's not like these people are young
anymore, you know? 26, 27, 28, and they
still do this [ __ ] I mean, I think they
still do in their 40s to be honest with you.
[ __ ] the game up, bro.
Um, where's this other earbud?
It's really bad.
So, what makes you think the next 108?
So, in them, so I got 16 numbers in three days.
Well, it's better than nothing. Well,
it's either escorts or nothing. So,
which one do you pick?
It's either escorts or nothing.
So, it's either escorts or nothing
cuz you're never going to get in a
relationship because it wouldn't happen
by now. Well, you Well, you you can get
in a relationship. Well, actually saying
that you can get in a relationship, but
just not in this country. You can get in a relationship. Um,
but you won't get one in this country.
So, I mean, you go to Cambodia,
Philippines, they want a relationship.
Um, they don't even want money either.
So, you could,
but in this country, you're not going to
get a relationship.
Well, I don't anyway from other people.
Where's my other earod?
Oh, what the [ __ ]
So yeah, man.
So that's the only thing you can do is
leave this country. You can you can you
you can literally go on Tinder, bro. You
know, if you're in if you're if you go
to the Philippines or you go to
Thailand, right, and you go on Tinder,
you can actually get people come to you,
get people actually meet you,
you know, like there's people that
actually want relationships with you out
there, you know, here they ain't interested.
Cuz I was thinking, what the [ __ ] is he
talking about a million followers? But
he's actually right. Unless you're some
sort of big YouTuber or you got loads of
followers, they're not interested.
So, it's just a waste of your time and
money even trying really. Yeah.
Yeah. I was just saying, Grevy, it's mad
like to be almost like 28, the same age
as you, and you're still dealing with
people that play silly games.
Like, when let's let's just like have an
open opinion here. Yeah. When will it change then?
Because it's been happening for years.
You've been up and down the country
numerous times like Ant-Man said.
How many more years into it possibly
changes? [ __ ] how could it? You know,
that's what I'm saying. My my question
is the n word. How could it? Not even
not even to be racist. Like it it it's
an expression. How could it? How the
[ __ ] could it, bro?
Cuz it wasn't it wasn't like this years.
It weren't like this two and a half
years ago, bro. I might have [ __ ] a
few up maybe two two years ago. Two
years ago. Yeah. You know, maybe you
could have, you know, maybe you might
have [ __ ] a few up, but bro, I'm
telling you, in the past year and a
half, it's been [ __ ] Probably even two years
>> to be fair.
>> Yes, PJ. Yes, PJ. What you do with my life?
>> No, just Monty's starting [ __ ] again.
>> No, Timmy. Timmy starting [ __ ] again.
Yeah, Timmy s your [ __ ] disabled face
out, you [ __ ] rat for a gun, man.
[ __ ] knock you out, you spasticated rat.
Yeah, you know what I was actually thinking today? >> What
>> I was thinking? One minute. Yeah, these
people on here. Yeah, they go on about
money every day. But listen, bro. Yeah.
>> If they've got all of this money, what
life are they living? Think of it. Think
of it. Think of it. They've got all of this money.
Listen, listen, listen. Stop reacting to
these little [ __ ] low lives here.
>> I'm not reacting. I'm I'm curious. No,
no, no. I'm wondering.
>> It's a shame. It's a shame. They haven't
got money. the disabled little [ __ ]
fat [ __ ] who get jealous over other
people when they in relationships. That's it.
>> Then call other people pedals and that's it.
>> They're just [ __ ] idiots online.
Yeah. There's nothing special to these
at all. If there was anything special to
these, don't don't you think they come
to me now
>> or they come to you now
>> or they want to come to us in Birmingham
or when whatever. Do you know what I
mean? They're [ __ ] weasels. All of
them in weasel. That's And they [ __ ]
know it. They know it.
>> Yeah. No, never. Never.
I got a new tattoo, mate. Did you see my new tattoo?
>> Yeah, I saw her, bro.
>> Nice. Is it? >> Yeah.
>> [ __ ] Natalie [ __ ] initial on me arm.
>> Nice, bro. When are you seeing her again?
>> Uh, next week. Next week's coming. >> Yeah.
>> Nice, man.
Met tomorrow in Birmingham. saying where
we going though it's not saying where we going but
>> you're going to Birmingham tomorrow
>> LJ is not even going Birmingham LJ
thinks he's meeting Natalie is [ __ ]
meeting Natalie Natalie's already told
me she's not she's not meeting him so L
can keep playing these little games with
me what's not even wicked Lord J you
want me to come Birmingham tomorrow if
you're going to Birmingham
yeah I will go Birmingham tomorrow if
you really want me to Lord yeah I'll
meet you there tomorrow Lord yeah but I
100% Natalie's not meeting you tomorrow.
You [ __ ] ugly man. Rice has got
better looks than you.
>> Yeah, man.
>> For [ __ ] sake, Lord J. Rice. Rice has
got better looks than you. Lord J on the
next level [ __ ] right there. Lord J,
you change your [ __ ] freak.
>> [ __ ] you.
>> Did you mean it? It won't change. Oh,
look. It's the boring repeating waste of
PJ saying that you're boring. Bye-bye. Blocked.
>> I'm not being funny, but you always
repeat, don't you? Lord J is a little
[ __ ] weasel sat on YouTube. Can't
even meet me. He can't even meet me.
>> This way. If they were better than us,
they wouldn't be sat on YouTube every day repeated.
>> No, they won't. Lord ain't got no
[ __ ] life. Wait till Lord actually
comes to England. Wait, wait, wait.
>> Yeah, man.
>> I meet him. I'll [ __ ] meet him. He
knows he will. He knows to meet him.
>> Where was Timmy when we were shouting
him out? Yeah.
>> Where was Where was Money Mike? Where
was that little clown grabbed hold of
you? All three of them were shouting
them out. Exactly.
She was with me, Lord. Yeah. Wait till
you come drinking me next time. Yeah.
You [ __ ] little things.
Yeah. You think I'm some soft ass, Lord.
Yeah. Literally. Literally.
I [ __ ] stop your joy two places. Lord,
you're not going meeting no Natalie. Lord J,
you think you are, but that's not
pissing me off cuz I already know you're
not meeting her. You think you freak,
>> I didn't know you were that desperate,
Lord J, by calling the [ __ ] out of my
misses and then sitting there saying,
"No, it's all banned to me and they
always do it." What? When you're the one
who docks to address as well as a mom,
Lord J. Yeah, you teach little freak.
>> Madness, lad.
>> Wait till it comes to England once.
Wait, wait. Anywhere. Anywhere. I just
go to him.
If he shouts out to me, if he shouts out
you, I will go to him. I will go to Lord
J. What's he going to do to me? What?
Back and forth. Back and forth saying,
"Come on then." Man, I belly I belly
punch him, man. I winged him.
>> I I just give him a good old kidney jab.
Punch him right in the side of his
[ __ ] ribs. I'll knock him down. Go
and breathe in, man. You won't be able
to breathe for a week.
>> I just kidney jabbed the [ __ ]
No, you won't fight a man like me. You
none of the usual fight a man like me.
All you in this community are scared of
a man like me.
>> Put me on big screen, please. Yeah,
>> put me on big screen. >> Okay.
>> Ghostbusters. Who do you want to go? The Washing. Washing.
Where you going to go? The Ghostbusters
in a neighbor.
Let me get it.
Can I draw it on here?
You peeps. YouTube in it. Look. Ghostbusters.
You got that.
Look. Ghostbusters. SP. I won't get him
on camera. Ghostbusters.
You can put back on normal now. >> Yeah.
>> Got the Ghostbuster machine on his back.
It's bad this situation, is it, Nicolai, bro? It's [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] not normal, bro. It's
[ __ ] up, is it?
>> No. Yeah, but please listen. Yeah. All
what they used to do. Yeah. We say [ __ ]
to try and rhyme people up. Yeah. Don't
wind me up. They embarrass themselves. They don't
>> They really do. They do. They really
[ __ ] do embarrass theelves. They
really do. I've had enough of these
little clowns in this community. They're
not bothering me by calling me a not
when they sitting there calling
everybody a nuts every [ __ ] day. And
then you got people in every video what
what I do talking about Lola all the
time. You [ __ ] idiots. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? They [ __ ]
idiots and they go around calling other
people pedos when they bring up my
children once again. Once again. >> Yeah.
These are the nons on this community. If
I wasn't n think Natalie would go out
with me. Would she [ __ ] Would she [ __ ]
Lord G? You're you're just upset because
you can't get a misses and you had a
shag since 1991, you [ __ ]
My norally what you do, Lord J, is spit
and [ __ ] gross. That's a good old
[ __ ] wank you do, Lord. Yeah.
That's it. A good old [ __ ] wank.
>> Yeah, pretty much.
>> Anyway, pitch, I'm going to shoot. Yeah.
>> Yeah, man. I'll talk to you later.
>> I'm at man's [ __ ] field bus station,
man. So, I'm going to jump on the bus.
>> All right.
>> See you in a bit. Yeah.
>> Yeah, man.
Yeah, Nicolo. So,
that's where we're at basically, bro.
It's depressing, isn't it?
You say [ __ ] going halfway across the
world, but bro, if that's the way it's
got to be,
that's the way it's got to be, bro. You
know, even if it is for a month, I mean,
Antman's saying he's coming back only
because of like the money he gets a
month from the working ain't enough cuz
he's like out every night, you know what
I mean? So, that's the only reason I
think he's coming back.
I said, "Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro. You're
going to be back to the I've got a
boyfriend [ __ ] again. Oh, [ __ ] that.
Imagine not hearing it for all them
months. Yeah. And then coming back
hearing it again.
Oh, no. [ __ ] that, bro.
It's boring, isn't it?
Remember, man, the only place you're not
going to get that is Asia.
Just sounds mad. Some of the things he
comes out with is sounds mad.
No, he's teaching English.
Do you know what made me laugh? Yeah.
Um, Antman said that he went to Benador
and they were saying it over there as
well that they've got boyfriends.
He said, um, yeah, they they said they
had it there, too. He said it's just
full of English people. Yeah.
Imagine that, bro. Going Spain and
hearing it in Spain. [ __ ] that, bro.
It's [ __ ] annoying as [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, it is annoying.
Yeah, bro. It's proper annoying.
It's depressing, bro. It is depressing.
We usually say it will never change.
How could it change, bro? How the [ __ ]
could it change? Everyone's still
[ __ ] on TikTok. Everyone's still on Instagram.
You will never change. Never.
It's the only place you're not going to get Asia.
Well, it's so mad to just say that, you know.
It's funny, bro.
It's madness, isn't it?
And it's all cuz of social media as well.
All because of social media. Yep.
Unless they were all going to go Belgium
and then they just decided to not go.
But how do you decide last minute you're
not going to [ __ ] go on a trip like
that? It's madness.
I mean, Nicolo
You remember that Mr. G account, Nicolo?
That Mr. G from Edinburgh?
Yeah, he was a [ __ ] ass.
Yeah. But how how do you
say you're going to go somewhere then don't go?
Then it's like, "Oh, I'll go to
Birmingham." Then then there's an excuse.
Then there's an excuse for that as well. Well,
never changes. Nicolo never changes.
They say about stopping in Birmingham,
but they don't realize that crazy [ __ ]
Peter Bennett goes everywhere.
I went to Wales on a Friday, then the
next Friday I went back to Wales. Um,
I done it as well with another city. I'm
sure I did.
Sure. There was somewhere else I' done that.
Maybe not. But
no, she says she's in Birmingham now. So
I was like, "Oh, I'll go to Birmingham."
And then she turned around and said, she
says, "No, she says, I'm quite tired and
I think I want to stop in Birmingham." I
said, "Haha, you don't want to come to
London." I could come to Birmingham. It
was fun last week, so why not? Don't
think I will have the time to go out
tomorrow to be fair. It's one of my
friends birthday, so I'm not sure. So
then I turn around and said, "Let's meet
next week." And if they still make
excuses, then I'm just going to delete their number.
Simple. Cuz I always give people the
beneficiary of the doubt, you know. But
if they say something about next week,
then yeah, I'm going to just delete their number.
Then obviously I went to Birmingham to
see Monty, didn't I? All right. And uh
obviously I killed two birds and one stone.
But then I've got this person as well.
Uh I'm on holiday that weekend. Sorry.
That was one.
Then another one reply back. These are
all the Birmingham ones.
I generally thought one of them would
have would have met, you know, like at
least one of them.
This one said, "Hey, um, what they say?"
They said, "Um, hi." Hey,
they said they said, "One sec. Hey, so
I'm going to be moving house, so not a
good time. Unfortunately, I'm also going
to be away at a wedding in Spain.
So that where was you thinking anyway?
So I said obviously Liverpool cuz they
live in Liverpool.
[ __ ] mad that is, bro. No, they
didn't reply, but they might reply at
some point. They're moving and [ __ ] But
I actually thought one of them would
have met, bro, cuz they all replied like
they all replied with enthusiasm. So I I
just thought like one would have met but
because I'm so used to it and it's never
going to change. So
so you know it's like it will never
change in this country. So there's
nothing to to to say or do. It will
never change. It's been the same for years.
How's it going to change, bro? So yeah,
not that one. I don't know. One of them might meet.
You would like to think one of them
would at least meet. But yeah.
Well, yeah. Enough is enough. That's why
I'm leaving England. That's why I booked
Thailand for [ __ ] um November.
I mean, that's why I booked the flights
cuz enough is literally enough.
And I'm not out today and I'm not out
tomorrow. Even if that football bet wins
tomorrow, I'm still not going out tomorrow.
I'll probably just chill and play
Franklin. Yeah, I still want to go out
tomorrow. Even if the bro, I weren't
going to go out last week even when the
football bet won. But because Monty was
[ __ ] he needed someone and that I
thought [ __ ] it, why not? And it so
and I said I was going to go. So, but I
won't even go out tomorrow, bro. Even
the Phil wins.
I've met them all now, bro. I've met them all.
You will never change.
I would like to say some people are
supposed to be single cuz you're not
supposed to be single. You're good-look.
But because of Tik Tok and because of
Instagram and these sibs, they [ __ ]
the dating game up.
That's how it is. So, and there's
nothing that can that can be done now.
You've done everything you've done, you
can do. You know, I've done everything I Um,
see this this stuff that's happening, no
offense here, this stuff should be
happening to people like Timmy
being a friend zone or being let down
gently or, you know, about a million
excuses. This stuff, like, no offense,
should be happening to people like
Timmy. It shouldn't be happening to
people like me. And in the 1980s,
it would not be happening to people like me.
You understand? This should be happening
to people like [ __ ] Timmy,
people like [ __ ] Money Mike, people
like [ __ ] Tiger. The It should be
happening to all of these people.
[ __ ] downright stinking ugly people.
It shouldn't be happening to people like
me. Cuz it wouldn't be happening if
there was no social media. It shouldn't
be happening to people like me cuz
they're not above you.
But because of these social media
bullets and these simps and where social
media has got in their head, it should
not be happening to someone like me.
Bro, if you if this was
even 2005, you would be pulling [ __ ]
with the way that I look now. You can't
even get nothing. You can't even get a
date out your own city. It's [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] bro. It is [ __ ] up, man.
You don't even get given a chance.
[ __ ] that. That's the kind of people it
should be happening to, not people like me.
I do say to my mom sometimes, I wish
you'd had me like in the 1980s, 19 even
Yeah. 1980s cuz
obviously best horror films, Chucky was
out in the 1980s. There was no social
media. Now, like you won't be with
anyone now. You won't have a child.
You're not you're going to have to look around
at other people and there's nothing you
can do about it unless you go Asia and
get unless you get a Thai bride. So
unless you go to Asia, you're just Asia,
you're just going to have to keep
dealing with it, looking at it.
It's [ __ ] up and there's literally
nothing you can do to change it as well.
That's the most [ __ ] up thing, bro.
You should be able to just go out and
just meet someone, get a date every week
or every other week, but nah, not in
this country, mate.
It's really bad. And I text some of them
numbers I got throughout the whole two
months saying, "Oh, they want to go
cinema tomorrow. They want to go
drinks." And yeah, none of them will fight back.
It's bad, bro. It is really bad.
They're not getting into relationships.
They've already been in relationships.
They've been in relationships already. So,
the only thing annoys me is the amount
of tried. That's the annoying thing about it.
That's the that's that's the that's the
worst thing is because of the amount
you've actually tried and the fact that
you're good-looking as well. That's the
thing that doesn't make no sense about
it cuz you're good-looking and you've tried,
you know, like
it's bad. It really, really, really is
It's really really bad, bro. That's [ __ ]
I need to try and think of a long-term solution, man.
To be fair,
imagine you were starting off now,
though. Imagine three years ago you were
starting off now.
It's depressing. [ __ ] It's not even
like you can say, "Oh, let me go out
now." You know, there's a little bit of
chance. Let me go out and show them
who's boss because we've done it a
million times. We done it last week.
You know, like we we done it last week
even though I've given up. You know,
it's that's the thing.
If it if it was how it was now, there'd
be no [ __ ] No, you know, I can't
even remember the last time I even got
got a kiss out of someone. That is bad,
bro. Cuz you know when we used to go to
the thing every week to the O'Neals, you
know, the Walder Street O'Neals, we'd
get like a kiss or a touch and we'd get
like a like that whole year when I met
USA Izzy, I went on so many dates, bro.
kisses, so many dates, you know,
explicit stuff in the club. Like there
was actually things I was like, I sort
of [ __ ] it up for myself. Like back
that year, I [ __ ] a lot of it up for
myself. And even when I came back from
Belgium, like there was times years ago
where I did, but the past two years,
bro, it's been dead as a donkey. I'm not
even I'm not even joking. Like the past two years,
um, that year was the best year, bro.
The whole April was good and then then
it's just going worse and worse and
worse and worse and worse. You can bar
you can't even get a kiss.
You can't even get a kiss which a kiss
is nothing. You can't even get anything. Um
I got 13 numbers in [ __ ] three days.
So in 4 days I got 16 numbers in 4 days and nothing. So,
I'm not sure what you could do, bro.
Unless that person comes back, that
20-year-old, you're [ __ ] That's the
only way I can I can see it. But they're
all westernized now as well, so that's no good.
It's really bad, bro.
It's really, really bad.
Um, and then obviously USA, you know,
even if you could get things like that,
you know what I had with USA, but you
can't even get that anymore.
You can't get nothing, bro. You can't get anything.
You can't get anything with anyone, you know?
But somehow these people want to make
you believe that one day it's going to
change. How How can it change?
Think of how quickly it change. Yeah.
When we met at USA, we had people that
same April. We had people April, we had
AP, we had people in I know I don't like
that [ __ ] but we had people that
April, we had that one in [ __ ]
Nottingham that April, April. What did I
mean? April, May, June. That whole
summer we we had [ __ ] But this has been
dried. It's been dead now for [ __ ] a
god. It's not It's not going to change,
bro. It will change for the worse.
That's all it will change for.
No, I don't I'm not going to do that,
bro. I don't like the [ __ ] But it's an
example, you know, a one night stand,
sex, whatever. It's an example. I don't
like the [ __ ]
The only reason I said, "Oh, I love
Morgan the other day is because [ __ ]
Monty kept [ __ ] going like Natalie
and it was doing my [ __ ] heading, so
I thought, [ __ ] it, I'll join in with
him." I don't [ __ ] like that [ __ ] bro. Sorry.
>> Well, obviously we still got them two
numbers. Maybe in two weeks they might
accept to meet if you go up there. One
of them lives in [ __ ] Liverpool, though. So, [ __ ] Liverpool. Yeah, man.
I could go out today and send it all day
long, but it's not going to change, bro. Yeah. Byebye.
And you know the thing is, you know how
hard relationships are, Nicolo. Like,
you know, get like um a relationship,
you know, like the thing is, bro, it's
not even like
obviously it's not important to a lot of
it. It's not even like you you can get
laid, but you can't get in a
relationship because, you know, like
let's just say like some people can't
get in relationships until they find the
right one. You can't even get laid.
Like, you can't even get sex. you can't
even get anything
until you is actually trying to find
someone that um
that actually wants a relationship.
So, you wouldn't even be able to even get sex
if that's what you know you wanted.
They spend a lot of time on this uh WhatsApp, man. Uh a
Yeah, exactly, bro. You can't even get a
combo out of them. Let let alone a date.
It's bad, bro. It is bad. It is really
No, I don't really want to go to
Birmingham again tomorrow, but if they
said yeah, then so be it.
You think I really want to go back to
that [ __ ] Oh, but so be it, bro. So be
it. Like I said, the only difference I
found in Birmingham and London is that
they actually replied back with enthusiasm,
which was nice, even though I don't
Well, one of them is definitely not
going to meet. I mean, it was nice, you
know, because you can't even you don't
even get that in London, but that's the only difference.
That was the only difference that I got. Um,
but I don't like Birmingham, but if they
said they would have met, then I would
have just went back there.
It probably would have cost like £300,
but so be it. Who cares?
They are [ __ ] NPCs.
And I got some I got some a lot of
numbers the two weeks ago as well. Don't
forget, I've got a whole collection of numbers. So,
it's really bad, bro. I wish I could
just find someone that doesn't play
games, just a normal person that's 27
and 28, but you can't find anyone.
They're all the same. That's what I'm saying.
Yeah. And then and then they say they've
got a boyfriend at the end of the
conversation. That's the worst is when
they talk back. Yeah.
There is a way. There is a way we can we
can get it back to the 1980s. If these
simps would just [ __ ] off and just stop
sing, then everyone's happy. They get
laid. [ __ ] I get in a relationship, I
get [ __ ] laid. They stay on the
internet and keep sing. Everyone's just
going to be a [ __ ] virgin now, bro.
People that's never had sex. Do you
understand, bro? You understand? It's
all these simps. If they stopped, Think
about it, bro. They think sing is going
to get them laid. They never get laid.
Simp get you laid, but they still simp.
If they stopped the sing [ __ ] they
would get no attention. They would need
attention and they'd give people sex.
But no, the simps can't help themselves,
you know, especially on Instagram. So,
it [ __ ] it up for everyone, you know?
Yeah. The Australians always do that,
bro. They love saying they've got boyfriends.
Like I said, once you've met, every
nationality you meet is the same. All
the Australian women are the same. All
Russian women are the same. All French
women are the same. They all do all the
same thing as the other people from the
other women. That's the same as their nationality.
You know what I mean?
You keep telling yourself that, mate.
There's plenty of people with [ __ ]
jobs and a car and muscles and they're
either really fat, ugly women or they
can't get anything.
You keep telling yourself that.
No, they [ __ ] don't, mate. You
remember when they used to tell me that,
Nicolo? Oh, a woman doesn't want a guy
that lives with his mom.
I live by myself. I was working. I was
going to the gym. Nothing happened.
Still got the I've got a boyfriend [ __ ]
That's just excuses.
I was living by myself. I was working. I
was going to the gym. Same old.
Same old. And I actually was doing that
for a very long time.
So that's all [ __ ]
And I was going to the gym as well, bro.
And I was working. I don't live by myself.
So, you know, it's [ __ ] bro.
They want people with a million
subscribers on YouTube.
Yeah. Unless you've got a million
Unless you're someone like Mashtag,
you're [ __ ] Or KSI.
No, you don't need to be KSI's level.
I'd say a million will do, but it can't
be under a million cuz there's some
channels that have got 200 of 200,000
subscribers, but that's not enough. It
needs to be like a million. They need to
be well known. So once you're well
known, then you can get if you if you
don't have a million subscribers on
YouTube, you're [ __ ] Um,
that sounds ridiculous, but it's true.
Like, do you ever do you ever watch
these YouTubers and you get them these
women? Oh, can I get a picture? They're
not going to say no to them people.
So, it's about money, but it's also about status.
That's the big thing. This is about
status. So, if you ain't got that, bro,
you can be as good-looking as as
anything and they don't give a [ __ ]
They're not interested. Simple.
You know, like medium subscribers would
do, bro. million
like someone like KSI or
Yeah, good for you. You must have got
lucky years ago.
Well, I get what I mean because I've
been up and out of the country.
Oh, well well yeah, but what if he
turned around and said, "Can you would
you shag me?" What do you think they'd
say? Okay. Okay. I was watching
Mashtag's latest video. Yeah. And this
woman come up saying, "Oh, you mash tag.
Can I get a picture?" What do you think
she would say if if he said, "Oh, do you
want to [ __ ] or he got her number and he
wanted to got he wanted a relationship?"
What do you think they're going to say
no to him? Of course, they're not going
to say no to him because A, he's
probably a [ __ ] millionaire and B,
he's got subscribers.
Like, he's he's well established, so
they're not going to say no to him.
No one. They're not going to say no to
him, bro. But they probably go on their
Instagram inbox and they get all of
these women messaging them, messaging
them, messaging them, [ __ ] KSI and
all of them. Bro, you think they can't
get laid? You think they can't [ __ ]
get in a relationship?
But I get what I mean. Anyways, to
answer your question, I get what I I get
what I mean cuz I've been up and down
the country. So, I get what I mean.
I get what I mean with these women. I
get it. I get exactly what I mean. So, yeah.
Well, maybe they wouldn't get with these
people, but they sure as hell can get their attention. But
imagine that never even worked. Imagine
they wouldn't even date a big YouTuber.
then you are [ __ ]
I mean, I went to Birmingham last week.
I got three numbers and
I I only thought one of them was going
to meet because of the way they replied
back and it was all of them. It wasn't
just one of them. But same old Saturday,
I guess. No date, watching the football.
Pretty boring life, isn't it?
Oh, they are slags.
They're [ __ ] evil as well.
But USA is evil as well. They are. They're evil.
You should say evil slags, bro. You
shouldn't just say slags. You say evil
But yeah, anyone would think I look like [ __ ] Timmy. [Music]
And I was thinking like in the cinema
was greasy. I'm probably never going to
get a [ __ ] again. All I kept thinking
about in the cinema was like [ __ ]
[ __ ] and [ __ ]
cuz there was some sex scenes, but
you're not going to get a [ __ ] ever again.
A [ __ ] bro. You can't even get a
[ __ ] conversation out of the [ __ ]
unless they're taking the [ __ ] piss.
A [ __ ] [ __ ] Nah.
Nah, you're [ __ ] Just accept the fact
that you're [ __ ]
And you weren't born in the 1980s and
there's nothing you can do about it now.
You can't, bro. There's nothing you can do now.
just wish I was born in the Chucky days.
I'm not even just saying that. I just
wish I was born in the 80s, bro.
But I wasn't. So,
to be honest with you, I'm surprised I
even Well, say that I did I did go all
over the [ __ ] country. But it it it
seems weird looking back on it to think
that like you actually did pull,
you know, like you did get kisses, you
fingered, you went on dates, you [ __ ]
in hotel rooms. Looking back on it, it
it seems mad because now you can't even
get a conversation out of the [ __ ]
So you're thinking like, geez, like
that's actually mad.
You know what would have been worse,
Nicolo. I said this to my mom the other
day is say you didn't have the house for
3 years, you would have been [ __ ]
See, it's not it's not too bad now cuz
I'm past the whole going out and I've
still got money and I'm not going to be
going out every week anymore anyways.
But let's just say in them 3 years when
you was in your prime. Imagine that.
Imagine that, bro.
Imagine that you you did not have that
house for 3 years.
You would have been [ __ ] You wouldn't
even have the money to even go out and
keep winding yourself up. It's [ __ ]
up, man. And don't forget that house was
once in a lifetime opportunity to have
had that house and three grand a month
for not working for a month.
That was a one in a lifetime um thing.
So, if you didn't have that, you would
have been even more [ __ ] you would
because you wouldn't have been able to
go out the way you did. So, it's bad. It
is bad, bro.
They would though. I think they would
shag him. I think they would though,
Nico. I think they would shag him.
So what you think if Mash tag Yeah.
wanted to get laid, no one would shag
him? Okay, let's just put let's just say
Mashtag wanted to get laid. Yeah. And I
want to get laid. Who do you think's
going to get laid? Me or him?
He would get laid, bro. Of course he
would. All he'd have to do is go on [ __ ] Instagram.
But what's weird is it happens to other
people as well. So it's not even just
me. Like I said, I watch this guy in
America. I watch other people do it and
they get the same [ __ ] as me. I have to
turn it off. It's annoying.
You don't know what I look like. How do
you not know what I look like, bro? I've
shown my face a million times. Yeah.
Remember that Natalie G wanted to meet
me years ago. Nicola.
Nah, I can't be doing that, bro. I'm not
meeting no woman off YouTube.
Yeah, I was thinking about that. USA is
he um the other day, bro.
He reminds me of Ant-Man.
He reminds me of Ant-Man. That um mash
tag. I don't know why. He just does.
Yeah, I was thinking about that US. I
was speaking to LT the other day about
that USA Izzy man and it's quite sad. I
don't like the [ __ ] but it is quite sad
what they doing it. They don't care
about anyone but themselves. They're [ __ ] selfish.
They're actually selfish, bro. bag.
Well, like I said, when I came back from
Birmingham the other day, I don't know
how I used to do them travel. How I used
to do that traveling, bro. Don't know
how I used to get on the piss and then
the next day come back to us.
That's what I'm saying. He's got the
clout. He got the followers. That's what I'm saying.
But obviously I don't have that. Uh,
but I guess she's not replying them. Same old.
Yeah, I know. It's hard to get that big, bro.
Yeah. No, he's not proper famous. He's
not proper famous, but he's famous
enough. Proper famous is like [ __ ] Dwayne Johnson.
He's not proper famous, but he's famous enough.
This is a YouTuber. But yeah,
just the same old, bro. It's just the Yeah.
[ __ ] depressing, isn't it, bro?
You remember you remember LT Nolan
when he was messaging USA is he warning her.
It will never change.
Yeah. What's funny, is it, bro?
Yeah. The attention was nice.
What do you think? Do you think
everywhere is the same, Nicolo, or do you think
do you think there's places that are
easier than others?
Like, what do you think is harder,
Birmingham or London, or do you think
it's the same?
I only thought it was easier cuz of the
numbers that I did get,
but there's no point going back to
Burman cuz I can't even get in anywhere
cuz the bounces are just [ __ ] Uh,
I don't know, man. I think everywhere is the same pretty much.
I don't know, bro.
What do you think? Um,
yeah, it is
I I went to Scotland. I didn't get [ __ ]
all. I remember I went to Scotland. I
didn't get [ __ ] all.
No, it's mad though. Like the women are
dead. You can't even get a [ __ ] date
now. Don's dead.
It's [ __ ] isn't it? It's getting worse, bro.
It It's getting worse. Yeah.
go back to B.
Well, to be fair,
I got um
it was Edinburgh, not Glasgow, but who
knows what difference that would make.
What if you went to Birmingham tomorrow?
Yeah. And you done it all again.
And then you got a hotel this time and
you tried to meet someone on a Sunday. Nah.
Nah. The bouncers are simps.
Uh, no one cares what you're saying. I'm
not even going to block you. I'm just
going to let you type and embarrass
yourself. Nah, bro. They're They're [ __ ]
They're stuck, bro. They're stuck in the [ __ ] past.
cuz he's trying to get in, bro. Them
bouncers are [ __ ] there. So, me and
Monty had a problem with one of them.
So, I'm going to block you actually my channel. Bye-bye.
It is bad, bro. It is bad.
I think it's cruel. Like people that
have children now, I think it's quite
cruel cuz imagine what it's going to be
like in another 20 years. Partnering
from gambling, no opportunities, can't
get a woman. Got to be even worse.
Yeah. Be even worse, bro.
Hopefully this football bet wins
tomorrow. Well, I say hopefully. I mean,
even if it does, I'm not doing anything. So,
got a good feeling about it.
Yeah. [ __ ] man.
Yeah, I enjoyed that McDonald's um
earlier. Sorry, yesterday. Greasy. But
it gave me the [ __ ] shits.
Can't even get a woman in your own
[ __ ] country. It's [ __ ] madness,
isn't it, Grezy?
It's [ __ ] depressing, is it, bro?
Depression did it.
That's a madness.
No, they're too stuck up in this
country, PC. No, I'm not horrible.
They're just too many stuck up [ __ ]
in this country that have unrealistic standards
due to social media. Nothing to do with
people being horrible.
That's how you know this guy right here
doesn't know about the dating game. to
even write a comment like that,
you can just tell that he doesn't know
anything about the dating game. So,
that guy right there that's just
commented he he doesn't know anything
about the dating game.
Do you not think it's [ __ ] up, Nicolo,
that that we were lied to our whole
life? We were literally lied to our whole life.
Oh, dude. That's nice, bro. Good for you.
Yeah, you must be in the Nile, bro.
See, you still get loads of guys that
are in the Nile.
They don't think the West is the problem.
It's madness, isn't it?
Like, how many approaching videos have I
put up, Nicolo?
But it doesn't suit these people cuz
they're in denial. So, no point me
having a conversation with them cuz
they're just always going to defend
women no matter what you show them. It's pointless.
This is why I booked Thailand to get
away from this.
This is why I'm going Thailand in
November to get away from this to get
away from this depressing life. You
know, that's one of the reasons I booked
to get out of here because it's no, it's
not, you know, a way anyone should live.
It's depressing, bro. It's not a way
anyone should live. Yeah, man.
I'm about to go to Thailand to get away
from this, bro.
Yeah. I'm not living the rest of my life
like this, bro. [ __ ] that.
It's too depressing, you know.
It's too depressing. Greasy. Home stops reflex
where you going Thailand. And yeah, it is lush.
Do you watch Timmy Greasy? I can't stop
laughing at Timmy, man. His face is funny.
[ __ ] depressing, lad.
One second, bro.
Yeah, man. And man moved to Thailand for
a better life.
Yeah. for a better life. >> Yeah,
I did go. I lied. I lied last time
saying I went. I didn't lie last time.
Who said I lied last time? I didn't lie last time.
Nah, bro. I don't like fun.
It's like what Antman says. cuz it's
either you kill yourself or you leave.
I think that's basically the the the
dilemma that um not dilemma um the
situation that he was in.
You either kill yourself by being
depressed in this country every day or
you leave. Simple.
That's it, bro.
It's [ __ ] depressing, bro. This
country, is it? the women, the people,
the government, just everything. It's
like everything in this country is
designed to [ __ ] you in the ass and
troll you and annoy you. I noticed that
about England. It's like everything in
this country is designed to [ __ ] you
over. Have you noticed that? The women,
the police, the government, the housing,
the [ __ ] people are [ __ ] Like,
do you know what I mean, bro? Like,
especially London as well. If you think
about it, it's like everything's decided
to [ __ ] you over in this country.
And the gambling as well. I forgot about the gambling.
It's like everything's a troll in this country. Yeah,
it's [ __ ] madness, isn't it, lad?
Why am I going to buy a house when I'm
leaving this country?
What about Sig, Nicolo? I could I could
try and get back with Sig.
What do you think,
Nicolola? I could try and contact Sig.
What do you think?
Yeah, but Sig was my mommy, wasn't she?
No, Nicolo, but she's my mama.
So she is
No, he's not on YouTube. He's living in Thailand now. No.
Yeah, he moved to Thailand because of the women
and I'm not far behind them to be honest
with you, mate.
I'm not far behind him.
>> Yeah, I should have I should have went
before him, bro. I tried way more times
than he has. That's how you know I've
got a lot of patience. See, people say I
ain't got patience, but bro, I only
booked this what, two weeks ago, and
I've been [ __ ] all over the country.
How's the cold approaching going? I've
not cold approached since Birmingham,
but same old.
It will always be the same old. So,
whenever, like I say, I go out, it's the
same old. It will never change. So,
I mean, it's not even a conversation
anymore, is it?
Because it would always just be the same old.
I mean, yeah, you can't even get in
conversation about it anymore. It would
always be the same old,
same old England, same old women.
Year in year out, day in day out, week
in week out, never change, never.
So, I mean, it's just same old England.
That's how you just end it to be honest
with you, bro. Like,
I should have a date this week. I got
enough numbers last week, the week
before that. Jesus Christ. I should be
on a date this week. the color. Then
yeah, I was just saying to my man back
here, bro, like unless you're a big YouTuber,
like you've got a million subscribers,
they're not interested.
Unless you've got a million subscribers
or a million followers because cold approaching's outdated.
But at the same time, it's the only
thing you can do.
No, I didn't get I didn't get their
numbers. I didn't get her number. I
didn't get that one's number.
So, yeah. like it's outdated now. But
it's the only thing you really can do
cuz dating apps are even worse. Dating
apps are even worse than approaching.
Because the thing is with dating apps,
right? You go on a dating app, you don't
know who the [ __ ] you're actually
speaking to and you're not even going to
get a conversation. Like you won't get nothing. But um
obviously if you get a number, you can
at least maybe get a conversation or
something. So they apps are even [ __ ] worse.
You just go around in circles, you know. So yeah.
Yeah. I was thinking about killing
myself earlier, but it's [ __ ]
depressing. This whole women [ __ ] is
Especially when you got a history like
mine. It's [ __ ] depressing. It never changes.
I wouldn't mind if there was a glimmer
of [ __ ] hope, lad. I I wouldn't mind,
Grezy, yet if there was some sort of
chance of it changing, but there's
there's no chance of it changing. That's
the that's the most [ __ ] up thing is
it will never change.
That's that is the mad thing. It's like
what me and Ant-Man was talking about,
you know? It's [ __ ] depressing. Nah.
It doesn't even like it's not even like
it would ever change as well. It will
always be the same forever
in this country in America and [ __ ] Canada.
You know, America seems even worse. You Yeah.
It's bad, bro. Yeah. Mom. play
dead on this meat and [ __ ] bro.
Just sick of playing stupid games with
people. Do you know what I mean, Grezy?
Stupid [ __ ] games.
the only stupid games.
It's [ __ ] childish at almost 28 years
of age, in it.
Imagine that. Going to Birmingham next
week. Greasy che to it all over again.
[ __ ] that, bro.
[ __ ] that, bro. Imagine that. Imagine
that. Yeah. You went to Birmingham
Friday and Saturday.
You stayed over Friday and Saturday and
you done approaches. Yeah.
[ __ ] me, bro.
Yeah, that USA like that USA is he
played games. cuz I stood up for myself.
Then she played the victim
cuz she didn't know who she was [ __ ] with.
Same as what you basically said. They
don't know who they're [ __ ] with. And
then when they then they play victim.
That's what they do because they don't
think because the thing is with these
people, right, they take kindness for
weakness. So they think that you're a
weak little [ __ ] right? But then when
you show that like you know you're not
to be [ __ ] with then they play victim
cuz that's all they can do.
That's the whole point of them being
narcissist. Do you understand?
Cuz USA was like, "Oh, let me [ __ ] with
this person. Let me mock this person.
Let me lead this person on and mock
them." And then when I stood up for myself,
yeah, she's still on YouTube. She just
doesn't. She is She's still on YouTube.
She goes on Rice's channel. So then
they take and then and then and then
what they do is then like the person
that you get to message them, they will
try to make that person feel sorry for them.
They'll try to get that person to feel
sorry for them. Um,
I don't know her channel, but I know she
goes on Rice's channel cuz I saw on
there yesterday. So, what they do
is then the person that like me them,
they'll try to put them on a guilt trip.
You know what I mean? Cuz they're
narcissists. You see, like USA is she's a narcissist.
She wanted war then she got war then she paid victim. So
strange is it strange people
cuz they're thinking bro
look at this little guy in a little
blazer. Look at this little guy in a
blazer being kind to me buying steak.
Let me just [ __ ] with his head.
Let me just [ __ ] with his head a little
bit. I don't expect anything to come out of this.
Yeah, I'm not sure.
But that's what how narcissists work, unfortunately. Grezy,
I'm out on the road.
Yeah, these [ __ ] are evil, bro. The [ __ ]
always make excuses for women.
Oh, change your look or no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no. Like, they always make excuses,
even if you do everything right or you
take any advice. They just always, it's
like they're scared of the truth.
That's what it is. It's like they're
scared. The truth is that there's too
many stuck up [ __ ] in this country
due to simps on social media, Tik Tok,
Instagram. That's the That's literally
the truth. Cuz there was none of this in
1980, 1990, even in 2009 to be honest
with you. Like this all started like the
the past couple of years. You're not the
problem. I'm not the problem. It's them
[ __ ] are the problem. It's like you
know that Joe. Yeah. He was saying, "Oh,
you need to speak to a woman for 2
weeks." But what if you talk to a woman
for two weeks? She's just going to stop
replying. It's the problem is they are
not interested. That's that's where the
problem stems from. It's them not being interested, you know?
Yeah. They'll always blame you. Like
there's not that Joe guy was saying,
"Oh, you need to speak to them a bit
more." When you can't even get a reply
out of them. It's them not being
interested, but or them playing games or
whatever, but they just It's just easier
to blame the poor man that's tried
everything. It's just easy that way.
Just blame the poor [ __ ] that tried everything.
It's just easier that way, you know?
No backlash. That's what it is, bro.
Yeah. People's was making excuses for
that USA. Is it? Oh, you messaged her
family, bro. Yeah. No [ __ ] I messaged
her family. I gave the [ __ ] how many [ __ ] warnings?
Do you know what I'm saying? Like I gave
that [ __ ] about a million [ __ ] warnings.
You remember Griezy? Don't even think
You remember You remember Greasy? Don't
even think about ignoring me, you little [ __ ]
That's what I said, bro. Yeah, I gave
No, to be fair, I did give them
warnings. I said like, "Can you just
apologize? I'll just leave it and that
and then whatever." Then they kept
changing their photo and then I gave
them more warnings and then I was like,
"Okay, you want to do the ignoring game?
That's fine. I'll just message your
father then." Simple.
Simple. I gave them enough warnings, bro.
All I wanted was a little apology. Greasy. But nope.
But they replied straight away to that
though, didn't they?
They replied straight away when you was
[ __ ] um messaging the father. Yeah,
that done the trick, didn't it?
They're all sick in the head, bro.
[ __ ] hell. They all sick in the head. Yeah.
Yeah. They're back together.
Do you know are people stupid on
purpose? I literally said I'm done with
approaching and then somebody asked me
um when was the last time you approached
when I literally said I'm done
last week because I was going to Birmingham anyways.
[ __ ] hell, bro. Yeah. So yeah,
I was thinking of playing Frankie today,
Nicolo, but I never
Yeah, I do.
Who could forget, bro? Who could forget? Yeah.
That's bad. It One sec. Yeah.
Yeah, it's hor
It's bad in it, bro.
Yeah, there's nothing. That's all you can do or leave.
Quiet is not an option anymore
that they give their number and they
reply as well which is strange because
why give a number to reply
to then not meet someone? That's the
thing that doesn't make no sense because
people say oh like why do they give
their number? It's not about the fact
that they give their number because then
simps are just going to say, "Oh, well,
maybe they felt uncomfortable or they
gave their number." But they actually
give their number and then they reply
and then keep replying and they still
don't meet you. That's the thing that's
weird cuz no one's forcing them to
reply. No one's putting a gun to their
head when they're in another city to
reply. They just will always take um
fault from the women.
The way they will see is that they're
never at fault. They can't do no wrong. Yeah, so yeah.
Yeah, but I was going central London anyways.
Yeah, I was going central London anyways though, so
yeah, that was last year. Yeah.
I'm going to go to sleep soon. I think
it's depressing, bro.
Staying awake is too depressing.
Play some Franklin, I think.
Which one, bro?
No, they didn't stand me up. No, they
didn't stand me up. I just told them to come out. The pup,
maybe. I can't remember, bro. There's
been so many of them. Yeah,
maybe. Yeah, I can't remember. There's
been so many of them.
Just the same old, isn't it?
But these people want to make you
believe that all of a sudden it's going to change.
How could it?
How could it change? It doesn't make sense.
Going wherever my little legs take me.
Do you remember that one grievy? Going
wherever my little legs take me in life. Yeah.
Maybe I should stop going outside. It
makes it worse.
I think I've got a right to be pissed
off. Grievesy, what do you think? I
think I've got a right to be pissed off
because of the amount you've tried and
No, no, no, no, no, no. I think you've
got I I don't think anyone could tell you nothing.
Another year, another year single. Yeah.
If any if luck can change at any time,
it would have changed in them three and
a half years. If your luck was going to
change, it would have tried it would
have changed in three and a half years.
Well, at least I left London this year. Few times. Yeah.
You're not You're not missing much,
Grezy. You're not missing much. [Music] Yeah,
we's never been abroad. Bless him. We's
never gone to another city. Bless him.
Oh, bless you.
Bless you in life.
[ __ ] even Rice is getting sex now.
But I don't I don't think it's a case of
of like some people are meant to be
single. I don't think that. I think it
is because of social media. I I
generally believe if there was none of
this Tik Tok, Insta [ __ ] you would have
found someone now. But I generally think
it is that
I generally think if it wasn't for that
you would be with someone. By you I mean
me. So like I don't think it's a case of
you know I don't think it is a case of that.
I think it's just social. You were just
born in the wrong generation
and you're [ __ ] now. That's it. So cuz
you know you know Thailand has been a
thing for many many a year. But the
thing is it weren't young people going.
It was old men going cuz obviously old
men can't get women cuz they're old.
Like old men can't get
sort of younger women that they want. So
they'd go Thailand. But obviously now
because of Tik Tok and all of this
Instagram [ __ ] people can't get laid
or they can't get relationships. They go
Thailand. Now it's younger people going
now or anywhere in Asia, Cambodia, Philippines, anywhere.
You know, the madest thing is is that
when you download Tinder, you get
matches from the Philippines.
Like you actually get matches from
people from there.
So you won't struggle over there, mate.
No, no way.
Here you have to put up with their [ __ ]
Year in year out, year in year out, year
in year out.
And it has no ending.
Well, I don't know why you're taking a
piss though, cuz it's a serious thing.
It's a serious thing. It's actually a
very serious thing.
What would have you actually done if you
actually wanted children? Like, I've
never wanted children, but what would
you do if you actually did want children?
[ __ ] You'd have to like adopt or something.
What would you actually do if you
actually did want children? Huh? [ __ ]
You would be [ __ ]
Germany, you would be [ __ ]
Imagine that though. You actually
Imagine you actually wanted kids.
You be screwed me.
That's [ __ ] up, is it? Yeah. Oh.
Oh, I never wanted kids. And even if I
wanted a kid, I would not have a kid
because what's the point of of bringing
a child when when they're my age, they
wouldn't even be able to get a girlfriend?
There's no opportunities. There's no
housings. Why would I want to bring a
child into this western [ __ ] hole? This
westernized [ __ ] hole.
That's like child cruel. That's like
being cruel to ch to a child.
Think about when they're [ __ ] 27.
They won't be able to find love.
They won't be able to get laid,
you know? They won't There's no opportunities.
Greavves thinks it's funny. I don't
think it's funny. I think it's [ __ ] depressing. Me,
>> Greavvesy thinks it's funny. Grievesy,
why do you find it funny, bro? It's [ __ ] depressing.
It is actually [ __ ] depressing, bro.
usually thinks it's all funny. It's
[ __ ] depressing. I'm going to take
some more, but I'm going to take some more.
Right. Forget about the bad experiences
and the fact that I'm completely
screwed. You see, this is why you feel
like this Uber job cuz it used to take
my mind off the fact that I'm completely
[ __ ] I'm completely screwed
cuz I had so much stress from the job
and that I I had no time to think of
like the fact that I'm completely [ __ ]
I mean, yeah, I was sing couples, but I
was earning money. So, it was like
now I've only got Franklin.
Now I've only got Franklin.
[ __ ] Franklin. Okay,
on the [ __ ] tap.
But don't worry, the next time you go
out, it'll be different. Even though
this has been going on for three and a
half years and it continues to happen,
don't worry. The next time you go out, I
mean, you've got more chance of [ __ ]
winning the lottery at this point. Think
of how many days in the total three
years we have gone out and we have done
this this [ __ ] We've traveled more
than anyone else in the country.
It's got to be It's got to be million.
It's got to be the [ __ ] lottery odds.
It's got to be lottery odds. Has to be.
It's got to be lottery. It has to be, bro.
I've probably gone out doing this more
times than my mom's done the lottery. My
mom's done the lottery. My mom does the
lottery every week. I've never done the
lottery. So, think about it this way.
Yeah. You've done this more times than
she's done the [ __ ] lottery. And
there's more chance of her winning the
lottery than you ever finding anyone. Yeah.
Which is, like I said, weird. I've never Yeah.
What was that, bro?
One sec, bro.
[ __ ] you. Never happens. Yeah, it never
It never happens in that way. Nope.
But obviously they had an ulterior
motive, but it still doesn't still
happen like that, does it? You know? Yeah. Crazy.
And also you know before that happened
also another thing you know before that happened
um I was I didn't get nothing for like two years.
So when I come back from Manchester you
know that time I got that one night
stand in Manchester. When I come back I
got nothing before Manchester and I got
nothing after Manchester.
And then I met her and then that same
year I got like three one night stands.
But now I'm not a sausage. I think I had
three one night stands that year, but I
had fingering. I had dates. I was living
a life. Life of life [ __ ] Larry. Now
you can't even get a [ __ ]
conversation out of the [ __ ]
Yeah. And after that it was [ __ ]
But I was It has definitely got worse.
Maybe I was just an unlucky few years,
but it's definitely got worse.
Definitely definitely got worse. Cuz
like I said, you can't get nothing now.
Not even a date and a kiss. Nothing.
>> [ __ ] nothing, mate.
They're all NPCs. You can see the
westernity in their eyes.
>> The [ __ ] NPCs.
They're spoilers. They're all non-playing characters.
Oh, you remember that one, don't you, Nikolai?
They're just full of [ __ ] [ __ ] These [ __ ] punts.
>> Yeah. Sig wouldn't give me a [ __ ]
She said, "I only give you a [ __ ] if
you eat me out." I said, "Fuck off."
Yeah. Can't get anything now.
Remember thinking of USA is he whilst in the bar
can't get attached anymore cuz he's
already found his mama.
Oh, we've seen
cuz he's already found his mama
already found his mama.
Why did my mommy
Yeah, I remember I had I had I had a
nightmare of that [ __ ] before.
Not not recently, like last year.
The actual nightmare was I went there
and we we worked it all out. We we we
patched things up. Yeah.
We packed we patched things up. Yeah.
You know how I got that nightmare? I was
watching this airline channel that went
to Boston. I was watching like um this
guy, he goes around the world and he
went to Boston and I got a [ __ ]
nightmare, bro. Watching it in it. Yeah. [Laughter]
What was that? One sec. Oh [ __ ] Yeah.
Already found your mama.
Because you already found mama.
You already found his mama.
Well, I think
I know you're mocking me, but I know
you're trolling me. Yeah. Uh,
It's [ __ ] it, bro.
Oh, [ __ ] hell. Last couple.
If you don't find shovel co attractive,
you're gay. I was thinking about that
earlier, bro. It's funny, isn't it?
God, I love to just [ __ ] lift up that [ __ ] copycat.
I would love to just [ __ ] lift that copycat up.
You know what I would do? I'll just tickle him.
>> You see me? I'm not in Chicago. I wear
pink and everything. Like I wear pink,
which is one of the colors that he said
he'd never wear. He'd wear purple but
not pink. I' I'd [ __ ] wear pink and
say [ __ ] Chev's [ __ ] ugly cuz I'm
not insecure about my sexuality
and I'm not a copycat.
You see what I mean? Look, people don't
do things the way I do things. You
understand, lads? Yeah. Oh, sir. All right.
once I was speaking to someone on the right there. Yeah, man. It's
It's a madness, bra. >> Yeah.
>> Oh, look. Someone's replied straight
away to negativity, bro. Well, I know
what I'll be doing tomorrow, mate. I'll
be in my nesticles.
Like I was saying, Groovy, it's so
[ __ ] up to be our age, you know, 27,
28, and you can't even find somebody
that doesn't play stupid games. E, it's crazy.
It is mad, is it, bro? Like, we're actually like,
we're not like little kids anymore and
these games never stop.
Madness, isn't it?
It will never change. Never.
You convince me, Grezy, how tomorrow is
going to be any different if I go out and try. Convince me.
Yeah. You like you tell me, you convince
me how it's going to be different and
I'll go out tomorrow.
You can't though. You can't convince me, bro.
We're past all that [ __ ] We're past all
of it, lad. Yeah. Yeah, man.
There's a check.
Come on, Grey. Give me Give me some
advice. How is this going to change?
Come on, Greasy. Tell me how how is it
going to change?
Lo saying I'm not. She's not meeting anyone, man.
Well, I'm coming back later.