What should I eat
today? I ain't ask KFC for a little
while. I think I'll just do KFC. But yeah.
Oh yeah. On this YouTube [ __ ]
ever like stop talking about themselves.
Like there's a there's a thing here.
Look, he told a lie nearly as big as his
nose when he lied about going to
America. He's an absolute failure in
life in everything. An immature,
socially awkward little boy. Bro, do
these people get bored of talking about
themselves every day like for a year on
end? Like all they do is self-reflect
their lives? Like these people, right?
Listen. These people that come on here
and call you this and call you that.
These are the same fat ugly little
mongos that ain't got nothing nothing
but benefits and YouTube. That's like
all these people do. All these people
do, bro, is is
selfreflect. That's literally all they
do. They bounce off of their own lives.
They call you everything that they are.
They're little losers that try to bring
other people down because they have
nothing. I tried to play a subway surf
there whilst live streaming. Because
they've got nothing. They're nobodyies.
Fat, ugly nobodyies. Think of it. When
do you reckon that? When do you think
the last time these people actually left their
house? Um, when do you actually think
these people left their house? the last
time these people actually left their
house. Bro, look what I done on Friday.
That's probably more than what they've
done in about 5 years,
bro. Like, without YouTube.
Um, you know what I'm saying? They just
self-reflect. Bro, I need to go to the
gym tomorrow. I need to do stuff, bro,
before my passport rides. I need to work
on that summer body, bro. We can't be
sitting on here entertaining these
weirdos all our
life. You know what I'm saying, bro?
I'm trying to multitask, lad. Yeah, I
need to go to a gym tomorrow, bro. I
need to start doing [ __ ] as well. Like I
told you, that gambling thing was a
one-off, bro. One second. I'm trying to
multitask and I can't talk at the same
time. Uh, I'm getting my passport as
well, bro. Yeah, we might have started
it date. We might have started it a bit
late, but you know, who
cares? People are just fat, ugly mongos
that's got nothing going for themselves.
So, they'd rather just sit on here and
self-reflect every day, calling people
skin or socially awkward or whatever the
[ __ ] It's just their own selves that
they're talking about because they don't
know you, bro. They don't know. They
only know their own lives. This is why
you don't catch me on here for like a
week, two weeks sometimes because it's
boring, bro. It's boring, you
know, when people just talk about
themselves. It's actually It's sad to
see people talk about themselves in that
way as well.
Let me see that. Yeah, he is a snake.
[ __ ] him anyways.
Anyways, I'm going to come back later anyways,
lad. Yeah, I'm definitely going to come
back later because after today, I'm not
going to be live for a little bit, bro.
I got [ __ ] to do. So yeah, I'll