Oh no. Go in the car, mister. Every time. Yeah, man.
Oh, you just [ __ ] the car up there, Franklin.
It's [ __ ] hot in it. [ __ ] hot.
Oh, get out. Get out.
There we go. Turn, turn,
turn, turn. There we go. Franklin. Franklin,
we'll go and play. We'll go and pick up
the little football bet win tomorrow for
you, Franklin, so we can pay your little
membership for the month.
I know you like your little membership,
don't you, Franklin?
I have to buy
I have to pay for your little membership.
>> I agree with you. I have to collect a
little money tomorrow from the bookies
so I can pay Franklin's little membership.
Otherwise, you'll cry. It's $14.99 a
month, but I also get Black Ops 2 as
well. So, it's all right. Not bad. Not a
bad trade. Not a bad deal.
Yeah, I bought Black Ops 2. It's going
to come out by next um bill next month. Hey, man.
Nice football win, isn't it? Hey, man. Dude,
let's go out of the shower. It's [ __ ]
hot. Yeah, Monty man's trying to set me
up with somebody.
That's good. Then we can go on double
dates, can't we, Greasy? Me and him, we
can go on double dates and stuff. How
cute is that? Yeah, man. Nah, bro.
It's so weird. Like this time last week,
I was in Birmingham Grezy. I was having a boogie.
I was having a [ __ ] boogie.
It's cute, is it? Greasy. [ __ ] [Music] Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, we won again. Yeah,
I put 80. I got to 13 uh 230 man and I
won last week's as well. So good money
ain't it really bro? £350 for stepping
in the bookies for [ __ ] two seconds.
Yeah I told you I'm good with the
football bets man
but you know the maddest thing about it. Yeah
I was going to do older than Colchester
and they both scored in the first
[ __ ] half. I said oh this bet don't
win bro. Like I I I was actually going
to do hold him in Colchester cuz I
always do Colchester and if I would have
won in the first [ __ ] half,
but it doesn't matter because Bristol won anyways.
I want to try and do three next time,
but I don't know about three, man.
That would be very hard.
Yeah, I'm good, bro. I'm I'm going to
use that money to go out drinking when I
go out next week or the week after 2:30.
Yeah, man. I'm going to get a haircut
and get on the piss with it. So,
yeah, that's two in a week, bro. I know
because I I used to do these both teams
as well, so I know like which ones have
good chances and stuff. It's good, bro.
There's no stress. There's no sitting on
a machine. You pick two teams. You put
your money in. Damn. Done, bro. 315 in 2
weeks or sitting somewhere for like
[ __ ] few seconds.
Yeah, it's good, bro.
Yeah, it's good.
You always bet Swindon. Always bet
I know about Swindenberg.
I don't know about Colchester.
Yeah. How much did you put on it?
Who just messages me? Oh,
who the [ __ ] just messages me? But yeah,
how much did you put on it?
So wait, so how much did you put on it?
Oh, what bookies did you use?
Oh, you got a little bit more than me then.
You must have used William Hill.
Yeah, but no, the first season I got good odds.
80 to 285. That were good. That were
good odds. The first the first one was
Yeah, you probably done you probably done million but
still a profit in it.
Yeah. I'm not saying my ones either,
bro. I'm not saying my ones either
cuz you know what these people like.
They they actually stalk my bets as well.
These people actually stalk my bets.
Like they're so sad. Yeah. That like
I'll tell like what I'll tell them what
[ __ ] teams. Yeah. And then they'll
stalk it. They'll actually stalk the
[ __ ] bets and make sure it's losing
to see if it's winning or losing.
They're [ __ ] sados, bro.
Like if we lost 80 pound, do you think I
give a [ __ ] about losing 80 pound? Do
you think that's even a loss to me, bro?
You know what I mean?
They're [ __ ] sados, bro. [ __ ] sados.
Yeah, we are in the money, bro. [ __ ]
350 in two weeks. [ __ ] from doing
nothing extra. It's good, isn't it?
What's the most emotional put on it? I'm
not putting more than [ __ ]
I ain't putting more than [ __ ]
[ __ ] £100 on it. No way, bro. I'd
love to put £300 400, but I can't lose
that kind of money, bro. If I was to put
three400 pound on something, I would
just play roulette. The most I put is
I don't know. Probably uh probably 100, bro.
It doesn't matter. Profit's a profit, is it? Nah.
See, what what I was thinking of doing
one day is putting 80 pound on two teams
and whatever I get back with a profit,
put it on another two teams. But
nah, that's like 250, 300 pound. We're
not risking that kind of money, bro.
Not on one game. Not on one game, bro.
So, I'm slowly back to living the life
again. I was in Birmingham last week,
went on a piss up,
won a football bet, won a football bet
this week. So,
you know, I'm slowly getting back there, bro.
I done [ __ ] good, bro. I done I've
done really good.
Yeah, I think 80 pound is my max
cuz if you do [ __ ] like 150, you might
as well just play roulette.
But I won't be doing one next week cuz I
might go out next week.
Probably not though. Maybe the week after.
Yeah. He said that he he might have
found me someone.
Yeah. He said he's hooking me up with
someone that he knows. So this could be interesting.
Monty doesn't speak to me anymore.
He only used me for a shoulder to cry
and some drinks and an omelette.
I was used and abused.
No, I'm joking. Monty's a full.
See, me and Monty's friends to the end.
Yeah, I know. He goes on like, you know,
he says that you obviously we've had our
problems in the past, but think about
it, man. I went all the way there, paid
for the night out. You know, we were
actually friends to the end.
I wish I had a friend like that that
does that. Nah. Nah, bro. Nah, ladies.
You want to do three teams next week, Stephen Howard?
You know, I I might do a football in
another two weeks and I'm going to do
I'm going to do two teams. I'm I'm going
to do three teams, but
that's going to be hard, bro. That's
going to be hard. But I think I could do it.
I think I could do three teams. But
see, if I just added that Colchester one
in today, it would have won. And I knew
that one. I don't know why I backtracked
on that one cuz I was going to not I
weren't going to do three, but I was
just going to do that one as a double.
But I reckon you could give it a Well, I would
You could get him in.
Yeah. 50 maybe.
Yeah. They just do 4050. I would
give it a whirl.
But the lineups have to be perfect. See,
I knew with that Swindon in Cambridge, I
knew it would have won. I knew it was
going to win cuz I know about these
these things, but I used to do football
bets all the time. I won a month in a row before,
but maybe I'll go in tomorrow and put
the 230 in Frankie. Steven Howard. Nah.
No. I put 15 Frankie. you [ __ ] last
week. Nah, bro.
No way. [ __ ] that. No [ __ ] way, bro.
Am I doing that [ __ ]
Yeah, do 50.
Yeah, I'm not doing one next week though
or the week after cuz I might be going
out and I need to focus when I'm going
out and drinking and [ __ ] and I don't
want to be watching football. Uh, I've
already made 350 profit in two weeks, so it's enough. Yeah.
Um, so yeah. Yeah, we can try it, bro. Like 4050.
oh, was that a both Scott? Oh, [ __ ]
[ __ ] That was a both, bro. That was a
both team to score no draw. If you put
80 pound on that, that would have been
like £500, you know.
Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ]
That That was a both teams to score, no
draw, wasn't it? [ __ ] That would have
been That would have been good, bro.
That would have been about5600 if we put
80 on that.
Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah. [ __ ]
Oh, I forgot about that, man.
Yeah, you can do you can either do a
treble both teams score or you do a
double both teams score no draw. Do you
know what I think we should do? I think
we should do a triple both teams to
score no draw and stick like4 on it.
That would be a lot of money, bro.
That'll be a lot.
But it'll be very hard to come in.
Yeah, that was a both teams got no draw
today, would it? [ __ ] Yeah,
cuz it was 21 and 32, wasn't it?
Yeah, but I reckon we could give it a while.
Yeah. No, we'll just do a treble. Both
teams to score.
50 might get like 400 maybe.
Hey, I won the football bet today, Nicolola.
I won the football bet again today. God
must be feeling toy for me, bro. It's
two in a row. Yeah,
I need to collect it.
Uh, probably collect it tomorrow. I'm
not going to go out today. I was said I
might go out next week, but I don't
think I'll go out next week either.
This time last Saturday.
No, this time last Saturday, Nicolola, I
was [ __ ] in Birmingham.
Monty says that he's hooking me up with
somebody and they said they'll have a think.
That's probably another rejection.
M I went to Birmingham today and done it
all over again. Nicolai.
I do it all over again. [ __ ] that.
Oh, I have done it before though. twice a bro. Yeah.
Yeah. I got an Indian bro. I got a vindaloo
and a chicken ticker.
But yeah, man. I've done good really
until I don't have the house anymore.
Still been having a better life than
these people on YouTube even though I
don't have that house anymore.
Yeah, you're doing good in it.
I go to Birmingham today, Greavves, and
do it all over again.
What do you think? Give it a while. Do
it all over again.
Do it all over again. Eh, [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] It almost [ __ ] killed me.
Yeah. What about USA? Izzy, Nicolola? Huh?
No, I ain't going out today. I'm not
going out next week.
Nah, bro. I'm bored. See, I told you I
was actually thinking of going Cardiff
again. I'm [ __ ] mad, you know, bro.
You see, the thing is with London, I
just get so bored in London and you
don't even get any replies whenever you
go out in London. Yeah. You don't even
get any [ __ ] replies.
That's the thing, bro. Like with
Birmingham. Yeah. At least you actually
got [ __ ] replies.
And yeah, two of them might still meet
you in like a month, but you don't get
no replies in London.
That's you just get nothing, bro. So
you you go Cardiff with like [ __ ]
£300. What did you What's that? You
cashing out 230. So that's basically
most of it in it.
You know that time I went to Cardiff and
the next week I went to Cardiff again. I
was a [ __ ] maniac, bro. Back then
I was a crazy [ __ ] back then, bro.
Literally was, bro. I literally was a crazy gun.
Still am, but not that crazy. Nice.
Might just go to Cardiff and do an all nighter. Yeah,
should do it every week. Just go to
another city every week and do an all nighter.
Oh, I've still got that video when I was
in Nottingham. Yeah. Where that [ __ ]
was sucking my dick. I said, "How did
you suck my dick like that? You made me
come everywhere." She said, "No comment."
She said, "No comment, um, Nicola."
So, yeah, man.
To be honest, I probably will go Cardiff
again. I'm sick of London, bro.
I am sick of me. [ __ ] boring, is it? Oh [ __ ] [ __ ] boss.
And Greavves never even left his little town.
Would you believe, Nicolo?
But the problem is though, Nicolo, the
problem is, man, is that you can go to
Cardiff and you might not even get in
anywhere. Oh, no single entry. No single
entry. That's the problem that you've got.
I've got a friend in Wales who I've not
seen for a very long time.
Um, so I could try and meet him, but
like you don't want to be going
somewhere, bro, and not being able to
get in anywhere cuz then you will be [ __ ]
Like you will be [ __ ] then.
You have to come all the way back home,
bro. The [ __ ] That's the worry when you
when you go somewhere like that. Yeah.
Oh, I don't know, man.
It's probably It's probably going to be
like two days a month.
I go out like two days a month. Yeah.
Imagine going to leads again.
What about going to leads again,
Greavvesy? Doing all nighter in leads.
Oh, [ __ ] that.
Go to leads and do an all nighter.
[ __ ] You'd be [ __ ] bro.
Go to lead. You aren't getting anywhere. Xbox.
It's quite a nice tattoo.
I like Franklin.
Franklin, stop putting up your middle thing.
But yeah, London.
London is [ __ ] bro. Um
What city should I go to next?
Let's have a vote. What city should I go to next?
Nah, [ __ ] that. I ain't going cool, bro.
That's way too far.
No, we're going Blackpool either.
Well, you didn't answer me, Greg. If I
done an all nighter in leads and then
came back to the nesticles, what would I be like?
the next day.
You would be fat.
You would be [ __ ]
Yeah, you would be [ __ ] for like three days, bro.
I've been to Cardiff twice. No, three
times I've been to Cardiff.
Could go to Cardiff today. Yeah.
F knows, lad. F knows.
Yeah, you'll fill me in. I've already
been to Cardiff twice
and no one fill me in.
But the problem is it's trying to get in places.
That's the problem.
That's the problem you got, bro.
See, I don't like London.
I'm getting bored of London
cuz it's like
at least with Birmingham you actually
got replies back
obviously like we don't know if any of
them one of them is definitely not
meeting but I don't know about the other two but
like you actually got replies back so
you should be getting replies back. If
you don't get replies back in London,
I don't know, bro.
I mean, you could just do an all night
in Cardiff. All nighter in Cardiff
and then [ __ ]
just don't book a hotel unless you pull.
That makes me sound like I'm skinned
when I'm not.
Nope. None of them. Oh, John West. I
went to Birmingham last week.
I got three numbers. They all replied
back and then they stopped.
No one knows about my YouTube channel,
bro. The West is just dead.
It's been that way for a long time.
Yeah, I had one, bro. Wasting my time.
Nah, it's just dead the west, bro. Uh,
trying to think.
Do you think everywhere is the same with
women we think so? Yeah. Yeah. 100%.
The only the one thing I was thinking of doing Yeah.
is staying somewhere for two days.
Like go to a city and stay there Friday, Saturday,
like Cardiff, like stay there Friday, Saturday,
but that's going to be quite expensive, isn't it?
just stay there Friday, Saturday. And
what if you can't get in anywhere?
That's the thing. Um,
could go Liverpool for two days.
H maybe I should go somewhere for 2 days
or one day somewhere one day somewhere else.
We got some exciting plans for this
channel, Grezy. We got some exciting plans. Um
I went Birmingham last week, John West,
to meet Monty. Did you see it?
I was thinking like Birmingham and Cardiff.
What do you think? Birming I was
thinking like Birmingham and Cardiff.
Well, obviously one of the days you'd
have to drink beer.
only beer because of um
you'd have to drink beer because of
if you drunk rum, you'd be [ __ ] for 3
days after that. Sorry. Uh,
I've already been to Scotland, you silly goose.
Yeah, Rice was messaging me. I was
thinking of replacing Monty with Rice Squeezy
cuz I was upset earlier and Rice asked
me how I was.
You see, me and Rice has never actually argued.
Maybe he could be my new best friend.
No, I'm joking, man. But he did actually message me.
What was good, John West? What? when I
went to Birmingham. Yeah, it was good, man.
Oh, I just run over the dog, Grezy. I
just run over the dog. Oh,
I just killed you.
Oh, the dog's attacking me. [ __ ] off,
nasty dog. Oh, the dog killed me.
Where to go?
Just stay in London.
Oh, what the [ __ ]
What was good though, John West, when I
went to Birmingham Monty? Yeah, it was
it was a blast.
I don't know. Um,
What I think
None of them blocks me up there. [ __ ] Um,
What to do? Um, Almost. Almost.
Trying to think.
>> What are you doing?
>> Yeah, I'm good, mate. What you doing?
>> Just playing GTA, bro.
>> What? What? What level? What level are you?
>> No, I'm just [ __ ] around on it, bro.
>> Are you?
>> Yeah. That John West is back. Do you
know? Do you remember?
>> Yeah. What you doing in this community
anyways with these old [ __ ] weasels?
>> I just come on to talk to Grey.
>> You Grimsy. You talk offline. Not on
this [ __ ] man.
>> Yeah. True, true.
>> You meeting up with Natalie again soon. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Me up with Natalie. Yeah.
>> We should all meet up sometime, bro.
Maybe in a month or something in
Birmingham. But just keep off YouTube, you know?
Yeah. Yeah. I'm not bothered if you want
or not. Yeah.
>> Whatever, bro.
>> Get me into that call approaching
[ __ ] again. Yeah.
>> I didn't get you into it, Monty. You
done it yourself.
>> Well, I'm not on here for long. I'm
going to jump off in a second anyway. I am not.
>> Yeah, man. It's [ __ ]
>> Yeah. And if that person if that person
gives me their number, Monty, we can go
on like double dates and stuff, can't
we? We can all go to Nando.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Of course,
>> go Nando. >> Huh?
>> Have a good
man. The best place to take a woman on a
date. Yeah. Is Gregs literally Greg. >> Gregs.
>> Yeah. Trust me, they love a bit of pasta.
>> What the [ __ ] Yo, Monty, do you know
what? Yeah. Do you know what it is,
Monty? Yeah. I can't help but laugh at
Timmy. Like, I know. Like, I don't want
to bring you into, but it's it's
something to laugh at, ain't it? This
community all to laugh at. They all just
ugly little [ __ ] freaks on. You ain't
got no [ __ ] life to be honest. Like,
like I don't I don't give a [ __ ] what
these people say about me, what they put
as the comments or whatever. Just a
[ __ ] weirdos to me, PJ. That's it.
They could say what the [ __ ] they want
to in any comment or whatever.
Let's get real. I'm not about social media. Yeah.
If getting real, I can get real. Do you
know what I mean?
But these are too [ __ ] to even leave the
front door. You know what I'm saying? >> Yeah.
>> That's what I mean. They [ __ ] idiots.
All the comments and all that. Don't
mean [ __ ] to me. They can rap what the
[ __ ] they want. They can call me [ __ ]
They can do all that [ __ ] They [ __ ]
bigger Mongos by sitting on YouTube 24
[ __ ] seven of their lives. You know
what I mean? What are these? They go and
get a job. These are God. You only 24
[ __ ] step off his leg ax. You know
what I mean? Go get laid.
>> They call they call people skinting it.
>> They can't do what I do.
>> They can't go out there and or whatever.
They got to sit in the else and [ __ ]
be checked off other people's eyes and
what other people do. That's it. That's
only what they do. It's full grown men
with a [ __ ] pale [ __ ] brain.
>> You know what I mean?
>> Yeah. It's the truth. It is. It is
[ __ ] true. Like John West. You John
West, man. He's little weasel on here.
Same as Shagger. Same as Dread Doll.
Same to all of them. Little weasels.
>> [ __ ] doesn't have a point. We are also
[ __ ] for watching a [ __ ]
>> Listen, all them Mongos or you who can't
actually get off YouTube who actually
haven't got a life and then you react
then you [ __ ] bounce up other
people's lives cuz you haven't got one.
That's about it. Yeah,
>> that's it. That's it. Like they ain't
got no life. I'm not entertaining these.
>> Yeah, I've got I've got Rice on
WhatsApp. He just messaged asking how I
was. That's it.
>> Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] about that.
Good. Good on him though. Shing K even
though Kay's using it for a PlayStation like >> Yeah.
>> How are you? How are you now? You eating good?
>> What does he play?
>> This girl said, "What do you play?" >> Huh?
>> This girl said, "What? What do you play?
Uh GTA 5
>> International GTA V.
>> You play Fortnite? Yeah, she plays Fortnite. Yeah.
>> Oh, really?
>> Yeah. Yes, play Fortnite. Why are you
downloading Fortnite now? Are you?
>> Yeah, we can play Fortnite together. I'm
on Xbox console.
>> He said we can play Fortnite together.
>> Um, send her send her your gamertag. She
said, "Send her a game." PJ
>> send it to you. >> Oh,
>> not PJ. Talk to us. He's here now. >> Hello. >> Hi.
>> How's it going? You okay?
>> I'm all right, thank you. How are you?
>> I'm good. I'm just playing some GTA. You on Xbox? >> Yeah.
>> Oh, okay. Um,
>> what are you on?
>> Yeah, I'm on Xbox.
It's TZ Pete X.
>> It TZ P
>> IT TZ P E T E X. >> Okay.
>> All right. I do want to go back inside.
>> Okay. I will accept you and we can play
some Fortnite together.
>> Okay, that's cool. My name is Storm, by
the way. So, it will come up as Stormy.
>> Okay. Nice to meet you, Storm. My name is Peter.
>> Hi, Peter. Nice to meet you.
>> I I I know someone called Storm from uh
secondary school from years ago.
>> I don't remember it.
>> What area?
>> Oh, they live in London. It's just
someone that I knew, you know.
>> Oh, no. I'm like Nottingham.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I know. I know. I
know. But it's just like it's an unusual
name. It's It's a good name.
No, thank you. I appreciate it.
>> All right, I'll add you when I go back in.
>> Yeah, no worries.
>> Hey, Jeff.
>> Yeah, you all right?
>> Yeah, I'm good. I'm good. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> There you go.
>> That's not Monty. That's not Jesse, is it?
>> It's not Jesse. No, is it for Jess? Oh,
>> here we go. There you go.
Get her added.
>> I didn't I She said she's going to add
me when she goes back inside.
>> Okay, there you go then.
>> I didn't real I didn't think she'd be on Xbox.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Download um Fortnite.
>> Yeah, I think I've already got it
downloaded to be fair.
>> There you go, lad.
>> How do I help you out? Yeah.
>> I'm joking. I'm joking.
>> I I I came to Birmingham and saved your ass.
>> Yeah. Okay. You come to Birmingham and
save me ass, page. Yeah. Okay. Don't rub it in.
>> It was cute though, wasn't it?
>> No, cuz it got me in a lot of [ __ ] off
Natalie. A lot of [ __ ] off.
>> I [ __ ] love that girl, man. It got me
in a lot of [ __ ]
>> Yeah, but you had a bloody good time, didn't you?
>> Of course I did. Of course I did.
>> We got We got [ __ ] pissed on an empty
stomach. What the [ __ ]
>> Yeah, I know. We got pissed on the empty
stomach. We didn't eat on nothing for days.
>> We done that, man. I don't know how we done that.
>> No, I know. I know.
>> Yeah, man.
Monty. What was I saying is um [ __ ]
Oh, what was I saying? Tune out. Oh, I forgot.
Yeah, I forgot, bro. [ __ ] um
Yeah. What are you doing today anyways?
Nothing. No, I got No, no, no. [ __ ] off.
Really? Just chilling. Really?
>> It's [ __ ] hot, is it, bro?
>> Yeah. Yeah, it is hot and it's [ __ ]
blowing too, mate.
>> Oh, how old is she?
>> He said, how old are you? >> 28. >> 29.
>> No, she's 28. 28.
>> Okay. I'm I'm 28 in two months.
>> He's 28 in two months. What you said?
>> 28 in two months.
>> All right, PJ, let you go. You got her.
You got her. She's going to add you when
you get when she gets in there.
>> Yeah, no worries, man. >> Yeah.
>> With you. What time is it? You want to
go now? I've got to be in next [ __ ] two.
>> Yeah, go then.
Watch this come through us. Yeah, watch
this cam through us.
>> It might do. I don't know. Hello, gorgeous >> Lee.
>> Yeah, it did. Slim.
>> Yeah. 80 to 230. So, I won two. I won
one last week and one this week. Nicotine.
>> Yeah, it was all right, man. It was a
good little pinch.
>> PJ, I'm going to jump. Yeah.
>> Yeah, man.
>> I'm going to be ringing up Natalie in a
minute. Anyways, talking to Natalie for
a bit in a minute anyway.
>> Yeah, I wait. I'll wait for her to add me. Yeah,
>> you're waiting for her to add you. Yeah,
>> she will do. Yeah, don't [ __ ] ruin
it, PJ. Yeah,
>> why would I Why would I ruin it? start
doing that [ __ ] weird [ __ ] low
voice pitch thing you doing and the [ __ ]
like that one.
>> Yeah, that one. Yeah,
>> agrees you likes that one, don't you?
>> No, you're a funny guy, PJ. Everyone just,
you know, I'll let you go. Yeah.
>> All right then. See you later.
>> But everyone likes that little voice though.
>> Yeah, man. It come in Slim. Yeah, bro.
It was good.
Oh, it come in. It was nice.
You do a football bet.
It's [ __ ] hot in it, bro. by a left.
Let's see if this person adds me. Hey,
Molly said, "Don't ruin it." What's
wrong with the little voice? I like the little voice.
Yeah, I put £80 on one last week. I won
280. I put £80 this week. I won 230. So that's 350
on two of the games. So it's not bad, is it?
Yeah, I'm not going out this week, bro.
And I probably won't go out next week
either, Slim. I can't be bothered going
out anymore, Slim. Bro, it's just the
same. I have a boyfriend every time.
Every time I go out, it's always, you
know, I have a boyfriend.
You know, I'm [ __ ] sick of it. Me Yeah, mom.
And I was thinking, Slim, yeah, that
like yesterday I was kind of depressed.
I I didn't go to bed until 6:00 in the
morning yesterday, bro. cuz I was
thinking of like all of the times I've
tried and stuff and how I'm single and I
can't find anyone slim.
I went to the cinemas yesterday as well actually. Yeah.
So I don't know bro and I went to
Birmingham last week. Remember Slim? I
went Birmingham with Monty last week.
Yeah, I'm going to go meet. Huh?
Yeah, Monty's helping me try and meet someone.
Monty should Monty should put in a good
word for me to be honest, bro. I [ __ ]
I helped him, bro. I went all the way to
Birmingham and I paid for us to go out
and stuff, which is not a problem, you know.
That's what mates do, mate. But still,
>> I think I'm going to need another fan. Bro,
this fan is not doing the trick.
Had a big one at the old house. It was
like £40 3 years ago. Massive fan. It is
massive. I just sold it cuz I was moving.
Has this woman added me yet? [Music]
This is how you record on Xbox. [Music]
I'm going to have to take my clothes
off, lad. I'm [ __ ] hot, man. There's No.
Oh, this is lovely, mate. Oh, [ __ ]
You know, just lying in bed chilling.
Oh, it's lovely.
Isn't it nice?
Oh, it's lovely Groovy
in my little nesticles playing Franklin. Uh,
nothing beats it. But I could do with a
better fan to be honest.
You want to get one of them Dyson fans,
Greasy? They're about 400 quid.
Yeah, they're about 400 pounder.
What do you see then?
[ __ ] falling apart. Why is still not
added me yet?
We can play some Black Ops 2.
I didn't know she has Xbox like me. Oh, nice.
Right. One sec. fan blowing.
This is so nice.
Oh, is that a message?
Why haven't you messaged me yet, Storm?
Yep. Mine's every I think mine's every
10th as well to be honest.
How much do you reckon that will be if I
if I went to Cardiff for two days
drinking Greavesy with hotels? £350
train, hotel and drink. You reckon 350 is enough?
What do you think, Grezy?
What would you say?
What' you say, mate?
Yeah, about that, matey. About that. [Music]
I like Franklin. He's cute.
Is Franklin cute? Grezy.
Franklin will die without the
membership. That's why we need to give
you extra money, Franklin, cuz then the
Xbox would stop being paid.
That's a nice name, is it? Storm. I knew
a Storm from secondary school years ago.
It's quite an unusual name.
Yeah. If I don't pay, then Franklin
doesn't get to play on Xbox. I agree
with you. You've got to admit the Xbox
controller is better.
100%. The Xbox controller is better, though.
100%. The Xbox controller is better.
I don't even know why I have an Xbox. I
always prefer the PlayStation. I don't
even know why I've got this Xbox to be fair. Oh, Franklin.
Oh, when I charge the um I'm charging
the um controller with my Samsung
charger, Grezy, and it somehow works. It
needs batteries, but when I put my
Samsung charger on it, it seems to work.
I'm plugging it on the wall. You know
that Samsung charger, the adapter, you
plug it to the wall. Well, I plugged it
in the controller and it seems to work. Strange, it
It's 5 right here. Oh man.
Grazy, you still there?
A little stitch picture.
You still there? Z,
you big troll. Oh, Franklin,
he hurt you.