What the [ __ ] is going on?
What the [ __ ] What the [ __ ] have I woke
up to, bro?
What the [ __ ] What the [ __ ]
What the [ __ ] What the [ __ ] is going on?
>> I'm not going out with Natalie no more.
I'm done with her. I'm completely done
with her now.
>> Hold on. Hold on. Why? Listen, bro.
Yeah. What do you mean you got kicked
out the golden? What the [ __ ]
>> Girl, because that girl got you to talk
to. Yeah. I only did that for you
because you were luring me. So, I
thought, [ __ ] it. LPJ actually get somebody
>> actually. I thought, you know.
>> Yeah. So, why did she get you why did
she get you kicked out though?
>> Because she's been chatting [ __ ] and
staring [ __ ] with other people and
everything else in this in this building >> with
she's supposed to be going out with,
>> you know, but I didn't know any of this
cuz I'm new here. Do you know what I mean?
>> Yeah. So I thought, okay, after when I
was on your live and that I asked if she
wanted to go shop because I thought
Natalie wouldn't take that offensive or
anything like that,
>> you know.
>> So So Natalie [ __ ]
started [ __ ] texting me saying it's
over and all that, asking another girl
to go to the shop with you. He only
asked to go to the shop with me because
she were getting bullied
in here. You know what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> I'm not crying over Natalie no more.
>> Yeah. All he does is keep ending it.
This tattoo on my hand, it's going. It's
>> What's she doing on YouTube?
>> And all that look, dancing around and
making [ __ ] off herself. I don't want a
woman like that. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean?
>> I don't I really do not want a woman
like that. I want a woman who respects me,
>> who listens to me, don't scout at me and
finish me because he asked a girl come
shop with me. It wasn't even like that anyways.
>> Yeah. even a girl, man.
>> I only done that for you and I get my
ass bit off through it. I only done that
because she was there. I don't regret it. >> Yeah,
>> I only done that because she was there for me. >> Yeah,
>> I thought [ __ ] it. I get you a girl who
will probably like you and appreciate you.
>> She's in the chat now. >> What?
>> I'm not asking if she's in the chat.
It's It's done. I'm done. I'm done with
women like that. treating me like a prick.
>> You know what I mean? I've done [ __ ] all
wrong to her. He only asked me to go
come with me because she's getting
bullied up a little prick in here. He
thinks it's hard as [ __ ]
>> You know what I mean? Me and my mate
walked to the shop and I've been with my
mates all night. My mates have gone back in.
>> [ __ ] had a [ __ ] in a empty Chris packet
when he was staying in a tent because it
had because it had no toilet paper.
>> You know, I'm not the one who pisses in
a [ __ ] piss bucket. Now in the bedroom.
Yeah. Definitely [ __ ]
>> She's saying she's tr She's saying she's
tr the [ __ ] out of you.
>> Troll the [ __ ] out of me cuz this tattoo
is going. This tattoo is going with that
75 quid what she can. She's paying for
it to get removed. It's going.
>> I'm done with
>> I made you I made you get an end I made
you get an end tattoo.
>> Yeah, but that's going. That's no
problem. You can just make me get a
brand new tattoo. That's fine.
I can get something covered off like that's not
>> for nonsmonger. Natalie,
>> just get kick her. Just kick her. Don't
Don't just talk, man. Just get rid of
her in it, man.
>> I'm done with her. I'm done with her.
Get rid of her. I don't need women like
that in my life. I've been talking to
another woman. Don't mind now. And it's
definitely no one here.
Definitely no one here. a woman who
actually appreciates me. PJ man,
>> why did you do all that N? Anyways,
>> I'm done with her anyways. PJ, I
introduced you to my mom. My mom [ __ ]
liked her and everything. She's a little
[ __ ] flag on YouTube. That's it.
That's it. The funny are black, mate.
They're funny. They're black. >> [ __ ]
>> I'm not even chatting [ __ ] black. I
might actually go and get tested out
because of the fact I'm black. And if it
was a joke, why do you think we were
saying that? I'm done with you. I'm
lally done with you now. All these ch
[ __ ] you know, I ain't even done
[ __ ] all wrong to you. I'm not even
going to cry over you anymore. You're
not even worth it.
You embarrass me.
>> She's embarrassment, mate. She's a
[ __ ] embarrassing little [ __ ] on
YouTube. That's it. Her life is YouTube.
Entertain little [ __ ] fat little old
men, Natalie. Yeah,
>> cuz I'm on 100% done. 100% done. PJ,
>> you know, I fell asleep, bro, at [ __ ]
like seven. I didn't wake up until now,
but I was tired, man.
>> Yeah. Oh, yeah. Natalie, and you think
that I'm talking to a 50y old woman? PJ,
does this girl look look 50 to you? And
tell me what you actually think about
her. This woman actually cares about me.
She's been awake all night. this girl
actually thinking about me being on the
street and all that. Look, I'm done with
N anyways. I'm single. I'm single. >> Yeah,
>> I'm single now.
>> Yeah, we can go out.
>> Been up all night getting pissed out of
her face. She's pissed. She's pissed. >> Yeah.
>> Getting chill over a girl who I don't even know.
>> Did you Did you drink yesterday?
>> No, I don't drink. I'm not even smoking
weed no more.
>> No, I didn't drink yesterday.
to walk to the show with me. [ __ ]
hell, that's pathetic. At least I don't
go on YouTube and blast my tits out.
>> That's not a girlfriend, mate. That's
just a [ __ ] muppet on YouTube and
say, "Oh, these little clowns, you know." >> Yeah.
>> She's not She's never going to get a man
like me again. Never. Only what she's
going to get is a little weasel off
YouTube or something like that. She can
do what the [ __ ] she wants to. I won't
be I pol I've deleted every single
picture of me and Natalie. They've gone.
I've deleted her. I'm not having no
pictures of her on my phone anymore.
The way she treats me.
You don't treat someone who you're
supposed to love like that. I only ask
the girl to go to the shop because she's
getting bullied or someone. Didn't
Natalie get backed up a man so she knows
how it [ __ ] feels.
>> Why was she getting bullied?
Because [ __ ] I don't know the full
story. I don't know PGA.
>> I just got dragged into something
because of that [ __ ] girl dragged me
into something. What I should have been
being dragged into. I got dragged into the office.
>> You know what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> [ __ ] hell.
And I'm keeping away from her. I'm not
going nowhere near that girl no more.
>> Yeah. There was a relationship with with her and
her boyfriend who I don't like. >> Yeah.
>> Who I don't like. Natalie should
understand all this.
Natalie should understand that I've got
a good heart and then [ __ ] I'm not
going to let a man body a woman. Either
way, I don't [ __ ] b this woman. I
don't like this woman. I don't know her.
I don't even know her name.
to come shop with me and my mate to get
her away from Dylan. That's his name.
Get get her away from Dylan for about 10
seconds. Don't know where shop is. It's
just around the corner 10 seconds away
and back again. I never leave this. But
I'm always talking about Natalie every
[ __ ] day. She knew we had a girlfriend.
There was nothing there with me and her.
Nothing there with me and that girl cuz
I never like I don't fancy her.
What? What does N want me to do? Day
one, I not talk to nobody.
You know what I mean?
>> It's called trust, PJ. If a woman don't
have trust in you,
>> what's the point being in the relationship?
>> Straight up.
>> It is. It is. Now, they don't trust me.
So, what's the [ __ ] point? I trust
her 100% until tonight. Until tonight.
100%. I trusted her 100%. I thought he
had the angel.
>> No m I had a dick. I had another [ __ ]
Kay added. That's who I [ __ ]
>> I'm not even joking. P. I'm really
[ __ ] worse than K.
They both the same, mate. They're both
the [ __ ] same.
All what they both do is shout and
[ __ ] end it when they want to.
>> You know what I mean? They don't let you
talk. They don't let you explain
yourself. They think they're right. They
think they're perfect. They think they
know everything what's going on in your
mind. They they now don't even know how
I feel about her. She really doesn't.
Of course, P now. Yeah.
>> I'm not going out with her. I can't do
this. I really cannot do this. You know,
>> you think it's funny. >> What?
>> You think it's funny, is it? this YouTube.
>> I don't think it's funny. I really don't
think it's funny one little bit. A woman
who's going on to YouTube to try and
make me jealous. You know, I can make a
[ __ ] jealous right now. What do you
think about this bird, PJ? I send you a
picture. I've been talking to her all
night. I got her phone number and it's
definitely not that girl over there.
It's definitely not her, Natalie. I'll
show you now. One minute.
Tell me what you think about it, PJ. Okay,
>> it's frozen.
Yeah, it's frozen, man.
>> No, no. I'm sending you the picture.
>> Oh, okay. One sec. Hold on.
>> Send you a picture. What do you think
about her picture?
I'm not playing games with me either.
>> Hold on. Hold on.
>> This girl actually liked me. He's
actually been awake half night thinking
about me being out on the streets.
>> She's all right. Just get with her in it.
>> I am. I am. I am. She appreciates me.
She likes me,
>> you know.
>> She even told me she's worried about me
being out on the streets all night
in the morning, you know.
>> Oh, of course I of course I'm going to
text her. Of course I am.
>> Someone's asking if you're okay. Yeah,
I'm good, mate. I'm actually [ __ ] I'm
actually good. I am actually [ __ ]
good. I'm not I'm not let letting
Natalie get to me.
>> Did Did he tell the girl he's homeless?
>> Yeah. Yeah, she knows I'm homeless.
Yeah, I've told her about Natalie as
well. I've told her everything.
I've told her she knows I'm homeless.
You know, this is madness YouTube, is
it? It just gets worse, boy, doesn't it? Yes. says, "But
I did love Natalie. I did really love
her. Why the [ __ ] do you think I got a
name on Miami if I didn't love her? That
should show Natalie how much I loved her.
>> That should have proved Natalie how much
I've heard about her by going out and
getting initial on my hand. He knows
that that girl also knows about the
tattoo as well.
He knows about the tattoo as well.
>> It's getting taped.
Oh, 10 minutes. Not even that. I'm
getting it covered up anyways. It's
going next week anyways.
>> What are you going to do? Get
>> Would you get it lasered off?
>> No. No. I'll just get it covered over
with a new tattoo.
>> What tattoo do you think?
>> I thought I don't know. I'm going to
have a look. But it is going anyways.
Natalie don't appreciate
>> has just been asking for LJ's number.
She's pissed, mate.
>> Yeah, she can. Yeah, she can. She can.
She literally can. That's how desperate
she is. Now, that's not going to make me
chish one little bit. Go for it.
That's not going to make me cherish one little bit.
Why the [ __ ] am I going to sit here and
get abused of another [ __ ] woman
again and get finished every time
without a comp without a conversation about things?
>> Was K was Kaylee the worst?
>> I'm not talking. Listen PJ abusive woman.
Yeah. Shouts. Yeah.
>> Threatens you. That's abuse
>> and call your name. That's abuse.
>> You know, I've never done that to any
woman. I've never abused any woman.
>> But Monty, I knew this was going to
happen. Like, not like this. Like, what
am I saying?
>> I knew like this. Once you get with
someone on YouTube. Yeah. Listen,
listen, listen. Once you get with
someone on YouTube and then [ __ ] goes
wrong, this happens. This is the problem
when you get with someone on YouTube.
>> Can't stay off YouTube. I wasn't even on
YouTube. I only come on YouTube to help
you out because you were there for me.
>> That's it.
>> That's it. And he only asked her to come
to the shop and go live. I knew Natalie
Bobby been watching. I didn't think
that' be a [ __ ] issue. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? Cuz I don't fancy
that girl. I don't know that girl. M
>> I'm not a [ __ ] around. I don't cheat on women. >> Yeah,
>> but I do move on fast.
>> Yeah, just get with that when you're speaking to
you should have got with someone you was
with me, bro.
>> I'm done with women. I'm done getting
I'm done getting her. I'm just done
getting I'm not even going to meet this.
I'm not even going to go out with this
girl on text. I've done that piss
Natalie off. I'm not doing it.
>> I can't do it.
>> I'm not that man.
But that obviously thinks I am that man.
I'm not that [ __ ] man to play with a
girl's mind or feelings. That girl were
getting [ __ ] bullied of a lad. So I
asked her, "Come on, we go shop with my mate Luke."
>> So me, Luke, and went to the shop,
probably around the corner. I got a
drink. Come back home back around here.
Next minute I'm getting pulled in the office.
>> Don't go with her.
Why? Because she will get into a lot of
trouble and about these textes he's been
showing you and all that lot about about
[ __ ] him and all that.
>> And I told him I'm not I'm not involved
in any of this. I don't know what's the
[ __ ] going on.
>> How do these people on YouTube at 5 in
the morning? Jeez.
>> Yeah. I'm I'm done with Ni anyways
either way. Not even that. She don't
even let me talk to her. She don't let
me explain what's going on. [ __ ] flipped out. >> Yeah.
>> And then she's on YouTube getting pissed
out of her [ __ ] face and then
thinking it's going to get get me
attention. You know, I've unblocked her.
>> Where is she? What channel is she on?
Haunty. What channel is she on?
>> That one know what she's there now. I've
not watched it all night. So if she
thinks I was watching it,
>> wait. Oh, hold on. Let me see. Miss
Unknown. Is she live? Yeah.
>> [ __ ] knows. I'm not ask if she is
unfollowed. PJ the [ __ ] what I was
watching on last night put me well off her.
It put me off her, man. Literally,
I'm done with that [ __ ] I don't want a
woman who's [ __ ] plastering herself
all over YouTube like that. I want a
woman who respects herself,
respects her body, respects his partner.
>> She's not live. She's not live.
>> No, no, she's not.
>> Was she live yesterday on that channel?
Yeah, last night I weren't even watching
her last night. As soon as she started
dancing, I [ __ ] off. Soon as she
started doing all that slaggy [ __ ] I
[ __ ] off. I deleted every single
picture of us both. I don't have no more
pictures of me and Natalie on my phone.
>> [ __ ] done. I'm done.
Natalie can sit learn so [ __ ] softly
what she's done now. I have done this
me. I already said on your live. I knew
that now they'd be watching either way
cuz she does watch. She does what and
she knows I'm going to end up on your
panel and I knew they'd be watching.
Know that everybody knows like that
we're going out with Natalie in this
place. Even that we're going out with
Natalie in this place. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean?
>> I thought me getting this tattoo would
actually show Natalie how much I [ __ ]
care about her and how much I do love
her. You got a tattoo tattooed though
yesterday. You do [ __ ]
>> I know. I know. I know. I know. And it's
going now. It's going. When I get paid, it's going
>> and Natalie is paying for it to get removed. Yeah.
>> With that.
>> Her channel was gone because she started
>> her channel.
fingering herself. She called [ __ ] Cauliflower dick.
>> Yeah, exactly. I'm done with her, mate,
mate. I'm done with her. My mom wait
till I tell my mom about all this about
her. My mom's going to despise of her.
She is my mom's going to [ __ ] despise
of her. My mom thought I had a good My
mom thought I had the one. Literally my
mom thought I had the one there with
Natalie. She thought I had my life set
with Nat. My mom was busting that that I
got with Natalie. It was
>> Jesus bing. I'm not bothered anymore.
Natalie wants to be this person. Let her
be this person. I don't want nothing to
do with that person. I thought Natalie
changed to be honest with you, PJ. >> Yeah.
>> I thought she cared. I thought she
[ __ ] cared about me so much like I
cared about her. You know, getting
jealous because I'm asking another girl
to come shut with me for. It's not like
I'm flirting with her. I only done that
for you. I'm not even talking to that girl.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I'm keeping her well away from her. Well,
>> women are trouble me.
>> So, what? So, she had black flaps.
>> Yeah. Yeah, she's got black flaps. I'm
not even chatting [ __ ] on that. I can
swear down on my kids lives on that one
as well. Not
>> Why would it be black though?
>> [ __ ] knows.
I'm not even chatting [ __ ] on that one
either. I was chatting [ __ ] about the
um getting tested out and that, but I'm
not I'm not chatting [ __ ] about that. >> Yeah,
>> I'm really [ __ ] not
getting the [ __ ] calling me to
[ __ ] that. At least I'm not a black jagger man.
>> You know what I mean?
>> She had me. You were [ __ ] so lucky
she had a man like me who would [ __ ]
care for her and [ __ ] love her till
the end of the world. You know what I
mean? I [ __ ] loved her, man. I did. I
[ __ ] loved her. That was only the
woman who who I've ever had feelings for.
Even though I girl to go shop on your panel,
>> you know what I mean? It doesn't matter
if he has to go shop with me.
>> It doesn't matter. That's [ __ ]
nothing. It makes it into something.
That's what she's done. He's made it into something.
>> No, you should do it. You should You
should make up with Timmy. It'll make
you feel better.
>> I'm not making up with no one in this
community, PJ. They [ __ ] need it. I
don't even got with Natalie to be honest
with you. I really shouldn't have.
>> That's why I would never get with a
woman on YouTube.
>> Kay for Kelly. She picks you up, she
dropped you. She picks you up and she
dropped you. That's exactly what Kay
done. Exactly what she done. Finish me
on the spot, then get back with me.
Finish me on the spot, then get back
with me. I said to myself, any other
woman does that, I'm walking. I'm [ __ ] walking.
And I'm sticking to my guns. I'm walking. Pedia.
>> Well, Monty, do you think it's weird
that I laugh at Timmy sometimes?
Embarrassing himself. I just find it funny.
>> This [ __ ] community is not even
funny, mate. Just embarrassing.
It's really embarrassing. If Natalie
thinks that I don't love her people, I
do love Natalie. Yeah, I really do love
Natalie, but I'm not playing these games
with Natalie. Do you know what I mean?
>> You know what I mean, PJ? I'm not. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? It's called trust.
I trusted Natalie. I trusted her. I
thought Natalie had trust in me by me
going shot with this girl, with my mate.
>> But it's obviously Natalie don't trust
me. Obviously not.
>> And only the person who I talk about is
every day is that [ __ ] woman. Every
day I only talk about Natalie. Every [ __ ] day
Natalie's just on YouTube have a [ __ ]
face flashing everything up. Just [ __ ]
it up, mate. I've done nothing to her.
Just [ __ ] it now.
>> I might just talk to this girl from
[ __ ] Liverpool. Me now and just be
over with, man.
get a tattoo.
>> You know what tattoo you should get? You
should get like a bear over it. Like a little bear.
>> No, I don't know what I'm going to get.
I'm going to have a look. I'm going to
have a look PJ cuz it needs to go now.
Anyways, it does need to go.
>> Get Ted the bear.
>> I don't know what I'm going to get off
of it. I'll get some off it anyways.
>> I'm never doing I think you should get a
woman how much I love him again. Never
Yeah, I think you should get Ted on it.
>> [ __ ] Ted.
>> Yeah, I'm not even crying nothing.
That's how serious I'm being.
You're [ __ ] through with me. You [ __ ]
with me twice.
>> Did she stay Did she just stay at home drinking?
>> Yeah, she stayed at home drinking,
shouting the head off knowing that she's
got flat mates like women who's trying
to properly sleep and she's on YouTube
flipping out over nothing. over absolutely nothing,
you know. She more w Malcolm can ring
me. She's not blocked.
The norm's not blocked,
you know. But I'm done with it, mate. >> Yeah.
>> She wants me and then she's got to do a
lot of [ __ ] running because I I'm not
doing this running [ __ ] anymore for a
woman, mate. It's doing my [ __ ] nothing.
I want a woman who loves me and who
trust me, who trusts me.
not just run away when I [ __ ] ask
someone to come shop with me. That's
[ __ ] pathetic, mate. >> Yeah,
>> it is. It really is pathetic.
I understand if I cheated on him, but he haven't
meet [ __ ] Ginger [ __ ] J ugly
little man. He really can. That's not
going to make me jealous one little bit.
That's just going to put me right off her.
>> It's the same as Kay and Rice. If K that
that put me well off Kaye.
>> How did how did Kaye even have the money
to go up to Scotland you think?
>> Must have got paid.
>> Yeah, that's mad bro. That that is
actually mad, isn't it?
>> Okay. Now, man, I was going to let
Natalie piss all over me.
>> How the [ __ ] did you even start [ __ ]
arguing with that rice? That's crazy,
isn't it? Like before I'm done with
this. I don't know if he's R is getting
all jealous. My phone's going to die in
a minute as well. So, no one will be
able to get hold of me until half 9 at 9:00.
If Natalie just want to talk about this,
you can really Where are you staying
now? You're not, are you? You're [ __ ]
>> I'm [ __ ] Yeah, I'm [ __ ] Unfortunat
because of that little [ __ ] [ __ ] in there
with her and her [ __ ] partner.
>> She's playing games. She's playing games
with that that little girl. I don't even
know her name, but she's playing games.
Some game or something with everybody in
there. I'm being told off the member of
Steph. Keep away from her. She's playing
a dangerous game with all of you in here.
>> Yeah, but you Yeah, but you like games, is it?
>> I don't like games, PJ. No. No. Not when
it comes to our relationships. No. Nice. >> Um,
yeah. Her name is Storm. >> Storm?
>> Well, you [ __ ] know it.
>> Yeah, she told me it, isn't it?
So, what are you going to do now? Like,
>> I only helped you out because you were
learn from me on [ __ ] because you
would learn for me. Do you know what I mean?
>> So, what are you going to what are you
going to do on um where are you going to
say now in the tent again?
No, I'm a [ __ ] staying in a tent again.
I'm a [ __ ] I'm not staying in no [ __ ] tent.
>> Mother [ __ ]
>> What you saying on the street?
>> I don't know what I'm going to do with
myself, PJ. What the [ __ ] I'm going to
do with myself? Yeah, I got a woman who
keeps on finishing me finishing me for absolutely nothing.
>> Think it's funny then going online
pressing herself on on there. I've done
nothing wrong to her.
>> I understand if I did but I actually didn't.
>> I done what I done for you. For you. Not
for me. For you.
>> I had my misses. I had Natalie. >> Yeah.
>> [ __ ] hell, man.
I had her. I loved her, man. I [ __ ]
did love her. M
>> I bet he did.
>> But after this, man, I can't. I just >> Yeah,
>> it's just bad, mate. Is she put herself
up there? She really has.
And I don't want a woman like that. Do a
[ __ ] man. I want a woman who appreciates herself.
And And she hasn't appreciate herself.
>> Ended when some guy come into a room and
they started kissing an Asian guy.
Yeah, I'm not worried about you peeps
either way. Either way, I'm not worried
about what you people with your [ __ ]
comments got to say.
At the end of the day, you us [ __ ]
weirdos in this community who get kicked
out of this [ __ ]
>> And now realize this [ __ ] She shouldn't
be doing this. We We were talking last
night, yesterday about this. If we got a
problem, we talk about it instead of
arguing and finishing each other off of
[ __ ] You could have just talked to me
about it instead. He got pissed and
start started shouting at me and [ __ ] doing [ __ ]
>> Nothing funny about it, is there? >> What?
>> There's nothing funny about it.
>> No, no, no. There isn't. There isn't.
No, nothing funny about it. If she
thinks that's going to get me jealous
doing that, that's not going to get me
jealous one little bit. That's just just
going to push me the [ __ ] away. Trust me.
What man would want his misses to go
online to do all that online? No man would.
No man would. That's [ __ ] disrespecting me.
I didn't even disrespect her. Well, cuz
she ask a girl to go shop. That ain't
really [ __ ] nothing.
That's nothing. Just asking someone to
come shop with bit me and my mate. No
one likes her in this building.
>> Was Was that true? Yeah. That was that
was an Asian guy actually coming on the
door when you was in Birmingham. Is that true?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Some black dude do
come to the door. Yeah, I told him to [ __ ] off.
>> How many times?
>> Couple of times, but I kept him telling
him to [ __ ] off.
>> What did he ask for?
>> He was asking for Natalie and all that.
Look, this is what I'm on about. This is
why I think I do need to get tested.
This is why I do think I need to get
tested. And you know what? I am actually
going to get tested.
>> I have I think I need to either way now
to be honest with you. So a black did
that did that did that not listen listen
that did that did that in itself not
raise flags red flags when that happened?
>> No because I thought n changed we come
to this agreement that we both stay off
YouTube that we both sort our [ __ ] out
and we talk to each other instead of
[ __ ] running away
but now she just keeps running away
instead of talking to me and sorting
[ __ ] out. This girl I don't even
>> When you said she wasn't here, what do
you do? Just left.
>> I didn't even say she was here or
nothing. I just told him to [ __ ] off. He
tried to get him past me. I didn't let him past.
>> That's madness. Wait, but how did he not
just knock the door or ring the doorbell?
>> You ring the doorbell and start banging
on the door.
I'm I'm leaving her now anyways. I'm not
chasing after Natalie cuz that's what
she wants me to do. She wants me to keep
chasing after her. I'm not even [ __ ]
texting her. She's unblocked.
She wants me. She can ring me. She can
sort this out now. I'm not sorting
nothing out what I haven't caused.
>> Just find some I think you should just
we just go out again and find someone
else. Me, bro.
>> I need to punch something. [ __ ] punch
>> What are you doing? [ __ ] [ __ ] man.
>> What the hell are you doing?
>> You're going to hurt yourself doing that. Jesus Christ.
What am I doing this?
What am I doing? this.
What the [ __ ] bro?
You're a [ __ ] prick, mate. >> Yeah,
I've done nothing to that woman.
Absolutely [ __ ] nothing.
I needed to punch that. Yeah. One more
[ __ ] punch. One more [ __ ] punch.
>> You're going to get sectioned if you carry on.
>> I'm done, mate. With him. I'm I'm done,
mate. I'm done now.
>> You're going to get sectioned.
>> No, I'm not. I'm done. I'm done. [ __ ] done.
No. Why the [ __ ] would you put her
initial on your arm?
>> I don't know. Because I loved him, mate.
That's why. Cuz she had the feelings for
that. That's why. Until last night. My
feelings just just disappeared. They
just went after I seen that doing what
she was doing last night. They just gone.
I've only loved that woman.
I've never loved anyone else in my
[ __ ] entire life. And then she just
goes and does and treats me like a
prick. Like I'm the I'm the one who I
ain't done nothing wrong. I'm not the
one who's sitting there and saying,
"Sorry, am I [ __ ]
I'm not even that girl's mate, mate. I'm
[ __ ] my man.
>> Jesus Christ.
>> I might just put this window through
with my face, mate.
>> Don't do that.
That's going to hurt.
>> She She had a man who actually loved her
for who she is. She did. She did. That
girl, I don't even like that girl, man.
I don't like her. I don't know her. She
wasn't my friend and I wasn't having her
as a friend either. I was already
socializing with people here. I don't
want no one as a friend in this place.
>> I wonder if she added me. >> What?
>> I don't give a [ __ ] PJ is or not. I'm
keeping away from me, mate.
It's nothing to do with me anymore.
Well, I'm not [ __ ] I've been told about her.
It's causing a lot of [ __ ]
And now we now Natalie just [ __ ] me
off with absolutely nothing.
Just be asking her to go to the shop and
get in her with you. >> Yeah.
>> I'm not asked any more, mate. To be a
little honest with you. I only helped
you out cuz you were there for me.
>> Yeah. last time when Natalie done this to me.
And I'm not going back down that road, peeps.
Peeps, I do love Natalie. I [ __ ] do
love Natalie. I can't say I don't love
her because I [ __ ] do.
I I really do love Natalie.
But if she's doing this to me, getting
with me, then finishing me when I'm
[ __ ] asking, talking to people, I
need to keep
You know, I've only been here on the
front on the front talking to not all of
them except for the pricks. I don't
chill with the pricks and she is a
[ __ ] prick. That girl is a [ __ ]
prick. She's with them.
They were going out with that Dylan lad.
I didn't even know that. I didn't even
know that until the member of staff told
me today she's got a problems with with
Dylan. How can you love a woman that
loves the black hawk? What is wrong with you?
>> I don't know. Please,
I don't know. I [ __ ] don't know. It's
love that you can't help who you fall in love with.
>> God bless you.
>> No, you can't, PJ. You [ __ ] can't.
And that woman thinks I don't love her.
She thinks I don't [ __ ] love her. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Prop [ __ ] my knuckles up there, mate.
>> Bless you.
>> No, man. She doesn't understand how much
I love her, mate. She She thinks me
talking to another girl thinks I'm going
to run off with that other girl. I'm a
[ __ ] I already had eyes for one woman.
You I did
and that was Natalie. Everybody knows
we're going out with Natalie here
because I couldn't stop talking about her.
I've got a [ __ ] initial on my hand.
Yeah. Where's the [ __ ] stone? Yeah. I
[ __ ] scared that [ __ ] off, mate.
>> Cold approach K again. See what happens.
>> [ __ ] you, man. Why the [ __ ] am I going
to go hold that ugly little [ __ ] [ __ ]
Listen, I will never go out with Kayie
ever again for shagging rice. If Natalie
goes and [ __ ] shags whoever out of
this community, I never [ __ ] go out
with her again.
>> She might have not She might have not
shagged him yet.
>> Oh, she has sh eyes.
>> I'm not one of them people who [ __ ]
around like this P. I'm not a [ __ ] around.
>> And it feels like I'm getting treated
like a [ __ ] around,
>> you know? I don't [ __ ] around with
women. I don't.
>> If I'm in a relationship, I'm committed
to that one person. Yeah,
>> that's me. I'm always committed to one person.
If Natalie's got crust issues, we'd be
talking to other women.
>> Did you like your Did you like your
piggy omelette in Birmingham? It was
nice, isn't it?
>> Yeah, that were gorgeous. That were nice.
>> That piggy omelette we had? >> Yeah,
>> that nice.
>> Nice piggy omelette.
>> I'm not going to cry over her no more.
She's the one who's going to embarrassed
herself now, not me
going all on YouTube. She's just done
enough of Kashing
herself trying to get me jealous and all
that. I don't give a [ __ ] what she's
done last night. Last night put me well
off her. And if that's what Natalie wants,
she's got it.
She's got If she wants me, she's got a
lot of [ __ ] work to do, mate.
A lot of [ __ ] work.
I went out of my way. I got that like
tattoo done on my arm could prove to
Natalie that no other woman can have me.
She's marked me with her name. She's
marked me. She's marked my skin with her [ __ ] name.
You know what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> She has marked me with her [ __ ]
initial. Yeah. And if that's not enough
to prove that I love that woman to
Natalie, what is
>> No, she has a UK biggest bouncer.
What is What is good enough for Natalie
to prove how much I love her? How can I
prove to a woman how much I love her
when she could just keep [ __ ] me over?
>> Is she actually a UK bouncer or you lying? >> What?
Nothing. Let's see what he says.
>> Yeah. What What did he say about that? About that?
>> No. Oh,
listen. I haven't done nothing to that
either way. Yeah,
she can be a prick with me all day long.
Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] anymore.
Yeah, she's got a choice. I can just move on.
>> What's her What's her channel, UK biggest lobster?
What's the channel?
This life is crazy. Monty,
you we got we got a big
>> I am thinking about it. Listen listen
now like I'm Natalie's got a choice.
Yeah. Can ring me up and talk to me now
and sort this out completely or I'm
first thing is waxing [ __ ] half n I'm texting.
>> No, that's not her channel. What's her
full channel name? Cuz I've just typed
it and it's not on there.
>> You know what I mean? So Natalie's got a
choice. She can ring me and sort this
out or I'm just [ __ ] of me. Someone
who actually does want me. Someone who
actually does care about me. Cuz this
woman was up half the night thinking
about me out on the streets and all
that. But Natalie. Yes, lad.
[ __ ] off, man. That [ __ ] [ __ ] in
that building, man. In that building.
No, villain's [ __ ] exm misses.
>> Villain's exm misses. [ __ ] [ __ ] mate.
>> [ __ ] get me into [ __ ]
Been showing me taxes and all that [ __ ] >> Really?
>> Yeah. Of mandolin and and that, you
know, she just finished me again because
they asked me if she want to go to the local shop.
>> Yeah, man.
[ __ ] pathetic, mate. [ __ ] man.
>> Not qu.
>> Well, what you go to?
>> I can't find her channel.
>> No. No. She's what I got here.
>> Is it true? Is it true, Haunty? Or is it
[ __ ] I can't find her. I just typed it.
>> My missy, she's [ __ ]
I can't find her channel all over YouTube.
flashing yourself all over YouTube
thinking it's some game while I'm playing
>> this conversation mean no game but misses
time's it now >> 5:55
>> you been kicked out
>> no I walked out
>> yeah that's good
>> I walked out no they were going to kick
me out I've just walked out I just gone
I just went I just gone
>> Is it true or
>> both of them
>> is it true I'll do legend.
>> I can't find the channel.
>> What do you mean?
>> I already asked that [ __ ] she wanted
to come shop with us to get away from
picking on her cuz picking on her is in it.
>> I don't know.
>> What's the title of the video called?
>> I need to see this. PJ.
>> Anyway, Py, I'm off. Natalie, you got a
choice. Ring me home or don't ring me. Yeah.
Yeah. You got a choice now. Yeah. PJ,
I'm off. Yeah.
>> All right, bro.
>> Natalie, you got a choice. Ring me or
don't ring me. I'll see you later.
>> Wait, before you go. Yeah, Natalie, you
got a choice. Ring me or just [ __ ] off.
Impulse cuz these tattoos getting gone.
So, you got today if not
what's her channel, honey. One second, Monty.
>> I can't find it.
>> I can't find it, bro.
What the [ __ ] is this channel? I need to see this.
Oh my god.
What the [ __ ]
Yeah. So, so there's no such video then, is there?
[ __ ] I just woke up. Money wanted me
to go on YouTube, so I went on YouTube
cuz money wanted me to. I was asleep
since 6:00 p.m. I must have been tired.
Jesus Christ, man. Oh, I [ __ ] missed.
It's bullshitting it. I'm miss
I'm [ __ ] hungry, dude.
I'm [ __ ] starving, bro.
I thought I see some piggies.
Should go bigger Pat. I found some piggies. This
YouTube thing is bad, bro.
It's [ __ ] bad, is it?
Madness. I'll be back later anyways.