box. Box pizza.
Yeah, Monty wanted me to tell you that
they're back together.
He wanted me to go live and tell you.
I'm quitting this YouTube [ __ ] anyways.
It's too freaky for me.
It's too freaky.
You're [ __ ] freaky. It's a freaky
[ __ ] community. Yeah, really. Mhm.
Yeah, bro. And if he wants me to send
messages, he he can go live himself in
future, bro. Cuz I kind of I want to be
involved with this [ __ ]
Um, no one's going to get hurt, bro.
These people don't even leave the house.
They can't get off of YouTube.
Well, that good vibes only. He stalks
me, bro. He's a creepy old man.
That good vibes only. He watches me and
he and he's blocked. Why are you
watching me if you're blocked?
Who will I talk to? Uh, my friends. Um,
my family. What do you mean? Who would I talk to?
I mean, pizza.
This good vibes only. This guy, he's
blocked on my channel and he watches me.
He's a creep.
He's a [ __ ] weirdo. He's only from channel.
That's how you know they're obsessed,
bro. And stalking my football bets and
[ __ ] They're [ __ ] weirdos on here,
bro. But yeah, they're back together,
which is good. Yeah.
Um, what's my opinion?
I don't have an opinion, bud.
Wow. I just told him to be careful.
He's blocked, but he still watches. What
a [ __ ] loser.
No. No. Listen.
Sorry, bro. I need to come off, bro, cuz
I need to see who can live without
YouTube, and I want to see if these people can. So, yeah.
I want to see if these people can live
up and if money wants to say something
in the future, he can go live on his own channel, bro.
I want to see who can actually get up it.
Well, every time I I try to quit
YouTube, [ __ ] Monty tells me to go live
or something mad happens and it keeps me
on here, bro.
Yeah, Monty. Monty's not coming on cuz
he's not allowed on YouTube. He said,
he just messaged me now. He's not
allowed on YouTube.
>> Yeah. Jamie said, "Thank you for getting
them back together."
No, he's not allowed on YouTube.
Well, obviously Natalie doesn't let him on it.
It's good that she was trolling Discord
though. I hate them bastards.
I'm glad to be honest. I know. I'm glad.
Nice piece of jalapen.
Come in the box.
I'm in the box, man. Boxing box. What?
He's back together with Natalie.
Yeah. She said he's not allowed on
YouTube, so he doesn't he doesn't want
to come on. Yeah.
Lost pizza wipes.
So hot today, bro. I can't stand it.
I haven't blocked you, Marty. I haven't blocked you.
Oh, I'm having this pizza,
pepperoni, jalapenos. I'll have the
other half a bit later.
Yeah, good. She mugged them all off, bro. Good.
They're [ __ ] [ __ ] That's Thomas.
I still don't have anyone though.
All my efforts, all my good trying and I
still don't have anyone.
It's like I was saying to Greg, it's not
that there's, like I said, um, like I
was saying, it's not that there's not
someone for everyone. It's the fact that
if there was none of this, um,
if there was none of this um, Tik Tok
[ __ ] I would have had someone by now.
I had my chances back when it was possible
and I ruined them. No problem.
I'm watching some GTA videos, please. Damn.
It's so hot, bro. It's unbearable.
It's unbearable, bro.
I hate this weather.
Bad. I've even got the fan on as well.
The favorite the the best month of the
year is March. March and April where
it's in the middle. I don't like it too cold.
I don't like the [ __ ] uh hot the
windows are open, man. Horrible.
March is the best. Early April
[ __ ] It's horrible, man.
I nipped the shock waves. That's about it.
Did you get your little McDonald Jack them off?
Imagine Scotland in January. [ __ ] that,
bro. [ __ ] that.
No. [ __ ] that.
You [ __ ] probably ch ice cream.
Yeah, that good vibes only a coward.
But I'm glad she trolled them all to be
honest. They're all [ __ ] cowards,
mate. And she used their money to go up
and see him, which is good.
Yeah, they're [ __ ] little pricks on
YouTube, man. I'm glad. I'm happy.
Only thing is now they're going to show
her. That's the thing. That's good.
I can't stand that Jack Jones man. Keep
seeing him all over [ __ ]
Facebook. I can't stand that. Yeah, [ __ ] up.
I still need to cash in this bet. Oh, [ __ ]
Man, just come in the box.
>> I need one of them dashing fans. Me, mate. Oh, [ __ ]
Okay, he wants to box.
[ __ ] I need another fan, bro.
I had a big one at my other house, but I
sold it for £10 because I couldn't bring
it with me and I was a massive fan. It
was I bought it for £40 years ago.
But the heat is unbearable, bro.
It's It's unbearable, mate. [Music] box.
>> I got two seconds and I'm up. >> Yeah.
Thank you for for getting out of here,
everyone. Yeah. Thank you. It's nice to say. Yeah.
>> Yeah. It's good though, is it?
>> No, it is. It is. But I'm going to shoot
now PJ. Yeah. So I'm not me and not off
YouTube now for good. We quit. That's
it. We're done. >> Really?
>> Yeah. Yeah. I don't even think we'll be
watching anymore to be honest. >> Yeah.
>> Watching or nothing because at the end
of the day it's [ __ ] me up is [ __ ]
everything up though.
>> Thank all them though for getting a real
life for me. Nice and safe like [ __ ]
hell. But I'm off now. Yeah.
>> Yeah, man. All right.
>> All right. I won't be coming back on no more.
>> All right. Good.
>> [ __ ] box.
Do you like the box?
We have a box. Good. [Music] Thank you.
It's a madness.
Cool. Antman left. Graves. Ant man left.
Yeah. Ant man left, bro.
No, he doesn't watch.
He doesn't watch, mate. He doesn't watch
at all. At all.
Oh, that's all. That's all, bro.
Where is he?
Yeah, I was just saying it's really hot,
Greezy. Really hot.
So, Grezy, is your birthday April or
March? Is it one of them? Hey, man.
I had a really good fan that was £50 I
bought years ago, but I sold it cuz I
was moving. So,
I'd get one of them Dyson's, but they're
like 400 breezes
and they don't go hot and cold.
Obviously, it's going to be winter soon,
so not worth paying out that money for.
You know what I'm saying?
[ __ ] hell, though. [ __ ]
your birthday is either March or April,
ain't it, Greasy.
You've got to be one of them.
Do you remember Steven Howard? He says
if the football bet don't win, he's
going to nick my teddy.
Oh, you're lucky. I wish I was born in
March at April,
but I'm I'm born a couple of days before
Halloween, so I mean that's good. I'm
gonna nick your telly. Yeah, he's a
[ __ ] troll. Is it? I think that's Tom
Wood, you know. That's Steven Howard.
I'm gonna nick your telly.
I'm going to make sure that [ __ ]
weird on it.
Oh [ __ ] bro.
March or April. I wish I My mommy was
born in April. We April the
I forget what what what day was but my
mama was born in April. We see actually
man trying to join. That's the virgin Monty.
Yeah, he's back with Yeah, I sp him.
money, if that's you trying to join, let
me know, man, cuz I think that's the virgin.
We don't have virgin on my channel, mate. Sorry.
Yeah, he's back with a
I was watching some WWE for a couple of
hours, Greeny. I was watching like old school WWE.
I felt like I was a kid again. Yeah, man.
Felt like I was a kid again. [ __ ] this heat.
I might need to go swimming tomorrow or something.
Maybe I'll have to go swimming. Oh, cuz
this heat is unbearable.
My mom was born in April.
I was I was born in April.
Best month. Not too hot, not too cold.
It's good. It's a good month.
What do you think the worst month is?
December, I think, cuz it's cold. It's
an expensive month.
January is [ __ ] as well. February is just pointless.
Yeah, I knew that wasn't new, Monty. I
think it's the Virgin.
Yeah, cuz January is [ __ ] in it. No one
goes out. It's cold.
Is Sheffield Is Sheffield the West Midlands?
Do you know
It's the West Midlands, isn't it?
She left Sheffield. Yeah.
Nah, it's the West Midlands.
No, it's it's West Midlands, bro.
No, it's West Midlands field. [Music]
If I do the if I do a video on the
Virgin Grezy, will you watch it?
I bet you'll get your little popcorn
out, wouldn't you?
I think of doing it with the with a pig t-shirt.
I mean, you've been reacting to me quite
a lot on his virgin channel. So, I mean,
it's only right, is it? Have to make
sure there's no creases in a pink t-shirt.
Go to the cinema, get yourself some
popcorn, some coke, easy. Yeah.
I don't really want to entertain that virgin though.
He needs to get laid. That's what he
needs to do. [ __ ] get laid. Get off
YouTube and get laid.
So, what would you do if you was merely
in this in this position? Would you
carry on trying every week, every two
weeks? Would you leave England?
What would you do? Powerful spell.
[ __ ] are you talking about?
Yeah, but I don't I don't seek
validation from women. Greasy.
I I went to Birmingham um last week cuz of Monty.
Because of [ __ ] Monty and [ __ ] Um
I I I don't, bro. I I went because of
Monty and I wonder if where I didn't go
out this week, did I?
I did go out this week. So
I'm too old to be going out [ __ ]
drinking every week now. I do. What do
you mean? Do your own thing like go to
cinema and stuff in it
pretty much. Yeah.
Yeah. It was nice, bro. It was nice. I
haven't finished all of it yet. I just had some
uh a minute ago. I was watching
I was watching some WWE
earlier. I was watching like The Rock and stuff.
Yeah, I like The Rock. He's my friend. I
just I follow like a lot of GTA
channels. Uh Grevy where it says, "No, I
don't put on the fridge. I put on top of
the microwave." And it says, "What
happens if you do this in GTA?"
Uh they do it from the first one to
five. Like, you need to watch it, bro.
It's good. Let me link you a video.
Actually, you need to sub to these
channels. They're quite entertaining.
One second, bro.
It's just a load of D's, lad. Yeah,
I think honestly my favorite Yeah.
wrestler. If I had to pick two, I don't
know, man. I like Randy Orton.
Yeah. Just watch that. It's just things
like that. I'd say
I don't know, man.
Are you talking about ones that are
still wrestling? Then maybe
I used to like I don't know. I like Randy, man.
I like Randy Autton.
I like Hornswaggle as well. He's little hornswaggle.
Don't know, bro. I don't know.
There's a lot of wrestlers, but there's
a lot. There's a lot, man.
Uh, not really, but I didn't really
know. I never used to watch him. I know
who he is, obviously, but I never really
used to watch him. I saw WWE a couple of
times when I was younger.
First, I watched Smackdown and then then
I watched Raw. Raw was a lot better than
[ __ ] Smackdown, bro.
I prefer the Raw one. I was right near the wrestlers.
God knows if it's still Smackdown and Raw, but
yeah, I used to like Raw.
I used to like see punk as well. You see
what I mean? Greasy.
And my favorite GTA is San Andreas.
Greasy is four. I ain't played GTA 4
since I was like 13.
14, I think.
No, not 13. I think I was like 15, actually.
I played it a lot, man.
Yeah. And there's this guy I met on
Smackdown versus Raw 2009 when I was 13.
And I still talk to him now. I'm 27 and
I think he's 32, 33. I met him like
over 20 years ago. And he come to
England once and I met him. He lived in
America, man. We still talk. We're still
homies, you know.
Yeah. I think I was like 11, 12.
And yeah, that's when I met him. Yeah.
I'm playing the game.
Yeah. Could be.
Yeah. Monty's back with Natalie Nicolo.
Come on. Not so long ago. Yeah, they're back together.
Now he just needs to stay off YouTube.
Now he just needs to stay off YouTube, man.
Like really needs to stay off YouTube. Oh [ __ ] Yeah.
Oh, that's good though. She trolled them
to get the money to go and see him.
Nah, it was all planned. I think it was
all planned. She just got the money off
of them from Discord and then just went there.
He doesn't get into into a relationship
so easy, though. Here's the thing, bro.
Like, I I could have met Natalie G.
Let Natalie G's met loads of people. And
don't forget, he doesn't live in London.
He's never lived in London.
You know, if I if I didn't live in
London, I probably would have [ __ ]
been with someone and you know, I've had
chances to be with people, but now it's
impossible because of this Tik Tok [ __ ]
Like, I had chances and don't forget he
doesn't live in London,
so it's a there is a big difference.
Like you saw when I went to Birmingham,
bro, [ __ ] all them free numbers replied.
When do you ever get three numbers that
all reply and keep replying? Never, bro. So,
I do think, like I was saying to you
earlier, I do think London is the
hardest. The only way you'll really
know, right, properly really know is if
you went out of London. If you went out
every day, if you went out of London and
you tried every week for a month,
cuz with the Birmingham one, you could
just say, "Oh yeah, you got three
numbers that reply, but bad luck." And
then then the next time you go out, you
might get something. But in London, it's
always the same. That's what I'm saying.
So, you won't really know
if you tried. Yeah. Yeah. You won't
really know unless you try for like a
month really somewhere else. Really?
But it says a lot when you get three
numbers and they all replied. That
That does speak volume, man.
That does say a lot, is it?
But like I said, if I go out next week,
I'm going Cardiff, bro. I already told
you this. I'm going Cardiff.
I told you this. I'm not I'm not doing
it in London, bro.
I can get there back drinking £100,
£130. I'll just go there.
Can't be bothered with London.
I don't know, bro. I must have been [ __ ] tired.
Oh, it's [ __ ] knocking, man. Yeah.
Uh, I was thinking about my mommy earlier, Nicolo.
I just can't I just don't know how women
can be so heartless and evil
to abandon something that they gave
birth to. It's mad, isn't it?
Do you remember Ant-Man? Other guys do it.
Other guy not doing it. He's obsessed
with other guys doing [ __ ] in it. And it
it's stupid because it doesn't change
your situation thinking about other people.
It literally doesn't change anything.
you know, and and as much as you say it
as well, Nicolo, they still compare you
to other people,
you know? It's it's ridiculous.
But yet, most of the people, you know, are single.
Yeah, I was going to do it, bro. If he
kept pushing me, I'm going to be like,
"Oh, guys, how are you doing it?" Cuz
this guy keep [ __ ] But it's [ __ ] bro. Because
it is It is [ __ ] There's there's,
you know, just cuz other people have met
someone, it don't mean you're going to meet someone.
If I if if you looked around and
everyone else was in relationships, then
maybe. But they make it seem like you're
the only one, but you're not the only one.
That Indonesian guy is single. All the
tenants are single. Most of the people I
know are single.
So it's like
they make it seem like you're the only one.
Yeah. He's obsessed with other people
getting, you know, it's weird.
It's so weird.
It is weird, bro.
Ways they they they do it, bro. you
know, they might have got lucky. They
might got lucky on a dating app. They
might have got lucky through work or
um you know, something like that,
which is not comparable to you.
This is what I'm trying to say. It's not
comparable to your situation
considering most of it is about luck.
You know what I'm saying? It doesn't make sense. So,
especially if they're rejecting you
based on your race as well,
bro. He said to me, you know, about
Americans. He said, "You didn't have to
go to America. It's like the Americans
came to you. Every time you was in
London and you tried, there were
Americans." He said, "You you had the
best of both worlds."
He said, "You didn't have to go to
America." That's what he said. The
Americans came to you and you knew they
were all [ __ ]
So you had the best of both both worlds.
That's what he said. He said, you know,
they're no good in America.
[ __ ] madness, bro.
when I had two dates in the um the same
day, Nicolola, the one with that one
with the freckles
and then the other one,
the Italian one that I knew where she worked.
Oh yeah, bro. I couldn't stand them. I
can't stand Americans. They're up their own ass.
Yeah, I can't stand Americans, bro.
I really can't stand them. I used to
hate them on the PlayStation as well.
Yeah, it was annoying, bro. I was like,
this and I'm thinking Fourth of July
doesn't apply here. We're not in
America. We're in England.
Yeah, they're [ __ ] bro. You get a lot
of them in Liverpool Street as well.
LT said LT said I'm a keyboard warrior.
Yeah, he tried saying that I'm a snake
about how I speak to him more friendly,
then I come to him and then I'm talking
nonsense about about him wanting my dead
girl that I was crying over. I'm not a
troll. I'm not a keyboard lawyer. Then I
put dead in question marks. She's an
absolute babe, darling.
I said to him, she's an absolute babe,
darling. Don't talk about my mama like that.
Oh no, not that one. It was another one.
And no, I didn't. I think she went back
to America. She was another troll.
Yeah, I think she went back to America, man.
She shot herself when I saw her again.
She didn't expect to run into me again. Yeah, man.
You've been here for a very long time,
ain't you, Nicola? I think you was that fire account.
Stig not Peter Belly's mama.
I just know it is in it. I bet you're
like some 50y old man behind that account
cuz you seem to you know too much.
You know too much.
Like that like that little Britain
scene. You know too much. Do you remember Grezy?
Yeah. She asked for my little Snapchat.
Yeah. But that doesn't mean anything cuz
my mommy offered me her number.
Do you remember that one Grezy? You know too much.
Yeah, this guy knows too much. It's true
though. Is it? Do you remember that one, Greavvesy? Ah,
I can't believe my She offered me her
number. I never got that again.
Well, well, when I gave somebody money
in Nottingham, they they they offered me
their number. But I've never ever had
someone offer me their number before.
I thought we us two clicked. I thought
we clicked. Nicolo,
can't believe they actually [ __ ]
offered me their number. That's crazy. Yeah.
Look at your little picture, Grezy.
You're obsessed with Stitch, aren't you?
Oh, bless you. Greasy is my biggest troll.
Greasy is my biggest troll in it. Yeah,
my nose is hurting me, bro.
[ __ ] nose is hurting.
Yeah. No McDonald's. No more McDonald's now, Grezy.
No more. No more McDonald's from tomorrow.
You're a nasty troll. You are.
Do you know what I don't understand
about Virgin Boy? He needs to come up
with some new insults. That nose thing
is boring, bro.
That is boring. He's He He's obsessed
with my [ __ ] nose.
He's obsessed with my I smell weed, man.
I can definitely smell that.
Someone's smoking weed, mate. Yeah.
Yeah. Someone's smoking weed, man. This cannabis.
No, you can smell it. You can smell it.
There's no rins in that game.
Greavves, you Greavves, you should come. Rand,
we can play GTA 5 together. Come Rand. Yeah. Oh
yeah. I only The last time I smoked weed
was with that Somalian
and the time before that was Amsterdam.
I don't smoke.
Oh, that's horrible, bro.
Yeah. Last time I smoked it was with
that Somali in Grezy.
Yeah. She gave me a [ __ ] Gezy,
what would you say the chances are of
getting sex in this day and age, Grezy?
If you was a virgin?
Nah, no chance.
Like, say you just wanted to get laid,
which is strange because people say
that, oh, people need to see women for
more than just sex. But there are people
that just want relationships
and they don't even give them a chance.
And also there's such thing as wanting
sex and a relationship.
It's just that when you're um horny, you want sex.
That's what makes me laugh when people
say, "Do you want a relationship or do
you want sex?" Because I mean
you they both go hand in hand.
I never understood that question
cuz you can also have a one night stand
with somebody and then start liking them.
So, I mean,
unless you're a [ __ ] um
what's that word called? Sexual where
you you like people based on
personality. Is it a pansexual?
What's that word?
What's that word? That's I think it's called pansexual maybe. [Music]
Sure it is.
No, it's not asexual. Asexual means you
don't like both of them. Asexual means
you're not attractive to men or women.
More you're not attracted to men or women.
I think it's called a panexual. I think
bar quest used to be.
Nah, I [ __ ] blocked her, bro. She was
a [ __ ] weirdo.
She's an absolute babe, darling. Uh
No, I speak to a [ __ ] in Scotland, but
she just ignores me. She says I just go
on about women and stuff. That's why she
stops speaking to me,
cuz I used to complain about women to
her and stuff.
Yeah, there's a transgender that lives
in Scotland. She lives in Glasgow.
Nope. She's not from this community. Yeah.
She don't want Yeah. Oh [ __ ] Yeah, man.
Cuz that's where we're at. What will
happen if I go out approaching Cardiff
on Saturday? Nicolo,
sometimes I think I don't know how the
[ __ ] I ever got laid.
I just don't know how the [ __ ] I ever
got laid, bro.
You do actually think like that though,
is it? Like when you come back from
places and [ __ ] and you get the same
I've got a boyfriend, it's like how the
[ __ ] did you even get laid
all the them times you actually did meet
people? It's mad, isn't it?
You go out, you get [ __ ] all it
and then you go out and you get [ __ ] all
in it, Nicolo.
Yeah, like that [ __ ] I got in the alleyway. it.
I think I've only had one date. No, I
had two dates this year. Do you remember
that one in Birmingham I met? She was
trying to use me for Weather Spoons at
Birmingham. She was stinking, bro.
Yeah, she was from Birmingham. I
remember that. I still got her number. I
messaged her saying, "Oh, I went to
Birmingham, by the way."
Yeah, she was from Birmingham. I remember that. Yeah.
Yeah. But now you can't get nothing, mate.
Nothing. Nothing at all.
Yeah, it was weird. And then she was
trying to point blank the night. I
didn't even like her, bro. I said, "I
know what you're doing."
Like, and I didn't even like her
anyways. And then she was trying to say
she didn't do it. I said, "I've just
seen you do it. Why did you want me?"
Yeah. She's like, "Oh, you go first." I
said, "Why am I going first?" Cuz we
ended it. And and I kissed her as well.
This is the weirdest thing about it.
She's like, "Oh, why
why are you I said, "Why do you want me
to go first? Let's walk to the train station together."
That's a bit dodgy. You know,
that was dodgy, isn't it?
I'm not stupid, matey.
So, I knew what she was trying to do.
And I didn't care cuz I didn't like her
anyways. But yeah,
they're [ __ ] at Nikolai.
Sig not eat a belly's mama.
S not eat a belly's mama.
She not Peter Belly's mama.
That made you laugh. in it.
You should be trying to be my mommy.
Yeah. You remembering it? You remember?
I think. No, I think No.
Uh, who's my real mama, Nicolai? Yep.
How do you remember this, you weirdo, bro?
My real mama. Um,
I don't have a picture. Um,
oh [ __ ] [ __ ]
But yeah, you
remember I lost 500 online in it, Nicolola.
I think I got it to like something and
then I didn't take it.
I think I did. I don't think I did lose.
I I think I might have won. I'm not sure.
Or I think I might have lost 250. I
can't remember. I think I won, didn't I?
I can't remember. But I know I think I
got to a certain amount that I lost it.
Yeah, I can't remember. But
who's my real mama, Nicolola?
That's my mama.
That's my mommy.
That's my mama. I can't believe LT calls
her a dead girl. She's an absolute babe, darling.
I literally wrote that to him. She's a babe, darling. Yeah.
No, that's my mama.
She's a coward, though.
She's a [ __ ] coward. I still see her
reply to people on [ __ ] LinkedIn. I
caught her on LinkedIn, Nikolai.
I caught her on LinkedIn and she replies
to um people, well, people like
colleagues and stuff.
Don't [ __ ] reply to me though, do
you? You little [ __ ]
Doesn't [ __ ] matter if someone just
wanted a one night stand. That just goes
to show how entitled they are, bro. They
think they can use people and then just
drop them without explanation. How the
[ __ ] bro, can people be so entitled?
They're so entitled, isn't they?
They are so [ __ ] entitled, Nikolai. [ __ ] hell.
No, because he's going to say, "I know
this is you.
I know this is you.
I know this is you."
Do you hear that? I know this is you.
She stopped pretending to be one of
these viewers videos.
No, I commented on her [ __ ] Facebook
thing. She's not blocked me. I said,
"Come on, you little [ __ ] Let me come
and see you." I said, "Come on, you little [ __ ]
I know this is you."
Imagine that though, Greavves. You're
messaging someone and they say, "I know
this is you."
That is a madness.
I know this is you.
That's mad. I know this is you.
Go get some help, [ __ ]
Where's that guy from Bristol I used to
speak to on Facebook? One second.
Where's he gone? Uh Kenji.
Kenji his name was Yeah. Kenji.
Yeah. He was [ __ ] around with my little Isabelle.
So, I had to uh
Yeah, I had to show him who's boss.
Yeah, I have to show him who's boss, didn't I?
Do you remember Scott messaging me?
You knew it was me. So, why didn't you just talk?
Why did you block me and stuff? That
weren't nice. Why did she do all of that
stuff? She should have just spoke to me
and stuff. She's a coward. Catch him.
He was saying I'm a stalker and [ __ ]
He's the one that told me to go there.
Where's that guy I used to speak to from Bristol? That's weird. Hold on.
Yeah, she was a coward. Oh, here he is.
Oh, he's there.
Yeah, [ __ ] coward, bro. Coward,
I remember one day when I was 19. Yeah.
I found £60. I turned £10 into £500 and
I found 60 on the floor. I think it was
£60 I found on the floor.
Good times, bro.
When's my mama going to speak to me again? Nicolo. My mama.
I'd say USA. Is he? People say that
Natalie G is a slag. That's what people
say. Yeah. But no one's more of a slag
than USA, is he?
25 people. Sleeping with 25 people is a
lot, man. That's [ __ ] a lot of
people, is it? music. At 27,
I think I've only slept with about four
or five people that weren't escorts.
Well, make her love me, Nikolai.
Nah, she won't. I called her the other
day. She said, "Hello." I said, "Go suck
your mom, man."
I said, "Go suck your mom."
She's a blocker.
She's a blocker, bro. As soon as you
message her, she blocks you straight away.
I think I've only had sex four or five
times that weren't escorts. Yeah,
which is quite normal, isn't it?
But I've had [ __ ] more times than that.
Yeah, I told her to go suck her mom. [ __ ] coward.
>> Yeah, she was 27 and I would She had 24
people before me. That's quite a lot, isn't it?
I said, "Why do you want to have sex
with condoms?" She said, "Oh, some guy
gave me something before."
I said, "You what?"
She said, "Yeah, some guy gave me um an STD."
Yeah, it's funny, bro.
No, that's not normal, bro.
20 20 20 24 people at at 27 is not. No.
What do you think this? Well, that one
in Nottingham was 20 and she had 20
people. She had already been with 20
people at 20.
That's the thing. That's what
contradicts it, Nicolo. Unless you find
the slag, you can't get nothing. People
hate on these slags, but if you didn't
find the slag, then you'd have no experiences.
Cuz if they're not a slag, they're time
wasters that won't even date you.
Do you understand? So unless you find
like a slag,
you won't get anything from anything,
you know, in any way. So it it just
contradicts the whole thing, isn't it?
What do you think will happen? Uh
please, if I went out approaching last Saturday,
if I went out yesterday approaching,
what what do you think would have happened? Think
I would have got laid or
what do you think would have happened?
I'd have more success. Ah, so what do
you think would happen? Yeah.
I've got to thank who USA is.
They never give it up. They just waste
your time. Remember
that one that I date that I went on a
few dates with when I came back from Belgium, Nicolo?
Nah, you wouldn't have pulled in, bumy,
bro. I've been all over the country and
I barely pulled. You will never pull in
these westernized countries. You will never pull.
By you, I mean me. Course, how are you
going to pull in, bro? Bro,
how could you? Nah,
you won't. It would never change. Yeah, me. Yeah.
Yeah. I have, bro.
You literally like honestly, bro, like
really really like all jokes aside, you
you actually have to leave the country,
bro. Cuz at at 27 or even 30 or 31, like
you should be getting laid every week.
You should be able to go out, get laid.
You shouldn't be dealing with these
problems in your prime years, but you
are. So like really the only thing you
can do is leave.
Anyways, do you remember Oh, back to
what I was saying. Do you remember that
one that I went on a few dates with when
I came back from Bel uh Belgium?
And I said, "Oh, you should come back to
mine on the second." We had two dates.
Yeah, I remember her. I went on two
dates with her.
See, I had chances back then, but not anymore.
So, it's not as easy as that anymore.
I met I think two people on a dating app.
I met her then I met that one in Read
and that was crazy.
So I [ __ ] went Oh, bro. I'll never
forget that Reden one. That red one was
scary, bro. Yeah, the park one. I think
I would have been with her now if I just
kept meeting her. But
yeah, I actually met her on Bumble, but
now it's just
Yeah. Yeah, we held hands and
[ __ ] But yeah, the red one was the
worst one, bro. I'll never forget that red one,
did I? Yeah. Yeah,
that 19 I said that to the to the
19year-old as well. She said, "Not she
said, "Not if you don't give me money."
I told her to [ __ ] off. She said, "Can
you give me money?"
And I was like, she said, "Can you give
me money?" I said, "No." Then she said,
"No, I can't be your girlfriend dead."
She said it so bluntly.
She said it so bluntly. I told her to [ __ ] off,
always asking me for money.
No, that's my mommy
who I met two years ago, Brooke. She
abandoned me. She blocked me and
everything. She She led me on.
Nah, I I'm not going to keep her, bro.
Why do I want somebody that I have to
keep giving money to? And she was being
entitled. She was being a [ __ ] No, she
turned into a [ __ ] in the end.
No, she turned into a [ __ ] in the end.
No, that's someone I met two years ago.
They abandoned me,
led me on.
She used to have no money in that.
She used to come around with the
tenants. She used to come in the room
and suck my dick in it.
But she was a [ __ ] though. She made me
like clean my dick and that which is a
turn off. Like I like a [ __ ] that would
suck your dick
and not she would make me like clean it
and that even though I said my dick was
clean. I don't like that. I like like
dirty like a not a dirty [ __ ] but
I don't know bro
cuz she didn't like doing it. So
she made me wash my dick. She used to
come around with the tenants um when the
tenants were there.
I own that tenants.
No, she did in the end. She did in the
end. They were getting bigger.
But that doesn't matter anyways, bro.
She was good-look enough. She was
good-looking, so that doesn't matter.
Oh, there's someone I used to see.
Yeah, I own the tenant, bro. I said to
that girl, listen, don't tell me you're
going to get your boyfriend on me, bro.
I'll slap you both up. Yeah, I told her
I'll slap your [ __ ] both up, bro. And
you said no one wants to suck my dick.
Here's the thing, bro. Yeah. You was
giving me your money and that girl that
you met in that house was sucking my
dick and she's 100 times better looking than you.
Yeah, I told her, bro. And I told the
other tenant, I said, "Yeah, you can
steal, but you can't steal to my face."
And one of the tenants said today, cuz
like I'm friends with three of them, but
I don't have a problem with three of
them. He's like, "Oh, I swear to God. I
swear to God. I swear to God um
I swear to God um that no one stole it."
I said, "Well,
yes, you did steal it because it was in the bag."
No, she was trying to say that I owed
her money cuz one of the tenants grasped
about like the house being took so I
said, "Listen, yeah, you little
[ __ ] Don't [ __ ] I own all of them
in a group chat, but they didn't say
nothing. All of them. I only had
problems with I had problems with two of
them, which was her and obviously the
one that I and then they're saying, "Oh,
no one stole your after save." So I
said, "Where's the after shave gone then?
Well, has it has it got legs and walked?
Because I know where all my stuff is and
we looked everywhere. So, yes, you did
steal the after shave.
Like, you're a barefaced liar. And how I
know that they're lying is because there
was clothes that I chucked out before
which I didn't want. And he was wearing
my t-shirt, which I didn't care cuz I
said, "Oh, yeah, you can have it." Like,
because I don't want it anymore. And I
said, "It looks good on you cuz we're in
the same like skin complexion.
Yeah. And with the same skin complexion.
And he said, "Oh, it's not yours." I
said, "Well, yeah, it is." Because I
remember buying it the day that I met
Izzy. So, I said, "Yeah, it is." And
then like he made a big deal out of it.
And he and he swore it wasn't mine. He
said that he got it from the buyer.
Said, "Brother, it's mine, which I'm
giving to you. You can have it, but I'm
telling you, you got it from where I
left it. I don't want it. I don't care."
And he was barefaced trying to say that
he got it from the buy. I said, "You
didn't get it from the buy. Stop being
ridiculous, you know. So, you've lied
point blank to my face already." So, I
mean, like, it's And then he cut the
t-shirt up, apparently. Which you didn't
have to. I said, "You can have it. I
don't want it, but I'm just saying you
found what I what I threw out. Stop lying."
So if someone could lie to your face
about that then I mean what did the
after shave just get legs and walk and
they all stick up for them each other as
well bro. So yeah
they'll never admit they're a lying
piece of [ __ ] So there's just no point
getting into it with them.
So I said you're not getting no money
back. [ __ ] off bro.
And a girl I own her proper [ __ ] own
her properly, bro. Proper own her.
Yeah. [ __ ] stupid little slag. Yeah, man.
She was going to call her boyfriend
because she says that I only owe her
150, which I don't owe her 150,
but she never said anything after that.
So I said, "Oh." And then what pissed me
off about it is somebody told my business.
Someone actually told my business. So I
just I'm just happy they they took the
house in the end. Obviously, we lost
some money, but that's it's only money,
bro. It doesn't matter. We can make more.
Don't really care about that. I just
hate them, bro.
So [ __ ] them. But yeah, I would have
stuck with her. If she wasn't an
entitled [ __ ] I would have stuck with her.
But she's entitled and
I didn't like her attitude in the end.
She was becoming more westernized.
Nicolo, you can see the westernity in their eyes.
You laugh at that, but it's actually
true. You can actually see the
westernity in their eyes. These women,
you actually can.
Yeah, you actually can, bro.
ain't you ever watch approaching videos?
I don't know. They look just evil like
MP. They're just NPCs. Yeah.
So that's where.
But yeah, I would have stuck with her if
she wasn't a [ __ ] But she is a [ __ ] So
But she was decent looking. She was
good-looking. She actually was
good-looking, bro. And she gained
weight, which made her look better. So,
yeah, she was good.
But her attitude just started stinking
and I weren't going to put up with it. So,
they just get more westernized as they get older. Yeah.
I don't know, bro. Maybe LT,
but I know one of them tenants
definitely stole my after the shave
cuz I know where I put everything. So,
so I know someone definitely had it away.
So, but they swore they never, but I'm
telling you, you [ __ ] did, which is
stupid because it lost smell to it. I
bought another one. I bought a small
one. It was £72. Yeah.
Yep. They were Yeah.
Is that is that Romania one in
Birmingham in a relationship?
I just seen her put a picture up of some guy.
I just asked her who's that in her store.
She doesn't She doesn't look that good
though to be honest.
Yeah, she doesn't look that good.
She doesn't look that good though to be honest.
See, there's one. But
even if they meet, they live in Liverpool.
So, I mean, what are you going to do? Go Liverpool. [ __ ]
She doesn't look that she doesn't look good anyways. Um,
trying to think.
What are you going to do, bro? Go
[ __ ] Liverpool. [ __ ] that. I'm never
going there again.
You know that time I went Liverpool, Nicolo? Nah.
Yeah, basically she was seeing somewhere
out. She was seeing someone else.
Oh, she said it's just one of her mates.
Uh, okay. So, it's just one of her mates.
See, she actually replies this Romanian.
It's mad how she doesn't go out with me.
It's weird. Anyone would think you look
like Timmy. No, basically she was gone for months.
Oh, she's one of her friends.
Um, doesn't matter. But listen,
um, basically she wasn't staying for
many months because she was traveling. I
think she was out the country. And
obviously I said to them like, "Keep
your mouth shut basically because I want
to try and get money every month from
her because she doesn't know about the
house, even if it's like one month."
Um, and then all of a sudden she uh she
said, "Oh, she wanted all of her stuff
gone all of a sudden." Like she she
tried to say, "Oh, I want my friend
stuff here." Like she tried to word it
around and then I was like, "She
definitely knows something. This is
dodgy." Because why all of a sudden is
she telling you after all of these
months to move her stuff? Um,
and then I said, "No, this is dodgy." I
mean, what's the coincidence? And then I
moved all her stuff and that and what I
was going to do honestly. Yeah. Was this
is what I was going to do. I was going
to see what would happen. Yeah. I was
going to take her stuff out the house
anyways and place it somewhere. But
we're going to steal her stuff. And if
she had paid and then she had come back,
then I would have gave her money back
with the stuff or like but if she kept
paying for month and month for month for
month and month, month for month and
month, then I would have just kept
taking it. And as soon as she comes
back, I would have just gave her the
money back. Like I weren't even going to
[ __ ] her over. But I was trying to say
to her like, "Bro, you weren't even
staying in the house. You weren't even
in the country. I don't know why you're
getting mad. like you you were paying
for a room that you didn't you weren't
even staying in until you come back. No
one knew if she was ever going to come
back. So then with the whole grassing
and then with the after shave thing I
said add me back in that group and I
just started on I just started on them
in it but that's it bro cuz it was annoying
because yeah if she had come back then I
would have gave the money back bro. I
was going to give the money back back to
that guy, but since they stole my after
shave, I was like, I'm not giving you
nothing back. [ __ ] you.
[ __ ] you, bro. But yeah, if that had
happened, then I gave the money back obviously. But yeah,
so someone grass, someone did, someone must have Yeah. >> Yeah.
But I was I weren't going to [ __ ] her
over. I broke the door and took all her
stuff. I mean, I said to her, "What
would you do?"
You know, what what would you do if
someone's not staying somewhere for
months and they're paying you anyways?
What why would you tell them?
You know what I'm saying? Like, why why
the [ __ ] would you? It's not like
they're going to come back and lose all
their stuff, is it? So, so yeah, madness.
But yeah, they're not good people anyways, bro.
Don't have to deal with her [ __ ]
Yeah, I said to that Romanian, I'll bless you.
It's weird how she replies back so fast.
That's why the whole USA Izzy thing is
so [ __ ] up because you actually met
her and got intimate with her and you
actually spent money on her and she
[ __ ] you over royally.
Whereas you can just meet someone for
like 5 minutes and they'll show you more
respect. It's mad.
That's like the whole mad that that's
the mad thing about it
because it's not very common, right,
that you [ __ ] someone or you get
intimate with them or whatever and then
they just randomly
block. It's not really
It's not really normal, bro.
It's not It's not normal.
The one in Manchester never done that.
She just said, "Oh, yeah, it was fun,
but I'm not looking for anything." Or,
"No, no, no, no."
So, it's not really common. No.
This one from France changed her number.
[ __ ] hate French women. I do, bro.
[ __ ] bastards they are.
They're such trolls.
I got this number at the train station. No reply.
Yeah, it's strange. It is strange
because you can literally meet someone Yeah. and
they'll show you more respect. Like you
can speak to them for like five or 10
minutes and they'll reply and then no
and then you can do that and then they
just block it so mad.
It is. It is. It's not normal, bro.
I've never had that before where I got
with someone and then they done that, bro. Never. Never, bro.
She's [ __ ] entitled as [ __ ] It's mad
how someone that looks like her can be
that entitled. Is it?
It is madness. How could
she don't want to know you?
So what happened with the whole Britney thing then? Nikolai.
She's quite an interesting unless she
was she. Nah,
I don't know how he could be obsessed
with somebody that never wanted him.
Like not like wanted him then not wanted
him. Someone he never ever met. Not even
met once. Never met.
Like never met. Like they never ever
met. and she rejected him and he and he
was obsessed talking about killing
himself and [ __ ] [ __ ] me.
Someone that he never even met and kissed. [ __ ] hell.
Some have rejected his ugly ass. It's [ __ ] mad.
Honestly, it's mad, bro. He used to
always go on about it.
Come to think of it, bro, these people
are actually worse than me. You know,
all right, Nicolo, do you remember when
he said he was going to go to that
girl's workplace? He said, "Give your
head a wobble. Stop talking about some
girl that don't want you." I'm not. Oh
my god, bro. Do you remember that one?
Uh, I'm not.
And he starts like having a [ __ ]
outburst and [ __ ] Well, I'll never forget that.
He's like reading the comments very slow
like this. You need to give your head a
wobble. Stop about some girl that don't
want you. I'm not.
Um, not there.
Why? Why? Why? Why did he Why was he
thinking of me? Why was he talking about
me? I didn't [ __ ] say it.
He don't don't want you, mate.
Don't want you.
[ __ ] don't want to know you.
He's [ __ ] up because of his childhood.
He was in a in care from a very young
age. You know, I'm not
USA. Izzy is a [ __ ]
She's going to look back on this [ __ ]
when she's 40, you know,
and she's going to wish she never done
it. Say she has a kid in the next year
or so. You're going to end up a lonely
old woman when she's 37, 40, and she
wish she never done this [ __ ] Which is
mad cuz they're so
they don't learn from each other. Do
they not realize that when they get in
their 30s, they're going to have no one.
That's that or like 35, 36 that no one's
going to want them. They don't even realize that.
Ant-Man's like, "Oh yeah, but even at
that age, they can get who they But they
can't though cuz that's why they they
they begging. Look, look at Jane for
example. She's begging attention off men
cuz no one wants her or no young person
wants her. I guess maybe they prefer
younger people that and then they can't
get younger people and they're that age.
Think about it, bro.
They're older than they seek attention
online, you know. Yeah. F. Oh no. Oh [ __ ]
Have you ever almost [ __ ] yourself,
Nicolo? I I have
few weeks ago. I almost [ __ ] myself.
I had these hot wings
and um it was about 7:00 in the morning.
I had to go back to the house
and obviously nothing's open and I was I
was I was on the bus here holding it in,
holding it in. And I come across the
some cafe which opens at 6:00 in the
morning. I ran in that cafe. I was going
to [ __ ] myself.
I'm not even joking, bro. cuz I had to
get a train from the train station. But
there was a cath right by it. I reckon, bro.
Nah, you don't. Nah, you don't. Of
course you don't.
You stalk people you love. Think of it.
He's been stalking me longer
than I've been stalking USA.
And then me and USA Izzy had some really
really nice intimate moments. So think
about it, right? I've not met this [ __ ]
in about 10 years and the cunt's still obsessed.
So read into that what you will, man.
[ __ ] man. I'm obsessed.
and I don't know why he keeps showing
his [ __ ] housing benefit.
Like, am I supposed to be jealous or something?
Am I supposed to be [ __ ] um jealous
of your housing benefit or some [ __ ] Jesus Christ.
Yeah. He needs validation that you've
not slept with them because he's never
slept with anyone.
He goes out of his way
to get them to admit that they've not
done anything with you or because he's a virgin himself.
It's quite strange, isn't it? Yeah.
I don't know why he keeps showing his
housing benefit. Like I said, bro, I
could have £500 to my name, £400 to my
name and I still have a better life than you. So yeah, man. Yeah,
life is about money obviously, but it's
also about how you live your life. You
know what I'm saying?
I can't explain it, bro. Like, yeah. Yeah.
I'm sure it was Michigan or Massachusetts.
No, I still want
No, I don't think it was Massachusetts.
Where was the other one begin with M?
I don't think it was Michigan.
No, there's another one beginning with M.
One second. Let me look it up. I just
know every single state off by heart. [Laughter]
Oh, it was Missouri. I think it was
Missouri, I think.
Was it Minnesota? Was it Mississippi?
No, I think it was Missouri.
Definitely wasn't Massachusetts. That
for a fact. Man,
back when dating was easier.
Yeah, I still got that hotel video, man.
I come across it yesterday. The one with
the Nottingham one. I said, "How did you
suck my dick so good?" She said, "No comment." Ah,
mad. [ __ ] mad.
Oh, the crazy bastard.
Crazy bastard, man.
No, I didn't. No,
I don't even think I lasted that long,
man. You done it in a certain way and I
just [ __ ] I think I just came.
We was foreplaying for a little bit like
kissing. I was touching her and that. I
didn't [ __ ] her cuz she was on her period, but
I kept moving her hand on my dick and [ __ ] Yeah,
that's why I stayed another day. That's
why I went back on a Monday cuz we was
fooling around on a Sunday. Yeah. Did I?
Oh, did I? I can't remember. Probably. Yeah.
Yeah. That was the OD pan one. She
stopped coming. I think she got in a relationship. Stupid [ __ ]
just stop coming around. Yeah.
You remember that American that gave me
a [ __ ] in the eleway? Nicolai, I
really want you, but I don't think you want me.
I really want you, but I don't think you
want me. I said I do, but not right
here. People are looking. God damn. God
damn you. Oh, [ __ ] What?
I really want you, but I don't think you want me.
That's funny, bro.
Must have. Yeah.
Yeah. And then I got my dick out and she
gave me a [ __ ] and I couldn't I
couldn't feel my body.
I don't even think I came to be honest,
bro. There was two was behind it. It was
in an alleyway in it. So,
well, I don't think you want me.
That was mad, bro.
Yeah. Her name was Sophie. He was
rubbing my todder the whole way through.
Yeah. I said I like boobies.
She said, "Lucky for you, I've got both." Yeah.
But they never follow it up. That's the
thing. They never follow it up.
The [ __ ] comments, bro. Yeah. Yeah, man.
I'm stuck in a toilet now. [ __ ] jalapenos.
Remember, the slower the better.
I said, "What are you doing?
You're moving a bit too fast here."
Yeah. I never forget when I went back to
the apartment, Nicola. I thought, "Oh,
she's just showing me around, isn't it?"
Like, I thought it was just some sort of
date or something. And I sat down on the
edge of, you know, like the edge of the
couch. And then she just started coming
towards me, kissing me. I was like,
"What the [ __ ]
This is crazy, man." I said, "What are you doing?
What the [ __ ] are you doing? Yeah,
it was the madness, bro. I never forget that, bro.
Yeah, it was bad.
Why Why would you say text me when you
get back if you were just going to do that [ __ ]
She's a [ __ ] lion, son, mate.
Yeah, I was young like two years ago. Yeah.
And then [ __ ] when I kept doing that
[ __ ] when when I was doing that Uber
Nickelo, it kept taking me to my mama.
It kept taking me to castle Nicolo with my mama. Yeah.
Yeah. I don't care about the [ __ ] bro.
Yeah. I don't care about that [ __ ] I
only went I only said that the other
day, bro, cuz Monty kept going on about
[ __ ] Natalie and where someone keeps
talking to you about something, right? you
you're sort of um
it keeps bringing it up so I just feel
[ __ ] it I'll go along with it. I don't
like that [ __ ] bro. I'll tell you if I
did. He's [ __ ] sick in the head bro.
He's [ __ ] sick in the head. Yeah,
>> I was saying as well, [ __ ] Nicolo,
right? I was saying to Monty cuz I
thought this that I said if she goes
there today and she tries, I'd slap her
around her face.
That's what I was saying. Um,
I was saying um
I said that if somebody was going to do
that to me
like I would have slapped them around
their face. I'm not joking, but I don't
give a [ __ ] if it's a woman, bro.
But obviously they're back together now.
She was trolling and she was trolling
because the way I see it is he I felt
sorry for money when I was listening to it earlier like he
She's siding with people that tried
ruining his life and it was annoying
just listening to it. But obviously she
was trolling them. But if she wasn't
trolling them then, bro, trust me, I
would have if it was me, she would be
getting a flap across her face. I don't
care if it's a woman. I don't give a
[ __ ] Like you see with me, I don't care, bro.
That's why people really
shouldn't mess with me in that way. But
but she was trolling them anyways. Good.
I didn't like listening to it, but it was annoying. Yeah.
Yeah. Does Chucky live there?
She thought I was never going to find
out her little name.
She She thought that I was never going
to find her name in it. Yeah.
trying to say I was [ __ ] grabbing her
and [ __ ] She's [ __ ] crazy, bro.
She's a crazy bastard.
Grabbing you. What the [ __ ]
She's mad like
[ __ ] blind spot on my nose.
Hey, bro. You're right. I'm just I'm
just on the point at the minute.
Oh, San Andreas.
How long do you reckon it would take to
save up to go to America if you're
getting £1,100 a month? Nicolola, I
think you could go in about four months.
Yeah, maybe about four months if you
lived off like 80 pound a week.
Yeah. Um, probably 4 months probably.
And man said he'd go to Thailand even if
he was just on benefit and did shoplift.
It would just take him like 4 months. Yeah.
Depends how bad you want something. See me
obviously I had savings. I won some
football bets. But with me, yeah, say I
wanted to save up to go Thai like
Thailand, America or somewhere. Let's
say for example it would take me 4
months to save. I could do it. I could
not go out for 4 months. Yeah.
Because I've done it all
cuz I've literally done it all. So I I
wouldn't be missing anything by not
going out because I've done it all. When
I had that house for so many years, I
lived the life. I went out, you know,
getting free grand a month. So, it's
kind of like I
got the right um
sort of obser
as well. So, it's like I I I
it could have went better to be honest.
If that makes sense. I could I could
easily do it, bro. Four months not going
out. What are you going out for?
You know, the country is a waste of time.
But I had savings, so I was like, "All
right." You know,
they weren't going to I generally
thought they were never going to take the house.
>> I thought they never going to take the house. >> Really? Yeah.
It took him like 3 years, man. [ __ ]
should have just put in my [ __ ] name.
Or if you had Uber, you can go in a
month on Uber every day. [ __ ] Yeah.
Football bets on the way forward, isn't it?
I still need to pick up this football
bet, Cory. Man,
80. I need to collect 230.
£80 to 230.
Nah, bro. Cuz they would have called the police.
Yeah. 230. I wish I done I wish I done
both teams to score no draw, bro. It
would have been like £500.
But still 150 in it. So,
and I won two I won 200 last week
150 this week. So, that's one that's 350
in two Saturdays. So,
but the only bad thing is like say you
were saving and then you lost all your
money gambling, you'd have to start all over again.
You'd have to start all over again.
That's the problem.
But you just wouldn't gamble in it. Like
no, they wouldn't.
They've got a court. They've got a
warrant, bro. It doesn't matter. They
don't care. They've got a warrant.
They've got a warrant signed by a court
by the court.
But one thing I don't miss about the
house is them tenants. the responsibility,
but I do miss the house. It's not even
just the money, bro. I don't really care
about [ __ ] money, but
I lost a lot of [ __ ] cuz of that house.
And I got into a lot of [ __ ] because of
it as well. So, like with the [ __ ] stupid tenants,
I just So, I'm just happy I don't have
that the responsibility of it anymore.
I don't know how I would have afforded
to go out, bro, like in them three years
if I didn't have the house. Now it's
okay cuz I've done it all. Now I'm just
chilling cuz I'm older
and I'm leaving anyways. But like in
them three years, three and a half
years, what if how would have you
afforded to been able to go out and
[ __ ] You would have been [ __ ]
You wouldn't have been able to do it on
like £1,100 a month, bro. No way.
No [ __ ] way.
No way in a million years, bro.
You wouldn't have. But now you just
don't go out much anyways. You know the
result in it. So yeah,
I've still got 2K. So not too bad.
You wouldn't have been able to though.
That's scary, bro.
So, I would have been in my prime,
not able to get women, not being able to
try to get women, and I wouldn't been
and I wouldn't have been able to afford escorts either.
Like, how bad would have it been, bro? Really bad.
There'd be no steak meals for USA.
There'd be nothing.
Yeah, I would have been [ __ ]
I don't know what I would have done,
bro. I don't think I don't think I would have worked.
But it's fun staying in the house cuz I
liked getting on with the tenants. They
used to cook for me and stuff. And
that's why I hated doing Uber because
I liked having my own time in the house
uh with attendants and stuff. But now
now I don't have anyone. I'll just I
would do Uber every day cuz I've got
nothing else to do. So I would just do
Uber every day. But sometimes like they
wouldn't have a shift and then I'd be
out all day and then but now like or
even if you live by yourself. Yeah. You
got nothing else to do. Do Uber every
day. It's either that or sit bored.
Yeah. So, I had I lived my prime really,
bro. I traveled all over England. I've
been abroad. I went out every week. Gambled, drunk
to the max. Now I'm not Now I'm at a
stage where I wouldn't even be going out anyways,
even if I had loads and loads of money. So,
it could be worse. It could be a lot
could be a lot worse, man.
Now, think about that. You didn't have
to work for three years
and you was getting 3.2K a month and you
didn't have to work for 3 years.
That's mad, bro.
I got my garments, bro. I need to get
them dry cleananed. I still haven't got
them dry cleananed yet. I got like four
stonies that need dry cleaning. So yeah, man.
Yeah, that was good.
It might have to be it might be back to
Coke bottles now. Nah,
it will never be that bad. When I don't
go out now, bro, it's not because of the
cost of it.
It's just cuz I can't be bothered.
That's what it is. It's cuz I can't be bothered.
It's [ __ ] boring, isn't it?
Maybe I'll put that 230 on Frankie. Nah,
I can spend on club. Of course I can
if I wanted to. I can go out every week
if I wanted to. Of
course I can.
I have two I have 2K. Yeah.
And I get the same money every month. Of
course I could. Of course I could. Clo every week.
Of course I can.
But I just don't want to. That's the
difference. I don't want to. Of
course I can, bro. I could I could
probably do it every week and probably
save like 300 a month.
I just wouldn't be able to save
anything. I'll just have the same amount
of money every month, which is fine if
you're not planning to leave the country.
Yeah, it doesn't matter, bro. You could
still save 250 a month if I went out every week. Also,
I get 80 pound every week on top of it
as well. So,
I could do it, bro, if I wanted to save
or not save. But I'd rather not and then
just save a little bit so I can, you
know what I mean?
You're not going to go through two grand
in a [ __ ] month. You know what I'm
saying? Realistically. So,
But I'm going to do it anyways, bro.
I'll probably go out like twice a month
or once a month. You don't need to go
out more than that. Already done it a
million times anyways.
The [ __ ] you going out for? I can, like
I was telling you, I can go to Cardiff
and back with a train and the drinking
for probably about £100, £120. So 150 maximum. Yeah.
I would even book a hotel, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, [ __ ] going out [ __ ] drinking
every week, bro. I would I wouldn't even
be doing that anyways.
I didn't even do it anyways when I was
getting that same income. [ __ ] that.
No, but so what about the Indonesian fellow Nicolo?
Oh, he's pathetic, man.
He's actually a sc he's actually a
scared [ __ ] And he
can change, though. You can change it.
You just have to go to [ __ ] Asia.
You just have to You just have to go to Asia, lad.
Then you will.
You just have to go to Asia.
Yeah, you go on you go to Thailand, bro.
You go to Philippines and you go on
Tinder and they all want to meet you.
They love white men
and you can get them without money as
well in the Philippines, you know.
Now, he wouldn't be married back in his
country because they only like white
men. Well, they most they they mostly
like white men. So
if you go Cambodia or Philippines,
you have none of these problems.
Even when you use Tinder here, um
now you got no chance.
You got no chance in this country if you
go Philippines. Yeah. or even you stay
here, you go on dating apps,
you can get um
you you get women that want to meet you
like from Tinder. You don't even need to approach.
But yeah, people don't think that this
country is the problem.
You got no chance. He He's especially
got no chance, bro.
He's [ __ ] He's Indonesian.
No go. No girl's going to get with that.
They're not even going to go for me.
And I'm [ __ ] white. He's [ __ ]
He's like the most He's one of the most
least desirable races.
And he's [ __ ] in Asia as well because
they only like white men. One sec.
I think ages ago. Yeah.
They have they they've got that look in
their eye in it that Westity. Yeah.
Yeah. It's true though.
They all have the same mannerisms. They
all say the same things. That's what
Ant-Man says. I said they're NPCs. He
said, "It does seem that way, don't it,
mate? They say the same things. They've
got the same mannerisms."
It does seem that way, mate.
Oh, what's this?
It sure is.
Yeah, you can't get one. What's this, Nicolo?
I'm I'm getting that costume, but I'm
ordering that costume right now. That Chucky costume.
I'm going to go out approaching in it. Yeah. Yeah,
£22 it is. I'm going to buy it now. £22.
I'm actually buying it, bro.
It takes two weeks to come.
I'm going to dress up like Chucky.
Yeah. And I'm going to approaching it.
[ __ ] it. Is it
see if there's any different results? Yeah. [ __ ] good.
Monty was going to lose his life today.
He was going to lose his life today.
Nicolo over the same website. You can
watch this on uh bye-bye.
My brother's worm food. Well, funny
enough, he was actually cremated and he
actually wasn't even my full real
brother. So, try again. Virgin boy.
Look, the same website you can lose your
life on, Nicolo.
This is part of the reason why I'm [ __ ] off.
Yeah, man. [ __ ] that. That's dangerous.
same website you can [ __ ]
you know new July. [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] that [ __ ]
Damn it, bro. [ __ ] that, man. Oh [ __ ]
How old was you when you first watched Chucky?
I was about 10 when I first watched uh
Charles Lee Ray.
Yeah, I was 10.
Yeah, that's [ __ ] dead, bro. [ __ ]
[ __ ] 10 hours, bro. Jesus.
It's [ __ ] up. Chucky.
Oh, there's a kid costume.
I didn't even realize there was a kid
one cuz I always said my nieces went
through a through a Chucky stage.
Oh [ __ ] I didn't realize there was a kids one,
bro. But that's definitely Chucky
cuz they went through like a Chucky
stage cuz obviously the height and the
hair and stuff. Oh, I didn't realize that
they actually went through Chucky stage.
Bro, if they wear this, that's definitely Chucky. Definitely.
Maybe she's all too tall now though.
How old is she? Seven.
It always reminds me of USA. Is he Chucky Nicolo?
You know, like the New York buildings and stuff.
You know, like the scenery. Ah,
now I'll never know.
Now I'll never know.
No, I'll never know. Oh
no. I'll never know. Yeah.
I was supposed to be there living there
having Chinesees every day.
Just reminds me, you know,
the East Coast just reminds me of it,
bro. Whenever I see stuff like the East
Coast of America, it just reminds me.
I wonder what would have happened if I
didn't go that night.
Now I'll never know.
Now I'll actually never know.
I will never know now.
Yeah, that's what was
that's that's what was supposed to happen.
I'll never forget, bro, when I said,
"Can I see your boobs?" And then she
pulled her top up.
She pulled her Calvin flying top up. How
cute is that? Yeah.
She was showing me her tattoos. Nicolola.
Yeah. She said my ex said that.
I said you got nice boobs and I was
squeezing them on the sofa. She said,
"My ex said that."
Then I started holding her hand. Nicolai,
how cute is that?
How cute is that?
Yeah, that was really cute, man. Really cute.
Yeah, they were soft and natural. Yeah.
And I said, "Oh, are you tempted?" She
says, "A little bit."
Then she started pulling me pulling me towards her. Oh,
that's a lovely little color.
Oh, I'm thinking of buying this t-shirt.
I might buy this t-shirt with it as well, bro. Look,
it says I'm your friend to the end.
>> Yeah. Nottingham is he had nice boobs, too.
Look at that t-shirt. It says, "I'm your
friend to the end."
That's funny as [ __ ] bro.
There's a few Chucky t-shirts on here,
bro. With the costume.
There's a lot of ones.
A Chucky cap.
Yeah, she had nice boobs though, man.
They were really big.
There actually is a Chucky cap. It's £24.
There's another one here. It's black.
Yeah, few chucky ones.
I didn't think there'd be so many to be
honest, but there is.
It's a cute little hat in it.
There's quite a few of them though. What's
It takes like two weeks to come though.
It must come from America, is it?
Yeah, she had nice boobs, man.
to feed baby Peter, isn't it, Nicolo?
Some of these won't come until like the
2nd of September. Jesus Christ. It must
be coming from America, is it? Damn.
There were some Chucky caps, but they [ __ ] two.
What would the baby look like if we had
a baby? Nicolola,
what do you think the baby would look like? Yeah, never.
never happened again.
Yeah, it's very rare, man, for somebody
to offer you their number. I was on like
a dry spell for two months, uh, two
years before that.
Yeah, it's very rare, bro.
She messaged me first as well saying,
"Oh, do you want to meet up Tuesday?"
She wanted to [ __ ] me there and then,
bro, that's mad.
Imagine just meeting a woman that just
wants to [ __ ] you there and then. That's
mad. I probably could have [ __ ] her
that night. I actually approached her. Nah, man.
Oh, what about this little cap?
What about this little cap?
Or do you want me to get the hat and the cap? Oh.
[ __ ] I'll get that. Yeah, man.
That little cap. It's £23.
It takes about 3 weeks to come.
Just wear like a chucky top and a chucky cap.
Oh, that's cute, man.
It's cute, isn't it?
Do I Do you like that little cap?
I that one.
to the top collection.
Hi, I'm Chucky. Want to play?
and I'm your friend to the end. Heidi. Uh,
no. We should do like this. Hi, I'm Chucky.
I don't know, bro.
It's too hot for that.
USA is what do you think the baby would
look like, Nikolai, if we had babies in it?
It would be cute, wouldn't it?
What do you think it would look like?
Why? Why was she kissing me?
Why was she giving me kisses?
I bet sometimes you'll be out on the
train or driving or whatever you do and
you'll think about things that I've said
and you'll just yourself laughing in it
because I do it.
I [ __ ] do it, bro. But why?
Why? Why did she scam me?
She was writing lover hearts and stuff. [ __ ]
Oh [ __ ] bro.
Scar me. Hi. Yeah.
Cuz cuz I think of like the comments
that you write in it like you know the
comments that you write. I think about
some comments that you write like
mocking me and it makes me laugh.
It's funny, ain't it?
So why why was she scamming me then,
Nicolola? Why was she scamming me?
What was she scamming me for? Yeah. Heat. Yeah,
they say all women aren't the same, but
they are. All westernized women are
exactly the same because if they were different,
they wouldn't say the same stuff like,
"I've got a boyfriend.
Um, I'm just not interested or the [ __ ]
that they do." If they if they generally
weren't all the same,
they they'd say different things. They
do different things.
But they don't.
Yeah, they're the same, bro. In the
western westernized women are the same.
Cuz they all watch the same Tik Tok
[ __ ] Tik Tok.
Yeah, they they they they uh
they all they watch the same [ __ ] on the
internet is it? So the only women that
will truly love you is Asian women or
South American women. They're the only
women that will love you. Not these westernized [ __ ]
See, Chinese is he liked me a lot,
but she just had loads of debts to pay and stuff. My butt.
Chinese Izzy was licking my butt.
I never had someone lick my butt before,
bro. That was weird. So Yeah.
It was only a few hours after.
How can they say all westernized women
aren't the same?
They are the same, bro.
Guess what's a mustag? Mash tag mashag.
He's an idiot, man. But he reminds me of
He reminds me of Ant.
It's the eyes and the nose, isn't it?
They look like each other.
I need to go to bed soon, bro.
No YouTube from now, bro. I need to come
off this [ __ ] Monty's got anything to say? Yeah.
What do you think, bro?
Do you think it will ever change in this country?
Never, bro. It will never change. That's
what Ant-Man said. And he said, "How's
it going to change?" He said, "It will
never change." He said, "When you used
to go traveling, they were laughing at
you." He said, "These women were mocking
you, taking the piss."
He said, "You never stood a chance."
That's what he said to me. He said,
"You've been up and down the country.
You never stood a chance." They were
just laughing at you
like they were laughing at me.
That's what he said the other day.
Yeah. I said to him like you can tell by
their eyes by looking at them. He says,
"Yeah, you can see the Westinity in
their eyes. They're all MPCs.
They're all MPCs."
I remember when me and USA Izzy was sat
in the taxi, Nicolo. She said, "I had a
great time today."
I said, "Me too, mama."
That's what I said.
Yeah, you can see the westernity in
their eyes though. I see it.
Look, I'll show you. Look. Right. Look. One sec.
Look, look carefully, bro.
Look in their eyes. You can see it.
You can see the westernity in their
eyes. You can't look.
They look like NPCs.
They're all NPCs. NPCs. What?
>> Yeah, it's true though. Look at their
eyes, bro. You can see it.
You can see the worst energy in their eyes. The evil Yeah.
They look I can't explain it, bro.
You can see it in their eyes, isn't it?
Look carefully. Can't you see it?
I know what he means though. I do know
what he means.
I show him these I show him these
approaching videos in it. He says I'm
sick of watching them. He said it's the
same guy approaching women and it's
always the same outcome.
That's what he says. He says it's the
same guy, different women, same outcome.
when I saw these these approaching
videos in it and they pop up on Instagram. Yeah. Yeah. Mom,
you see the widility in their eyes?
It does. It actually it actually seems like
where they watch too much Tik Tok and
that it takes over their life.
It's like in their brains, you know? I
can't explain it, bro.
I'm sick of seeing it. He says
hello. He says I'm sick of seeing it.
They're laughing at us
now. Have you seen what the government
does now, Nicolo? that they um
they um make you verify your age now
before you can
go on it.
Have you seen what they've done now, bro?
USA is he looking old as [ __ ]
She looks old now. Yeah, but once you
verify, they ask you to do it again.
[ __ ] that, bro.
You verify it and then they ask you to
[ __ ] do it again.
Do you remember Scott though, Nicolo? Scott Jobert
all at the table on Thanksgiving talking about me.
Pair of [ __ ]
Them two are pair of [ __ ] mate.
You can see the westernity in their eyes. [ __ ] hell. Scott Jober.
Scott Jober. He says you little [ __ ]
[ __ ] hell, bro.
You must be some mental little [ __ ] messaging me. [Laughter]
You remember that? Yeah.
I'm part of the family now. Yeah.
He was a cheeky little [ __ ] that he was.
Yeah, he was a cheeky [ __ ]
God damn it. I wanted to [ __ ] slap
him up, bro. The [ __ ] does he think he's
[ __ ] talking to? Fat [ __ ] Yeah.
Do you remember the voice notes of that
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] bro?
He was actually winding me up.
He said he was going to cut my dick off
and show it to my mom.
No, no, mama. Yeah, Scott.
Do you feel sorry for Scott Nicolola? Nah.
Good old Scotty. Um,
not in this country. They're
not interested in this country. No.
Do you remember Casside Mark's old
videos? I'm going to go and I'm going to
gamble today and I hope I [ __ ] lose.
I hope I lose.
That's what he says. I hope I [ __ ] lose.
I want to do something dafted.
Whoever them days, I'm going to go to
the bookies. I'm going to do something dafted.
I'm all right, bro. Oh, Stephen Howard,
come on your real account. We all know
that shoe Tom Woods.
This you know this Steven Howard
account. Nicolo said that if he if he
loses this football bet, he's going to
steal my telly.
He said, "I'm going to nick your telly."
Yeah, Tom Woods. I'm in your real
account, Tom Woods.
I'm going to nick your telly.
This is Tom Woods, bro.
It's the same It's It's the same atmosphere.
Is that the real Timmy?
Timmy, listen. I went to Birmingham and
you done nothing.
Me and Monty called you out. Yeah.
Love it, bro.
My mommy said I was cute. Nicolo,
she said she goes for guys like me with
beards and dark hair.
And I said, "That's me. I'm that person."
Then she says, "Yeah, pretty much.
That's why I gave you my number."
I was like, "Oh, I'm in here. I'm in for
some sort of relationship. Oh,
it was it was it was all a lie,
wasn't it? It was all a lie.
It was all the big fat nasty light, was it?
Is that the real Timmy?
Oh my god.
this the real Timmy.
Timmy, shut up, man. You're not going to meet anyone.
Why do you come on YouTube still acting
big to me? You always you always get
your ass whooped.
You've never ever won a fight. You've
never ever took a W. And you still come
on YouTube calling people out.
You still come on YouTube calling people
out. It's mad.
Yeah. You've never won.
You never took a W against anyone.
They're the same people every night.
You remember body man used to say that Nicolola
it's the same people every day same atmosphere
same people same [ __ ]
the vinity in their
Oh, I'm tired, bro.
Um, Monty and Natalie G's back together. Yeah.
They're back together, which is good.
Now we can shut the [ __ ] up. Oh,
yeah. They're back together.
I'm going to nick your teddy. [ __ ]
hell. You weirdo, bro.
I'm going to come and nick your ty. See
what I mean?
Why am I [ __ ]
Oh, yeah. He won't contact me anymore. Yeah.
Yeah. They all forget about Peter Belly.
Peter Belly just gets left alone. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm going to nick your telly.
The Steven Howard. Who is just Who is
this Steven Howard account?
He was a Steven Howard the cop, bro.
>> Yeah, it was a good football bet, wasn't
it? Steven Howard,
good football bat.
I want to nick your tenny. [ __ ]
weirdo. You are weirdo, bro.
I want to nick your tell.
I'm going. I'm tired. Yeah.