Yeah, man. Oh, [ __ ] I need to get some
batteries for this controller, man. Just
checking to see if it's the same people.
You know what I mean, man?
Weekly um welfare welfare checks.
Just checking to see if it's the same people.
Probably not though because everyone
else is skint
got no friends and stuff. So it's
probably not the same people to be honest,
you know. Hopefully I'm here all by myself.
Oh, two people already. Oh my god.
Hopefully it's not grievy or anyone like that, man.
I should I just want to be here by
myself on my live stream. No one
joining. Just peace.
Just peace, you know. No one join in.
Just peace. Peace and quiet. No one typing, you know.
Why people? Oh, that's a lot, isn't it? Gy.
Yeah, man. Sorry. I don't comment don't
really come with this [ __ ] anymore.
Oh. Ah, I can't be off with it, man.
Same same projecting people. I don't
really bother with it anymore.
Oh, really? You know,
sorry, I'm a bit hung over from
yesterday, but you know, the only
maddest thing with this is that
you know when you're off with [ __ ]
Yeah. Even like a day or two and then you
and then you and then like you're
watching something else. Doesn't matter
what it what it is you're watching.
Yeah. And you look back on this place
and you actually think that they really are
[ __ ] spastics on here. Like I I know
I know you say it. Yeah.
When you're on here and that
when you're on here and that, but I mean
like you know when you actually you're
on like another community day, day and a
half, two days and you actually look
back, you actually realize how [ __ ]
it actually is.
You actually do realize it. It's crazy.
And I know I've had I've said things and
I've had to rephrase what I meant, you
know, and stuff.
Like when I said like, "Oh, if you if
you come on YouTube every day, how can
you have all of this money?" I should
rephrase that. I mean, you can have
money, have a life, and be on YouTube.
Yeah. An hour a day. I used to go gym
every day. I used to go go on YouTube,
but I think it's more the fact that they
spend all day every day on YouTube typing.
Do people with friends a life and money
do that? No, they don't. So, you know
that that's that's what I meant by that.
I mean, you can have a life and be on
YouTube an hour, 2 hours a day, an hour
and a half a day. Of course, you can.
Anyone could do it. after work, after
the gym. Like I said, I back in the Rick
Mace days, I used to literally go on
YouTube at night after I done everything.
It is a proper
Yeah. You know what?
I don't even need to say it, bro. To be honest,
what's happening? Yeah, always do. Oh,
Joe, nice to meet you, man. Uh, nice to
see you again. Yeah. Do you know I won
two football bets in a row, right?
So, not last week, the week before that.
I think God must have felt sorry for me,
bro. I put 80 and I got 280. And then
last week I put 80 and I got 230. I got
a 20 football bet for Saturday. I mean
that's that's good. And I put that money
aside and I went out yesterday cuz I
hadn't been out for like two weeks. I
don't really I'm getting too old now,
man. All this [ __ ] Obviously you
don't want to know how my day went
yesterday because that would just be repeating. I mean
same old England. Does that does that
say does that tell you everything you
need to know?
I mean I only bet on the football now
man and even though but the thing is bro
it was like well I lost 50 on Frankie so
it was 300 up but I mean that's not bad
300 pound extra for two weeks for this
happened two teams. It took took less
than one minute doing the the the um
it it it took less than one minute doing
the um sorry I'm hung over uh doing the
football bets. So I mean
uh yeah and I've got to I want to try
and but do you know what man I wish I
had [ __ ] both I wish I had both score
no draw man that would have been like
600 700 pound
but that's risky bro I mean and the
thing is with that right what's going to
annoy you with that is that if one draws
you're going to think oh [ __ ]
oh [ __ ] you're going to think what the
[ __ ] bro I wish I just done normal both
teams are scored so that's the [ __ ] thing with
Yeah, but I'm not going to do that, bro.
Am I? I can't afford to be losing three,
four, [ __ ] 100 pound. Even though I
could do it. I wouldn't do it, bro. I
wouldn't do it. But I was thinking of
doing that, like winning and just
sticking it all. But no point, bro. I'm
happy with the little wins.
But I was thinking of doing that
before I'd even won it. But I don't know
about that, bro. They're big. Yeah, I
don't I don't if I was to do that, I
would just go on roulette. If I was if I
if I was to g if I was to put any more
than £100 on the football, I would just
go on roulette or the slots because
there's no point sticking it when one
team's going to [ __ ] you up. It's
pointless. I'd rather just go roulette
with it. Me, if I was um I was to put
250 on something, I would just play
roulette. It has better odds, I think. Yeah,
>> because with football all you need is
one team. I don't know how I won two in a row.
But yeah, I went out yesterday, Joe, man. And
it's get it's it's getting worse. You're
not going to believe this if I told you
this [ __ ] man. I literally went to the the hairdressers.
No, it won't be a few grand. What from
what£300 on two teams? It won't be It
won't be a few grand if you done both
teams to score. No draw. It would be.
Yeah, but that's a risk.
No, it wouldn't. Not £300 on two. It's
like 900 pound.
No, it's not. It's like 900 pound. 950
maybe. It's not a few grand.
>> No, it's nowhere near a few a grand,
bro. It's not that much cuz it's only
two teams. I got lucky. Not last week,
the week before. 480 to get 285. That
was good odds. That was actually good
odds for both teams as well. And
obviously I just used the 200 to go out drinking. So
uh when I go out drinking, which I don't
even go out every week now, but yeah,
it's not a few grand, bro. What the
[ __ ] If you put 500 pound in, you
probably get like 1,500 back. But
obviously 500 a lot to lose on a [ __ ]
football bet. So that's where they have
you buy the balls. But I got this one
anyways. I put 20 pound on three teams
and 20 well 2120 on three teams because
I had 23120 so I just put £21 on then
the 20 p on three teams
and it returned 142 off £21 20. Yeah.
Anyways, I went I went to the barbers yesterday
straight from the barbers first
approached her on opposite the road. You
never guess what she said, Joe.
You never guess what she said. I done
actually six in a row yesterday sober
and it was literally the same [ __ ] Like
I was actually starting to panic. I
weren't going to get any. I got five
numbers but I went through hell and back
trying to get them numbers and back
again. It was hard. It it truly truly
truly is never going to change in this
country. I've accepted that now. I've
actually bro I told you this. This is
why I don't go out anymore.
I'm too old for this [ __ ] bro. You're
going to laugh at this. You're actually
going to laugh at this. Yeah.
But I've actually started watching like
WWE again. Like when when I used to be a
kid. I'm just watching like old old WWE
matches. Yeah. Just sit and chill. And
then the next week I'll go out. It's
that's the [ __ ] I'm doing now. Getting
into like WWE.
Well, I'm not getting into it because
there's no I don't like the new ones.
But that's how bad I actually get.
It's [ __ ] It's bad, bro. [ __ ] But
I got an escort yesterday, Joe. And
luckily, I didn't get any [ __ ] from
them. It was actually a right to be honest, though.
Yeah, you need to Well, you don't need
to leave the country. I mean, you can
keep using you can keep using escorts,
but that that's your only thing. Which
makes me laugh because these women,
right, they say that like
that they that that people only want
them for sex and people don't want
relationships. That's what they say. Oh,
people only want sex and no no.
But when you try to actually speak to
someone, literally the only thing you
get is I have a boyfriend. So, I mean,
[ __ ] You got a funny way of showing how
you only want relationships, don't you?
You know what I'm saying? And how to buy
new after shave and that. And it's like,
bro, I know. I I understand. I'm mature.
I I said this to Ant-Man as well
yesterday. I said it to a few people.
Like, I understand that this is the way
it is. Um, but you can't help fathom how
like [ __ ] up it is. I don't know how
like you can't see how mad it is. How
you can be like
[ __ ] decent looking. You can dress
good, you can smell good, and you can't
get even a conversation out of someone.
It's just it h you when you don't go out
Yeah. for two weeks, you don't forget.
It's just a reminder of how bad it is.
It's just a reminder of how bad it is. I
think that's the right word, reminder,
cuz you don't forget that it's it will
never change in this country. But I
mean, yeah, it was it was constant
yesterday, bro. It was constant
yesterday. So that that led me to my
point to Ant-Man is that what would
possibly give people the impression that
it would change?
What would actually what gives you the
impression that one day all of the [ __ ]
that's been happening for years is going
to stop happening? What would give you
that impression? And I don't think
anyone could answer that because it's
never going to happen.
So, and it was winding it was winding me
up yesterday. Don't forget [ __ ]
Ant-Man ended up in prison. Not me,
you know. So I mean he done [ __ ]
worse than what I did. So well acted
worse than how I acted cuz he ended up in prison.
He said anyone else if they were you
they would have killed someone by now or
ended up in prison. I think they would
have 100%. Yeah.
But yeah. So they don't So yeah, it's uh
Oh, we just walked into a pub with an
axe only and he went prison. See, I
wouldn't do that because I don't want to
go prison. Think of it. They're already
winning by denying you a love life,
denying you a sex life, and then you're
going to end up in prison as well.
That's the only reason I never um
done anything like that.
So cuz I'm just no point going prison,
you know? Could
you imagine he went through half of what
I went through? Jesus Christ. He would
have killed someone by now. Anyone would
have, to be fair, if anyone's been
through what I've been through, they
would have ended up in prison or killing someone 100%.
That's how you know that I'm not normal.
How like I've not done anything. I just
can't be asked with it, bro. A normal
person would have killed someone by now,
bro. I'm not even joking. I swear to
God. I promise you they would have, you know,
or like they would have left or gave up.
They would have just left by now or they
would have done something but still be
trying. I mean, that's the point.
But yeah, I don't know what gives people
the impression that it's going to change.
What do you mean I don't have the balls?
I just don't want to go to prison. Why
would I want to go to prison? But you
want me to do something that lands me up
in prison? Why am I going to do that, bro?
Why am I going to do something that ends
me in prison? That's ridiculous.
Um, and he said he was going to either
end up in prison. I said to him, "You'd
hate London." You know, I said to him,
"Yeah, that you would hate London
because London is the worst place for it."
like he he
London obviously I know England's
England it's the same everywhere but
London is the worst place for stuck up
people cuz I recorded my approaches
yesterday and I sent it to him I sent it
to like a few of my friends and London
you bro London's even worse than
anywhere else in terms of stuck up
people so bro you wouldn't like it here um
and I was saying to him that basically
if I lived anywhere else but London I
probably would be out every week Cuz
when I went to Birmingham, at least I
got some replies,
but there was this woman. Oh, she was
pissing me off yesterday. She's like, oh
yeah, she's not looking today. No, no,
no. So I was like, why are you in a
nightclub giving your number messaging
every single day? It's just like, it's
just like, how long are you going to
keep dealing with this [ __ ] bro?
You know, but no. And I told Jo, no, I
told Ant-Man this. The only reason why
you went before me is because
I thought that I weren't going to end up
like you having to leave my own country.
I never thought that I would not. Not
that I thought I was better than him,
but I just didn't think that I would
have ended up the same way as him cuz I
thought, oh, maybe he gives off like off
vibes or I don't know, maybe people deem
him in a in a in a different way that
they see me. Um, and I have more of a
chance than him, but clearly not. So yeah,
you never you're going to laugh at this.
Yeah. You know this um Indonesian guy,
right? Do you know he messaged me
yesterday? He's like, "Oh, um how how do
other people get in relationships?
How do other people get in
relationships?" And I was like, "I don't
know, bro. I mean, they might have got
lucky. I mean, it's not going to wait
for it. I mean, it's not going to change
our situation if we find out." That's
what that's my problem with Ant-Man.
It's like as you go on about these other
people, but the thing is is
that's not going to help the situation
that you're in that I'm in even if we
found out. But then anyways, that's what
the point. And then he then he turns
around and says to me, "Oh, mate, cuz I
want to duplicate them." I said,
"Brother, how the [ __ ] are you going to
duplicate them when you're scared to
talk to a woman? How are you going to
duplicate anything? You're you're scared
to speak to a [ __ ] woman. So, how are
you going to copy anyone? It doesn't
make any sense.
Um, what do you mean I take it
literally? Well, it shouldn't be a no.
That's the whole point is you're
good-looking. You look good. You smell
good. You shouldn't be getting a no.
That's That's the whole point is what
I'm saying. You should be given a chance.
In the 1980s, you would have been given
a chance. In the 1990s, you're not fat
and ugly. You don't look like Timmy Eldridge.
That's the bit that's hard to fathom. It
would be different if you was disabled
or ugly or fat or I don't [ __ ] know,
bro. Like, what? Nothing wrong with
that, but that's just the way society
sees people, I guess. Um, you shouldn't
be getting those. Just like you should
you wouldn't be saying no to people if
they [ __ ] come up to you looking
decent. That's the whole point. That's
the whole argument.
You know what I'm saying? Cuz the thing
is it contradicts everything that what
people are saying. People are telling
you, "Oh, it will change one day. Life
changes." No, no, no, no, no. Whatever
[ __ ] it is they're telling you. But when
you're going and speaking to people,
they're not interested. No one that
you're going to meet in this country is
going to be interested.
So, I mean, why do people keep saying
that it's going to change? How is it
You know what I'm saying? So,
it's strange. You're good-looking as
well. That's the maddest thing about it
is you're act like me. I'm I'm decent
looking. What I just say decent looking.
You look normal. Whatever the [ __ ] it
is, whatever that means. It's Do you not
understand how [ __ ] up it is
and how like none of it even makes sense?
So they so they waste your time and they
waste their time. What's the [ __ ] point?
But then they'll moan that they can't
find anyone that wants um that don't
want sex. They're going to moan that
they can't find anyone that wants a
relationship, yet every time somebody
tries to get in a rel tries to get a
relationship, tries to get to know them,
they pretend they've got a boyfriend. So
make it make sense. You know, you're
writing on the internet all of these
things that you want and what you don't
want. You said that a lot a lot of the
time these people given up. They've
given up on dating because they can't
find somebody that don't only
want sex. When somebody is coming to you,
you know. No, no, no. I look, bro,
listen. I look more than okay. And we're
not talking about my looks. I look
normal enough. I look normal enough. And
I'm not getting into a conversation
about my looks, bro. It's it's
pointless. It's boring. And at the end
of the day, your opinion on me, I don't
give a [ __ ] about your opinion on me,
bro. Like, at the end of the day, I'm
not scared to show the way I look. I'm
better looking than anybody on this community.
And I don't care if you think I'm ugly.
I don't care what you think. I look
better than anyone on this community.
And I'll prove it. So, there's no point
having there's no point you talking
about my looks when you're not going to
show your face. There's no point even
having an opinion on my looks if you're
not going to show your face.
This is pointless cuz you're never going
to show your face. Let's compare you and
let's compare me. Yeah.
Let me tell you this, bro. It's the same
thing with the whole weight thing.
A lot of you people on here. Yeah.
You'll be obese. really really really
really fat, right? Like really fat. A
lot of you are. And then you'll see that
I've gained a little bit of weight cuz I
don't know, I don't go to the gym
anymore. Whatever the [ __ ] reason is, right?
And then you're talking about my weight,
how I've gained a bit of weight. I'm
like, [ __ ] you're obese and you
should worry about losing your weight
and coming on talking about [ __ ]
mine. I was like, do you know how silly
that sounds? If I'm ever 1% of what you
people ever are, bro, I'm going straight
to the gym the same hour. That's how bad
it is. You know,
I said I shouldn't. I'm not comparing.
I'm just saying you're talking about the
way I look. Yeah, you're judging me. So,
I said, "Okay, show your face then.
Show me your face. If you can't show me
your face, then there's no point talking
about me. I'm not comparing myself to
you. I'm just saying like I'm I'm better
looking than any everyone on this
community. That's literally how it is.
Literally, it is how it is. You know
what I'm saying?
Uh, it does. It gets to me, bro. Nothing
you have ever said about my looks get to
me in a million years. I still show my
face. I will always show my face. Do you
think whatever you say about my looks,
you make me insecure? Are you crazy?
Bro, I'm better looking than anybody on
this community, it doesn't get to me.
I'm not the one that can't show my face.
You can't show your face.
Loads of other people can't show their
face. I'm not the one unable to show my
face. Nothing you ever say ever gets to
me. It literally does not get to me,
bro. Because we all know how you people look yourselves.
Bomb. Virgin boy. Jamie Thompson.
Brother. So I'm not wearing my hat to
cover up your messy hair. Bro, stop
being ridiculous. Everybody knows why I
wear a hat. I've explained it a million times. Okay.
Why don't you show your face wearing a hat then?
Ah, bro. Okay. Why don't you show your
face wearing a hat then if that's what
you think it is? Okay. Okay.
Why don't you show your [ __ ] face
wearing a hat and you're gone? Bye.
Well, I can I can show my face right now.
You don't get to me at all, bro. Oh, [ __ ]
Oh, you you what? You think only chabs
wear hats, bro. Come on and show your
face, man. You're talking about me.
You're talking about my looks. Let's see your face.
Let's see your face, bro.
Let's see your face.
I mean, what what have you got to hide?
Nothing you people ever say will ever
get to me, bro. Because [ __ ] 90% of
it is just projection to begin with. So
it's like what the [ __ ]
Yeah. You wouldn't wear tracksuits either.
Bro, I'm not the one that's scared to
show my face. That's the difference.
You know you. Nothing you say about my looks
will ever get to me. It will get to you
though because you can't show your face.
I can. So who is the one that's being
get out? If you can't even show your
face, then yeah, it says a lot. You
know, just like when you call people
skin, you're just you're just talking
about yourselves. That's why I laugh at
it, bro. I just sit there and laugh at
it. Like, it actually is funny. I was
saying before you joined. Yeah. When you
actually look back on it more and more, more more.
You You just laugh at it. It's something
to laugh at in a way, but I do feel
sorry for you as well. I actually do
feel sorry for you in a way. Yeah. All
right. So, bro, you're just saying that
to try and hide the fact that you're
ugly. Bomie used to do exactly the same
thing. Oh, I'm not showing my face. No,
no, no, no, no, no. But we all know,
bro, why you people don't show your
face. Cuz me, if I went on a community
full of people, right? And I was like,
"Oh, you look like this. You look like
that. You look like this. You look like
that." And then they turn around and
said, "Oh, really? Why don't you come
and show your face?" I'll be, "Okay."
See, that's the difference. I wouldn't
hide what I look like
cuz you, you know, you'd get more
respect if you can actually show your [ __ ] face.
You know, you do realize you'll get a
lot more respect for doing that when
you're when you're talking about other people.
It's like Bob, say the bomb went to the
gym, he grew a beard, he got a job, and
he come back on here. Nobody could tell
him anything. If he came on here and
started showing his face, what could
people say? I said the same thing to LT
the other day. What could what could
anyone actually say? Nothing. You know,
but you can't find someone's identity
just through their Facebook, bro. Come
on, man. Used to use the same excuse.
You know these excuses that you use,
you've been you've been using it for years.
And trust me, bro, none none of you
people annoy anyone.
You know, none of you people annoy
anyone at all. You just embarrass yourselves.
You really don't like psychologically
[ __ ] with anyone. You don't bother
anyone. Like I said, remember what I
told you about you wasting your life
all day, every day on someone. It says a
lot about your life. Remember what I
said that when I said that before? It's
like this whole nonslegs, right? when he
shows me his benefit money. Do you think
that bothers me in the slightest?
No. Why would it, bro? I mean, Joe, why
would it? That's not my 10 grand that I
asked for. That's not my 10 grand. I
want my 10 grand. I'm saying it like I
want actually 10 grand. But, so I know
that if nobody can show me it, then I'm
still the winner. I mean, you can make
excuses saying that I don't have a
thousand to show and all of these
things, but we all know the truth that
no one has shown me 10 grand.
You know what I'm saying? So, I mean,
that says it all. So, it doesn't it
doesn't annoy me. It's just in a way it's it's um
in a in a way it's something to laugh
at, but then at the same time is
actually embarrassing how you're
spending all your life trying to
convince people that you're not skin
when bro you [ __ ] are sking. Remember
I told you it takes [ __ ] three things.
Do you understand laddy?
when in poverty savings or no poverty.
How much how much money do I have right now?
How much money do I have right now?
Well, bro, if that's the case, then show
me my 10 grand then. 10 I mean, can you
show me it? There you go. You can't. So,
at the end of the day, bro, you don't
know exactly what I have. And I actually
get more than £1,000, bro. So,
you don't show your face on here cuz
you're all ugly.
Nah, I'm not back, man. I'm just bit
bored today. I need to message these
numbers that I got. Nah, I'm just You
don't show your faces on here cuz most
of you are just butt ugly and you don't
want anyone to have anything on you,
which I get, you know, cowardly, but I
get. I mean, look what happened to
[ __ ] Pat Mustard. But here's the
thing, Joe. You haven't showed me my 10 grand. So,
and do you remember what I told you
about the three things?
Do you remember Do you remember what I
told you the other day? Did you not
listen to what I said the other day, lad?
I literally said I could have £400 to my
name. Literally only400
and I'd still have a better life than
all of you.
Read into that what you will. And no, I
have a lot more than 400. But it's an
example. Do you understand what I'm
saying? I would still have a better life
than than all of you. It's like Ronald
Pump said, "People were jealous of me
cuz more money, better looking, better life."
Even if Right. This is this is what I
was trying to explain to you the other
day. Say you have more money than me. Yeah.
Say say like more money like say say for
example someone on here has more money
than me, right? and I get, let's just
say I got £800 a month, 750 a month,
someone has all this money, okay, but
I'm going to have the better life
because I'm better looking. I can go
out. I socialize. I used to travel a lot
as well, which I I I [ __ ] left London
[ __ ] two weeks ago, you know? So,
that's it's also about a life that you
live. I mean, there's no point having
all of that money and being ugly and
having no life. Do you understand? It's
not just one thing.
Do you understand what I'm saying, bro?
I've never lost a loved one
that was close to me. So, that's what
I'm that's what I'm trying to say. And I
have to rephrase, and I did rephrase
what I said cuz I know how silly it
sounds. Oh, if you had all of this
money, you wouldn't be on YouTube.
Um, you know what I'm saying? Like, uh,
yes. And um yes, there is proof and I
don't need to prove myself to you. Um
everyone knows I've been abroad. And
another thing is uh what you made me
lose what I was saying now. No, sorry.
It's not that you can't come on YouTube
every day if you've got all of this
money. That's actually not true. I used
to go to the gym. I used to go to the
gym. I used to come on YouTube every day
when I was at the gym when I was 2122.
Like think about it. I was 2122. Yeah.
And I used to go to the gym. I used to
come on YouTube for an hour a day. What
I mean is, I had to rephrase what I
meant. You people would not spend all
day every day on YouTube.
All day every day on YouTube doing what
you do if you had all of this money in
this life. That's that's the whole point
I'm trying to make. I mean, yeah, you
can come on YouTube, but it's what you
actually do. Like everyone's seen what
you people do and it just points to a
disturbed individual with no life.
That's all it points to, bro. And I was,
bro, even back when I was 21, I was
broke as [ __ ] and I still had a better
life than all these
better looking, better body, me Izzy, I
had [ __ ] all, bro. You know, I have a
lot more than I [ __ ] do that now than
I do then.
You know what I'm saying? And I and I
still had a better life because it's not
just money, it's different things. Do you understand?
Like I've never been jealous of anyone
in my life, but there is people that I
um envy, you know, and look up to
because they've got a good life,
you know, and it's not and it's not just
about money. It's also about how you
live your life. Uh it's hard to explain
what I mean, but I know what I mean.
It's like all of this [ __ ] whole
nonslegs thing. I laugh at it, bro. Just
think of it. You're saying that you've
he tried telling me before he had 100
grand. I said, "Okay, you've got all of
this money." Okay, but you got no bed.
You've not been abroad cuz he didn't he
hadn't been abroad at the time. He has
no bed. He's never been abroad at the
time. He's barely been anywhere. But you
claim you've got all of this money.
See how nothing is making sense here?
You understand? So
it's like you need to have money, live
the life, and
be decent looking. It's it's different
things. It's different things, you know. But yeah. Yeah.
In fact, you're saying that I'm living
in poverty, right? Let's just say I'm
living in poverty, Joe.
But I went out yesterday. I socialized.
I got some numbers.
I [ __ ] I can go out when I want. I'm
still I'm better off than a lot of other
people and I have a life. I'm better off
than most people are here. But I'm but
I'm living in poverty. So you claim. So
let's just say that we agree with that, right?
You know, let's just say that we we I
agree with you. Yeah. Okay. So I'm
living in poverty. So then shouldn't you
people have shouldn't you people be
having a better life than me then? Okay.
Well then that's well I mean if somebody
in well that why is somebody in poverty
living a better life than you then?
Think about it. Where did I go to two
weeks? I went to Birmingham. I went on
the piss. I went on the piss a couple of
times last month. I went on the piss
yesterday. Are you I I [ __ ] in school
yesterday. Well I got blowj say. Why is
a somebody in poverty living a better
life than you? You know, apparently I'm
living in poverty. Okay, so I'm living
in poverty. So why is somebody living in
poverty have a is having a better life than you?
That must mean you're really damn bad
then, isn't it? That's what I'm saying. So
it's it it is it is strange, bro. Like
where did all of this money thing come
from? Like people asking to show money you know.
Yeah, Monty's never going to do the same for me
to be honest, but no one will ever do
the same for me. So, [ __ ] man.
You know, um,
so yeah, that's what it is basically.
Oh, [ __ ] This is going to die, wasn't it?
>> Yeah. So, it's kind of like where did
all of this money thing come from? show
money. I mean, I used to just show money
just to wind people up. And then I
realized And then I realized, right,
that when you show these people money,
they have nothing to show you. And the
reason that they bring money up is cuz
they're skin themselves. And bro, it's
not a hard thing to do. All you got to
do is show 10 grand. Why is no one
showing 10 grand? You know, and then you
said, "Oh, why don't you have the money
to show now?" Um because I gave you
three months to show me 10 grand. None
of you wanted to show me 10 grand. So
what I done with that money was I bought
clothes. I went out on the piss, which
is still money.
I still have things to show for that
money. So you've still been shown the money, you know?
So that's it.
Um so why can't you show me 10 grand?
That's the whole point. You know what I mean?
So, yeah, man. Yeah.
But yeah, back to the women thing.
Anyways, it is it is [ __ ] up.
Yeah, I went out yesterday, bro. Uh,
man, I met a homeless guy actually from
Newcastle. Well, I didn't meet him. I
was at the cash point and I said, "Oh,
you from Newcastle and shit." And he
said, "Yeah, I know the accent of Milo
in it." So, yeah, he went homeless down
here. I said, "Good luck to you, matey.
Good luck to you." That's what I said. But, um, yeah.
Yeah, man. I got a fresh trim yesterday, bro. Fresh.
>> I need to put my t-shirt on.
>> Oh, actually, I don't want to put that
t-shirt on, man.
>> No, it was white.
Oh, [ __ ] I I like that t-shirt. [ __ ] it.
So, yeah, man.
Oh, [ __ ] Hopefully that's it.
>> If it goes then my phone's dead. But
yeah, I mean. Yeah, man.
The dating game is getting harder here,
Cory. Man, I I done five approaches
yesterday. I recorded all of them.
And I have a boyfriend. I mean, [ __ ]
God can't even get a conversation out somewhere nowadays.
What would give you the impression that
it's ever going to change? I mean, I
come out with that intelligent question. Uh,
I come out with that yesterday, bro. Cuz
I just asked a couple of people on
Instagram, what what would give you the
impression that one day it's going to change?
And I don't think anyone could answer
that because what would give them what
actually would give them the impression,
you know? It's just too many stuck up
people here. There's too many stuck up people.
It's It's impossible, bro.
I think that person on Reddit was right.
Too many stuck up [ __ ] in your
country. I think literally that is what it is.
I recorded the approaches as well.
Yeah, maybe two years ago, bro. But now
you can't even get a conversation out of
someone unless they tell you to have a
boyfriend. That's the only thing you can get.
Nah, you won't be all right, bro. Not
now. 2 years ago, you would have been
all right, but not now. Now it's just
it's gotten worse.
But what makes me laugh is how people
make it seem like so easy.
not not make it seem like they they they
well they make it seem so easy with the
way that they talk about it like oh yeah
you just jump on a dating app. It's like
no bro it's not as easy as that. Um
and I wouldn't mind if it's like you're
actually trying to only have sex with
these people and they're saying no I
don't want to have sex I want a
relationship but there you couldn't even
get a friendship with a woman. You know
how you go out, right, and you um like
you make new friends when you drink and
you like I've made lot so many new
friends going out contacts all around
the country. You know how you do that
normally. You couldn't make friends with
a woman. Even if you wanted to be
friends with someone
um like say you generally want cuz I
guess there is some people out there
that want you wouldn't even be able to get that.
They're too stuck up
like there's there's nothing you can
even get. Like even if you generally
wanted a relationship and you didn't
care about sex, you won't even be able
to get that. It's like Tik Tok. Yeah. Has been
It's like they've got Tik Tok in their body.
It's like Tik Tok has has has taken over their mind.
It's like Tik Tok has um
how do I say it? It's like, you know,
it's like someone's it's like someone's
unscrewed their back and put Tik Tok
batteries in it.
You know what I'm saying? And now they
they've they put Tic Tac they put Tik
Tok batteries in it.
Yeah. You won't you won't you won't get
laid in this country, bro. Unless you um
you get uh
unless you meet somebody from South
America or something.
South America's good as well. South America, Asia,
but anywhere the West. Ah, good luck to
you, mate. Good [ __ ] luck to you.
It's all I'm saying. Yeah.
Yeah, it's like they they they they put
Tik Tok batteries in them. You can see
the Westinity in their eyes, Joe. It's
like what Antman said. You can see the
Westinity in their eyes. It's true
though, isn't it?
[ __ ] me, man.
>> Yeah, man.
It is strange though because like I
said, they go on about how they want
relationships and they don't want
somebody that just wants sex. Well, if
you're rejecting most of the people that
are approaching you, how are you going
to find a relationship?
Because by the time you're in your 30s,
you're going to meet people that only want sex.
You know what I'm saying? Like, that's
all the people you're going to come
across very soon. and then you're going
to moan and winge about it. I mean, if
you want to if you want to stay single
your whole life, then yeah, you do you,
man. But don't then start moaning in
your 30s how, oh, I'm I'm sad everyone
only wants sex cuz you had your chance
and you [ __ ] blew it. So, yeah,
they should. It's It's I'm surprised
they don't learn from each other. You
know what I mean, Cory? like, "Oh [ __ ]
this person got to their 30s and in
their 80s and now they don't have many
options. Ah, I don't want to end up like
that person, so let me give someone a
chance." It's like, it's stupid really
that they don't learn from each other,
learn from each other's mistakes, you know,
cuz it is going to come to an end. They
are going to age a lot quicker and then
they're going to have less options and
and they don't learn from each other.
It's it's crazy.
You would have thought they would have
learned from each other. They don't.
It's strange, bro. It is. It is strange, man.
It is bad, bro. It is bad.
I'm just in my little nesticles.
[ __ ] hung over as [ __ ] Yeah, I was
drinking white rum yesterday cuz I
figured I'm not going to go out again
until Saturday. But yeah, man.
I don't know. I do not understand.
You know, hey, the thing is, Cory, you
know, when when you're not on here
anymore, like a day, two days, 3 days, 3
weeks, is what I was saying before you
joined, you actually realize how disabled
this community actually is.
You said you was gone for 9 months. I
bet there'd be one day where you'd be in
the gym and you'd think, "Ra, this is actually
really [ __ ] This is actually a
disabled community." I I bet there's
been times, bro, is it? Cuz there had
been times in my mind like I'd be
thinking, bro, I watched I was like,
bro, that community really is full of
[ __ ] retards, isn't it?
Yeah. You actually realize, bro, how
actual how none of it makes any sense at
all. Like, they come they come on here
every day, bro. I I should have laughed
because I actually feel sorry for them.
They come on here every day calling
people skin, right?
And then you show money, then they can't
show you anything. Yet they have all of
this money, yet they waste all their
life on YouTube all day, every day
hating. But they've got such a better
life. If they've got all of this money,
why they got a better life than you? Why
don't they get a better life than you?
Show them who's boss. But they can't.
It's It's like I I keep saying I could
have £400 to my name and I would have a
better life than all of these people. Um
so I mean what's money if you're not
going to do anything with money?
Stupid is it?
Like I said I used to be skint when I
was 21 22 and I still had a better life
than all of them and I used to do my
balls in constantly.
I used to get like £700 a month, bro.
And I still had a better life somehow.
Then all of these people that claim they
have all of this money. It's ridiculous.
What the [ __ ] is money, bro? If you're
not going to actually do anything with
it, it doesn't even make sense.
And yeah, like I said, I've shown money
before when I used to win in a casino
cuz I had because I had the money in the
c I had the money there because they
paid in cash, which is how I realized
that none of these people show you
anything. You understand?
Think of it. Why do they need me to show
money? They've got all this money,
right? Can't they see their own money?
You know what I mean?
You know what I'm saying, bro? [ __ ]
how the [ __ ] are they like how they um
why would they want you to show money
when they they money to see? You know,
there's little things like that to own
them, bro. They've got all this money.
Why do they want to see yours? They're
not insecure, are they?
So, yeah, it's funny, bro. Run away. Yeah, man. Literally, man.
And apparently I'm living in poverty.
What kind of content would you like to see?
Oh, do you know what I need to? I need
to go swimming, bro. Oh.
Yeah, Peter Bell is very hung over today. Cory.
Oh, I'm so [ __ ] man. That white ram,
it kills you, man. I'm telling you.
Like I said, I'm not going to go out now
till Saturday. So, I was all right doing
that. See, I can't do two days in a row.
I can't do two days in a row. If I drink
rum, I can't do two days.
So, if I do two days, I have to stick to
beer. You see, say me Yeah, man.
I do remember Cory what Ant-Man said. It
will never change.
It will never change, bro.
He said, "How is it going to change? It
will never change.
I'm dead, bro.
It will never how it will never change."
I'm not laughing at that, but I'm just
laughing at like kind of the way he said
it. I had a breakfast. I just feel sick, man.
It's [ __ ] a hangover. Let me message
these numbers anyways. [ __ ]
No, I'm going to wait a little bit so I
can ask some of them how their day is
going because not all of them I met when
they were drunk. So, do do you reckon
Antman was right then, Cory? That it
will never change.
Yeah. Even the Ukrainian ones are saying
they've got boyfriends now. Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It gets worse, bro. It gets worse and
worse and worse. Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Poke in hell. Yeah, man.
Oh, I'm going to go sleep, bro. Oh, man. [ __ ]
It will never change.
and they just aren't interested in this country.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, man.
They only come out with the most funniest sayings.
He comes out with the most funniest
saying only man.
[ __ ] hell, man.
a shower, you know, bro.
I hate this [ __ ] man.
That's the thing I hate is a [ __ ]
hangover, man. It's [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] happy hour, man.
It's [ __ ] a happy hour.
Well, I'll be back later, maybe.
Then I'm gone for another week, two weeks.