Told you I'd be back.
Yeah, there's something else. Yeah, man.
I'm just chilling playing some [ __ ] GTA, bro.
I got this football. Yeah.
Yeah, man. It was dead yesterday. I
still ain't got any replies back from
these [ __ ] numbers.
It's [ __ ] impossible, bro. It I'm
going out tomorrow, but that's just cuz um
I've had my haircut in it, so [ __ ] it. I
guess I'm street approach sober. I
probably be me done for like
3 weeks to a month.
Probably not. I can't going out. Oh,
Nicolo, I was looking for that change
yesterday, bro. Oh, [ __ ] me. I I on six
approaches. Yeah. Sober. Oh, five sober.
Well, six sober. I recorded six. Uh,
five. I recorded them, bro. As you can
tell, I'm still hung over. Same [ __ ] I
have a boyfriend. I have a boyfriend. I
thought, "Fuck this, mate."
You know, it's a It's like they've got
Tik Tok batteries.
But I'm going out tomorrow cuz I've had
my hair done. So, that would be me done
for like three weeks a month.
Yeah. Not money or anything. I just
can't be [ __ ] with it, bro. like
generally can't. It's boring as [ __ ]
Five numbers, no reply back as yet.
Yeah, it will never change. Like what
Antman says. You know what he says? No,
none of them. You know what Antman says?
He says is he says that um you keep
showing me these approaches.
He's like he's like um
what did he say? He's like, "Um, why do
you keep showing me it's just the same
[ __ ] from the start? Start to finish.
It's just different characters."
He said, "They're just different
characters. Same finish, same start."
You know, just He said it's just the
same old [ __ ]
It is bad. Yeah, it is bad. It is bad.
Very bad, man.
Nah, you're not. Well, I done sober approaches yesterday.
I done a lot sober yesterday and it was
I got a boyfriend non-stop.
Nah, it's not as easy as that anymore.
Two years ago it would be
two years ago it would be. Now you got
no chance something has changed in them
last two years. But I'm telling you
something in them last two years have changed.
And the reason you can't keep doing them
sober after like the fifth one is
because it starts affecting your mental health.
That's why it's hard to keep doing them sober.
You get what I mean, bro? I'm out
tomorrow anyway. So
then that's me for like 3 weeks to a month.
3 weeks a month probably. Probably man.
Obviously, I'm not going to pay that
money to get a haircut and only go out
one day a week, am I? That would be foolish.
Yeah, I went to an escort at the end of
the night. It was actually good to be
honest. [ __ ] stop my [ __ ] dick.
I just put 20 on three teams returns 140.
I need to try and get um another
delivery job as well, bro, on Monday,
bro. I need to start making some money.
I don't want to end up like skin virgin.
You know what I'm saying, bro? [ __ ] it.
I want to end up like that. I need to
start making some [ __ ] money, bro. Serious.
Have you been to
Nah, never been there. I've never heard
of that. What the [ __ ] is that, bro?
Um, but I did do them so yesterday, bro.
I done one like right outside the
barbers when I got my haircut. Same old
Wait, what am I going to wear tomorrow? Hold on.
It's hard, bro.
And I'm not going to have time to do it now anyways.
No, I've never heard of that.
Just looking for that change, you know.
And man says it's just the same characters. Yeah. Yeah,
isn't it? Oh,
I [ __ ] my hell, bro.
It's actually [ __ ] me up, you know,
bro. The actual It's actually [ __ ] me
up. You know, this is why I don't drink, Mom. No,
it will never change.
It will never change.
Like an man said, it will never change.
It's not changed in 3 and 1/2 years. So,
it's not going to change now.
It will never change.
How is it going to change?
That man teaching English in his
Lancashier accent. Lesson, I'm going to
have to order some more food, bro. I'm [ __ ] starving.
This is why I don't drink rumb. It [ __ ]
you up. But because I weren't going out today um
today, obviously I could drink it
yesterday cuz I can't do it two times in
a row. So obviously I'm going out tomorrow. But
that's what I mean, bro.
It's hard to um
It's why I don't drink rum, bro. This
makes you tired and hungry and [ __ ]
man. Yeah, mine was good as well. I'm
going to order a McDonald's. Yeah,
I'm trying to find a way where I can get
loads of money, Nicolola, so I never
have to work again in my life.
I'm going to have to try and win a big
football accumulator or something.
I don't know, bro. I want to do this.
Figure something out.
But once I start when I start uh thingy
again, working again, bro, there's not
going to be going out every week like
Antman. I'm just going to go. I'm just
going to get money and go. There's not
going to be like going out every week. I
don't I still asked them, why did you do that? Like
why did you go out every week before
going to Thailand?
Why why not just stay for a month and
just [ __ ] off and teach English? What
was the whole point of going out every
week? I went I didn't go out yesterday
was the last time was the first time in two weeks. Um
so I mean and I'm not going to go out
for like a month after tomorrow cuz I
can't be bothered, bro.
It's [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] man. But yeah.
Well, I told him about the one their
eyes, but he he come up with the
Westinity. Yeah. I I I I was the one that said
gave her their looks, bro. Yeah. It's
like Yeah. And I met an Australian
yesterday as well. We was talking in the
park, Nicolo. And then she hit me with
the old I've got a boyfriend. I was
like, "Oh, no. Not that [ __ ] again."
Yeah, it will never change, bro. It will never change.
Maybe I might become like a Tik Tocker or something.
Bro, you know that Indonesian guy, he
said, "Oh, do you know what he said?
You're going to laugh at this." He was
like, "Oh, how do other people get in
relationships?" I was like, "To be
honest with you, I'm not sure." And to
be honest with you, it's not going to
change our situation. So it's the point.
It's a waste of time wondering and
figuring it out because it's not going
to change our situation.
So it's no point wondering. There's no point.
A a wise man once said, this Birmingham
guy said to this guy on the train,
um, don't dwell on things that you can't change.
That's what he said. He said, "Don't
don't dwell on things that that you
can't change." I think that's a that's
that's a good quote. He was talking to
somebody else, but we was all having a
conversation, which I think is the
truth, cuz what what's what's the point
in trying to find out? And then he then
he said, Nicolo, that he he would
duplicate them. I said, "You will
duplicate them? How can you duplicate
when you're scared to approach?
You're scared to even talk to a woman.
How How are you going to duplicate it? The [ __ ]
It's How How are you going to duplicate
it when you can't even approach one?
That doesn't even make sense.
Yeah, I got five numbers. I got a Scottish number. Uh
yeah, I got a Scottish number, bro. Got
a Scottish one.
I got a Brazilian one as well, but she's
back in Brazil now. Yeah, long story.
That one in Birmingham was being a [ __ ]
Nicolo, as well. Yeah, the one in
Birmingham was being a [ __ ] Yeah,
he's being a [ __ ]
Nah, even being good-looking is not enough.
I'm decent looking. I think I was
looking snack yesterday. Nice clothes,
Reese's clothes, nice trainers, nice
haircut, nice beard, smelling good, and
I can't even get anything but I've got a boyfriend.
Yeah, I mean, I got five numbers, but it
was very, very hard to get, bro. Like,
it was very hard to get.
Like, it weren't Oh, yeah. You just went
out and you got five numbers. It was
[ __ ] hard. At one point, I didn't
even think I was even going to get one number.
You can't stop. You can't stop getting
that I've got a boyfriend [ __ ] It's
[ __ ] annoying, bro.
Do you remember when we was having that
um conversation? Yeah. About how?
Let me do it for like two weeks. Nah. No
way you can do that. Two weeks. But by
the fifth one, by the fifth one. Yeah.
You'll just get depressed
and you won't be able to fathom how
[ __ ] up it is. You're not going to do
it two weeks straight, bro.
Cuz um it's not going to happen, lad.
It doesn't work. It doesn't work. That
if they say they've got a boyfriend,
right, then they're not going to give
you their number. And if they do give
you their number, they're just going to
It's not going to work.
Trust me, bro. It's you're wasting your time.
Cuz even if you get a number, they're
just going to not beat you.
So, it's just it's a waste of time, bro.
That that one in Birmingham was like,
"Oh, I'm not looking today." I said,
"Well, why are you in a club? Why are
you giving your number? Why are you responding?"
Like, they complain like we was talking
about earlier that they complain that
there's the the men um they only want
sex. They say that, "Oh, men only want
sex. Men only want sex." But yeah, I'm
sure there's genuine people that come
into their life like
myself who either wants a friendship or
a relationship and then all you get is
I've got a boyfriend which then puts
them in a uh position when they're in
their 30s then everyone will just want
them for sex. So they bring it on
themselves really like you shouldn't
feel sorry for them and they don't learn
from each other either. A smart person
would be like, "Oh [ __ ] this person was
picky and they were a [ __ ] all through
their 20s and now they're 30 and now
nobody wants them and now the only
people that get with them are people
that just want sex." It's not like they
learn from each other. They make the same mistakes.
Um, and then when they are that age,
then only people want them for sex.
So I was having an argument with this
[ __ ] [ __ ] on Reddit. Yeah, she lives
in New Zealand. She's English. She's
She's coming back to London. I said,
"Listen, shut the [ __ ] up, you stupid
westernized cunt." And I said, "If
you're ever in London, let me know.
Bring any man you want as well. Let's
see how big you are. Let's see what you
can say to my face. And you can bring
any man you want. I'm not bothered."
Just shut him out. But yeah, like that's
what I don't understand. That's that
that's the thing I don't understand.
You know, it's weird. Anyone would think
that you look like Timmy Aldridge.
Jesus Christ. I can understand if you
look like Timmy Eldridge. Then it
wouldn't piss me off. If I didn't look
like If I look like Timmy Eldridge. Yeah.
Then I don't I'd understand why this is happening, you know.
Uh then I Oh, well, I know now. I'm
still going to do it anyways.
Yeah. It's not like you look like
[ __ ] Timmy Aldridge or anything. You
know what I mean?
That's that's the thing that annoys me.
That's the thing that pisses me off about it.
You know what I mean?
That's the [ __ ] that pisses me off, you know? Yeah.
I met a homeless guy on the street
yesterday. Nicholas from Newcastle. Oh,
it was bringing back memories, man.
But yeah, none of them reply back.
Well, we'll be getting some more
tomorrow anyways. And then that's me
done, bro, for a long time.
It's a madness, isn't it?
Looking for that change.
Yeah. Do you remember when Laney said that, Nicola? that?
Do you remember Virgin Boy trying to
cover up his real his real sexuality?
Cheryl Cole's fit. Cheryl, do you know
what? I might do a video on that. [ __ ]
it. One of those. If you don't find
Cheryl, mate, you was put into care at a
very young age.
You was put into care at a very young
age because of it.
You know, you had no mother figure.
You know, your mom starved you starved
you almost to death. You know,
I think about it sometimes when my mommy
makes me um a lamb shank. Oh, I I I
found one of USA Izzy's friends on
Instagram. I said, "You should really
know what your friends really like."
I I didn't do it intentionally. Like, I
just come across her cuz I typed her
name. I was, "Oh, I just messaged her
saying, "Oh, do you know what your friend's like?"
He's an able [ __ ] offenders. Yeah, bro.
I just like the odd time. Very very
rarely if I come across someone and I'll
just tell them, but I don't go out of my
way to [ __ ] with her.
[ __ ] it off.
Do you know what your friends like?
Who the [ __ ] is this guy? Oh,
this guy just messaging me. Says, "Sorry
for my delay in response." That's all right, mate.
You don't need to be sorry.
Yeah. So, that's how it is, Nicolo.
basically. I mean, yeah, it's
you're [ __ ] I mean, you're not damned
if you do that. I mean, nothing's ever
going to work in this country. But,
I mean, back when you thought there was
hope. It's like you either give up or
you try and you just become depressed
from trying. So, there's nothing you
really can do.
Have some breakfast early as well. This
is why I need to I'm not drinking rum
again. I'm not drinking rum tomorrow, bro. [ __ ] that.
I am not drinking [ __ ] rum, bro. Ever again.
Hungry, tired, hungry, tired, [ __ ]
headaches. I have to take [ __ ] cocoon
more, bro. But you can't resist the
happy hour, Nicolo.
You can't resist the happy hour, you
know? You don't think of the next day.
That would have been three times I ate
out. [ __ ] hell, man.
I had a kebab earlier. You just eat and
eat and eat and eat and eat. No, not
again. It's gone now. But you just get
so hungry when you drink rum.
Beer's all right. Like you don't I don't
get the hangovers with beer. I just get
a bit tired. And beers are fine, but any
kind of beer is fine. even mix a beer.
As soon as you get on them spirits,
as soon as you get on them spirits,
um, you're [ __ ] You know what I mean?
It does. Horrible, bro.
Horrible. You can feel it in your eyes as well.
But these um Yeah, I think when you go
out and you try again, you're just
reminded what your life is always going
to be here. I have a boyfriend. and I Um, yeah.
Or if you go to Thailand or you keep use
or you just use escorts.
I mean, yeah, it might not be the same,
but it is No, they're not even that sexy in London.
London. I I I actually went out cuz I
was bored yesterday, bro.
I don't think anything's ever going to
change. I was just bored.
I'm going to get a chicken back. Grievy.
Yeah. Do you know what I've been doing?
I've just been watching WWE. Nicolo. I
didn't go out for two week two weeks. I
was just watching like WWE and [ __ ]
reminded me of being a kid all over again. Yeah, man.
Just watching WWE get up. The old ones,
not the new ones. I don't like new ones,
but I was watching like old Royal
Rumbles and [ __ ]
Yeah, it's madness.
You know, this escort said to me,
I said, "Did you like sucking my dick?"
at. She said, "Hi, love."
I said, "Let me know when you're back in
London." And she said, "Yes, sure." I
said, "Did you enjoy as well?" She said,
"Of course, you're so hot. Next time
we'll spend more."
She let me come in her mouth, which is good.
I don't care if they don't swallow it,
but who the [ __ ] wants a [ __ ] if you
can't finish in someone's mouth? The
[ __ ] whole point of a [ __ ]
It ain't that [ __ ] bad, [ __ ] What the [ __ ]
It's just [ __ ] liquidy.
It's not that [ __ ] bad. Jesus Christ.
Yeah, they're my favorite. Them two are
my favorite, bro.
Yeah, probably does.
You're sucking my balls as well.
Yeah, Stone C. Yeah, they're my
favorite, bro. Them two are my favorite.
I like um
I like I like them, bro.
I like Rey Mysterio as well.
They're all good. Not all them, but you know
with them too. Yeah, definitely. Definitely.
So yeah, you're you're best off just
getting an escort.
I'm sure you could get an escort to like
have a baby with you if you saw her
enough times and looked your best. I you
could either go down the escort route or
[ __ ] Asia or South America cuz it
ain't ever going to change. It's like
Ant-Man said, Nikolai, I've told you
many times before, the only the only
place you're not going to get that is Asia.
The only place you're not going to get
I've got a boyfriend Phil is Asia. I was
dead, bro. Just that sentence just makes me laugh.
It's just the same [ __ ] different characters.
Oh, [ __ ] sake, bro.
He said that's the only place you're not
going to get it. And I've lost a lot of
confidence and a lot of energy as well,
bro. I'm getting old.
I'm [ __ ] retiring from [ __ ] this approaching [ __ ]
Greasy, I'm I'm retiring.
The only place you're not going to get
that is Asia.
That's funny as [ __ ] right? Let me look
on the McDonald's menu.
One second, Grezy. Oh, yeah.
There's a lot of um there's a lot of
ignorers as well. Nikolai,
what should I get? Greavvesy.
I don't want a nuggets again. I don't think
I'm just going to get a Big Mac meal. I think. All right.
Yeah. Let's get a Big Mac meal. Chicken mac.
This is why you don't drink rum people.
Every everything I told people I [ __ ]
meant, bro. It [ __ ] [ __ ] you up,
What the [ __ ]
Virgin boy could handle run.
Ah, V. Virgin boy. Virgin boy could
never handle best.
Not virgin boy. Virgin boy. [ __ ]
Virgin can't swim.
You agreed with me in it though,
Grievousy, when I told you that they can
only pick on the kids because as soon as
somebody becomes an adult, they don't
want to know. They can only pick on kids.
They can only pick on kids, but they
can't pick on actual adults. Have you
noticed that while I was telling you
before? And it's not like they were also
a kid. They were basically [ __ ] adults.
And then to think now that the only
thing the only way they can kind of win
is by crying to the boys in blue. How
[ __ ] up is that?
Just think about that for a second. They
start a load of [ __ ] on YouTube, then
when it all gets tough,
they run to the boys in blue.
Is that not mad to you?
Always the boys in blue.
>> I used to say, "I don't give a [ __ ]
what's socially acceptable, you little [ __ ] virgin."
He used to say, "That's not socially
acceptable." I said, "I don't give a
[ __ ] what you think is socially
acceptable or not, you [ __ ] lanky virgin cunt."
You got starved by his [ __ ] mom.
That's what I used to say. You [ __ ]
[ __ ] Now [ __ ] up and suck your dad's dick.
And you know that I used to win all of
these arguments, isn't it, Nick? I'm not
the one I'm not the one running to old Bill.
You know, no, I ain't getting confused,
bro. I just got the food. [ __ ] them. No. Yeah, man.
But hopefully they ain't got them Tik
Tok batteries in tomorrow. [ __ ]
Yeah, hopefully they don't. No.
Oh, my eyes greasy. My [ __ ] eyes, bro.
I'm going to say to my mom, make sure I
never drink rum again.
Just remind me. Yeah. Yes.
Yeah, Virgin Boy does it as well. It's
like that police show. He said that he's
going to call me for a voluntary
interview. He's not called me yet. If he
calls me, I'm going to tell him to [ __ ]
off. I said, "Listen here, dickhead."
Yeah. Whenever I go to report stuff, you
[ __ ] tell me, "Oh, I need to report
it to [ __ ] face." Because that's what
the solicitor was telling me to do. Oh,
report it to Facebook or report it to
this, report it to that. I'm going to
say, "Listen, why don't you take some of
your own advice and piss off? I ain't
going." If he when he call if and when
he calls, that's what I'm actually going
to say, Jim. I'm going to tell him to [ __ ] off.
Um, take some of your own advice. Have
you forgot what you said to me?
Yeah. They like to play two sides of a
coin, these pigs.
Like, that's literally what they told me
about eight times. And the only reason I
done it is because of like the solicitor
um that they told me that I need to do
it, you know, for like the courts and
[ __ ] So like they had no excuses and
that's what they kept telling me. So I
don't know what it's over. I don't know
if it's the USA Izzy thing or
um they said something about Instagram,
but it's not serious. I don't know.
Maybe it's the USA Izzy thing. I don't
know, bro. I don't know what the [ __ ] it
is, but he never called it anyways. I'll
turn the [ __ ] off. Simple.
You can't you can't play two sides of a coin, matey.
You want to work like that, bro. I mean,
yeah, women are definitely cowards, man.
That USA is the biggest coward. Played
with fire and got burnt.
I told all her little mates about her.
Yeah. I told all her little mates
about the [ __ ] that she is. Yeah. [ __ ] bastard.
[ __ ] hell, man. I think of you when
I'm out, you know, Nicolo. Like when
when you cop my little sayings. It's
funny, isn't it?
So why did my mama leave me? Nicolo, you
need to say something funny so I can laugh.
you to Instagram. That's another thing
these women do. They actually report you to Instagram. Yeah.
Yeah. I was looking up that Andre the
Giant. I didn't know he died in 1993. I
wasn't even born in 1993. What the [ __ ]
That's like [ __ ] WWF. I used to play
uh Legend of Wrestlemania.
But 1993, I was even born in 1993.
That's madness, bro.
You know that guy, he was an actual he
was an actual giant.
Like he was he was he was an actual
giant. That [ __ ]
like bro his hands was the size of
obviously they couldn't treat [ __ ] like
that them days in it. So,
obviously it wasn't a probably wasn't
recognized back then. You know what I mean?
But um yeah, he was [ __ ] he
know I don't understand with these
people. Yeah. They say, "Oh, I don't
want to watch WWE cuz it's fake and no no,"
but [ __ ] that they watch is fake. like
Friends, comedy shows. I mean, that's
fake. So, I mean, it's no, it's no
different really. It's Do you not
understand what WWE stands for? What's it called?
Think the E is entertainment. I think
it's Worldwide Entertainment or
something. But the point is the E is entertainment
just like all the other things that are fake
like shows and [ __ ] So it's no it's not
really it's no no different really
just don't like fake things at all you know
but I'll be out looking for that change.
I'll be looking for that change tomorrow, Grezy. Uh,
you want me to dress up as Chucky and do
the approaches, don't you, Grezy? Oh, my
Chucky caps are on the way, Nicolo. I
ordered them 4 days ago. The Chucky
caps, they should be here in like maybe
seven days. I've ordered them from China. So, yeah.
I know like a lot of people like boxing,
but I don't like boxing, man.
My dad like boxing, but I don't like boxing.
I don't like it, bro. Over. Yeah, cuz
football's [ __ ] I hate football. Yeah.
Let me ask you a serious question. Yeah.
clowns of Chelsea. Do you actually think I'm gay?
Let's Let's have a vote on it. Except
Grievy cuz Grievy already answers. Does
any Do I give off any impression that
I'm gay? Like straight gay, not bisexual
gay? Cuz I don't think I [ __ ] do. And
I certainly [ __ ] ain't.
Virgin boy said that if I don't find
shovel car attractive, I'm gay. I know
my sexuality. I'm I'm perfectly straight, mate. Perfectly straight.
I'm just not a [ __ ]
I'm just I'm just not a copycat.
You know what I'm saying? I'm not a copycat.
[ __ ] did what? Show signs that he was gay.
By the Oh, that receipt by the way,
Nicolo is Monty's haircut. He paid £52
today for his haircut.
I think she's [ __ ] ugly. And I've had
more women than him.
Who says that you're gay if you don't
like Sher Cole? Where have I heard that
one before? Oh yeah, when people in
school used to say it because they used
to copy each other. [ __ ] bunch of
copycats. No mind of their [ __ ] own.
He's a [ __ ] copycat. He is. No mind
of his own.
Yeah. Where did he get that money from?
Maybe someone in London. Yeah. Yeah.
Average. Yeah. Yeah. But he was like,
"No, if you don't find her attractive,
you're gay." I was like, "How the [ __ ]
can I be gay?" He's like, "Nope, you're
gay." I was like, "I'm I'm not gay."
The [ __ ] So yeah, he's just a copycat.
He's definitely a copycat.
I don't even think I'd actually cold approach her.
I don't actually think I'd even think I
would actually cold approach her to be
fair. Not my type.
But then again, I'm not a copycat. Know
what I mean? Nikolai.
Yeah. I don't know if he still skip, but
Oh man, I am [ __ ] And you know
another thing is when you got this
hangover, it's hard to sleep as well. Yep.
I don't really like any celebrities, bro. Nah, not really.
Do you still think of USA? Is he Nicolo? I don't. Nah.
You even have ugly women that think
they're better than you. Imagine that.
How mad is that, bro? Ugly women.
I met a couple of spastics yesterday,
bro. There was two women I approached
and they were actually disabled,
which obviously I didn't realize they
were disabled, but they were [ __ ] disabled, bro.
Like not like lit like they were very um
not like in a wheelchair, but you could
tell by the way they were talking that
they bit like N's boy.
Yeah, bit like slow.
I kind of just walked away. I can't explain why.
Well, you know, people on Reddit,
Nicolo, they they they say go to bars
and [ __ ] They say go to bars and pubs, Nikolai.
They say go to bars and pubs.
But what happens if you approaching bars and pubs?
Yeah, this woman had a go at me today on
Reddit. All because I showed her the
truth. Cuz I showed her my code
approaches from yesterday. She started
like attacking me, saying, "You're this, you're that."
No, only two of them cuz I didn't
realize they were [ __ ] slow, bro.
What the [ __ ] So, um Yeah. Um Yeah.
And then she started attacking me
cuz the truth hurts. That's why they
don't like these approaching videos
because the truth hurts. It shows women
in a bad way and they don't want that.
So that's why they start blaming you for
recording and attacking you. Very, very
simpy behavior, I must say.
I'll just go I'll just go back to Sig L.
I'll just go back to Sig. It's not a
problem, you know.
I don't even know what that word means.
I don't know what that word means, bro.
I don't approach Asian women, bro.
You mean like Chinese
I bet you'll be walking down the street
sometimes, the Nicole, and you start
laughing in it, at some of the things I've said
in the past, right? Yeah.
Yeah. I don't I don't like Chinese.
Yeah. But why did Ant-Man say the only
place you're not going to get I've got a
boyfriend is Asia?
Why did he say that?
He said the only place you're not going
to get that is Asia.
The ones that say they've got
boyfriends, they're so full of [ __ ] bro.
They are so full of [ __ ]
They're [ __ ] full of [ __ ] They ain't
got no boys, man. Bro,
>> what do you think, Jensen? Do you think
one day I'll meet someone in this country?
Let's have a vote. No way, bro. No [ __ ] way.
Yeah. I had to stop talking to that
19year-old though, Nicolo, cuz I She was
becoming more westernized.
She was coming a bit of She was becoming
a bit of a [ __ ]
Oh, here we go. One second, lady.
I'm coming up. I'm coming. Coming.
>> I'm on 66. >> 66.
>> 66. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Thank you.
There you go. I said it.
You're going to say that to the wrong
person one day that actually understands
it. Thank you, C.
I said thank you, D.
I fought, man. Remember
when I was doing the Uber? You remember
when I was a driver?
Yeah. Remember when I was a little
driver? The car on my little bike. Oh,
mate. Was long.
It was [ __ ] long, bro.
Why do I want to go?
cuz I'm sick of the [ __ ]
I'm sick of the I've got a boyfriend
[ __ ] You're going to laugh at this Nicolo. Yeah.
I met this Brazilian yesterday
her friend, but she could speak English.
So, we kept translating
and we speak to like 40 minutes.
Oh, can you buy my friend a drink? And I
said, "What do I get out of it?" Like,
"I don't mind buying you a drink and
just getting on it and shit." I said,
"Okay, I'll buy your you and your friend
a drink if you give me a little kiss."
And the reason I said that is because
she's she was going back to Brazil
tomorrow, which is today. So, I thought,
"Fuck it. I might as well get try and
get something out of it whilst I can.
It's not like I'm ever going to see them
again." They weren't having it for toffee.
But the good thing with Brazilians is
they never say they have a boyfriend. Nah, never.
I just got a McDonald's chicken mac.
You never get it, bro. I know I never
got any tips. Well, yeah, I did get tips
cuz Uber used to tip it. Yeah.
Yeah. Uber used to tip me out.
I'm never drinking rum again, bro. [ __ ] that.
No, but this really is right that
they're not interested in this country
or is he just talking [ __ ]
No, you won't get laid. You go west tonight.
You won't get laid because you're westernized.
Is that man right though that they're
just not interested in this country
or do you think he's just talking [ __ ]
No, he obviously is right. Is it?
I was in a club yesterday and all they
do is have that westernized look.
I'm sick of the look that they have.
It's so westernized.
They're evil eyes. I don't like it. It's
so weird. Their evil eyes.
They just got Tik Tok brains. M.
They're so evil looking.
Have you had a chicken macol? I can't
believe I've ate out three times today.
Walkers that rub.
All because of that rub. E. All because
of that [ __ ] rub.
Yeah, good day.
So, what did USA do to me, Nicolo?
The good thing about going out is you
make new friends, you make new
acquaintances, but you get pissed up and
you all have a laugh.
You all have like a good laugh. But with
the women, it never changes.
I was still looking for that change.
Can't find it anywhere.
Looking for that change.
I'm always looking for that know.
Oh [ __ ] The [ __ ] out of me, bro. [Applause] [Music]
Why was Virgin boy success with Britney?
He never wanted his ugly ass.
She never ever wanted his ugly ass.
Why was she Why was he obsessed with
somebody that never wanted him? Like
never not wanted and then never wanted.
She literally never wanted him. Never
even got into it.
He never wanted you.
You crazy obsessed ugly bastard. Yeah.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
I've still not been showing my 10 grand.
Guess no one has it.
Guess no one has run.
You don't want to know this. I don't
want to know you. Literally. Yeah. I'm not
give your head a w.
I'm not. I'm telling the story. Right.
I met some guy yesterday from Wington at the pub.
and we was having banter and he said
he's from Brmley.
I said, "Oh yeah, I know a virgin from
there. Big big virgin. You probably seen them before."
And um I was telling them that basically.
Well, them chips were nice cuz
McDonald's chips are nice when they
first come out, aren't they?
And I was saying, "Yeah, he used to say
that um Brmley's London is Oh, it is." I
said, "It's [ __ ] a mate. You are
nothing to [ __ ] do with us." Um,
it's [ __ ] Kent. You're a Kent [ __ ]
But it was just like coming down here
and [ __ ] It was But it it really isn't
London. Like it it really isn't London, mate.
Yeah. Ain't London.
There are some people I met from uh uh
Leicester yesterday and they said, "Oh,
you don't sound like a typical London."
I said, "What? Because I don't sound
like Danny Dyier. You think all people
from London sound like Danny Dyier? I
think that's what they were expecting. You know,
I said, "Oh yeah, people used to say I
sound like I'm from Manchester. Then
they said I sounded like I was [ __ ]
from Birmingham." I said, "That used to
offend me when people used to say that I
sound like cuz I don't sound like them [ __ ] cunts."
Do I talk a bit with this team? T the
team. I don't [ __ ] do. I sound like that. No.
I hate that accent.
It's horrible, bro. It's like you know that Proven.
It's horrible, bro. They add Rs to their
[ __ ] to their words.
I watch that pros.
Oh, I watched that video the other day.
Pro selling £300
and bro, what the [ __ ]
We done a video to lose £300.
This is my money to go out for the
weekend. Well, what what is even the
point of showing £300? Is that I don't I
don't understand that, bro. Is that just
what a lot of people do?
It's just the madness, isn't it?
Some people in this community is very very insecure.
Do you know who that pro is greety?
Oh, I bet you do.
I bet you do. Hey, Grezy.
Prominent loans. Yeah.
want to know your ugly ass.
Why are you so obsessed with my mama?
Why is Virgin boy so obsessed with my mama?
He clips some sort of sick fantasy
with my mama.
You're [ __ ] [ __ ] weird.
Who does that sort of [ __ ] bro? Come on now.
Who does that, bro? [ __ ]
This burger is so creamy.
Oh, it's burn. It's going right now.
Nice and grooy.
You know, it's not. It's a propney
accent. It's not an essence accent.
That's a proper prop accent from London.
You just don't hear them as much
nowadays. It's like, you know, that
black guy in the video where they call
that um guy speaking to kids online and
he's like, you're a pair of [ __ ]
That's a cocky accent.
That's not an essence accent. That's a cocky accent.
Daddy dies from Cannon Town, which is 10
minutes away from where I'm from. He's a
cockney just like that black guy. is a pop me.
Yeah, there's different d there's
different dialects, you know, in London. So,
no, he's definitely from London, bro.
It's a cocky accent,
just like that black guy. You know, one
of the video.
No, but he's he's a [ __ ] leader.
Have you heard that guy in Liverpool
that for chicken um
chicken and a can of coke? That accent
is so put on. But yeah, he Liverpool,
but it's exaggerated. Have you seen that
guy? I tell you what though, I was watching him.
He kept going on about chicken and
chicken and chicken and you know when
someone keeps going on about it. Yeah,
they made me want it. So, in the morning
at 10:00, I ordered the KFC in the morning.
I had five pieces of chicken and chips.
He kept going on about chicken and
chicken and chicken. It made me want some
[ __ ] That's what happens. You know,
people keep going on about see it.
But that accent is is exaggerated.
Yeah, I got something in the morning, 10
in the morning. It was the other day.
The chicken was [ __ ] beautiful. It
They kept going on about chicken, bro. It's annoying. Yeah.
You know what?
I actually I actually feel sorry for
Virgin boy Nicolola
taking out his
little benefit money every month. That
was a benefit.
It's such a desperate attempt to to try
to convince people that he's got skin.
It's it's such a lame desperate attempt you know
it's something to feel sorry for is it really
you are sting a [ __ ] stimp
saying before he showed 14k I was like
mate listen no you bloody didn't so 14
grand I think what what had happened
mate is you've been sucking your dad's
dick too much and where he spunked in
your [ __ ] eyeballs. You actually
forgot how much money you've actually shown.
That's what happens, mate. You probably
come too many times up your [ __ ]
eyeballs. You know, you probably that
you probably not realize that you're
showing the same benefit, buddy every
month, mate. It's embarrassing now.
When am I going to see my [ __ ] 10 grand?
Still waiting, Nero. Still waiting for
this 10 grand.
I think I'll be waiting forever, lad. [Music] Just [ __ ]
I'm not blowing now. Uh-uh.
Oh, it's nice. I went down nice. I'm
never drinking love again. Be refreshed.
Yeah, the banana milk sense the best.
Banana milk sense the best.
That's the only way I like.
So why is Virgin boy so obsessed with my
mama? obsessed with my mama.
I messaging my mama and [ __ ]
He's a very insecure virgin.
Shut the [ __ ] up.
I'm not [ __ ] with that little burger. No way.
No [ __ ] way, man.
I'll pay £1,000 to get a [ __ ]
Why not bing like that
to get a restraining order?
Why is that dog laughing like that, bro?
It's [ __ ] annoying.
Yeah, I never meet someone with autism.
It's very dangerous.
He's a dangerous virgin. Especially when
they're a virgin like him.
Especially when they're a virgin like him.
Um, you should you should have known how
[ __ ] up it was. Being obsessed with a
girl in another country that never
wanted. That's scary. That is
being obsessed with somebody you've
never met that never wanted you, that
you've never even met. That's scary, bro.
make up suicide stories.
But they are making up suicide
stories that you've tried killing yourself.
I always blame Monty. I said, "I met
that [ __ ] virgin cuz of you."
[ __ ] hell, bro. If it wasn't for you,
I wouldn't have met that [ __ ] I said
that to him when I met him as well. I
said, "Bro, why did you have to
introduce me to this [ __ ] virgin?"
I used to feel sorry for him on the
PlayStation cuz he used to get bullied.
So, I felt sorry for him cuz people was
bullying him. I just thought that he
was, you know, misunderstood, misunderstood. Um,
you know what I'm saying?
People used to pick on him for his shitty clothes. You know,
proper weird kid.
He used to make up like sex stories as
well. Well, all sex stories. There was
someone called Hannah Nos that met him once and um
he went she went back to he and she never uh um
she uh she rejected him. She didn't suck
his dick. She didn't do any of that
stuff. He would No, she never she knew
any of that stuff, mate.
Yeah. Well, he didn't at first. He was
actually a weirdo. That guy from
Birmingham. He used to [ __ ] teddy bears
and [ __ ] which I wasn't even aware of
until after I met him. But no, he was
obsessive, but when we stopped talking,
he just stopped. Yeah, I was thinking
about him when I was in Birmingham. I
wonder I wonder if he still lives there.
[ __ ] 10 years later, he's 9 years
later and he's still living there. Yeah,
apparently he used to like shed bears
and [ __ ] Monty told me. But I didn't I
didn't know any stuff.
That's the first time I went to
Birmingham when I was 19. So yeah,
but he was obsessed with he was obsessed
before I met him. Like he always wanted
to be on the phone with me and stuff,
but yeah, he left me alone. So maybe he
was just lonely then. But this virgin,
you can't get rid of him. You can't get
rid of this [ __ ] virgin, mate.
You can't get rid of the [ __ ] skin
Yeah, he's obsessed with me.
So, I was saying to Guzy before, Nicolo,
that these people can only pick on kids,
but then as soon as somebody becomes an
adult, they don't want to mess with them anymore. Virgin boy,
Virgin Boy, [ __ ]
people from Skype. They They don't They
don't want to [ __ ] with people that when
they're adults. It's weird.
It's cowardly. Really? Very cowardly.
It's madness, isn't it? I reckon if I
was still 18, 19, I think I'd have
people [ __ ] with me, bro.
I'd have people [ __ ] with me, bro.
He come off social media.
Nah, no. Because I don't really come on
social media anymore.
He said I need to try in another country
with the approaching and [ __ ] He said,
"Oh, you have to try another country."
That's what he said.
No. Yeah. Conrad was a coward. He done
done to me what he was moaning about women doing.
So cowardly he was moaning about what he
was doing. Exactly what he was moaning
about women doing.
the ghosting and [ __ ] Wonder what
happened to that con. Yeah, Conrad. Yeah.
Yeah, man. Oh, [ __ ] Oops.
Oh, I'm not looking forward to the
[ __ ] tomorrow, Nicolo, man. I'm not
I'm not looking forward to it tomorrow.
I have a boyfriend [ __ ]
Oh, I'm not looking forward to it, man.
You never know till you try.
So they say
Yeah, you never know. She give it a go.
Do you reckon my mama would ever speak
to me again? Nico, my mama.
Oh, that went down nicely.
Yeah. One second, bro. I'm talking to these tenants.
Yeah. I told her to go suck her mom.
I said to these tenants, "Why do you lie
and steal? It's against your religion.
You might as well just eat a pork chop.
You might as well. This is why I hate
Oh, I shouldn't even say this, bro. I'm
I'm starting to like
really dislike like Muslim people, bro.
I was going to send a voice note, bro,
and start like madness.
Like, just get a pork and just slap it
around their face. You might as well, bro.
You might You might as well eat pork.
They might as well eat pork. They might
as well eat McDonald's cuz they do other
things that are forbidden.
You know, you don't want to eat a pig,
right? But you want to lie and you want
to steal and be a [ __ ] It annoys me,
bro. Like, he's lucky that day. Yeah. I
didn't give him a good [ __ ] hiding.
You know, my last day at that house.
Yeah. He weren't opening the door.
Um he weren't answer he weren't um
answering the door.
Uh and they're still saying that they
haven't stole my after shave. Bro, I'm
going to start getting racist to these
people cuz they're they're really
starting to annoy me now, bro. Like, I'm
not even joking. Bro, stop winding me
up. Like, you know, the last day, bro,
it took him like 10 minutes to open the
door. They thought I was going to [ __ ]
them up. I said, "I'm not going to do
anything. I'm not going to hit you, bro.
I'm not going to say I'm not going to do
it and do it." But I'm just going to be
saying now, if I see one of you, I am
going to hit you. I'm telling you
straight now, I'm going to hit you. When
I see one of you,
I'm going to I'm going to hit you. And I
am actually going to do it this time cuz
you're [ __ ] winding me up now.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
going to get a pork chop and slap it
around their face. That's what I'm going
to do, bro.
Yeah. Why? Why don't they like pork? You're
And they're trying to say that they
didn't steal the after shave, but they
have because I know exactly where it was.
And I had to buy another after shave.
Like one of them was starting. Yeah.
Trying to say, "Oh, I owe him a
deposit." He said, "I'm going to come to
here." I said, "Bro, come right now.
Come right now." And as soon as I said
that, he shut his mouth. He stopped
then. He stopped his [ __ ] I was like,
"Bro, you're not someone that can start
something and not finish it, are you?"
Like, why? Why do you do this [ __ ] This
is why people hate Muslim people. This
is why people are racist toward you. Do
you understand that? Not me, cuz I
couldn't give a [ __ ] But this is this
is, you know, at least the ones that
are bored here will tell you that they
drink, will tell you that they do things
that they're not supposed to do, but the
things that they're not supposed to do
is not harming anyone. The stuff that
you are is harming because you're
stealing. You're lying. It's like, bro,
don't I'm going to I'm going to send a
voice note, bro. All right. Don't don't
ever ever call yourself a Muslim again
cuz you're not a Muslim, bro.
You're not no [ __ ] Muslim. Shut the [ __ ] up.
And they'll lie to your face as well.
Like even when they're caught, they'll
still lie. And they'll lie for each
other as well. They'll actually lie for
each other as well. That's another
thing. And even when they're caught,
they'll still lie. Like I have like a
few examples. I was like, "Bro, they
must think that we're the stupid ones.
They literally must think that we are
the stupid ones." Even though they come
here and they don't even know English
when they first come here, they actually
think that we're the stupid ones,
you know? Like,
yeah, there's only two of them people in
that house that I still like that never
changed and they were just like down to
earth. But the others I told them all
about us themselves. The girl, all of
them. I told them all about themselves,
bro. And well, most of them. Yeah.
I didn't get any Muslims out on dates.
Which Which Muslims did I get out on
dates? No, I didn't.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Yeah. I just said
I just said, "Haha, stop talking shit."
You have to remember I'm not the stupid
one. You are. Like, remember that.
Keep remembering that. You're not
talking to me like I'm stupid. You are
the stupid ones, bro. Like, I don't know
how many times I have to say this.
Cuz if they if they keep winding me up,
I'm going to find that house they're in
and I'm just going to smash it up. Like,
I they said that it's 2 minutes away
from the other house where I used to
live. I said, "Bro, if they keep winding
me up, I'm just going to brick the
[ __ ] window. I will just brick the
window." Simple. And then like then then
they're going to have to just pay for the [ __ ]
um they're going to have to pay for the
[ __ ] window because I would just
breakick the window. Like they are they
are actually starting to wind me up now.
You can't lie to me. You stupid [ __ ]
Yeah. One second you.
You stupid [ __ ] I was born I was born
on a day. I was born on a day and the
day wasn't yesterday. If you keep
winding me up, I'm going to go there.
I'm going to brick that window, bro. I
swear down, I'm going to brick that [ __ ] window.
I swear to God, I'll just camp outside.
And listen, I said, "You can't lie to
me, you stupid [ __ ] I was born on a day
and the day wasn't yesterday." Yeah,
these [ __ ] bro. I swear to God,
I'm going to buy one big pork chop and
I'm going to start ticking them with it.
You know, that's what I'm going to do,
bro. I'm going to get a [ __ ] pig and
I'm going to start. And I was like, they
why do you lie? Like, don't lie unless
you can lie. It just makes you look like a [ __ ]
And if you keep winding me up and
winding me up and winding me up and
winding me up, I'm just going to brick the window
and then you're going to get in [ __ ]
with your from your landlord cuz you're
winding me up, bro. Like, do you really
really want me to come and cause some
damage? I don't care who you know. I
don't care how many cousins you know. I
don't give a [ __ ] bro. I seriously don't care. You know?
Yeah. No, but it's only 2 minutes away
from the house, the other house. So,
>> yeah. I don't give a [ __ ] how many
people these Muslim people know. I don't
give a [ __ ] bro. They're all [ __ ]
when they're by themselves. That's
another thing. There's only one of them
that's actually right. like he's
actually cool, like he is actually down
to earth. But I mean that's one in so
many. He actually is cool and he never
changed. See, see people's true colors
really come out greasy. And you know
that's why it's important sometimes for
these things to happen because you know
like you you see people's true colors. You understand?
So sometimes these things um they have to happen.
Yeah. [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] bro. Um but
this guy, he never changed. Like he was
still down to earth, the one that I used
to go clubbing with. So that's why I
just said to him, bro, like I've got um
Yeah, man. I've got enough respect for
that guy because he never changed once.
He never changed once ever.
um throughout the whole time. So, I
mean, those are like the real ones.
The far few between he's cool, man. But
the these other ones as well. You're
trying to tell me that you've not stole
my after shave when I'm telling you you
have stupid [ __ ] You're you're
going to laugh at this, Nicolo. Yeah.
This is how dirty these [ __ ] are,
right? They are. So, you know, like when
I met Izzy, do you remember that boss
t-shirt I was wearing when when I met
Izzy? You know the gray one? You know, a
few years ago, like when I was on that
700 pound a month and I won money on the
roulette and I bought a new top to go
meet Izzy. I don't did I buy it cuz I
knew I was going to meet her. I just
bought it the day that I met Izzy. Do
you remember like four or five years
ago? What's so obviously cuz I wore it
so much I put it in the wardrobe. The
boss one, the gray one. I put it in the
like I threw it away. like so if anyone
wants it, they can have it. And this
particular tenant has the same skin
complexion as me and he kind of looks a
bit like me. Um, and
he was wearing it. I was, "Oh, that
looks good on you, man. Did you like
it's good cuz I didn't want it anyways."
And he says, "Oh, no, no, no. I got it
from Dubai." I was like, "Well, you
didn't because it's the exact same top
that I've put in that in that wardrobe.
I I know what I bought." and he was
barefaced trying to lie his way out. I
was like, "Bro, you can have it. I don't
want it. I'm just saying like it's it's
yeah, it's what I left. That's good. You
can have it. There was no problem." And
he kept lying and lying and lying. And
then in the end, he just he just uh he
just cut it up. And it's it was the one
that I bought. It [ __ ] was. And it
weren't what something that you'd buy
like a like a normal night t-shirt. and
it could be mistaken like a like a
common t-shirt. It's I've never ever
ever seen anyone wear the same thing
ever again. And even though they're
caught out, they still lie. They're
still dirty, stinky liars. Whereas most
people, like if they get caught out lying,
um then they'll admit that they're
lying. It's it is what it is. They will still lie.
like it's mad
which is frowned upon against their religion. Um, so yeah,
that's it, man. It's uh it's a madness
there. And he was it was the one that I bought.
Obviously, it was the one that I was
bought. I bought. Why? Why lie? Like you
I you need to understand I'm not from a
third world country.
I'm not the stupid one. Remember that,
bro. I am not the stupid one.
If I see any of them, bro, I swear down
I'm going to punch them up.
Except one of them because he's cool.
And yeah, but two of them, actually. Two
of them out of like seven out of them, I
won't. But if I see any of them, bro, I
swear down I'm going to really, really,
really do them some damage, bro. And I'm
thinking, bro, like you made me buy a
new after shave. Yeah. Which cost me
£72. So I'm thinking, bro, I should just
go and do the windowing. I should just
go and do the windowing to pay for. Do
you know what I should do? Do you know
what I should do? I say, "Listen, if you
if none of you are going to own up to
the after shave, I'm going to do the
window in or I'm going to do one of you
in when I see you." Simple. If none of
you's going to own up to it, then bro,
guess what? I'm going to break the
window and I'm going to deny that it's me.
That's what That's what I'm going to do,
bro. That's honestly what I'm going to
do. If they want to go around stealing
Yeah. and lying, then I can make their
life hard as well.
You know what I'm saying, bro? I can I I
like I'll just make their life hard.
And they also hid the receipt as well.
Like I'm easy, but I don't give a [ __ ]
who you know, bro. You know what I'm
saying? I don't care. I'm not asked. You
know what I'm saying? But I'm really not asked.
I said, "If you say you ain't done it
again, I'm I'm I'm I'm going to come to
the house, bro. Like, when I'm in thingy
again, which should probably be
tomorrow, the next day, I'm just going
to find the house that you're in cuz
you're always going back to the old
house." So, like, do you really want to
keep lying and keep trying to wind people up?
I actually have a picture of me in the
mosque, by the way. I actually got a
picture of us in the mosque. Um yeah,
I went to the mosque on Ramadan um
because they were giving out free food
and they invited me to the mosque cuz
I'm not going to turn down free food.
So, I must be the only one that um
um I must be I must been the only one in
that mosque that wasn't uh that didn't
have a circumcised willie.
But I'll just say to them, yeah, bro,
like they're [ __ ] as well, bro. Like,
I've seen how they move. That guy
thought I was going to hurt him. He's
like, don't hurt me. Don't hurt me.
Like, bro, he was worse than how I was with Prime.
Like, he he was worse than how I was
with Prime. He was [ __ ] himself, you know.
Bro, if he this guy needs to stop
texting me, bro, because I'm really
going to just end up doing them their windows.
If you want to keep lying, then dirty thief.
Yeah, they're circumcised. They're
they're child abusers. Why the [ __ ]
would you cut a child's dick off? Yeah.
Why would you cut [ __ ] skin off their
dick unless it's med unless it's for a
medical reason? It's child abuse. It's
actually child abuse.
I mean, if there's if there's a reason um
listen. And then he he started getting
the [ __ ] he said and then he started
threatening me, making empty threats.
Then when I said, "Okay, come now." He
said, "Oh, I'm going to call the police.
I'm going to call the police." [ __ ]
pair of [ __ ] You know what I mean?
Yeah. I said to him, "If you keep
winding me up, bro."
Yeah. I'm going to say, "If you keep
winding me up, I swear to God, I'm gonna
really, really, really, really come and
do them windows in, bro, I don't know
where you live, bro. Listen.
I'll find out where you live.
I'll find out where you live. And I know
where you work as well. So, you keep
winding me up. I know where you work as
well. I know where I want to use work.
I'm going to keep going." You know what
I'm going to do? I'm going to go to that
Zara tomorrow. I'm going to go to that
Zara tomorrow, bro. I will just
embarrass him in front of everyone where
he works. I'm going to embarrass him,
bro. Don't [ __ ] with me, bro. Seriously,
you know? Yeah. And that's the thing,
like, if you want to keep lying and keep
denying [ __ ] I'm just going to go to
his workplace tomorrow and just
embarrass him in front of everyone
like, and he will not be working there anymore.
No, he's he works in security.
But he's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, man. So that's it.
You know what I'm saying?
You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
I'll just go there, bro.
So, he's a security. He works in
They're all [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
That's fair, bro. I think I think the
window is like um yeah, he's a skinny
[ __ ] He's a proper [ __ ] as well. He's
like, "Oh, you're going to hit me.
You're going to hit me. You're going to
hit me. You're going to hit me. You're
going to hit me."
I I'll make you buy a new [ __ ]
window, mate. You made me buy a new
after save. I'll make you buy a new
[ __ ] window. I'll smash your [ __ ]
window in. Oh, I smashed the [ __ ] door in.
Stupid [ __ ] [ __ ] there.
Go and eat a [ __ ] pork chop, you dirty [ __ ]
I'm going to go to that Z tomorrow with
a pork chop, bro. I'm going to go there
with a with a pork chop. Cuz I used to
like cook pork and he used to say, "It's
disgusting, man. It's disgusting."
Well, I'll [ __ ] slap you in the face
with a [ __ ] dirty pig.
Yeah, I've got some pork in the fridge.
It's out of date. I'm going to come
tomorrow with out of date. The um the
pork's out of date. It's been in there
for 3 days. I need to chuck it. I might
just go there with the pork chops, but
I'm going to [ __ ] it.
Yeah, this guy is really annoying me, bro. I'm in. Uh,
listen, bro. One second. Let me
voicemail this guy. Uhuh. One sec.
I'm going there tomorrow, bro. [ __ ] it.
You better hope he's not working there
tomorrow because he gets shifts and
different um things, but I'm going there
tomorrow, bro. 100%. I'm going there
tomorrow. [ __ ] it.
I'm going there tomorrow. You'll be
working. I'm I'm in central London
tomorrow anyways. So, it's not a
problem, you stupid little [ __ ] [ __ ]
it, bro. They're winding me up now, bro.
They're actually starting to piss me off
now. You know, I told you many times
like, "Leave me alone. Leave me alone.
Leave me alone."
Are you going to admit it or am I going
to go to your workplace tomorrow?
You know what I'm saying? Simple.
Cuz I'm going to start getting racist
now, bro. I swear to God, I'm going to
start getting racist.
And I'm not even joking, but I am
actually going to start getting racist.
But the thing is, I'm not going to run
to the [ __ ] police. That's the
difference. I'm not going to run to the
[ __ ] police like you did.
Um, I can't do anything. Remember, you
made empty threats a year ago. Yeah. Not
a year ago. What am I talking about? A
month ago. I told you the address. I
told you to come. Then you started
talking about how you going to call the
police. How you going to call the
police? Cuz you shhat yourself. You
shacked your pants. Yeah.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
Yeah, man. Simple.
This guy is really really starting to
annoy me. I I'll I'll see him tomorrow anyways, bro.
So, I'm just going to embarrass him in
in front of everyone. I'm going to
embarrass him in front of everyone.
At least be careful what I say on it cuz
I don't get my channel banned. But yeah,
they're [ __ ] pissing me off though. Like,
I respect a a a Muslim bar if that eats
pork. If somebody ate pork and drunk,
I'd be okay. Well, this is stuff that
they do, you know.
[ __ ] He's cousing up as well, which I
reckon he's cousin could probably give
me more of a fight to be honest. But I
told And I said, "Yeah, I just told you
last night, you can come to the house.
You can come to the house, right? Yeah,
you can come to the house and we can
meet, bro, and I'll [ __ ] you up." Cuz he
kept making threats. He said, "Oh, yeah.
If you don't give us £250,
I don't even know." He's like, "Oh, I'm
going to come to the house." I was like,
"Bro, come right now cuz I'm not giving
it to you. So, you might as well come
now. There's no point you stressing over
this, that, and the other. I'm not
giving you nothing." So, be a man of
your word and come and see what happens
to you. Oh, I'm going to call the
police. Oh, you know what I'm saying?
So, you make empty threats and when you
realize you can't back them up,
what's the next thing, bro? It's the
boys in blue. You're a [ __ ] [ __ ]
man. You know what I mean? Then it's the
[ __ ] boys in blue. Make up your
[ __ ] mind. Which one is it? Oh [ __ ]
Just making a cup of [ __ ] here, but
there's not enough water.
You're a [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. You're an absolute stupid.
Come to bro. [ __ ] This guy is really
starting to annoy me, bro.
I told you come and see what happens to
you. Then you said you was going to run
to the police.
>> Yeah, you live near Station. [ __ ] off,
bro. You don't live near no station, you
stupid [ __ ] Muslim.
Listen, bro. I You told me Yeah. You
Yeah. about how
not trying to get people off the stand, bro.
Yeah. Come on your ones. Come on your
ones by yourself
and see what happens to you. Simple
about you're going to go on people's
doors and people's sister's doors and
people's mom's doors. Bro, you get yourself hurt.
Like he doesn't he doesn't understand that.
Do you understand? I'm not He's not the
neighbor. I don't have to see him every
day. They're not going to be reporting
my mom for making noise. You understand?
It's a completely different situation.
Now he's trying to say that he lives in
[ __ ] Ilford. He doesn't live in no
[ __ ] Ilford, man. He's a [ __ ] idiot. Don't forget
they need to understand, bro. Like, you
can't play with me, bro.
That's the thing. Stop it.
you might as well eat pork.
My dad used to hate them, you know,
these Muslims. And I just used to think,
oh, he was an alcoholic and no, like I
tried to give them a chance and that,
but I I can see why now. I can actually
see why now, you know. I actually can
see, yeah, okay, the ones that are born
here might not eat things that are
halal. They might drink, but you know, it's,
you know, at least they admit it. They
own it, you know, to be fair.
I just put it down to like he was a
[ __ ] alcoholic and [ __ ] but at the
end of the day, yeah, I can see what he means.
Trust me, bro. You don't you you know
don't want to do business with them.
They shift is about 60 70. So either way
I'm going to make you lose money. Either
way, I'm going to make you lose money if
you don't admit to it. And then you're
so you don't live in no [ __ ] ill,
bro. Trust me. Keep winding me up. I'm
already going to where he works tomorrow
cuz I'm in central London anyways. You
know, I'm in central London anyways by
the Oxford Circus. So, yeah.
Yeah. Nah. No. No. No. No. No. No. No.
No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No.
No. Not at all, bro.
But they're pissing me off. There wasn't
no deposit anyways. You didn't give me a deposit.
He's about nothing. Well, you made empty
threats. Yeah. And somebody told you to come. Like you
you you started backtrack you you started backtracking
all this [ __ ] You're not about that life.
You're really really not about that
life. You know, you're not about that
life, bro. Stop it. You know,
King getting scared now trying to say
that you live in Ilford. Stop being a
scared [ __ ] Stop trying to throw the
scent off what you've just said. You're
trying to throw me off the scent. Oh,
bro. Like, it's not going to be funny.
Like, when I see one of you, I'm already
going to where that guy works tomorrow.
I'm just going to embarrass the [ __ ] out
of him. I'm going to show everyone that
he's a [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah. I'm going to
embarrass him where he works. I'm going
to tell him about himself where he
works. It's going to be a Kenji
situation all over again.
You don't live in no [ __ ] ill. Shut
the [ __ ] up, bro. Stop talking [ __ ] You know
He said, "Oh, you want to do this? What
is it for cooking?" I said, "Bro, listen
to me." Yeah. You and you and this guy's
playing games. Stop it. Yeah. Tell your
friend to shut the [ __ ] up. You know,
yeah, that's all you can do is evidence.
You're a [ __ ] bro. You're a [ __ ]
You're a [ __ ] I'm Come right now,
then. I'm I'm telling him to come now.
Come now. Come now, you [ __ ] stupid
Come on, you stupid [ __ ] [ __ ] And go
live on your [ __ ] phone. Yeah.
You know, I swear there's only one of
them tenant chair that was actually
good, bro. I swear to God.
Sorry about I'm texting.
You're pathetic, bro. You're really, really pathetic.
You're really, really pathetic, bro.
You're pathetic, bro. You're [ __ ] absolutely pathetic.
Yeah, report the fact that you stole my
after shave as well. One of you stole my after shave.
This guy is a [ __ ] bro. It's like he
he wants to try to fight. Yeah.
And then and then he and he's talking
about running to the police.
He really is a [ __ ] bro. Cuz he knows
he can't come cuz he'll just get [ __ ]
up. Do you want to sound greasy?
I said to him, "Let's fight. Let's have a fight.
Let's have a [ __ ] fight, bro." It
madness, bro. But then they go on about
black people. This is what makes me
laugh is that they go on about black
people, but they do they do the same
[ __ ] themselves. Grezy.
I mean, what is the actual reason that
they don't like piggies? Let's get into
it. You know what? Because they
apparently eat their own [ __ ] Okay. But
I mean, you can't be a nice bit of piggy.
But you can't be a bit a nice bit of piggy.
You know what I'm saying? But like, what
the [ __ ] You know what they're missing? Must
be a piggy, mate.
It's funny when I told them about the
house. Imagine I didn't tell them about
the house, Nicolola, and then the baiffs
just come. I wish I'd done that now. You
know, imagine that, bro. And they come
back and the house has been um repossessed, you know.
It's been repossessed in it.
Imagine, bro, like they just come back
and it's been repossessed.
That's what I should have done, you
know? Oh, like they got woke up.
Imagine, bro. It Yeah, that would have
been funny, isn't it, bro?
Imagine. Get your magic.
That would have been jokes. Imagine, bro. Imagine.
madness, lad. One sec. Yeah. It's like
[ __ ] USA, is it? Like, say you had a
address yet and you went all the way
over there. They're all sitting on the sofa.
Um, sitting on the sofa, chilling,
saying, "Ah." And then all of a sudden,
bam, bam, bam, the dog goes. The dog
goes, mate. Yeah.
I don't like the fact they called a girl
my business as well.
They think because they're in another
country they're safe in it, Nikolai.
They they would have got away with it if
it wasn't for you meddling kids. Yeah.
Yeah. Sitting sitting on a sofa like the
Simpsons. Good old Scott in it.
Good old Scott.
Just shout through their letter box.
Isn't it? They'll be like, "What the
hell in it? I've come to see my mama." Yeah.
Oh, Prime, this better not be the real
you, Prime. Because do you know what? If
it is you, I'm not even going to
entertain you, mate. I called you out
when I was in Birmingham. You saw it.
You must have heard about it. And I was
in Birmingham overnight. And also Timmy
saw it as well. So don't start coming on
here saying about, "Oh, where do you
want to meet?" No, no, no, no, no. Bro,
I was live about three times and I was
in your city
and I wanted you to move me. I I
literally said, "I'm not moving. I'm in
your city and I'm not moving." And you
you you you you're not about that life.
You're not about that life.
You are not about that life. I was in
Birmingham two weeks ago. Everyone saw
it. I went to meet Monty. Yeah. So,
don't [ __ ] come back on here. Yeah.
And try to um make it that you ain't you
you've not you don't know about it. How
the [ __ ] don't you know about it? Isn't
it funny how whenever you go to these
people's cities Yeah. they don't know
about it, mate? I was in Birmingham overnight
and everybody can confirm that I was in
Birmingham. Oh, you didn't see it?
Really? Well, you can come to London tomorrow.
Yeah. Should you come to London
tomorrow, ma'am? Was I in Birmingham, Greavvesy?
Yes, she picked up the phone. Uh, Nicolo
saying hello. I said, go suck your mom.
He keeps blocking me on WhatsApp as well.
Yeah, bro. Come to London anytime you
want. I was in Birmingham two weeks ago
and you didn't meet me. Did you? Did
you? Team Tim, did you?
[ __ ] I can't stand that [ __ ] gummy accent, mate.
It gives me [ __ ]
gives me cancer, bro. I hate that accent.
O tin tin. That's how you [ __ ] talk.
The [ __ ] is that kind of accent, mate?
Hate that accent. It's probably the
worst accent in the whole of England.
So, what? Where is my mommy now anyways?
Nicolo, you don't even type anymore.
There's no point you even coming on
here. You don't even type.
I know this is you.
You know how she was still playing games
though, saying, "I've got your number
saved." Why have you got my number
saved? She's a game player. Yeah, man.
Oh, so you'll join the hangout. Yeah.
You you you'll join the hangouts then.
Okay. We'll see if it's the real you
and we'll arrange a meet up for tomorrow. Yeah. Uh
join the hangouts. Hello.
No, you didn't tell me to wear shoes
either. Join the hangouts.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Join the hangouts.
Yay, I join Hangouts, mate. Join our apps.
Join our house, man.
Yeah, that's fake prime.
Taking a bubin away from its mama. though.
Nicolo taking a bubin away from its mama.
What do you think of that? Nicolo
taking a baby away from its mama.
I found a new picture of USA. Is he? I
found a new one.
She's very Syrian looking.
He's very Syrian looking. Okay. Yeah, I
messaged her friend. Bye-bye. Fake Remember
though, other guys do it. Watch out,
Nicolo. The other guys.
Stay away from the other guys.
You'll be walking in the Weather Spoons
with your woman.
And then the other guys come.
Other guys do it.
It's always other guys, isn't it? Other
who's in the title? Other guys.
I'm a guy.
I'm going to go on the table and [ __ ]
and and and do that. You know, do you
remember the El Stewart parodies, Nicolo?
Did do you ever watch the Mr. Doodle uh parodies?
Yeah, it's just her friend.
Do you remember the elves doing
paradies? I might play them on the TV in a minute.
Yeah, it just every time I watch them
though, it just reminds me of Mick
Jonathan Robinson. Dirty [ __ ]
It just reminds me of that [ __ ] nons
Mick [ __ ] Robinson. Dirty bastard.
You know, I ain't even told you
everything about him, you know. I've
only told you little things.
But by going to Australia, it was all of
a sudden gonna
change what he done. Nah. Nah, mate.
[ __ ] dirty [ __ ] nonsense, mate.
Oh, it was nice, man. It was nice. Yeah.
>> Yeah. I love Alf.
>> [ __ ] him up, Alf. [ __ ] him up.
Want to watch some Alf.
Oh, poor Franklin. Nicolo. Poor
Franklin. Is it? Poor Franklin.
Yeah. In Cardiff.
Yeah. Another day I went home alone
looking for that change, you know.
You need to watch out for the other
guys. Dreams the other guy.
That's what you need to look out for,
bro. Look out for the other guy.
The other guy.
Other guy. Do it.
Right. I'm going to play this for Grezy. Yeah.
Where's that [ __ ] remote?
What is that [ __ ] remote?
Oh, one sec. Squeezy.
[ __ ] wrong one.
Oh, cuz it's a back. Uh, Alf.
Ow. Got him.
>> Go get him, Al. Never mind.
>> This bit. I love this bit. [Laughter]
>> Your face, gun. It never gets old. But
it just I don't know, bro. Every time I
watch it, it just reminds you of Mick
Jonathan Robinson and he's very, very
devious but very dark path. Rezy. very
devious but very dark.
Isn't that right, Nikolai?
I mean, people don't get put into care
at a very young age for no reason. Yeah. Just looking.
Same [ __ ] different characters. Disney music.
Who the [ __ ] is this? I think this is
Virgin Boy. Sure it is.
>> You're not allowed to talk about me, Big N.
Told you. Bye-bye. Bing, Virgin. Knew it straight away,
mate. I've been [ __ ] I've been
talking about you for the past 2 hours,
you [ __ ] ugly ton.
[ __ ] off. Go suck your dad's dick and
show the same,000 that you've been
showing for two years. I knew it was
that virgin straight away.
I literally knew it was that virgin
straight away. Mate, listen. Do you want
to do you want to do you want to play
the bed game instead of the money game?
Let's play the bed game.
I can show you my bed.
Something that you don't even have about
you've shown 14 grand, mate. You've
never even had four grand in your life,
you skin bastard. The only thing that
you [ __ ] show is is your benefit
money cuz you're [ __ ] skin.
Skin and then a [ __ ] skin flint. You
ugly ratfaced skin bastard with no bed.
That's what you are. Now [ __ ] go and
suck your dad's disabled dick. I'm
bothering you now. Right
back on to uh this.
You know what I've got that you don't?
Got a mom, got a bed, got more money
than you as well. You still ain't show
me this 10 grand. Got more in life than
you. I'm not balding like you. You are
rapidly balding, son.
Rapidly balding. Sort that ugly face
out, mate. You might get a shot at getting laid.
Might actually get laid if you sort that
ugly face out, mate.
might might stand a little chance of getting laid.
You [ __ ] ugly rap based bastard virgin. Anyways, 6% now. Yeah.
[ __ ] obsessed ugly bastard.
[ __ ] I knew it was that virgin.
Yeah. Tilly of Damation. That's where
the phobia of Oh [ __ ] That's where the
phobia of dogs come from.
Anyways, let me b his virgin. That's
where the phobia of dogs come from.
Tilly. Tilly the dalmatation. [ __ ] your
ass up, mate.
[ __ ] your ass up.
You're jealous of anyone that's that's
been loved by their mom.
This is this is why you're so [ __ ] up,
Virgin boy. Because of your [ __ ] childhood.
Because of your [ __ ] childhood, man.
You know, you little [ __ ]
Oh yeah. Um yeah, he used to shake on a
bridge. Like a tiny bridge. You know the
one in Stratford
used to shake like a [ __ ] [ __ ] scare the heights
[ __ ] he is a little [ __ ] in real
life. He's just some irrelevant little
virgin [ __ ] in real life. I told Monty
this as well cuz Monty man's never met
him mate. It's like there was these
black kids right and it they literally
threw water at his back. They literally
threw water at his back. I said, "You
know them guys are throwing stuff at
you." He like, "No, no, no." I said,
"They are, mate. They can they can
detect a [ __ ] virgin a mile away.
They probably see that lanky Kent
Spacker from a mile off. Say, who's this virgin?"
That's obviously how you know you're
from London. I would just say, "Fuck
with this." Yeah, it's plasticated.
Yeah. It's when um his stepdad had him
up against the wall.
>> Literally had him up against the wall.
literally got his throat. His stepdad,
right, had him up against that wall.
Philillip Campbell, his name is from Leeds,
his stepdad, his mom's boyfriend.
So, you can understand why he's so angry
at the world and and so bitter because
of his childhood,
mom not wanting him, starving him to
death almost. It's like, no wonder he's
so bitter towards anyone that has a mother.
You know, it's because he's never had a
mother that wanted him.
You know, that's why he's such a nasty little [ __ ]
What happens, mate, when you're abused
as as a kid?
Put into care. It's madness.
You used to [ __ ] starve me. [ __ ] starve the
[ __ ] hell, man. Yeah, the Dalmatian.
Oh, [ __ ] Can you be scared of a [ __ ] Dian? Come on.
I can't wait until his dad dies, you
know. I'm going to throw a party when
his dad dies, bro. I'm going to invite
everyone around for YouTube.
Going to get like a bottle of champagne
and I'm going to get like the most
expensive bottle of champagne when his
dad dies. Swear to God. Which I'm not
probably going to know when his dad dies
to be honest cuz he's not going to say.
His dad's probably already dead to be honest.
When his dad dies, I'm going to throw a
[ __ ] good party. Bro, trust me.
Trust me, Nicolo. I'm going to [ __ ]
I'm going to throw a good [ __ ] party.
You know how he speaks about dead people
and he's done it with a few uh people
that are dead. When his dad's dead, bro,
we're going to have the biggest laugh ever.
But the whole of the whole of YouTube's
getting invited. I'm be like, [ __ ]
worm food that you're not seeing again.
That's what, bro? I'm going to I'm going
to mock it so hard cuz he's like took
the piss out of people's dead relatives.
I'm going to be saying that [ __ ] worm
food. You're not seeing again. He's a
nasty [ __ ] bro. You you know how this
whole YouTube thing started, bro? With
this [ __ ] and his [ __ ] mouth. Yeah.
That's how that's how all of this
YouTube [ __ ] started. Yeah. Because you
know how I've known the [ __ ] for so
long. Yeah. and he used to that's how it all started
because of this whole like he's
disgusting vile mouth for somebody
that's such a lanky virgin [ __ ] in real life
and anyone would think that you're
dealing with [ __ ]
that you're dealing with a [ __ ]
that you're dealing with [ __ ] Mike
Tyson here but you see the size of him
in real life he's he's a little lanky
[ __ ] that would never say anything to
anyone. He probably worse than the
tenant. And that tenant was bad, bro. By
the way, he was begging. This this
little [ __ ] would not say boo to a to a
goose. A defenseless goose in real life.
But yeah, everyone's everyone's welcome,
bro. When he's when his dad dies, we
will have a big party, mate. A [ __ ] big party.
Trust me, mate. And it'll be on me as
well. It'll be on [ __ ] me, lad.
You're not coming in, you virgin. Bye-bye.
Yeah, he's got an ass. And that's the
whole thing. Yeah. Um I kept trying to
meet him cuz I wanted to smash his face
in um because of all of the nasty [ __ ]
he was saying, but obviously he doesn't
want to meet an adult because that's
what, like I was saying to Grey before,
when you become an adult, these people
that are three, four years younger than
you, older than you, they no longer want
to [ __ ] with somebody when they're an
adult because they're all [ __ ] I
used to have it with American people as
well on the internet. And it could be
verbal, it could be physical, it could
be anyway. They don't want to deal with
somebody once they're an adult because
they can only pick on like kids. So then
I, okay, since this [ __ ] keeps ignoring
me, I'm going to message all of his
friends. Then I made a YouTube channel
and that's how this little virgin come on YouTube.
this [ __ ] That's how he come on YouTube
cuz I run a YouTube video showing all of
his friends because he kept I said come
and meet me so I can smash a [ __ ]
face in you ugly [ __ ]
and he just kept ignoring it and then
I'm blocking and then blocking. I was
like [ __ ] this message all the [ __ ] friends.
Yeah, that's how it started. That's how
this whole YouTube thing come about, bro. You know,
he's an absolute [ __ ] wet wipe in your life.
You know, skinny as can be. Skinny,
skinny, lanky [ __ ] Yeah.
And how does how would somebody remember
all of that from years ago? It's made
up. I shot myself in the Eminem shop.
That's literally made up. Who would even
remember all of those details? See, all
of the things that I say is the truth.
Um, I remember when he tried chatting up
this um, Spanish Eminem worker, Eminem
shop worker, rejected his ugly ass.
That's another thing. Why does he say
that he's never been rejected when he
has been rejected?
He's been rejected by Britney. He's been
rejected by other women. And he says
that he's never been rejected. He's,
"Oh, I never been rejected." Whoa, you
[ __ ] up. What do you call Britney then?
If you've never been rejected, what what
do you call Britney? N
he's such a loser, bro. Such a such a loser.
I think he needs to get laid.
Can't be easy being a 31y old virgin.
Can't be easy, can it? [ __ ] hell.
You actually start to feel sorry for
these people. Do you know that? You
actually start feeling sorry for them.
You really start feeling you actually
start feeling for them, you know.
Yeah. Well, I mean I do.
>> Yeah. It's a madeup story. Yeah, that's
what I mean. He make makes up stuff.
all made up.
That a virgin boy is a big [ __ ] liar.
He used to say, "Yeah, when you when you
have to use you have to have ID." He's
like, "Um, no, you can't use escorts
unless you're 18." I said, "How the [ __ ]
are you telling me you're a virgin? I
literally [ __ ] escorts. I've been
[ __ ] them since I was 17." No, you
didn't. because um my dad uh he he
worked in the industry
and they definitely ask you for ID.
I mean you can look it up on Google. He
talks a bit
like that. Um
so you have to you have to you need ID.
Uh they they ask you for ID and this was all
to try to
make himself feel better. The fact that
he was the virgin the whole time, which
I didn't realize at the time cuz I'm
young and I don't know as much as I did
now. And I didn't know it's because he
he was the virgin. He is the virgin,
which is why he used to keep calling him
because he's the big one himself.
I didn't know it.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. He didn't want to
believe it because cuz he's a virgin and
he's he's skinned so he can't even use
that school to be scared of women. Um he
used to try to find every reason to
disbelieve it cuz that's the whole point
of being an insecure virgin. That's why
he stalks all of the women that I've
been with because he's insecure
um and messages them knowing that he's
going to get the answer that he wants
because the way he's messaging them and
what he's messaging them about. It's
because he's still a virgin. And because
he's insecure about it, he doesn't want
to be alone in it. So that's why he goes
on about escorts and stuff. And I've
done about [ __ ] I used to all the
time when I was 17. And I don't know why
he didn't believe it. It's not something
that people would lie about paying for
sex. And it's because he didn't want to
believe that anyone was having sex cuz
he's never had it.
That's that's that's what it was. Now I
I understand it now.
He's he's a jealous, insecure little
virgin. That's what it is. He's he's a
jealous insecure virgin. You remember
when he was he was trying to uh stalk
the maiden head one suming the messages.
He's a proper loser.
I'm younger than him. I've got more
money than him. I'm better looking than
him. have more life experience than him.
It's like what that Ronald Pump said,
Nicolo, you're better looking than them,
you got more money than them, and you've
got a better life to them, and it kills
them. Facts, though, it it's facts. It
actually is facts. He doesn't come with
him anymore. But
yeah, see we was talking about money
earlier, Nicolo. And I my point is the
whole point with this money thing is is
that okay, let's just say that these
people have got more money than me,
right? But they got no looks, they got
no life experience and they don't have a
life. So therefore, anyone that's got a
less a lot less money than them is has a
better life than them because they got
all this money, but they sit on YouTube
all day every day. What's that? What
would they even be jealous of?
Do you think it sounds believable? Oh,
I've shown 14 grand. I've shown 14
You ain't even got a bed.
You can get a really good bed for about £450, £500.
You don't even have a bed. You've never
seen 14 grand in your whole life.
You don't have a bed. And then he used to say, "Oh,
you live with your mommy. You live with
your money." I think I was about 20 at
the time. I I mean a lot of people live
in London, they live with their parents.
I mean, still people now live with their
parents. It's not exactly ideal, but
it's nowhere near as bad as this
virgin's making it out. And that came
from because his mommy starved him and
his mommy didn't want to know him um and
doesn't want to know him. He doesn't
like anybody living with their mom or
seeing their mom. Another form of insecurity.
Um because it's like yeah it's not ideal
but I mean I can think of a lot worse
things than living with a parent bro.
You know what I'm saying? You've never
worked a day in your life. You live in a
[ __ ] [ __ ] housing with no bed in
it which is what the police actually
said where he actually works. Sorry not
works where he lives. You've literally
never worked a day in your [ __ ] life virgin boy.
you know, and then anyone would [ __ ]
tell you that as well. I've actually
worked, me, I've had a few I've had a
few jobs, me,
you know, and
first one when I was 19. That virgin's
never worked. Virgin has never worked, mate.
What's S? What the
I don't know what he has.
He doesn't work. He's a skin bastard.
He's never worked a day in his [ __ ] skin life.
[ __ ] work. He's too much of a thing
to work, mate. [ __ ] it up.
It doesn't work.
Do you remember that time? Uh yeah. So I
went to um
to our parents. uh you sat at the table
and uh they asked me what I did for work
and um I told them that I was a uh publicity agent
and uh all of a sudden I I went home and
uh she she blocked me and uh I tried um
wondering why she blocked me. Maybe
maybe her parents put her up to it or something. Um,
give your head a wobble. Stop going on
about some girl that doesn't want you.
>> Oh, no.
Well, I I'll never forget that. Like
four years later, it wasn't [ __ ] No.
But what's the [ __ ]
Yeah. [ __ ] starts having a [ __ ]
outrage and [ __ ]
[ __ ] hell, bro. It's mad.
[ __ ] got rejected. Yeah, man.
He's another one that's a simp. If you
think about it, he actually simps
and um he's never had a normal woman,
yet he still sticks up for them. He gets
overprotective about women. He's like an
example, but all he's ever dated is
plastics that don't give him sex.
Like, if anything, you'd think I'd be
the one defending them.
He defends women, but women don't like
him. And the only people that he can get are spastics,
but he he defends women. It's mad, isn't it?
Yeah, I remember that. Yeah.
You just know that he's a nons because
how he keeps going on about like
um 16 year olds and how he tries to
justify it when a normal person
wouldn't. I I keep it real with you.
I'll be straight with you. I probably
would [ __ ] an 18y old. Well, not 18. Probably 19.
No, not 18. I'd say probably in terms of
[ __ ] probably 19. In terms of dating,
22, 23. I mean, whenever somebody would
mention a 16y old, he'd go, "Oh, it's
not certain states in America.
It's not uh it's not certain states in
America. It's it's not 18 here." Like,
he wanted the age to be lower.
Whereas me, I would I would bang a 19y
old. Yeah, 100%. But I wouldn't date a
19y old. I would I wouldn't date I
always used to say it's 18 and above.
18 and above,
mate. 18 and above. When I was getting
on the train and and that used to
trigger Why would that trigger somebody
that's not on?
It's mad. It's um
why would that trigger somebody that
wasn't a pedophile?
Think about it, bro.
Understand what I mean? Yeah.
The way he tries to justify it as well.
Why would you want to be with a 16y old? anyways?
You couldn't even date an 18year-old.
You couldn't even date a 19year-old.
They're too immature.
And that 18year-old, I was just banging
her. Like I weren't dating her. I was
just I was just [ __ ] her.
You're not coming in, you virgin. Bye-bye.
Yeah, big nose this, big nose that. I
mean, bro, I'm a million times better
looking than you. You're obsessed with
my [ __ ] nose, but bro, like, have you
seen your rat face?
Have you seen that ugly face that you've
got before talking about other people's [ __ ] nostrils?
You insecure little virgin.
Are you kidding? Yeah, I know my nose
ain't big, bro. And he's It's never made
me think it's big. It's never made me
insecure either. I don't know why he
keeps going on about my [ __ ] nose.
Must be jealous of it or something.
[ __ ] It's crazy, isn't it? It's [ __ ] upset.
All we got on about is my little It's my little nostrils. You're
an insecure virgin.
[ __ ] tired. I am though.
Like I said, I'm not drinking mom
tomorrow. [ __ ] that. I am [ __ ]
Oh, [ __ ] me.
Nicolo, how hard is the last CTA mission?
Yeah, he's obsessed with my hair yet
he's the one that's already bored.
I don't go on that channel, bro. I don't
argue with people that don't show their
face. I don't even go on that channel anymore.
I said, "Come back when you can show
your face. Come back when you can meet
me. And if you're not doing any of them
things, I'm not I'm not reacting to it." Simple.
He's a coward. Everyone knows that Red
Star is the biggest coward on this
community, bro. Like, he is like,
everyone knows he's a coward, bro.
That's why no one pays him no mind no more.
Well, I like, you know what I found so
funny? Yeah. The last mission, you know, Big Smoke.
Um, bye-bye, Virgin. Um, yeah, Big Smoke
when he says everyone will remember my
name. The story line was so good, is it?
Well, you want to see me do GTA? Well, I
want to do Franklin.
What? Like Franklin? Poor Franklin.
Franklin's Franklin's cute.
What do you want me to do? San Andreas. [ __ ] hell.
The last mission.
He's like, "See you around, officer.
Yeah, when he was dead, he said, "See
you around, officer."
So the the the start was actually the end.
Yeah, Franklin is a lovely little character.
Yeah, he is.
Do you know what the characters called
in Vice City? This is a trick question
for Grezy. Do you know what the
characters called in Vice City?
I bet you don't know, do you? Tommy.
Yeah, Franklin's a cute little character.
King King's met Franklin. Yeah, it's Tommy. Yeah.
Yeah. Phantom's a lovely little character.
I've got a feeling DJ 6 is going to be
[ __ ] I don't know why I have this feeling.
How did he die?
Yeah. Grievy. Grievy. You didn't know
who that was, did you? Hulk Hogan.
You didn't know who that was, did you? Heart attack.
Yeah. It can happen to anyone. A heart
attack. Quite scary.
Yeah. Yeah, I don't think we knew who
who it was.
I actually found out cuz my mom told me
and I was, you know, oh, it was an old
one. I said, what's his name? And then
she told me and obviously obviously I
knew who it was. So,
do you remember Nicolo? You said a
19year-old had no boobies.
You're a [ __ ] creep you are. Yeah,
bro. I love I love the GTA San Andreas
ending grievy. You know when the um the
fire thing falls off the bridge,
the fire engine, whatever it's called,
the the the one where um firefighters go
on the fire grade thing, it falls off the bridge.
But I don't explain how he lost his leg.
Yeah, I don't. But her boobies got bigger.
No, GTA San Andreas.
Those were the good days though.
Smackdown versus Raw 2009. Staying up
until 5:00 in the morning. No stress of
life, no nothing. Just being an all innocent kid, you know.
Yeah, it was good times, man.
It was good times.
Oh my god, this virgin is still doing
[ __ ] live streams about me. [ __ ]
hell. He's obsessed, man. You know, even
the solicitor said this. I went to see
the solicitor two weeks ago cuz I had to
go see the solicitor.
Yeah. And and the solicitor even said literally obsessed.
Actually is obsessed, mate. He
really really obsessed.
And don't forget that this is the same
virgin that called a place. He's a
[ __ ] he he is obsessed.
Like next level, man. This virgin is so obsessed.
He's a stalker.
No wonder Britney rejected his ugly ass.
He's [ __ ] ugly ass, mate. [Music]
I can't even remember what she looks like. Baby,
if you don't find Shel Co attractive, you're gay.
You're a copycat. A sexually frustrated
Yeah, he's a copycat. Nah, nah, bro. Nah.
So, what do you think's going to happen tomorrow, Nikolai?
Oh [ __ ] bro.
Can't wait to go to Thailand in two
months, bro. I can't wait.
You You laugh though because Ant-Man's
not even put up with 1% of the [ __ ] I
have. And he hated flying. He's He was
scared [ __ ] of flying, bro. And he swore
he'd never do it again. That's That's
the mad thing.
Well, I think I was always expecting that change.
You know what I mean?
It will never change. Yeah, bro.
I don't know how I would have done it,
bro. Like, years. I don't know how I got
[ __ ] back when I used to get [ __ ] I
don't know how I done it, bro. Seriously,
don't know how I used to do it.
I don't know how I used to do it, bro.
And I wouldn't have been able to done it
without without the house either.
Obviously, I don't go out much anymore
cuz just can't be bothered with it. But
imagine trying to do it without the
income of the house as well.
So let's just think of like a normal
person's life, right? Like let's just say
what would you be doing normally to
another house? So say you're working,
right? So you're going to work to make
money and then you're depressed. So you
got the women to deal with
and then you've also got to go to work every day.
You would have never been able to do it,
bro. You would never been able to do it.
Working and then [ __ ]
and then um having to go out and then
find the time to do it. It's mad, isn't it?
We are hoping for a change, but it will never change.
I said that to Antman, but Antman keeps
saying it will never change. Never change.
I think I'd be too depressed to go into work.
I'm going to send you what Ant-Man sent
me. Yeah. One sec.
Would you do Virgin boy's girlfriend?
I'm going to send you what he sent me.
Yeah. But don't send it to anyone else.
Say that virgin boy is probably going to see it.
Him teaching English in his little lank
in his little Lincoln accent.
Yeah, she's [ __ ] stinking, son.
Yeah. One second, bro. Right here.
What is that? One sec.
Yeah. I'm going to send you what he sent me. Yeah.
He will never change.
I can't stop. You don't stop getting
that I've got a boyfriend in it.
It will never change. What is that?
You see what I mean? It's never going to
change. He said in his little accent.
Yeah. In his little accent.
Plan B works perfectly. He said,
"Yeah, it's never going to change.
It's never going to change.
You can see the westernity in their eyes.
No, he's not from Yorkshire. He's from Lincolnshire.
Two different things. It's never going
to change, mate. Never going to change.
Yeah, but it's true though. How is it
going to change?
How is it? How is it going to change
though? How is it How is it going to change?
How is it going to change? It will never change.
It will never change, mate. Never change.
He's right though, isn't he?
In a nickelo is right.
and man says the approaching
the approaching videos I sent him are
the same it's the same um it's the same
film just different actors
he said it's just different characters
same film different characters
he said it's the same old.
It's the same old.
He said same ending and same beginning.
Oh, that man's too funny, bro. He's too
funny. He says it's the same old [Laughter]
You can see the westernity in their eyes. You know,
it's never going to change. There's the change.
One second. Are you still there, Nicola?
I'm going to get it where he's saying it.
And man says that I'll never change. He
says it will never change and you will never change.
One second. Let me get up. Why did you
Hey, click on the um link that I sent you, Greavesy.
Do you remember when he said Nicolo,
even if I have to [ __ ] their kids to
[ __ ] them? Do you remember when he said
that, Nicolo? He said, even if he needs
to do their kids to do them. That was
mad, didn't it? Yeah.
[ __ ] funny. It's [ __ ] it.
Right. Click click the link I sent
Greavesy and tell me what you think.
He's right in it.
That man's a troll there. throwing it.
He said, he said to me, "Look how many
Americans you've met in London. It's
like you didn't even need to go to
America. It's like they came to you.
They done you a favor by coming to you."
when you know how [ __ ] they are. That's
what he said.
What was that?
I think he's What's that?
And the man said it's not a laughing. Huh?
Yo, can you hear me?
on the P. [Laughter]
Oh, I'm dead.
Oh, can you hear me? So, I had to throw some under
concept. I'm trying to still find it.
He said he had he said he had to throw
some underpants out
and man it. Yeah,
I did hear about that actually. Yeah.
He said that they're NPCs. Nah. One second.
Send you one sec.
Yeah. He was saying yeah there
you can see the west you can see the
westinity in their eyes. They're just
like NPCs. He said that's why I'm glad I left.
Yeah. See he said he's glad he left
because of that. You can just see the
MP. You can just see it in their eyes.
You can just see the westernity in their
eyes. They give you that look, you know. That's mad. Oh yeah. Man,
I'm just playing some Franklin.
We're looking for that change tomorrow.
Fingers crossed it. Steen Howard. Oh,
Yeah, it will never change.
He said, "How's But he said, "How's it
going to change?" You know,
how's it going to change? He said,
"How's it going to change?"
He said that you could wear a million
dollar suit and you're still going to
get I've got a boyfriend. Is that true, Nicolola? Yeah, man.
Is he right about that though, Nicolo?
You're still going to got a boyfriend? Yeah, man.
Nah, man. They're not kids. They're not
kids. He's showing me people that he's with.
It's never going to change, mate. Never never change.
will never change, mate.
I remember when I was approached with
Ant-Man, he was telling the two women to
kiss each other. He said, "Kiss each
other in front of me." I was dead.
It was funny. Do you remember when he
was approaching with me? Yeah.
It's not changing.
Do you remember when he was rubbing the
bald guy's head, Nicolo, and he was
smashing the pub up?
He was smashing the pub up.
That was funny, isn't it?
That was funny, is it? When he was smashing
when he was smashing the pub up in it.
That was funny, bro. That
when he smashed the bookies up.
Do you smash the bookies up? I was dead, bro.
And he he was asking for a job at the bookies.
And the guy was like, "Since you're
addicted to to the machines, it's
probably best that you don't work here."
He's funny, brother. It
What do you mean things What do you mean
things will never change?
So, what's what's pl what's plan B?
Nah, it wasn't Non's videos, bro. It wasn't.
Obviously, it wasn't, bro.
So, what's plan B?
Here's the deal, Stephen Howard. If I go
out approaching tomorrow and I don't get
I've got a boyfriend,
I'll um I'll give you my TV and the £1,000,
but I can't get it once. If I don't get
it once, deal
sounds like a good deal, isn't it?
How's that for a deal? Huh?
So, what's plan B anyways, Nicolola?
Give me some advice without trolling.
There we go. So, we might not even get
I've got a boyfriend tomorrow. Yeah.
Hopefully we don't get it tomorrow.
Maybe it will change tomorrow. It will never change.
He said it will never change.
I'm dead far.
Who do you think would win in a fight,
me or Ant-Man?
Ant-Man would beat me, bro.
You remember when he um put that thing
on his channel when he got trolled for
it, Nicolo? Where he got with a girl and
she was underage and he didn't know and
he went to court and then like people
started commenting and he deleted it. He
deleted the video. Do you remember?
Yeah. Do you remember that video?
I looked his name up. He's He's been
done a few times, hasn't he?
He's got like I think he said he's got
like 27 convictions. [Music]
I wonder how he done prison.
I wonder how he coped.
No, he's my friend.
[ __ ] that. [ __ ] [ __ ] that.
No, he's my friend and man.
Nah, it's not fun. When you actually do
hear it is annoying.
It ain't It ain't It ain't funny, bro. Nah,
it's funny until you actually start
hearing it again and it's and it's when
you hear it sober, it's so [ __ ] annoying
cuz it gives you a taste of what it's
always going to be like in this country.
I still got the approach where I approached USA,
do you want my number?
I said, sure.
I even went to different cities to try
to stop hearing the boyfriend [ __ ] Nicolo. And
I still kept hearing it,
waiting for that change.
You just will never stop hearing it.
It's so [ __ ] annoying, bro. Oh, it's annoying.
I even travel to different cities to to
try to stop hearing it.
[ __ ] you hear it everywhere. It's annoying.
You know, it's not fun when you're
hearing it. It is annoying, bro.
I probably won't even go out tomorrow to
be honest, bro. I can't be asked.
It's It's not It's I'm not laugh. Even
when I watch videos, it annoys me, bro.
I hate hearing it. even happening to
other people. It's [ __ ] annoying.
And it's not And they don't have
boyfriends. They generally don't have boyfriends, bro.
It's full of [ __ ] They ain't got boyfriends.
They're just not interested in this country.
But I mean, it's okay not to have kids,
you know what I mean, Nicolo? I mean,
John Cena don't have kids.
So, I mean, it depends how you look at
it. There's a lot of people that don't have kids. Yeah.
There's no famous people that don't have kids, you know.
You remember the [ __ ] in the Weather Spoons, Nicolola?
the 250 lb blow drop.
Oh yeah, bro.
Crazy times, eh?
looking for that change. Uh,
I feel normal tomorrow.
I hate that boyfriend [ __ ] man. I hate it.
Gets me down.
Yeah. Well, you better start having them
soon, otherwise it'll be too late.
Uh, I've never wanted kids, luckily.
But if I did want kids, I'd be [ __ ]
I'd have to like adopt.
I'd have to adopt some kids.
If I If I wanted kids, I'd have to
[ __ ] approach every single day and
probably end up sectioned.
I don't I've never wanted kids.
Oh, the good old American Nicolai. I
don't know. I'd have to No, seriously.
I'd probably have to adopt if I actually
wanted kids. I'd probably have to adopt.
Yeah, I'd have to adopt. I'd be [ __ ]
Imagine that, bro. Like, if people that
actually want kids, you can't even have
a kid if you actually wanted a kid because
cuz of the um boyfriend [ __ ] You can't
even [ __ ] stop hearing I have a
boyfriend, let alone get in a [ __ ]
relationship to have kids.
So lucky I never wanted kids. You [Music]
know it's better.
Yeah, it went numb from the [ __ ] Nicolo.
So, why didn't things work out with Sig then, Nicolo?
Why didn't things work out between me and Sig?
What happened there?
What? What happened between me and S
Nicolo? Why didn't it work?
How do you How do you know she wasn't my
mama? Yeah, but you don't know that.
Could have been my mama. Huh?
You don't you don't know that though.
How do you know that?
Yeah, but you don't know who my mama is.
Sick sick level of you know. Yeah.
Yeah, she did. She had big boobs. Hello. You know,
sign up Peter Belly's mama.
Why do you come on with your silly
comments? Trying to w me up with it. Huh?
Yeah, she did have milk. She had big boobs.
You remember the swan? I had two one
night stands. I had a one night stand
one and then I had another one.
Do you remember Nicolola?
Two one night standing space. I had a
one night stand on my birthday from the swan.
Now I don't watch porn anymore cuz it
keeps asking you to [ __ ]
verify your age over and over and over
again. It's [ __ ] The whole government thing.
I had one sound on my birthday two years ago.
It was fun, man. Oh yeah,
she was wanking my dick. Yeah.
Madness to say
I don't I didn't like John Cena's
finishing move though. I think it was
whack. That's the only thing.
There's so many
good like my I think my my favorite finishes. Yeah,
it's got to be um
the stunner and probably the pedigree.
I think that's the that's my two favorite ones. That [ __ ] that. Um
I didn't like his finishing move.
I think it was whack, bro.
Oh, yeah. The only fans won.
Yeah, it was good, isn't it?
She used to come around and satisfy
Peter Belly's needs.
She used to just drive to me. I used to
just pay her. I used to win money all
the time at the casino. She used to We
used to [ __ ]
But yeah, his his finisher was [ __ ]
John Cena's finisher was just [ __ ]
I didn't like his finisher, bro. What
the [ __ ] is that?
That could barely I I didn't like the
finisher, man. What was it called again?
Can't even remember what I know what it
is, but I forget what it's called.
STFU or some [ __ ]
I forgot what it was called.
Yeah, I didn't like the finisher, bro.
His finisher could have been better.
I'd say the pedigree and the stun is the best.
I think so.
I just Yeah,
I don't know how the Undertaker done
that for so long. I would have laughed.
That's why I could never act cuz I know
I just end up laughing.
I would just end up laughing here. Nah,
that's why I can never act.
Yeah. Yeah. I used to like CM Punk. He
was all right. Yeah.
Yeah. I used to like Edge as well.
I used to like Edge. Um, yeah.
Yeah, Edge was good, too.
Don't think he's still there. Probably
not. But yeah, CM Punk, I think he's
still there now.
Imagine me and USA. Is he watching
wrestling together, Nicolo?
Cute, isn't it?
Yeah. I don't really know much about
him. I know who it is, but
Yeah. Did you like that video of me
getting a [ __ ] Steven Howard.
Yeah. It's a good video, is it?
Yeah, I've had a lot of [ __ ] in my life. Me.
Imagine trying to get a [ __ ] now though, Nicolo.
Without using an escort, huh? Good luck with that. No way.
Nah, you wouldn't be able to, bro.
Nah. No way.
No way, bro.
Do you know Sheamus Nicolo?
He gives me jokes. That's Sheamus, but
he's so pale.
Yeah, but I [ __ ] her a few times
and she sucked my dick a few times as well. So
when I tried to meet that Nottingham one
again, she said she had a boyfriend. I
was like, "What the fuck?"
Uh, but I [ __ ] her. No, but I got with
her a couple of months ago,
so I [ __ ] her a few times, so no,
my victim. Well, what about my mama, Nicolo? Huh?
What about my mama?
No, I'm kind of done with it. I'm not
going out tomorrow, bro. I don't think I
can be bothered. I already got a few
numbers. I'm not I'm not doing it.
I'm not going out tomorrow. I can't be
asked with it anymore, bro.
I can't be [ __ ] I'm tired.
I'm just going to watch the football.
tomorrow, bro. I can't be bothered to go out again.
No, I can't be bothered, bro.
I got five numbers. I'll just have to
try and message him again.
to go to this place.
Yeah, I tried two years without a shag
before. I tried two years in London. Yeah,
I I I went out two years in London,
right? I got [ __ ] all. Then I went
Manchester, I got laid and I come back
to London. and didn't get anything for
like another 6 months. Then I met my mama.
Then when I came back from Manchester,
that's how I met my mama. No.
Can this Indonesian guy stop asking me
to go out with him?
But yeah, I was I've been on a two-year
dry spell before Manchester.
So, it's been a lot worse than [ __ ] a
year, mate. Trust me,
it's not easy. You can't even get laid
barely in this country, bro. It's depressing.
Yeah. The 19year-old was good at sucking
my dick. She was.
I used to tell her to come around. and
she used to meet the tenants, eat food,
and she would just give me a [ __ ]
It probably won't happen again. I don't
have the energy to do it anymore. I keep
going out, wasting time, wasting money.
I ain't got the energy for it. I've
already been laid. I've already had [ __ ] So,
I don't care anymore, bro.
I go out and when I can be bothered, but
it probably won't ever happen again.
It's gotten worse.
But that one in Nottingham, she was good
at giving low jobs as well.
So the 19year-old had like a small
mouth. So like my big dick, all you
would see is my big dick in her mouth.
And she was struggling some of the time.
And I used to just [ __ ] her face, bro.
It was hot.
I don't know how I I don't know how I
used to do it, bro. I don't know how I
used to do the traveling. I don't know
how the [ __ ] I used to do it.
Cuz like how I'm feeling now. I went out
in Manchester, I I I drunk two days in a row rum.
And when I was staying near um Old
Trafford, Yeah. I went two nights on the
piss drinking rum.
And I traveled all the way back. I don't
know how I used to do it when I was
coming back from Birmingham. I don't
know how I used to do it, bro. I swear.
I was like, "Fuck." Can B even do Birmingham nowadays?
Takes his toll on you. Toll on you, doesn't it? It does.
I don't know how I used to do it, mate.
Especially the traveling hung over
like back from Newcastle and [ __ ] [ __ ] knows. Yes. I mean, yeah,
it was good l though.
USA Izzy didn't even have the best hits.
The one in Nottingham had big tits. Sig
I remember. Do you remember the one I
was fingering in O'Neal's Nikolai?
I was just finger blasting her. He was
like, "Oh, it feels good." No, no, no, no, no.
Yeah, we need to leave England, bro.
That's what we need. I was thinking
O'Neils and [ __ ]
It was hot, man.
Yeah, but what about my mama?
Yeah, I tried to create a new chapter la
yesterday, bro. I went out yesterday,
but they all have boyfriends apparently. Bro,
I don't think I'm going out tomorrow,
bro. I can't I can't be hearing that I
got a boyfriend, bro, cuz I'll probably
just snap if I hear it tomorrow again.
I'm sick of hearing it, bro.
That's why I need to take breaks from
it, man. It's annoying hearing it.
That's why I take breaks
cuz it's just a reminder of how you're completely [ __ ]
It's a It's a reminder how you're
completely and utterly [ __ ]
Whenever you try, it's just a reminder.
So, is my mommy an oldie as well, Nicolo?
No, I I only have one mama.
Nicolo, I've got one mommy. E,
that's not my mama. Yuck. Yuck.
That's not my mommy. Yuck. Gross.
Disgusting. You're not my mama.
That's not my mommy.
We don't even have the same taste in
horror films and
stuff like that.
How the [ __ ] can you be? My mama. Oh,
that's my mama.
Yuck. Yuck. You're not my mama.
You remember Nicolo?
Why did me and
Nicolo? Why did me and USA Izzy have the
same taste in horror films and foods and stuff?
But it's like we had the same minds
cuz me and Laney are completely
different. She hates horror films. We've
got different taste buds. Like me and
Laney are completely different in in in
basically mo most ways.
But me and USA Izzy, we seemed exactly
the same and stuff.
Why do you reckon that is?
That's the one, Captain.
Yeah, like the little curls. My hair
goes like that, too. Yep. That's the bet, Captain.
That's the one, Captain. Captain. Yeah.
Yeah, same fins, same eyes. Why do you
think it is, Nicolo?
We got the same hair. My hair gets a bit
curly as well.
Oh, you're looking really pretty, mama,
in your new in your new Instagram display picture.
You're looking really pretty, mama.
Did you get your hair done?
Sit down, mama.
Give me that spoon.
Remember that in Tom and Jerry Nicolo?
Did you make this for me? M.
Oh, I'll never forget Little Cracker.
He's so cute.
Yeah, we got the same eyes, same hair.
It's my mama. Nicolai.
Yeah. Same eyes, same hair, is it Nikolai?
Yeah. Now we'll meet someone.
Now we'll meet someone we least expect to Nicola.
Let me see if a friend messaged me about one sec.
Yeah, I messaged a friend on Instagram,
but she hasn't replied back.
She's ignoring it.
Go get some help. You [ __ ]
Go and get some help. You [ __ ]
Do the nic. Yeah.
The only thing I have is watching WWE
and playing Franklin.
If I was a virgin like uh nonslegs, I'd
probably approach every day, but I'm not
and I can't be bothered with it, bro, anymore.
That's why I take like two week breaks
always like I've got a boyfriend and I
can't be asked.
They're all MPCs.
Scar seems that way, mate. They all say
the same thing, same mannerisms.
No, I'm I'm chilling tomorrow, bro. I'm
a guy. I can't be bothered. I went out Thursday. Nah,
I'm going to stay tomorrow, bro. Uh,
maybe I'll go Newcastle tomorrow. Nicolo,
I just go to Newcastle tomorrow. No.
No, she didn't say she didn't um
she never said that. She said there's no
point us meeting. We can't understand
each other cuz the language barrier.
She said, "Don't text me again."
Which is weird cuz we was kissing and touching. Strange.
Yeah, I put 20 pound on it. Yeah.
I was squeezing her boobs, man. In the bar.
That's way up.
Do you remember Sheffield, Nicolola?
What do you remember from Sheffield when
I went to Sheffield?
Yeah, it's always excuses.
It will never change. Oh man.
Ah, you remembering it? It was funny as
[ __ ] in it, bro. Yeah.
I I'll never forget that, bro. It was
funny, isn't it?
That was a good night out.
It was fun, man.
What if I go Liverpool tomorrow? I need
to go to Liverpool again. I've not
really been I've only been once.
I've only been Liverpool once.
And I got I got a boyfriend there, too.
Oh, yeah. No, he said that if the police
if the police catch him with cocaine, he
said that he would say that he got raped.
Yeah. He was like an Irish traveler,
bro. He was giving me jokes, man. He
said, "Yeah, I'll just say I got raped."
I was dead.
I was [ __ ] dead, bro. He just said He
would just say that he got raped. Yeah.
It was a It was It was It was a proper
piss up, bro. It was a proper piss up.
It was a good piss up, bro. Yeah.
You could never do that in London, bro.
Never. We all got on the piss the next
day as well. It was It was a vibe, bro.
It was a vibe.
What I like about I like Sheffield. It's
good. It's a good place in the West Midlands,
I think. Yeah,
it's good for the West Midlands.
I like Sheffield
cuz it's not as far as Birmingham, but
it's still the West Midlands. Yep. Uh,
what what do you think the best city is
for a night out, Nicolo?
I think it's
Newcastle for where where I've been. And
the second one maybe
second one maybe I don't know.
I don't know, man. I think Newcastle was my favorite.
I don't know what the second one would be.
I don't think I have a second one.
Newcastle's my favorite though. Yeah.
Now, Sheffield's in the West Midlands.
It's like the outskirts of London. It's
not too far. Yeah.
No, Sheffield's the West Midlands.
It's not too far.
I like Sheffield.
Cuz Sheffield's quite small,
so it's quite good. You know, Sheffield.
Yeah, I like Sheffield.
What's your favorite city for a night out, Nicolo?
I remember the first time I went
Newcastle. I kissed three women.
That's funny. So, they were getting each other's germs.
Yeah, I remember that.
Every time I go to Newcastle, I get
treated like royalty.
They all love me there. But in London,
you can't even get a conversation out the bastards.
You can't even get a conversation out
the bastards, mate.
Liverpool. I've only been to Liverpool
once, but the problem with Liverpool is
Yeah. What if you go all that way and
you can't get in anywhere?
You know, like the B like Birmingham, we
me and Monty was lucky to was able to get anywhere.
Yeah, that's what she said to me.
We was kissing and touching.
I I would go back to Liverpool, but what
if you can't get in anywhere?
Then you're [ __ ]
And it ain't funny, bro. I went
Newcastle before. There's some places
that weren't letting me in. And like, I
hope I've not come all this way for no
[ __ ] reason. I would do Liverpool
again, but it's just too expensive, bro.
It's probably going to cost like £400.
It's not worth spending £400 on, you know.
But one day I'll do it again.
I was staying in a Travel Lodge by the sea.
when I went Liverpool.
It's a bit like Birmingham though,
Liverpool, is it Nicolo? They're quite similar.
Birmingham, uh, Liverpool, they they're
quite the same, aren't they?
What do you think?
They're a bit similar to each other.
Both West Midlands.
They're both in the West Midlands.
Yeah, West Midlands is Birmingham, Wolverampton, Sheffield, Liverpool,
loads of uh places. Yeah,
quite a few places.
Oh, is that the real Mark Taylor?
You know, I was [ __ ] trying to help
you all them years. You do realize that,
Mark? You would have ended up getting
[ __ ] nicked for it. You know,
you you you're going to you're going to
end up getting [ __ ] nicked for it.
You know, you're nicked.
He didn't even know what that [ __ ]
meant. He didn't even know what that [ __ ] meant.
Now you're a psychopath, Mark.
I can't believe you you [ __ ] um
uh what was it?
Morgan. Oh, really, bro? That's good, man.
So, you done with lying about uh living in Japan?
You you done with them lies.
You know I caught you years ago by your
time zone. You're not smart, are you really?
I think you probably got um the same
condition as Nons has got. I caught you
out, bro. By your time zone.
You have to wake up pretty early to fool me.
And you know the funny thing is Mark
that you got your nose is five times as
bigger than mine and you've got a bald head.
Think about it Mark. You know
it's uh and then and you go on like
you're this badass on the internet but
you call the police on people. You ain't
[ __ ] If you lived there I would slap
the [ __ ] out of you and your boyfriend
at the same time.
You're you're you're you're a 40y old
man that calls the police on people.
You've been owned.
You've been been owned, bro. You're a
40year-old man that looks like he's got
cancer going around calling the police
on people. You're not about that life,
bro. You're not about that life. Lying
that you live in Japan. You should be
ashamed of yourself. Bye-bye now. Yeah. Scott Jobert.
is a [ __ ]
Should I go to New Jersey and slap this [ __ ] up?
Imagine that, Nicolola, going all the
way to New Jersey to fight this Mark.
It'll be funny in it.
That be content, bro.
Liverpool's not far from London though,
is it? Uh, Steven Howard,
Liverpool to London. It's not too far, is it?
It's not that far, is it?
What do you think?
London to Liverpool. It's not too far, is it? Imagine
going to every city again. Yeah. Nicolo
doing Friday and Saturday. Like Friday,
Saturday, Liverpool, Friday, Saturday,
Manchester, Friday, Saturday, Newcastle,
Leadeds, Cardiff, Edinburgh. Imagine
that, bro. Two days in a different city every week.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
I'd be interested in it.
But what's in Glasgow? I've never been
to Glasgow, Nicolo. What's What's What
What the [ __ ] is in Glasgow for me?
There's nothing in Glasgow for me, is there?
Bro, there's nothing [ __ ] there for
me. It's why I don't go.
There's nothing there for me.
Let's go now.
What the [ __ ] is it?
Never stalked anyone in my life, bro.
What the [ __ ] are you talking about?
Not me, bro.
Don't know what you're on about.
Nope. Never been to court for anything like that.
You are completely wrong. Never been to
court for any woman.
You're wrong. In them two words. You're
[ __ ] yeah. You're wrong.
You're 100% wrong.
So what? You defending yourself is
stalking now. Come on, man.
Stalking. You're always stalking when
you're you're whenever they're whenever
they're wrong, you're you're stalking, aren't you?
Yeah. That's the way it goes, huh? You
give it, but you can't take it.
That's like a lot of people though. You
You give it but you can't take it. And
then when you can't take it, you accuse
you stalking card. I like that. I like
that. It's cute. I like the word
stalking because it's so cute. And
people use it so like
in in uh
they use it in the wrong way.
They don't actually really know what
stalking is. I've actually been stalked.
Their definition is a woman gives you
[ __ ] you retaliate, and then all of a
sudden you're stalking.
But they don't actually know the real
definition of stalking.
That's the funny thing, bro.
It's not It's funny, man. Yeah. Bye-bye now. D do
did you watch the horror film Steven
Howard yet I told you about? Bring her back.
You need to watch it. It's a good horror
film. Lovely Australian horror film.
Yeah, you know, bro. You know, Yep.
Watch the horror film I told you about. Steven Howard
Watch it. Give it a little watch
this football better win tomorrow. Steven Howard,
we need to win a big bet so we can retire.
Oh, did you actually watch it?
I think it was pretty good. Me,
I think it was good.
The acting was good in it as well.
Good afternoon. Good acting.
Yeah. Hopefully me and you win a big
football bet, Steven Howard, so we can um retire
and never have to work again. Huh?
Yeah, that's the one.