Oh,
bro. This is bad,
man. It's bad.
We trigger the rat face virgin. We got
the rat face where it
hurts. 15 second video. I got the rat
face where it hurts by the
pockets. Oh, I love it, bro. It's a bit
it. You done a 16 second video telling
me to look in the mirror. You [ __ ]
having an autistic outburst. [ __ ]
calm down, mate. Your rat face might
fall off, you little ugly rat
bastard. [ __ ] hell. Sort that ugly
rat face out. You look like a rat. The
one that you still
virgin. You got me out now, lad. [ __ ]
hell. But we'll have fun for today, bro.
And then obviously I'm gone tomorrow cuz
Yeah. Can't be holding with these
spastics week in week out, bro. Like I
said, it's it's okay for over a over a
little weekend. You know what I'm
saying? But nothing more than that, bro. You
know, I know clothes was only one
example, you know, that
[ __ ] ugly rat. Ugly rat
virgin. It's the truth in it. What I say
about this little virgin is the truth. you say,
"Hey, I understand your community post
if I'm honest with you to be honest
because clothes was only one example."
Okay, so hold on. So you've got all this
money. Okay. Okay. So, you've got all
this money, thousands and thousands and
thousands, and you've shown 14 grand,
and then the only thing you have to show
for it is a shitty suit. Doesn't add up.
When something doesn't add up, it
doesn't add up. You are literally skint.
You got shown money on Friday, you ran
away again, you little skiff flint on a
grand a month. It's probably triggered
you because I showed more than a grand a
month of your money. You got shown
money on Friday. You ran away like the
little [ __ ] that you
are. You understand?