Yo, man.
Just had the old uh bindy. Yeah, nice [ __ ]
Yeah, I told you I'll be back. I just yammed it.
[ __ ] losing that football bet to one
goal was pretty depressing.
Well, at least I'm not more frustrate.
At least I saved myself the pain from
not going out today.
You know what I mean?
Not going out again with that [ __ ]
It's good, isn't it?
Yeah. Trying to get on this [ __ ] play, man.
[ __ ] depressing, isn't it, man? What
a depressing [ __ ] life.
And they tried to say that gambling is a
[ __ ] form of entertainment.
What? One that ruins someone's whole [ __ ] mood.
Yeah, that's so entertaining, isn't it? losing
140 pounds in one go.
But you would have won. Yeah, that's
very entertaining, bro. I'm very entertained.
Like very entertained. Yeah. Bye-bye.
That's Timmy, by the way.
I've never heard of someone saying your
appearance isn't sloppy.
Madness, isn't it?
It's depressing, isn't it, bro?
I can't believe I was actually going to
go out today and do it all over again.
Well, I'm [ __ ] mad now.
Yeah, I think it's time to leave, bro.
You're ready for it. I'm not even joking.
Yeah, [ __ ] It's [ __ ] depressing, isn't it?
I dealt with enough [ __ ] on [ __ ] Thursday. Yeah,
that was nice curry. Nice curry. Nice Bye-bye, Virgin.
Bye-bye, Virgin boy.
You know what's so funny is that that's
not even my brother.
Well, it's my half brother who I never
live with, who I saw once.
And you know the maddest thing is is
virgin boy. You would never ever say any
of that stuff to anyone's face for
[ __ ] sake. What what threat do you
pose to anyone? Mate, listen.
You got starved by your mother, which is
why you hate people that live with their
mom. This is why you're jealous of
anyone that's got a relationship with
their mom. Your mom starved you. Yeah.
Her boyfriend. She's not even that big.
Yeah. He had you up against the wall and
you shot yourself. He literally was
strangling you and you done nothing
about it. But then you come online,
Facebook, YouTube with this big mouth.
You are the biggest [ __ ] virgin autistic coward
I've ever come across in my whole life.
But you've got such a dirty [ __ ]
mouth. It's probably where your dad
[ __ ] put his dick in your mouth about
a million times when you was a [ __ ] kid.
Cuz your mom didn't want you. That's
probably where where it stems from, bro.
That's probably why you've got such a
vulgar mouth cuz where your dad used to
[ __ ] stick his dick in your mouth for
some extra money
cuz you you know you for someone that is
a little [ __ ] in real life, you've got
such a big mouth.
You're not the only one that's, you
know, had a bad childhood. Just you was
a mistake. You [ __ ] Your mom didn't
want you. Just like Britney didn't want
But you know, there's people that's had
worse childhoods, mate.
And you know, you're not the only one.
Your mom just didn't want you. It's like
she could see the future.
see the future. You
[ __ ] hell, man. Yeah. Yeah, literally.
Come on, Greasy. Yeah.
I can't believe that [ __ ] bet lost.
That's [ __ ] depressing, bro. What the
I thought we would have been safe, man,
with football bets, but clearly not. Yeah,
I'm not going to kill myself, but I hope
I die in my sleep. That is depressing.
Really, bro. Really, really depressing.
Indian was nice, by the way. Mhm. Yeah, man.
Yeah, I had the Indian, man. It was nice.
Probably just play some GTA, watch some
WWE and hopefully sleep and not wake up.
This life ain't it. Antman had the right
idea, was it?
Ant-Man seriously had the right idea, man.
He had the right idea.
Smart move, isn't it? Yep.
It's like even if they gave me the 20
back, it wouldn't make any difference
because it's not about it's not about 20 [ __ ] pound.
It's not about 20 obviously. It's not
about 20. What the [ __ ] bro? I don't
give a [ __ ] about 20. It's not that.
It's the whole you just got [ __ ] over
by one goal.
It was the only thing to look forward to
winning. I actually I was expecting to win when
there was only one goal left. There was
only one. They only needed to score. Of
course, I was expecting to win. The [ __ ]
So, I guess I can't even do that anymore then.
I don't think you understand, Greavves.
I was dressed. I've done my hair and
everything. Put my after shave on.
Was ready to go out. But
you can't go out like that, bro. I
happen to think of that. Then you're
going to deal with [ __ ] with women
again. You just need to leave. End off,
bro. I just need to leave. That's it. Um
Yeah. I think it's that's it, bro. Just
leave and that's it in it. Don't look back. Yeah. Yeah, man. Yep.
Just sat here playing Xbox.
I want out of this life. It's depressing.
It's such a depressing country to be in, isn't it?
Such a depressing country to be in.
Can't get laid, no opportunities,
can't be in a relationship.
I mean, the list goes on and on and on
and on and on. It ain't it ain't a life
for a young person. You know, when
you're young, you should be living your
best life. You know, you can't you can't
live your best life in this country.
You know, you can't live your best life
in this country. It's [ __ ] depressing, you know?
You can't even date. You literally, you
can't even [ __ ] date. It's [ __ ]
depressing. You can't date. There's
[ __ ] no opportunities.
It's just like it's just it just the
country is designed to annoy you.
It literally it it's literally designed
to [ __ ] you up. This country is designed
to annoy you. That's what I'm under the
impression of with the gambling, with
the women, with the government, with the
whole system. It's just a country that's
designed to [ __ ] you over.
I feel like that, you know, bro, it
seems like a troll country.
Like that might sound ridiculous, but it
actually is designed to like annoy you.
It feels like it is designed to annoy you, you know.
What? What? Actually, I don't have King
cuz King doesn't live with me. But yeah,
and there's no new horror films on. So, yeah,
you can't win. You go out and try, it
makes you depressed. You don't try. It
makes you annoyed. You don't try. You're b
You see what I'm saying? That's why you
need to meet in the middle. Yeah.
It will never change.
Do you think it will change, Greavves?
Like your honest opinion, do you think
you will just go out one day and all of
a sudden it like by you I mean me and
it's just going to be different? Nah. Never.
It will never be different. It will
never be different in this country.
Nah. Why? I didn't go out today. I went out Thursday.
I'll probably watch Friday the 13th
today. I've not watched that in years. I
can't even remember what happened in it.
Yeah. Do you think one day I'll go out
and it'll be different? Easy.
I just don't see how it could.
Don't know what what your opinion is.
What's your opinion on it?
And actually I don't have king cuz king
doesn't live with me. So yeah, [Music]
how is it going to change? It is. It is
like what Ant-Man said though, Greasy.
How is it going to change?
How the [ __ ] is it going to change?
It's true though, is it? How is it going to change?
How How can it Well, they're going to
ban social media or what? Huh?
What? They going to ban social media?
Are they going to ban Tik Tok or what?
No, it will never change. Never.
I can't do that, man. I don't I don't
get to that bit yet, Grezy. because
they've all got boyfriends apparently.
So, I can't do that. You see, because
when I approach someone, they say
they've got a boyfriend.
So, I mean, most of the time it's sort
of, "Hi, I have a boyfriend." So, we
never really get to that bit. We never
really really get to that bit
because they just say they have a
boyfriend before you even get into conversation. So,
I mean, we don't really get to that bit
to be honest. It's hard trying to get a
conversation out of someone. So, I can't
remember the last time I had a
conversation like that. So,
Do you think Ant-Man's a troll, Greavvesy? Nah.
You think he's a troll, Ant-Man? Nah.
I mean, I can send you
I mean, I done some approaches on Thursday and
they just weren't interested.
So, I'm not sure how it's
how it's going to change, bro. I mean,
the one from Scotland replied uh earlier
and now she stopped replying.
It's always like it's so hard to even
get a conversation out of anyone
nowadays, let alone [ __ ] interest, you know. No,
it's hard to even I was lucky to even
got a reply back.
They just aren't interested in this
country. as ridiculous and mad as that
sounds because it doesn't even make any
sense, the whole country. But I mean,
you got It does seem that way, doesn't it? Yeah. [ __ ] depressing.
Good thing I didn't go out today. Yeah,
life just seems so pointless, doesn't it? So pointless
live, get bad experiences, die. You know
what is the point in this life? I really
don't understand, bro. To be honest with
you, I was fine earlier until that football bet.
I'm not even joking. I was fine. Well,
it wasn't fine cuz I had to deal with
the [ __ ] women [ __ ] as usual, but you know,
you know what I mean? Yeah.
If somebody had a bet to if somebody had
a bet, right?
I bet you it'll be different today.
Grezy, you know what I would do? I said,
I bet you it won't. And I would bet all
my money that it wouldn't be different.
All my money but £200 so I could go out
and drink. And I would approach every
single woman I see.
And it and and I would literally bet on
all of my money that it wouldn't be
different cuz it will never be
different. That's how you that's how you
know I'd win.
I would bet all my money that it would
be exactly the same. I could tell you
exactly how it would go as well. No,
that's the only way you'll um
It's bad, bro. It is bad.
Where's Joe? I don't know why this joke
comes off for a couple of days.
It's [ __ ] depressing, bro. Yeah.
What what what do what do you think
would happen if I run out today, Grezy?
You should sort of been you should be
settled down by now.
Should be settled down by now with someone
or like have flings or like [ __ ]
buddies, whatever it is people want. I
shouldn't have to be still trying in my
time of life, you know?
I shouldn't have to be trying from the
from, you know, still trying.
I don't know.
The escort still comes. see her. But I'm
not doing that. It's too long.
Do you remember that Spongebob um
when he when Patrick was like, "What do
you think?" And he was like, "Do you
really want to know what I think?" No, I
think No, no, no. He said it to Mr. Krabs.
He says, "What do you think, Spongebob?"
who says, "You really want to know what I think?"
I think it's when he was spending all the money.
Do you remember that one? You remember?
I think it's when the when he was
spending all his money. You really want
to know what I think? [Laughter]
And he goes into like a He goes into
like a run. You remember it, is it? [Laughter] You remember?
Yeah, I'm [ __ ] suicidal me.
I'm really I'm suicidal me, mate.
It's [ __ ] depressing, bro.
Oh, here it is. Here it is.
Yeah, here it is.
Yeah, it's depressing, bro.
At least if I die, I'll be with with all
the other dead people, in it.
I'll be with all the other dead people. Yep.
There you go. Greasy. Ah,
you can't get laid, you can't get into a
relationship, you can't get anything.
And man said, "Yeah, if he if he dealt
with like half of what I dealt with, he
would have been gone years ago."
That's what he said. Yeah.
You really want to know what I think? I
told you I watched all the um Spongebob episodes. Yeah.
Yeah. I was one go away from £140 and
when I didn't win it, it was it
depressed me, bro. Yeah.
It's just too depressing, bro. I
couldn't go out. I was all ready to go
out and everything. Nicolo. Um,
I just went I just ordered an Indian. Yeah.
I wonder if they've got their Tik Tok batteries in.
It's the same ending. It's the same
start and the same ending, just different characters.
He refers to them as characters.
That's mad, bro.
That's what Ant-Man says. Same
beginning, same ending.
Just different characters. [Laughter]
just different characters.
Yeah. They they they withhold they don't
only withhold sex, they withhold a
relationship as well.
They also withhold a relationship, a
friendship. They withhold everything.
Yeah. They withhold everything, not just
sex. [ __ ] hell.
It's like this country is designed to
[ __ ] with you, you know.
I can't believe Shbury never scored. I
can't believe I got let down by one team.
What creep Howard?
Who? Virgin boy. Oh,
it's the same ending and the same
beginning, Grezy. It's just different characters.
It's just different characters, is it? Yeah.
The only place you're not going to get
that is Asia.
Well, the only place you're not going to
get that is Asia. Nicolar. Yeah.
Very patiently get Asia.
It's [ __ ] mad. Do you think he's
right, Grezy? Do you think that man's right?
[ __ ] can't even get a [ __ ]
conversation out of someone.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] depressing, isn't it?
Well, hopefully I die in my sleep. E,
that's all you can pray for.
It's so mad how that football bet causes
so much depression as well, but Secular
Slot says it's a form of entertainment.
So he says, but I mean I weren't very
entertained. It ruined my whole day.
It fueled negativity.
Yeah. Form of entertainment.
A form of entertainment. Really?
Yeah. I'm very entertained. Not.
It's [ __ ] depressing, bro.
Want to know what I think?
You really want to know what I think? Well,
you really want to know what I think.
Now I'm sleepy. Let's go.
This cycle is depressing, bro.
Can't make any money.
I just hope I have a heart attack in my
sleep today, man.
This life is depressing, bro.
What about you? Did you losing that
football bet piss you off?
[ __ ] pissed me right off. That did.
Yeah, you can't do nothing.
You might as well just not been born.
You might as well just not been [ __ ] born.
Well, I'll be going out now for another
month anyways. So,
no point going out doing the same thing,
getting the same results,
getting becoming depressed.
Nah, it's no life for anyone, mate.
It's no life for anyone really, bro.
Well, I done my good deed for the month anyways.
Yeah, man. I got a [ __ ] haircut for nothing.
I got [ __ ] a haircut for [ __ ] nothing. Yeah,
suicide's the only way out, it seems.
Yeah, you can't use it. All you ever get
is I got a boyfriend. It's all you get
all your life.
That's all you'll ever get all your life
is I have a boyfriend. I have a
boyfriend. I have a [ __ ] boyfriend.
That's why I didn't go out today, bro. I
just got rechanged. Yeah.
It's like torture being alive, isn't it?
It's actually like tor It's actually
like torture being alive, isn't it?
in it. It is actually like torture being
alive, isn't it?
Nah, there's no point in sending it. For
what reason, bro?
For what? What am I sending it for? I
got five numbers on Thursday. One reply.
The rest didn't want to reply. That's on them.
No point going out to have a repeat on Thursday.
Send it for what, bro? What's What's
there left to prove?
Send it for what?
Yeah. Well, there is something better to
do. Sit on my ass. That's better than
hearing and I've got a boyfriend. It's
[ __ ] depressing, mate. On Thursday, I
I heard it like five times in a row.
It's [ __ ] depressing. It drives you
mad. You know, you know when you keep
hearing it over and over and over again,
it actually drives you mad.
I rather just sit here on my ass. That's
a better thing to do. Yeah.
Yeah. That's a better thing to do is sit
on your ass. You probably got more of a
chance of pulling sitting on your
[ __ ] ass than approaching.
It's what I like. I like peace.
No, I've got a boyfriend. And there's
certain conversations I have in my head
that annoys me. Like on Thursday, that
Australian, she said she come here from
Australian, but she Australia, but she's
finding a place to move with her
boyfriend. You don't have no [ __ ]
boyfriend. Shut the [ __ ] up. If you had
a boyfriend, where is he? Why the [ __ ]
is he not with you? Well, you you come
from Australia. Yeah. Okay. You're sat
by yourself. Where's your boyfriend?
Well, did he find a job so quickly that
he's at work? It's [ __ ] It's annoying, bro.
It's annoying as [ __ ] I'm sick of
hearing it, bro. You know,
pisses me off.
You ain't got no [ __ ] boyfriend. Doesn't exist.
How many do you think lie about having a
I think three and 10 actually have a boyfriend?
I actually think three three out of 10
actually have a boyfriend.
I'd say about three out of 10.
I don't know what you think. I'd say
like it's not even 50/50. No, it's not
No way. Mm-
It's not It's not even 50/50. I would
say three out of 10 actually have a
boyfriend. Me. Yeah.
Because there's no way it's 50/50
because think of think of people you
know, right? How many men do you know
that are single?
How many women do you see that are single?
But yet what? They all seem to have boyfriends.
It doesn't add up. The maths don't add
They're not alone. Yeah. It's like that
one from Australia. She doesn't have a
boyfriend. It's just a [ __ ] line they
say. Boring, repetitive
[ __ ] that they they've been saying it
for [ __ ] years, mate. Like, you
basically grown up with it now.
You know what I mean? You've grown up
with it. It is boring, bro. Boring as
[ __ ] It is boring, bro.
Honestly, it's it's [ __ ] annoying
when you're doing it sober. It's
annoying as [ __ ] Trust me. Yep.
Yep. Cuz their boyfriend don't exist.
It's hard to have somebody next to you
that don't exist. Yep.
Oh, they say they're going to see their
boyfriend, which is [ __ ] It's just
the same [ __ ] bro. It is just It is
just the same [ __ ]
I'm sick of hearing it, bro. Really sick
of hearing it.
But you get people say, "Oh, you'll get
someone. You'll meet someone." But every
time you go out, it's the same. It's a
replica of the last time you went out.
Yeah, I've decided I'm leaving, bro. [ __ ] this.
I've actually decided. Really have
decided now, bro. Like really, really, really.
But I think that's what you're left with
at the end. You either kill yourself or you leave.
I think that is generally what you're left with
cuz bear in mind I I didn't go out for
like two weeks.
I didn't go out for like 2 weeks and
it's like oh [ __ ] I'm still dealing with
a boyfriend [ __ ]
Yeah. It's either you leave or suicide,
bro. That's the only thing. Yeah. Yeah,
that's what you're left with basically.
Same as that man.
That's what you're left with. You know,
boring as [ __ ] You and I have a
boyfriend all your life. It's [ __ ] boring, mate.
Oh, what's wrong? Just these stuck up
women in this country,
whoever you are behind that account.
Just the same [ __ ] we've been dealing
with for years. Ow, it just hurt my tongue.
Just the same old boring [ __ ] trying to
date in this country. Nothing new.
It's not going to work. It's not going
It ain't going to work, mate.
There was one that said they were seeing
someone and then they said they were
casually seeing them and I got their
number and I messaged them. They
replied, then they stopped replying.
It's just the same thing. It's the same
thing every time you go out. It's the same thing.
So, yeah, it's a replica of the last
time you went out. Yeah.
Well, I'm yet to meet one that's not.
They are here. They are They are here in
England. They're all stuck up.
Pretend they got boyfriends when you
speak to them. Reject you. Seems that
they all are to be honest. All the ones
I come across. But I'll take your word for it.
Yeah, they seem that. No, man.
Chbury let me down. I just needed Chbury to score. Yeah.
Yeah. They don't even let you be. Yeah.
It doesn't matter what the [ __ ] you
want, you're not going to get it.
friendship, relationship, sex, you're
just living to be depressed, you know,
especially if someone's like a virgin as
a like if they're a virgin and stuff as well. Oh [ __ ]
But they are all up their own backsides
and then you get Australians that speak
to you and then as soon as you say, "Oh,
let's get your number. Oh, I have a
boyfriend." I think them ones annoy me
the most, you know.
Yeah. And there's someone for everyone.
Oh, how long have I been hearing that
saying? I've been hearing it for [ __ ] 12 years.
I've been hearing that. I've been
hearing that saying since I watched WWE
when I went to see WWE Raw and WWE
Smackdown. I've been hearing that saying
since I was a child and I'm still hearing it.
No, it's not about luck. It's just
there's too many stuck up [ __ ] in
this country. It's nothing to do with luck.
It's nothing to do with luck at all.
There's just not someone for everyone.
It's nothing to do with luck.
I've been hearing that [ __ ] saying
since I was a [ __ ] kid.
There's someone for everyone. I've been
hearing it years and years and years.
And every single time you try and speak
to someone, it's the same result. I have
a boyfriend. [ __ ] this.
You know what I mean?
Same depressing depressing [ __ ] Every
single time you go out, you lose more.
You lose hope more and more and more.
That's the thing, Nicolo. Every time you
go out, you lo you lose hope more and
more and more.
That's what happens. You lose hope the
more you go out and you try. So, it's a
catch 22 cuz the more you try, the more
depressed it gets you.
So you can't you can't you can't win.
You either be bored at home.
Yeah. You make friends with guys all the time. Yeah.
I made some friends on Thursday. I made
some good some good friends, man. Yeah,
you always do, bro, when you go out. But
you can't even get a conversation at a
woman. And when you do it, so I have a boyfriend.
And I'm frightened, bro. If I keep doing
it sober and I keep hearing it, I'm
going to end up hurting someone. But I'm
not even joking.
But if I if I carried on doing it sober,
I will end up punching one of them, you
know? I'm not even joking, bro. It's
[ __ ] annoying, bro. You don't
understand. It is annoying as [ __ ]
sober. It is so [ __ ] annoying, bro.
how hard it was trying to get them five numbers.
[ __ ] annoying, bro.
Yeah, you can make friends with guys and
and stuff. Yeah,
there's someone for everyone, eh? Uh,
I guess that's B.
Yeah, they just they just ignore or say
they got a boyfriend.
It's mad, isn't it? Mad.
Who's the worst? I think Australians, isn't it?
Yeah, I think Australians are the worst. Yeah.
[ __ ] I got a boyfriend. [ __ ] off.
Swear if I hear that one more time, I'm
going to [ __ ] fly kick someone. It's
[ __ ] annoying hearing it. [ __ ] It's
so annoying hearing it.
How many times have you reckon you've
heard that in your life, you know?
How many times you think you've heard
that in your life?
[ __ ] it's so annoying.
I have a boyfriend. No, I have a
boyfriend. I have a boyfriend. That's
all we ever [ __ ]
know what I mean.
[ __ ] hope I just die in my sleep. But honestly,
that football bet tipped me over the
edge as well. Enough to get anyone down.
[ __ ] probably more than a million times.
Probably more than a million times.
And that's all I would have heard today
if I went out. So I got a lucky escape. Really
mad. How you can look normal, dress
normal, smell good, and you can't even
get a conversation. It's madness.
All you ever get is I got a boyfriend. Emily,
bye. Bye-bye. It's my stick. Yeah.
All you ever get is I have a boyfriend.
It's mad, isn't it? You never stop hearing that.
You never stop hearing that, bro. Yeah,
it's [ __ ] up top of that.
They ain't got no boyfriends. People
from Ukraine are saying it now as well.
Yeah, even people from Ukraine are
saying it now. Um, Nicolo,
they are for me. They're just not
interested in this country. It's what my
friend said. He said that they're just
not interested in this country. Yeah.
They're just not interested in this country.
Yeah, he's right.
[ __ ] hell, man.
Yep. It will never change. Never.
How is it going to change?
he Ant-Man said, "I watched your videos.
It's just the same shit." Yeah.
He said, "I've watched your videos. It's
just the same [ __ ]
But how is it going to change though? How?
Because what he means by that is like
how like he means how in what circumst
what example is it going to change? Tik
Tok's out there, Instagram's there. What
what's going to change? What like you're
going to go out and suddenly it's not
going to happen?
How is How is it going to change?
How is it going to change? It's true
though. It's It will never change, bro.
It will never change.
It's just the same [ __ ] That's why he
says he doesn't watch my approaching
videos anymore because it's the same [ __ ]
He said, "Once you've seen one, you've
seen them all." He said, "Same same
ending, same start, just different characters.
I'm I I actually think I'm just going to
give up here right now. Honestly,
I think we really really need plan B
now, bro. This is really like I can't
keep doing this, man.
It's not going to
you're not going to, you know,
it's not going to change. You either
stay in board or you go out try and make
yourself more depressed or you leave.
That's it, bro. That like that's where we're at.
That seems to be where we're at here.
You know what I mean? That's just where
we're at in it.
Yeah. That's where we're at, bro.
I hate that boyfriend [ __ ] mate. I hate
it more than anyone. I hate it, bro. [Music]
Yeah. Well, nothing's ever nothing's
good in my life.
I wish I'd never been [ __ ] born,
mate. This this is a depressing life, bro.
This ain't a life for anyone.
I guess I could just be dead, man. It's like [ __ ]
Nothing. Nothing. Life has nothing to offer.
You can't get laid.
You can't get a friendship. You can't
get a relationship. Gambling's
everywhere. The system's [ __ ] You
can't make money. There's not really
anything to be here for.
There's nothing really to be here for to be honest.
Can't even get a date.
Should be on a date this week. Yeah.
[ __ ] Monty, man. [ __ ] him.
But nothing good has happened in my
life. So I want out of this [ __ ] life,
bro. I'm getting old now anyways, man. I
don't have as much energy anymore
as I used to.
No, it's not a blessing for me. It's [ __ ] torture.
When I went out Thursday, it was torture
here when I have a boyfriend. I have a
boyfriend. I have a boyfriend. It's
[ __ ] torture. I wouldn't call that a
bless a blessing. It's [ __ ] depressing.
That's what it is. It's [ __ ]
depressing. [ __ ] hearing it. Sober.
Hearing it is so annoying.
30 soon. Nowhere near 30.
I'm nowhere near 30, mate. Another just
two and a half years. I'm nowhere near 30.
I don't know why people think 27 is near
30, but for some reason they do, but it really isn't.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I won't be out now anyways for
yeah about a month.
I mean I got enough numbers on my phone
anyways. So a month minimum.
Yeah minimum. Bro,
it's too depressing
to go out and keep trying and getting
the same [ __ ] week in week out. Week in
week in week out. Week in week out
expecting that change but that change never happens.
That change never happens.
Now I just feel like gambling all my money.
I don't even gamble anymore. I only bet
on the football now, but
I'm not going to do it anyways. But
feels like we're reliving like a year
and a half ago.
It's like a year and a half ago all over again.
Life is [ __ ]
I hate life. I hate living.
No, I can't I can't bang a mil, bro. I
can't get a mil. I'm too young for them. Ask them.
I'm too young for them, bro.
They wouldn't get with me. I'm too young for them.
Mad. You can be like normal looking or
decent looking and smell good and look
good and you can't even get in a relationship.
[ __ ] hell, man. What's it going to be
like in 30 years?
What's it going to be like in 30 years? You reckon?
What do you reckon it'll be like in 30 years?
I can't believe Shbury never scored.
I actually can't believe they never
scored, man. Did you think they were
going to score? I thought they were
going to score.
Yeah, I got some Chucky caps coming. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm I'm human as well.
No, I don't feel better. Hopefully, I
die in my sleep. Yeah.
What do you reckon we h What happens
after we die?
I think we just It's like before we were born maybe. Yeah. Yeah,
it's [ __ ] depressing, bro. I don't
think I can bet on the football again, bro.
That is depressing, isn't it?
That was fate.
I could have done with that £140.
I could have done with that 140 quid,
mate. And I'm pretty sure you could have as well.
I can't believe that, bro.
That is [ __ ] depressing.
I could have done with that £140.
really could have. Yeah. Yep.
I want to go back to that betting shop
and smash it up, bro. It's annoying.
It is [ __ ] annoying, bro. Yep.
I can't believe they didn't score.
This bad, isn't it?
It ruined my whole day.
It actually ruined the whole day. But
then secular slot says it's a form of entertainment
in his little Glaswegian accent. He says
it's a form of entertainment.
What's entertaining about getting your
ass [ __ ] I bet I don't I don't know
what's entertaining about about that.
But I won't be out for a month now anyways, so be bothered. [Applause]
Yeah, I can't be bothered, mate. I'm
done here now. When I say a month minimum. Yeah. >> Yeah. bad.
How's it going to change? Huh?
I just had an Indian. I've already ate.
Oh, Nicolo, that rum [ __ ] me up, you
know, man. It made me so hungry the next day.
It made me so hungry the next day. It did.
No, I just had [ __ ] Guinness and
white rum. I didn't mix them. It was the
[ __ ] rum. The white rum makes you so
hungry the next day.
That's why I stopped drinking spirits.
I'm still not 100% today either. I'm
like 90% better, but I'm still [ __ ]
from Thursday a little bit. It's [ __ ] mad, bro. Yeah.
Makes you [ __ ] the next day.
See, Guinness, you don't get the
hangovers with the Guinness.
You don't get it with Guinness. You
don't get hangovers or anything like
that with beer.
That white rum is so strong.
So, if you go to the Simmons, Yeah. the
rum is 2 pound50.
So, I was, "Oh, let me just get rum.
It's cheap. 2 pound50."
£250 for some rum.
And then the next day you're [ __ ]
It makes you [ __ ] as well. Yeah.
Yeah. It's a depressing life, isn't it?
Depressing life, mate.
What about doing approaches in America? Nicola.
Nicola, how what about approaching in
like America? What would they say there
if you're approaching America? Yeah.
What would I say in America? Do you think
boyfriend is it?
I have a boyfriend. I have a boyfriend.
The only place you're not going to get
that is Asia. Antman's Antman quiet. One second.
I've just I've just watched another approach
straight away. Hey, I've got a
boyfriend. I don't know why this is
popping up up on my [ __ ]
Do you know what? It's actually
sometimes it is actually funny. But see
what I mean? See,
I'm going to send that sad man. That's
all you get. That's all you ever get. Look. Look.
That's all you ever get. It's them Tik
Tok batteries, bro. Look. Look at this.
They put subtitles. Look.
Boyfriend. Boyfriend. See, they've got
Tik Tok batteries, bro. They need them
Tik Tok batteries removing.
Look, I have a boyfriend. See what I
mean? Why does this keep coming up on my [ __ ] Instagram?
You know what I mean? Yeah. You can see
the westernity in their eyes.
And man says, "You're not clicking on my
videos anymore because it's the same shit." One sec. Yeah, man.
Same same charact No, it's different characters.
Yeah. See, it's just it's just different
characters. I just sent it to Ant-Man.
I'm [ __ ] going I'm I'm going Asia,
bro. [ __ ] this. I'm not listening to
this for the rest of my life. [ __ ] this, bro.
That man was like, "You should have
left. It's your fault. You should have
[ __ ] this, bro. [ __ ] listening to this.
Yeah, I was dressed up really good today
as well, but
just went back to the old nesticles. Yeah.
Why is Morgan's friend not replying back to me?
Maybe I'll send her a photo of Peter
Griffin. That'll surely get her attention.
Have you noticed as soon as you send
another message they reply when they
should have replied in the first message
if they were going to even reply?
It will never change.
Oh, it will never change. Never.
That's kind of keeping me alive, bro, is
I want to play that GTA 6.
That's if I'd even be able to afford it. But yeah,
I mean, it comes out next year, isn't it?
A fondle. What the [ __ ] is a fun?
What the [ __ ] is that?
What the [ __ ] is a fun door, man?
What do you mean? At least I had a [ __ ] gripe.
But yeah, it will never change, bro. Never.
That looked good earlier. Me, bro.
You'd got I have a boyfriend.
What would have happened? What would
have USA done if I was black?
Would have would have would have the
story been any different. No.
What if I was black? Nicolo,
you really want to know what I think? Greavvesy,
Do you really want to know what I think?
You really want to know what I think.
They're all [ __ ]
Do you want my opinion, Jippy? Yep.
They give up the goods for some men. Greavesy. Grezy. They
They give the good up. The goodies.
Yeah, they give up the goodies.
Do you want to know what I think?
Yeah, that guy is a [ __ ] bro. I'd slap
Oh, bro. I would slap his girlfriend up
in front of him.
I would actually slap, you know, I could
beat him in a fight, right? Is it?
You realize Peter Bell is quite strong.
I would slap his girlfriend up in front
of him, bro. It wouldn't even be a joke.
I don't like men that try to look good
for women, bro. [ __ ] angers me. I
hate it. There's nothing worse.
But to be honest, it would never ever
come to that.
Because the thing is, you know why it
would never come to that? Because what
it is with people, right? If you show
people you're not scared, they don't
[ __ ] with you. I'll give you an example.
Right? On Thursday, I was in this bar.
And he's like, "Oh, uh, someone sat
there." I said, "I'm only leaving my
drink there." And he said, "Why?" I
said, "Because what if?" And he's okay
then. And there was like three of them.
Bro, like people it it's very rare [ __ ]
would ever turn into a fight. Once you
show that like once you match their
energy, bro, they back off. That's why
it never ever turns into anything like that.
Do you understand? Because once you show
you're not scared,
then bro, they're not even going to try
it. That's the thing.
You know what I mean?
You know, I'd slap him up in front of
his girlfriend, bro. I wonder where he lives.
Yeah, but I I'm limited to what I can do
in that situation because of my mom. So
that's that's the only problem cuz
obviously my mom and like
[ __ ] that's that's a bit different. You
know what I'm saying? So
that's the difference, bro. You be careful. Yeah.
But that USA is his boyfriend. I would
eat him alive, bro. It's not even a joke.
Cuz if I'm sticking on someone, you're
not getting involved. I don't care who
she is to you. I don't care that she's
your girlfriend. I don't give a [ __ ]
You are not coming anywhere near me.
That's the way I see it.
You know what I mean?
You know what I mean? Like Yeah. Yeah,
I hate men that try to look good for
women, bro. It actually annoys me.
It actually triggers me. It triggers the
[ __ ] out of me.
I hate people that try to look good for
women. Are you the same or is it just
me? I don't know if any user like that
as well. I hate it.
Are you the same or
so wonder where he lives? He must not
live in Miami then. I'm guessing not.
See, these Australians, they move here,
but then they claim they've got
boyfriends, which doesn't make any sense.
You don't have uh trouble pulling women.
Yeah, you keep telling yourself that, man.
You keep telling yourself that. Yeah.
Wonder where he lives, man.
I'm trying to find out who he is, but I
can't find him.
For the life of me, I can't find him.
Yeah, you keep telling yourself that, man.
Uh, USA is his boyfriend, so I guess he
doesn't live in Miami, though.
Do you remember Charles?
Do you remember Charles? Um, Nicolola Charles. Yeah.
Oh, really? Good for him, man. You want a medal?
Yeah, man. Good. Good for you. Yeah.
I don't understand, Nicolo.
Yeah, people always say, "Don't compare
yourself to others, right?" But they
keep comparing me to strangers in relationships.
They compare me.
Do you reckon that Charles could beat,
for example, John Cena? No. Nah, mate.
you could probably beat me, but I'd give
it a shot. I'd give it a go.
But do you do you reckon you could beat John Cena, Charles?
Nah, mate. I don't think so.
Nah, bro. He's [ __ ] himself in it.
Could you imagine?
Don't you think it's [ __ ] up though,
Nicolo? That this serious this YouTube
[ __ ] is serious. I could have died that
time, you know,
LT coming my house and I wasn't there
that night. I was in Nottingham. I could
have died, you know.
Yeah, that's part of the vendetta, man.
That's part of That's part of the
vendetta. Do you not understand?
That's part of the vendetta, lad.
It's to keep you single. This is why you
need to leave.
Well, me, not you. But yeah,
and she got and she gave that guy with
stupid tattoos a relationship as well. If I find out,
you know, if I find out who he is, I am
going to message him.
I'm not going to like go out my way to
find him, but I will message him because
I feel like Greavvesy, someone like
that, everyone should know what they're like.
But I'm not going to go out my [ __ ]
way to find people. But if he comes up
like her friend, I found her friend just
randomly. So I message her friend.
They want to [ __ ] with you, you [ __ ] for
them. It's like what Monty It's like
what Adman says. You want to take my
[ __ ] money, I'll take yours. You know,
you take you you want to take my [ __ ]
money, I'll take yours.
He said he smashed Bet Fed up. You take
my money, I'll [ __ ] take yours.
It's class from Ant-Man, is it? Uh, you
want to take my [ __ ] money, I'll take yours.
before you can say Mr. Magcoo. Yeah.
Yeah. So many simps nowadays. There's so many simps.
Do you think I'm the reason they broke up?
Who knows? I could have been.
I think I was because soon after that
they broke up in it. So yeah. Yeah, man. Yeah.
You think you could beat me in a fight, Grezy?
You think you could beat Pete Peter
Belly in a fight?
Yeah, that's like me with a 19year-old.
I told her, "Fuck off." When she said,
"Oh, I'm going to block you." I said,
"Bye." You didn't see me acting like
Monty. I just said [ __ ] off.
I said bye-bye then. I'll never beg.
I'll never I'll never beg someone, bro.
Nah, don't give a [ __ ] me. And I met
that 19year-old loads of times. I said,
"Fuck that. I ain't begging no bitch." Yeah. Yep.
Ne. You want to take my [ __ ] money?
I'll take yours. Grezy. Yeah.
Who do you think would win a fight? Greavvesy,
me or um USA Izzy's fella.
I think Peter Belly would win.
I'm big and strong.
I'm actually quite strong, you know.
He wouldn't beat me though, bro. He
because even like even if he would beat
me Yeah. Just the fact that he's trying
to look good for a woman would make me
just like finish him.
Even if I lost, I'd finish him, bro. I
don't like people that try to look good for women.
It It It triggers me, bro. It does
trigger me. I would whoop his ass, bro.
I would whoop his [ __ ] ass,
you know, because there's nothing What?
You can lose a fight. Yeah,
you can lose a fight. There's there's
nothing wrong with losing a fight, but
if you know a woman's in the wrong
and then a [ __ ] guy is a s and then
he beat you in front of that woman, I
could never live it down.
I could never ever live it down, bro.
You know what I'm saying? I could I
could I wouldn't be able to let it lie.
No, I wouldn't be able to. That's [ __ ]
You think I'm going to take an L in
front of a [ __ ] that I know is in the
wrong and them [ __ ] are laughing at me?
No way, bro.
No [ __ ] way. It's like that Polish
bouncer. I didn't give a [ __ ] how big he
was. I kept telling him to come around
the corner. He wouldn't come well come
towards me and he wouldn't move cuz I
knew whatever happened, win or lose, I'm
going back with a hammer.
I will go back with a [ __ ] hammer.
I was being racist and everything. [ __ ]
that. [ __ ] that, bro.
Yeah. I'm not saying I would win, but I
would get a laugh laugh.
Get a load of water balloons and start
throwing at them as well. Yeah,
that's what you could do. Yeah.
Nah, nothing changes.
He wouldn't whoop my ass at all, bro.
He wouldn't whoop my ass at all. You know,
do you remember that dusty showbiz?
I [ __ ] knew it was in a mile off, bro. Yeah.
Oh, one sec.
By the way, that USA Izzy tries mocking
me, you know,
she would like um you know, with this whole
Facebook thing is a game. You
understand, Nicolo? Like they're
blocking the unblocking and then
privatizing and not privatizing. You
know, it's all to try to um
mock me. You do realize that, is it?
You didn't realize that. Yeah,
I would love to slap that USA in her face, bro.
I would actually love to
slap her in her face, bro.
That USA is a Yeah, just pull her hair, bro. Yeah, man.
I would love to smash her [ __ ] face in me.
Do you remember Miss Scott getting like
overprotective and [ __ ]
Overprotective about his daughter.
Remember, dude is funny. Yeah.
>> Why would I get tased?
I want to smash her [ __ ] face at me, bro.
Do you want Do you want to see what I'll
do to her, bro? This is what I'll do to her, bro.
but a lot harder. Just get my hand and
fish and smack her across her [ __ ] face.
That's what I'll [ __ ] do, bro. Yeah,
[ __ ] nasty [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. It's funny, isn't it?
Do you like it, Grezy? Yeah.
You like it, bro? Yeah.
Do you think the [ __ ] would try and fight back?
Do you think she'd try and fight back?
I'd smash her in her face, bro.
I'd smack her in her [ __ ] [ __ ]
face and rob her.
I'll show you scared of you silly [ __ ]
I know this is you.
You know what I mean? Yeah.
That's what I would have done if I knew
what she was like. Uh
oh. I would have stole her um passport
and her phone. I would have stole her
phone as well.
I would have stole her phone and her
passport. She would have been [ __ ]
If I knew she was going to do all of
that, bro, I would have [ __ ] robbed
her phone and her passport if I knew she
was going to start talking [ __ ] when she
went back home. Yeah.
Why do the Uber keep sending me to
elephant and castle? Nicolola. Huh?
[ __ ] elephant and [ __ ] castle.
What the [ __ ]
Did you even That was a place.
>> [ __ ] hell, man. [Music] Yeah,
I'd love to kick her in the front, mate.
I would love to just give a a big kick
up the [ __ ]
You know what I mean? Grezy.
Hey there, little [ __ ] I grieves.
Can I show you a video?
Yeah, that USA isn't he's a [ __ ] bro.
He's an horrible horrible old
Yeah, I went on my Instagram. These
approaching videos keep coming up and
it's annoying Grezy. It's the same old
[ __ ] Same old start, same old ending,
just different different characters.
It's just the same old.
It's just the same old I have a
boyfriend. I'm Why do they keep coming
up on my Instagram? It's annoying, bro.
It's [ __ ] annoying, bro. I hate it. Yeah. Ah,
and man said he's not clicking on my
videos anymore, Greavvesy. He said it's
just the same [ __ ] Is he right? Cuz I
send him like approaching videos that I
get on Instagram. You know, this guy he
goes around approaching. He said he
doesn't want to watch them anymore. He
said it's just the same [ __ ]
Is that true though?
Yeah. He said it's the same [ __ ]
He said, "Stop sending me it." He
doesn't want to watch it anymore.
He said he left to get away from it. Creepy.
Yeah. It's true though, is it?
I said to him, "You find it funny." He
said, "No, I didn't. I found it
depressing. That's why I left. It's
[ __ ] depressing, isn't it? Yeah.
This room smells nice, you know.
I just took some cocoon.
Yeah, that's why he left. He said he
left because of the boyfriend [ __ ] Yeah,
that's why he left, Grezy, isn't it? Yeah. It's depressing.
It's [ __ ] depressing. He said
it is [ __ ] depressing, bro.
Can't even date in your own country.
What do you want to see? What new stuff
would you like to see? Huh?
It will never change.
You want to What? What kind of game?
What do you want to see? San Andreas.
Yeah, but you never answered my question though. Greasy.
Is it ever going to change?
Like, am I going to go out and [ __ ]
stop hearing the I've got a boyfriend?
Like, when's it going to change? You
didn't answer me.
Yeah, but how do you know it's not?
Don't just don't just say that it's not
going to change. You need to
You need to tell me why.
Why is it not going to change though?
Why is it not going to change?
And I No, you have to mean what you say.
Don't just say things cuz you think I
want to hear it. If you say something,
you need to explain why. Huh?
Why is it never going to change?
It will never change.
You need to be.
So what? I'm never going to get So
you're saying I'm going to be single forever, Greavesy.
That's quite concerning.
So, how am I going to get sex then, Grezy?
Okay. Well, how will I get sex? That's
the last question.
Yeah, but I I want to find someone. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm trying to how I don't know how
to do an Xbox stream.
I'm not sure how you do it. You know, hey One sec. Yeah.
Is this Nicolo guy a troll grievy? Do you reckon?
Do you reckon he's a troll?
Yeah, I think I'll troll Nicolo, man.
You need to stop trolling. Well, let me
try and see about this Xbox thing. I
need to charge my phone. I can't charge
my phone and use the controller at the same time.
[ __ ] hell, man.
Do you remember that Joe I like?
He's a copycat. Oh, do you remember that
Joe was saying it as well as a joke? He
said I like sh.
Do you remember Grey the way he said it?
I said you're a copycat then, aren't you?
Yeah, he's a copy. He's a copycat.
Right. How do I go live on this?
Oh, she did add me that storm.
The one that Monty was saying about. Oh, okay.
She's not been on here for 3 days.
See, I'm still new to this Xbox thing,
you know, but she's not been on here for
[ __ ] 3 days,
so I'm not really used to Xbox to be fair.
Wait, what's one sec? One sec. One sec.
How do you go live? I've got a few
someone added me. Bless you. I got a few um Xbox
requests saying, "Oh, bless you.
Record." What happened? Start recording.
Oh, here we go.
Oh, I got it here. Was that you added me, Greasy?
Enter this code. No, that's set up. Link
your Twitch account. No, I don't want to
do it on Twitch. I want to do it on YouTube.
It's in it, Grezy.
Why do people randomly block on Reddit?
Since when did you have an Since when
did you have an Xbox? Mhm.
Well, but it's saying link your Twitch account.
You can also link your Twitch account
here on your console.
But it doesn't say anything about YouTube.
It says Twitch. It doesn't say YouTube.
That's what I'm saying. Look, I'm here.
it says Twitch,
it doesn't say YouTube greasy.
It says link your Twitch account.
That's what it says. Yeah, Franklin.
>> Maybe because it's an old Xbox maybe. Or
Xbox controller is way better though. Yeah.
Oh [ __ ] I can't afford it, mate. Yeah. Oh, [ __ ]
Oh, I love this bed, you know, Grezy.
It's nice to be back in this bed.
Yeah, Greavves is rich.
Yeah, that's weird, isn't it?
You can on um
you can on PlayStation.
You can do it on PlayStation though. It uh boyfriends.
Yep. I'm I'm still undefeated.
I'm still undefeated, mate.
No one's showing me 10 grand.
Why can't you show it now?
that. Why? Why can't you show it now?
Why can't you show me it now?
Will you be able to show it if you go
out every week
drinking Greavesy? How how do you come ac£,200 me?
You have £35.
How do you How did you get that money, Grezy?
I've got about £1,200, mate.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
How do you get 35k? >> Yep.
Oh, you just worked and saved, did you?
Oh, bless you.
Bless you then.
Do you still think I've got agophobia? W
I I had that paranal tentonitis greeny
but that was cuz I think I must have
banged my foot. You remember when I was
like limping for like six weeks?
But I don't have any conditions like any medical conditions
that I can think of, bro, that like
would stop me from working. No,
I mean my back sweats, but I don't think
it's anything like what you're saying,
bro. I don't have any uh the only thing
the only thing that I have
is um travel sickness.
So like say I'm in a car too long, yeah,
I will just like throw up if I don't get
out. It's like really bad. But obviously
I don't get them on trains and
I don't get him on um
I don't get them on trains
or planes and [ __ ] So, but I do get it
still like even to this day.
And it's bad, bro. It's bad.
I don't have any conditions that stop me from working.
like medical conditions. I don't think I do.
But that foot thing was so weird, Greg.
I couldn't even walk, man.
And I thought it was like an overuse of
my foot, but I don't think it is cuz I
do a lot of walking and it never come
back. It was weird, bro.
It was so weird. Oh my god, bro.
I don't know. That was [ __ ]
And I had to go on the date limping and
[ __ ] That woman from Birmingham said,
"Oh yeah." I said, "Basically, I'm I'm
walking a bit funny. I hit my foot." She
said, "Oh, is that why you're walking
like a spacker
as a joke?"
She wanted me to buy her food. I said,
"I'm not buying you food. Buy your own
food." Dude, I ditch I ditched her. I
said I'm going toilet and I never came back.
What do you think of that, Grezy?
Yeah, I said I'm going. I'm come I'll come back.
Never. Never came back.
Only cuz she wanted me to buy her some
food and stuff. Hello, [ __ ]
Oh, yeah, Richie. I was going to go out
today on the drink and doing some
approaches, but my football bet lost.
All I needed was one goal. All I needed
Have you ever heard of that condition? Um, Reevesy Acromegula.
What's it called? Acrogala. Megali or Acqui.
Can't even pronounce it.
I was looking it up last night. It seems
that it's uh quite rare.
Basically means where um you become very large. Very large.
Greavvesy, why don't you come here and
suck my willie?
Why don't you come here, Greasy, and
suck my uncircumcised Willie?
Sorry, I didn't mean that.
Right. Can Xbox. Oh,
what? Queezy, my uncircumcised Willie.
I hate it, Richie. Bro, I hate it.
I hate it, bro. Look, I was watching an
approach earlier. Yeah. And look,
I have a boyfriend.
Why are you circumcised, bro? You Muslim,
I got a boyfriend. Boyfriend. Boyfriend.
[ __ ] off. It's annoying.
Why are you circumcised? Are you Muslim?
You must have been Muslim at one point.
No. Yes. You must have been Muslim then. Yeah.
Yeah. You must have been Muslim.
Yeah. If you've got like um thing,
right, where your skin don't go back or
you really need it, then yeah, you get
circumcised. But getting circumcised
just for religion is child abuse, man.
That is child abuse.
You know, you know Ant-Man's skin
doesn't go back on his dick.
I can't. His skin don't go back on his
dick. I said, "Uh, you need to get circumcised."
Like, his skin that you don't go back so
he can't like [ __ ] with a condom and
[ __ ] and you can't get [ __ ] I said,
"Uh, yeah, you need like a slit on your
dick, man." But he never paid it no mind.
You know what I mean?
Yeah. I had to keep pulling my my skin
back for like 2 weeks cuz at 19 someone
was like, "Oh, you got formosis." And I
didn't realize that like the skin was
supposed to go back and um they gave you
like exercises and then eventually it
went back. But you should have saw all
the smegma that built up over the years, Nicolo.
When it finally went back, Jesus Christ. So muchma. Yeah.
Now, Barquest was a snake. Don't you see
what he used to do? Yeah.
He used to like be all nice and that and
then when Pat Mustard come in, he would
switch. Do you remember that, Nicolo?
That's why me and Monty used to say he
licked ass in it.
Yeah. Do you remember that?
Yeah, I didn't like it when he used to
do that. He used to lick ass.
Yeah, with that when that Pat Mustard
used to come on. And don't forget, yeah,
he paid L J for L J to come here. So,
he's not a good person at Bar Quest.
Do you remember? So yeah,
I would love for that L J to come back,
bro. I would [ __ ] him up so badly.
I would [ __ ] him so hard, Greasy. I
would [ __ ] him so hard completely, bro. Yeah.
Where's my mama? Nicoloa.
Nicoloa. Where's my mama?
Do you think she sucks a lot of dick?
Do you think that USA Izzy sucks a lot
of dick? Nicolola
probably. Is it?
She likes to suck dick.
She's a dick sucker.
Yeah, she sucks loads of dick, man. She
sucks load of loads of black dick in it.
Yeah. She said the slow. She said, "How
many people have you slept with?" I said, "3."
I said, "What about you?" "Yeah, you'll
be my 25th.
The slower the better.
What the [ __ ] Who even says that?
I'm beating the dog up. Franklin killed
the dog. Oh, Franklin.
Franklin. Franklin, what are you doing?
Yeah. Did you really poo on cam?
No. So why why did she say the slower the better?
What the [ __ ]
That's so weird, isn't it?
So why? Listen, why is me and Laney
completely different then? Nicolola, I
like Horus, she doesn't. I have sugar in
my tea. She doesn't.
I like hot food. She doesn't.
Why do you think?
Why are we all different?
Because surely if she's my mom, we'd be
the same though.
So surely if she's my mom, we'd be the same though.
Yeah, I don't look like any of my sisters.
I don't look like any of them.
I don't look like my dad either. So, who
knows where I came from.
I don't look like nothing like my
sisters. The only one I kind of looked
like was my half brother who wasn't
really anything to me. That's why it
makes me laugh when people comment here
and say, "Ha, he's dead." Like, bro, he
didn't even live in London.
I didn't really [ __ ] know know him, bro.
They think he gets to me. It's funny.
The [ __ ] But yeah.
So, what is Laney not my mama? The color
Is she not my mama?
It's that little we Scottish one. um
message me back in it.
So yeah, I've got these numbers. Um I'm
going to message some of the Birmingham
ones again next week. Try and get them
to meet and if none of these numbers meet them,
I give up, bro.
I give up for real. I'm [ __ ] off.
I bet you miss USA is his boobs, don't you, Nicolo?
My ex said I had nice boobs, too.
She said we was going to see each other
again in Iceland. Nicola,
I said to I remember I said to her,
"Yeah, do you know what I said to her?
You know what I mean? Do you know what
I'm said? Do you know what? Do you know
what I said to her?
I said to her, "Oh, like I said to her,
um," and this is actually a true story.
I said, "Oh, can you be my girlfriend
now?" She said, "Oh, it's a bit early to know."
When we were sat on the couch, I was
touching her in it. And I was like, "Oh,
we should be boyfriend and girlfriend."
She's like, "It's a bit it's a little
bit too early to know.
I swear to God, bro. I swear to God. I'm
not even joking, bro. I swear down.
I swear now, bro.
A what a lovely site.
She said she likes my little hair and stuff.
Yeah, I said it on text as well. She
said, "Oh, it's a little too early
tonight. I thought I found the one.
I thought I found one." If you're like, "Yeah, jump."
Yeah. She said it's a little too early to know. Is it
A little too early to know. E. See, we
have we have to think of like old
experiences, Nicolo, because we can't
get new ones. So that's why we think of
the old ones because we can't get new ones anymore.
Do you remember when I was sleeping with
Sig and I was telling her about it?
Yeah, I was telling her about it.
Sig was nice, you know. She bought me chicken.
It was actually nice, Sig.
She bought me um She bought me chicken. Yeah. Yeah,
but I shagged her a few times,
but I just got bored of shagging. I just
wanted I just want my my my hood to
suck. I don't care about shagging, bro.
No, I don't care about shagging.
I just want [ __ ]
Who cares about shagging, bro? [ __ ] that. Yep.
But yeah, I can't do it anymore, bro. Like
sat there on the street approaching
The tenants knew about it as well that I
only would like [ __ ] I wouldn't
really be asked about the sex. I don't
care about sex.
No, I just want my dick sucked. Constantly greasy.
I don't give a [ __ ] about sex.
No, never. No, cuz I'll just use
escorts. No, I was I was dressed up to
go out, Cory. Yeah, I was just about to
go out. I done my hair. I put my
turtleneck jumper on. I was all ready to
go out and then I was one goal away from
winning my football bet. And it was just
a buzz kill.
Yeah, exactly, bro.
It's like USA, is he? Yeah. if if she
ever got if she weren't a [ __ ] in that,
as long as she gave me a [ __ ]
Um, and then she like I had her boobs,
that's fine, bro. I wouldn't care about
sex or anything else.
I don't give a [ __ ] about that.
I don't care about sex.
Well, you done some approaches, Cory.
I miss fingering in the nightclubs. That was fun.
I remember I had one moaning in the
O'Neal's grievy. I was fingering her.
She says it feels good.
And then halfway through she was crying
over her ex.
I was like, "These [ __ ] are unstable.
Why are you approaching Corby? You've
got you've actually are you actually
trolling or you actually being serious?
Yeah, she was crying and she kept
sticking her boobs in my face. And
that's how I got chucked out. The O'Neal was
No, she actually did do that.
I said, "Oh, you okay?" She says, "Yeah,
it's just it's just my ex." I'm not even
joking. She was crying over her ex and [ __ ]
Yeah, that's fingerling the [ __ ] out of me,
bro. [ __ ] off. Newcastle ain't that bad,
man. Get yourself out there. If I was in
Newcastle right now, I'd be out, bro.
I'd be out, bro, drinking. Are you mad?
If I was in Newcastle, bro, I'd be out drinking
every week. You mad, bro? What the [ __ ]
You probably live in the easiest city.
Newcastle is like I would I'd go out
every week if I lived in Newcastle, bro.
I swear down. I've been Newcastle three
times. I liked it every single time I went.
Like, that's my honest opinion, bro.
It was actually good every time I went.
It's good, bro. And you never know
really what you're going to get. So
that's why I would go any anywhere. Even
if I lived in Leeds, I'd be out every week.
Anywhere but London, I'd be out every week, bro. Believe that.
Go out, get on a piss.
Trust me, I would go out every week if I
lived in Newcastle, bro. I swear to God,
would I in Manchester? Nah.
Manchester is just like London.
Greasy, you need to do some traveling,
man, before you [ __ ] get too old. I
keep do I keep saying this to you.
You should you should do just go to some
places like Scotland and that you got the money.
I would mate.
So what did you just do? Approach the soar. Yeah.
I can't believe you're older than me and
I've been to more places than you, Grezy.
Each their own. If you don't want to
travel, just don't. Isn't it?
I mean, my back sweats, but I don't
think it's as bad as what you're you're saying.
Ain't there anything you can take for it or what?
Like any medicine or
Yeah, I feel sorry for Greavves. He lost
his parents as well.
Grey's been through quite a lot.
Well, my back sweats, but not like that.
I don't think so. Anyways,
do you have any medical conditions, Cory? Nah.
Yeah, bro. No, none of the gyms near me,
None of the gyms near me have a sauna,
bro. You got to go like central London
and [ __ ] I've only been to a sauna once
in Scotland and it was good, man.
Whatever you do, Cory, when you go when
you go drinking again, stay away from rum.
That rum, bro.
The ne the next day it kills you, man.
Hungry, tired, hungry, tired.
You feel it in your body. You can't even
sleep. It just lasts for like 3 days.
It's bad, bro. That rum.
Any kind of spirit is bad.
If you at least I just stick to
Guinness. I just try to stick to
Guinness me cuz you don't get the hangovers.
That's why I try. That's why I just
stick to B me normally.
I've still got it in my system, you know, bro.
Even though it's Saturday from Thursday,
still it's still there a little bit.
It's not a joke, bro. It's not a joke.
I miss USA. Is his boobies greasy?
They were quite large, Grezy.
That's my mama you're talking about.
Ah, you're trying to be like a seaside
mark in it, Grezy.
Uh, is that a is that is that a quote
from Seaside Mark?
because he says the same thing about his condition.
He says that yeah I would have worked
all my [ __ ] life. He said but I
didn't have that. Yeah.
Dude, did you do like USA
is his boob squeezy?
Well, you're not having USA, is he?
She's my mama.
She's my nice nice mama.
Do you know what I say to Lady
sometimes, Grezy? What are you doing
sitting outside by yourself, mama?
I'm trying to be like little cracker
from Tom and Jerry. Are you okay there, mama?
Yeah. What are you doing, papa?
Remember from Tom and Jerry?
But no, USA is my mama. Yeah. Yep.
Where's Monty? He's not on here anymore.
I think you like the look of USA Izzy,
didn't you, Greavvesy?
I think you think she's pretty, don't you?
She has like really droppy eyes from all the weed.
You like her, don't you?
Have you ever heard of that condition I
told you about? Um, Greavvesy Acro Megali
Mag I can't even pronounce it. Was it Arolli?
Ghyro. No, it's Aro Maggali.
It's a growth condition
we if you've never heard of it before.
It's killed. It's took a lot of people's lives.
You never heard of it? It's took a lot
of people's lives. Gre
Yeah, it's took people's lives, man. [Music]
Took a lot of people's lives. Yeah.
Can't get over that football bet, Steven
Albert, man. We would have won three
times in a row.
Can't believe I can't believe Shbury
[ __ ] up, man.
I can't believe Shrewsbury [ __ ] up
right up, man.
That would have been nice little win.
would have been too easy. It
uh it was 20 pound. I just needed
Shrewsbury to score for 141.
I had a treble. Both teams to score.
Two of them won. The other team score
team scored. We just needed one more
goal. We needed one goal, bro. But nah.
And they had to hold a half time as
well, bro. I was like, "Yes, I'm going
to win a treble. I'm going to win a
treble both teams to score." But nah.
Yeah. Same repeating people in it.
I know, bro. I know.
It just ruined my whole mood.
It ruined my whole [ __ ] mood, bro.
Even with football, it ruins your whole mood.
This is why I don't really gamble
anymore, Cory, because I just it just it
just it just kills the vibe.
kills the whole vibe. It's just a buzz
kill, you know.
I literally got changed and didn't
bother going out.
Now, you can't go out and enjoy yourself
when you have to think about that. You
was one goal away from £141,
which might not sound like a lot to you,
but it would have paid for the night out.
I would have paid for the night out, bro. You know. Yeah.
I hate losing, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, man. Of course I do.
Of course I do, man.
I like I used to like you, Cory, but
then you never you never met me when I
came to Newcastle. You was full of excuses.
He was full of excuses, Cory.
He was full of excuses, lad.
You should have met me when I was in Newcastle, man.
What do you mean you was in a little in
a bad place?
What are you doing, mama?
You said it all all by yourself, mama.
One second, bro.
Oh, you was in a bed sit. Oh, bless you,
Dad. If you're using a little bed sit
believe some of these Spongebob videos
are like 15 years old. Cory,
I can't believe some of them are [ __ ]
15 years old.
Can you uh Cory,
God bless you then.
I love Spongebob. Grezy. I like
Spongebob because it's from England as well. Spongebob,
ain't it, Grezy? Yeah.
I like Spongebob because it's from England. Sorry.
It's a good show.
Yeah, we got [ __ ] bro. We got [ __ ]
with this bet this week. We got
completely [ __ ] Completely [ __ ]
What's the lineup for next week?
USA Izzy had big boobies.
Right. What's the lineup for next week? Hold on.
It's too early to see yet. Oh, [ __ ]
Well, let's put 200 pound on a
a four-fold both teams to score. Steen
now, but let's do it next week in it.
We'll do a four-fold both teams to score.
That's pushing it a bit, ain't it, Grezy? Yeah, [Music]
you always do Coldchester and you always do Swindon.
Always do Swindom.
Oh, here's one. You're definitely going
to get this one Tuesday. Yeah.
do Colchester and Cambridge. That's
definitely both scoring. I mean,
and then do Swindon.
Yeah, that's a good one, bro. It's an a
boost as well.
Yeah, if you put £80 on that, that's 264.
Yeah. So, you do right Colchester and
Cambridge and Swindon and Barnet 80
returns 269, which is good odds to be fair.
That's good odds.
Let me add a third one.
Fleetwood and crew. Nah, no, no, no, no.
I don't think that one. Maybe, maybe.
And maybe Bristol Rovers.
Maybe you could do Bristol Rovers as
well and hold them.
I just stick to them two.
That's good odds. That is
why do I miss my mama grievously?
Why do I miss my mama? Graves.
So, how do So, how do I get it back?
So what I come So what I come out of her
so greasy. So what I come out of her I vagina. Grezy.
Is that right?
You sure about that?
So, how long was I in a stomach for?
Yeah. But was I in her belly?
Yeah, but I must have been in her belly, right?
Yeah. But I must have been in her belly. No,
I can't believe she put me in care.
We She put me My mama put me in care.
She put me in care.
I was squeezing her boobs for like 30
minutes straight. Greasy.
I kept doing it in the elevator back as
well. It was fun times.
Yeah. So, where's Tam now then?
Where's Tam now?
Yeah. So, if he's adopted me, then where
is he then?
Does USA Izzy's boobs get you turned on, Greasy?
Do they get does it does does it turn you on
a little bit? Is it?
Yeah. Grooy likes boobies as well.
Yeah, you do.
Why don't you like boobies, Grezy?
Yeah, man. Good luck to him.
Not getting pissed
cuz they're just going to get rejected
by women, isn't it?
I mean, I had
Yeah, like I said, I don't drink every
week anyways, Grezy. I go out every two weeks,
but I'm kind of like bored of it, you know?
Going out here and I've got a boyfriend
[ __ ] coming back with a hangover.
It gets boring as you get older to going
out drinking, you know.
I don't know about you, but yeah,
there's no point going out getting
pissed if you can't get laid. Yeah,
I guess the only way to enjoy it again
if you don't go out for like a month or
6 weeks. Maybe then I'll enjoy it again.
But I don't know. I just get bored of it.
Maybe cuz I've done it more than most. Yeah.
I mean, I went out, like I said, I went
out on Thursday, didn't I? So,
What do you think would have happened if
I went out today, Grezy?
It's all about breaking the cycle. It's
like Ant-Man said, you're in a cycle.
You don't even realize it.
If you don't break the cycle, you're [ __ ]
You see how I break the cycle with
gambling, going on roulette, it being
rigged, me getting mood swings. You
know, it's all about breaking breaking
the cycle. You know,
is that right, Grezy? It's all about
breaking the cycle.
What do you think, Greavves?
What do you think USA is is doing right now? Greasy.
probably right. What? Like a random man. Is it
Yeah. Texting Greavesy.
There so many stuck up [ __ ] in this country.
Greavvesy. So many stuck up [ __ ] Let's
see if I get any uh
should I go out drinking tomorrow, Greavvesy?
No, not tomorrow. Next week. Nah.
Probably won't even be able to [ __ ]
afford it soon.
I'm going to do that football belt on Tuesday.
Yeah, I probably got football on Tuesday
to be fair.
Yeah, I think that bet's a good one,
man. It might come in.
Then I'll put the money away and then go
out. Not next week, the week after. Yep, baby. >> Mhm.
the co Cambridge Colchester
and this wind bro 100% mate. Yeah,
that's 260 wins. Put the money away. Go
out the week after with the money. Yeah.
That's all you can do in it. Yeah, man.
I miss USA. Is his boobies grievy? Is that normal? One
about that, bro.
I want to block these [ __ ] tenants, bro. Yeah, man.
Just looking for that change.
I mean, Cory being out there looking for that change.
So, you doing a football bet on Tuesday, Grezy?
What a [ __ ] buzz kill.
You're doing it. Yeah. Um,
you can do it in the in the bookies or online.
What would have happened if I had done
approaches today? Um, Cory, if I went
out, what would have happened?
Yeah, we can all get on the bet in it. [Music]
it's the same old sad song. Cory, you
got Hey, message me on Instagram. Let me
send you something. Yeah. Um,
yeah. My email is it tzpjx@yahoo.com.
Yeah. Give me your number. I'll WhatsApp
you in it. it tzpx@yahoo.com.
I remember I emailed USA is he
taking a baby away from its mama.
Taking a remember that one grievy taking
a baby away from its mama.
Why do you mock everything I say?
Why do you take the piss out of me?
It's like everything I've said you just mock
taking a baby away from it mama.
Was that cute? What I said?
Peter Belly can't get attached anymore
because he's already found his mama. Remember
you used to take the piss out of me. Yeah.
Do you want my opinion, Zippy? Uh uh. Daryl [ __ ]
I'm going to put it up actually.
Do you want my opinion? Zippy [ __ ] Yeah.
We're going to do you silly goose.
Well, I just messaged you. I messaged
you, silly goose. Did you get it? I'm
going to send you some of my approaching videos. Yeah.
You better not give it to no [ __ ]
I don't care if you do, bro.
I send you some. Yeah,
I've done quite a few, bro.
Watch the first one. What?
There you go. Enjoy, bro. Watch it and
tell me when you've watched it.
Okay with you, boss.
Is that okay with you, boss?
a little fright there. Yeah, man. [Music] Yeah.
Shut you out.
I don't want the [ __ ] back.
She's all old now.
You know what I mean, bro? Nah. Nah, bro.
That's not my mama. Yuck. Yuck.
Because he's already found his mama.
Cory because he's already found his mama.
Oh, do you like that, Grezy?
Because he's already found his mama. Oh.
I need this delivery job, man. I want to
start making some money, bro.
[ __ ] store waiting waiting for that change. Yeah.
Should I go on roulette right now?
Steven Howard, should I play some online roulette? Nah,
I need money in case one of these
numbers want to meet, you know, next
week or two weeks. [ __ ] that, bro. Nah.
No, I'm joking. But I'm playing that [ __ ]
Let me see if there's any like slots. One second.
I might have a gamble. I don't know. Let me see.
Maybe like £50 or something.
Is that okay with you, grievy boss? Okay, boss.
No, I'm only Let me see if they have
Frankie then I might do like 20 20 or something man. Listen.
I don't want my friends.
Yeah, they all got reference.
I just sent you another thing.
Let me know.
I might give this little roulette a while.
Yeah, I would give it a whirl.
You reckon I said give it a whirl?
No, I want to play Frankie.
No, I'm joking, bro. I can't really do
it to be fair.
No, I'm not doing it, bro. That
don't know what I was thinking. Sorry.
Huh? No, I'm not doing that, bro. [ __ ] that.
It's not worth a while.
It's really not worth a while, is it? Nah.
Let me know. Let me know.
Oh, I got a little message from my mama. One sec.
Sorry, did you hear it though?
But did you hear it? It's never going to
change. It will never change.
Do you remember? It's never going to
change, mate. Never going to change.
Yeah, I'll get Laney on it as well.
Yeah, but what is it? Do you think it's
ever going to change here, Cory? Nah.
So what what is
what is what is Ant-Man right about?
What is Ant-Man right about Cory? Like what better?
>> Yeah, but what what's she right about?
Yeah, but what Yeah, but what's she
right about though?
Yeah, but what what's he right about?
That it's never going to change. Yeah. Could Yeah.
Could be. Yeah. Or you could be a virgin
like someone we both know. Could be a
virgin at 31.
Could be a virgin.
Could be a 31y old virgin, mate.
So what? Ant-Man's right though, is it?
Yeah, it's never going to change, mate.
Never going to change.
I'm talking to Richie.
I just sent you something on WhatsApp, Richie.
Me, Cory, and USA. Izzy smoking weed.
you still there? Yeah,
crazy. I'm going to watch my mama on TV.
I'm going to watch my mama.
Richie Demar. Yeah.
What would happen if I got USA? Is he
pregnant? Greavvesy. Then what? Uh,
nothing yet. I was going to
what would happen if I got USA? Is he pregnant? Greavvesy.
That's what I should have done.
Then I get some money from the government.
More money from the government. Mama. Yeah.
Yeah, we're a couple now. I sent you a video.
Send you a little video call. Yeah.
Do you think it would be cute? A baby
baby Peter Greezy. Huh? Yeah.
What do you mean? I wouldn't bring it up, right?
Why would I be I'd look after the bubba?
Why wouldn't I? Oh,
No, don't be silly, Grezy.
I would love to buff Shin. I'd stick it
in a Celtic baby grow.
I'd stick it in a Celtic baby grow.
Oh, it'd be so cute. He wouldn't be in care.
No, not at all.
We look after the baby together.
It'd be cute.
Cory, go on WhatsApp.
Why is she Why is USA is he addicted to sex? Squeezy,
why did she [ __ ] me without getting to
know me or anything?
They said that that they say that women
don't want just sex
and they want a relationship. Well, why
does she just want sex?
Cuz if I wanted to do the same thing,
I'd get judged for it.
If I had done exactly what she done, I'd
get judged for it. And
you see how it's double standards, Greavvesy.
If I just wanted to go and [ __ ] a woman,
I'd be told, "Oh, women want not all
women don't just want sex and no." No,
no, no, no, no.
So, it's okay for a woman to literally
just want to [ __ ] me straight away,
but we can't we can't want to [ __ ] them straight away.
It's not exactly fair, is it?
Cuz imagine it's greasy, right?
Imagine I took somebody out for a drink
and I tried to take them back to mine straight away.
I'd get ridiculed for it.
But it's okay for them to want sex or me straight away. Weird.
I don't get that. I don't get that.
You think that's double standards, Greavves? Yeah, kind of.
There's a lot of double standard things.
Why would you want someone to Why would
you want sex straight away?
Why does she want sex straight away?
Do you think that's a bit boring,
Greasy? Cuz most people they need a
connection, don't they?
Do you want to look at that [ __ ]
Yeah, but it's weird. She wants sex
without knowing someone though. Don't
you think, Grezy? Yeah. Yeah. Exactly.
Bless you, Greasy.
You just like stitch, don't you, Greasy?
I wonder what you look like, Mia. I've
never seen what you look like.
I wish women were nice people,
but they just they're not.
Could you actually imagine women were
nice people and actually interested like
not every single one of them but say
they actually did exist out there where
they weren't actually
boring and evil and they were actually interested. Imagine that.
You know, the [ __ ] up thing about this
grievy is that if I didn't approach
right, I would never even get a
conversation out of someone. Like, I
mean, like texts. I mean, like, you
know, when I text somebody's numbers and
they reply back to me. You wouldn't even
get that if you just message women online.
Like, you have to do all that epic just
to get like people texting you. It's
[ __ ] up, man.
You're looking cute. Uh, Cory,
bro, you got gray hairs like me. I've
got some gray hairs now. No,
not at all.
Do you like kissing, Grezy? Do you like
kisses? I like to be kissed.
I used to go out every week kissing
women every week, every two weeks.
back before it was possible.
All the time I used to, but not anymore.
I used to love being kissed and stuff. We
I just like spooning and touching boobs. Really greasy.
Why don't you like it anymore?
Yeah, I used to like kissing and
touching and stuff. It was fun.
Oh, bless you then. If you liked kissing, Greasy.
Yeah, I used to I used to kiss in the clubs.
God bless you.
Are you a good kisser, Greavvesy?
I kissed a virgin.
No, I never kissed that [ __ ] virgin. You mad?
You remember Greavvesy? I like Sh.
That's what Joe said. He was trolling, isn't it?
Yeah, he was trolling.
You like he said I like shovel. Wow. I agree
when he typed it.
Yeah. He was just taking a piss, man. Is it?
Nah, he was taking a piss, man. He's not a copycat.
Come on, man. We're better than that on
this channel. We're not copycats.
So me, you agrees he's going to do the
football bet? Yeah.
Um if we win, we all going to get on the piss. Yeah.
We're all going to get on the piss.
N me and you should we'll get on the piss we mama. Huh?
What woman do you think I should have
stayed with out of all of the ones I met? Grievy,
I think they were all baddies. What do you think?
I think all the women I met were baddies.
What do you think, Graves?
Okay, just just one more just just this
question then. Oh, bless you then. If
you're relaxing, you're relaxing. Oh, bless.
Bless you then if you're relaxing. Oh, bless.
That's so cute. Bless you.
This is what you need to do, Grezy. Yeah.
What? What about you find someone
that you take it slow with and then you
meet another one for like casual sex and
you keep meeting the other one for casual sex
until you um until you're official with
the one that wants to take it slow.
That's what I do. I tried to find some that uh
that take it slow and then ones that are
faster. So the ones that are faster, you
just kiss them and then the other ones
you keep seeing them until you're official
and obviously you're not you're not
cheating. I think it works perfectly, you know.
No, I'm not taking things for a joke at all.
Oh, this is what I had the other day
in the toy carvy gdy jacket. Oh, bless.
I love King, you know, they're so good
for mental, you know, doggies, greasy,
they're very good for your mental health.
I just seeing King's little face, you
know, cuz in the end, it doesn't matter
how bad life gets, you've always got
that little face to look at.
It's cute, isn't it?
Ain't it, Grezy? She has a cute little face.
King of it. Oh,
are you going to get a little whiffed? Graves,
you're going to get a little whiff. Oh [ __ ]
Oh, bless you.
You still relaxing, Greavvesy. Bless you.
Oh, you tired, Basha. Oh, bless.
I'm a bit tired as well. Greasy.
Yeah, she wants you. Uh, What's up? Yeah. Come, bro.
Grezy, you still there? Boss, I love
this bed. You know, I miss this bed.
Oh, I did miss this bed, Grezy. I missed
this bed so much. Oh, better than
sleeping on the [ __ ] floor. Yeah, bro. One sec.
I lost 20, too. You [ __ ] Yeah.
I have a boyfriend. I hate it, bro.
It's just something they say, ain't it?
I have a boyfriend. They're all MPCs.
Them Tik Tok batteries.
They got Tik Tok batteries.
It's the only place you're not going to get that.
Why Cory is Ant-Man, right?
He said the only place you're not going
to get that is Asia.
Do you think he's right?
Yeah, but do you think he's right? He
said the only place you're not going to
get that is Asia. obviously, bro.
He said he's been in Asia now for a few
months and he hasn't heard it once. Richie.
He said he hasn't heard it once. I have
a boyfriend. He said you don't get over there.
You get ahead of man.
You [ __ ] get here.
You get [ __ ] here, mate.
Oh, it's hot again.
Yeah, that bet was annoying, bro.
It was [ __ ] That bet was annoying.
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
I'm going to sleep anyways. Talk tomorrow.