Beep beep. Yeah, man.
I'll be off tomorrow.
off this [ __ ] for a week, two weeks.
Don't know how people can go on it every
[ __ ] day. Jesus Christ.
Every day for years. It's madness, isn't
it? I don't know how people can be on it
every day for years.
Every single day. Every day for years.
It's madness, isn't it?
But I ain't got a life in it.
I ain't got a life, de lad. That's why. Oh, Franklin.
Yeah. I'm glad I didn't go out last night, man.
I'm glad I didn't go out. I'm really glad.
Nothing to hear the boy and [ __ ] Oh,
lovely. Is it man? Just peace, you know.
You know, you just like peace. Nice
Not here without that [ __ ] [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] horrible. Yeah.
And I figured I proved my point more
than enough times.
So, nothing left to prove now. Yeah, man.
I got dressed up and everything for it
and then I just realized, oh, you know
what you're going to get. So,
Yeah, no point
wasting time, wasting money
going out here in England. It's always
the same [ __ ]
So yeah, man.
I was watching some Reddit stuff yesterday.
Um I was watching some Reddit stuff
ask like where people have posted why
they've given up on dating
and someone was like oh like you replied
to one person saying it's not that bad
for decent human beings. I said it
[ __ ] well is you can't even get a
conversation out of them [ __ ] about
it's not [ __ ] it's not that bad for
decent pe human beings. And then you got
people saying how they got friends with
benefits. How the [ __ ] do they get
friends with benefits?
Well, I don't I don't want to know
because it's not going to change my
situation, but at the same time, you
you'd think like strange how they're
saying that because how how how does
that even work when you can't even get a
conversation out someone? It's
interesting, man. Is it?
But I'm not actually wondering because
it's not going to change my situation
knowing if I found out.
It's not going to change my situation.
So, it's just a waste of time.
You know, don't dread on things you
can't change. That's what I say.
No point thinking about something you
can't change in it.
Best quote in the world.
So you doing this football bet on um
Saturday greasy sorry on Tuesday.
Well bless you. I already went to I
already went to the shop this morning. Yeah.
Yeah, this escort was expecting me
yesterday, but I didn't go. Be [ __ ] Yeah, man.
Uh, at least I saved myself some money
yesterday and [ __ ]
Why not going out?
Lucky me. Lucky me.
I'm so happy I didn't go out yesterday.
It's mad how like a loss of a football
bet can ruin your whole day. It's mad, isn't it?
It's crazy how it can ruin your whole day.
I'm not on a 20 pound football bet. It's
[ __ ] It's a buzz kill.
But like I said, the country is designed
to [ __ ] you over. This country is
designed to annoy you.
So it does it does make sense. annoys
you with the women, annoys you with the
gambling, annoys you with the [ __ ]
It's just a country that's designed to
piss you off. The people as well, not
even just the women, the people. It's
just a country designed to annoy you.
It's like a troll country
with the troll face. That's what it is. Yeah.
And what's boring about it is it never changes.
Uh, oh, I was expecting you yesterday.
I'm glad you come on Sunday.
I'm glad you come on Sunday, man. I
weren't expecting you back to Monday.
Uh, no, I went out Thursday. Same [ __ ]
I have a boyfriend. Same old boring. Um,
then I done a football bet for Saturday.
And I got I done a treble both teams to
score. I just needed one goal to win me £140.
And I was dressed up and everything.
nice clothes after shave. I was ready to
leave the door and that just ruined my
whole day. Like I just had a shower,
went back to bed, had some food, play
GTA. It just ruined the whole day. I was
like, "Fuck that, bro. I could have done with £140.
I could have done with it. I could still
afford to go out, but I obviously I
could have done with the extra money,
you know? I'm not on here pretending
that I'm [ __ ] rich because I'm
[ __ ] not. [ __ ] one bastard [ __ ] girl.
And they had the whole half to score as
well. It was Shrewsbury they had to
score and they [ __ ] me up.
So then I was like there's no point me
going out cuz I'm not going to enjoy it
now cuz I'm going to have to just think about that.
And then I have to deal with the [ __ ]
from the women as well.
So I'm not there's no point. And I did
go out Thursday as well. I did go out
Thursday approaching. I got five numbers
only one replied. So I mean I did go out
Thursday as well. So yeah,
doesn't matter. It's still good. I could
have done with that £140. That would
have paid for the night out,
you know. I could have done with it,
bro. I got [ __ ] by one goal.
Stupid [ __ ] [ __ ] in shoes. Bastard.
I've never come that close before on
three teams, but yeah, it just ruined my whole day,
so I just chilled. It didn't get me mad
or anything. It just ruined the vibe. It
just killed the vibe.
So, how am I going to Why am I going to
go out when I have to think about that
[ __ ] If I was already out, then it
would have been a different story. But,
but I was dressed up with everything.
Dressed up, ready to go out. And I was
like, "Oh, well, I'm just going to get
the same [ __ ] as I did Thursday." And I
have for the past three and a half
years. So, yeah. Yeah, man.
Sounds like you meant these spread the
winners before I actually
just thought that they were going to
score cuz they had a whole half to score.
So, yeah, then I have to go out, deal
with people pretending that they got
boyfriends. [ __ ] [ __ ] all that. I
won't be out now for like two, three
weeks, I think. Probably about two, three weeks. Yeah,
I went out Thursday. So,
like I didn't go out so Thursday.
It's a waste of time going out in this
country, is it? This never changes.
Never changes. Never changes.
Never. In this boring country that's
designed to [ __ ] you over. This country
is designed to annoy you. It's a troll
country. That's what it is. this
country, it's designed to piss you off.
But like um yeah, it's if you actually
think about it, it's actually it is
actually designed to annoy you. This
country, if you think about it, the
women, the gambling, um
the government, the people,
the waiting around for things. It's just
an annoying country, isn't it? It's a
[ __ ] annoying [ __ ] country. Even when
I used to go work and I gave up with the
whole dating. I hate this country. I
hate the [ __ ] people in it as well.
They're all [ __ ]
you know? It's not even like it's one or
two things. It's just all annoying.
So yeah, I got nothing left to prove
anyways here. So yeah, cuz if I won the
football bet, then
it would have paid for me to put up with
the [ __ ] that you always keep putting up with.
I'm not being paid to do it. So why am I
going to waste my money going and doing
it? You know, that's why I was saying to
Ant-Man yesterday, this is why I didn't
do anything drastic in all of them
years. Because every time I used to go
out, I used to win money. So I couldn't
really complain cuz well, I was winning
money. So if you're not winning money,
that's why I didn't do anything in them
years like smash someone in or something
because I was winning money. So why
would I give a [ __ ] if I'm winning money, bro?
can't complain when you winning money.
And I think to and I was saying to him
that's probably why I didn't do anything
in so long
like end up in prison or something.
That's probably what it was. Come to
think of it now.
I'm Yeah, cuz you'd go out cuz the whole
routine used to be you go out on a
Thursday and you'd win money. Oh, I won
money so I don't care what happens now.
I'm going to get laid at the end of the
night. I'm going to get numbers and I'm
going to get laid and I've won money
which I wouldn't have got if I didn't go out.
Or maybe you'd win money at the end of
the night, but normally it was you'd win money before.
So that's why probably that's probably
why I didn't lose it all them years. So yeah, man.
And that's crazy. I didn't even realize
that until yesterday. That's probably
what it was.
You know, say you went out now and you
won 600 700 pound. You wouldn't give a
[ __ ] about getting rejected all day,
would you? Like, you wouldn't give a
[ __ ] would you really? So, yeah. >> Yeah.
It wasn't about being a sore loser. It
just killed the vibe. I wasn't
screaming, shouting that it was rigged.
It just pissed me off a little bit.
It could have been three wins in a row,
but nah, it would have been too easy. I
don't know how that I don't know how
they didn't score. They were playing
home as well. I don't know how they
didn't [ __ ] score.
And it was only 20 off like the winnings
from like a week ago. It wasn't even
like I went out to spend money again. It
was just £21 I had done on it. So yeah,
>> I don't think people like me should
gamble to be honest, mate. I really
don't think people like me should gamble.
I really don't think people like me
should gamble, man. Honestly,
country though, bro.
I really do hate it. >> Yeah,
I'll probably be out again in about 3
weeks, a month. Yeah,
nothing to do with money. It's nothing
to do with money at all. It's just I
can't be bothered dealing with the same [ __ ]
And I figured I've got enough numbers.
And one replied,
I mean, you can't keep doing this the
rest of your [ __ ] hunting life. You
know what I mean? I'm getting old now as
well, so I can't keep doing this the
rest of my life. So yeah,
it's bad though. It is bad. It is bad.
It's bad. It is It's the way it is, you know.
But what people really need to deal with
now to be able to have children, is that
what really people need to deal with
now? But to actually get married, to
man. Like, is that what you really have
to go through nowadays? Even to get a
friendship, it's nothing normal about
it. [ __ ] disgusting.
[ __ ] absolutely disgusting. is. So yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. This country annoys the [ __ ] out
of me, bro. It bugs the [ __ ] out of me.
But I go out most days now. I just
chill, man. Playing Franklin. I just
hate this country
for various different reasons. I [ __ ]
can't stand it, mate. Stand it, you know.
Same with America, same with Canada,
same with all of these westernized
countries. I hate them. Hate all of them, bro.
Cuz the people are [ __ ] and the women
which makes the country [ __ ] So in any
of them, you know.
So yeah, man, that's where we're at. Listen.
Somebody said to you know what somebody
wrote they wrote just stop looking in
time you might find someone without
looking in the meantime work on your
personality uh you can't change your
personality and there's nothing wrong
with my personality just like there's
nothing wrong with 80% of other people's
personality I saw another comment you
made. You should also perhaps avoid and
assuming people don't have boyfriends or
girlfriends. They do. Uh they don't. Um
which is what I replied back with. Um
most don't look up the statistics. I
would say more people are single
nowadays. They don't. You know, I know
there's people in their 30s and [ __ ]
but no, they don't. If you look up the
statistics, right? Look up the
go off by people that you meet, right?
Look at people that you meet.
Is it funny how there's so many single people?
So many single people. And I'm not
assuming I know. Um I'm not assuming I
[ __ ] well know. Um because I've got
loads of friends and most of them are
single and they've got no correlation to
each other. Oh yeah, I know people that
are in relationships. I do know people
that are in relationships, yes. But
there's also many, many, many, many,
many, many, many, many, many, many, many single people.
So, I mean,
I'm not assuming. I literally know they don't.
I don't know why we're still on this conversation, bro. [ __ ]
I don't know why we're still on the same
um subject about like do people pretend
or they don't pretend. I don't know why
we're still on this subject. They
clearly [ __ ] pretend, man. What the
They [ __ ] pretend, man. Don't be silly.
It's time to start growing up, man.
Of course they [ __ ] pretend they got
[ __ ] boyfriends. Well, what the [ __ ]
about stop assuming? Stop assuming they
literally What would you say? I would
say nowadays, Grezy,
well, dating apps don't work. So, yeah. Yeah.
Um, Grezy, what what do you think?
I would say more people are single
nowadays than not. I don't know about you.
I would say I'd actually say more people
are Oh, I'd probably say it's roughly the same. So yeah,
I'd say probably more people single or
it's probably about even.
What do you think?
Nah, no way. I don't even see that many
I don't see even pregnant people nowadays. So yeah.
Well, I don't even see many pregnant
people nowadays and I go out all the time. So yeah,
one second, bro. Yeah, man.
I'm not having this conversation. Oh my
god, it always goes, Greavves. I find
I'm having the same
conversation, bro. Like you you you you
show an approaching video. Yeah. And
then I say, "Oh, like you just get the
same [ __ ] how like oh I say like they
pretend they have boyfriends. How would
you know that?" And it's just the same
conversation every single time.
It's just the same conversation every single time.
I'm not answering it because it's self-explanatory.
If you can't if you can't figure it out,
it's your problem, bro. The [ __ ]
You know what I mean?
I'm done with this this conversation.
I'm done with this conversation.
And it's like you can't even speak to an
impartial person as well.
I just like I just end the conversation,
bro. Like when I feel like it's just
going to go nowhere, I just end the conversation.
You know what I'm saying?
They are lying. They are lying. You can
assume that they're lying. I I'll give
you I'll give you an example, Greg. I
was speaking to an Australian for 5 minutes
um the other day.
And when I when I went to ask for the
number, they was like, "Oh, yeah. I've
got a boyfriend. We're finding somewhere
to live." So, you come all the way from
Australia with your boyfriend that's not
with you in a big city like London really, you know,
you know what I'm saying?
Um, so what? You're in a big city like
London all by yourself without your
boyfriend eating alone on the grass.
You know what I mean? Yeah.
Yeah, that's it, bro.
So yeah, bro.
So what would you would you say that
person was lying about having a boyfriend?
Okay. Like that example that I just given you,
what would you say, bro?
That's [ __ ] as well, isn't it? Yeah. Yeah.
Okay. I just gave you an example. Yeah.
That's one example.
I mean, that's an example, isn't it?
They [ __ ] lie. They're all liars,
bro. I I mean, I said it yesterday.
Three out of 10 actually have boyfriends.
Literally, three out of 10 have boyfriends.
I mean, if there I mean, I I estimate
three out of 10. You know, you said
there's a there's a growing population,
but I don't even see pregnant people anymore.
anymore. They're all pregnant, but you
you don't even see them like you used to.
So I mean yeah
it's mad it
It doesn't. How many single people are there?
>> So that's supposed to mean what to me
exactly? So let let's just say there are
people that are in relationships. Is
that supposed to
be relevant to my situation or something?
Okay. So let's just say that you're
right. Okay. And does that somehow mean
that there's hope for me because
strangers have done it? You know, that's
the same argument I used to have with um
hat is you're not these people. You will
never be these people and these people
are not you. So if you think about, you
know, other people doing it, other
people not doing it, is that going to
change the position that you're in? No,
it's not. And then and then if if you
realize that it's not, then it's just a
waste of time thinking about other people. Yep.
You know what I'm saying? The question
was is more people but they don't have
boyfriends. They don't have boyfriends.
Bro, come on, man. Let's not be silly
about this. You know,
it's I would say it's about the same.
No, honestly. Honestly, I would say it's
probably about the same. I would say
it's about the same. But yeah,
I would say it's about the same.
I would say honestly it's about the same. Yeah, man.
that is probably around about the same
cuz there's so many single people like
all the tenants I knew that were single
um people that I've met were single I
mean some of them were in relationships
but most of them they're single
most of the people that I've come across
are actually single that have got no
like correlation to each other, no
connection to each other, not even have
the same hobbies. Most of these people
are [ __ ] single.
Isn't that a madness? Isn't that a whole
entire [ __ ] madness?
How most of the people that you come
across are actually single
or they have the same struggles or they
might not even have the same struggles,
but they're just single.
More people I know are are definitely
single than in relationships. But yeah,
every woman claims she has a boyfriend.
Well, 90% of them claim they've got boyfriends.
Boyfriends? Who the [ __ ] are they
boyfriends, bro? Who the [ __ ] are their boyfriends?
What? Casper the ghost,
you know? I don't even want to talk
about it anymore, bro. It's just too depressing, you know?
Yeah. Well, the the the the bet is
Colchester and Cambridge, both teams to
score, and Swindon and Barnet, both
teams to score. I think it's Swindon and
Barnet or Swindon and Barrow.
And it's Tuesday. I think it's either
league one or league two.
So yeah, man. Yeah, man. So, that's it.
That's why I didn't go out on Saturday,
which was yesterday, bro.
I don't even think I'm going to do the
bet. I don't need to win [ __ ] £300
for what? I'm not going out this week.
Next week, sorry. And I'm not going out
the week after. So,
so I don't even see the point in me even
doing a bet, to be honest. So yeah.
To be honest, bro, like
people on the internet, they attack you
whenever you show them the truth.
They actually attack you for trying and
showing that you're trying, they
literally attack you.
And then it's, oh, how do you know
they're pretending they're boyfriends
when most people are single? I mean,
it's self-explanatory. It's literally self-explanatory,
you know? It's And then you just have
the same conversation that drags on and
on and on and on and on.
How do you know they're lying,
[ __ ] Of course they're lying. I
don't think you actually understand how
many people I actually know.
So, you know, all of these people that are single,
but yet they're all in relationships.
It's such a boring conversation. One
that I won't have to have when I'm out
of here anyways. That's another one I
because I'll never hear it again. So, if
I never hear it again, I'll never have
to [ __ ] talk about it ever again. Do
you know what I'm saying?
But that's the thing with these people,
Greavesy. They only see things from
their point of view. You understand?
See, they only see things from their
point of view. That's why they like attack you.
Um, they attack you for trying and
showing how [ __ ] up the dating game
is. They actually attack you for it,
which is strange.
If you don't lick women's asses and
pretend everything's fine, they all hate
you. They will attack you. They go mad.
Do you know what I'm saying? Like it's
strange. Like you you're showing them videos.
You're trying to
not I don't know what you're trying to
do. Trying to make people understand,
but then they're just attacking you.
They're just verbally attacking you cuz
you're not licking their asses.
It's [ __ ] up, bro.
This child's getting away.
They attack you.
They attack you for trying. It's mad, isn't it?
Same old boring conversation. Eh,
it should show now.
No, it should just do it on William Hill.
Just do it on William Hill.
I said I said to the person, um, I'm not
going to I'm not going to take the bait.
Nice try. I said, you don't know my
personality. You're just attacking me
and making up things because I've shown
how [ __ ] up the dating game is. I'm
not going to take the bait. Nice try, though.
Nice try, mate. So, you know, all of
this like paragraphs and [ __ ] it's it's
trying to bait you.
It's literally trying to bait you. Nice.
Yeah, nice try.
Nice try, matey. All of this is trying to bait.
They're trying to blame my personality
because I can't even get a conversation
out of someone.
Wow. Personality. Ah wow. So like when I
approach five people on bro, you can
literally go up to someone right in any
train station and you can say one word
and straight away they'll say they're
not interested. Where the [ __ ] does this
personality come into it?
Where where does the personality come
into it when you can't even say one word
without either hearing I'm not
interested or I have a boyfriend or all
of this [ __ ] Where does all of this
extra stuff come into it?
It's strange. It's really really they're
so in denial
and they take See, with me, I don't need
to insult people when I'm having an
argument. I don't need to start making
up and insulting people. I'm not
throwing my dummy that dummy out the
[ __ ] pram like these people. They
literally don't go for any of that stuff.
It's like I've literally got videos of
me approaching people,
literally trying to start a conversation
with someone, which is the the the first
steps to most things, and they pretend
that they've got a boyfriend.
What the [ __ ] are you even talking about
on Reddit, bro? It's madness.
say stuff like that, bro. Women
themselves or simps. They getting so
high rate, like attacking me, writing
paragraphs and [ __ ] And all I done was
show them a [ __ ] approaching video.
talking about banging hookers in a third
world country. Uh they're not third
world countryics and they're not
hookers. So what? When you go to the
Philippines and you go to Cambodia, what
they're all prostitutes,
brother, you can literally go on a
dating app. You can literally go on a
dating app and get a girlfriend that
does not ask you for any money.
You can gen you can generally
get you anywhere, buddy. It won't get
you far in life. You don't want to end
up like 70 [ __ ] odd realizing that oh [ __ ]
you can generally get relationships over
there and not hear that I have a boy I
have a they're not all [ __ ] hookers
there's people over there that want relationships so yeah
oh no no no no When have I never ever
listened? I think I have listened to
that many many many many times. No, when
did I ever say that that's wrong?
I mean I mean I mean I I I have
literally said that uh that that's not I
never ever said that was wrong. I think
I have answered and then you've not come
back. That's what happens. Um, I mean, I
never ever said that was wrong. I think
I said the same thing many, many times.
I I literally said that's the only thing
you can do. Whether it's creepy or not,
that's the only thing you can do because
dating apps do not work. You do not meet
people through friends. So, creepy or
not [ __ ] creepy, that's all you have.
That's literally all you have. So it
doesn't matter whether it's creepy, not
creepy, [ __ ] works, don't that's
literally all you have. That's literally
your only ounce of hope.
So I mean you there's no alternative. So
I don't know why why you even say, "Oh,
it's this, it's that, it's this, it's
that." There's literally no alternative.
And I also think I said as well, if I
didn't approach, I'd be a virgin.
So, okay, we've we've established that,
but there's no alternative
because of social media. So, I mean, and
don't start talking about other people
now, son. Stop talking about other
people. You know what I'm saying?
So, that is literally the only thing is
approaching in in in in literally any
thing, you know. It literally is the any
and I'm not your mate either. So I don't
know why you're calling me your mate.
I'll never be your mate. But uh it is
the only thing. And if I didn't
approach, I'd be a virgin. So you
telling me that I'm wrong? Are you
telling me am I Are you telling me that
I'm wrong? No one asked anyone out immediately?
I've never asked anyone out immediately.
What? What are you making things up for?
I've spoke to people and all I get is
I've got a boyfriend. I' I don't ask
people out immediately.
Must be making things up, bro. because
that's not what happens on my channel.
You always defend women. It's never
going to get you laid. How many times do
I have to tell you simps? It won't make
women want you. Stop sing.
It will never get you laid. Stop sing.
Yes. And dating apps don't work. So it
is pointless having the same
conversation over and over again. Okay.
Cold approaching is weird. Whatever. But
dating apps don't work. Simple. Dating
apps do not work. And I'll tell you
another thing that doesn't work. Simp.
So stop doing it. [ __ ] hell.
Stupid idiot on Reddit. Man, stop
[ __ ] sing. It will never make women
like you. It will never get you laid. I
don't know why they still simp. It's mad.
So yeah, if I didn't code approach, I'd
be a virgin. What have you got to say?
What have you got to say about that,
Beige? Man, let me let me ask you Let me
ask you this question. If I didn't
approach, I'd be a virgin.
A kissingless stateless virgin. What's
What's your opinion on that?
You have Do you have an opinion on that?
Or I mean, you can't say I'm wrong cuz,
bro, I'm [ __ ] right. I'm telling you
right now. If I didn't, I'd be a [ __ ]
virgin, man. I'd be a virgin, mate. So,
what's your opinion on that? Something
that's creepy and weird is the only
thing that got me dates and laid
and all the other things never worked.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. You told You just told
me that approaching is weird and creepy.
But if I never done that, I would be a
kissless virgin that's never been on a date.
Is that how you'd prefer me? madness, bro.
Okay, you need to take your time. Oh,
right. You're never You simp are never
going to learn, are you? You're just
going to stay in denial for probably the
rest of your life.
You go and you try to speak to someone,
they say they got a boyfriend. You will
never learn. Even the videos didn't show
you anything. I truly am wasting my time
trying to explain this anymore, bro. I'm
going Asia anyway, so it's not my problem anymore.
It's like even when you're shown the
truth, you still deny it. I give up,
bro. You're a lost cause. Yeah, man.
Keep sing anyway. See where that gets
you in life.
It's not my problem anymore anyways. I
didn't go out yesterday, so it's not my problem.
You really really are just never ever
going to stop sing. It's just it's very
hard to actually find somebody that
just doesn't do anything but lick
women's asses. It's mad. It's It's so
You can't even have like a debate.
I just had it with this guy on this
[ __ ] website, bro. He's just sat
there [ __ ] defending women, making
out making up all sorts about me. He
doesn't even know me.
I told him about a million times, you're
not going to bait me, bro. I'm not I'm
not taking the bait.
I'm not taking the bait.
So, you can say what you want. I'm not
I'm not taking the bait, bro.
Uh sing doesn't work. Women do not like
simps. Women don't like simps, but yet
they still s and they still don't get
laid. It's embarrassing.
It's embarrassing. It doesn't get you
laid, which is the whole reason why
you're sing in the first place. S does not work.
And you'll learn that when you're older.
It literally will never get you laid.
And you still simp. I don't know why
they do it. They stick up for these
stuckup [ __ ] that don't even like
them. It's a It's got to be a mental
condition. There's got to be some sort
of condition. They stick up for women,
yet women don't like them. It doesn't
make any sense. It doesn't I've had more
women than probably you. And I [ __ ]
hate them. I hate the [ __ ] They're
[ __ ] nasty, evil bastards. And I'll
say to anyone's face, I hate them. And
I've had And I've had more than you. I
could put money right on the table right
now. I've had more than you. And I will
never ever defend them because I know
what they're like. I've met them. I know
what they're like. Stuck up evil [ __ ]
What would I be defending them for?
They're [ __ ] pure evil. And I
probably have had more than you.
Or let's just say I had the same as you
then. And I [ __ ] can't stand them. I
don't know how people can sit there and
and defend them, you know, even when
it's not me. I'm watching these videos
of other people and it's winding me up.
I hate I hate watching it. The stuck up
[ __ ] I hate seeing it. It keeps
popping up on my Instagram every time I
go on the explore page. Riz channel
approach riz channel. I'm watching it
and watching it even annoys me. Like
even when it start happening to me, it's
[ __ ] annoying, bro. Even when it
doesn't even happen to me.
It's a It's But no, no, no, Grezy. It
does. It does annoy me. Even watching it
annoys me. I could not be out for 2,
three, four weeks, a month, whatever,
and I click on these videos and it
annoys me. Even watching it annoys me.
Happening to other people. Yeah.
You You never guess what I said to this
[ __ ] I'm not even going to repeat it on here. Yeah.
Yeah, you you never guess what I [ __ ]
wrote to her. I'm not going to write on here
because it's [ __ ] annoying. Because
it's [ __ ] hunting [ __ ] annoying.
You know, cuz it's annoying hearing it.
You know how annoying it is hearing it?
Even when it's not happening to me that,
oh, I've got a boyfriend.
It's annoying because it's [ __ ]
annoying, bro. It's boring.
You know, even when I tell Ant-Man some
[ __ ] he says it annoys him hearing
about it. It's [ __ ] annoying. And
then when you have these stupid people
on Reddit just simply just sticking up
for women all the time. Why do they do
it? I don't understand why they do it,
you know? Why do they constantly lick
their ass? Like me, do I don't know how
many times me and had the same
conversation. Why do they do nothing but
lick their ass? I don't I don't get it.
And then they attack you for showing the
[ __ ] truth. You show how bad it is
and how it never changes. And then they attack you.
You show combos, right? You show
approaching videos and then they
literally attack you for it. They're
actually attacking you. They're not even
giving you advice.
Well, trust me, mate. You No, you
[ __ ] have not, you know.
Yeah, but what about when you speak to
them and they keep pretending they got
boyfriends? You completely ignore that,
didn't you? I noticed that you ignore
things. I I I think you completely
ignore these things. I've literally
shown you videos.
I will show I've shown you videos. I'm
not telling you anything. I'm showing
you things. You understand? I'm showing
you what I'm experiencing and you're
still arguing with it. What's I'm going
to make another [ __ ] Reddit account
and tell that [ __ ] to go get [ __ ]
art. She's [ __ ] annoying me, bro. I
swear to God.
I told the [ __ ] as well, when you're in
London again, because she lives in New
Zealand, right? I said I I said I
basically said, yeah, um when you're in
New Zealand, when you're in London
again, I'll say I'll [ __ ] say to your
face in front of any man, any sid man,
all of the things that I brought to you on Reddit,
I will say the same to you.
You know what I'm saying? Okay, Joe. So,
what does that tell you? That means
you're going to be alone forever and and
and single forever then, doesn't it? So,
then your situation's never going to
change then. That's my whole point
is you're good-looking and you can't
even find anyone. How depressing is
that? That would make anyone depressed.
And I'm not going to get into a
conversation about my looks again. How
depressing is that having to keep
dealing with that all your life? Me
adman year in year out, year in
depression. Depression because of it,
having to deal with it. No wonder you're
so [ __ ] depressed and hate them.
Anyone [ __ ] would be because it's the
same story time and time and time again
and time and time again. The same old
advice, the same old story when you go
out. You know what I mean?
The same old being alone forever. Yet
people tell you, "Oh, you don't know
what the future holds. You don't know
what life says." Life changes. Life
changes. Never changes. Just like what
Ant-Man says. Never changes.
You know why they want you gone? You're
good-look. There's nothing wrong with
you. Look at all of the advice, bro.
Look at all of the advice people give
you on Reddit. It will change. You don't
know what I've been hearing it for
years, man. I've been hearing the same
advice for years. There's no reason to
get you gone. You're good-looking. You
should have You're you're normal
looking. There's no reason to get you gone.
And it this happens for years and years
and years and years and years. And this
is exactly why I booked this flight for
November. Yeah. That's exactly why I
[ __ ] done it. I'm not dealing with
this [ __ ] anymore.
You know, [ __ ] same old [ __ ] [ __ ]
never [ __ ] changes year in [ __ ]
year out. you know,
stop only seeing it from their point of
view or your point of view. See it from both POVs
if you're actually going to write stuff.
You know what I'm saying?
Why do they want to get you gone? They
complain that all men are the same, that
they can't find anyone. Isn't that just
defeating the object? They literally
come on here and moan and complain and
moan on and complain that all men want sex.
They can't find anyone. Do they not mo?
Because I've seen them do it. I've seen
them do it on online.
You know what I mean? You only see it
from their point of view. That's the
problem. You know, you speak about other
people, right? Oh, but the thing is you
only see it from their point of view.
That's the that's the thing. And then
when I say why don't you see it from
another point of view and then you
don't. So it's a madness. Why why are
they getting you gone? People on Reddit
say that you know your time is going to
come. You know you're going to meet someone.
You're doing what you can do. No.
>> So what why you gone? You're not ugly.
You're good-look. There's nothing wrong
with you. There's nothing wrong with
your personality. There's nothing wrong
with your approaches. What's the reason
for it? Come on, let's talk, bro. No
one's getting blocked. I didn't block anyone. Simple.
You know what I'm saying? No. Why are
people so depressed killing themselves
in these westernized countries? Go look
up the suicide rate in Asia. Yeah.
Go and look up the suicide rate in Asia.
Barely barely none, bro. And they're
third world countries.
A lot of people kill themselves in these
countries like England, America,
women, government, [ __ ] like that. Loads
of things. It's they're backward countries.
They give you advice on Reddit. You show
them whatever you show them you've done.
And then as soon as you show them, they
attack you. They literally attack you.
That is the definition of the truth
hurting. They literally like tell you,
"Oh, you need to do this. You need to do
that. You need to do this. You need to
do that." And then as soon as you show
it, they attack you and and or they
simp. I mean, what the [ __ ] What's the
point in giving advice and if someone
takes your advice and then they show you
how [ __ ] up the game is, you then
start attacking them? What's the point?
You know, it's [ __ ] stupid, man. It's
[ __ ] Ricky Doodalus.
No, you don't have problems. I just
don't like seeing other people go
through the same [ __ ] It's annoying. It
is annoying. It's [ __ ] boring,
you know? I hate it. Like, who the [ __ ]
do they think they are, you know? It's
like watching somebody with attitude.
When I'm watching this [ __ ] on Instagram
and it ain't happening to me, it's
annoying. Who the [ __ ] do they think they are?
You know what I'm saying? There was
[ __ ] one I was watching. I think it
must have been London. Must have been
London. Y um I think it was a few hours
ago, bro. And she had this attitude,
man. If somebody gave me that attitude,
I would have box them in their face in
front of any [ __ ] man. And the reason
I always have to bring men into it is
because men like to s and they try to
look good for women, which is why I
always just bring them involved, which
is the same thing as what I said to that
USA. I said, "You can bring your man as
well." I don't give a [ __ ] when I was
saying that [ __ ] like um three months to
four months ago when I was in that room,
let me come next Thursday or Friday, I
think it was, bring your man, I will do
it in front of him or any man, you know,
I don't give a [ __ ] because we know that
that's what it's going to be anyways cuz
you these men love to try looking good
for women. Another thing I hate seeing,
bro. Another thing I hate seeing. It
pisses me off. Swear to God, it pisses
You get on nights out as well, man. You
get on nights out as well.
cuz that's what it would always be cuz
they would always try and get involved.
You know what I mean?
Don't know why they do what they do. I
don't know. I don't know why they
don't know why they defend them like that,
you know? It's not like they're famous
and they're like millionaires and they
can get any woman they want. Women
literally don't like them and they still
defend them. It's just bizarre. It's to
me it's like a mental condition. [ __ ] autism maybe. Autism maybe.
I don't know why they do it, bro. I can
understand if they were famous, they can
get any woman they want, but they don't.
Women lit. They The maddest thing is all
of these simps, right, have had less
women than you. They've had less sex
than you. They have had less women than
you and they still defend them. It's
[ __ ] bizarre, mate. It is bizarre.
It's And they still defend them. It's
It's got to be some sort of autism, maybe.
I think it's [ __ ] autism, baby, bro.
I think they've got autism or something.
They've got to have autism, bro. Definitely.
Hold up. I thought it was a controller,
man. [ __ ] They have [ __ ] autism or
some [ __ ] It's got to be something like that.
And again, you go by your point of view,
then when somebody says theirs, why
don't you see from their point of view?
You got to understand, Joe. People keep
saying that life changes, things change,
you meet people, but every time you you
go out, all you hear is the same old.
So, is it wrong to believe that things
are never going to change? How is it
going to change? It's like Ant-Man said,
how is it going to change?
How is it going to change? It's like
what Ant-Man said. How is it going to change?
You know, how is it going to change? Why
would somebody want a good-looking
person gone? You're not fat and ugly.
That's the whole point. You know,
you'll never understand it cuz you can't
even answer anything when somebody asks
you something back
because it's annoying, bro. That's why
it affects my life cuz it's [ __ ] annoying.
And then, oh, what? You got to go to
Asian hookers, bro. They're not all What
do you think? Every single person in
Thailand's a prostitute. Everyone in
Philippines is a prostitute. No. No,
they're [ __ ] well not.
There's people there that don't even
want just sex. They want relationships in Philippines.
So, what what are they all um are they
all prostitutes then? Well, everyone in
AIDS is a prostitute then because
they're not a stuckup [ __ ] So, because
they're not a stuckup [ __ ] they're all prostitutes. Okay.
They're not [ __ ] prostitutes, bro.
The [ __ ] All of them. Nah. Nah.
[ __ ] Malaysia as well. That's another one.
Why does the truth hurt so much? I don't
understand why the truth hurts so much, you know?
I don't understand why the truth hurts so much.
Crazy, man. I mean, they're the ones
that gave you the [ __ ] advice.
So, what do you do moving forward then, Grezy?
Keep getting the same old [ __ ] Oh, I
have a boyfriend. You have a boyfriend.
>> Keep watching this [ __ ] on Instagram.
Like, is is that is that your definition
of moving forward?
Is that your definition of moving
forward? Same old [ __ ] in England.
Same old [ __ ] [ __ ] that never
changes. Oh, it will change. Life
changes. You can't predict the future.
They're cowards on this Reddit, man.
They're [ __ ] cowards.
Well, I mean, most women in in England
date people for money.
So, I mean, the same can be said about that.
I mean, but there's there's women that
date men. I mean, it's like right now,
if I was a if I was a millionaire or I
had loads and loads and loads of money,
I'm sure I wouldn't be having these
problems with women. So, it doesn't just
work like that in in in in Asian
countries. It happens everywhere.
England, America. Yeah, there might not
be I mean, bro, the poverty line, but
they they also use you for money in
these westernized countries as well. So
you can't even date in your own country.
It's [ __ ] depressing, bro.
But they do it in in westernized countries, too.
Making me feel suicidal yesterday
thinking of this [ __ ]
that along with the football. It's [ __ ] depressing.
Yeah, I don't know who this buzz guy is,
but I went out Thursday, bro. I didn't
go out Saturday. I went out Thursday
and I kept hearing the same old [ __ ] I
have a boyfriend. I have a boyfriend. I
have a boyfriend. And you just never
stops. It doesn't matter what year, what
day. I don't know about five sober.
I done about five sober
and you just get the same old I've got a
boyfriend. I've got a boyfriend. I've
And the thing that annoys me about it is
is what I was trying to explain to these
people. It's it's not like you look like
Timmy Eldridge. I don't know if you know
who Timmy Eldridge is. You know, it's
not like you're fat, you stink, you're
ugly. You know, there's no reason for
it. There's no reason for somebody to
not be to not because again you can see
it from their point of view which yeah
you should see but you also need to see
it from other people's point of view.
You don't look like Timmy Aldridge. You
don't look like [ __ ] Dave Tiger. You
know you don't look like any of these
people. So there's not really a reason for it.
You know there's not really
Do you understand what I'm saying, bro?
There's no reason for it to
There's no reason for it to keep happening. Yeah.
Yeah. I don't really go out much
anymore. Me, I go out like once every 3
weeks to a month now. If that I I can't
I can't be asked with it anymore, bro.
And it's not even just that. It's the
whole the way the whole country is. I
hate it. It's not even just one or two
things. It's the people, the women, the
way the government,
uh, the gambling, the [ __ ] waiting
around for things,
[ __ ] delays. It's everything I hate
about this country, bro. It's not like
one or two things. I hate all of it. I
hate the people as well.
Everyone's got the same attitude.
Um, I don't like I just don't like this country, man.
So, I just don't like it. It's cuz I'm
not fully English. Uh, well, I am fully
I really really am fully English. I'm
I'm not even hardly any Turkish, so I
mean, yeah, I mean, I'm I've got white
in me. I've got a bit of Scottish in me,
a bit of German in me, and a tiny tiny
tiny bit of Turkish in me, which is
which makes me white.
I'm fully English, and I hate this
country, and I've been in this country
my whole life. Got a British passport,
never been Turkey, never spoken a
language. I'm I'm basically just English
in it. I'm basically white.
It's an annoying it's a it it just it
just annoys me this country. No,
no. The only other thing I am is tiny
bit Turkish, which basically I shouldn't
even mention it because I'm just white basically. Bro,
you know what I'm saying? I hate
England. Even when I used to work, I
used to hate go I used to dread doing it
cuz of the people. Like even when I gave
a sh uh gave up with the whole dating
thing. I used to hate um going in
to like the work and [ __ ] cuz of um
I buzz, you know, my friend Antman, he
just says um they're not interested in this country.
I think he's right in it.
What a mad thing to say. they're not
interested in this country. But
obviously he's right cuz whenever you
try to speak to someone
that the same thing happens
well for most for most people, you know
what I mean? So clearly they aren't
interested in this country unless you're
a big YouTuber or a Tik Tocker.
You know what I mean?
Surprised more people don't kill
themselves to be honest
over this [ __ ]
Mad isn't it?
But the only thing is Buzz is that you
know like when they're 30. Yeah.
No one's going to want them and the only
people that want them are people that
just want sex from them. So they're
really silly, bro. They they're really
silly that they don't learn from each other
because the thing that they moan about
will 100% only happen when they're in their 30s.
It does get you down. It's [ __ ] depressing.
It's [ __ ] depressing seeing it,
hearing about it. It's [ __ ] It is
It's [ __ ] depressing.
I don't know how it doesn't [ __ ]
depress anyone else. It's [ __ ]
depressing as [ __ ] It's boring as well.
Bors me, bro. That's why I booked this
thing for [ __ ] November. I'm bored of
it, man. It's [ __ ] boring as [ __ ] You know,
it is boring, bro. It is boring.
[ __ ] boring it is.
But we know what we need to do anyways.
So there's no point going on and on and
on and on on on about it.
It's like they attack you for trying.
They attack you
for taking their advice and shows it
doesn't work. How does that even make sense?
And then they go on about people's
personality. There's nothing wrong with
your personality. You know, I've got
friends. I lived with people. Everyone
likes me. Nothing nothing wrong with
that. But it's just excuse after excuse
after excuse, you know. You know, 19 [ __ ] 80s.
Like they use 1980 [ __ ] excuses. And
the the only reason I ain't done a video
on it is because it's just always the
same. If I do a video, it's just the
same thing that I've already done said before.
You know what? What's there to do a
video on? Oh, that they don't go for
personality or Yeah, we've said all of
this stuff before with these [ __ ]
We've said it all before,
you know. There's nothing left to be
said about it. That's why I don't make
videos on it anymore.
It's depressing, bro. There's literally
no changes in three and a half years.
There's not one single change, you know?
It's [ __ ] depressing, bro. So, yeah.
[ __ ] enough to get anyone [ __ ]
down. That's why I'm leaving.
Yeah, that's what I'm doing. I'm [ __ ]
off in two months.
I'll be out in two months. Well, 3
That's the change I'm making is [ __ ]
off out of here. Cuz this is too depressing, bro.
It's too depressing staying here, you know?
It's too [ __ ] depressing, man.
Staying in this country, man.
Yeah. Let me see. I heard about that. Whoa.
Yeah, you got Bed, man. Yeah.
Where was this?
How the [ __ ] did he get into fights,
bro? I've never been in a fight when
I've been on a night out. Well, I've had
people try it, but then they know not to
[ __ ] with Peter Belly. Isn't that right, Grezy?
I used to go all over on a night out. I
never got into any problems. Yeah.
Yeah, I've never got into that kind of
I've never got into that kind of [ __ ]
So, what happened to Mike and Charlie?
Did they get a hide in Yeah, man.
Just looking for that change, eh?
Looking for that change.
[ __ ] hell, bro. Never.
You never change, mate. Never change.
Never change. Never change.
I'll be back later anyways. Bye.