Oh, thanks for finding my new channel,
man. That's fine. I'll just make another one. Yes. Subscribers.
No worries, man. Just make another
channel. No problem.
Yeah, it's not a problem to me, bro.
You know, every single time, right,
these people come here when they do
this, it just shows what they are. fat,
ugly, stalking, nothing but stalking and
YouTube in their life. It's it's it's
funny to me, bro. I just made another channel.
Just made another channel, bro. It's not a problem.
I mean, all of my
It's just my approaching videos that go
up there. I just deleted it all, man.
It's no problem.
You know why the [ __ ] are these fat ugly
munters on here trying to talk about
people's looks when we've all seen what
these people look like whenever they get
exposed? Like that that is the most
funniest thing about it. Like bro, you
people can't even show your face due to ugliness.
Like bomb is a prime example of what
probably I would say probably most of
these people here probably look worse
than the bomb to be honest with you.
They they probably look worse than him,
man. Just like Gray Cat. [ __ ] You're
all ugly fat stalking bastards.
You ain't got a life but YouTube. You're
so fat and ugly. It's the truth, bro.
It's not even reacting or being
triggered. It's It's facts.
You're coming on my other channel
calling me a M. Bro, have you seen
yourselves when yourselves get exposed?
Please, bro. You're only the only people
that them names affect is yourself,
which is why you don't show your face
because you're an ugly bastard.
And we know like the excuses that you
make. Oh, well, people's going to find
out who I am. No, no, no, no, no, no.
But never, no one found out who the bomb was.
Um, nothing, man. They just found my
channel through Reddit and they just
started stalking me. So, I had to delete
all my videos. So, I'll make some more
videos later and put it on my other
channel. Not a problem at all. Not a
problem at all. These people, it says a
lot about their lives coming on YouTube
years and years reacting to me. Now, I
say that stuff about reacting because I
know it annoys you, Joe, because they
they literally are reacting to me. I
showed you that person's channel right
earlier and he's been doing it for [ __ ] years.
They are [ __ ] fat, ugly stalkers.
It's the same account, bro. [ __ ] the
Flash, Red Star. Bro, whatever you say
about what I look like, it has no effect
to me because we all know what you
people look like, you're all fat and
you're all ugly. That's why you all get
all excited. Yeah. When you know someone
gains a bit of weight cuz you think
they're becoming fat and ugly like you.
But bro, that ain't ever happening. You understand?
Fat, ugly, jealous stalkers. And in a
way, it's good when they do this though.
The more and more they do, it just shows
that you've got something that they want
and can't have. But the more they do
this, yeah, stalking every day, it shows
that they're jealous of you. That's the
only thing it shows. React to me
reacting not reacting, the only thing it
can be is you've got something that they
want because that's the only thing I
that that it would be is damn right
jealousy. Because if they if you was if
if someone was better than you, you
would not be wasting your time on them.
You would not be stalking them. The fact
that they keep doing it, you got
something that they want. It's simple as
that. It's the same as somebody that's
in love. Because you can't say that they
do it for reaction because they are
reacting. I showed you the whole channel
of [ __ ] years of reaction.
So I mean, what's so your reaction? You
know what I'm saying? All right. Right.
Right. Okay. And I'm showing you that
they're reacting to me. Okay. Okay.
Okay. Let me repeat this again because I
think that you're quite slow. Okay. And
they are reacting to me every day and
stalking me. So they're stalking me and
reacting to me for reaction.
Okay. And so they're reacting
99% of their life all their life to get
a 1% of reaction. Okay. And then you got
a 1% of reaction. And then what? Okay.
So, you spend all of your life reacting
to me every day,
99% of your life, and then I give you 1%
of a reaction. Okay. And
but you said I'm a skin ugly m
it doesn't make sense. You're talking
Okay. Okay. Right. Right. Right. But I'm
making them react to me. Do you want me
to Okay. Okay. Okay. I'm trying to
explain to this Joe guy a million times
and he's not understanding. They are
reacting to me. They are triggered over
me. I'm literally showing you that
they're spending all of their life
reacting to me. Are you a Down syndrome?
I've literally shown you them reacting
to me and being triggered over me. Are
you a Down syndrome? Like I've literally
explained this about Bro, I swear this
guy's got down syndrome. I swear to God
he doesn't understand like anything you
say to him. Are you a [ __ ] Like, cuz
I was I was asking for you yesterday,
bro. Are you really really so much of a [ __ ]
No, no, no, no, no, no, [ __ ] I've
just explained this to you about three times.
They are reacting to me year in year
out, year in, year out. Okay, I'm going
to stop talking about this because
you're a [ __ ] You obviously don't
understand this. Must be some sort of
northern thing. You literally I'm
reacting to it because I'm trying to
explain it to you, but you're too much
of a Down syndrome. You don't understand
it. So, anyways, moving on. End the
conversation then. Okay. Listen,
[ __ ] When people try to get a
reaction, they write stuff for about two
or three minutes, right? And then they
get a reaction like from Timmy. They
don't react all their life. They don't
react their life away to you to try to
get a reaction unless they're jealous.
But you still don't seem to understand
that, bro. You you you you're slow in
the head. You know, I know you like to
try and say that I'm slow, but you
really really are a Down syndrome. You
know, you really really are a Down syndrome.
You would not waste all your life doing
this unless you was jealous. That's the
only thing it can be. Blame reaction all
you want, but it's not a reaction. It's
not a reaction. And it says everything
about your [ __ ] ugly lives when you sit
on here doing it every day. It shows
everything about your [ __ ] ugly lives
that you waste on YouTube. You're saying
that you're getting a reaction, brother.
You're wasting all your life on YouTube
to get the reaction. So, I'm already
living in your head. Even if I'm giving
you a 1% reaction every [ __ ] 4
months, every 5 months, I'm living in
your head every single day of your life.
So, bro, I'm still the winner. Reaction
or no [ __ ] reaction. You understand?
>> [ __ ] weirdo stalkers, man. I swear to
God. Hey, I'm making a new channel
anyways, bro. [ __ ] weirdos.
These people really have been bullied
all their life, ain't it, bro? They
really really are such bully victims. I
I actually I swear to God, it's like,
okay, okay, let's let's um Okay, let's
let's let's let Let me give you an example, right?
So, let's just say that I got a reaction
from Timmy. Yeah, Greasy. say that like
he reacts like really really good and
it's the most funny reaction. Yeah.
Let's put this into perspective cuz this
Joe guy is a bit slow. Would you waste
every second of every day all your life
for 5 years doing videos to try to get his reaction?
No, you would not because you've got a
better life than him. You You
understand? And I'm trying to explain
this to this Joe guy, but he seems a bit
slow. Let's just say Timmy, right, is is
going to explode in 5 months. Yeah.
Because Timmy always used to react.
Yeah. Would you waste all your life
every day stalking him until you got
that reaction? No. The only people that
do that are people that are jealous.
That's the only people that literally do
that. So, bro, you are slow. Of course
you're [ __ ] slow, bro. You're an
idiot. I showed you that account, right? Stalking me,
right, for literally for years. And they
don't stop. Even when they don't get a
reaction and your thing is, oh well,
yeah, they do it for reaction. But then
even if they don't get a reaction, they
still do it. You don't understand. You
literally don't understand basic um you
just don't understand basic [ __ ]
So you would spend four months of your
life reacting to get a reaction, huh? I
mean, that just takes the whole point of
it away. Like you you're generally you
generally it can't be explained to you,
bro. You don't understand. You literally
don't understand, right? No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. But they're reacting to me, which is
what I'm trying to explain to you. They
are reacting and being triggered over
me. That says a lot about their life. It
doesn't. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. So, hold on a minute. So, getting
So, you would stalk someone every day
for 4 months, right? But you're missing
the point that they're reacting to me.
You don't understand it. There's no
point. There's no point trying to
explain it to you, bro. You were down.
There's no point trying to explain this
to you, bro. You know, you really are a
Down syndrome. You You don't understand
it, bro. They are reacting to me every
day. Even when I'm not reacting to them.
So therefore, they're losing. That's
what I'm trying to explain to you, you
know. And even if you don't react, they
will still do it. Think of it. Just like
that Red Star account. Yeah. I did not
react for like 4 months. So even Bro,
bro, even if you do not re Okay. Okay.
Okay. Okay. Let's do a deal right here.
Right now then. I will never react to
these people again. Ever again. and
let's see if they stop doing let's see
how long they keep doing it before they
get a reaction again. Okay then let's
put it this way then. Okay. Okay. Go and
subscribe to that Red Star account.
Right. That sad little stalking cowardly
bastard [ __ ] Ugly boy. Right. Go and
sub to him right now and I won't react.
And then you tell me who keeps doing it
and doing it and doing it and doing it.
Exactly. They won't stop because they're
jealous. It's jealousy. Yes. I know they
won't stop. That's jealousy. That's the
whole point I'm trying to make. That's
the jealousy of it all. Better looking,
more money, and a better life than them.
That Ronald Pump was so right. You know,
do you know what he says? They'll never
leave you alone. You're better looking.
You got more money and a better life.
And I and I never ever listened to him.
He said, "They'll never leave you alone.
Get off of YouTube." And he was right.
It is jealousy. They're jealous of me. I
used to think that, you know, in the end
that like they were just trying to get a
reaction and it was just a bit. But he
was right. Better looking, better life
and more money at them and it kills
them. He was so right, you know. He was
so right about that.
I He was so right, bro. I swear to God,
bro. That Ronald Pump account, he said,
"You got better money than them, better
looks, and a better life, and it kills
them. Just get off of YouTube and live
your life." That's what he said. That's
actually what he said and it kills them.
Get off. And it's true. It is actually
true if you think about it. Yeah. I
thought this guy was just chatting [ __ ]
But it is the truth. It is the truth. It
is the truth. It actually is. It is. It
is actually jealousy. You got better
looks and better money. That's what they
hate. It's the truth. It's It actually
is the truth. Yeah.
better looks and better money and it
kills them. That's what it's the truth.
Cuz if you've been looking for years,
Yeah. how long they've been doing this,
it actually is the truth. Bear in mind,
yeah, these people are fat and ugly.
They got no money. That's why they're on
here all day, every day. Think about it,
bro. Yeah. Our life might not even be perfect.
No one's life is perfect. But they're
fat and ugly sat on YouTube, no money.
That's what the That's where the
jealousy comes from. But anyways, sub to
that account. I'm not reacting to these
people no more. So, you will see who who
keeps doing it then.
Who keeps doing it then? Listen, the
thing is, Greavesy. Yeah. You could not
react to these people for 10 years and
they would still do it. Say I come on
YouTube every day and on this account,
right, and I put all my approaching
videos on this channel and I lived, say
I lived my life on this channel. Yeah.
And let's just say 5 years went past. I
don't know what content, just say
different kinds of content. Yeah. So 5
years, bro, come back on here in 5
years. No one would get a reaction and
they'd still be doing it. So that just
defeats the whole object of what of what
you're trying to say.
That defeats the whole object of what
you're trying to say because you know
full well that even if they don't get a
reaction, they still do it. And it's not
that they're typing for a reaction. It's
what they're doing to get a reaction.
You are reacting being triggered to get
a reaction which contradicts the whole
of what you're saying. People write
stuff to get a reaction. People do stuff
to get a reaction, but they don't stalk
someone all day every day to get a
reaction. That only says stuff about
their own life.
But yeah, they would I should have took
that Ronald Pumps advice. I think I
might actually take his advice. You
know, you know what? I might actually
take his advice, bro. He was actually so
right. He is actually so right. It is
jealousy. It actually is. Yeah, it is
jealousy. More money, better looking,
better life. It It is jealousy.
Definitely. Definitely is jealousy.
Yeah, 100%. I should have just come off
this [ __ ] a long time ago, bro. Yeah,
they never stopped because they're
[ __ ] retards. They're jealous fat,
ugly people. Have you seen half of the
people what they look like on it? All
fat and ugly. All fat, ugly, complete
bully victims that can't get off of
YouTube. And that's why they're going
mad, bro, when I say [ __ ] because what
I'm saying is the truth.
So what I'm saying is the truth, you know.
Anyways, I need to make a new YouTube
channel to put all my other [ __ ] on that
channel, bro. Yeah.
Fat ugly people that ain't got a life.
That's what they are, bro.
No, no, no, no. Yeah, but he doesn't
have dedicated stalkers. No, no, no. But
you're missing the point, Joe. It is
they are jealous of me. There's no doubt
about that, bro. Reaction. No reaction.
Would you spend all of your life
stalking somebody that you was better
than? No, you wouldn't. No. No. No. You
don't get it. No, no, no, no, no, no.
You do not get it. If you was not
jealous of somebody, you would leave them alone.
Yeah. If they won't leave you alone,
you've got something that they want. I'm
That's the Listen, bro. I'm not stupid.
Yeah. I don't know how you you might
think I'm stupid or
t think Okay, let me let me let me let
me Okay, let me put it like this, right?
Virgin boy, ugly bastard, skin, no life.
[ __ ] all [ __ ] all going for himself. Now
I'm making a statement, right? Like
they're trying to make a statement about
me, right? Am I going to spend every
second of every day stalking that [ __ ]
on YouTube? Right? Listen to me. Am I
going to spend every second of every day
um stalking that [ __ ] on YouTube and
doing videos every day on YouTube?
Am I? No, I'm not. And why am I not
going to do that? Right. Right. You're
not understand. You're not understanding
what I'm saying. You're not getting what
I'm saying. So, there's no point. You're
not You're not understanding. No, you
wouldn't do that because you've just
said that you're better than them. So,
if you're better than them, that you'd
live your life.
You know what I'm saying? Uh what what
what are they actually jealous of?
Better looks, had more women than them.
And yes, I have had more women than
them, shown more money than them, better
clothes than them. Um
[ __ ] um you know what I'm saying?
These people still won't leave me alone.
Nature girl, I'm going to have to come
off this [ __ ] They're still stalking me
every day. They're still stalking me
every day and [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying?
They got me banned. They never got me
banned from anywhere, you idiot. Listen,
Joe, they don't affect my life. I don't
know why you keep going on like they
affect my life. They don't affect any
aspect of my life. They're the ones that
are coming on YouTube every day,
triggered, triggered as day, triggered
over me every day. They don't affect my
life, bro. That I affect their life. And
they've never got me banned from
anywhere. Where the [ __ ] have they got
me banned for? From, mate.
They are triggered over me from the time
they wake up to the time they go to bed.
As soon as I switch this YouTube thing
off, I don't care about none. No one.
They are. I've literally shown you a
triggered bastard on YouTube every day.
He is so triggered. Look at how he's
writing. I'm affecting them. I'm in
their head. They're not affecting me,
bro. I've been on here for years and
years and years and years and years. The
only reason I stop I stopped watching
them is cuz they're [ __ ] repeating bastards.
They're the ones. GameStop, they done me
a favor. Casinos, they done me a favor.
They didn't get me banned from any pubs
and they didn't get me banned on Reddit.
Try again. milk. Try again. Gamtop done
me a favor. Casino don't care about
Reddit not banned from pubs not banned
about. Try again. And another thing is
even if that was the case, right, bro,
we live in London.
If somebody got me banned from a pub, I
could go to a million one other pubs and
go back to that pub. Try again. Now, I
will tell you how I affect their life
because they come on YouTube every
single day stalking me and being
triggered over me for years. That's how
I own them. Yeah, that is how I own
them. That they come on YouTube
triggered to [ __ ] every day. I put the
evidence out there. That's me owning
them in their head for being better
looking, more money, and a better life.
So, whatever you think that they do to
me, they don't do anything to me. They
have to come on here every day reacting
to me. React. What? What have I done to
their life? What have I done to their
life? I'll tell you what they've done.
It's jealousy. That's what I was
thinking. nature. It is. It's like what
Ronald Pump said to me. You're better
looking, you got more money than them,
and you got a better life than them, and
it kills them. Just come off of YouTube
and live your life. I will tell you how
I've affected their life. Every single
day I come on YouTube, they waste every
second of every day talking about me and
being triggered over me. That's how I
keep affecting them. Just by going live
on YouTube, I've got channels dedicated
to me. They can't stop talking about me.
That's how much I'm affecting them.
Whenever I go out for a drink, they're
triggered over me, jealous over me,
reacting to me. I don't do anything to
them to them,
you know? And they haven't got me banned
from any of that [ __ ]
So, I've just told you how I'm affecting
their life, but they're not you're not
telling me how they're affecting my life
cuz they didn't get me banned from anywhere.
You know, you know what I'm saying? This
Joe guy is he doesn't understand. I
don't think this guy understands anything.
You really really don't understand.
Like, you don't affect anyone's life.
They don't affect my life. They just
repeat themselves and embarrass
themselves on YouTube. They've been
doing it for years. Would I still be
here if they affected me? Would I still
be here laughing at them, right? No, I
don't do it. I I come on YouTube and
they're [ __ ] obsessed with me. Look,
four likes already. four likes already
cuz I know if somebody was an ugly ma I
wouldn't give them the type of date. So
they they contradict their own they they
contradict themselves. They're saying
how you're ugly and all of this but they
can't shut up about you. Must be
jealousy. Must be jealousy. I mean the
evidence is there. I mean there's no
point talking about it. All of these
people call you all of these things but
they won't stop talking about you and
obsessing over you. It just points to
jealousy. any anyone would tell you
exactly the same thing if you went on
the street and I'd be like, "Would you
waste your time on an ugly balding
manta?" No. Because you're better than
them. So, it has to be jealousy. That's
the only thing it can be is jealousy.
Jealousy every day. That's that's all it
has to be. That's the only thing it can
it can point to. There's nothing else it
can point to. Literally nothing. And you
can't say that they do it for a reaction
because a they react to me and b even if
you don't react to them they'll still do
it. It has to be jealousy. And even
doing this every single day for reaction
that's also jealousy. So even if they're
still doing it for reaction then I mean
it's it all points to them jealous of
you. They're jealous of me. I don't know
what it is I've got,
but um I got something they don't have
and it and it and it bugs them and it I
don't know what it is. Better looks,
more money, I don't know what it is, but
there's something that bugs them that
I've got that they don't have, which is
why they embarrass themselves because
you know this whole [ __ ] on YouTube,
they're embarrassing themselves. You you
do realize this. Like you can say this
and that, whatever, but all they're
doing is embarrassing themselves, you know?
One second, bro.
Uh, I'm making a new channel and I'm
putting all the videos back up, bro.
I'll put them on a new channel, man. I
just don't want these little retards
following me around.
I'll make another channel, bro. I'll
make another channel. So, yeah.
And I mean, Donald Trump is a big is is
a bit different, you know? He's a
[ __ ] he's the [ __ ] he's the
um what's he the
president of [ __ ] America. I mean,
Donald Trump is a lot different to me,
mate. Yeah, it's all all it comes down
to is jealousy. And I would say to you,
bro, that they look worse than I would
say these people look worse than the
bomb. Think of it, bro. Yeah, you've got
more money than them. You got a better
life than them. And you're not ugly like
them. Like, it doesn't matter how much
money, say, I don't know, even if you
had [ __ ] £800, you still got more
than them. Whatever, 2,000, £5,000,
whatever. The evidence is there, bro.
The EV The evidence is there. How can
you argue with evidence?
Everything that these people do, they
talk about themselves. Like, bro, I went
on my new channel. I looked on one one
uh comment. Haha, you're a ma. I was
like, "Bro, have you seen your own
faces? Have you seen your fat, ugly
selves? You do you understand, bro?
They're all 40year-old odd bully victims
that get bullied every time they try to
leave their house. They're bully
victims, bro. They have to be to come on
here and do this every day. They have to
be. They have to be bully victims."
Yeah. [ __ ] off. Look, and and and you
know, the maddest thing is Yeah. They
will beg people to do their dirty work
as well. like that red star. He's been
doing it for years. He has been doing
this for absolute years, lad.
Absolute years. All his life is
dedicated to stalking me. But then why
would you do that to a 27y old bing ma
and then it's the 47y old ba which is
himself. That's how I realized that he
was talking about himself.
But um I don't think as much as you you
explain this to um to just Joe guy, I
don't think he really really understands
because there Okay, let me let me go on
this Red Star channel right now. Yeah. Again,
all I see is reaction.
All I'm seeing is him reacting to me.
Right. Let's go in the videos. Right. So
I would say from all his YouTube career,
I might have reacted three times and he
has been doing this for years. But you
want a reaction from me? If you go up
and up and up and up and up and up and
up, this has been going on for years,
but I've only reacted about three times
in them years.
Yeah, you keep telling yourself that,
bro. Yeah, you keep telling yourself
that, bro. You millionaire. Yeah. So
yeah, Cory, I'm going to make a new
channel and put all the approaches on
that channel, bro. Don't worry, man. I'm
going to put it all on that channel. Not
a problem, man. I'm just going to upload
them on another channel. I don't want
these uh um
Yeah. So, if £1,400 isn't a lot of
money, where's my 10 grand? And this is
exactly why I come off this community.
Cory, do you know this is exactly why I
come off of this, bro? It's because of
these people. This is why you'll see me
off for like a week, two weeks, a month
because of these people. You actually
lose brain cells with these people.
Oh, so you want me to forget him now?
I'm spooing facts. Yeah, I've already
seen your win.
Yeah. Well, show me my [ __ ] 10 grand
then. If £1,400 is not a lot of money,
millionaire, where's my 10 grand?
I want to see my 10 grand I've been
asking for. No one can show it. And then
it's just the same conversation over and
over. And this is why I don't come on
here anymore, bro. This is why I don't
[ __ ] with it. This is why I don't really
really I don't really come on here anymore, lad.
Because of these people. That's exactly
why, man. Because of these retards on
here. It's why you don't see me on here
every day. Like, you know,
there's no point of it, man. There's no
point of it.
No, I'm not. It's not about nothing will
change. I'm saying that he does what he
does because he's jealous.
And then you will say, "Oh, what's there
to be jealous of?" Bro, you're the one who's jealous.
You're the one who's jealous. So, you
should ar you should know what you're
jealous of because you won't stop. So,
at the end of the day, you would you
yourself would only know what you're
jealous of. It's not for me to say.
Peter, where are these so-called women
then? Uh, where's all these so-called
women? Um, ones I've shown plenty of
times on my YouTube channel. Yeah. And
see, this is exactly what I mean. It's
the same old on here. This is why I
don't bother anymore with it. This is
exactly why I don't bother. All of these
women that I've put on my YouTube
channel whilst you put none up. You
know, where's all your women? Where's
your 10 grand? And this is exactly why I
don't come on here anymore argue with
these people because they're all
spastics. There's there's no point, bro.
They just ruin it. They kill it. Like
people try to have a normal
conversation, right? And then you get
the 40-year-old no hope and spastics.
They just ruin everything. Which is why
that's why I made a new channel and put
all of my approach on the new channel
and they found it.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Monopoly.
Anyways, where's my 10 grand? Lush. Mr.
Millionaire. You going to come and show
me my 10 grand?
Show me my 10 grand, millionaire. I want
to see that [ __ ] 10 grand. [ __ ] I
wish I could sit there and say £1,400 is
um a lot of money is not a lot of money.
Show me my 10 grand, Mr. Millionaire.
I'll put the link up. See, with these
people on here, right, they like to
start [ __ ] they can't finish, you know?
They like to come on with their [ __ ]
selves year in year out. These people
have been doing this [ __ ] longer than
women have been saying that they've got boyfriends.
Anyways, I'm going to put the link up
and you're going to show me my 10 grand, right?
And I want to see my 10 grand. One
second. And I'm not going to answer
anything you say until you show me my 10
grand. Millionaire. Right. There we go.
Show me my 10 grand. Red store ain't
done it. Virgin boy ain't done it. Joe
ain't done it. And I don't think you're
going to do it. There you go. There's
the link. I'll wait for you, man. Show
me my 10 grand. I'm skin. I'm this. I'm
that. You ain't hit the spot. Oh, you've
just embarrassed yourself. You've come
on here acting like you're a
millionaire, but you can't show me 10
grand. All you've shown is your skin.
That's all you've shown. All you've
shown is your skin. I've got you right
where I want you. Can't even show me 10
grand. Yes, sir. Bam. Body, mate. Yep.
Joe, we've been hearing that excuse for
years. Imagine having 10K cash in your
wallet, mate. There's such thing as a
bank account. I mean, there's such thing
as going to the bank.
But you ain't got it because you all
skimp projectors. That's what it is.
I've got you right where I want you.
Bam. Made you start something you can't
finish. [ __ ] bro. Just literally. Yeah.
Get up. Walk into a [ __ ] wall, bro.
Yeah. And [ __ ] get off of [ __ ]
YouTube and stop starting [ __ ] you can't finish.
It makes you look like a [ __ ]
[ __ ] I have to say this to the
[ __ ] tenant the other day. Get down
for YouTube. Stop embarrassing yourself
every [ __ ] day and get a [ __ ] life.
[ __ ] me. Why would I show bunch? Oh,
here we go. The excuse again. The excuse
Excuse again. Look, he's just
contradicted himself. Oh, listen. He's
just He's just contradicting himself,
lad. He's just contradicted himself.
I've shown him tons and tons of women.
Then he's asked me where my women are.
But then when I've asked him to show him
money, he can't show nothing, [ __ ] boy. Yeah.
It's because you ain't got no money.
That's why. Because you ain't got none.
Same old boring conversation.
You ain't got You ain't going to show
none cuz you ain't got none. Just like
you was asking me to show you [ __ ]
women and I've shown plenty of plenty of
plenty of women. And what if I turn
around and say I don't want to show
women on the internet? Stop
contradicting yourself, dumb nuts. Stop
contradicting yourself. You have just
come on here talking about money. You
are, bro. You are saying, £,400. If
£1,400 is nothing, then you must have
£10,000. Simple, right? For somebody to
say £1,400 is nothing, you must have at least £10,000.
Exactly. Another one that started
something that he can't finish. So, at
the end of the day, no, no, no, no, no.
If you're saying £1,400 is nothing, you
should have at least 10 grand. I would
say most people that said that would
have 10 grand. And now you're
backtracking when someone's asking you
to show 10 grand. Mate, get off of
YouTube and stop starting stuff you
can't finish. You're not intelligent
enough um for it. And I'm not the one
making Who said £1,400 is a million
dollars? I never said 1,400 is [ __ ] a
million dollars. Who the [ __ ] said,
1400? You're saying that you've wiped
your ass with it. You're coming on here
like you're a billionaire. You're coming
on here like a [ __ ] billionaire or
1,400. You've never seen £1,400 in your life.
You know what I'm saying? Like you've
wiped your ass with it. Why are all of
these people so rich, but they spend all
their life on YouTube? This is what
makes me laugh, right? They all got
money. They've all got all of this money
apparently, but they're sat on YouTube
all day, every day. It doesn't make
sense, does it?
If they had all of this money, why the
[ __ ] are they not living their life? I
don't understand it, bro. Because they
ain't got no money and they ain't got no life.
>> That's three weeks raises.
>> Yeah, bro. You don't even have £1,400.
You don't even have 1,400, bro. You
don't have [ __ ] all. You can't show [ __ ]
all. And why are you talking about £1,400?
Who said anything about £1,400, mate? If
I had £1,400, I have £1,400 more than
what you've got.
But that's not what it is. No one said,
"Why are you talking about £1,400 anyways?
I've just put the link up and you're not
coming in and showing me anything.
You people are just delusional idiots.
No one talks like that, bro. No one
[ __ ] talks like that,
you know? Only fantasy that ain't got no
money like yourselves." And then it's,
"Oh, I don't want to show money to
strangers." What do you mean you don't
want to show money to strangers, bro?
You keep asking people every day to show money.
So, you're all millionaires, but you
ain't got a life. It's hard to believe,
you know? It's hard to So, are you going
to come and show money or not? So, okay.
Are you going to come and show money or not?
And you just said that, "Oh, why am I
going to show money to a stranger?"
Well, that's Well, then, but you asked
me to show women. You said, "Where are
all these women?" So, you've asked me to
show you women, but then when as soon as
I've asked you to show me money, you're
saying, "Oh, I don't show it to the
strangers cuz I ain't got it." Make it
make sense. Which one is it? So, I
should people show stuff or shouldn't
people show stuff?
So, you're asking me to show you women,
which I've already done a million times,
but then when I ask you to show
shopping, oh, I don't need to show
anything to strangers. Make it make
sense. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, are you just one
of them, bro? One of them free accounts
that come here telling everyone they want benefits.
Is that what it is? Is that like is it
just Okay, someone's come on here and
showing money. One second. Hold on, bro.
Let me let them in. One sec. It's going
to be 10 grand.
>> That my 10 grand.
>> Yes, it is, Peter. It's a lot more money
than you've ever seen in your life.
>> Let me see that 10 grand.
>> There it's there.
>> Yes. Can you count it? Yes. Oh, so it's
not 10 grand.
All we know is you're a big nose.
>> Yeah, big nose monster. Listen, Troa,
we've already seen what you look like.
You fat ugly bastard. You're boring now,
mate. Yeah. So, you're doing the same
thing again and again. They must be
jealous, bro. They must be 100% jealous.
Must be jealous of something. Big nose,
ugly ma. Bro, you're boring now. The
only people that are insecure is
yourselves. You can't even show your
ugly faces. Think about it, bro. They're
coming on here for years, lad. Yeah.
Talking about the way I look. I'm not
hiding my face. They are cuz they know
what they look like. Ugly fat people.
Just like the bomb, you know, just like,
you know, you know what I'm saying? It's
like, bro, every all of these people
that come here and try to talk you talk
about your looks, bro, they're a million
times uglier than you will ever be. Like
I don't think that they understand, bro,
that they don't bother me. What? They
can say a million things about my looks.
They don't bother me because I know what
these people look like on here.
Yeah, I'll be next. You keep telling
yourself that, man. You keep [ __ ]
telling yourself that. [ __ ] off. You weirdo.
You're boring, mate. You're boring.
No one's scared of you, bro. What are
you going to do? [ __ ] send posters,
bro. Everyone knows what you do on here.
Come on, bro. You're supposed to be
psychologically [ __ ] with my head,
but you're not. And this is Cory why I
don't really come on here anymore, lad.
Because of this [ __ ]
Like, cuz they just Yeah, man. Like,
it's just the same jealous people every
single day. This is why I don't really
like coming on here anymore.
a bed and other stuff. Stop taking the
piss. But yeah, I've had to delete my um
videos on my other channel because they found me.
So yeah, I just make another channel and
put the project videos on there and then
just send you a Cory, man. Yeah, it's
not a problem, man.
Yeah, I made that channel specifically
cuz I didn't want them following me.
Specifically didn't want them following
me. It's not a look thing at all.
Listen, you're sat here talking about
the way I look. Yeah. About a million
times. You look like this. You look like
that. Bro, who's the one that's still
showing their face? Me.
I'm the one that's showing my face. No tramodel. No [ __ ] [Music] um
no um tramodel. No [ __ ]
red. No one. I'm the one that's all
showing my face.
They're not. So at the end of the day,
bro, like who's the one that is bothering,
you know? You can never do this, bro. Look,
you can never do this. Think about it,
bro. They can never do this. They can
never show their face. They love to show
I liked wearing hats cuz I like wearing
hats. Balding? Nah, bro. Not even 1% balding.
And no one has ever told me I'm balding
but these bold people. Virgin boy, Red
Star. Only these people Yeah. that are
bored in themselves or bored only try
and call me bored. It's only them people
that already bored. Literally, bro,
they're the only people, bro.
No one's ever used that as an insult.
Not one person.
Not one person, bro.
>> I don't have any I don't have any I
don't have loads of things, man. I'm
just a normal person. Yeah.
Yeah. West Western women. Yeah. I went
out on Thursday. Chubs. I didn't get
anything. But I've got a boyfriend.
Yeah, I didn't get nothing, bro.
Don't got to make another [ __ ]
channel and uploading videos back on there. [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] man. I just don't want
these people following me, lad.
I just don't want these people following
me, you know? Yeah. Yeah, man.
What do you think?
Why do you say westernized women are horrible? horrible, bro?
Yeah, they are. They are, bro. They are.
I think the only thing that's keeping me
alive is probably GTA [ __ ] 6. To be honest,
if I die, bro, I can't I won't be able
to play GTA 6. So,
I don't think I'm doing a football bet
next week in uh
Yeah. Nice sarcasm, bro. Nice sarcasm.
Yeah. It will never change in this
country, bro. It's depressing. But what
are you going to do about it, eh?
You need to leave, man. What's the point?
If you don't leave, then
what's the point? Yeah, man.
Please have a shower later. So, why
can't Red Star do this?
Well, would you want to be would you
want to be alive, Joe,
when you have to keep dealing with this
[ __ ] from women? It's [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] depressing, bro. Oh, [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] depressing. Would you want
to [ __ ] live when you have to keep
dealing with their [ __ ] every time you go out?
Are you actually on the beer later? I
ain't been out in on a Sunday in ages.
Nah, I probably won't be out for like a
month to be honest.
I ain't I ain't going out for a month to
be honest. It's dead in this country,
bro. Like, it's not even money. It ain't
even money. It It really isn't. I just
don't It's just dead to go out like in
this country now because it's always the same thing.
That that Thursday was last time was two
weeks. It's just dead. It's pointless
even going out, bro. It's same It's like
the same outcome.
It's a It's like the same outcome with
just different characters.
Yeah. It's not It's not a nice um
place to be. What I don't understand
with these people on Reddit, Joe, is
they give you advice. Yeah. You take
their advice. If you show them like
approaching videos and messages and then
they actually attack you, it's like
they're scared of the truth.
It's like they're scared of the truth.
So then they just attack you and like
basically abuse you kind of in a way.
Don't know, man.
It's weird, isn't it?
I think my approach is tell you
everything you need to know. I don't
know how they can still tell you that
there's hope, Joe. Every time you go
out, it's it's the same. You're you're
basically [ __ ] Cuz it's like, say you
you didn't go out. Yeah.
Well, nowadays it's a bit different cuz
I've already done it. But say you were a
bit younger and you didn't go out. Oh,
I'm horny. I want sex. Or maybe somebody
wants a relationship. Oh, let me go out.
And then when you go out, you don't get
nothing but the same old [ __ ] which
then causes more and more and more
problems. So, it's like, oh [ __ ] what
do you do? If you try, you're [ __ ]
And then if you don't try, you're bored.
So, what what is there? Nothing.
That's That's the bad thing about it.
There's not really
me. I just I'm just I can't be asked
with it. me like to be honest. So yeah,
I was all dressed up yesterday. I was
ready to leave the Dodger, but because
of that football bet, I was like, "Nah,
I can't be asked." And I was still 280
up as well. It was only £21 I lost. I
just I can't be bothered dealing with
the boyfriend [ __ ] It's [ __ ] boring, mate.
Yeah, I can't be asked with it, man.
It's [ __ ] BS the [ __ ] out of me.
That's why like
Yeah. And there's me thinking I was
going to do approaches for two weeks
sober. [ __ ] that, bro. It's depressing
as as a [ __ ] I swear to God.
You know when you don't go out Yeah. you
you kind of
forget. Not forget, but it kind of heals
a bit. Yeah.
It's bad, isn't it?
This [ __ ] up, is it?
I'm still trying to think about what I'm
actually going to do, bro, from here.
There's clearly no one out there for
you. I mean, you've tried a million million times,
so there's no one out there for you.
So, that's why I was getting into things
to try and take my mind off of it. Like,
I was trying to get into WWE again.
Silly things to get my take my mind off of it.
How I'm completely [ __ ] Not sure.
Well, let me try and make this new
YouTube account. Now,
see these people once they get a hold of
your channel, they ruin everything.
They ruin everything.
So, let me make a new channel now.
They just ruin everything
here. Is not bad cuz I just go live on
this channel, but I don't post content. Yeah,
I think so as well, bro. See, look. He's
still stalking me. That's what I'm
saying. He's still stalking me, bro.
That that red star is still stalking me.
Oh [ __ ] bro. It's just like the
Smokeoky Bee. He sits online all day,
every day calling everyone else exactly
every single thing that he is. What a
sad, pathetic little M special beat is.
But bro, this doesn't trigger me because
that Smokey Bee has been called out a
million times and he won't meet anyone.
So I just gave up with him. looks like a
spazzy version of the I IB for final
boss. What has he done for you to want
to destroy him? I mean, that's a good
question. And I can tell you exactly
what I've done. It's having a better
life and being better looking. You know,
these people, don't forget, these people
are in their 40s,
[ __ ] most of them are [ __ ]
disabled. They ain't really got a lot in
life. So, they see somebody that's
younger than them, better looking than
them, just a better life. doesn't need
to be loads and loads and loads of
money. And that's what they don't like.
So what it is is they hate the fact that
they can't change their own life, which
is why none of these people that do this
are in their 20s. Cuz these people in
their 40s, their lives are [ __ ] It's
over. So that's why they do this every
single day. It's because it's jealousy.
It's hatred and jealousy. That's what it
is. They latched on to anyone that's got
a better life than them.
Because if you see they're prolific with
it. It's not like they just write something
um to get a reaction one. They are
literally prolific. Like they won't stop
ever. Like even when they're dead, they won't stop.
You know, it's not like they just write
something and then well, you go on for
like No, no, no. They literally don't
stop. Think of how many years they've
wasted of their life doing this. Think
of it, bro.
How many how many years have they wasted
doing this? And I'm still here. And I'm
still [ __ ] here, you know?
And the thing is, bro, listen, listen,
listen. I'm a big boy. I can take it. I
don't give a [ __ ] what any of these
people say about what I look like.
But guess what? What I say about you
and what you look like, [ __ ]
it hurts you. That's why you can't show your face.
See, the thing is, Cory, right, me and
you, we can show our face. These people
can never show their face. That's where
you'd always win. That's where you'll
always win the argument cuz they can
never show their face. We can show our
face. They can't show their face cuz
they're ugly. Just like the bomb. So,
it's that's where you'd always beat
them, you see, because Yeah.
No, I want to see £10,000.
No, you can show me £10,000. What I've
been asking you for. You ask me, right, for £10,000, right?
Right. Show £10,000.
Simple. I want to see £10,000.
You're making this seem a lot harder
than it is.
You know, you're making it seem a lot
harder than it actually is.
I want to see Listen, listen, listen,
listen. Okay, how about you do this? Go
to the bank tomorrow and take out
£10,000 in cash. You got no excuse. It's
Monday tomorrow. the bank holiday
tomorrow. Listen, go to the bank
and take out £10,000 in cash. Not a problem.
Not a problem. You You can easily do
that. Stop making excuses. Go in the
bank, withdraw £10,000, and show me it.
Simple. There's no excuses.
Yes. That's why I said to you, go to the
bank and take out £10,000 cash. you know,
go to the bank and take out £10,000.
It's not that hard, is it? Come on, simple.
Can I ask you this question? Right. So,
where did this whole money game
come from? Who started this whole money
game? Any ideas? Any ideas, Cory? Any
any ideas who started this?
Did because I'm trying to think who
actually started this.
Was it Timmy? Who was it? Who was it?
All this this money game is, right, is
just skint people that
it's just skint people that have no
money, so they want you to show them
money because they ain't got no money.
Because the way I see it, bro, is if
you've got all of this money, can't you
look at your own money? That's that's
what I I started saying to him. I was
like, "Hold on. You've got all of this money, right?
Then why why do you want other people to
show money? You've got your own money to look at
and they can't do that because they're
skin. I mean, that's that's that's a
good little saying, isn't it, Grezy?
Should we start Do you know what we
should start doing after this money
game? We should start showing who's got
the better life. You know, I think I
think this whole money thing now is
outdated. I think we should start
showing who's got the better life. I
mean, that's something new, Grezy.
That's something that like I'm sure
you'd love to see. We've done the money
game for years. Let's show who has the
better life. Let's show who's the best
looking. You know, like a big like
battle thing, you know, like like like
you know, something like that. Like I
I've shown you I've traveled Oh. Um, you
want to you you want to Okay. Well, I'll
show you what I've shown. I've I've
shown I've been up and down the country
numerous times. I've had various
different women. I've had£100 steak
meals. I've [ __ ] loads of [ __ ] I've
gone out spending £700 on a date. What
can you show?
Can you Can you have showed me on
planes? Yeah, let's start playing the
the life game cuz I'm already winning by
by a lot. Yeah,
we should start. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So,
that's what I've shown. Let's see what
you shown. What you've shown.
Yeah. This escort was waiting for me
yesterday. Greavves. I didn't end up
going. I couldn't be bothered.
has to be. No, it doesn't have to be
experiences from today. No, it doesn't.
No, it doesn't. No, it does not. Well,
okay. I went to Birmingham two weeks ago
and I spent £200.
Okay. Can you show what you've done?
That's more than what most people have
done in here in probably a decade. Okay.
I went to Birmingham. I spent
200 pound. Yeah, you've seen that. Let's
let Okay, let's see your life.
You remember Joe? I like Chev.
Uh, okay. So, I went to Birmingham,
£200 I spent. Now, it's your turn.
Come on. Let's see.
Oh, I have I have videos of them trips.
Oh, one second. One second. You said the
pass don't count,
you little copycat. I agree.
You're trying to take the piss, aren't you?
I like Chev Cole. You're trying to take
the piss, isn't it? Right.
Let's see what his reply to this. Hold on.
Why did you say that you was Why was you
taking a piss when you said that I like Chevo?
You You was trying to take the piss out
of me in it. Cuz you know how I You know
how I'd react, didn't it? Cuz you're a copycat.
You're just copying
One second. One second. One second. One
second. One sec.
Oh, okay. This red star has replied,
right? This red star has replied yet.
Now, one second. What? This is actually
good. What has he done for you
to want to destroy him? One second. One
second. How long have you got called for
rape of women and kids? Never raped a
woman and kids. Called for acid attacks.
That was [ __ ] years ago when I was
21. Bullies women. Harasses them. Never
bullied anyone. Never harassed anyone.
Blames everyone else for his failings in
life. Sublets his house. Nothing. No
harm in subleting. So he's just made up
things to become obsessed. Um, and you
know what, right? I'm going to call this
guy out one more time. If he has got
such a problem with all of these things,
come and meet me tomorrow then it's like
listen bro you have begged this [ __ ]
London Taylor this black guy numerous times t
okay come and meet me and I'll smash
your face in if if if this is really
really bothering you that much. Meet me
and I'll smash your teeth down your throat tomorrow.
Yeah, you beg London Taylor. Come on big
man. You know, you're on YouTube
reacting every day. I will I will travel
to anywhere you want and I'll smack your
teeth down your [ __ ] throat and then
you can add one of them.
[ __ ] what the [ __ ] a sublet in a
house got to do with you? [ __ ] he's
talking absolute [ __ ] [ __ ] acid
attacks. What the actual [ __ ] is this
weirdo going on about?
What the actual [ __ ] If you've got a problem
Yeah. Hey, I don't give a [ __ ] about
court. [ __ ] out of here, you dirty
grass. You dirty [ __ ] grass. Don't
even come in with your grass and talk.
You know, blames everyone else for his
failings. Is this guy sick? Okay. Well,
come and meet me then. Come and meet me,
big man. If you've got all of this
energy behind a keyboard, big man, come
and I'll slap your face. I will [ __ ]
get my hand and [ __ ] slap you across
your [ __ ] bald head with it. Baldy
bastard. And I'll show everyone the true
ma. The m of all time. Bomb number two.
I've offered I've offered to travel as
well. Like it's not even like I've said
I'm going to waste your [ __ ] time. I
will travel to where you want and I will
give you that chance to do something
about it, Mr. Coward. I will give you that chance.
I don't want you to keep tormenting
yourself and embarrassing yourself on
YouTube every day like you've been doing
for years. I'll give you the chance. I
don't want you to travel to me cuz
obviously your anxiety is a bit too
much. I'll give you every single chance
to come and do something to my face. You
begged the black man enough [ __ ]
times, you coward. You cowardly bastard
behind your little gay account. You know
what I'm saying? You know,
I'm going to call this guy out one more
time and I'm going to give him a chance
to come and do something about it. And
if he's not going to do anything about
it, then stop winding yourself up
because as soon as I make this new
channel, right, I'm I'm going to tell
you exactly what I'm going to do again.
I'm going to tell you exactly what I'm
going to do again. Right? Bullies
[ __ ] women. I'll [ __ ] bully you
and your [ __ ] mom to your [ __ ]
face, you silly [ __ ]
I will bully you and bully your [ __ ]
mom as a woman to your face, you silly
[ __ ] You know what I'm saying? [ __ ]
stupid. This is jealousy again, bro.
This is what I'm saying.
Let me reply to this stupid [ __ ] bro.
One second. I'm going to go anywhere he
wants, you know? Let's see how much he
cares about what I've done. One second,
bro. [ __ ] this.
At least they won't be talking over each
other this time.