Hey man,
sorry man. I was I was a little w
yesterday owning the owning the virgin.
Sorry about that, man. Yeah.
Sorry, I had to add that synth thing in
it, man. Uh, I had to add that uh
I had to add that simply
generally a little bit why people defend
women when they when they don't get
women into it. I don't know about it.
So, I had to add that in there, bro. I
know it seemed a bit like it was it was
it was off topic, but I don't know, man.
That really confuses me why people do
and it actually makes you feel like it
actually reminds you how good you've had it.
Did you know what most simps are like? So yeah,
sorry about that, man. I had to add it
in there, but I had to add it. Oh man,
this [ __ ] ain't charging proper, is it, man? [ __ ]
I swear this has got a better controller, man.
If I were someone like these people, I'd
be actually hating women.
But they defend them. It's magnet. Strange.
Don't know why they do it. They do it on
Reddit as well. It's strange. Autism maybe. Who knows?
Something's not right, is it?
Strange. Yeah, just had to add that bit
in the video. The simp thing. No, wait.
I'm going YouTube after today anyways,
man. Oh, [ __ ] cuz of uh by the fourth
day it becomes weird again.
I said one, two, three, and then four
and it becomes weird again.
Yeah, man. It's clear these people will
never ever stop. They ain't got a life.
I should I shouldn't be entertaining
these low lives to be honest with you.
It's fun for like a day or two, but it's too much.
It's all right, you know, but the thing
that these people actually like they
actually live for this. Like these
people actually live for this. It's not
even like they they wake up and one one
day a week they do this or two days a
week or every two weeks. They actually
live for this
madness, isn't it? That how without self projecting
and [ __ ] they have nothing in their
life. They actually live for it. these
these low lives on here. It's mad, isn't
it? What's happening? [ __ ] all, bro. Just chilling.
Yeah, I had a got a bit of a headache.
So, Oh, that video brought you back
then, didn't it? Best. Yeah, I blocked
Monty. Oh, I I met Monty yesterday. I
met Monty uh two weeks ago, but I
blocked him, lad. Yeah, I blocked I
blocked Monty, bro.
Cuz um I didn't like what he was saying
that I'm the one that needs to grow up
yet he's 35 cried over a [ __ ] woman.
Um and I just didn't like the way he's
like turning like in in roundabout ways
so I just blocked him. Yeah, bro. That's
the thanks you get, eh?
I mean, I don't know who you can
actually trust. You know, Bar Quest
licks ass when Pat Mustard in town.
[ __ ] Monty man [ __ ] you know switches
[ __ ] maybe I could be able to trust Squeezy
rock cuz you always used to lick ass.
Yeah. Getting ready for uh GTA 6, man.
But I'm not going to say bad stuff about
money. I don't do that, bro. I don't I
don't I don't um meet someone and then
start saying mad stuff after I've met
them. That's what [ __ ] do. Like the
virgin virgin boy does that. And other
people as well. I don't do that [ __ ]
man. I just So I just don't agree with
them and just stop talking to them, you know? So
yeah, I'm still dealing with the
boyfriend [ __ ] Uh rest
and and man and man's in Thailand. He's
living there now. He wants me to come
out there. He said it's never going to change.
So, I don't know, man.
Yeah, it's coming out. Well, no. It says
it's coming out May 2026.
Nothing will ever change, bro. Same old,
bro. Is it? Same old, lad. Same old.
Yep. Same old. Bas bought me a game.
Maybe October, maybe. But it is
scheduled for May, but they might keep
delaying it. Who knows? Yeah.
H I remember. Good old Park. Park bought
me a little game. I'm playing GTA right
now, bro. Oh, I got an Xbox now. Xbox on
a TV. I'm playing GTA 6.
Yeah, I'm playing [ __ ] um GTA 6.
I think the Xbox controller is a lot
better. Not GTA 6, GTA 5 or GTA 6. Oh,
it's just the old Xbox One. Yeah, I got
it a couple of years ago.
A few years ago, bro.
Plant a piggy on there.
What? You got Xbox?
It's ITZ. Oh, by the way, I've got Black
Ops 2, by the way, cuz Black Ops 2 is
the best Call of Duty. It's ITZ PX.
Yep. It px.
I do remember
do you remember you when you used to say to boy
you said you remember that
you said that you remember you said that
you remember it don't you the live stream
you said that you remember the live
stream don't you
know it's px X. No, no, no. I t Z P E T E X
I T Z P E T E X add me cuz I'm not going
to be on here for a little while after
today, bro. After the third day, it
becomes weird again. And it's weird how
people actually live for this [ __ ] as
well doing what they do on it over
there. That's why you don't see me on
there. But do you remember Vest? Um,
stop going on about some girl that don't
want you. Uh, I'm not.
And he starts pulling the door. I'm not.
I'm not, mate. I'm not.
No, I would never get old. Breezy. I
think this was before your time. Yeah.
Oh, it's class, man.
Do you I think Do you remember it? Do
you remember it? [ __ ] Do you remember
it? I'm not. No, he done it. He done it
like this, bro. He done it like this.
No. No. Let me Let me replica it. Hold on.
Let me try and use the fan as a door.
One second. Yeah. He he does it like
this. Look, stop go
stop. He like he clicks the comment.
He's like, "Stop going on about some
girl that don't, you know, give your
head a wobble and stop going on about some girl
that don't want you." Oh, no.
That's what That's what he done. Then
then he started talking about me and Isabelle.
Sorry, mate. Then he started talking
about me and Isabelle.
[ __ ] weirdo, ain't it? We had some
good times, didn't we?
Yeah, we had some good times me and you
is it TZ P X?
What man? Listen. I T Z P E T E X.
Do you remember Barcast?
[ __ ] mad bastard him, ain't he? Yeah,
he's a nutter.
It will never change.
You should be able to find it. I t Z P T E X.
This is just the thanks I get for going
to Birmingham. Grey,
you really want to know what I think?
You want to know what I think?
Yeah. Bquest, we can watch Spongebob
together and watch Little Ponies.
Well, you want to know what I think?
It's the way you said it. Is it? Yeah.
Well, you really want to know what I think?
So, you you saw you saw me in Birmingham
with Monty then? Yeah, man.
They're all [ __ ] You had me.
Yeah, I got Black Ops 2, bro. I bought
Black Ops 2.
Black Ops 2 is the goat, man. Black Ops
2 is the [ __ ] goat.
Yeah, I had to delete all my videos on
my other channel, lad. [ __ ]
these people discovered me. I think
that's how they were discovering me,
bro. From like Reddit.
That's how they were discovering me. Yep.
Nice, man. Nice.
It be like the good old days. Bquest.
Oh, bless you.
You been watching any um you you been
watching any like horror movies?
I can't remember if you said you was
into them, but I've been watching quite
a lot to be honest.
Where How do I go on this?
I'm still getting used to this Xbox
thing, you know.
I'm not Oh, here you go. Yeah, I'm still
getting used to this new Xbox thing,
bro. I can't say I'm used to it cuz I
just played the game on it. So,
how comes you've got an Xbox?
I don't understand why. I thought, see,
I'm PlayStation. I don't know why I got
an Xbox. I got it a couple of years. Oh,
here we go. I got it a couple of years ago.
Oh, here you go. Yeah, I got it a couple
of years ago.
The Xbox, man. Um, man, I didn't really
get start I didn't really start getting
into gaming cuz I didn't have a TV for ages, you know?
Do you know what I'm saying?
Like, um, I had to phone I had to own
the Virgin early, Nicolo. So yeah, I had
to um I just bought Xbox cuz I feel like
the Xbox looked better. But I've always
been PlayStation. Don't I have always
been PlayStation, but I don't know. I
just fancy the change all them years.
Saying that I'll never move to iPhone
though, which is strange. I've been
Samsung all my life and I don't think I
could ever move to iPhone.
I don't think I could ever move to iPhone, bro. I'm not.
Stop. Yeah. Stop going on about some
girl that don't want you.
Yeah, she doesn't want you. Remember that barest?
You remember when I put you up in the
pedo groups? See me and Bar quest has
had beef as well. Do you remember when I
used to put you up in them pedo groups?
Yeah, that's bro. That's cuz you used to
lick ass, man.
Yeah, that's cuz you used to lick ass, though.
You drove me to it, man. You [ __ ] You
made me You made me do it because you
was licking ass,
you know, [ __ ] licking ass, man, all the time.
But the dating game is getting harder
now, you know. Um, Bar Quest lad, it's
it, you know, like two years ago, 18
months ago, it was actually like
somewhat possible. Even though it was
very hard, it was you could get kisses
and dates. Now you can't even get nothing, bro.
I can't I can't even.
This seems to have gotten a lot hard. I
think most people moved to Tik Tok now.
But it's okay. Me and you can be together.
Oh, I don't know how it is for gay people. But
I don't know now. And it's you can't
even talk to anyone now, bro. It's It's
hard now. I went to I went to
Birmingham, bro, and I got three
numbers. But the mad thing is they all
replied with enthusiasm. But then when
it come to meeting a few of them, they
they didn't want to know. So I still got
some numbers I could try from a few
weeks ago, but after that I'm done, bro.
I can't be asked for it, lads. Yeah.
Do you remember Do you remember USA? Is
he um Bquest? I like it that Bquest is
back. You know, me and Barrist go way
You know, me and Bquest.
Me and Bquest go way back.
Uh, yeah, we do.
But saying that, bro, I should hate you.
You [ __ ] paid LJ to come here. Why
would you of all people pay the L to
come here, lads?
You know, that's crazy, man. You paid LJ
to come here. I could have got hurt. I
could have got seriously injured.
I mean, that's like that's the thing
that's kind of mad now. [ __ ] the licking
ass. That's whatever, bro. That's
whatever. But you actually paid someone
that could have come and actually
seriously hurt me.
Yeah, but it could have. It could have.
You knew he wouldn't fight. Yeah, that's
true, man. Now you're back for good. I
have to [ __ ] stay, bro. [ __ ] sake. Jesus Christ.
All right, bro. I was watching. You know
what's got Hey, Barus. What's What's
your favorite GTA? Everyone else
answered. Mine is San Andreas cuz I
think the story line is like the best.
My My favorite one San Andreas. Yours is
probably four. Grievy's is four. Mine is San Andreas.
Yeah. So, you're the same as Grievy. I
just I don't know. I think the storyline
is just so good.
But yeah, Grievy picked four as well.
But I think San Andreas just has it made, bro.
You're not into GTA. How can you not be
into GTA, you silly goose?
How could you not be into silly?
Yeah, I can't remember three. I have
played it, but I can't remember it. This
GTA 6 better be [ __ ] good.
They've had us waiting for [ __ ] 14
years, bro. They better [ __ ] be good.
But yeah, Black Ops 2 is the best Call
of Duty, bro. It cost me £1199. It was
actually £32, even though it's an old
one, but it cost me £1.99, you know.
So, was you watching the whole time?
Were you watching the whole time then? Bquest.
Look at you watching the whole time.
Just picking your moment. When to
comment again? Just sat there picking your moment.
Bless you then.
But yeah, I don't know. I see the thing
is with me, bar quest, I don't care
about sex. I just like [ __ ]
So, I don't even give a [ __ ] about sex.
I hate I had Well, I had Oh, last I went
to an air school last week. I didn't
even have sex. I got [ __ ] I didn't
have sex for like eight months, bro. I
just get [ __ ] from like, you know,
paid services or when I used to have
someone. I don't even [ __ ] me.
Why have you found dating impossible
though? Have you been trying or
something? Or I thought it would have
been easier for by people or gay people.
I could go I could literally go to a gay
bar and I would have people hitting on
me. I could go out for 12 hours approach
and I wouldn't even know to get a date.
[ __ ] up, bro. And it's madness.
No, I can't be bothered with it anymore,
bro. I don't really go out much drinking
anymore. I can't afford it like I used to.
I was getting like three grand a month.
Now I don't get as much now. But it
doesn't It's not even just that anyways,
bro. Like I've still got money. I can
still go out, but I just can't be asked that.
I think you're like two years older than
me. So two years younger than me, sorry.
Yeah, I don't bother anymore.
You remember Antman?
So, um, Best, how's it How's the
approaches getting on? How's it going
on? How's it getting on? I bet you're
out there killing it. How's it going on?
They've all got boyfriends.
I said, "Calm down, Antman. We don't we
don't want you to end up back in prison.
Calm down. He said
I I'll never forget that.
Um no yeah I'm almost well yeah I'm 28
in two months. Yeah.
Bro, why do you keep talking about that
prime thing? I was literally in
Birmingham two weeks ago calling out
Prime. I was I was in his city calling
him out. That's outdated now, bro.
Yeah, I did you, man. Did you get it?
Sorry, just the spastics on here, bro.
Bro, I was in Birmingham calling him out
like two weeks ago, bro.
If he didn't want to come out, then
that's on him, bro. What the [ __ ] do you
want me to do?
I could imagine being starved by my mom.
My mom is actually a very nice mommy.
My mom's actually My mom's a a nice D is
a very good mom, you know,
like an actual very very good mother. Really is,
you know, not like a certain person's
mom that starved them and put them in
hospital. Some people e
I could imagine uh touching my [ __ ]
face and and having a baby face cuz I
can't grow uh facial hair. Some people
but it was a good video though. What the
video that he done of me was pretty good
man. It was pretty pretty good. What bit
did you like particularly of the video?
I don't know why he thinks he can he
could try with Peter Benny. I don't know
why he actually thinks he could try. I'm
a d I'm dangerous.
Um I have [ __ ] people running to the
police over YouTube.
Oh, I got teeth as well. I didn't get
stolen by my mom either.
He wasn't a big man when he [ __ ]
stepped when he stepped that I didn't
[ __ ] up against the [ __ ] wall. Did he?
I did have you, bro.
And I want this Indonesian guy to stop
messaging me, man.
I wish he would just stop messaging me.
[ __ ] sake. I wish he would just stop
messaging me. This [ __ ] this
Indonesian guy, bro.
You can't even speak to him and you're
scared. What are you messaging me for?
[ __ ] it up, huh? Yeah.
Do you remember Bark Quest, Nicolo?
Nah, not really.
Do you remember Bark? Don't you, Nicolo?
I think I'm I'm scared to approach now.
Nah, I don't think I could ever be. I
just think once you get to a certain
age, you just realize it's never it's
never going to happen in this country.
You get to a certain age, you know?
The only the only time I get a break for
it is when I'm asleep or eating a lovely McDonald's greasy.
That's the only time I get a break from it.
You know, that's why I love it when I'm
about to fall asleep cuz I don't have to
think about it.
Bet you look like a right. Yeah.
Why the [ __ ] is he doing a video showing Hulk Hogan?
I don't understand. Yeah. He says that
I'm I'm the ugly one, but he's the only
one that can get disabled women. And I
have basically been in a relationship.
Basically, I have. And I've also had
chances to be in relationships as well,
but I've never been with an Oompa Loompa
disabled girl that can't talk. I can
remember that much.
And uh yeah, and bro, you [ __ ] live
with your [ __ ] mom, bro. He literally
Yeah, I don't know who you live with,
Bar Quest. Yeah, I've said it many, many
times, right? That it's not um it's not
ideal, but it's nowhere near as as bad
as that virgin's making out. It's
nowhere near It's nowhere near as bad as
he he's he is making out loud. He lives
in a [ __ ]
care home with no [ __ ] bed in it.
What the [ __ ]
It's nowhere near as bad as that
virgin's making out. I mean, what what
does what does most people do? You know,
he's never worked in his life. He's
never paid rent or anything.
All because his mom hates him. He
doesn't like anyone else having a
relationship with their mom.
You know what I mean?
He doesn't like anyone else having a
relationship with his mom because his
mom hates him.
It's crazy, bro. Is it
crazy? Is it? It's crazy, man.
Yeah, but I'm the ugly one, isn't it?
Yeah. That's why you're the one who's
stalking the women that I've been with
who's a jealous cuz I'm the ugly one in
it. That's how ugly I am in it, Nicolo.
I'm so ugly, right? That I can get all
of these women that he can't get that he still stalks.
Sorry, Nicolo. I had to add the simp
thinking simp thing in there because I
generally don't understand yet. I say
one thing that's [ __ ] up, bro.
Yeah. Like, oh, like they're stuck up
and they pretend they got boyfriends.
harmless things that I back up and then
you get all of these simps that have
never had women or had less women than
you and they sit there coming to their
rescue like Superman.
They actually makes you think, "Oh [ __ ]
how bad how good you actually had it. If
any woman should be licking women's
asses, it should be me."
But they just defend them and they don't
get them and women don't like them.
They're to their rescue like Superman.
I don't know why they do it, bro.
>> Why do they do it though? Why do they do it?
Why do they Why do they defend women?
I'd love like a a proper debate about this, bro. You know,
you reckon it's autism or
I'm I'm generally curious like why they do it?
just sit there and defend them like the
way they do. I just don't know why they do it.
And I like I like I forgot to mention
the thing is that you say that I'm an
incel, but I've had more women than you
and I've had more sex than you. So, how
can I be an incel when I've literally
had more women than you? What? Because I
don't cuz I'm not a s. So, because I'm
not a s and I don't lick women's asses,
I'm an incel. Okay, then. Oh, is that
the new word now? Yeah,
I think it is autism. A lot of people
do. Okay. Okay. Let me let me let me let
me use this analogy. Yeah.
How many women have you seen me with on this community
and I've never seen a day in my life?
How many women have you seen Virgin Boy
with and Laur with?
Anyone would think I should be defending
them because I've had sex and I've had
women and I've [ __ ] and I've had my
dicks. I'm the one that should be
defending them, not them.
But I can't defend them, bro. I think they're [ __ ]
You know, I I've approached people before um
Bquest and they've said, "Oh, not
interested straight away." And just
their genu behavior.
I don't know how people can defend them,
especially people that's had worse than
me. That's what I don't get it. I don't
know how they defend them, bro. But they
still do. Me and Antman always talks
about this. But
they're stuck up and [ __ ]
Nah, not anymore. I'm not. I used to be
when you could actually pull.
Do you remember that that American one?
That was my mama Bquest.
That was my mummy. My mommy abandoned me. Uh
yeah. Do you remember Barker? She'll be my 25th.
She said the slower the better.
Are we boyfriend and girlfriend yet, Nikolai?
Are we boyfriend and girlfriend yet?
But no, they are rude, bro. You you
approach people and they they sometimes
they just say they're not interested,
which is strange because people sit
there and say that you're going to find
someone. But when you try and speak to
someone, you get people that are being rude.
Yeah. It was funny, is it? Are we
boyfriend and girlfriend yet? Well, it's
a little early to know.
No, mama. It's not early to know. Mama,
what are you doing sitting on the couch
all by yourself? Mama.
Yeah, it's cute, man. It's cute. Imagine
that, though. Bar quest, you kissing
someone and they say that you you'll be their 25th.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro. Oh, you know who
I can't stop laughing at, Barest? Timmy.
Sometimes I'll click the YouTube app and
Timmy's face comes up.
Yeah, I went out in the feelings. I went
out in the in the in the fields B West
and I sent her a voice note um
reaching out my little love for her and
she didn't give a [ __ ] She left me all
alone and she didn't care.
She said, "Oh, thank you for reaching
out." I said, "Can we talk on the phone?"
Yeah. I was in I was in a bad place then, bro.
like, oh man, that was that was that was
bad times, but I don't even like
thinking of it. And that's how I how I
knew they were true. I had to buy a new
phone as well, Nicolo.
I had to buy a new phone as well.
The phone was like, and I texted them
and they were just like, "Fucking,
I think it's best we go." our separate
ways. I said separate ways. You've
literally told me to come to [ __ ]
America and get a tattoo with you. What
do you mean go separate ways?
Then send another message then just
blocked like the coward that she is. So
I have to write barest
I have to write bar a um poem. Yeah.
I can't stop laughing at Timmy's face.
You know when Timmy comes back on YouTube? Remember Timmy?
I used to send it to Monty. Yeah.
When he actually You said you'd get with
Timmy. Timmy Park.
You said you'd get with Timmy.
Oh, that's funny. Yeah. You said you'd
get with him in it.
I think you send me a little message. One second.
What you get? What you see? Would
you get with Virgin Boy?
You have to admit though, Xbox has got
the better. It's got the better controller.
You love I like your personality, but
you're not my type. Oh, look at the little ponies. Oh, bless.
Oh, I'm looking at little ponies. Oh,
Isabelle was a little pony.
I used to call her a little pony. My little Isabelle.
I used to think that if we had a baby,
it would come out as a as a pony.
That's my mama. Well, no, she's not my
mommy cuz she's too old. She's too young
for me. But yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Izzy, that's my um she was a pony.
Do you remember? Oh,
I said your little hair, you look like a little pony.
Yeah, look, I was out there. I was out
there last week looking for that change.
It would And man says it will never
change. Never change, mate. Never
I don't even know why we're laughing at
it, bro. It's [ __ ] depressing.
So what? You don't You don't think I'll
find anyone in this country? Bar quest.
Is that what you're saying?
Is that what you're saying, lad?
What do I eat today? You might Really?
What would give you What would give you that impression?
What would give you that impression, lad?
You'd get You can't even get a one
night. You can't even get laid now.
But I mean,
maybe if you Well, technically, same
thing. Yeah. But I mean, that's even
hard now. I can't remember the last time
I kissed someone.
I used to be able to kiss someone all
the time, but I can't even you can't
even do that. I mean, like in the clubs and [ __ ]
but you can't even do that now.
Like even that is very very even
difficult to get. Can't remember the
last one I kissed in a club. [ __ ]
Do I have money? Yeah, maybe 1,200. Um,
do you see me doing that Uber delivery,
Mark? I was doing that Uber delivery.
Did you see it?
I was getting a lush can.
What do you mean they're all stuck up?
What? Women all stuck up. Yeah.
Yeah. Women all suck up. Yeah. Obviously
that's who you refer. I don't know if
it's any different in Ireland.
I don't think it's as bad in Ireland. Is
it not like
is it bad? Is it bad in Ireland or
But they say it's a hookup culture.
Oh, I done a nice stunt there.
Yeah, they say it's hookup culture.
Yeah, they say it's hookup culture, bro. Yeah.
Imagine quest. Me, you, and Izzy having
a free me, you, Izzy, and USA. Izzy
having a form.
Wow. What a lovely site.
That's a lovely site, is it? That would
be the dream, isn't it?
That would be living the dream. Yeah.
Yeah, man. That would be the dream, eh?
[ __ ] Got run over. Franklin. I think
Franklin's a lovely little character.
Barkfest. He's my new favorite. Oh, Franklin.
I don't know if you like Franklin. Oh, Franklin.
Oh, Frank. He got run over.
Yeah, I was speaking to some guy in
America yesterday, um, Ohio, like the
southern state, and he said there, like
it's impossible there, which I knew
America was bad, but I thought the
southern states would be a little bit
easier, but he said, "Nah,
kind of fancy something, you know, B West, not McDonald's.
Not sure on piggies.
>> Oh, poor Franklin. Poor Franklin.
He got injured. He got caught in a
crossfire. Poor Franklin.
[ __ ] hungry, man.
Bit hungry. Not too hungry, but
don't have anything in. I haven't been shopping, bro.
I think I'm going to have to get a
I'm going to have to come. I'm going to
have to get a McDonald's.
Yeah, I'm going to have to get a McDonald's, bro. What?
I don't really get much [ __ ] on my
channel anymore. I think it's because I
help Look, I helped Monty. Yeah. And he
just [ __ ] [ __ ] me over. I'm
probably going to get a chicken mac meal.
Let me ask.
Yeah, I'm going to get a chicken back, I think.
Have you had the new spicy nuggets?
They're quite lush, you know.
They're quite lost, bro.
Are you going to get a McDonald as well?
It's [ __ ] greed. You got me into this
McDonald, you know?
Right. I only like cheese on mine though, so
I don't want no sauce, no lettuce.
I like KFC, but KFC is too expensive.
When you order it, it's too expensive.
Like £26, bro, I'm not paying that. I mean,
I'll have to eat later again as well. So
I won't be able to obviously
Yeah, I'm ordering McDonald's, bro. [ __ ]
it. Wait, wait. Let me see what his responses.
If not, I love KFC, but
it's ridiculous, bro. Like, it's that's
why I don't really go Nando anymore, to
be fair, cuz it's too expensive for
chicken. I could afford it obviously,
bro, but it's just too I haven't been to
[ __ ] I think it was I went the first
time the other day in like months.
What's your What's your favorite food?
Oh, I tell you what I did have yesterday
the other day is a nice kebab. A nice
shish. Oh, it was lovely, bro.
What's your favorite then? What's your favorite food?
Yeah, I think we do have one. Have you
Have you got Have you got Have you got a Slim's chicken?
Have you Is there a slim chicken?
Oh, yeah. You can't You can't beat
pizza, bro, with with some nice
jalapenos. it. Nice pizza with jalapenos
and a bit of tandoori chicken.
Yeah, I'll try it. Bro, you you should
try slim chicken. Now me, bro, I tell
you a story. Yeah, I can take hot food
unlike Virgin Boy. Um I like Jalapenos.
I like biryanis.
And um I went to Slim Chickens. It's
called Dave Chickens. And I tried their
Reaper burger. Um, it's called a
Carolina Reaper Burger to be exact. And
they said that it's very, very hot and
only three people was able to do it. And
then they said, "Oh, you need to sign a
leaf." And I was like, "Okay, we're
getting into some serious [ __ ] now."
Generally, I thought I could I could
have it. Then I started biting it, bro.
And it almost killed me. Like every
every other bite and bear I could take
hot food. Um,
and every other bite
it was [ __ ] bro. It was like hell.
It was horrible, bro.
Yeah. I don't know what they what
they're [ __ ] putting that. But yeah,
man. So Chick-fil-A. I'm going to I'm
going to I'll try that, bro. But
I think my favorite has got to be like a
nice biryani, bro.
I think like a nice cooked homemade
biryani. I used to live with tenants and
they used to cook like a biryani and it
has to be a homemade one made by like a
Muslim person. Oh, that is next level.
Trust me, I don't know. I think that
birani's got to be my favorite.
But it has to be homemade. Um, that curry. Oh, yeah.
What's your Where do you get pizza from
though, Bar Quest? Cuz I don't I don't
really like Domino's. I do, but I don't
know. It tastes I I went Papa Papa
John's last time,
but I think homemade one tastes better.
The biryani is like basically it's like
it's sort of like um lamb or chicken and
they cook it with rice and like spices and herbs
similar to a curry kind of
but yeah it's banging. It is it is
You have jalapenos. I can't I can't have
a pizza without jalapenos man. But the
thing is, I found like other shops
better than Domino's and Papa John's. It
could just be a normal shop that no one knows about,
but I find there's so many more better shops than
than um than them ones.
What am I up to today, bro? Just
chilling. There's nothing to do. I don't
do anything most days. [ __ ] boring.
Well, bless you then.
Bless you then if there's not a lot of options.
Yeah, I'm doing nothing but just chilling. Yeah.
I won two. Do you still gamble bar
quest? I only gamble in the football
now. I won two weeks in a row, but I was
one go off [ __ ] £140 on [ __ ] Saturday.
I only put 20 pound on it.
Yeah, I just do the football very thingy
now. I don't do the roulette or Frankie.
Oh, bless you then if you want. Yeah. Bless you.
Let's share them.
You got a lot of money in it. Bquest. Bless you.
Wild quest. Rich. Yeah, man.
I used to have a lot more than I I did,
bro. Trust me. I used to have a lot more
than I did. I don't care though really.
I lived a good life for four years so
not I'm not asked.
Yeah, I was doing Uber Eats. I made 90
in a in a day.
I made a 90 in one day. B Quest on Uber
Uber Eats delivery. It was [ __ ] hard.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] long though, man.
You can make like4500 pound a week doing it.
No, you won't make it every day. You
won't make it every day. You make it
Saturday, Sunday, and then some days
will be 40 and 50. But the point is, if
you worked every other day, you could
still make hundreds a week.
But if you bet Yeah. But it's long hours as well.
So no, you could probably
There was one guy when he was doing
delivery, he made 144 in 10 hours. But
there was one Sunday I worked like 8
hours and I got like £50.
But the point is, it's like you have to
if you done it every day or every other
day, it would add up at the end of the week. Basically,
you can still make4500. So, it's what it is. But nice, man.
How How much do you get paid?
Yeah. 500 a week on top of what you already get.
How much do you get a month now? I get like
I get 1,100.
So 400 more than what I used to get. But
is what it is.
So obviously if you got £500 a week on
top of that then
it's good in it. But I won some football
bets as well
which was like £300 together. So
yeah, lucky you man.
Yeah, I used to get three grand a month
for like three years. Bar quest not working.
I used to get three grand a month when I
used to sublet the houses when I used to
sublet the house. But yeah, I can't do
that anymore. So yeah,
I used to just get 3k a month for doing
nothing 3 years. That's why I was able
to travel and [ __ ] escorts and [ __ ] like
that, you know.
But it ain't all good though cuz the
responsibility and it was annoying. But
I used to just get that every month.
Just normal three grand a month for
doing nothing. Is it?
Three grand a month would have been nothing.
I don't know how what I would have done
in them in them three years if I wasn't
on that kind of money, bro.
I generally don't know what I would
actually do in terms of like going out
and drinking and [ __ ]
I'll be [ __ ]
Oh no, you wouldn't be [ __ ] You would
just adjust. But see, I don't care now
cuz I don't I don't really do the going
out anymore. You know, when I was doing
it like three years ago, I've done it so much
that it doesn't even make a difference
to me because I I stopped doing the going out.
So, it's not like I feel like I'm I've
done it all. Like the going out, the
[ __ ] drinking, the escorts, the
[ __ ] the gambling. So, Yeah, man.
I remember when I used to get £700 a
month, walk, I used to get 700 pound a month.
Yeah, I used to get £700 a month.
She has a lot. Remember
that bar? 700 a month.
I think it went up over the years,
didn't it? Yeah.
But my Uber account got banned, so I
can't do that anymore.
I'll try to do it again.
Yeah, I get like 11, but
women aren't the best. They're [ __ ] evil.
I don't know how people can [ __ ] defend them.
Yeah, I get £,100. I've got no bills.
Well, I got two bills was like 30, but yeah.
And obviously I can't pay rent because I
don't have it. So can't give what you don't have.
No, no one, bro. Just talking about it.
Yeah. You pay rent and [ __ ]
I had none of that. I had no free brand
them up as well.
I don't know how you can [ __ ] say
women are the best. They're f I think
they're all [ __ ] evil. for me and suck up.
Uh, no. I'm an incel, but I've had more
women than you.
Yeah. Okay. Even though I've had more
women than you and I've had more sex
than you, I'm an incel. Yeah. You're
you're exactly what we was talking about
earlier. You people that don't get women
that women don't like will be so fast to
defend them, but you don't even you
don't even had a woman.
That's a madness. I don't understand why
you people are not hating them.
I definitely don't understand why you
people are not hating them. Women hate you.
You're not gay. Uh so because I don't
lick women's asses, I'm gay.
So because I I share my opinion that
make I literally think that they're evil.
They're evil. Nasty, horrible bastards.
Why the [ __ ] would I be gay?
What? Because I'm not a s. Why would I
be an insta? What? Because I'm not a s.
Generally sharing my experiences.
Everyone's everyone's everyone's
entitled to their experiences.
What What else do you have to think?
Why would I be gay? Because I'm telling
you what women are like.
What the [ __ ] You use the word gay. I
generally hate them, bro. And I've had
more women than probably any anyone on here.
So, the question is, do I actually have autism?
All women are exactly the same, bro. I
have met so many women and they're
they're all the same. You know what I
used to find as well, Barquest, that
with a woman of a nationality, right?
Every nationality, women, most people
know most people they were not in
relationships. And yes, they are evil.
They're [ __ ] proper stuck up and
proper evil. You know what I used to
find bar quest that every n different
nationality that you'd meet would all be
the same. I give an example. So if you
met five French women, they'd all be the
same trolling. If you met Brit, all
British women, they'd all be the same.
Stuck up American stuff. I found that
most of the women that you'd met, if
they were the same nationality, they
were all the same. I met about six
French seven French people and they were
all the same. They're all non-playing characters.
So, because I don't lick women's asses,
I'm an ins. I'm the problem. Okay. Did
you watch my approaching videos, bro?
Oh, was I the problem when I tried to uh
start a I'm having this conversation
with you again? I remember you, bro.
We've had this conversation before.
Yeah. Hey. Yeah, we've No, we had this
conversation before, bro. And I think I
showed you videos as well. Yeah, I'm not
having this conversation, bro. Bro, I'm
not having this conversation again.
Yeah, I showed you videos where I
approached women and they were stuck up.
Oh, yeah. I remember you, bro. Yeah, I'm
not having this conversation with you again.
All of these little simps that don't get
women that have had less women than you
are or defending them. This is exactly
what I was talking about on my video.
Simps that don't get women should be
hating them, but they're defending them. It's crazy.
Was I the problem, PC, when I approached
somebody and then they pretended they
had boyfriends or they said straight
away they weren't interested? Was I the
problem that time as well?
There's no point me showing you videos
because no matter what you're shown,
you're just going to deny it anyways.
So, it's pointless, lad. Well, my videos
say that I'm not the problem. Okay.
Well, let me tell you something. My
videos sure say that I'm not.
Well, my videos say otherwise, and it
shows they're the problem. And actions
speak louder than words.
My my videos say otherwise when I've
gone out speaking to them. So, and they
keep pretending they got boyfriends.
My videos say otherwise.
So, you think I don't think my videos
show and actually speak louder than
words? Uh, you got Snapchat? I'll show
you them if you want, bro. Oh, [ __ ]
[ __ ] Where the [ __ ] is this? You You
really want to see it? But if I show you
them, you're going to have to pro
probably watch them, right? Right.
Add me on Snapchat. Now, the thing is I
I I want I want to be critiqued. Yeah.
Um uh 66 66. Yeah.
>> Yeah. M
Well, have you got WhatsApp? I'll give
you my number if you want. Everyone's
got my number. I won't talk to you. I
don't want you to try and tell me I'm the problem. Yeah.
Right. But one thing, I don't want to be compared.
I don't mind constructive criticism, but
I don't want to I don't want to be compared.
I don't want to be compared to strangers
cuz that's wasting everyone's time, if
you know what I mean. Hey, Bar Quest.
Yeah, add me on WhatsApp. I'll send it
I'll send it to you on WhatsApp.
I want you to tell me to my videos. Come
on. You've put me in a bad mood now.
keep defending women, right? Why do you
people keep defending women when you had
less than me? Bro, I I'm starting to
diagn I'm starting to uh think that
you're [ __ ] all the Listen, PC,
message me on WhatsApp. I'm not going to adopt you.
I want to show you this, bro. I want to
I want to show you my videos.
Yeah, bro. [ __ ] him anyways, man. Listen, bro. Right.
You know that you know that in you know
why do you keep singing? It will never
get you women. I've had more women than
you and I hate them. And I tell my mom
the same. I generally hate them.
They're [ __ ] evil. They're [ __ ]
I've never been shown any different.
It's like a a person right that believes
in in in [ __ ] God. They've been
brought up to not show any different.
How can you believe something you've
never seen? Anyways, PC, I'll give you
my number and I'm I swear to God I'm not
going to dox you, bro.
Well, bro, if I'm saying something, I'm
obviously saying it for a [ __ ]
reason, aren't I? Listen, [ __ ] all of
that, bro. Just message me on WhatsApp,
bro. Can you message me on WhatsApp? I
want your number. I promise.
Well, have you got any email?
You don't have happy relationships. Most
of you don't have relationships.
Listen, can you email me then?
I hate women.
And I probably have more than anyone here.
It's got to be my
Yeah, some Okay, some. Okay, fair.
I have good.
No, listen. Trevor Dawson, I don't know
why you're still talking [ __ ] mate. I
was in Middlesborough. You didn't even come out.
Are you forgetting that time I traveled
5 hours and you didn't come out, bro?
Why are you still typing on YouTube,
bro? Embarrass him. You people got no
shame, do you?
I went to Middlesbr. I don't know if you
ever saw it
West, but his [ __ ] ass didn't come out.
No, stop using that as an excuse. No,
no, no, no, no. Everybody knew I was there.
Everybody knew I was there. Stop with
the excuses because if that was really,
really true, right? You would have
walked to the exact same place as I was
there. My looks, I'm better looking than
you, you ugly bastard.
I'm I'm not the one sing over women like
you, mate. Listen. I'm better looking
than you, you ugly northeast bastard.
And at the end of the day, mate, if that
was the truth, right?
You You would have just went there to
see. You northerners are all the same.
You make the same excuses. You make the
same excuses. You northerners are all
built the same, bro. You use the same excuses.
You use the same [ __ ] excuses. You do
the same thing with London Taylor as
well. You You'll agree with what? Hold
on. Hold on. What? You agree with whatever Dawson
if that was true then you would have
walked to that location.
You would have walked to that location
and you would have seen that I was
there. So you can't even use an excuse
because you're 5 minutes away from where
I was. It's all excuses with you
northerners. And also with the bomb I
went live in Manchester and everyone saw
it. You northerners are all full of
excuses. You're something to laugh at. You northerners
have been using the same excuses for
donkey years. It's the same excuses with
different people that you use. I was in
your town and you couldn't even walk 5
minutes up the road to see if I was
there. You couldn't even walk 5 minutes
to prove I wasn't there. If I wasn't
there, bro, stop it. You're embarrassing
yourself. Right. Middlesbrough is 5
hours away from London. Stop talking [ __ ]
Stop talking [ __ ] You northerners are
built the same. You're all the same. You
[ __ ] northerners have been doing this
since [ __ ] women have been saying
they've got boyfriends. [ __ ] off. Huh?
Because I done a video showing where I
was. I'm blocking you now. Anyways,
mate, you're all full of excuses. I hate
this, bro. I hate listening to these
excuses. They used to do the same thing
with London say that it's always these
excuses with these organizers. It's
always the same [ __ ] excuses with
these people, bro.
You know, I don't know how many times me
and London Taylor waste our money. Yeah.
Going up to see these [ __ ]
Northerners and they don't come out. I
don't know how much money we've [ __ ]
wasted doing this. It's annoying, bro.
Just seeing that, bro. I hate that. I
hate that [ __ ] bro. I swear. [ __ ] simp.
I tell you what, PC, right?
I'll put some approaching videos on my channel.
Um, and I'll send you them at some
point. Well, my other channel.
No, bro. I'm not coming. No, you annoy
me. Using them excuses are annoying me, bro.
All full of excuses.
all of excuses.
See, the thing is, if I was a mad [ __ ]
like I was back in the day, I would have
went to middle school today.
If I was a mad [ __ ] right, like I was
years ago before I knew what these
people was about, I would have went to
middle school today, bro.
I hate people like that, bro. Making
excuses, you know, but I hate it. So why can't
why people have their own opinions on women?
Why do you um do [ __ ] that will ask you about it? H
I tell you a story. You're still there. What?
Why do these simps go mad
when nothing you're saying is even offensive?
You say that women are stuck up because
of your videos and they all go on the
bandwagon and start insulting you. So,
is there any point of anyone even having
a different opinion than if you're just
going to get insulted?
It's like you you It's like someone
gives you advice. Yeah,
you take their advice and you show the
bad side of women, then they will attack
you. So, I mean, is there a point of anyone having
saying anything then? Because I just get
attacked and there's no point.
Despite trying to say that I'm the
problem, what when you're trying to
speak to people and they're giving you
attitude and they're pretending they got
boyfriends, that's that's me being the
problem. Or when you've approached
people in the past and they've said
straight away they're not interested.
Oh, when they've messed around with you.
What? That's my fault. I asked for that
to happen. Think about what you're
saying, bro. So, I I asked for that to happen.
I I asked for that to happen. I done
that myself. Yeah. [ __ ] simple, bro.
I swear to God.
I'll give you my WhatsApp number. You
can text me, bro.
I'm going to show you some of these. 07542 382759.
I'm going to show Bar some of these
messages I've got as well. I want I want
I want constructive criticism. Don't
agree with me if you don't want to agree
with me and don't disagree with me if
you don't want to disagree with me. I
want you to do, but there's only one
thing you can't do is compare me to another person.
That's the only thing I won't have
because that's a waste of everyone's time.
I embark with some of these things, bro.
Not even these approaches. And I want
you to tell me and don't just say I'm
right if I'm not right.
I hate them excuses, man. That's why I
had to block him. I hate it. I hate it
when they used to do it to London Taylor as well.
Even when me and London Taylor was
beefing, like I don't like them excuses, bro.
Oh, you done a pre-recorded video. Oh,
no. [ __ ] if I done a pre-recorded
video, why didn't you walk up 5 minutes
up the road and you would have seen I
was there then?
[ __ ] I hate them excuses, bro. I
swear to God.
like, but yeah, just message me now.
Message me now and I and I'll message you, bro.
And you if I'm wrong, then then say I'm
wrong. Don't tell me I'm right. If I'm
if you don't bring it,
>> sometimes they make me feel like I'm the
virgin. Sometimes these simps actually
make you feel like you're the one that
don't get women like them. I haven't had
Right. Here we go. Okay. So,
I'm going to send you some approaching
and I'm going to send you some screenshots from numbers
that I've got from approaching as well. Right. So,
one sec, bro.
And the numbers are basically people
that I've approached.
What is that? But it one second.
My eyesight's getting worse.
You need to give me your honest opinion
on these. One second, bro. I'm I'm
coming back. Yeah. Hold on because I
can't see my
I can't see my
One second. I can't see my thing. One
sec, bro. Give me two seconds. Yeah.
about that, bro. [ __ ] Yeah, I sent you
basically a lot of stuff, bro.
I don't know what the fitness my screen's [ __ ]
but basically that's that's the gist of
it. I mean, they're they're they're
fairly recent ones. So, you need to tell
me specifically what I'm doing wrong.
Cuz if I didn't want constructive criticism,
I wouldn't uh
if I if I didn't want constructive
criticism, I wouldn't like
wouldn't post online.
I generally wouldn't even post online, bro.
It's okay, but just just not to be compared
and you need to watch the screenshots on
some of the numbers, but anyways. Yeah,
you'll find yourself in a dead end. you
you you'll find yourself in in a in a dead end. Trust me,
I think so. Hey, can you give
that insel word is so boring now, bro.
It's like it's the same as calling
someone a [ __ ]
It's the same as calling a woman a
[ __ ] It has no substance.
Just like calling someone an insult.
It's It's crazy
cuz I'm sure most insults have never been laid.
Strange, isn't it? I'm sure that I'm
sure most of them has never been laid
for my knowledge. But they call you an
insult cuz you don't lick women's asses
and you're sick of dealing with their
[ __ ] [ __ ] madness, isn't it? I
really wish that was PC I was sending
that [ __ ] to, Dad.
I need to put some of that [ __ ] on my
channel, bro. I need to make a new channel, man.
I'm even a good text as well.
Have I got any more? I could
I just got so many of them, bro. I even
sent you a few more. Like, not videos, screenshots.
Don't know what more you could write.
I got an Irish one, by the way.
and it's not about one second.
I don't know if I sent you this one already, but
cuz I couldn't see them probably cuz
they were fuzzy. Well, that's sending you. So,
yeah, you know about Re, don't you? And
then another thing is it's not even
that, it's also the the text as well
from somebody's numbers as well. You're
trying to say it's me. How how the [ __ ]
could it be me?
Otherwise, I wouldn't post [ __ ] online. So
yeah, man. But yeah, just take your
time. Anyways, that's just the gist of
it. Once you've seen that, it's
basically just the same as most [ __ ]
And then also the screenshots as well.
some of them were.
It's bad, isn't it? I could never imagine,
you know, how bad it would feel if she
was actually a virgin. Like some of
these s like some of these simps. It's
bad enough. Like it's bad enough how it
is, you know, already, you know.
Then the last thing I would be doing is
is is is [ __ ] defending them. It's
madness. It honestly is madness.
I think they actually generally believe
that it will get them laid.
I generally think by them defending
women they they generally think it's
going to stop women hating them
cuz you're the one getting [ __ ] for it.
But you're the one that's been with
these women. It's just a matter that's
the matter that's the bit I don't get.
and someone that's see you speak to
someone like LT he will give you more of
like an honest answer he'd be like oh
you're going it's the way you're going
he'll be like oh it's the way you're
going about it like we know women are
this but you need to act differently you know
so that one is uh so that's like a I
would say that's like um a normal answer
what he gives he says Oh yeah, we know
what they're like, but you you you know,
you don't react to it and [ __ ] But the
way these people defend them is is strange.
Even though it had nothing to do with
Virgin Boys video, it is very very very strange.
Why they why they defend them. I don't
understand why. I'll tell you a story,
Cory. Right. There's this incel guy and
he's actually classified as an incel
and he's from England, right? and he's
actually a virgin. I think he's 32
or 33 and he is actual virgin. People
tell you he's a virgin, right? Um when I
was having problems with USA is he um
uh he was basically saying, "Oh, I don't
like what you what you're doing and
thinking you you you [ __ ] what?"
Well, that's beside the point here. One
second. You're you're a 33y old virgin.
Think think about that. He never even
like got school as well. Like he it's
not even like he tried to change yet and
he's defending these women.
[ __ ] me, bro. I'm lost for words.
You're def you're defending women and
your and your 33y old virgin. And he
actually is. He'll tell you as well. He
come from the incel community, mate. I
would literally be in prison if I was
you. That's how bad it would. I wouldn't
be defending women. I would be in prison.
But they still defend them.
It's madness. I could understand if they
were like a celebrity and they got all
these women and they genuinely got women
and never had these experiences, then I
could understand why they they'd want to
stick up for them. Then it kind of would
make sense. Okay. You know, so say you
say you was someone like Justin Bieber
when you was getting all these women and
then you know, but these people don't.
They've had less women than you. That's
the whole argument. That's the whole
argument, you know.
And the things you're saying aren't even offensive.
They're not even just, oh, they're stuck
up. They pretend they got boyfriends.
That's not even offensive. That's the truth.
Why does Why does the truth rattle these
simps? You know, cuz I used to use the
excuse before they've got moms and
they've got sisters. Yeah, but what
you're saying is not offensive. It's the
truth, you know.
I feel sorry for them, bro. I really, really do.
And one day I wake up and Yeah.
Yeah, man. Cory's watching my little not
watch my little videos and [ __ ] Yeah,
it is bad, bro.
So people because of experiences like
that, Mar is why people think what they
think because of experiences like that.
So this is basically what I've been
dealing with for years. That's the
that's the gist of it. You know, I don't
need to bore you with basically every
other thing I'll show you is exactly the
same thing. And that's why people feel
the way they do. You know, people don't
need to be incels. People don't need to
be virgins to be saying the stuff that
I'm saying. It's just facts.
I mean, you know, let let me tell you
something about this man, right? Would
you believe it if I told you that he has
not been through 5% of the [ __ ] that I
have and he left three times and I need
to know, bro, not even 5% of what I've dealt with.
But then they say that not women are all
the same. I mean, okay, let's let's go
by the ev evidence. They all say the
same thing. They all do the same thing.
They all have exactly the same mannerisms.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah. But anyways, now join basically
that's the gist of it. Anyways, um Bar Quest,
everything else I would show you is
exactly the same.
I mean, I got five. I went out last
Thursday. I like to go out drinking on
Thursdays for some reason. Not every
Thursday, but I got
five numbers and I got one reply.
Yeah. Yeah, bro. But you know, every
what you basically seen there was
basically the same thing what you deal
with every time. Well, you don't
normally get replies, but yeah, I mean
that's it's just the same.
And you saw one as well where they said
that they were going to meet and they
didn't meet as well. This is what you
put up with, bro. This is the [ __ ] that
you put up with trying to date in this country.
So, but then people when you say your
opinion, people make it seem like you're the incel.
This is what I'm saying, bro. It's crazy.
If I generally thought that they were
different, I generally would say it. I
generally would be like, "Yep, I'm
wrong. They're not all the same." You
know, I've met someone. I would
generally generally generally
um would would say, bro,
you know, how can you believe something
you've never seen, you know? It's like
that's why I don't believe in God. Don't
know about you or you Muslim, but I
generally can't believe something I've never seen.
Have you ever seen an elephant, man? No. So
yeah, man. That's that's it. But they
generally are all the same, bro.
And I've tried more than anyone in the
world. again. I know it sounds unusual, Oh [ __ ]
Yeah, you can see the Westinity in their eyes.
You can You can see the Westinity in
their eyes. Marquest,
they're like NPCs. Yeah. [Laughter] Wow.
I mean, yeah. So basically the so my
question um what I'm asking is um what uh
have you got any constructive criticism?
I'm going to be very very surprised if
you can critique any of them any of the
approaches any of the messages which I'm
happy if you can cuz I will listen but I
from what I'm seeing from a normal
person I think you pretty much done everything.
I think I'm even good at texting. You
see, some people got bad at texting, but
I think I even
at texting as well.
So, it wasn't even like I was good at
one thing. I feel like I was pretty good
at both to be fair.
Let me see if I don't think I sent you
that, did I?
Oh, I sent you. Yeah, I basically have
that's basically But like I said, it
wasn't that bad 15 about 15 months ago.
It wasn't as bad as that. You could
actually get dates.
You could actually Something's changed.
It's gotten worse.
Oh, that pony is cute, man. [ __ ] hell.
yeah, I rate the police.
Don't give it a while.
Look at you.
Yeah, I I don't think there's there's I
mean, if there is if there generally is
right something that um that I could
have done differently, then bro, I'm I'm
here. You know, no one's getting blocked.
But then people wonder why you feel the
way you do. I don't understand what else
how else can you feel. I bet it just
annoys you looking at it. I bet like me
showing you that probably just annoys
you. I know with me when I used to watch
like approaching videos from other guys
doing it. It just annoys me. Not like
literally like annoys me where it's
winding me up, but it just I just just
like slightly annoys me. I just turn it
off. I don't even like watching it, bro.
It's annoying as hell.
Probably probably annoys you even even
watching it to be honest. I bet it
probably annoys you.
And man said you can see the westernity
in their eyes. Yeah, it is. It's
annoying, isn't it? Because obviously
like stuck up people and it's because of
like watching stuck up people, isn't it?
I just had McDonald's moves. Just an Nodox.
You can see the Westinity in their eyes.
I'm one. Which one? Which one did I do
it wrong with?
Yeah. See, I basically said bar quest my
um videos to critique.
Um but I don't think there was anything
you could say, but they still gave
people the chance because Yeah.
So what do you do? Keep going out and
dealing with their [ __ ] You know what
I'm saying? Like this what I mean, bro.
I was I was going to go out Saturday. I
got changed Saturday.
One second. I have a picture actually.
No. Anyways, I was going to go out
Saturday and I lost the football bet. It
was only 20 and because I'd already been
out the first, I thought, "Fuck this.
I'm not even going to go out. I'm just
going to stay in and chill." And I just
stayed in and chilled, bro. But yeah.
But yeah, anyways, that's basically it.
A million fold to be honest with you.
We've been dealing with this [ __ ] for
years. Me and Antman, you know,
Antman says that they're just not
interested in this country.
Bar quest. He says that they're just not
interested in this country
because I always thought with Ant-Man.
Yeah. That maybe he was giving off like
weird vibes or
you know or I don't know he was a bit
off or people thought he looked weird or
too old or I don't know. Not not that
thought was bad. I always thought that
maybe it was something like that. But
then the same [ __ ] started happening to me.
But he said, "Oh, he thought the same as
me, like it could have been me." But I
was like, "But yeah, that's fine." But I
don't take offense. But why would you
think that when I sent you my approaches,
you know? I thought the same about you.
But obviously I showed you my
approaches. So, I mean, I Why would you think that?
It's just funny that you did, but
yeah, but yeah, I mean, we basically
thought the same with each other.
They're cute. Cute though.
I like the little P. Lilo and Stitch Quest. Oh, that's key.
And I think I look pretty good as well.
Well, pretty normal. Let's say pretty
let's let's say bar look pretty normal as well.
It's bad, isn't it? Very bad.
We was talking about cartoons, man. I like um
you know when when Virgin Boy used to
say Shel Cole was was uh was fit.
Um he was he was copying the crowd. He
was following the crowdress.
Um, my favorite character at the moment
is Franklin, but I don't know, man.
What? I don't know. I like Spongebob Squarepants.
I don't know. I think Spongebob
Squarepants is my favorite.
Oh, I ordered some Chucky caps, by the
way. They're coming soon. I'll show you
them when they arrive.
Yeah, I got some Chucky caps. They
should be here in maybe 5 days.
Yeah. like some child play caps. I bet
you'll like them.
Ramsey, why was he saying Cher's good-look?
Copying the crowd, isn't it?
Copying the crowd.
So, yeah, with with me, I'm pretty much
stuck in a loop.
Did you find my Did you find my approach
smooth them question? Did you like it?
I'm not as good as I used to be, bro.
Because I've done about [ __ ] 4,000 of
them and it's always the same [ __ ]
So, I can't be asked anymore, bro.
Really can't be [ __ ] I like
remember that Joe wrote that green.
Yeah, he was on a wind up, wasn't he?
That Joe was on the wind up highlight. [Laughter]
Do you remember? Yeah.
Timmy owned himself.
Um I was talking to Bar quest.
So how how is this going to change then quest? Yeah,
do you like shy
like squeezy like sh
Why? Why does Would you would you still
rate me a seven out of 10? Um,
would you still make me a seven out of 10?
Cuz we have to also go by looks as well.
Okay. Okay. So, let's just say that
you're Okay. Let's just say for argument
sake, we'll meet in the middle, right?
You're 7 out of 10. 7.5 out of 10.
You've approached, you seem confident,
your text, right? What gives the what
gives people the impression that you're
going to meet someone?
What actually gives you the impression
that you're just going to randomly meet someone?
So, the reason I can't believe it, Bar
quest, right, is I've you've not seen
this because you was off of YouTube for
[ __ ] like two years, but I used to
travel all the time up and down the
country. Maybe you saw the videos. So,
if all of this shit's been happening for
three and a half years,
then why how would it all of a sudden change now?
But saying that 2 years ago is actually
easier. So, I mean, if you still doing
it how if it was easy then you probably
would have found someone. But now it's
just on it's like FIFA, right? You got
[ __ ] normal mode, medium, you got
hard, and you got extra hard. Now it's
on extra hard.
And I've I've been getting people saying
to me, "Oh, you need to go on Tik Tok."
The tenants were saying, "Go on Tik
Tok." People never told me to go on Tik
Tok before. Tik Tok's become bigger.
Yeah, it's been out for years, but it
wasn't as big as it is now. Sorry. Uh um
bar quest um yeah and and man said that
they're just not interested in this country
which is true but how can people from a
whole country not be interested
but obviously it's right is it cuz if
they were interested then you would have
met someone in
They're just not interested in this country. Yeah. [ __ ] mad.
You think I'd meet someone in Ireland? Bquest.
Oh, bless you. Australians
are coming out with really good horrors lately.
It's a hookup culture. Yeah.
I don't know how you what you going to do, man.
I'll show you one.
Yeah, that them them them them them them
them them them them them them them them
them them them them them them them I've
only watched two Australian horrors and
they were like really good man
Australian they they do some really good horrors man
I mean actual horror films they don't
know they need to stop making new ones
Yeah, that last horror film I watched
that was Australian was [ __ ] up, bro.
You still need to watch it. I don't know
if you watched it, but
Yeah. But yeah, you need to watch it, lad.
Mark and his ponies. Bless him. Oh,
you remember Mr. J?
Do you remember Mr. J? [Music]
the same thing, just different characters.
Do you know what? Do you know what he
says? Do you know what he says? Greet.
No, he ain't been around for ages, man.
He is. Do you know what an uh Do you
know what Antman says? He says, "You
know, these approaching videos, they're
all the same same ending and same
beginning. It's just different characters."
He said, "Same ending, same same
beginning, just different characters." [Laughter]
Oh, that's funny.
just to become this. Yeah.
Show you something.
So, which one did you think I could have
done better on? You said there was one
that I could have done better on. Which
one was that, boss?
That's so cute, man.
Yeah, that's cute, isn't it?
Do you still watch anime porn?
Do you still do you still watch anime porn?
We usually you watch porn, don't you?
We usually can't live without sex and women. This is Frank. Franklin.
Franklin's a lovely little character,
isn't he? Greasy. Frank. Poor Franklin.
Oh, poor Franklin.
One second. There's heat. What's that?
Are you leaving?
What's up? I want to show you something. Don't leave. Oh yeah.
Who would you say? No. What about Virgin
boy? He's a He's a [ __ ] virgin. Franklin.
Oh, [ __ ] weapon.
Oh, bless you.
You remember Gre
was trolling in it that Joe.
I agree with you was trolling in it.
Yeah, he was trolling, bro.
Yeah, he was trolling.
Yeah, but Greavves you like Greavves
like Cheryl Oh,
did you did you watch my video on Virgin Boy Grey completely destroyed
You you show it, didn't you?
God says that you keep trolling me
crazy. Is that true?
You're a troll, man. No, you're a troll.
No, you're trolling me. Did you see
that? I I own them, bro.
I owned I owned them a lot of J's
yesterday. I [ __ ] owned them. Say that
[ __ ] on to me.
God bless you then if you went out for an hour. Yeah,
you reckon I should go out and do some
approaches this week.
What do you think would happen?
I [ __ ] pulled the virgin's pants down.
I pulled the virgin the virgin boy's pants down.
It would be a good It would be good, bro.
You reckon it would be good if I go to
um if me and Virgin met out for a fight?
Shut up. You can't show your bed, you bun.
Shut up, you rat face m.
You ain't got a bed. [ __ ] off. You ain't
got a bed, you rat face m. Shut up, bun boy.
You want a rat face, bun? Your face
looks like it's melted.
Well, you like it, lad.
If I If I You know what? He literally
went to the police.
Imagine this guy. Imagine going to the
police. Yeah. Crying. Now, just just
think about this for a second. Yeah.
Imagine going to the police crying like
a little [ __ ] You're being owned on
YouTube every single day. Like imagine
imagine that to begin with. Like
someone's owning you so badly on YouTube
and pulling your pants down so bad that
the only thing you got left in you like
the loser you are is crying to the boys
in the blue. Just just just imagine
that. And then when you realize that
doesn't work, you still come on YouTube
doing what you do. Bro, I don't think
anyone in the world has ever done that. You know,
he is. Imagine being that. Bro, I'm
telling you, this guy wants to be me.
I'm telling you, this virgin seriously
seriously wants to be me, bro. I'm
telling you. Like, no. No. Serious, bro.
I don't mind a laugh. I don't mind a
laugh. But I was like, "Yeah, how how
could that lanky stream of [ __ ] piss
call anyone a loser when he literally
ran to the police over YouTube?"
Like, bro, imagine crying to the police over YouTube.
You got And he's saying to me about,
"Oh, I've never had a girlfriend. I
basically have had a girlfriend and I've
never had a disabled girlfriend like
you. I'd rather no I think everybody on
this community would agree with me when
they would say they'd rather have
nothing than have that. Like I would
rather have nothing than have that. I
don't think most people would agree with me.
He says that I'm what I don't
understand. He says he says that I'm
ugly but I've got I've pulled all the
women that he wishes he could have had himself.
That's how I just stayed that to him. I
said, "Okay, I'm ugly, but why is it
that you're the one with the disabled
girl? Why is it that why is that Peter
Belly is the one with the
on the subject about sing?
He really really doesn't realize how
ugly he actually is. He He resembles a rat.
Like he he actually is the most ugliest
thing I've ever one of the most ugliest
things I've ever seen."
You must realize that ain't it? Yeah, exactly.
He says, "I can't attract women. That's
projection. I've literally had more
women than he's ever had in his life.
And I've never had to resort to disabled."
Which doesn't make which the thing is
not life yet. Do you want to know why I
moan about women? I'll tell you right
now why I moan about women. It's because
I think they're stuck up. I think it's
[ __ ] up trying to date in this country.
He's not [ __ ] seven foot. [ __ ]
seven foot, is he? [ __ ] He's a 6'
nothing. [ __ ] 7 foot. He's a 6'
nothing. String a piss [ __ ] 7 foot.
So you dare try to [ __ ] insult
7 foot. So I just come on here, bro, and
just like say that it's [ __ ] up. And
cuz I think it is [ __ ] up, but I
generally hate women. And I and I
generally mean it. But then the thing is
they come on here
then then try to make it seem like I'm
the incel that's never had women. I give
my honest opinion which is not
offensive. And I've got all of these
simps that have never had women come and
attacking me calling me the incel. What the [ __ ]
What? Because I don't understand it. I
genally generally don't understand
um these simps. I really really I I I
can't stand women and I've had more
women than them,
but then they they jump they jump to their rescue
and then they s and it's got Yeah, it's
autism. It's definitely autism. It's
definitely definitely autism.
They make you think that you're the
incel that's never had sex because you
don't lick women's asses.
What the [ __ ]
they are? I generally think women are
evil. I generally do think they are.
I generally think they are evil.
I can't stand them. You know, like I'm
being real, bro. I actually generally
feel, you know, I generally generally
generally I think they're I think
they're evil. I think they've got no
heart. What the [ __ ]
It's not even like you're saying anything OTT.
Not one of them but me. And I said, "No,
if I'm if I'm ugly, why are you why was
you the one stalking my sloppy seconds?
Why was you the one stalking all of
these women I've been before? I'm the ugly one."
I didn't really get an answer to that, did I?
Virgin boy can't show his bed. Virgin
boy ain't got a bed. He's too skint.
But like I said, I'm off here after
today. Anyways, bro for a little bit. I
got barest numbers now. I only went to
Bquest numbers. You know, you know, you
know what I find weird about this life?
Yeah, I got interrupted earlier is that
these people do this for a living. It's
all they have in their life. You know,
it's mad to think that
this is literally their life.
This is literally all they have.
Like it's not like two days a week or
one day a week or an hour a week, an
hour every day. Like their their life is
literally doing this. Like imagine
Yeah. waking up every day thinking who
am I going to [ __ ] with today on YouTube.
[ __ ] hell, bro. Imagine that. Like
and they don't stop as well. Like it's
not even like they they get bored
because they've got nothing to do. They
literally do it every day. They've been
doing it every day for years.
You know how stars have been stalking me
every day for 5 years.
Think about that, bro.
Just just imagine it. Imagine it in real
life. It's a madness, isn't it?
That is a madness. How can they even [ __ ]
get bored? I get bored after like 3 days
watch this video.
I'm watching LJ's video.
Old blue eyes.
You have in [Laughter]
Who do you think would win in a fight?
Cory, me or LJ?
Yeah, I will. I will. I will.
See what I mean? One second. Yeah. Yeah. Send
They're fast enough to click on Peter
Griff in the strawberry, aren't they?
They're fast enough to click on Griffin. Yeah. Comp. Yeah,
I'll be back later. Yeah,
I'll be back later, lads.