Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ]
I need to do that [ __ ] football bet
tomorrow, don't I? [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. I need to have football back
tomorrow. I forgot all about it.
I figured, bro, yeah, I'm not reacting
to the I'm not reacting to these people.
Not that I do anyways.
Let them be skin all day on YouTube
reacting, bro. Leave them to it.
No, I'm not reacting to these people, bro.
You need to stop sending me Hey Cory,
you need to stop sending me that stuff
on WhatsApp, bro.
I'm not interested in keyboard warriors,
you know? If it's arguing with like
Timmy or something, bro, then [ __ ] it.
I'll do it in it. Cuz at least I know
like Timmy meets, bro. But yeah, stop
sending me videos of that [ __ ] skinned virgin.
Yeah, bro. At the end of the day, just
let them keep embarrassing themselves.
You know, once you've owned someone
once, yeah, you don't need to own them
again, bro. Just let them keep
embarrassing themselves and showing
themselves up on YouTube for what they
really are. Skin flints. Know what I'm saying, bro?
Let them keep showing themselves up, bro.
Are you getting on this bet tomorrow, uh, Cory?
It's like I was saying to the voice
though, bro, these people are actually
skin. That's why they spend all day on
YouTube. They don't get paid for it.
Like you said, they do this [ __ ] for a
living. They don't get paid for it cuz
they ain't got no life. They got no
money. That's why they sit on it all day
every day, bro.
Figure it out in it.
You getting on this bet, mate?
I might stick Yeah, I'm going stick 80
pound on it tomorrow. I just put more bet
and if it wins I'll go cinema. Well, I'm
going to go cinema anyways and then I'll
go out then maybe the week after that. Yeah, man.
cuz I've got a uh football bet, bro.
Double both teams and score 80 returns 269.
You should get in on it, bro.
I'm putting 80 on it
cuz I don't like the Saturday games.
Yeah, I don't like the Saturday games,
bro. So, I'm going to do Tuesday.
I kind of want to put 100 on it to be honest.
Did Let me see.
Oh yeah. I like Timmy's videos, man.
They're actually quite entertaining.
Yeah. It's funny, is it, bro?
So, you want to get in? You want to get
in on that uh football back tomorrow, bro?
>> Yeah. I might stick 100 on it. I don't know. Yeah, man.
800. I'm out, man. Um,
Colchester versus Cambridge, winning
versus Barnett. So, if it wins,
I go out the week after then and
obviously that's me done literally for
the month. I go out like twice a month maximum drinking.
Twice a month max
cuz this is boring otherwise.
It's boring otherwise, you know. So,
yeah, I need to see that new Superman as well. Superman. Superman.
Yeah, I won I've won two football bets
in a row. I lost last week's one, but I
won the week before and the week before that. So, yeah. Yeah, man. But yeah,
there's games on tonight, is there?
Yeah, but not the English league. They
Yeah, but not the English league league. you know.
So, you don't think that I've got a
boyfriend? You don't think that I've got
a boyfriend? [ __ ] is going to change, Cory. Nah. Nate, did you
I don't really bother with it anymore,
bro. I can't be asked. I've had enough
pictures. I know the country is dead.
I'm going to work with some of the
numbers I've got and then
um obviously if they get nowhere then
I'm probably going to have to leave,
bro. I can't lie.
I can't be bothered with it, bro. It's
not worth the effort that you put in.
You know, I've already put more than
enough effort into this. I can't be off
with it anymore, bro.
Come on, son.
>> What did I say to you, matey?
What did I say to you, my dear?
Yeah. What? Yeah, but what did I say?
What do I say? How do I say it?
They just aren't interested in this country.
One sec, bro. They're just not
interested in this country.
Oh, one second, bro.
Um, [ __ ] all, bro. Just chilling, man.
I need to do that football bet for tomorrow, man.
You know what I find so mad, Steven Howard? Yeah.
Is that these people waste their life on
me every day for free.
Like they don't get paid to do it. They
just sit online cuz they're skin and
they don't get paid for it. Yeah. And
they and they waste their life every day
for free on me. It's mad, isn't it, bro?
They don't get paid or nothing.
That's the madness, bro. Uh Cambridge.
Who is it? Colchester versus Cambridge
and Swindon and Baret.
Yeah, bro. It just goes to show that
they're jealous, man, because they don't
get paid for it. I could understand if
they got paid for it, but they just
they're happy to come on here every day
wasting their life away,
not leaving the house, ain't got a life,
and they don't even get paid. That's the
thing. They don't get they don't they
don't earn a living from it. Madness, isn't it?
It is a madness.
They just self-reflect.
Just little self-reflectors
just like L. Look, he's just come up
lonely peak. It's just self It's just
self projecting. That's what they do,
bro. They sell.
None of them make money, but they just
sit online every day wasting their life
away. It's mad, isn't it?
What? What's up, bro?
Yeah, they're just they're just self
projectors. That's what they are, bro.
They're just self projectors.
Yeah, they spend all their life doing
this as well. It's not even like they're
like a It's not even like they're
winding people up
um like for two days or a day, a week.
They they they literally live to do
this. Like they wake up, get out of bed.
They think, "Oh, who can we mess with
today on YouTube for free?"
Man, don't they ain't got a life, bro?
They are skin. They really are skinn.
They spend all day, every day on YouTube
skin. That's funny, isn't it?
Basically, whatever these people Whatever
these people say about you, it actually
applies to themselves.
That's the number one on this um community.
Took your advice. What advice?
What's your advice?
I don't know who you are.
Yeah. What they, like I said, what they
say about you, Cory, applies to themselves.
Otherwise, they wouldn't be on here all
day doing this.
See, you like it, Nate.
Doing this for free.
They're getting paid.
paid by the hour.
I'm putting 80 pound on it.
But yeah, I clicked on the video cuz you
sent me Oh, you're triggered, man. You
went live for 23 minutes talking about
me. Yeah, that's definitely triggered.
Triggered skin. Yeah, it's all them,
bro. Ain't it? It's all these people.
Yeah, it's all these people on YouTube
then, isn't it? Going live 23 minutes
talking about me. Yeah, that's triggered.
Yeah, man. Triggered cuz everything I
say is the truth in it. So that's why
they get triggered.
Think of it. Yeah, Cory, bro. Like,
answer me this question, bro. Yeah. Do
you really think if they weren't they'd
be on here every day? All day, every
Would they be on here
all day, every day doing what they do?
No, they wouldn't, bro.
Go, go figure it out, bro. It doesn't
take Einstein. It's cuz they are skin.
You know they are skin, lad.
They're in a bad place in life, lad.
I just spent 15. I just had a kebab, by
the way. £15.
It's mad how like they you could be gone
for like 10 years and they'd still be
doing it, isn't it? It's crazy, man.
Jealousy is like a is a drug, isn't it?
I think it's like a It's like a disease,
jealousy, isn't it?
You had a mix shift, bro.
You know what I fancied? I just
remembered this right. I fancied like a
chicken ticker, but you can't get it
anywhere. I had it once when I was in
Cardiff. So, you got chicken donut, you
got lamb donut, but then you got chicken ticker.
And I couldn't find it anywhere, bro.
But I had it when I was in Wales. But
yeah, I don't know where you can find
that. That is banging, bro.
I don't know if you know any places, but
hey, Nicolola, I just had a [ __ ] mix
shish, man. But I was fancying a [ __ ]
um chicken tick a dollar, but I couldn't
find any kebab shops that done it.
The last time I got it was in Wales,
bro. They're lush them. That is a good
kebab. If you want to start being like
obsessed with kebabs, then that's that's
that's a good kebab.
It's a chicken ticker donor. The lambdon
is [ __ ] It's too greasy. And the
chicken one's me, but the chicken ticker
one's the best. I can't I don't know
where where they don't do it anywhere.
This was in Cardiff.
So, but I had it like last year. So,
yeah. Nice, man. You're getting on this
football bet tomorrow. We're doing this
double both teams to score.
I'll be c I'll go to a cinema on Saturday. Yep.
It doesn't bother me anymore, bro. It's
It's your problem now. It's not mine. I'm leaving.
I'm leaving in two and a half months.
It's not my problem.
It's your problem, bro. It's not mine.
you know, good luck to you.
It's like what I said to my friend. He
wanted me to um
he wanted me to um
go and um meet him
on Saturday. I said, "I'm not meeting
you, bro. I'm done. I don't care. Good
luck to you.
Good luck to you.
It's going to get to a point where even
if I go out drinking every two weeks,
I'm just not even going to approach
anymore because I already know the outcome.
What's the point of approaching if you
already know the outcome?
But I guess the drink is something to do.
You need to break the cycle, matey.
But yeah, it's not my problem anymore,
bro. It's not my problem anymore. So,
there's no point even approaching
anymore, is there? Yeah.
See, I hate like defeat and having to
like know that I've got to leave my own
country, but I can't deal with this the
rest of my life, bro.
Hearing about like it's actually
depressing, bro. Like, you don't understand.
But hearing that I got a boyfriend [ __ ]
I don't know how I done it every day
like back last summer.
I was probably a bit younger then and
I had more hope and Yeah.
But you ain't got no hope now.
So nothing's changed in 18 months.
It's the I've got a boyfriend [ __ ] bro.
It piss It pisses me off. Like sober. I
don't want to hear it, you know?
I'm I'm sick of hearing it, bro. I
really really I'm sick of hearing it.
That's why I used to stop for like four
weeks to six weeks.
Um, I just had a mixed sh kebab grievy,
lamb and chicken. But what I what I
actually fancied more was a chicken
ticker kebab. A chicken ticker donut,
which is very, very hard to get. The
last time I had one was when I was in
Wales, but I can't find anywhere here
that does it.
You got chicken, then you got lamb, then
you got chicken ticker. But most places
do the lamb and chicken, but not the
chicken ticker. It seems that it's very
hard to get.
Yep. You also get in a club as well, but
I'm I'm trying. Do you Does anywhere
near you do the chicken ticker, Donna, Grezy?
It's very hard to get, man. I'll just go
back to Wales to just get it. You know
what I mean?
Have you ever had it or have you ever seen it?
It's called a chicken ticker. Uh donor,
have you have you ever tasted it? of us, you know,
a chicken ticker uh dollar is nice
when you can actually get it, which is
[ __ ] almost impossible to get.
What if you get a number though, Nicolo?
What if you get a number?
Yeah. What do they have the ticker one
where you are? Cuz I I had it when I was
in Wales, but nowhere here does it.
But no one
nowhere here does it. I've not even seen
it walking past places.
But you didn't answer me, Nicola. What if I
get a number and I text the number then? Then what?
Greasy, we're getting on this bet tomorrow.
But the problem is, Grezy, is if we lose
the bet, they're all going to be
laughing at us. All four of us. All four
of us is going to do this bet and
they're all going to be laughing at us.
I was going to say, yeah, you could
probably approach somebody and try and
go on an instant date, but even then, it
doesn't matter what you do. Like, I've
walked with people. I've took things
slow, very slow, and they're still not
interested. So, it's just a waste of time here.
I've took things slow.
Um, you know, been as best as I can and
they still just ghost you. You'd think a
lot of them would just like not do it
out of respect, but they still do it.
It's just a waste. It's just a waste of
time in this country.
But they're all going to be laughing at
us for losing a little bet. Yep.
They're reacting for reaction. Isn't
that right? Um Nicola
Joe says that they do it for reaction,
but they're reacting for reaction.
Seems a bit absurd, doesn't it? So, you're reacting
every day for 4 months to get a reaction.
Seems mad to me. So, hold on, hold on.
So you you come on YouTube every day,
every second of every day, reacting to
me every day
in hopes that you get a reaction twice a
year. Oh, okay. Fine. And then when you
get the reaction, then what?
Seems a bit pointless then, doesn't it?
Wait, let's understand this. So you you
come online every day of your life from
the time you wake up to the time you go
to bed stalking and reacting to get a
reaction out of me twice a year.
Huh? Says a lot about your life then, doesn't it?
And I think that's the bit that people
don't understand is you're not typing
something for 2 seconds to get a
reaction. You are literally spending all
of your life every second of every day
free of charge. Mind you, these people
don't get paid for doing this.
And that's how you how I came to the
conclusion, Nicolo, that they are the
skint ones. Cuz if they weren't skin,
why would they waste all their life not
getting paid stalking and reacting to
someone every day?
It's cuz they're skin. That's that's the
only thing it can be and they ain't got
a life. Low lives. That's it.
And you get a reaction and then what?
So you get a reaction then what?
So then you get a reaction then what?
I Greavvesy, can you help me with this?
Greavvesy, can you can you help me with this, lad?
Cuz maybe you're a bit more intelligent than Joe.
So maybe you could you could help me.
So I understand that these people come
here every day to get a reaction. But
so they they want a reaction. Yeah. So
they want a reaction out of people. So then
why? So why are they coming on YouTube
every second of every day reacting to
you to get a reaction? That just
completely misses the whole point. I
would have thought and they don't get
paid for it as well. Now I can
understand if they got paid for it.
That's why I don't really come on here
that much, bro, because I don't get paid for it.
Like so there's no point. Like I'd
rather be doing something where I'm
actually gaining. You're not gaining
anything on there. You're just wasting
your life. Really, if you think about it, bro.
Yo, I made it.
I was thinking of Liverpool early, you know. Nicolola,
I kind of want to go Liverpool again.
Only been once.
Could give it a whirl, would it?
I don't know about that, mate. you know.
No, I can't afford it, mate.
I can't afford it.
No, I'm joking, bro.
So what will happen if I go Liverpool then?
And then what will happen if I go Liverpool
doing all night and then come back? [ __ ] it now.
Yeah. Not interested. Uh, I had it
before when I was in Liverpool. I
remember it. I've only been Liverpool
once, but I remember I do remember it.
Um, I have a boyfriend. I'm not
interested. Yeah, I do remember it.
they're just not interested in this
country. But I will do an all nighter in
Liverpool to say I've done it all. What
do you think, Greavves? an all nighter in Liverpool,
go there at like get there for like 300
p.m. and then come back at like get the
train at like 8:00 in the morning the next day. Yeah,
I will be absolutely [ __ ] though, man.
I'll be [ __ ] for like four days after it, Grebs.
What if I go there and I can't get in
anywhere, Nicolo? Because I'm not with a
group of girls or single entry. You know,
that's the thing, is it?
Then you'd be [ __ ] is it? Then you'll
But Liverpool's not too bad, is it?
We Oh, do you remember John? Do you
remember when I met Turkish John Nicolo?
Do you go far back as as that?
Me and John? You don't remember, do you?
Greasy. But Liverpool ain't that bad, is
it? It's like the outskirts of London, isn't it?
Yeah, it's not that bad. It's like the
outskirts of London though.
Yeah. The outskirts of London.
I kind of want to have a go on Frankie, you know, kind of.
Yeah, I blocked Monty, but I don't want
to speak to him again.
Nah, don't try and tell me to grow up
and [ __ ] try and blame me.
I approaching [ __ ] almost lost you
relationship when you weren't even in a relationship.
You really want to know what I think?
You want to know what I think?
And people people never ask again after that. Madness.
Yeah, it's all right, bro. this
community for one or two days, but then
it just becomes the same atmosphere.
It's the same atmosphere. You know what I mean?
It's the same atmosphere every day. Yeah.
>> What do you think will happen? Stephen
allowed if I go to Liverpool and start doing approaches.
What do you think?
You reckon I'll get laid?
What do you mean? Do you reckon I'll get
It's a hookup culture.
[ __ ] a hookup culture, bro. What the
[ __ ] I'd love to know [ __ ] hookup culture, bro.
hookup culture. Is it
[ __ ] hookup culture?
How could it be hookup culture?
See you and Howard.
No, but did you see them people? They
say it's a hookup culture, you know.
Yeah, but they say on Reddit it's hook off cover.
You can't even get laid.
They hook up culting my ass. You can't
even get a conversation out of them.
You don't even get a kiss or a touch or anything.
So, how am I going to have baby Peter
Nicolo? How am I going to have baby
Peter belly? Hey,
What do you reckon they'll say? Boyfriend.
They've all got boyfriends.
Yeah, man. Just whatever you just don't
compare me to strangers.
Yeah. Just don't I hate when they
compare you to strangers, you know?
You reckon it's going to change, Nicolo?
You reckon it's going to change?
It's depressing, isn't it?
See, you're just taking the piss out of me now.
This is why I don't like you people on
YouTube. You just mock me.
Well, I don't know. Maybe you go out one
day and then you don't hear I've got a
boyfriend. Reevesy, do you think it's
going to change?
How? Yeah, but maybe I'll go out and
I'll stop here. Yeah, I've got a boyfriend. Grimsy.
Okay. Okay. What if I go to Newcastle then? Nicolo
said not Peter Belly's mama.
Yeah, it's very I think I lost it, bro.
I lost the energy. I lost the confidence. Yeah.
See, back 15 months ago, 18 months ago,
you could actually get dates. You could
get dates. You could get kisses. Can't
get nothing now.
You could have the odd one night stand.
I had one on my birthday, a one night
stand. But what if I go to Newcastle, Nikolai?
Okay, I can go to Newcastle then. What?
I can go to Newcastle.
Ah, you didn't mention that one, did you?
Yeah, I kissed three people with when I
was in Newcastle the the well the second
time I went.
I don't think the numbers replied, but I
remember getting kisses.
Yeah, the numbers don't reply in London.
Well, I did get one reply from a
Scottish woman. I might just say to her
this week, "If I come to Scotland, would
you meet me?"
I'll just go Scotland. [ __ ] it. I got no
plans Saturday. So
yeah, they never reply in London. It's
weird, isn't it?
They never reply.
Well, some of them do, but like not
compared to like Birmingham and [ __ ]
They like to [ __ ] you over in the end.
The ones that reply like to play the
long game and then [ __ ] you over. Don't legy.
Do you remember the French one? She
said, "Oh, I wanted to dress up in my
little dress for you." I thought, "What
the [ __ ] She's trolling."
She said, "Oh, but I want to wear my
little dress for you." [ __ ] troll.
Do you remember that one? That was mad,
bro. What the [ __ ] No one on Reddit
told me women were like this.
You know what about my mommy? Nicolola,
what about my mama?
What about my mama?
I don't say that I saw you over there
anymore. I ain't said that for like two years.
I've not said that for like two years, bro.
Um, so what about my mommy?
Could you imagine doing an all night in
Newcastle? [ __ ] that.
Yeah. So, how am I going to get my mama back then?
Could you imagine you done an all
nighter a year in Newcastle and
Liverpool, no sleep? Yeah, mate. You
would be [ __ ]
Do you think you could actually do it?
Like, go Newcastle, get on the piss,
next day, get on the piss, no hotel,
just straight drinking for two days, and
then come back to London. Nah, mate.
Do the Newcastle on a Friday and
Liverpool on a Saturday.
Yeah, I only I can touch my mama.
Only I can.
Why are you calling me a [ __ ] mama?
Why are you calling me mama?
Why are you calling me a [ __ ] Mama
legendary is in it, bro.
Oh, did you have a little ching chong we
mate? That'll be sick.
Why are you still a virgin? Oh, Quezy.
You're my mama. No one else is.
So what do you say? Is he really my
mommy? Wait. So So who's Laney then? If
that's my mama, who's Laney?
I bet when you're out and about
sometimes you think of my sayings and
you start laughing in it.
Taking the baby away from this mama.
You just started copying what I was saying.
So who's Laney then really?
So what's the?
So what's the story then? So but
but I I I hadn't been in America then. I
was I've never I'd never been by that point.
So how could my mommy be So how did I
end up here?
Sigma was never your mama. Huh?
I always say to like Laney and that that
like we we're so different. Different
tea, different taste buds, different
everything. How the [ __ ]
I do say sometimes, you know. Or maybe
it could have been that Albanian. That
could have been my mama. The people say
I look Albanian, but
maybe I've got two mummies.
So, how did I end up here then? You know,
yeah, that Albanian one had big boobs as well.
She abandoned me as well.
I've been abandoned by my mas. Greasy. [ __ ] hell.
Rubs is my biggest troll.
Yeah, he's my biggest troll.
Taking a baby away from it mama.
Yeah, Greasy is my biggest troll, man.
Would you like to see me in Scotland on Saturday? Grezy,
do you remember that? It's okay. He said
he said you can you can win it bungle if
you swallowed [ __ ]
Do you remember that one? Grooves he
something you've always wanted. Oh you
lucky [ __ ] You could have won it bungle
if you swallowed [ __ ]
You remember that one the sippy?
Do you want my opinion? Zippy gun. Yeah.
You never saw my other mommy, did you, Grezy?
You never saw my Albanian mama, did you?
You never saw my my mama, did you?
Oh, no. You did when we was kissing. Yeah.
What are you doing outside by yourself, mama?
Oh, you never saw my mama.
One second. I'll show you her.
I should have a picture. One second.
Yeah, just different characters.
That's what man says. Oh, look at my
mommy. As you can see, she had big
boobies as well.
But obviously, I didn't get too attached
with this one because obviously I didn't
get the milk. Nikolai.
I only got the milk from one of them. So
yeah, she had big boobies as well as you can see.
Same beginning, same just different characters.
Just different characters. Yeah, that
was my other mama.
I've got her boobies as well
who's kissing and stuff.
Yeah, bit sad when my mama left me, but
I didn't get too attached.
It was sort of fun.
Same beginning, same ending. Just different characters.
I have a boyfriend. Yeah. A year.
I hate it, bro. Like, it's funny
laughing at you.
And man says he doesn't find it funny.
No, it's it's all right laughing at,
bro, until you actually have to go out
and hear it sober.
Then there's no laughing now, is it?
That's what Antman says. He said, "No,
it's not funny. It was depressing." He said,
he said, "It's not funny. It's depressing."
So why can't Virgin Boy get anything
normal than Nicolo? Nicola.
So, we all doing this bet tomorrow. Yeah,
we all doing this bet tomorrow, lads.
But like I said, if we lose, them [ __ ]
on LJ's chat are going to be laughing at
us. They're going to be mocking us.
Them [ __ ] were laughing at us. And then
we're going to have to [ __ ] meet. And
we're doing this bet tomorrow. Yeah.
Yeah, me Steven Howard and Grezy
just different characters.
Who do you like better? The the Albanian
one or USA Izzy?
I like I like uh
I think I like USA is he not USA is he
obviously that I like the Albanian one
man her boobies was bigger
the I'd say the Albanian I'd say the
Albanian one bro
if you win the bet you can afford 17
McDonald's. Think about that. Grazy,
think about that. Eh,
I don't know how I did it, mate. I don't
know. Well, the Albanian one, I
approached her outside of work and she
couldn't really um
speak English, so I had to translate
Um, so we was just texting and then we
just met. I think we met on a Tuesday.
We was talking about how we were going
to kiss and stuff. Anyways, so
imagine I was starting off now and I say
say I got like 700 pound a month,
Nicolo, and I was starting off now.
Say I was a virgin.
Yeah. You can't even get a date.
If I was a virgin, right, then
I'd probably go out every day and try
till I found someone or But I just don't
have the energy for it anymore, bro. I
can't be asked.
The Albanian one was good, but she
couldn't really speak English.
She was Imagine getting a free with USA
Izzy and Albanian Izzy.
Imagine having a free with both of them.
[ __ ] hell. Imagine that.
Do you remember the one that I had a go
at at the park? Nicola,
I don't, bro. I think when I used to do
it, it's because obviously I didn't have sex
and obviously I wanted my sex drive was probably higher.
So, but now I just don't want to put up
with it. I can't be asked.
I wish that Albanian one would meet me again, man.
So, what did my mommy do when I poured
out my little heart to her then, Nico?
when I poured out my little heart to her.
Nah, about five. I'd say
I'd say after about five. Yeah. No.
So, what did my mommy do when I poured
out my heart for her? Nico,
I want to try this Scottish one on
Saturday. I'll tell her that I'm just
going to go Glasgow.
Oh, that's going to be a mad one, isn't
it? But who who else lives in Glasgow though? Nicolo. Oh [ __ ]
Who else lives? Who else lives?
Yeah. Who else lives there? If they say
Yeah. They said they live in between
Glasgow and Edinburgh.
So if I go to Glasgow, who else lives there?
Do we know anyone that lives there? [Laughter]
That's my daddy. Yeah.
He says you need to go see a psych psychiatrist.
He said in good faith you can benefit
from seeing a um psychiatrist.
So why why did my mommy
why did my mama leave me? Yeah,
his friend was all right, but he was a [ __ ]
But yeah, the Albanian was better than
USA, I'd have to say. Yeah.
Yeah. I like the name Franklin. If I had
two puppies, I'd name it Franklin and Tam.
Greavvesy loves King. Greavvesy loves
Everyone loves King. Kingy.
Yeah. Name it Franklin.
Franklin. That's a funny name. Franklin.
God bless you then. It's nice seeing Bar
Quest again. Do you remember when Bar
Quest used to lick ass though?
Just different characters.
Nah, he's not, bro. He licks ass.
Yeah. Was I wrong for blocking Monty Greavesy? Nah.
This what happens when you're there for
people, Nicolo? They they stab you in
the back. You buy someone a nice steak dinner, you know,
and they [ __ ] you over like Mrs. Mrs. Jo B, you know,
and then [ __ ] Yeah.
What is a snake, man?
What do you think?
just stupid characters.
He doesn't even He doesn't even like
call them people, does he? He just calls
them He just calls them characters.
Not even people characters.
Characters, you know.
That kebab was lovely, mate.
Uh, Jack the Ripper from PlayStation.
This is what I mean. I could actually
fuckle Monty. You know, if it wasn't for
Monty, I wouldn't have met Virgin Boy.
That won't leave me alone. I wouldn't
have met [ __ ] Jack the Ripper.
That was his name on PlayStation, Jack
the Ripper. You see what I mean? Cuz I'm
Monty. I met all these weirdos.
You know what I mean? Yeah.
Yeah. I had a nice one night stand on my
birthday two years ago.
I was going to go to Manchester. I
thought, "Fuck this." And I walked back.
But I actually got a one night stand that day.
She sucked my Willie, too.
She had big boobies, too.
I said, "Oh, I'm going to I'm going to
get you to get I'm going to get your
nails painted and stuff."
Just feeding them a load of [ __ ] And
then when I got when I got in their
knick-knocks, I ran away.
When I got in their knick-knocks, yeah,
I got a good one on my birthday, bro.
I got it from the swan. I went to the
Swan and I got uh one night stand at the Swan,
but I had to stop going there cuz I
don't like the music, bro. It's all
Irish and [ __ ] But the reason I like
going there, I haven't been there for
ages. But the good thing about there is
that there's no um
they're less you're more likely to kind
of get something because some of them
are Irish. Whereas if you go Simmons in
like central London, they're all stuck
up. Every single one of them more than anywhere.
Even though like
the music's way better in the Simmons,
but the they're just less stuck up at
the Swan cuz it's outside of Central.
Does that make sense?
Yeah. The swan. I ain't hid out for
ages, man. Swan. No.
Swear I met Sig in at the swan. Vessa.
Oh, bless. Yeah, it was better than um Yeah.
I have a boyfriend. Do you? Yeah. Yeah, man.
You can see the westernity in their eyes. [Music]
What about if you if you approach an
Italian, Nicolo? Do they say they've got boyfriends, too?
Nah, he blocked me. He was an Irish guy
and he wasn't He didn't wear glasses either.
just different characters.
She They all look like NPCs, bro.
They're all NPCs.
He says, "I don't want to watch that
[ __ ] anymore." And man says that in it.
He says he doesn't even know how I can
laugh at it.
They're all NPCs, in it. Why have they
got that look in their eye, Grezy?
That just westernized look.
It's them Tik Tok batteries in it.
You can actually see.
Ah, you remember that, don't you,
Nicola? You You know too much, mate. You
know too much.
Yeah. I was going to kiss. Yeah.
Why do they have that look in their eyes? You know,
it's the same. He says, right? He says,
you know what he said? It's he says, let
me give you this analogy. Yeah. It's
like watching a movie, the same movie,
but different actors. It's still the same movie.
That's what he says. Let me give you
that an analogy.
It's the same movie but different actors.
That's what he says. [Laughter]
Is that funny? Crazy. So,
do you reckon I'm mature or immature?
Gy, I'm I'm quite mature with it.
Tik Tok batteries
[ __ ] grievy. Did you ever watch Bad Santa?
Good. Good movie. See that bad Santa? Huh?
Yeah, you should watch it, bro. It's uh
that's probably my favorite movie.
It says there's a new conjuring on, but it's 2013.
But it's 2013.
but it's 20 It's a 2013 one. It says What's
See what I mean, bro? Oh [ __ ]
Yo, man. Sorry, bro. I was doing something. Different characters.
Same ending, same beginning, just different characters.
You know what that means? Yeah.
Hey, bro. Can I Can I send you something, Nicolola?
Can I show you something?
One sec. Let me upload it.
but even old people are saying it. One sec.
One second. It's uploading. Yeah.
One second. Yeah. What's up?
It was big, bro. [ __ ]
That even old women are saying it now, Nicola.
Even [ __ ] old old [ __ ] women are
saying it. And look how they have to
think about how long they've been with their boyfriend.
It's [ __ ] bro. I don't know why it
made me laugh. It ain't even funny. But yeah.
You know what I mean? But
she had to actually think about it a
year. It's [ __ ] bro. Ah.
So what? You don't think she had a boyfriend? Huh? [Music]
I said to adman, why do they say they've
got boyfriend? She says that it's cuz they're [ __ ]
You know what? Yeah, I might give Virgin
boy a good bet some.
I might give Virgin boy a bet.
That's good football bet tomorrow.
I I don't think I can sit there and
watch somebody I met [ __ ]
seven times d a virgin. I don't I don't
think I'm that cool, bro.
I a good football.
Yeah, I don't want to see him die a virgin, man.
I want to give him a plan, right?
Yeah, exactly, bro. It's cuz they're
simps. All of these like
I know, bro. I know. I know. It's mad. Yeah.
All the little simps on Reddit will say
it's men that don't have the
personalities. And is it mad how all of
the men that approach they do the same [ __ ] to?
I've got a very good personality,
but they say I ain't got one. It's mine.
Even though I've made friends all over
the country and
got friends and [ __ ] they they still
tell me I ain't got any personality.
Are you taking a piss out of me, Nico?
Right. I'm going to get Virgin Boy on a bet tomorrow. Now listen,
suck your dad's dick. He'll probably
give you about 50 60 pound, right? You
get that 50 60 pound,
you put on a double both teams to score
if you're listening and you will be able
to afford an escort and then you'll
finally be able to get laid. Yeah,
I think that's a good idea for Virgin Boy.
What do you I think that's a good bet for Virgin. >> Yeah. What happened
on his back?
You ready to go on this bet?
I'm just eating some crisps.
I had chicken sensation crisps.
The people on Reddit say that I'm going
to meet someone. Yeah,
I have a boyfriend.
The only place you're not going to get
that is Angel.
that is Asia.
The only place you're not going to get I
have a boyfriend is Asia in the world.
The only person I'm going to get that
why do I give bad advice you think
they tell me that I'm going to meet someone. Um,
I had a woman, she started abusing me
yesterday cuz I showed her like my
approaching videos and then she started
saying, "You're creepy recording." No,
no, no. It's like any bad thing you show
about women, they all go mad at you.
They all literally they all go to try
and [ __ ] smash ahead of him even when
they're shown evidence. It's it's crazy.
Virgin boy is a simp.
He defends women yet
I've had more women than him, but he
still defends women. Simpy behavior. Mad
[ __ ] mad behavior.
simp over women yet he's still a virgin
and he's dating a disabled girl that can't talk.
The last thing I would be doing if is
defending women, mate, if I was out that
[ __ ] hand in life. But they still
defend them. It's man.
They still defend women. Madness.
What's your Reddit?
One minute, bro, cuz I'm in the middle of typing.
Remember, keep trying, Nicolo.
I bet you just come here taking a piss
out of me, is it? I bet you coming here
on a Saturday. Yeah. With your little
mates drinking beer and you will watch
me typing [ __ ] Taking a piss in it.
Yeah, that's why I don't try anymore,
bro, cuz I already know the result.
You remember Oreo man
Gy? Why think you're the [ __ ] when you
know you ain't the [ __ ] You know why
think you're the [ __ ] when you know you ain't [ __ ]
You know what I mean?
That's why I always look at it. Mhm.
You know, you [ __ ] M
greasy. Is this Nicolo's trolling me? Is
he taking a piss out of me or is he is
he a cool guy? Is he one of the brothers?
Nope. I wouldn't.
I want to have a free with that Albanian
bro in USA. Is he?
I want to have a free with them.
You remember that video of me getting a [ __ ] nicot.
Yeah, if you could have a free with both
of them in it. there
and have [ __ ] USA.
I mean, you've only got one dick, so
what would you do? Cuz I'm not eating a
[ __ ] out, so I wouldn't eat anyone out. So,
I'm not sure. Have one on top. Yeah, you
should both have them sucking your dick.
I mean, you can [ __ ] them both in it.
I'm up some crisps.
Yeah, the Albanian ones I think I think
they're roughly the same size maybe.
So why didn't I like the Why didn't I
like the girl tenant then Nicolo?
So why didn't I really like the girl tenant?
Yeah, but why though?
Why? Imagine I [ __ ] both of them. Yeah.
Again, the Albanian USA Asian and they
both got pregnant.
Then what would happen?
That would be exciting.
You think USA is ever gave a blow job, Nicoline? Nah.
No, I don't think so. No, man.
Remember Damon when he said, "How do my dick taste?"
Yeah. Yeah. She said, "You give me one
if I eat her out." I said, "I'm not
eating you out."
So why wasn't Sig my mama then?
Yeah. Yeah. Baining. I kind of was
getting attached to her. Yeah. By one was nice. You know
what I mean?
You remember the Snapchat? You remember
the Snapchat messages?
Why don't my mommy ever speak to me anymore? Excuse me.
My mommy will never speak to me again.
Peter B can't get attached because he
already found his man.
You just mock me.
That's all you're doing is mocking my sayings.
Um just chilling, bro.
Went out on Thursday. Same old
Same old boyfriend [ __ ] Same old scenario.
Just chilling, bro. Yeah, man. Had a
kebab. Having some crisps. What are you up to?
Yeah, man. They're upset. You know the
maddest thing. Yeah, guys. Yeah. They
sit on here every day being obsessed all
their life. Yeah.
And they're not even being paid money for it.
They're proper like [ __ ] skint
saddos, bro. For real.
They're actually proper skint saddos, lad.
You know why they they call people skint
ghosting? Because they are skint. Think
about it, bro. Would they would they
would they be sat on YouTube all day
every day obsessed if they weren't skint? Exactly, bro.
Exactly, bro. Exactly.
Ronald Pump said before that you're
better looking than them, you got more
money than them, and you got a better
life than them, and it kills them.
Big up Ronald Pump, wherever the [ __ ] he
is. But it's true, bro, because they
don't get paid to do this. See, the
thing is ghosting yet. I don't You see,
I don't really come on here much
anymore. Like I'm I'm gone for like a
week, two weeks,
3 weeks, like so you know, you know, you
don't really see me on here much, bro.
Cuz I don't get paid to be on here.
I don't really get like
anything from being on here. So, I don't really,
you know what I mean, bro?
Cuz I'd rather be doing stuff where I'm
actually gaining money or doing
something. You know what I mean? Yeah, that
will never stop, bro.
I could go I could literally do YouTube
YouTube videos for 10 years
and then I could come back, right?
And I could I could look at their
channels and they'd still be doing it.
They'd still be doing it.
Now it's boring, bro. Uh
um Monty's kind of snaked me in a way, bro.
So I just blocked him.
He was trying to say, "Oh, I need to get
off of YouTube and grow up." And that I
almost cost him his relationship for
taking him out approaching when he
wasn't in you weren't even in a
relationship and he wasn't even
approaching. So what? You're trying to
blame me when you was the one [ __ ]
crying? Like, [ __ ] that, bro?
You know what I mean?
Yeah, man. I [ __ ] me hard.
I just blocked him in the end.
That will still be back to video. Yeah,
cuz they ain't got a life, bro. They're
skin. That's what I mean.
They ain't got a life. They're jealous
and skin, brother. They skin.
Look at that. Um look at that red star,
right? He says I'm triggered ghosting
and he's the one making videos on me
from the time he wakes up to the time
that he goes to bed. He is the triggered one.
He got he's got he got himself confused
with me. I mean that is severely
triggered to sit on YouTube all day
doing videos on someone. You must be triggered. Good, man.
>> I need to go back to Liverpool. Ghost
then. I need to go back to Liverpool, bro.
I mean, what it depends what you mean by
better. I mean, the women are the same everywhere, bro.
To be honest, they're all just not interested.
They found my other channel, by the way.
So, I had to um make a new channel cuz
these little weirdos discovered me.
You doing football match tomorrow?
You doing any football match tomorrow?
I was saying to Virgin Boy Ghost in that,
you know how he sucks his dad's dick for
extra money. Yeah, I done a treble both
teams to score and I got let down by one goal,
£20. I was one goal off £141.
[ __ ] Shbury let me down.
Yeah, I was saying that basically um you
know Virgin Boy, right? I was going to
give him a little bet to do. Obviously,
he'd have to suck his dad dick um to get
a bit of extra money cuz he's skinned
first, but maybe I was going to tell him
to get like 50 60 pound and maybe put on
like a double both teams to score and
that way he'd actually be able to lose
his virginity and he won't die a virgin.
Um, I was thinking of doing something like that
cuz it's hard to see someone still be a
virgin at 30 years of age.
Trust me, it's different when you've met
somebody seven times, bro. And they're
still a [ __ ] virgin.
So, all you got to do is suck his dad's
dick, get like 40, 50 pound if you can
stretch to it, win a football bet,
and he'll be able to get laid. Let's get
a nice escort. A nice escort for about
150, bro. Banging escort. Jobs a good.
So yeah, I was one go off of 140 pound
ghosting. It ruined my whole day, bro. I
was going to go out Saturday drinking. I
was just about to leave the house, but
because I didn't win that football bet,
it just it was just a buzz kill. Yeah, 100%. What's that?
Do you know what I don't understand?
Ghost in here is that
is that you know when I say like, "Oh,
women are cunts." No, no, no, no, no. Um,
you know when they say I um,
you know, like when I say women are
[ __ ] and they're stuck up in that. I
don't know why you get all of these
stimps. Yeah. That I've never had a
woman, right, that's had less women than
you comment on their defense. Like
you'll literally say like, "Oh, they're
stuck up or they're arrogant or you
spoke to one and they didn't even give
you the chance." like not even anything
offensive. And then you get all of these
simps that have never had women that
women don't like all go to their defense.
It's got to be like autism or some
something, bro. It's got to be something
like autism. Cuz if I was if I was these
people, I'd probably be in prison.
I wouldn't be [ __ ] sing. I wouldn't
be [ __ ] defending women. I'd probably
be imprisoned or dead.
You know, it's bad enough the position
that I'm in and I've been with the these [ __ ] women.
I hand on my heart, bro. I've got no
good words to say about them. I think
they're all stuck up, westernized,
trolls, and arrogant.
And sometimes they actually make you
forget that you're the one that's
actually been with them, not them.
That's my That's my honest That's my
honest opinion, bro. I'm not not even joking.
But they defend them. It's bad.
Just one of those things. Eh.
Yeah, man. Do a double both teams and
score. And I don't really like the
lineup on Saturday ghosting, bro.
Because uh I always use Wind and
Coldchester and Cambridge, but I don't
like who they're playing. So
cuz coldest is playing shoes on Saturday
and I don't think I want to bet on that. since
they [ __ ] me.
All we needed was [ __ ] Shbury to
score, man. I would have got my first
ball. Both teams to score.
So we bet lads. Yeah. Hold Hot boy.
Did you hear what I said though, bro?
What do you think it is? Ghosting, bro.
Oh my god.
When you finally lose it, Nico,
if you follow my tips, mate,
you'll be getting laid in no time.
You'll be getting laid in no time. You
follow my football bet tips
today. Tomorrow will be the day
where you finally get laid.
You finally lost it at 31 years of age.
What do you think, Steven Howard?
I'm going to have to do this video very
early for him tomorrow. I'm going to
Listen, I'm going to do 80. Obviously,
you go around quickly and suck your
dad's dick. He'll probably give me 40 quid.
half of what I'm showing yet, half of
what I'm putting on. But nonetheless, it
it will be enough for
for a nice win to get you an ethical
court so you can get laid.
Understand Steven Albert.
I don't want to watch somebody die a
[ __ ] virgin. That's heartless.
You know what I'm saying? Steven Albert,
that's [ __ ] heartless, mate. You know,
I can't I can't sit there and watch
someone die a virgin,
you know, never having [ __ ] never
never experience them sweet sugar walls.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
I can't I can't watch someone die of virgin, mate.
So, if you follow the um I mean, a
couple of us are in, aren't we? though. Wow.
Bro, you What do you mean [ __ ] that?
He's He's going to die a virgin.
What do you mean [ __ ] that? You want him
to die a virgin or something?
You want to You want him to die a
[ __ ] virgin, do you?
Why do you want him to die a virgin? Huh?
You'll never get laid, mate. Never get
laid. The ugly face scares them away. You know,
you know what I mean, bro?
Hello. Hello, Mark. You all right?
These people are still skit on YouTube, Mark.
Yeah, these people are still skit on YouTube.
Oh, nice. Nice.
It's so [ __ ] skin. Yeah.
All right. Suicide Mark. These people
call you skin because they are skin. Yeah. Bro, listen.
They call you skin because they are
skin. It's like this cuz they are skin.
That's why they call you skin cuz they're skin.
Get it right, bro.
No, I'm not. I can't check. But I'm
doing something at a minute.
Think about it, Mark. Think about it.
Think about it. You do you think they'll
be sat on YouTube all day, every day if
they weren't skin?
Think about it, bro.
Do you think they'd be sat on YouTube
all day, every day if they weren't skin?
You know, that's how you have to look at
it. See, I'm not I I come off of YouTube
for like a week, Mark. You know what I
mean, bro? Like,
did you see me meet Monty the other day? Mark,
where you where you living now, Mark?
What uh what city Where
are you now? When you
when you finally lose it.
When you finally lose it.
Trust me, mate. It's like I can I can actually
still remember when I was 17 and I lost it.
You know what I mean?
Can actually uh I can actually remember
whatever you [ __ ] do. Don't die that
[ __ ] virgin mate.
Whatever you do don't want to die a virgin mate.
It's very very important.
Little virgin [ __ ]
That's trying to help you.
Well, I'm out of here. [ __ ] out.