[ __ ] it up. Yeah. Yeah.
Done the football bets.
Yeah. I was I was Oh, let a few people
join. I'll explain.
So, I couldn't do a video, bro, cuz of
the [ __ ] stalkers on here in it. You
know, in case you win one of them, you
know what they're like on here, bro.
I done like a 6 minute video and I was
like, "Oh [ __ ] I'm actually [ __ ]
I had to do it quite early as well, but
then I thought, oh [ __ ] I'm just like
wasting my time and shit."
You know what I mean? Cuz I can't
obviously show them where I'm betting, man. [ __ ]
Cuz I actually felt like I was doing a
good deed, you know? So, yeah. Yeah, man.
They stalk you. Probably like call them
up or something. They're [ __ ] like
it. Yeah, I weren't going to come on
YouTube today, but obviously we're doing
a football me, Steven Allen, and Greavesy. So
wanted Virgin Boy to get in on it, but [ __ ]
couldn't do that video, man, because
it's shown where I'm doing it, you know. [ __ ] Yeah,
you got a lot of stalkers on here. Is it
to get you banned from places?
The skin low lives. You know what I mean? So,
you know what? I don't understand. Why
are these people making it so
unbelievably difficult to show me my £10,000?
Just just just just
have a think.
Right. These people have been on here
for [ __ ] years saying to people that
they're skin when they're skin
themselves and they're making it mission
impossible to show me this £10,000.
Like, don't anyone have like a bank
account or or something or cash or some
sort of account? It's cuz they ain't got it.
They don't show it because they ain't
got it. That's what it is. I mean that
in it that in its [ __ ] self, bro,
but it doesn't need to be. It could be
any amount, bro. They're making it so so
difficult for people that ask, right, to
show money every day. They're making it
so uh difficult for them to show theirs
cuz they ain't got none. the skint. I'm
only on YouTube today. [ __ ]
uh doing the football with these [ __ ]
I suck £100 on it or try to get that bit
extra from 20 pound, you know. So yeah,
£100 on two teams. I've already
basically considered it lost to be
honest with you. So there's no point
saying, "Oh, you lost that. I don't give
a fuck." I probably just said I've
already lost. I don't care.
So yeah. So it's not going to be a W
because I've lost a football bet cuz
yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] Oh [ __ ] I
actually done two football bets. I
done£10 on four teams. So it's obviously
less likely to win, but who knows? Maybe.
Yeah, I didn't play Frankie or anything,
man. And I'm good with that. And I was
even going to do like a little guide for
Virgin Boy to stay away from the
machines and cuz you don't end up like Timmy
saying that Timmy's probably got more
chance getting laid to be honest. So, uh
maybe we can talk about Timmy all we
want, but he's probably got more chance
of actually getting laid
if you think about it. But you know,
just I don't know. I like to give people
try to help people when I can. You know
why are these people making it so
difficult to show me 10 grand?
So difficult, bro. A year and a half
still no one's
What would that tell you, bro?
Have a have a have a think.
Have a think.
Yeah, man. You are special. You are
special needs. What are you doing today?
You sat on YouTube skin talking about yourself.
Another L. What was the L, bro? What L
have I took? I've been asking to show 10
grand for a year and a half and no one
showed me it. What L was that? Show me
less than what I've asked you to show.
I was just having I was just talking
right here to these people that watching
it. Why is it so hard for one of you people
to uh show me 10 grand?
Because you ain't got it cuz you're
skin. And even when you try and show it,
you end up showing less. How
of course I own them, bro. Because think
about it. Listen, I've been asking Okay,
let let's just put it this way. Yeah,
now now how long have I been asking
people to show me 10 grand?
Why would you show me an account that
has less than 10 grand if it's
I if that's your gambling account,
wouldn't you just show your main account
that has the 10 grand I've been asking
for? [ __ ] 18 months later, bro, and
I've still not been shown [ __ ] 10 grand.
I mean, I'm not going to start calling
people skin, but it doesn't look good, does it?
Of course, I own him, bro. He actually
thought, "Oh, yeah, we got one up on
me." I just saw that now. I didn't even
see it yesterday or that. Bro, I won't
ignore it. Like, bro, it doesn't make
sense. You don't just have 9 grand,
which why is he so so shame to say that
he's got nine grand? That's not bad
having nine grand,
you know? What's Why is he pretending
it's his gambling account? It's it
that's that's all right. It's it's enough,
you know? And he's also talking [ __ ]
because didn't he say that he uh he lost
three grand the other day.
So he's also he's also been caught out
lying as well. Oh, you are skinned, man.
Nothing skit about me, matey. I just put
£100 on a football bet. Nah, not as
skint as you people, mate. Not being
able to show 10 grand. You people
asking. That's why you waste all your
life all day, every day on YouTube
because you asking.
What you say about other people, you're
talking about your [ __ ] [ __ ]
selves, mate. You wouldn't be on here
for years if you weren't skin. You people asking,
you can't even show me 10 grand, bro.
Get get out of here, man. Get on my
level. Anyways, back to that. Uh, didn't
that guy say that he lost three grand?
Didn't my man say that he lost three
grand? He said that the other day. So,
he's also been caught out in a lie cuz
he said that he lost three grand, right?
Wait, hold on. If he lost three grand,
look at look at the account, right? It says 888.
But he said he lost three grand.
That You see what I'm saying, bro? He's
an idiot. He's They're all They're all
fantasy on here.
You It just doesn't make sense. Why do
they do this every day, bro?
The fact that I'm still asking 18 months
later for somebody to to to beat my
amount speaks volume, bro. Speaks [ __ ] volume.
They ain't got it. That's what I'm
saying. They ain't got They ain't got it, bro.
They call people skin cuz they're skin.
Think about it, John. Yeah. Look at what
these people do every day. Yeah. From
the time they wake up to the time they
go to bed. And they don't get paid for
it. And they don't get paid for it. The
stalking, the obsession, the keyboard
warrior [ __ ] And none of them get
anything out of it. No money. Their
bills don't get paid. Would they really
be doing that if they weren't skin?
Think about it, bro. Not not calling,
you know, people for a living. I'm this,
you're that, [ __ ] Would they actually
really be doing that if they weren't
skin considering they don't get anything
out of it,
which is, like I said, I weren't going
to come on YouTube today cuz I don't get
paid for it. It's a waste of my life and
it's a waste of my time. I did say we
was going to do the football, so I
thought I'd host a show for us all, you know,
and I was going to do a football bet
vlog, but then these stalkers will start
calling up the bookies and [ __ ] So,
that's why I I didn't do it. I would
have showing you the balance on the
thing cuz I'm not showing no money. I am
not showing no money in cash.
Not one single pound am I showing you.
Not even a penny. Till someone shows me
my 10 grand, I ain't showing [ __ ] all,
which they should really really listen to.
So I spent £110 on football bets today.
Got him right next to me.
Right next to me, bro.
Me and Callie was talking about this
last night about coming off this [ __ ] but
what the [ __ ]
Oh, did the game crash?
Well, mate, you mean I feel like
Undertaker, you know? I genuinely Oh,
the game crashed. [ __ ] I actually feel
like the Undertaker.
You know how he got undefeated for like
21 years? I kind of feel a bit like him, you know, undefeated,
you know, like when he got undefeated at
Wrestlemania all them years. I I I feel
like him. Like no one no one can beat
me. Like I swear to God, no one can beat
And then finally I'll get beaten by
[ __ ] Grezy. All right, bro. Did you
do the football bet? I stuck£100 on it
for a laugh. Did you do it, bro?
Please tell me you done it.
Yeah, bro. Dude, stick 100 quid on it. I
would. [ __ ] it. I just I did. I put 100
pound on it, bro. It's right next to me.
Show you if you want.
Look, I done two football bets. And if
it loses, I don't give a [ __ ] So,
there's no point saying, "Oh, you know,
yeah, you lost." I don't give a [ __ ] bro.
I'll show you, bro, if you want.
>> I done two football bets.
Look, can you see it?
Don't know if you can even see that.
£100 returns £333.33.
And this one,
this one here, look,
that's£10 on four teams. That would turn
509, but obviously I'm not expecting
that to come in. Be nice if they're both
coming. And then you get these people
commenting, yeah, saying, oh, I need
football bets to win to go out. How's
that then? If I've just spent £110 on football bets,
I literally could go out whenever I
want. I can go out this week if I want
to. I just like the feeling of
winning money because this because this
the thing is grievy because this country
is so [ __ ] right? That you're only
limited to really what you can do like
the cinema, win a football bet, go on a
piss because it's so [ __ ] I don't feel
like it's worth me wasting my money on,
you know, like, you know, hearing that
I've got a boyfriend, just stupid
[ __ ] people, and because I don't
I don't want to waste my own money doing it.
So, I'd rather just put a football bet,
put it away, and then go out the week after.
Like, if this football bet wins, I'm not
going out this week. Go out next week,
something. Maybe the Yeah, maybe the
week after. I don't [ __ ] know, but I
won't be going out this week. I need to
go cinema. I need to watch Superman. Yeah.
You know what I mean, bro?
Greasy, come on, man. You need to go to
Scotland. You don't want to You don't
want to be old, bro, and then look back
and realize that you were like these
people. Think of it. We're me and you.
Yeah. We're We're We're We're 20. We're
in our 20s. We're still We're still
young. We're not like these people, you
know. You've always wanted to go to Scotland.
You've always wanted to do that.
You can do it tomorrow if you wanted to.
You should you should do some things,
man, before you get old like these
people. I'll be going to the gym again soon. [ __ ]
you should you should I don't know, man. Why not?
You should do it, bro.
should do a little um Scotland tour. You
should go Edinburgh and go Glasgo. Why
not? Just go Scotland for 3, four days.
You'll like it, bro. You know,
I don't want to end up like these
people, bro. Old and [ __ ] disabled
and wasting all of my life on here.
Like, I'm on here today. Yeah, cuz I
said I'm doing the football reviews.
Cuz we like to do the football. But
after today, bro. Nah.
What? Waste of my life on here, bro. [ __ ] that.
I'd love to. See, if I got paid for it,
I would do it. If I got money for for
it, then yeah, I would do it because
time is money. But I don't get paid.
They never [ __ ] paid me. YouTube
never [ __ ] paid me. So what what do
you want me to do, bro? sit on here and
argue with jealous self reflectors every
day of my life. I look back in like 40,
50 [ __ ] years and realize what the
[ __ ] was you doing?
No, because what these people do, they
ain't got a life. You know, these these
skin people on YouTube, they ain't got a
life. This is why they live to do this.
They live they live to do this. We know
me and you. Yeah. We we just we just
have a laugh, right? We just take the
pierce and oh, bless you, you know, but
they they actually live to do this. They
live for this. Their life is this. You
know how people live for certain things?
They're they're they're they live to
[ __ ] with people online because they're
skinned. You know what I mean?
Yeah. That's what they do, bro. They're [ __ ]
So, yeah, bro.
Yeah, you could just go, bro. You could
just catch a train. I mean, you're not
too far from Scotland.
I went Scotland from London. It was
[ __ ] long, bro. I'll never forget
that. I got the train back two times
because the first time I was in
Newcastle, so it was only um an hour and
a half from Newcastle, but I got the
train back two times and oh, it was
[ __ ] long. I think I got the last
train back and then the first train back
when I went twice. It was long, bro.
[ __ ] long. The train back is long.
Yeah, I get it, bro. But they're not
winding people up, though. They they
they are. Hey, Joe. I like it when
you're here, Joe. Uh, I done two
football bets. I put £100 on uh a double
both teams to score.
And then I done a four-fold £10. So, I
spent 110 on football bets today. Now, I
done a I done a football bet for the V
uh a video for the Virgin, basically
giving him like some football tips. Um
but then I realized, [ __ ] they're
actually going to like call up the
bookies and [ __ ] So, I did upload it
cuz I know I said I was never going to
like entertain him again, but it was
more of like a a help video,
you know, a help video, not like a not a
response video that like I'm not going
to I'm not you I'm not a narcissist. I'm
not like a selfish person. You should
see like what I did for Monty. I'm not
that way inclined. I'm not going to sit
there and watch someone that I met seven
times die a virgin. I'm not going to sit
there and watch that. So, the whole
point was I was going to um say to him
like I done the video early cuz
obviously, you know, I said if you
quickly go to Cuden and you quickly give
your give your dad a [ __ ] it'll
probably give you about 50 quid. And if
you put 50 on two teams, hopefully it
wins. Um, you'll be able to get an
escort because the whole thing stemmed from escorts.
Our sort of uh relationship sort of
stemmed a lot of it was to do with
escorts. Escorts got brought up a lot of
the time. So, I feel like if he if he
could finally afford one,
you know, then maybe maybe he'll stop
the YouTube [ __ ] Who knows? You know,
I'm so clever in it, man. I really,
really am. But no, a lot of it did
revolve around escorts.
So, I thought, what better way it
started there. Let's end it there, you know?
Yeah. But yeah, hopefully this this
football bet wins. And I don't know why
people like you, Joe, think I need to
win to go out. I don't need
Take a look at your main. Let me see.
One second, bro. Hold on. Uh, one sec.
See, hold on a minute.
You want me to show you 28 grand?
So, you showed me £14,000. Okay. I don't
Well, do do you want me to tell you
something? I just seen that now. I've
just seen that now. And I'm not going to
block you, but do you want me to say?
Yeah, that's the rules. Yeah, that's the
So, you ain't You ain't got much than 10
grand. Okay. 14 grand. I don't have 28
grand. There you go. I don't have £28,000.
So, I mean, that's all a lot of these
people had to [ __ ] do all these
years. Yes. Nice, man. Nice. Nice. But I
don't have £28,000.
So, I can't show you what I don't have.
Simple. And that's what a lot of these
people should have done. You know what
I'm saying? But yeah, man. 14. Yeah.
Yeah. But nice nice n grand in that
other account, but it ain't your
gambling account. You can't even keep up
with your own lies. You gambled. So what
you cuz you said you gambled threek the
other day, right? Yeah. Nice, man. I
don't have 28 grand.
So yeah, thank you, bro. 18 months
later, somebody actually beat me,
but can I ask you something, Smokey?
Listen. Listen. So you beat me finally.
Yeah. And I admit, bro, I don't have 28
grand. Just admit you don't have it. I
don't have it. Like when I say you,
obviously not you. I mean, when I was
arguing with these people before, just
admit when you don't have it, I don't have £28,000.
I admit it. Just like a lot of these
people that weren't you should have
admitted they didn't have £10,000. You
know what I'm saying? So that's it. But
guess what? I'm not going to deny that,
Smokey B. But I will say something
though, you know.
Yeah. It's because they are skin.
No. Yeah. They're they're calling people
skimp because they are skin. I mean,
look what they do all day every day on
YouTube. They would be doing that if
they weren't skin. Yeah. The truth is
that they're skin. I mean, I ain't got
£28,000, but I'm not skin. No, they they are skin.
They are skin.
Which is it? Which is another thing,
Joe. Why didn't L just do that the same
as like what I've just done now? Do you
have £28,000? No, I don't. Like,
wouldn't it have been just easier if
they just admitted that they never had
it instead of dragging it on? I don't
have I don't have £28,000. Simple. So,
that way just stop. But let me tell you
something as well before this guy. I
don't have £28,000. Smokeoky B. I don't.
But let me tell you what I do have, bro.
I have a better life than you. And if I
had the money that you had, bro, I'd be
doing a lot more than what you're doing
on YouTube every single day. So, I don't
need £28,000 to have a better life than
you. And no, I don't have it. So, you'll
be waiting a very long time to see it.
But I do have a better life than you.
I've probably done more things in my
life than you have. That's what Lord J
should have done. Just admitted that he
didn't have the £10,000.
Just like Virgin boy. Just admit that
you don't have it. Don't show less and
then keep asking you to show money.
What I pro what what what he's probably
done though is he's probably just added
more money in that main account with the
nine grand which it doesn't matter. You
still shown it anyways. But yeah,
I mean you kind of had to show it, bro.
Otherwise, you would have just got owned. So
yeah, he ain't got loads of money, mate.
He tells you that he's got loads of
money, but he doesn't have loads of
money. That LJ is is [ __ ] skint cuz
you wouldn't be on here all day every
day if you weren't skint.
That's that's the logic I go by. If you
had all of these, if you had a life and
you have all of this money, you wouldn't
be sat on here every day doing what you
do every day. Not that you wouldn't be
on YouTube, you just wouldn't be on here
all day every day doing what you do.
They call people skin cuz they're
skinned themselves. It's It's
self-explanatory. You're skinn. I'm
skinn. That's That's basically what it
is. They go by their own line. They go
by their own lives on here calling
people skin. I just showed you a
fucking£100 [ __ ] football bet. What the [ __ ]
But how many people put [ __ ] But I
don't have £28,000.
So you waiting a long time for that, matey.
Dust the world.
But like, shouldn't you like
with all of that money, man? Like,
shouldn't you be doing stuff with your life?
You know what I'm saying? It's it's it's
crazy. Like, like I said, I'm not going
to be on here after today for a little while.
I'm not saying never ever come on here,
but if you had that kind of money,
shouldn't you be living the life that I
was [ __ ] living for 3 years? And I
don't live it much now because I've done
it all. Like, shouldn't you be living
that life, bro? Rather than coming on
here wasting your
I can understand if people was doing
this. Yeah. If they were if they were
old and they were That's the only thing
it could be is if they're old and skinn,
which is why they would do what they do
every day. There's there's no other
justifying it because they don't get
paid to do it. They do it free.
You know what I mean? Well, I mean, if
they're saving for something, but I
mean, like, what the [ __ ] have they been
saving for all of these [ __ ] years?
Know what I'm saying? So, it's strange.
It's It is rather
It is rather strange. And I do football
bets, bro, cuz I not cuz I need the
money to go out cuz I just like the feel
of winning money, picking something and
winning it. I don't [ __ ] need it, man.
But all like L J, right? Listen, listen,
listen. Look, look at what that Smokey
Bee's just done. If L J is not skint,
why is he not shown 10 grand? Why in all
of them 18 months has he not shown me 10
grand? Stop saying, "Oh, no, no, no. You
no. Why did no one on here show me 10
grand but Smokey B 18 months later?
Why have you made it so difficult?
have you made it so unbelievably
difficult to show me that money? Cuz if
I This is where it ain't making sense.
You've made it so unbelievably
difficult. And you start the game. You
all you people on here, you started it
like, "Oh, show money, show money, show
money." And you've made it the most
impossible to show yours.
when I don't have much money, bro. I've
not been skimped for the past 3 years.
You do you really? Well, except from
that time around Christmas. That time
around Christmas, well, I had like 20
cuz I gambled a lot. That's the only
time that I've been skinned in the past
3 years. Even if I win this football
bet, I'm not going out this week. I
don't Like I said, bro, like you
remember what I told you about breaking the cycle?
You remember what I told you about
breaking the cycle? Well, I might go out
if one of these numbers want to meet me.
But you remember what we spoke about the
cycle that needs breaking and if you
don't break a cycle that you're basically [ __ ]
I mean, think about it, bro. If I go out
this week, even if I win the football
bet, what do you think's going to
happen? We'll be back to square one again.
So, it's time for plan B. You see what
I'm saying, bro? It's very easy to to be
into that cycle and then, you know, not
even realize you're in it. But the same
thing is going to happen again. So
that's why I said, "Okay, well, what
I'll do is if I I'll get these I'm going
to do it whether I win the football or
not. I'm going to try and get some of
these numbers to meet me." Oh, if they
don't meet me, okay, I'm going to go to the cinema.
Do you know what I'm saying? If you
don't break the cycle, you're [ __ ]
Simple. You never ever I broke the cycle
with Fishing Frenzy. I broke the cycle
with roulette. If you ain't if you don't
break a cycle, you're you're [ __ ] basically. So,
I normally come in here when I've lost
gambling. Well, I don't gamble on
anything but football. So, I mean,
that's a bit hard because I don't gamble
on slots. I don't gamble on roulette.
So, I mean, are you forgetting that I
literally don't gamble on any form but
football anymore? Oh, you must have
forgot. So, I mean, that's that's a bit hard.
That's exactly what I'm talking about,
bro. And that's why I'm going to
Thailand. This is why I'm explaining to
this show. Listen, bro. You got a good
chance of this football bet coming in
today, which is a little bit of extra
money. You've got enough numbers on your
phone. Even if you need to travel, we'll
travel. It's not a problem. You don't
get anything from them numbers on your
phone. Leave. Simple. No more going
around in circles. No more me coming on
here moaning. You know, you just leave.
You've tried more than anyone in the
world. Leave. Leave while you still can.
Because in in 5 years, in 10 years, you
there's not going to be no Thailand
anymore. There's not going to be no Asia
South There's there's not going to be no
South America anymore.
There's not going to be
none of that anymore because it's just
going to become like the West. You know,
Thailand's not how it was 10 years ago.
You think it's how it was 10 years ago? No. So
saying that probably I probably I don't
know when I'll be out again, bro. I just
don't see the It won't be this week,
you know? Yeah, of course I'm not happy
cuz I'm back here. How can anyone be
happy when they're in this depressing country?
How can anyone be happy here? It's depressing.
It's a [ __ ] troll country, bro. Do
you know what they need? Do you know
what they need to do with this country?
Yeah. They need to put a trolls They
need to put a troll's face as the flag
because it's literally just a troll
country. It's designed to annoy you.
That's that's what this country is. It's
designed to piss you off with the women,
with the gambling, with the government,
with the waiting around for things,
you know? It's it's a country designed
to annoy you. That's what I think. Um
politics as well. So, it's a it's just a
country designed to annoy you. That's
what I think. Anyways,
it's not just the dating. It's you can't
even go to [ __ ] work in peace without
dealing with [ __ ] I mean, [ __ ]
hell, bro. Like,
there's so many different things, bro. Like, so yeah.
I don't know, man. I don't know. It's
hard to explain it.
Yeah, I got enough numbers anyways,
mate. Even though if I need to go
Scotland this week, I'll go Scotland. If
someone wants to meet it, I don't really
care, bro. I'm I'm I got nothing to lose
at this point. But at the end of the
day, if none of them want to meet, then
that's the end. Uh
I'm waving my white flag, bro. I think
I'm I'm retiring, lad.
It's not full of opportunities, though.
Most people in this country are [ __ ]
skinn. Look up the statistics.
You can't even get a date. You can't
even get [ __ ] laid.
It's a [ __ ] depressing country. It's
[ __ ] depressing, bro. What the [ __ ]
I mean, yeah, London. You can get jobs
in London, but it's not about lack of
opportunity. Just the country is just
[ __ ] It does. It doesn't matter about
that. It's just the country is just [ __ ]
the way it's run. That's what I mean by
it. It's not about that there's lack of
opportunities or whatever. The country
is is [ __ ] The women are [ __ ] The
people are [ __ ] It's full of [ __ ]
Everywhere you go, it's the same people.
It's the same thing, just different
characters, Joe. It's the same thing,
just different. Now, I I even said to
this woman yesterday, if I was still a
virgin, I said to this woman on Reddit
yesterday as well, if I was a virgin, I
would have I'd be in prison now. I would
be in prison. If I was sat here right
now, lad. Yeah.
No, I don't need to show you anything.
I'm not showing you anything. No, I
don't need to show you anything. If you
don't believe me, that's on you, bro.
I'm not going to lose sleep. But yeah,
if I was if I was a virgin, bro, I
generally would have done something
crazy, bro. I'm not even joking. But I'm
Yeah, I just can't be asked. See,
I just trying to think of the good
times, bro. But it is a depressing country.
I hate England, bro. I hate it. Yeah.
God knows what it's going to be like
when in [ __ ] 25 years when [ __ ]
children are my [ __ ] age.
God knows what it's going to be like. Jesus,
mate, you're not going to send me five
grand, bro. Listen, listen, listen,
listen, listen. You're gonna send me
five grand? Really? Okay, bro. So, why
didn't you show me £10,000
when I've been asking for 18 months? So,
you're going to show me five grand. So,
I assume you got more than 10.
Why Why didn't you show me How about
Okay, how about you? How about you show
me 10 grand and I'll show you a picture?
How about you show me £10,000 just like
Smokeoky Me did and and I'll show you a picture.
That sounds easy, isn't it? Yeah. Just
like just like Smokey Beed since you're
asking something for me. Yeah. Okay.
Yeah. Show me 10 grand and I'll show you
a picture. Is that a good deal? That's
something I could actually That's
actually something I could actually promise.
Don't know what to eat today. What's everyone having?
Oh, you still there, Joe?
I need to I knew there was something I
had to ask you.
I'm talking like I actually know these
people. I mean, I guess it's good when
there's genuine people on here, you
know. Ah, I knew there was something. Nice.
Really? Can Can you show me 10 grand?
Well, show me 10. Show me 10 grand then. Nice, bro.
I'm going to ask Biggy. One second. One
second. One sec. One second. One sec.
One sec. Hold on. Yeah, man.
Can I ask any of you this question? Yeah. Is
do do you Daz? Are you you live in Liverpool, right?
I need to ask you this question because
I'm sure this is a this is a uh out of
London thing. Seems seems to be I can't
find it anywhere.
Are you uh
are you in are you in you're in
Liverpool in it? Franklin.
Oh, I need to I need to say something to
Greavvesy as well.
Oh, you're in Liverpool, isn't it, Daz?
Okay. Well, I'm just going to say this
to anyone. Does anybody know? Does
anybody know? Does anyone know somewhere
in London that does a chicken ticker don
kebab? Cuz I still can't find it. Like
when I was in Wales and that's what I'd
like to eat today.
I I don't think we have that. It's okay.
I'll just wait.
You You'll wait. Yeah. Until the chicken
ticker dollar has been made. That's what
I'll just do. I'll just record me record
me saying that. Oh, I I'll just wait
until it's been made.
You know, Greavvesy, I was eating some piggies earlier.
Nah, I was eating some piggies earlier
and then I saw their face. They come up
on TV and I don't think I can eat
piggies anymore, bro. They're [ __ ] ugly.
Like they they are really ugly. Like not
the baby ones, the [ __ ] their actual
the adults. Their face. I couldn't finish it.
They're [ __ ] their whole face is just
ugly. Them piggies.
It's [ __ ] disgusting, bro. I don't
think I can eat pork anymore. No. They're
[ __ ] ugly, bro. Them pigs.
That's so funny.
Yeah, I want it. I want I want a
chicken, bro. It's [ __ ] lush. Can't
get in London.
You can't get it in London, bro.
No. Looking at them pigs, though, bro.
They're [ __ ] ugly. I probably won't
be able to eat pork now for a long time, man. Nah. Nah, bro.
Has any of your kebab shops got a
greasy? The chicken tickadona. Have you
heard about it or have you seen it anywhere or
I said yesterday but I can't remember if
you answered. I can't find it anywhere here.
It's [ __ ] banging. It is.
And it doesn't it doesn't chase it
doesn't it's hard to get man. It might
be one of them things you can only get
out of London
cuz I ain't never seen it here bro. Never.
It was in Cardiff. Maybe we'll have to
go to Cardiff and get it again. But yeah,
picky piggy piggy in the middle.
That's okay. I'll just just wait.
You wait? Yes. Until it's been made. That's funny.
Yeah, but I can't um I can't I couldn't
find it anywhere, bro.
That's the best chicken tick I don't
know is that [ __ ]
It's making me fancy like a a tandoori
chicken today, you know,
like an actual tandoori chicken.
Let me see. I'm going to keep trying,
but one second.
I'm going to keep trying and I'm going
Right. Kebabs. Yeah,
that's okay. I maybe you're getting like
a Indian place also.
Well, if it's is it chicken tickon?
Yeah, but it has to be chicken ticker
donut though. There's a difference.
Yes. If it's a chicken ticker donut.
But it depends what that consists of cuz
that's there's lamb donut, there's
chicken donut, then there's chicken ticker donut.
But yeah, probably. Yeah, we don't have
that. I can't find it nowhere.
Burger. Burger. Don. Okay. Donuts.
Lamb donut. Chicken donut.
Can't find it anywhere, mate.
Can't find it anywhere.
Yeah. Same thing again.
Why is this so bloody hard to get, man?
What is this? Is this
This is hard, bro. Is it?
She don't want to know.
He don't want to know you.
She don't want to know you.
Okay. How about this?
N this is going to be very hard to get.
All right. Kebab house. Okay.
Kids meal. What? Donna kebab.
See the same thing again. [ __ ] off.
Donna kebab. Chicken donut. Mix on.
Right. Don a kebab.
Chicken on a Nope. I thought it was
going to say ticker then.
No. This is impossible to get, bro.
There's got to be some [ __ ] one that does.
This is London for [ __ ] sake. Not Kent.
Not a [ __ ] part of Kent.
Chicken shoes kebab.
Okay. Okay, kick kebabs.
Okay, here we go. We should get it here.
We should get it here. Now, then it goes back to normal.
Then it just goes back to [ __ ] normal
chicken. This is going to be hard to get, man.
Damn. Ticker chicken ticker. Why don't
they just have
Right. Let's try this place.
Why is this so [ __ ] hard?
I don't think you're going to get it. Grezy, try here. No.
Well, I don't think you can get it, Grezy.
That's okay. I'll just
I'll just wait.
No, you can't get a photo for coffee, man. [Music]
Nah, I don't think so, mate.
I can't find it, bro.
Why don't they have it?
Let me put my let me put my location to
Cardiff. Yeah. And let's see how easy it
is to get
if anyone could know an address in
Cardiff or something. But no, we don't
have it here, mate.
That's madness, though. That is mad. How
the [ __ ] don't they have it? Madness, bro.
It is strange, isn't it?
All right, it
Well, not really.
So there's only
there's only 16 kebab shops in Cardiff, right? Right.
Oh, see what I mean, bro?
No, that can't be right.
Right. But what meat is that?
Right. Don't know. Yeah. But what is that? Don kebab.
Yeah. But what meat is it? Is it
Chicken donut. Chicken ticker kebab,
which could also be the chicken donor kebab.
But is that donor or is it?
That doesn't really say, but I think
that's the one.
speaking to Kab, but that might not be the donor.
I bet I'll find it here.
Yeah, but it doesn't say the meat. No kebab.
Well, I don't think you you I don't
think they have it.
Well, I don't I don't think we can have it because
They don't sell it. It's okay. I'll just Wait.
Well, I don't think we're going to be
able to get it.
Do the way you said it. Well, I don't
think you're going to be able to get it, mate.
A bless you.
What? Whole size hot starters? Nah, bro. I'll just
wait until it's been made.
German kids meal smooth movies.
So what happened with Britney then?
Where is he?
What happened with um
what happened with um Britney Graves?
Well, I don't think you're going to be
able to get it chicken dollar. Nah,
this is quite hard, bro, to get
even in Cardiff. I don't know.
But then you need to go on the actual lamb donor chicken shamb chicken donor.
No, we need a chicken tab.
Desert. This might do it here. This is a
Indian kebab shop.
This is one [ __ ] trying to find this,
isn't it, lad?
You can't even get it there. Nah.
Well, I don't think they have it,
so we're not going to be able to. But
that's what I'd like to eat tonight.
But it's what I'd like to eat tonight.
Well, I don't think I don't think we
have it. Well, that's what I'd like to eat tonight. What?
Well, I'm just going to end up going
back to Wales, bro.
I swear to God, I'm just going to end up
[ __ ] going back there and getting it.
I might do a video um to you, Greavvesy,
dedicated to you.
But it's what I' it's what I'd like to eat tonight.
It's what I'd like for my for my tea tonight,
right? I'll come back later. Yeah.
when the football starts.