Yo. All right.
This football bet ain't looking good,
but like I don't give a [ __ ] about £100 really. Nah,
I don't give a [ __ ] about £100, mate.
But yeah, you better get on them bets.
I'm coming off this [ __ ] after this
anyways, bro. Or after tonight.
Like I said, I decided yesterday.
Where is creepy, bro? Very, very, very
creepy, creepy, creepy.
Creepy crops, bro. I'm telling you,
this community is [ __ ] weird, bro.
You want the link?
Is that the real you, man? Uh, one
second. Give me a [ __ ] man.
I'm coming off this [ __ ] after today,
bro. One sec.
One second, bro. I had my phone back
link for some reason don't work. Come on. Hello.
>> Where's [ __ ]
>> He's not on here anymore, man.
>> Is he back with that? >> Yeah.
>> Well, he's back with her. >> Yeah.
>> But why is he not back online?
>> Because he doesn't want people finding
out where they are and [ __ ]
>> Well, easy. Don't go. Yeah. Obviously,
it's not going to last. You know that. No.
>> Yeah. Obviously not, bro. And then I
just said to him, "Don't come running
back to me again because she's just a
snake, isn't it?"
>> A woman actually goes online like she
did and showed them finger herself in
front of the community. Is that what is
that a woman he really wants to be with?
>> Yeah, true.
>> In my eyes, in my eyes, that's just a
dirty [ __ ] right?
>> Yeah. Are you Are you still with K? No,
>> she's here. Say hi. Hi. >> Hi. You text,
>> can you go on data? How dare you? >> Huh?
>> You text key and ask the data.
>> No, never. What the [ __ ]
>> I did barbecue.
>> You wanted to go for a barbecue?
>> What? Mom got her. >> Yeah.
>> So, you did?
>> Yeah. You wasn't with her.
>> Well, she never had feelings for anybody
on this internet anyway. So, she would
have put you on a [ __ ] barbecue. Thank you.
>> Yeah, that's good then, isn't it?
>> Yeah, you need to get yourself a
girlfriend and settle down, bro.
>> Yeah, man. I'm just I need to Bro, this
community, you need to get off this
community, bro. It's super weird, man.
>> Yeah, I know. It's full of pedophiles
just like you out.
>> So, you PJ, you're still on it.
>> How long have I Yeah, because Monty got
me back on it. That's why.
>> [ __ ] off. He's still here.
>> No, he Yeah. And why? How did I get back
on it? Cuz I'm on it.
It's like he gets you back on it and
then he and then he leaves himself. You
know what I mean?
>> What happens on the night you went out
with [ __ ] then?
>> He didn't do anything with anyone.
>> Who was that guy?
>> Just someone. It was just the the
girlfriend that I was talking to. He
didn't do anything with her.
>> So, welcome. Who was he holding around? >> No,
>> bro. The only thing he was going on
about when I met him was Natalie. That's
all he was going on about.
He wasn't talking about anyone else. He
didn't talk to anyone else, you know, like Yeah.
>> None of my business anyway.
>> No, I know. I'm just [ __ ] And he was
trying to say to me, yeah, how Oh, I
could almost lost my relationship over
that. I said, "Hold on a minute. I went
out to sue you to have a drink with you
cuz you cuz you was crying over Natalie.
I was trying to help you." And then he's
trying to blame me.
>> What the [ __ ]
Well, he thought it was his fault.
>> What do you mean? He's trying to blame you.
>> Like, basically, he was saying, "Oh,
because I met him." Yeah. And we went
out for a drink. Yeah. And Natalie
thought that he was talking to other
girls. That's my fault. I said, "Hold on
a minute. She wasn't You wasn't with
her. And when you was crying over her,
messaging her, she wasn't me. She wasn't
thinking about you or doing anything.
How is that my fault?"
>> Well, Matie was taking the piss out of him when
>> That's what I'm saying.
Well, when didn't Natalie actually do a
broadcast saying that she was going to
go out um to a pub and flirt with a lot of
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> She was also he was being reringed with
them two on and she would have taken the
piss out of [ __ ] >> Yeah.
>> If I had a woman that did what she did,
I would never be with her. That's a that
is a a poo of slag.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
And if he
>> went there to try and help him and [ __ ]
and he had no money in that as well. So
I thought [ __ ] it. So
>> if he ever if he ever gets pregnant or
she gets pregnant, sorry, she he needs
to get a DNA test cuz I believe she's
one of them people that shag anything.
>> Jesus name is the same.
>> Yeah, cuz he cheated with Casey.
>> And she forgave him lots. >> Huh?
K forgave him a few times when he
cheated on her.
>> Yeah. Yeah. He But I I just thought it
was pathetic how much he was crying over
that. I told him that as well when I met
him. I said, "Bro, just leave it."
>> Back together when she basically made a
fool out of him all over the internet.
Then they're back together. Like she was
clear she didn't want him back and she
was calling him a [ __ ] and everything.
>> She got money. Do you know how she got
the money to go to Nottingham? She got
it from that Jaden. So the whole thing
was he she was supposed to go there and
[ __ ] his best friend, but she just went
there and got back with him.
>> So why was they arguing then on that
live stream then? Why was she
>> I think she she's apparently she's like
that when she's drunk. You know when
she's drunk she she switches and [ __ ]
>> Yeah, but she was shouting get off me.
Get off me. What was that about?
>> [ __ ] knows.
>> Cuz he was like oh I ring the police or something. It's
>> bet's not looking good. Uh Steven
Howard, bro. I put 100 on it. But yeah,
I don't know what happened there. [ __ ] knows.
>> So, is he still home?
>> She was maybe playing Yeah, maybe she
was playing hard to get. I I don't I'm
not sure. I've never met I've never ever met her.
>> Is she Is he still homeless? >> No.
>> Is he not in that homeless sh anymore?
>> No. And I said to people on YouTube,
"Oh, he's just living with Natalie." I
didn't say where. And then he had a go
at me. I said, "What the fuck?" All I
said was one thing.
How can he live with Natalie if she's
supposed to be in a girl's HMO?
>> Yeah, that's the point.
>> I don't know where I don't know. I know
they're living together, bro, but I
don't know where they are.
>> Yeah, but she quoted and said online
that she's in a a girl's place that no
boys allowed. So, how does that work if
if if she's in a girl's place, no lads?
Something doesn't add up somewhere. >> Odd.
>> Well, she went on a live stream that night. Yeah,
saying that um there's no men allowed here. So,
>> how's that?
>> Maybe maybe she said that just to put it
off the people and maybe she's still
living in the same location. That's my
honest opinion cuz it's a bit
coincidence that that flat that they had
was nice. Perfect. I don't believe
kicked out of it. I really don't.
>> No, but why was she building to HMO? He
goes back to Mansfield in that shelter.
Now they're back together. It it doesn't
add up. Something's weird.
>> And then she hated it all over the
internet. He was crying all over the
internet. Then he was saying, "I'm gonna
shag Tom Dickinary when I go out with PJ."
>> Do you know my theory on it?
>> I think my theory on it, right?
>> I think she's pregnant. The trolls will
find out about it. They acted out the
scene to make it look like that she was
left and he left her. She did what she
did for on purpose when she was drunk to
make it look like it was real. They got
back together. She's still having a kid.
And I think that's what it is. They're
just pulling people off the scent
>> cuz they could. That's right.
>> But the thing is, right, he used to go
mental at me, right? When I used to call
him [ __ ] She's called [ __ ] and he
takes her back.
>> Is it like one rule for one?
>> Yeah. He said he said he said that's the
only woman he's ever loved, isn't it?
>> Oh, [ __ ] off PJ. He was with me for 10 years. Get
>> I know. I know. I'm just saying what he
said. You heard him say the same thing.
>> He [ __ ] in bed, by the way. Just like to, >> huh?
>> No, he is actually [ __ ] He He literally
He doesn't even perform properly. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, I know. I was dirty. Little
secret. You got a small wheel.
>> So, what happened at the end of the
night when you two were hammered then?
>> Huh? What happened at the end of the
night when you two were hammered? Uh,
>> so I went back to where he was we went
back to where he was staying, right? And
I um and then we went into city center.
We went back to the city center about
7:00 and then um I just got the train back home.
>> Oh, so you didn't stay with him then?
>> Nah, I can't stay on other people's beds
and [ __ ] you know.
>> [ __ ] hell.
It was only w too Birmingham's far but
it's not like too too far is it but yeah
it's come back. Yeah.
>> Do you like drinking with [ __ ]
>> It's all right. Yeah.
>> Really? Did he not cause any arguments?
>> No. He was a bit hyper but no he was all right.
>> When did you last drink
>> shouted at a bodyguard or some [ __ ] was you?
>> Oh yeah.
Yeah. Lab was being a prick.
>> Yeah. Was that Mongol's fault? Cuz
>> No. No. He was No. No. Basically, he was
speaking to someone. Yeah. Um, you know,
like, you know how people line up to get
into the club and there's like a metal
thing over it? He was only speaking to
someone and about kept saying, "Oh, step
back, step back, step back." He wasn't
even doing anything wrong. He just started.
>> So, no, he was No, they all he was being
a prick to be fair.
I just said, "Leave it." Yeah.
>> So, you you staying in are you staying
in Scotland now or you going back?
>> I'm just on a break. I'm allowed a
>> How you how you have you been out before or no? >> What
>> have you been out very far or No,
>> what nightclubing?
>> No, I just like to see where girls going
at city center.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Do you like it? Well, they're filming
the new Spider-Man up here, isn't they?
>> Yeah. But do you like how do you find
Glasgow? Do you like it?
>> Yeah. It's actually um
different, I should say. The accent's different.
>> It's dangerous, isn't it?
>> I don't know.
>> Oh god. So long then. No,
>> I blocked him.
Wow, that friendship lasted.
>> No, because I'm sick of him bl for for
for [ __ ] holding out anything that I
only tried to help him. [ __ ] that.
>> He's a user anyway when he's on a use.
That's what he does.
>> You know, I went up there, I spent 200
quid, you know.
>> 200 quid. And what did he pay? Nothing.
>> He didn't have anything. He had 20 pound
to last him two weeks. Well, no, no, he
did buy He did buy a drink to be fair.
He did buy a drink or two drinks to be
fair. He had changed to be fair.
He did give what he could, but yeah.
>> Come to Glasgow and I'll show you the party. >> What?
>> I said come to Glasgow and I'll show you
Welsh man parties.
>> Yeah, but you don't you don't really go
out though, do you?
>> Trust me, I'll show you the party. Your
best experience of your life. >> Really? >> Yeah.
People were Welshman parties. Mhm.
>> Sounds Sounds good, man.
>> You would I might have to give it a whirl.
>> You would lose week of sleep. Trust me.
>> Yeah. I've not been to Glasgow. I've
only been to Edinburgh.
>> Yeah, Edinburgh looks nice, doesn't it?
I've been through there.
>> Yeah, it is nice. But but they say
Glasggo is better to drink, but
Edinburgh is like it's nicer to like
look at this. So, whatever. Yeah.
>> If you want a good experience of
drinking and partying, go to Cardiff.
>> How did you get up there? >> Train. >> Coach.
>> The How long did that take?
>> Well, I live in the Midlands, don't I? I
live in I live in Leicester, don't I?
So, it's not that long.
>> It's still quite far though. [ __ ]
Scotland, is it?
>> Yeah, I did a nighttime one. >> Jesus,
>> it's 9 hours all together.
same distances from Leicester to my
hometown to be fair.
>> Maybe. Yeah, Plymouth's even far from
me. Plymouth is very far from me.
>> Yeah, I don't live in Plymouth.
>> No, I know. I'm just saying that as an example, it
>> I'd love to see you in Cardiff partying.
>> I've been to Cardiff.
>> Have you?
>> Yeah. Three times, bro. I used to go
there drinking. Yeah, I've been there. It's good. >> Good.
>> I talk about Cardiff. Yeah. I tell you
something, Bryce. Yeah. You know when I
was last in Cardiff? Yeah, they have
this thing there. You know how they've
got lambda and chicken donor, but in
Cardiff they have chicken hikadona, but
they don't have that here.
>> And I really fancied it. I was looking
for it today and yesterday. I can't find
it anywhere here.
>> It's nice food in uh you should go to
Wales try experience where it's got nice
food in there too. Like lash.
>> What? What? Welsh food.
>> Yeah, it's nice.
>> Yeah, I want to try Welsh rabbi.
Honestly, Wales and Cardiff are the best places.
>> Yeah, Cardiff. I always I've been
Cardiff a few times, but I might go
there maybe next week or something. I
get that chicken ticker.
A chicken ticker. Donna. Oh, it's
[ __ ] hot, man.
>> PJ ask K out. She's not even interested
in PJ cuz a real man.
>> Don't react to him. Just ignore him.
He's not there.
>> All right. Yeah.
>> Who is it?
>> Very fortunate.
>> Just ignore it, bro.
>> Don't react. That's what he wants you to do.
>> They want you to react to it. >> Yeah.
>> He's just n anyway.
>> But you ain't been carded for years, isn't it?
>> I haven't been here for seven years, mate.
>> That's a long time.
>> Not really.
>> Of course it is.
>> Have you been for seven years? I The
last time I went to Birmingham but two
weeks ago was like two and a half years
ago. That was long. Yeah, but I could go
back to Cardiff and people know me in
Cardiff probably because I used to go
Cardiff a lot.
>> What? Like around the city center even.
>> Yeah. Everywhere, mate. I was liked
>> madness, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Welsh people know how to party.
Like the Glasgow people go to Wales and
then they go to Cardiff. But the fact is
if you go with a Welsh man, they pay for
your drinks all night >> really.
>> And you don't have to put any money in
your pock literally you you won't have
to take no money with you. You be
drinking out of their pockets all night.
>> Sounds good, isn't it?
>> Yeah. They are respectful people, Welsh
people. And the Scottish love the Welsh, too.
>> Do you know where St. Davids is?
>> Yeah, I know where that is. Yeah.
>> Yeah. I got a friend that lives there.
He said it's [ __ ]
>> Some places are crap. It's like It's
like Glasgow. Some places are [ __ ] in
>> Are you living in a HMO? >> No.
>> I thought you was.
>> Why? What the [ __ ] Who said that?
>> No, I thought you was.
>> How can you get kicked out of a country, you [ __ ]
>> I tell you, these people are funny as
[ __ ] You can't get kicked out of the
country. Sorry to By anyway. >> Yeah.
>> You know, you must have to murder
somebody or [ __ ] whatever. It's just
they [ __ ] idiots, man.
>> They are idiots for me.
>> Honestly, PJ, I've been on honest since
2018. Yeah. And the it's just the the
community is not being disrespectful or
rude. It's full of nonsense, mate. Yeah,
it is not. DJ,
>> when are you going to buckle up? Cuz
you're like 28 in September, aren't you? October.
>> No, you don't even know my You don't
even know my birthday, is it?
>> Well, I am older than you by two months, I think.
>> Yeah, you're born in August, is it? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, I'm born in October.
>> Yeah. See,
>> this football bat ain't looking good, Joe.
[ __ ] one nil, the other's nil nil.
But you never know, man, do you? You never know.
>> Uh, Jack, man, have you have you seen
all the women that I've pulled on my
YouTube channel or do you seem to have memory loss?
>> Anyway, I'll speak to you later. It was
nice talking to you. Yeah.
>> Yeah, bro.
>> Well, peace out.
>> Oh [ __ ]
>> Yeah, it's not looking good, Joey.
Bro, Joe, listen. Yeah,
I have to
I have to come off this [ __ ] after after
today though, bro. Where will they all
now go, bro? No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no. Look at all of
the women that I've been with. Bro, I
need to come off this [ __ ] after today
though, bro. I promised I was going to
stay here for the football. This is
really, really, really getting weird, bro.
No, no, no. It's getting weird. So money
gets me back on here. Yeah. And then he
pisses off and he leaves me on with these freaks.
[ __ ] off, mate. [ __ ] off.
Just these weirdos on here, bro. And I'
I've just realized that like I said in
my video, they're never ever going to
stop, bro. They're never ever ever going to stop.
And I don't want to keep giving them
content even when I'm ignoring them,
bro. like that. Clearly never going to
stop. [ __ ] them, bro.
Okay, Cambridge has got a penalty. Come
on. Come on. Come on.
Yes. One. Now we just need Swindon and
that other [ __ ] now. Don't end nil.
Nil. We got one in the bag. Now we just
need another one.
Oh, mate. Come on. Where are these
women? Don't you worry where these women
are. And you're banned. Bye-bye now. And
this is exactly what I mean with these
idiots on this community, bro. I just
want to kind of get off and live my
life, you know, even for a couple of
months. These these weirdos are never
going to stop.
They never Oh, come on, bro. [ __ ]
hell. Now we just need them.
I knew that Cambridge and Coldchester
one would be 1-1. Now we just need that
[ __ ] swindling game. They're still
nil nil, but you know, they've got a whole
they got a whole half. Yeah,
they're never ever going to stop on
here, bro. Never.
And I'm not going to I'll still come on
here now and again and go live and [ __ ]
I'll still come on and go live like very
rarely and [ __ ] Don't worry, man. But
Oh, mate. Come on.
Come on, bro.
There's not going to be content though.
If I win, I'm not going out. I'm still
not going out this week and I'm going
away in two months anyways. I I don't
think you believe I'm actually done with
this country, Joe. I'm actually done in
this country with women. I I've made my
mind up now, bro. 100%. I've made my
mind up. Even if I win, I'm still not
going out. I I I've made up my mind,
bro. I I literally generally have. So
>> I made my mind up, bro.
Just like Ant-Man did a long time ago. So
think is the best way, bro.
No, I will message the numbers I've already got. Yeah,
one's I got the first one in the whole
in in in the in the first half. Now I
just need Swindon and the other one.
They've just got two. What the [ __ ] Two
2-1. They got another [ __ ] goal 2
minutes later. So it's 2-1. Now we just
need a Swindon game which is nil nil.
Oh, what the [ __ ] man?
So now it's two one, not one. Okay, so
that one's done. Now we just need the
other one. So I'm done. Um, yeah, I'll
message the numbers I've already got for
like this week, but I ain't going out
like doing this approaching [ __ ] anymore, bro. Nah,
I'm not doing it anymore. [ __ ] that.
Nah, of course they're not, mate.
They're going to [ __ ] score.
How much did you put on it? I put £100 on mine.
Yeah, I got £100 on mine.
No, they're not going to screw me, bro.
Yeah, I put £100 on it. I basically can
just kiss goodbye to it, but I put £100
on it this time. Swindon,
Barnet, and Colchester in Cambridge.
Yeah, I don't I don't Well, I put I I
put £110 on football bets today.
I done one 10 pound one and one 100 pound one. Yeah.
Can't believe that I got that that one
in the first half. Now we just need these [ __ ]
I think we're going to win this one,
bro. I think we're going to win.
Doesn't matter if it's nil nil, bro. We
still got a whole half.
It's the last 20 minutes that count. So,
but I probably just probably going to lose.
Hey, bro. You're not you're not going to
get a reaction, so there's no point.
Yeah, bro. So, you're not you're not
going to get a reaction.
So, there's no point looking for one.
So, what are you going to do after
today, lad? Like,
what are you really really going to do after today?
You're not going to be able to project
your [ __ ] life onto me anymore. You're
not going to keep being obsessed. And
what are these pe How are these people
going to cope?
How are these people going to cope after today?
You fat ugly 40 year olds ain't got a life.
How you going to cope, man? What are you
going to do, bro? What are you going to do?
Yeah, these people are seriously jealous, bro, of something.
They're I I you know, I don't know, bro.
I don't know what I think they they've
just been bullied their whole life. The
these people like Red Star and all. I
think they've generally
they've got some sort of hatred and jealousy
um or or something. Yeah, they they've
just been bullied their whole life.
Well, I'm going to I'm going to torment
them tomorrow, bro, cuz I'm coming off
this [ __ ] you know. Yeah, it's all
right for the It's all right for a wind
up and for a reaction, but they they
they generally are jealous of something.
They generally are jealous of something
because you know they don't even [ __ ]
know you, bro. They're It's like even
when I was doing with that with that
Smoky Be earlier, bro, I was thinking,
bro, we don't even know each other and
we're arguing on YouTube with these
[ __ ] losers that ain't got a life.
That's all they are. They're [ __ ]
just losers that ain't got a life.
That's That's it, bro. [ __ ] jealous
of some [ __ ] [ __ ] knows. I've got so
many 40-year-old men that are obsessed
with me, Steven Howard.
Generally, I think I've got so many men
that are obsessed with me. It's mad,
isn't it? 40 year olds as well. Did you
ever see Monty get that?
Did you ever see Monty get that? Nah.
Did you ever see Monty get that, bro?
Nah. Did you ever see anyone else get that?
Nah, I don't think it's crazy. I think
it's just weird and jealous.
I don't even think it I think it's
weird. It gives me the ebiejibbies.
Mad. They're clearly jealous of something, bro.
Clearly jealous of something.
It's cuz their lives are [ __ ] They're
all old, wrinkly, disabled.
So that's why they uh
do reckon this football bet's going to come in. Steven Howard
[ __ ] better do matey.
Oh yeah, I'm off after today anyways.
Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ] Reeves, I forgot to tell
you. I got a I got a stitch
I got a stitch puzzle. Mhm.
I got a stitch puzzle, lad
given to me, which I'll probably do when
I can be bothered.
Yeah. What you think is going to win?
You think the bet's going to win? Yeah.
I've got more on it than [ __ ] you.
I'm just going to just start going to
the gym, getting ready for my um holiday
because I realize that you these people
are not going to stop on here. These
insecure, fat, ugly, insecure people
ain't going to stop. They're not going
to stop. So, there's no point me being
on here entertaining these fat, ugly low
lives. And even when you're ignoring
them, you're actually giving them
content to put on their channel. [ __ ]
them, bro. Fat ugly losers.
Not wasting my life on air, bro. Not
wasting the 20s I've got left on here,
bro. You mad? [ __ ] that. We need fat ugly people.
They're [ __ ] weirdos. Yeah, man. I
don't know. Double both teams to score.
We already got Colchester and Cambridge.
Now we just need Swindon and Barnett.
Yeah, they won't stop, bro. I should
have left this [ __ ] They're clearly
jealous of something though. They are
clearly clearly jealous.
You know, you know, you don't see it,
but cuz you think it's all a joke, but
you don't actually see the other side to
it. Like they're they are jealous, bro.
They are they are jealous. For them to
do this every day from the time they
wake up to the time they go to bed. They are jealous.
Like they are really jealous, bro. Like
they they they are, bro. They are. And
only you can know what you're jealous
of. Uh, and then don't ask me, don't ask
me, bro, what what they're jealous of.
Only they will know what they're jealous of.
Cuz they don't even know you, bro. Do
you not know how weird this is? They are
40year-old [ __ ] mongos, right? That
don't even know you. And they do this
every day. They do it for a living.
They do it for an actual living.
That's what when I used to cold approach
these women and I never used to get
anywhere. I used to say, "Oh, if only
I'd put x amount of hours into working."
And then when I actually finally did,
oh, I actually made some money.
Yeah, maybe I'll get an escort. Maybe. I don't know.
I won't be going out this week and I
won't be going out next week either.
What's the point? It's just the same
characters. I'm waving that white flag.
Just wave that white flag in it.
Yeah. Like imagine imagine you done your
all imagine you done your content here
for like 10 years, bro. And then you
look back and they're still doing it.
That's a murderous.
I've also got a far fold as well.
Not in this country, bro. Like I said,
I'll message them numbers that I got the
past few weeks again to see if they want
to meet me up to that uh next this next
this week. But I won't be trying again,
bro. I've made my point here.
I've made my point enough times. So, got
nothing left to prove.
I hope the Swindon and Barnet [ __ ]
they both score.
Come on, you cunts.£333,
so it's good. Is it?
Lucky I didn't do that Bristol game, is
it? Would have been [ __ ] I was
thinking of doing Bristol, you know.
Yeah, that's what I'm doing, bro. I'm
making content for my other channel. No,
I don't want these [ __ ] following me.
And there's like no point even trying in
this country anymore.
Maybe maybe I'll give it another week
before messaging them. Maybe
maybe do it next week. Maybe. Who knows?
But I need to go to the pictures.
Yeah, I made content for my other
channel where these people that's why I
made the other channel. So these people
couldn't find me. I don't want them
following me about these fat ugly mongos.
It's just it's the same ending and same
beginning, just different characters.
Just different characters
madness, bro. I was speaking to Bess earlier.
Come on. You I think this is going to
[ __ ] off Steven Howard, bro.
Well, I always bet Swindon, so no
regrets. Probably should have done the
Chillingham game now, but
do you reckon they're going to score?
Both of them and Bar's
got one of them scored already. It's
good we got we got both teams to score
the first half.
What was the odds on that? Three to
that was three to one, wasn't it?
[ __ ] better come, mate.
They're nil nil at the moment, but then
they got a second. They got a hole.
So, what about my mama and Nicolo? Nikyo. Niko. Yeah.
They're just not interested in this country.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
Why can't they touch my mama? Why?
You know that number messaging me was
LT. I've got LT saved as [ __ ] I don't
actually know why, but I've actually got
LT saved as [ __ ]
I know. It's a bit rude, isn't it? Yeah,
he's lying saved as [ __ ]
My uh phone book.
I don't think it's going to come in for
toffee, mate. Oh, Cruz beating Fleetwood
2-0. Well, that's my uh fourfold [ __ ] already.
Yep, that's my fourfold [ __ ]
People showing money, bro. Listen, them
bank statements could have been from
anywhere. Them bank statements and them
bank accounts could have been from
absolutely anywhere, mate. Yeah. And
that's not even me making excuses. Yeah.
Because two people's been called out on
it already. Yeah. Literally, you showed
a bank account that could be anyone's.
That's not even me making excuses. That
is actually serious, bro.
You know what I'm saying, bro? Like,
come on, man. You didn't prove any of
the money was even yours.
So, you haven't ruined me. And guess what? Yeah,
we're we're not done. We're not done,
bro. [ __ ] we're not done. Let's
say you ruined me. Let's say that you
actually ruined me. Yeah. And that is
actually your money. Yeah. Okay. I give
you the benefit of the doubt. You want
to play the good-looking game? You want
to start showing your faces?
You know, you want to start showing your faces?
Nah, best off not doing that, mate.
Think about it, bro. You technically
can't do that. Cuz if you done that,
you'd end up like the bomb.
You know, you'd end up like the bomb,
bro. You can't show your faces. Cuz if
you showed your faces, you could
literally could never come back on here
again. Get rejected. Well, guess what?
I've had better looking women than
you've ever had. And that's not even me
just saying it. The proof is in the
pudding. Brother, listen. Like I said,
show your face.
You can't show it. None of you can show your faces
due to ugliness. So, you shouldn't be
talking about And no, no, no, no. People
have been caught out showing fake bank statements.
Do you actually realize, right, that
people have shown fake bank statements before?
You know what I'm saying? And that other
people have. What? You You mean one
person? You mean one person have? Bro,
one, bro, listen. The only one that
showed the money that I'd asked
if it's even real is that Smokey is at
Smokey B. He is the only one that has
done it. And how long did that take? 18
months. Have a word with yourself. You
didn't show me money. You ain't showing
me money at all. The only person that
showed me money, if it's real, is Smokey
B. Why are you talking [ __ ] You didn't
show anything in 18 months.
So, 20K investment red. That's not his
money. And there's no proof that is his
money, bro. If it's really your money,
show some cash. Cash.
If that's really your your body, show cash.
Yeah. You're talking about yourself.
I've had more women than all of you and
I've got money. You How much money do
How do you know if I'm skinn or not?
This is exactly why I'm coming off of
this community, bro. This is exactly why
I'm coming off this community. Yo, read
all of these comments, right? These
self-p projecting comments. This is
exactly why I'm coming off. And I've
made the decision to come off and stop
arguing with these disabled people every day.
This is exactly why, bro.
you know people self- projecting you
their [ __ ] lies onto you every day. This
is exactly why, bro. You're one of the
reason. And I'm telling you, I'd rather
just make go make a fresh channel now
where these people can't find me. People
are actually going to be genuine.
Bro, listen. You got beat at the money
game for 18 months. You got shown Okay.
Okay. Okay. Okay. So, why did you not
show me my Okay, let's everyone stop
talking for a second. Yeah. Right. Let's
everyone just stop talking, right?
How many months did I show you that £6,000 for?
How many months did I show that money
for? You had three months to show me
money and you didn't play the money game
with me. Get the [ __ ] out of here. 3
months is a very, very, very long time.
I could still be showing the exact same
amount of money now and you still won't
show it. It's because you people asking
and that's why I'm not arguing with you
anymore cuz it's the same [ __ ] with you
people on here every day. Bro, bro,
listen. Listen, listen. Did you not just
hear what I said, Joe? When you show me
my 10 grand, I'll come back to you. Yes.
When you show me my tech and this is
exactly why I'm coming off of this
stuff. This is this is exactly why I
want to start fest because of these
people. Because of these self-p
projected ugly people. This is exactly
why I want to come off of it. This is
exactly why. It's the same conversation.
It's the same argument. Bro, you got
shown thousands and thousands for months
and you couldn't show me anything. I'm
not having this conversation with you
again. Show the money again. What? For
how how long do you need to be shown
money for? Okay. Okay. How long do you
need to be shown money for? You weren't
showing nothing in them 3 months. You
showed me nothing. Listen. Listen. Stop
talking a second. One second. Hold on.
You got shown money for 3 months and you
had nothing to show me in 3 months. Bro,
bro, bro, hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
Hold on. Hold on. Three months. Why did
Bro, none of you have money, bro. None
of you have money.
That's the funniest thing about it is
none of you people have money.
None of you have got money.
Bro, my my bet is losing. I don't give a
[ __ ] if my bet loses, bro. None of you
have got money. Look at your lives. Sat
on YouTube every day, bro. Low lives.
Can't leave your house. None of you have got money.