Right. So, this is going to be a v a a a
video to well live stream to Timmy. Wow.
Always draws you back into this [ __ ]
Yeah. Not I'm not responding to these
stupid little [ __ ] mongos like
[ __ ] Red Star and them little fat
ugly mongos ain't got life. But yeah, I
thought I watch your live stream, right? One second.
And would you believe that this guy's
actually more more disabled than I can ever be?
Deadly lady chucking out. But anyways,
yeah. One second. Hope you're watching
this, bro, cuz this is dedicated to you.
Yeah, cuz I've actually got experience
in this. This goes to you and this goes
to secular slots because I've got
experience in this, right?
Let them join.
Ah, bro. I'm doing I'm doing this to
Timmy. Yeah. One second. Let a few more
people join. I'm really want I want to
You know what it is? I want to be live
now whilst I'm in the mood, whilst I'm
angry. So I can tell you exactly what it
feels like. So uh yeah, cuz I don't want
cuz if I calm down, I don't want you cuz
obviously this is where you could end up
in prison or you could end up mingling
someone in or ming the shop up. So it's
important I do it now. It's important
that I do it now. Stop talking about
yourself. Uh yeah, you are a skin mon.
Um anyway, so listen, I want to do this
video now whilst I'm in the mood, right?
And this is literally dedicated to
Timmy. This ain't no virgin legs or
[ __ ] fat ugly red that ain't got a
life. I'm only doing this for Timmy.
Yeah, listen. Yeah. One second. then
more people join cuz there's no point
trying to explain it to you when when
I've calmed down because then it's going
to be a lot harder cuz I could have just
done something end up in prison or
smashed up something. I don't know why
these little self-perfections are still
calling me skit when I've literally
shown more than they ever have. Must be
talking about themselves. That's why
they're on here all day every day. But
that's not the point. Right. What's it
right? So let me tell you something to
me. Yeah. cuz I've just I've gambled a
bit today cuz I went to the cinema. Yeah,
we've got enough people on it now. You
can you can watch this back. So, I went
into the uh [ __ ] sake. Went into uh
the betting shop, lost £50 on fish and
frenzy, then I don't know 50 football.
Went to the cinema to watch Superman.
Came back from the cinema, then I
watched uh then I put £50 on roulette.
Bro, I wanted to literally kill someone.
Yeah. Don't give me this [ __ ]
[ __ ] about how, oh yeah, well, if
you put some money away and50 or£100, it
doesn't matter how much you lose, it
doesn't matter how much money that you
have left. It where that doesn't come
into any of it, bro. This does not come
into any of it. If I lose, I want to
kill someone. Like, that's how I And
this is exactly why I've not done it for
four, five, six months, bro. You don't
all You also don't realize there that
even though I've not done it for like
what four, five months. I mean, I've
only just started doing the football bet
again. It brings it all back from all
them months ago where they kept [ __ ]
you over and [ __ ] you over and
[ __ ] you over and [ __ ] you over.
It doesn't matter how much money you have left.
It doesn't matter. I If I carried on, I
would have ended up killing someone in
them four or five months cuz I know what
I'm capable of. If I carried on, let me
let me want to tell you one of the
reasons why I stopped Timmy. Yeah. Cuz
if I carried on, I know my temper. Yeah.
And it's worse than Ant-Man's. And I
would have ended up seriously seriously
killing someone. Like I do you know the
reason why I didn't smash up the shop
today, bro? Cuz I don't have the energy.
I can't be bothered. You understand? The
only people you do is bully yourself.
We're not We're not here for you
spastics today. We're having an honest
um we're having an honest chat about
gambling. We're not We're not
entertaining you little skifflings ain't
got a life that self-reflect every day.
We're talking like proper proper proper
[ __ ] So that's why in them four or five
months I would have ended up I would
have ended up probably murdering
someone. And I and and you know when I
say this stuff though I'm not I'm not
chatting [ __ ] Just like when I said I
went to Birmingham. I'm not chatting [ __ ]
And it's like and another thing I'm not
lying about Joe when I say this as well
is you know when I said if if I was a
virgin right like you know these simps
that defend women. If I was anything
like them, I would have gone on a
killing spree. I would have I would have
I would have because I didn't lose much,
bro. One I done a 50 football bet and
put 100 pound on the property. I didn't
lose much. I done a football I done a 50
boat score no draw. Yeah, I went to the
cinema as well to watch Superman. It's
not about the money, bro. I've still got
money left. I got plenty of money left.
I can do what I want.
So at the end of the day,
so bro, if I was like one of these
virgins, like it's like this is what and
and I never got and I never had a woman
like them never like never been with a
woman, I would have I would have gone on
a killing spree. I would have gone on a
killing spree. This country is a troll,
bro. I'm telling you right now, this
country is a troll. You know,
you know what I mean?
So, it's like uh it's not uh you know
what I'm saying? This country is a
troll, bro. You get [ __ ] over with the
women. You get [ __ ] over by the
weather. The people annoy me. And then
you get [ __ ] over by the gambling as
well. You get [ __ ] over with
everything in this country. I was like,
bro, it's been like 4 months and it's
still the same [ __ ] It's still the same
old four months later.
That's like the ser closest to serious
like four or five months, bro. What the
[ __ ] And it's still the same [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. You know.
And it was so bad I had to get the long
way home. I had to get the long way home as well.
You know, I I had to take the long way
home because I was so agitated. I
couldn't even keep still.
I'm good, bro. I just don't like the the
whole the women [ __ ] and the gambling
[ __ ] in this country. Well, I don't
really gamble anymore, but like the
women [ __ ] It's all designed to [ __ ]
with It's all designed to [ __ ] you over.
If you think about it in this country,
it's all designed to [ __ ] you over.
Gambling, women, [ __ ] it. It is
really, really, really, really, really
bad. Really bad.
What I don't understand is why people
think that you need to be skinned for it
to affect you. like Timmy. Oh yeah, if
you got some money in your wallet, just
just take put 50 pound um aside and then
gamble with that and then Okay, so what
is that? Okay, then so what? Okay, so
you lose £50 and then you're okay. Yeah.
Do you know what I'm saying? Like no,
it's not, bro. It's bad. It's bad news.
It's bad bad news. You know, that's why
I stopped all them months. Like, you
know, this is the first time in months.
This is actually the first time in
months, you know, and all of these
people that are sat here saying skint,
you know, it's Yeah, it's not about the
money. Yeah, it's not about the money.
You know, it's not about the money.
That's the whole point. It's not about the money.
It's about just losing on them. You know
what I'm saying?
I don't have the energy to smash up a
shop. I would I was going to do it, but
there's no point.
You know, it's madness, bro. He doesn't
understand. And this guy is more [ __ ]
disabled than I could ever be. What the [ __ ]
Doesn't matter that it's only money,
bro. I could I I remember I had a back
date back money of £4,000 before. I lost
a 100 pound and it [ __ ] [ __ ] with
me for like half an hour, you know? It's bad, bro.
And and and I keep seeing these stupid
comments as well to Timmy that you don't
want to end up like me. End up like me.
I'm thinking, bro, listen, I'm not
perfect here. Yeah, but I've probably
got a better life than most people on
here that are that are doing this
trolling [ __ ] bro. I'm not addicted to
gambling. What? Because I lost a
football bet and it affected my mood.
Yeah, it's always done that. Like, I
don't know why these people seem to
think I'm addicted to gambling, bro. The [ __ ]
They They're idiots, bro. They're [ __ ] idiots.
But yeah, it's [ __ ] man. You get [ __ ]
over with everything. The women I was
going over my approaching videos earlier, Nicolo,
and this I think I've got about 300
approaches. Uh um
Okay. I don't have a better I don't have
a better life than most. No way. Well,
then, bro, if you've got a better life
than me, then get off of YouTube and
stop trolling every day then. Okay.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Should we Should
we Should we Should we go You know what?
I'm not going to even have this
conversation, bro, cuz I know what I'm
saying is right. If you think you're
right, then good for you. I'm not even
going to have this conversation, bro.
You You can't have conversations on
here. So, there's no point, you know?
There's not even no point even having a
debate because you don't understand
anything. You don't get anything. So
there's there's there's literally no
point in even me wasting my time
explaining anything to you. I'm just
trying to get [ __ ] Timmy to
understand. It's like the whole money
thing. You don't understand how the game
works. You keep going back to square
one. So I let you crack on, bro. If you
want to think I'm sk think I'm skin.
Good for you, bro. I don't give a [ __ ]
You know, it's that's that's fine by me,
bro. I know what I am and I know what
I'm not. So if you want to call me what
you are, that's on you, bro. I'm not
going to No one's going to stop you doing that.
But any it's to Tibby to help him really
understand the severity of it.
If I was doing this for four or five months,
I would have seriously ended up in
prison. Like, I'm not even joking, bro.
Or at least I caught paying a [ __ ]
fine. So, it's just not worth it for me.
First time in months and months and
months, almost six months. So, I'd say
Yeah. You know what I'm saying?
Yeah. And all of that six months before
it matters as well because you didn't
win in them six months either which led
you to stop actually doing it, you know?
So the industry is dead. And I was like,
bro, the ind what the [ __ ] bro? Like
the dating game is dead. The in the
gambling industry is dead. Like imagine
it was one or the other. Imagine the
dating game weren't dead and the
gambling industry was dead or the
gambling industry was dead, but the
dating game wasn't dead. Imagine it was
one or the other. At least life wouldn't
actually be too bad then.
It's why everyone's leaving now.
Everyone's leaving England now. They're
going Dubai. They're going [ __ ]
Thailand. It's It's depressing. It's a
depressing life here, you know. It
really really is, you know.
I felt like smashing someone in.
Well, I Well, I know it's dead, so you
know, you think what you think. I think
what I think.
There's no point arguing about it, is
it? I I was was going through my videos
and I think I've recorded about 300.
Do you Do you not actually think it's
mad how the gambling wasn't that bad two
years ago and the dating wasn't bad at
two years ago? Have you noticed
everything's got worse?
Yeah. Talking about yourself again, bro.
Like I said, if you people weren't skin,
you wouldn't be on YouTube every day
doing what you do. So that's actions
speak louder than words. So I'm not
going to even get into it, bro.
If if you're not skin and you got all
this money, why are you coming on
YouTube every day [ __ ] with people
for free? Bro, ask yourself that in the mirror.
You clearly ain't got a life. You
clearly are skinned yourselves.
It's mad. You call people skin even when
they've shown you thousand and they
still show you thousands. It's mad. But
like I said, you're self projecting. So,
I mean, what else can you actually say? Um, so you've got it's
so that's that's what it is. And you're
done. Yeah, bro. Like I'm not coming on
here to like um try to like have a
debate with you people cuz I realize
that we're beyond that now when we can't
have debates. You It's like Joe, it's
like you seem a bit slow as well. But I
like to think you're just trolling and
you're just trying to [ __ ] with me cuz
no one can be as No one can be that
stupid, man. Come on.
You know what I'm saying, bro? Like you
you don't understand things in your
head. I was trying to explain this to LT
as well yesterday, but he didn't seem to
get it either. So, I just put it down to
it's just the [ __ ] community in it really.
Bro, you you are slow, bro. You got
explain the money thing about a million
times and you still go on and on and on
and on and on and on and on and on and
on about it. You know what I'm saying?
It's It's ridiculous, bro. Like you ask
people to show money cuz you ain't got
money yourself. If you had all of this
money, go look at your own money, bro.
Go look at all of this money that you've
got that I ain't got cuz I'm skint
apparently. That's all I just say to
these people now. And then what what
what's their what's their comeback, lad?
You know what I'm saying? You know what I mean?
No, but LT made a fair point. He was
like, "Oh yeah, that six grand. You you
don't have it." I said, "You're missing
the point. You people got shown money multiple times,
literally multiple multiple multiple
times and different amounts of money and
you you still didn't get the point where
it got shown to you for about three four months.
Um, and you just don't understand it.
So, there's just no point getting into
it, you know. So, yeah.
Uh, it's pretty common here when you're
either mad skin or venting. So, what do
you expect? Any thoughts on me telling
you that I've literally not been skinned
for about 3 years,
apart from that time in December? I've
never skimped. I've not been skinned for
about 3 years.
So, I mean, am I am I lying? No. I've
literally not been skinned for about
three and a half years. Literally,
I've never ever had to worry about money,
you know. Hey, Bing, I'm going to block
you, bro. What have I told you about
thinking that I'm Monty or Timmy? Bro,
I've told you. I find it very insulting.
You're not good enough to troll me.
You're not a good troll. Stop it. So,
listen. Listen. Let me let me explain
this to you.
I have not been skimped in three and a half years.
Three and a half years. I have not been
skimped. Maybe even four years. Trust me
on that one. The only time I had no
money was December last year. Yeah.
Really? Yeah. Really?
So, I mean, what the [ __ ] If I was skin
right now, I'd say, "Oh, I'm skinn. I've
got no money. Oh, I get money. Yeah,
again. Oh, I might win a football bet.
Bro, I've literally not been skinned for
almost four years.
So, I mean, you've been shown money.
You've been shown a life. You've been
shown everything. Can you still call
people skin? So, at the end of the day,
it's like, yeah, and I did do something
with the six grand. I went out drinking.
I got escorts. I got designer clothes.
Something that you never done. Something
that you rich people should be doing if
you have all this money. You know what
I'm saying? But yeah, I'm not going to
get into it again anyways. So,
still trying. Bro, you don't know where
I live. But anyways, I'm blocking I'm
blocking these idiots anyways, bro. I'm
not having this conversation. You know,
you call people skint because you skint
yourselves. You know, you've been shown
money multiple times. You can't show
nothing. Look, same boring boring story
every time. You know what I'm saying?
You're boring, bro. And I've come back
on here tonight because I was pissed off
because of the gambling, which is what
I'm trying to make Timmy understand.
That's the reason. That's the reason.
Yeah. You want the reason? Because I'm I
was pissed off cuz I lost money gambling.
Even if it was a small amount of money.
Yeah. I really really shouldn't gamble,
bro. I really But this I don't gamble
though. But I don't gamble. This is the
past. This was the first time in four or five months
and it seems nothing has changed.
So yeah. Well, yeah, of course it's
gambling. I literally said it was
gambling. You know,
I could go out tomorrow and get on the
piss if I wanted to, but I'm not going
to do that, am I? You know. So
yeah, I'm just trying to explain to Sim.
I got a 50 football bet on.
Think about what you're saying. I'm
skinn. Yeah, I lost £100 a fy. I put a
50 football bet on.
Yeah, bro. I'm very skinned.
Like, bro, it's like
literally, man, if you got all this
money, live your life, man. Get off
here. I don't mean get off here like,
you know, never come on. Listen, just
just you got all this money, all of you.
Everyone's skin. I'm skinned. Live your
life, bro. Get off here. Come on here an
hour a day. Come on. You got all this
money. Come on. Come on. Come on. You know,
you know what I'm saying? No, no, no.
The women thing was annoying me in the cinema, you know?
So, like, [ __ ] off, man.
The women thing is [ __ ] annoying as
[ __ ] bro. It's [ __ ] wrong. All of
it's wrong. And you know what? I I know
that I'm It's It's an irrational feeling
with the gambling and it's an irrational feeling with
uh what's the other thing? Um
I don't know what else gambling and but
with the women thing, I don't think it's
irrational. I think it's justified. Why?
By irrational, I mean no one else acts
the way I do. But if it annoys one
person the way it annoys me, that's a
problem, you know.
But the women feel I don't think that.
No, I don't think that is irrational.
You know, you going out hearing I've got
a boyfriend and then pissing you off. I
don't think that's irrational. I think
that's how it should be.
No, it wasn't today. There was no couples today.
So, I don't think that's irrational. I I
don't go out for that reason.
I've got about 300 approaching videos. [ __ ]
bro. Record it. I've got about 300 recorded.
No, what I'm saying is I tried to
explain to LT the same thing I tried to
explain to you. You have been shown
money multiple multiple times and when
you're shown money, you run away, which
is why I don't waste my time anymore.
That's why. Not because anyone skint.
Yeah. You've been proven to be what you
are just like what these machines have
proven to be what they you proved what
you were like for [ __ ] three 4 months
when you were shown that money. I'm not
wasting my time unless I'm getting paid
for it. Simple. Yeah.
And that's it.
But yeah, I've got about 300 approaching
videos recorded. It's mad how long it's
been the same [ __ ] for.
But it's still worse now. It is still
worse now. But it's mad how some of them
were like a year and a half, two years
ago, Nicolo, and it's the same [ __ ]
You're watching the same [ __ ] literally.
And then Superman was kissing in the
film and that and I was thinking, "Oh,
Nola, you can't even watch a film
without it being without it being um
without it being like some form of some
form of a sex scene. It's a madness,
isn't it, bro? These simps should should
all come together and and and set a
campaign against women. That's what
that's what these simps need to do." You
know how like there's a KKK for people
that are racist towards black people.
These simps, I can't even imagine how
they feel being virgins, never even
being with a woman, and and and they sit
there and they and they defend them.
I think it's madness. I generally think
it's [ __ ] madness cuz I'm thinking,
oh, I feel like one of them people in
the bodybuilding form, but except that
they never lost their virginity until
they were 37. I feel like I feel like
one of them. It's bad enough to be in my
position, bro. This is why people kill
themselves. I'm telling you. Yeah.
I'd say in my whole time doing this, I
would probably say I've done about
close to 5 6,000 probably. Yeah,
I've done more than anyone in the world.
Easy. Easy, bro. Easy, boy.
Yeah, easy, bro. Easy, man.
I would say 100%. So, I spent like 160
today just [ __ ] going cinema.
Cinema was like almost 40 quid. Oh, but
I'm scared. Oh, yeah.
So, yeah, I'd say probably 56,000.
It's madness, isn't it?
Nope. I lost 100 on the FB and I done a
d I done a football bet 50 pound both
score no draw returns 438.
I think that's got some sort of chance,
don't it? You know, but yeah. Yeah.
You know what you should do crazy? Yeah.
These people want to see money. They
should come and you should you should
pick people to come on the hangouts and start talking.
You know, it's like that Nicolo account.
I know that's for [ __ ] that Joker. He
knows too much, you know,
and anymore. Um, bro, I stopped for like
four months. Five weeks is nothing. I
stopped for like four months, bro.
I've only started doing the football
bets the past two weeks, but bro, I've I
ain't I haven't done gambling like that for months.
Months. Literal months because of this
because of this problem. Every time you lose,
why can't you just have a normal life
and you don't get [ __ ] over by the
women? you don't get [ __ ] over by the
way. It just never it will never change.
Oh, my [ __ ] WhatsApp got deleted
and then I had to reinstall WhatsApp and
then it just [ __ ] it deleted a lot of my um
my chats, my convos.
Show it as
Yeah, them numbers are all [ __ ] I
tried with all of them numbers.
So, I'm officially [ __ ] now. I am not
going out again. You can [ __ ] right off
if I'm going out again. You know, I've
tried more than enough. More than more than enough, you know.
I'm not doing it, bro. [ __ ] off.
Let me try and back up my chats.
cuz it said it backed up weekly. So,
the last backup was 2nd of March. It
can't have been cuz it was doing it
every week. Huh?
Probably. I think I got about 200
numbers, bro. Yep. He's living there.
Yep. He's living in Thailand. Yeah.
Yeah, I deleted all my chats cuz I had
to reinstall [ __ ] WhatsApp.
So, I had to delete some numbers that I
deleted before. So,
so it looks like I'll have to I'll have
to do what he does. Simple.
It's mad how hard it is to get [ __ ] a
woman in this country, bro. It's mad. I
wouldn't be sing if I were these people.
It's like 60 p a pint over there.
But yeah, they're just not even some of
the fat ones, Joe. We're doing the
ignoring and that. So
I I I don't know, bro. I really really
don't know what Yeah, it's about 60 p.
That's how cheap it is over there.
This country there's just too many stuck up [ __ ] So
[ __ ] up, man. Is it? Yeah. I messaged
some numbers. They said, "Oh, I can't I
can't listen. I'm at work." So I typed
it. I said, "Oh, let's meet up." Another
one, "Let's meet up." They're just just not interested.
You know the best thing you can do?
Yeah. Is go gym.
Go gym. [ __ ] escorts like every week and
just leave, mate. That's literally all
you all you all you can actually do, bro.
Like that's literally all that's like
the that's like the actual plan. I mean, you don't
I mean I mean you could stay here, but
you won't get a relationship here.
Whereas in Asia, you'll actually get a
relationship. So, which I think most
people just want more than sex, but you
can't even get a relationship here. So,
and the thing is, you know, these these
the these these people that approach
these women, right? I I watch a I watch
a lot of this stuff on Instagram and it
never changes for them. It's never like,
oh, they they stop hearing about the
I've got a boyfriend and they get the
same [ __ ] and then it's like, whoa, hold on.
it I if one of them cuz obviously
they're in the same position of you as
you they're doing the same thing as you.
If they got it to change sometimes then
maybe you'd think oh okay well maybe you
could get that lucky. Now bear in mind
I'm not I'm not comparing before you
start saying I'm contradicting myself
because these people in the same
position as you. They're doing the same
thing as you. So, I'm not saying I'm
saying that if it if one of them got
lucky, maybe it would give you some kind of hope,
you know, maybe it might give you a tiny
bit of hope, but nah, they it doesn't
even change for them easy. It just annoys me.
Yeah. Uh, I sent it to I sent one to
Ant-Man earlier. He said, "Bro, I've
already told you it's the same [ __ ]
this different characters. It's like
watching and he named some actors. He
said, "Oh, it's like watching Superman,
but it's just a different actor. It's
the same. It's the same film." He said
it again earlier. He said it's it's like
watching um Oh, what was it, man? He
said some film, but instead of this
actor, it's that actor. It's just different characters. Madness, bro.
That is a madness, bro.
just different characters.
Yeah. Well, I didn't think I was going
to end up like Ant-Man, did I? I always
thought that he was giving off weird
vibes. Yeah. And I said this to him as
well. I said to him, "Do you know what
it is? I always thought that there was
something about you." Yeah. That was
putting people off. Maybe you looked a
bit old or maybe people people thought
you was ugly. I don't think you're ugly,
but maybe there was something that you was doing
which was weird. You know, I just
thought, "Oh, yeah, it's him." But then
it started happening to me and then it
started happening to other people. So,
I'm thinking, what?
Yeah, exactly. That's that's basically
what we were saying. It's like I can't
remember the exact quote, but he was
like, "Oh, it's like watching this with
but instead um
Oh, I can't remember the actors." He was
mentioning actors, but yeah,
it doesn't Yeah, exactly. But it's still
the point they're not pulling. But it
doesn't matter whether they're being
serious or they're doing it for fun. It
shows the whole how bad it is.
So, I made a new channel anyways.
So, what what do you think I should do
about it, Joe? Go on. Let's hear your opinion.
What what what what do you think I
should do about it if you're not
trolling? Go on.
It's bad, bro. It's [ __ ] bad.
Oh, I don't know. Don't um I've done a
bet for Saturday by the way if you want
to copy it.
Um done a few bets here as well.
Yeah, it's Fleetwood because they [ __ ]
me last time and Cole Chester and Barrow
double both teams to score.
Uh both teams to score, no draw.
And uh 20 pound returns.
Uh sorry, I put 50 on it. Yeah. And this
is what I'm saying, bro. Like they he
can try and call me what he wants, bro.
Everything that these people call you is
themselves. Yeah. He calls me a virgin,
but I've been seen having sex. I've
proved I've had sex multiple times. It
doesn't Bro, listen. What do you not
understand this by now? What they do on
here? They call you what they are themselves.
I was going to do Swindon.
It's because he's a virgin himself.
That's why he thinks about it. He's a
virgin himself, mate. Just like these
people call me Skint and I ain't been
skinned for three and a half years, but
they still call me Skint.
I don't give a [ __ ] what he's at, bro.
I'm not entertaining a keyboard warrior,
a scared, obsessed keyboard warrior.
Good for him. Let him keep wasting his
life away. Listen, let him keep wasting
his life away for free and not get paid for it.
You know, more fool him. He's just
embarrassing himself. Let him keep
embarrassing himself. He's not being
paid for it, is he? So, um
yeah. So, I was before I was really
interrupted, I was going to do Swindon,
but I weren't feeling Shrewsbury. I
don't like betting on Shrewsbury. So,
yeah, I just done a 50 pound double both
teams to score. So, it has a good return
on it. So, I couldn't do 80 on [ __ ]
two teams, both scor. So, just put 50
quid on it.
I need to win some [ __ ] big money,
bro. For real. Yeah.
Yeah. If I had done a both teams to
score, not last week, the week before
that, and I had 80 on that, it would
have been a lot more. That was a both
teams to score, no draw.
I'm just going to do both teams to score
no draw now.
So, I don't think I'm up now. I think
I'm even. No, I am still up. I must be
What do you mean reset? Reset what?
Wait, hold on before you go. What do you
mean by reset? Do you think one day
you're just going to go out again and
it's going to change?
Well, you're you're just going to go out
one day and all of the things that's
been happening to you for years suddenly stops.
What you need to do. No, this is this is
what you need to do.
I think this
this is what you you you
really Nicolo, this is let me let me let
me say this to you. Yeah.
I lost fucking£100 on the machine today.
You really want to know what what what
you have to do here in this country.
You really want to know what you do.
This plan works perfect. You know,
you need to book flights, right,
about four months in advance. How much
are they? £700. So, £700. Yeah. And then
you need to go out every week drinking
just once a week. Once a week. And you
see if you meet anyone before them three
or four months. And obviously, if you
don't meet anyone before them three or
four months, you leave. And you was
right all along. And obviously if you do
meet someone then you just don't go.
So if you you you need to confirm that
it was a right idea you was making and
what better way than to go out once a week
which is um
obviously what is obviously the plan.
So that's I mean I'm not going out once
a week but you know you know what I'm
saying. But saying that with me I would
just work for a month and [ __ ] off. I'm
only going to go out every week cuz what
am I going out every week for? But you
know there's you got two ways, you know? Yeah.
Who the [ __ ] does this LT think he's
talking to, bro? I showed him I showed
him a question. I showed him a [ __ ]
You want to click on it and you'll know,
bro. I sent you something. So, click on
it in it. The [ __ ]
But listen. Um, yeah, you can't. No, not
No, obviously you'd have to do it drunk.
No, you'd have to do it drunk.
And that that's not because I'm scared
to do it sober. I'm just
I'm just um I just don't like the way it affects me.
It doesn't affect you as much when you're
when you're drinking doing it. But I
used to I've got so many sober ones,
bro. I've got about 300 recorded.
Some of them were bangers, bro. I was
better at it when I was younger, but
it's still that I have a boyfriend.
You will never stop hearing it.
Do you remember Michael Jackson in my
head saying, "Oh, the next time will be different."
Nah, I'm done with it, bro.
I need to really think about what I'm
doing now because I'm not getting any
younger. And I've tried more than anyone
in the world as well. So, if I didn't
try more than anyone in the world and
whatever, then it'd be a different story. But
just what what are the odds? Just just
calculate the odds that the next time
you go out, all of this stops all of
this stuff's going to stop.
I was thinking of USA today at the
cinema. Um, Nicola,
don't know why.
Look, there's no point me doing them cuz
if something would have worked, it would
have worked by now.
You know, you know, just today, right,
with the gambling, I was going in this
cycle for so long. That's why I stopped
doing it. Do you understand why I
stopped doing it? Cuz I broke the cycle
with a sledgehammer. If you don't break
a cycle, you're [ __ ]
You know, if you don't break a cycle, you're screwed.
So you need you need to break it one way
or the other. You need to either Yeah, that's it.
You can even book something for 6
months. As long as you know you're out
of here, you're out of here. You know,
you're counting down the days. So, I
mean, you could still try every week if
you want. And if by the one million
chance you did meet someone, then you
just don't go on the plane. You know,
it's only 700 [ __ ] pound. You know
what I mean?
You get what I mean, don't it?
But there's a pub that I want to go to.
I was thinking of going this week, but I
just don't want to be wasting money here anymore, bro.
I just I just I don't I don't I don't
see the point in doing it, you know?
I [ __ ] text about five numbers today
seeing if they wanted to meet this week.
All full of [ __ ] excuses. Why is it
so hard in this country,
you know? Why is it so bloody hard in
this country? But they call it a hookup
culture. They say it's a hookup culture. Nicola.
[ __ ] hookup culture. You can't even
[ __ ] get laid.
Golden goose. Yeah. I don't go I don't
go drinking in Stratford, bro.
I don't know why it's so hard to find
someone in this country. I would love to know, bro.
It's madness, isn't it?
I think going out once a week, leaving
in 6 months is the best thing you can do, you know,
cuz you know that you're not putting up with anymore.
Yeah. How how are you supposed to get
friends with benefits? That's what I'd
love to know.
Think about it. If I didn't have this
house, right, for three and a half
years, I'd probably be a virgin.
Well, like I mean, obviously I [ __ ]
escorts and [ __ ] but think about it. I
could actually have been a virgin.
Just just just think about how mad that
is. all of the advice that you get on
Reddit. Oh, you'll meet someone and uh I
probably would be a virgin cuz I
wouldn't be able to afford to gone out
and keep going out and you know what I'm
saying. I'd be [ __ ] bro. I would
actually be [ __ ]
You know, even if I only had it for like
a year, I would be That is [ __ ]
scary, isn't it?
To think about that. That's actually
scary, isn't it,
bro? It's not mental. They're just self-reflectors.
He's not the only one, bro. We got
someone in a [ __ ] bed sit with no bed
calling me [ __ ] skint every day.
Imagine that. Somebody in in a in a
[ __ ] bedsit with no bed is trying to
tell people who they're living with and
how much money they've got. Yeah. Yeah.
But yeah, I won't be going out this
week. I can't afford it if I'm trying to
save. And I would do it anyways. I mean,
by can't afford it, I mean I won't be
able to do and save what I need to
actually be doing. So
yeah, I'll watch it in a bit, bro, when
I've ended the live stream.
I thought I would have actually got a
meet up this week, but no.
No, I would never change it, bro. It's a
horrible, horrible life, isn't it?
[ __ ] depressing, bro. It
don't know how you react when you lose.
It feels like you're being [ __ ] It
feels like you're being trolled. That's
what it feels like. It actually feels
like you're being trolled.
You get [ __ ] over by gambling. You get
[ __ ] over by women. And the only
reason you you you get the urge to
gamble is because of the women. Because
you don't get buzz from the women. You
don't get high from the women.
You know that say that's what saved me
all these years is when I used to win
money at the casino. If you think about
it, that's what used to save me
all of them years.
all of them years. That's what was
actually saving me. Now I actually
realize it now.
It's cuz you actually used to win money.
So you don't give a [ __ ] what's happened
when you've gone out. You've won money,
bro. Who gives a [ __ ] That's if you
think about like it's actually that mad.
It's why so many people killed
themselves and they're virgins. You see,
I was thinking of the good times as well
when I was in a cinema earlier.
I used to just go win money
and then just go approaching and I
wouldn't care what would have happened
because I want money. So, I knew I was
getting laid at the end of the day. I
knew at the end of that night I was getting laid.
It would be like if I if I'm going out,
I'm getting laid because I would just
pay for it. So, I wouldn't go out if I
if I'm if I'm not going to get laid
to get it. So, yeah.
And anyone sometimes I feel like I'm one
of these incel v not incel virgins but
these simps you know the typical s but
you've actually been with [ __ ] that
and that's the maddest thing about it.
>> The only way you can make money nowadays
is if you save up enough money to start
your own business
or you invest or you you win the lottery.
But it's getting harder as well. Like
there probably will be a time where I do
end up skin.
But I've kind of gone I've done the
going out. I've done the banging. I've
done the [ __ ] I've done, you know, for
three and a half years. But it's
possible. Anyone can end up skinn
[ __ ] ass nonslegs. He's skinn every
day of his life. Nicolo, he'll tell you
all about being skinn. He is skinn. Skim
bastard in the bedset.
Yeah, I mean it's it's it's a gamble,
isn't it? It's you you would need to
find the right business, of course, cuz
obviously even when you're starting your
own business, you're it's a form of
gambling, isn't it? Because
you can't really do any you can't even
win money anymore like you used to be able to.
At least you used to be able to get
dates with a woman and used to be able
to. You can't even do that anymore.
But unless you've got anything booked,
you're booked. You're [ __ ]
Think about it. Whether you try, whether
you don't try, it don't matter. If
you've got that flight booked, you know
you're out of here. Simple.
You know that you are out of it, lad.
You know what I'm saying? So that's
That's step one.
I love to go back to America. The thing
is with America is the dating game is dead there.
The dating game there is just dead. Same
as it is here.
I don't know how the [ __ ] I got USA and
[ __ ] these other people. I'd love to
know, bro. But it wasn't it wasn't as
bad as it was back then.
You know what? I think even if I wanted
kids, I would never have kids. I think
it's cruel like to have a child now.
They'll [ __ ] be my [ __ ] age and
they'll be completely [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah, I do.
Even them sex opportunities. I don't
know how I done it. Well, I done it cuz
it wasn't impossible back then.
It's mad. It's like
every time you should you go out, you
should get a date.
You should get a date.
I've got Oh, bro. Come on, man. Why do
you want evidence? You're still going to
say that I've not gone.
Just like you call me skin and I've
shown more money than anyone in this
community. Just like you call me a
manta. Yeah, I'm better looking than
everyone on this community.
Bro, whatever. Why would you just like
everyone see me have sex and you still
call me a virgin? Is there a point me
wasting my time and your time anymore?
Cuz you're not going to believe anything you shown. So,
but yeah, I wouldn't Superman was quite
good to be fair, but I pref I prefer
Spider-Man. I've always preferred
Spider-Man, but it is still a good film.
It's the first time I've not watched a
horror in the cinema for like [ __ ] 12
years. I think the last well except on
the Peppa Pig big thing, but on a
serious level, I think the last thing I
watched was The Inbetween Us.
Yeah, I've always preferred Spider-Man.
Me, I didn't like Batman and Superman
was meh. But I was so bored today. I
went to see Superman. I was that bored. So
And I thought, let me try and win some
money to go out at the weekend.
But I just lost 15. I spent 160 today. Well,
but hopefully this football bear comes
in tomorrow. It's only two. Both score,
no draw. Nice £438.
It's [ __ ] hard, bro. Is it?
Yeah. Yeah, I put £50 on Frankie.
Why don't I stop gambling, bro? I hardly
ever gamble. This is the first time in
like 4 months I've played them machines.
I don't, bro. I don't gamble.
And the reason I've done the football
bets is because
uh I try I need to try and win some
extra money before I can actually until
I get a job of some kind.
But I don't I'm never going to go skimp
from gambling, mate. Don't you worry
about me. That's the last time I played
that bar roulette for about 5 months.
And then you get the [ __ ] from women as well,
you know? Even if even if that USA Izzy
[ __ ] was still speaking to me,
Nicoloba, she abandoned me.
Like things should have [ __ ] worked out there.
I would have went over. I would have
lived there. I would have went, bro, and
I would have went and lived there and
never come back.
You know, it's only 7 hours on a plane.
You know, I got promised the world.
But the [ __ ] [ __ ] abandoned me.
That's how it should have been.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] [ __ ] abandoned me, you know.
Yeah, but bro, you understand the the
thing is, man, is that, you know, I've
been around the country approaching and
all you ever get is, "Oh, I've got a
boyfriend. I've got a boyfriend." It's
just it's with me. It's it's [ __ ] up.
My my situation is different than most
people's. I've tried more than anyone in
the world. And it's not even just about
that. It's you can't even get laid.
You literally can't even get laid. It's
not even like it's one or the other. You
can't even get [ __ ] laid, bro. It's So
yeah, watching them approaching videos is [ __ ]
Yeah, she's she's full to blame, bro.
She's full to blame.
I'm not going to go to [ __ ] Miami,
Rob. What for somebody to call the police?
You know what I'm saying? If if I if I
knew where they lived, then I'd probably
just go on their door and ask them what
the [ __ ] their problem is.
But, bro, you know what that you know
it's the boys in blue.
As soon as you step foot on that soil,
You know it's the boys in blue, mate.
You know it's the boys in blue. So
yeah, with this situation, you need need
something booked because you don't have
anything booked, then
it's pointless. You're always going to
go around in the same cycle cuz even if
you go out every week and you go around
in the same cycle, you know you're
leaving. So once you're gone, there is
no cycle that's going to keep happening, you know,
and then there's This one of these women
had braces, bro. And they were they were
average. And I was trying to meet them
and you can't even meet them, bro.
You can't even meet them. I was trying
to meet her and
you can't even [ __ ] meet them.
they're all [ __ ] mate. There was one
saying, "Oh, I'm going Spain. Just I'm
at the airport." I said, "Oh, let's meet
next week then."
It's so hard trying to date in this country, bro.
I was thinking about coming a becoming a
wrestler. Nicola, going to the gym and
training to be a wrestler. I mean,
that's surely got to pay some good
money. Or a boxer, perhaps.
Maybe I could become a wrestler or something.
She weren't even that bad to be honest.
She was just ginger and had freckles.
She weren't even that that that that bad.
But yeah, they used to think I was mad, you know.
They used to think I was [ __ ] cuz uh
yeah, I was thinking about maybe
becoming a wrestler or something.
You know, I'm not I'm not too old, am I?
They're um But your them dates. I used
to just uh
I I used to just uh
I used to just um tell them about the
the USA is it used to think I was weird.
And then it's like when you finally have
moved on, you now you can't find no one.
Now you can't find no one. Now when you
have actually moved on, now you can't
find no one. So
I supposed to go to Nandos with Sig the
next day. Nicolola.
Yeah. Yeah. WWE or maybe like a boxer.
Maybe I'm thinking of doing that.
But the thing with that is you're not
going to be liked. There's only very few
wrestlers that are liked. So,
you're just going to be imagine being in
the Royal Rumble here and you have to
keep [ __ ] being thrown out cuz you
are never going to win. It would be very
hard to be
to be liked. You know, there's only a
few of them that are like, but
it be a fun job in it.
But yeah, she did she did snipe me.
Do you want my opinion to be
Why is it so hard? One second.
Did you watch the new Superman Greavves? Um,
that Italian one that didn't let me kiss her.
Doesn't matter what how much money I've got, bro.
Why does it matter? All you need to know
is I'm not skin.
No, cuz I didn't go on a date with that
one. That's the one that I met with
That's the one that I met when I was
with um Monty. No, that was the one in
Birmingham. I approached her. She gave
me her number and we was chatting every
day. She weren't an ignorer and then she
come out with excuses and then she said,
"Oh, I don't feel a spark." I was like,
"What? You've literally gave me your number.
You gave me your number and then
you're messaging back and you don't even
want to meet.
Yeah. No, but yeah, that was just an
excuse though. What? The pal the the Palestinian.
Yeah. It was just It's just bull. Yeah.
That's the [ __ ] you deal with in this country.
That's the That's the [ __ ] that you
deal with in this country,
you know? It's been happening [ __ ]
years, bro. There's always different [ __ ]
Oh yeah, the what? The white one. Yeah.
Yeah. Check this. She approached me.
Yeah. She approached me and she was
like, "Oh, um,
she approached me." Said, "Oh, yeah.
You're good-looking." Gave me her
number. Then we when we scheduled to
meet on a Thursday, I limped a [ __ ]
stupid [ __ ] date. And then she said
she doesn't feel the vibe after like 20
minutes. I was like, "What the [ __ ] You
basically you approached me and you gave
me your number."
Like, it's madness, bro. All of this
[ __ ] Surprised I I haven't ended up doing something
all them years.
I didn't grope her tip. I touched her
tit with consent. But yeah, but yeah.
So yeah, I've been dealing with so much
[ __ ] in this country.
Do you remember the O'Neal was water
street? Um, Nicola
[ __ ] up, eh?
It will never change.
Reckon this football bat shall win tomorrow.
Yeah, that O'Neal was sick, bro.
That's where I got that [ __ ] from
that American Nicola.
It's bad here, is it? Really bad.
Why are you out on that one, bro? I put
50 quid on it.
Yeah, I put 50 on that.
I do quite high football bets, don't I, Nicola?
I probably won't be out drinking again this month.
Nah, wait this. I've done my deed.
But yeah, I think that's probably all
you could do, mate, is like find a side
hustle, maybe like Uber and something,
deliver, and just literally just go out
once a week, bang an escort at the end
of the night, do it every week for like
four months, just leave.
I can't afford to lose that kind of money, matey.
That's a lot of money to lose, bro.
On on a on a football on a [ __ ]
football team, you know what I mean?
But yeah, you could do something like
that. Yeah. Probably be like 1,800.
They pay you in cash as well, wouldn't they? Yeah.
I mean, that's probably the only thing
you could maybe do to get money, but
obviously if you lose, you're [ __ ]
So, that's the thing.
Like, generally like, yeah,
but you you would be [ __ ] basically.
Oh, imagine having that four grand on
Imagine having that five grand on a 1 to
75. Oh, mate. [ __ ] me. How much is that?
It's like 300,000 in it. 300k.
Well, how much was that return? 500 on a both £500.
I'm sure it's like 1,800, isn't it? 1,700. Yeah.
[ __ ] hell, bro. Good night.
Cost a lot, bro. It [ __ ] hell.
>> I don't think I could put £500 on a football mate.
But imagine you put the [ __ ] 1800 on it.
Oh, mate, you'll be loaded.
I won two in a row as well. [ __ ] Yeah, man.
Why don't you want to do the both score
no draw? Come on, let's give it a whirl.
Steven Howard, the first week of
football we got it in. Come on, give it a whirl.
I would give a little try.
Give a little while. I would. [ __ ] it.
I'll put 50 quid on it, mate. I was
going to put 80 on it.
Is that right? Grezy. Give it a little while.
Give it a little try.
So, what should I do? Saturday. Greasy. Go out.
No, I'm going to stay in a B Franklin.
[ __ ] hell, man.
So, Grezy, give your honest opinion. Do
you think Virgin Boy is obsessed with me?
Why is Virgin boy so obsessed with me? [ __ ] hell.
Virgin boy is obsessed with me, Greavvesy.
Why is virgin boy obsessed with me, lad?
Leave me alone.
Leave me alone, you [ __ ] virgin [ __ ]
You know what I mean? Yeah, man.
What do you say?
No, but it returns a bigger amount.
Isn't that right, Grezy? Imagine having
£500 on a on a both teams to score
treble. Both team treble both teams to
score no draw.
You would [ __ ] rake it in it.
You would. We almost had I almost had a
[ __ ] treble last [ __ ] week, man.
I got some popcorn here from the pictures. Grim.
Oh, I love popcorn. I love sweets and I
Been doing them for years.
Four years, baby.
I mean, your popcorn and sweets, you [ __ ]
been doing it for years. Same result.
No, I can't get anything. But I've got a boyfriend.
Every time I approach, all I get is I've
got a boyfriend.
Well, they're not interested. Yeah,
I just gave up in the end. Yeah.
Yeah, it's sad.
I mean, popcorn and sweets. New Hog.
Mick Jonathan Robinson was a dirty bastard.
He was a dirty bastard.
Mick Jonathan Robinson. Dirty dirty nons. Yeah.
Yeah. They've all got boyfriends, gone.
Um, had a few dates, had a few one night
stands, but now I can't even get a
conversation out of them,
you know. Yeah, I got some pick a mix
and some popcorn. Mc Jonathan Robinson
was a dirty [ __ ]
Dirty bastard. He was Yeah. dirty [ __ ]
I know. They're just not interested in this country.
I mean, some of them even say I'm not interested.
Some of them even say, "I'm not interested."
But yet you get people on Reddit that
say, "Oh, you'll meet someone. You'll find someone."
Everyone you meet ain't interested.
They've got They're already in a
relationship with their phone.
Imagine everyone on Reddit told the
truth. Could you Could you imagine
everyone on Reddit told the truth? The
truth would be something like, well,
unfortunately because of the day and age
we live in, we live in a very
westernized country and women are stuck
up due to simps. So, I would advise you
to go try yourself, try your luck some
in some other country. But if you do
want to try, that's at your own risk. You know, you know, it's crazy.
But no one on Reddit ever says that.
They never tell the truth. Pretty bad.
on five friends
getting a interested jet pilot.
That's funny, man.
So, what would you do if you wanted to
get laid in this country, Nicolo? Say
you was a virgin. Yeah. How how would
you get laid, do you think? Yeah.
If they really had boyfriends, put it
this way, right? If they really had a
boyfriend, they' just walk off.
They would just walk off, bro. Think
about it, bro.
They would just walk off. Like, I have
so many approaches, bro, that I put on
my new channel where these people can't find me.
You know what I'm saying? Like,
so if they really have boyfriends,
they'll just walk away.
Like, don't sit there and start talking to you.
They don't have boyfriends. I'm sick of
[ __ ] people saying, "Oh, they do."
They got [ __ ] boyfriends.
You can't even. So, how are you going to
get laid then?
How would you get laid
if you wanted to?
Yeah. No, Australians always chat, but
then they just say they've got a boyfriend. Um,
the Australians always do it, but then
they just say they've got a boyfriend
and then the Ukrainians, they give their
number and then they just don't reply or
they just [ __ ] you around. It depends.
It depends where they're from. You know,
every nationality is the same. Once you
meet a French woman, all the French
women are the same. Once you meet an
American, they're all the same. Every
woman you meet,
depends where they're from, they're all the same.
The French ones will just troll you
in in in such a funny way.
Oh, here we go.
Why do they say that? Why do they say
they've got a boyfriend bomb?
Hope you ready for this, Nicolo? Here we go.
Is it because I'm a manta? It's so
predictable, isn't it?
This is what happens when you've been on
it for years, lad.
Yeah. Let me guess. Is it because I'm a
to do that? Yeah. Pick up a hobby.
You got too much time on your hands. Yeah.
Still no replies. No.
Yeah, it's bad enough.
Yeah, it's really bad.
Yep. They say to me, right, like
meet people through friends. Meet people
through friends. And I explain to them
like, oh, like people out for
themselves. And like I've never met
anyone through friends. Yeah,
bro. You're talking about yourself. Yep.
Congratulations. You're talking about yourself.
You are uneducated, more educated than
you'll ever be. No job, got more money
than you. Um, I've got family unlike
you. My teeth are fine. Yeah, bro.
You're just talking about yourself. We
don't have time for self projectors.
We don't have We don't have time for self projectors.
Bad teeth. I got [ __ ] perfect teeth.
What the [ __ ] Must be talking about
your [ __ ] self as usual. Never got
that one before. Bad teeth.
Yeah, you're talking about yourself. And
it all it proves that you talk you're
talking about yourself because you sit
on here doing what you do every day. You
hate the world because you're fat and
ugly and skinn. That's why you people do
what you do on here every day cuz you
ain't got a life. Like, think about it,
bro. I was off YouTube days. You can't
even take two days off YouTube. It's
literally your life, bro. You know what I mean?
Her bad teeth. I've got better teeth
than you would ever have. That's why you
resort to sing. That's why you resort to
defending women because you're a loser.
Just like most of you simps, right?
You know, you you you s because you
can't get women. So, when somebody shows
you evidence, oh, you go on a on a high
defense. Why do these people defend
women? Like when do they realize,
Nicolo, that they're never it's never
going to get them losing their virginity?
They're never ever ever going to get
laid. Why are they defending women when
I've had more than them?
It's not even like the [ __ ] you're
saying is offensive,
you know? It's not even like the [ __ ]
you're saying is offensive. The the
things you're saying is true and you've
had more women than them. It's proven,
as immature as that sounds. So why are
they sat there defending them every
time? It's never going to get you laid.
I would be on a killing spree right now
if I was if I was in these people's
[ __ ] shoes. Yeah. It's not just
Reddit though. It's everywhere, bro.
Instagram, YouTube. Even on this
community, they're simps
cuz I don't say anything that's really
bad. I just say they're all stuck up and
and then they go straight to their defense, which is
it is a form of simp.
You're scared to do it. You just do it.
So like, bro, all these people, they're
talking about themselves.
No family, bad teeth. Bro, I have I see
my family every day almost. Everything
is about their own lives cuz they won't
be doing this all day every day on here,
bro. They'd be living their life. They'd
be living their best life. Know what I'm
saying? But they're on here in year out.
Everything they say applies to themselves.
Everything Everything that these people
say it applies to their own lives.
What you call me is yourself.
So yeah. Uh anyways, back to before we
was rudely interrupted, right? Uh by the
simp. Uh yeah, they tell you to meet
people through friends, right? And then
he'll be like, "Oh, like I've never met
anyone through friends. People out for
themselves." Then it goes into a whole
another conversation. Oh, you need new
friends. and no n and then it just goes
into a completely different conversation
because people are out for themselves.
Bad friends, good friends, they
literally are. No one's going to
introduce you to someone, especially if
they're single. So, and then because cuz
it's happened for me, then they start
comparing me to other people. So then
it's just it's just pointless me even
saying it anymore because it kind it
then becomes a comparing you to other people. So
it's like think about it this way. If
you took their advice, you you would be a virgin.
Like think think about it right here.
Yeah. If you took their if you took
think of me for example, right? If I
took these people's advice on here, I
would be a virgin.
Let that sink in for like two minutes.
Cuz what what advice they give you? They
they tell you to go on dating apps and
they say that you meet people through friends.
And I've proved that that is not the
case for everyone. But then they say,
"Oh, well, other people have done it.
Other people the clues in the title,
other is not you.
You you understand what I'm saying?
You you understand what I'm saying? It's
not um it's not comparable.
And I think that's a lot of the reason I
don't really come on the internet
anymore, bro, is because of the sing
them just defending women like all the
time. It just it gets me down. I just
simp. So, I just don't bother with it.
They seem to think that once you have a
job, you live. Bro, I I've lived by
myself. I've had a job. I've gone to the
gym every day and it made no difference.
But the problem is is you can't say that
stuff on the internet because if you say
that stuff on the internet, you just get attacked.
You just get attacked.
You understand? So like
say anything, man.
So yeah, these simps just
just defend women. I don't know why they
do it. Autism, but
I don't know why they defend women.
Uh if I was them, I like I said, I would
have gone on a killing spree here.
you know, and they defend them badness.
Social social media is just toxic, isn't it?
I've got the best teeth than anyone in this community.
I never said everyone in a relationship
is a s. I'm saying the people that are
simps is when I say, "Oh, women are
stuck up and they [ __ ] about having
boyfriends and then people come and
attack you." Yes, it is simp because a
lot of these people have had less women
than you. I've had less sex than you and
they're still defending women. It's like
it's some sort of autism or something.
I've had a virgin, right, [ __ ] say to
me, he actually is a virgin. He will
tell you he's a virgin. Um I think he's
32 and he's never kissed anyone,
nothing. And I found him on the Oreo man
channel and he and he told me with the
USA Izzy, it's enough. I said, I'll tell
you when it's a [ __ ] enough,
sunshine. I'll tell you when it's a [ __ ]
enough. You know, when I was writing
them [ __ ] comments and that um so I
mean there's there's that is simp.
The last thing I would be doing is defending women
like if I were them. Well, each their own, bro. Um,
his name was
No. What was his name? [ __ ]
I think it might No, no, no.
It was something like that. Yeah, maybe. Um,
no. It wasn't&m. That's the black guy.
No, no, no, no, no. He was a good [ __ ]
He was. Um, no. It was someone else. So,
I was like, I'll tell you when it's
enough. I will [ __ ] tell you when
it's a [ __ ] enough.
Just like a couple of months ago.
Remember what I said to the [ __ ] I'll
go there next month.
I'll go there [ __ ] next month and
I'll [ __ ] smack you up in front of your boyfriend.
I said that [ __ ] a couple of months ago,
bro. Yeah. And I had to bring the
boyfriend involved obviously cuz my
man's going to try and act big. I just
don't like the whole
people trying to look good for women. It
just drives me mad. I hate it.
Like I just don't like people look
trying to look good for women. I just
don't like it, bro.
Women are [ __ ] [ __ ] They're [ __ ] evil.
These people should [ __ ] like I said,
set up a campaign or something, you
know, against women, but instead they
sit there and defend them.
Cuz think of it, Nicolo. Yeah. You know
when I say all of this [ __ ] Yep.
Let me let me let me How do I say this
to you, bro? Like, let me let me give an
example. Yeah. Like, you know my history
with people that I've been with and
[ __ ] Yeah. And then you see Virgin Boy,
right, in the bedset. Now, let's just
use that as an example. You've seen that
I've had [ __ ] [ __ ] more [ __ ]
than him. [ __ ] that he was so jealous
of me being with that he tried to get
with them himself and he's the one sat
there defending women. Like say that I
do a video like saying, "Oh, they're all
dickheads." And he will literally write
a paragraph defending them.
And it's like I just said right now if I
was sat there with a disabled [ __ ]
woman in a bedsit,
I would the last thing I'd be doing is defending them.
So, I don't know why they
I don't know why they why they do it,
lads, but they do it.
And sometimes we actually forget who the
virgin actually is. They actually
sometimes make you forget that
um they've been with less people than you.
They actually sometimes make you
actually forget that. Does that make sense?
Strange, isn't it?
I can understand if they were defending
like Chinese women or like Asian women
or something like that, but they're
they're just [ __ ] here. They all
they're just [ __ ] here, you know?
They're just [ __ ] Yeah.
And I think I said because I wanted to or something.
Yeah. Yeah. I remember that. But it's
happened a few times.
Yeah. He tried that out to me big. I
said, "Listen, bro." Yeah. Stop your
[ __ ] in it. Stop trying to look good. He
He was a proper proper s cuz he didn't
need to do that.
I hate people [ __ ] trying to look
good for women. I would, bro. You know
what? I would love to just slap though.
Here's the thing. Yeah. I would just
love to slap that USA up in front of her boyfriend
like just just one time to prove her
point. [ __ ] hate people that that
defend women. I hate it, bro. Makes my blood boil. You know,
I can understand people defending
children because children are innocent,
but [ __ ] they I don't know why they
defend women. I hate it. me.
I hate women, bro. Like, you don't
understand. And then when you have
people [ __ ] defending them, it drives
me [ __ ] mad.
It's mad. It does mind nothing, bro. It
doesn't mind nothing.
You remember that American guy when he
was like, "Oh, don't talk to her." And I
told him, "I [ __ ] talk to her. I want
[ __ ] trying to act [ __ ] big to me
or you, you [ __ ]
But the guy weren't even [ __ ] with her.
You remember they had to stop let the
the army people in the O'Neals,
you know what I mean? Yeah. I've been I
know. I don't even know how I'm still
here, but I don't even know how I'm
still in this country to be honest.
So much [ __ ] So much [ __ ]
But people still think one day it's just
going to change.
How's it going to change? How
you I've been through a lot of [ __ ]
That's what makes me so unique. You know
this mad is it? Yeah. But people still
think one day it's just going to change.
So yeah, you don't really know what to do.
Do you think I'll be able to get laid
again in this country, Grezy? Yeah, them
numbers have gone to [ __ ] Anyways, Oh yeah.
Yeah. Do do you remember the flesh guy?
I think the only thing you could
actually do here Yeah.
go out every week and get an escort
every week till you leave.
I can't possibly think of anything else.
Obviously, you need a job first and make
money for the escort that, but I mean
I mean what do you spend every night?
You go out like 200 maybe.
And this for like a good 6 months, four
to 6 months. What do you think?
I think so. Yeah. Make sure
here's the thing though, bro. But when
you go to Thailand, there's people that
actually want to be in a relationship
with you. But what Ant-Man was basically
saying is that it's only people in their 30s
is is in their 30s.
Well, they did that guy really actually
start trying to blame my [ __ ] teeth
for why women are crunched in this
country? What a [ __ ] s.
They nitpick, don't they, Nicolo?
They nitpick. They actually nitpick and
just make stuff up.
Firstly, it's [ __ ]
Bro, look at my Show you my receding
hairline, bro. Look at your own baldy
head because the only one that's already
bled is yourself. Go in the mirror and
give yourself a laugh. You're already
bowled. Ain't no one balding. Ain't no
one balding on this chat, bro. But you.
You're already bowled. You've already
receded. your little self projector.
You're already bored. The only reason
you tell me that I'm receding is because
you know that you're the baldy bastard
and you hate it because I've got more
head and you t out keyboard warrior. Yeah.
So yeah, that's pretty much it, bro. But
you can only get people in their 30s. So
I mean, would that be any good to you?
I noticed these these people in this
community hate anyone that's better
looking than them and anyone that's got
a better life than them. I've noticed
that, bro. People in this community,
they hate anyone that's not hopeless like them.
It's [ __ ] madness, isn't it?
It's so mad.
Like they they hate I've actually like
thought of this, bro. Like they hate
anyone that's not
that's not hopeless like them.
They're [ __ ] bro. All of these people
in this community yet you know what they are greasy.
They're [ __ ] skin [ __ ] fat ugly
people who ain't got a life.
I swear down, bro. They actually are like
just fat, ugly,
old people that ain't got no life. Yeah,
what they are, bro. 100%. They're [ __ ] losers.
Sat on YouTube every day making fake
accounts to get blocked. I'm telling you, bro,
they hate on anyone that's better
looking than them, that's got a better
life than them, that's younger than them.
I swear to God, bro, you don't you don't
you don't type anything back, but it's the truth.
They're [ __ ] proper losers, bro, on this community.
They're [ __ ] proper bully losers.
If I'm all of these things, bro, why
don't you come and show your face?
Think of it. Yeah.
Why do you think Redstone all of them
can't show their face?
Okay, look at all of the people that
haven't been able to show their face
before. Hat, gray cat, [ __ ] bomb. And
look what they look like, bro. They're
[ __ ] all ugly.
All ugly fat people that ain't got a life.
That's what they are, bro. They project
their their reality onto you. That's
what they do, bro. Mhm.
Fat, ugly, low lives. And they seem to
go for me more than anyone else.
Yeah, they're definitely jealous of something, bro. Definitely. Definitely. Yeah.
Why do these pe will these people ever
get bored of self projecting?
It's so mad like how they can do it every day.
Sit here and self-reflect every day of their lives.
You don't think it's insane? Like
just coming on YouTube every day putting yourself down.
It it must be not good for their mental
health, is it?
It can't be good for your mental health,
you know, coming online every day
putting yourself down,
calling yourself skin, calling yourself bold. But it's m.
These are very salty, but they're very nice here.
That's why I don't really come on here
anymore. I won't be on here again.
Come to my lad. I just come on here to
do video. Timmy
need video on me.
Y fat ugly people. They ain't got a life.
They're fat ugly people that ain't got a life.
Right, Timmy, leave your videos up cuz
I'm going to watch them. Um, bro,
did he actually say that?
He doesn't need to feel sorry for me, bro.
He needs to feel sorry for himself.
You could not. Okay. Do you want me to
be honest with you? 100%. Like not even
bullshitting, no projecting,
no nothing. Do you want me to be 1
million and 100% honest with you now?
You know, Virgin boy's girlfriend,
the disabled one, Natalie G and Kaye. I say,
"Bro, you couldn't pay me to get with
any of those women. You generally could
not. I feel more sorry for him that he
had to resort to that,
you know. I I would rather be single.
Literally, I would rather be single.
Bro, look at all the [ __ ] I've had in the past.
They've never ever been like any of them.
Any of them. Any of them. Yeah,
someone's got memory loss.
He needs to feel sorry for himself, mate.
He doesn't need to feel sorry for me. I
would I would never
ever ever resort to Kayie, bro.
No Kie, no G.
No [ __ ] Sarah. [ __ ] hell no.
Hell the [ __ ] no. So,
think of it, Greg. Yeah.
Would you get with any of those women?
Would you would you get with any of them?
That 19year-old that I was with was
better than all of them, bro.
That 19year-old was better than all of them.
I wonder what else she's getting on.
Remember that 19year-old
I don't know how people can't hate women.
women. I [ __ ] hate them, mate. I
don't know how people can't.
I don't know how people can't, bro. They're mad.
They're [ __ ] mad. Who's that?
Nothing will ever lose it.
Virgin boy will ever lose it. You reckon that m
will never get laid
by will Never get laid out. Virgin boy.
You never get
what you say. Virgin boy. Virgin. Mhm.
He should get on the football bets, man.
He needs to go on the football bets.
He needs to go on them [ __ ] football
and he'll [ __ ] get laid.
Oh, mate. Yeah. Remember
he tried it with USA and she rejected him.
He was messaging USA. Steven Aaron.
He tried him with USA. Is he? She
rejected his ugly ass. [ __ ] Yeah.
He thought he could make his move,
but she won't have another virgin boy.
He might he thought, "Oh, maybe maybe
because Peter Benny got some. I I'll
finally lose my virginity." [ __ ] off.
You're going to die a virgin.
You know what I mean? Whack off. You
won't have none of it, mate. She won't
Yeah. You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
She tried He tried it on with USA, is
he? She didn't want his ugly ass
No, none of them have.
But they still sit there and defend
women all day like I'm the virgin. Like
I've never had women.
All cuz I've got a different opinion,
Grezy. I get treat I get attacked and
treated like I've never been with a
woman. What do you want me to do, bro?
I'm sorry. You want me to start licking
people's asses? Oh, women are so lovely.
They're not stuck up. They don't pretend
they've got boyfriends. Like, do do you
want me to start licking people's asses?
Am I Am I supposed to start licking people's asses?
I don't I don't know what they actually
want from people.
You know, you're not even saying anything offensive.
I've been seen with the most money on
here, the most women on here, the better
looking on here, and still people talk [ __ ]
Still people talk [ __ ] bro.
Yeah. Still people talk [ __ ] M
[ __ ] lord indeed.
You're going to die.
You're going to [ __ ] die a virgin.
Oh yeah, we had [ __ ] Virgin boy by
messaging her. He thought he was going
to get some of the action.
Isn't it greasy? He thought he was going
to get some boobies, but no. [ __ ] straight rejected.
Same as Britney [ __ ] rejected you.
They want your ugly ass.
You understand me, mate? They want your
ugly ass. Can't blame her.
Can't [ __ ] blame her, though. Yep.
Yeah, I know. There's so many simps. So
So many simps, lad.
this [ __ ] stupid WhatsApp thing as well.
I like Timmy's gambling videos, man. I
actually do like gammy's gambling videos.
Yeah. He thought he was going to get
some of USA. Is he?
He got so jealous when I got without
USA. Is he? He was so jealous. Super jealous.
Don't know why he gets jealous of people
that get get with women. So jealous.
I've never known people so jealous of
people that they don't even know.
Yeah. He he fought right.
He he he
know how it is Steven Howard, right? You
got to understand
this this dude, right? He's met me seven
times. Now, think about it, bro. Ever
since I've I've I've met the [ __ ] he's
been projecting his virginity on me,
them seven them seven, eight times I met that virgin,
he you know, he he's older than me.
Think about it. He's older than me by
two years and a half, right? So, he's
older than me. Think about it, bro. I've
got more life experience than him. I'm
better looking than him. I've had more
women than him. Better looking women
than him. It's like he he he's autism.
Doesn't want to admit that. So, he he
goes all mad like, you know, because
he's he's just a jealous bastard.
He probably never thought that I'd been
better than him. I would have had a
better life than him.
You know what I mean?
At my uh age,
you know what I'm saying, bro? So
yeah, but USA is reject rejected. Absolutely rejected.
rejected his ugly ass.
Why don't that Ronald Pump come on here anymore, Grezy?
He said, "You need to get off of YouTube
and live your life."
That's what he said to me. He said, he
said, "It's jealousy. You're better
looking than them. You got more money
than them, and it kills them, and you
got a better life than them." Should
have took his advice, really, in it.
So then I thought to myself, why not
become a wrestler?
So I've been thinking about becoming a
wrestler. Might take three or four
years, but Yeah.
Yeah. But would people really get
jealous of money?
But yeah, just think about it, bro.
Why did he keep projecting his virginity
onto me, though?
You creepy virgin.
Why won't he meet me now?
He He He didn't mind meeting me when I
was a [ __ ] 19 a [ __ ] 17y old. Why
won't he meet me now?
And I tell him how much of a virgin he
is to his face
that he can only meet kids, can't he?
Can only pick on kids.
But he can't he can't pick on a grown
man though, can he?
Nah. You know, mate Grezy that as soon
as somebody turns into a grown man, it's
the boys in blue, mate.
It's the boys in blue.
You should know this, mate. It's the
boys in blue.
Yeah, it's the boys in blue, mate.
It's mad. I was I was always the boys in blue.
So yeah, go on that football bet. You can't.
I should have done a big football bet
when I had like [ __ ] 7K. I should
have just put like 1k on the football in
it. Steven Howard. Jesus.
No, like £500. Should have put like £500
on the football in it.
You can do that if you had seven grand
in it. Put £500 on the football.
Yeah, you could do
otherwise I'm gone. Yeah. Seio.