Yeah,
[ __ ] madness last night, man. Jesus Christ.
You're all [ __ ] weirdos on this
community, aren't you?
All little weirdo low lives, ain't it?
Yeah, you actually are, man.
Weirdos sat on [ __ ] Reddit. Yeah.
Refreshing the [ __ ] refreshing the [ __ ] homepage.
What [ __ ] losers?
I messaged thinking about that last
night as well. You know that? Yeah. Just
sat on Reddit. Yeah. Just you can just
tell they're in their mommy's basement.
Yeah. Just on that Reddit homepage just
refreshing it. Refreshing it. Refreshing
[ __ ] proper loser community. This is
proper proper loser community. Yeah.
Some madness, isn't it? You'd think
you'd actually you you you'd think you'd
actually know these people,
you know? You you'd think you'd actually
met some of these losers on here,
you know, but you actually haven't.
I think I think it's mad, you know,
the lengths they go through to to to
stalk someone. It's crazy.
It's mad. They're proper proper losers.
Really are in this community, you know.
And that's why they don't that's why
they don't understand it, you know, when
you're when you're talking about the
money thing because they're [ __ ]
disabled. I know it now. Yeah, I know it
now. You know, just listening to Timmy,
that's what like probably most of these
people on here are like just disabled.
Disabled fat, ugly skinned people ain't
got a life, you know? That's what they
are on here. Therefore,
I'm hearing about [ __ ] this person's
done this video, this person's done that
video. I'm not even on their I'm not
even on their channel.
Yeah, it's mad.
It must be hectic being new people, you
know, having to come on here every day,
being obsessed with people that you
don't know, that you're jealous of,
having to go on an app and keep
refreshing the [ __ ] homepage. It must
be really, really hectic being you. And
the best part about it is you don't get
paid for it.
Oh, [ __ ] Franklin died. The best part
about it is you don't even get paid for
it. You do it for free.
What a madness proof. You do it for free.
You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
[ __ ] Did you Did you hear yesterday
Timmy trying to call me a virgin? Ah,
that's why I say to anyone, it's no
point showing these little self-p
projected disabled people anything cuz
all they're doing is calling themselves,
you know. All they're doing is talking
about their own lives, you know? So,
there's like no point even showing these
people [ __ ] anything,
you know? Cuz Yeah. Why do you think I
didn't show them videos that I had
yesterday? Cuz it's pointless. Because
whatever you show, they're just going to
say they're still going to just keep
calling you what they are themselves.
Skin, virgin, all the things they are themselves,
you know? That's why they repeat
themselves cuz they're talking about
themselves. So they only have themselves
to go off by
these little bongos on this community,
you know? That's it.
I notice no one else gets this [ __ ]
either, you know, like no no Timmy, no
no one else. I notice no one else gets
this stalking like this. Must be jealousy.
Must be must be. Must be jealousy 100%.
Well, it's not must be. It is jealousy.
Of course, it is.
They're [ __ ] They're freaks. They literally like
they don't even like type on someone's
chat trying to wind them up. They
actually go to great lengths to actually
stalk people. They're [ __ ] losers,
bro. You know, they used to do it on TSO as well.
They actually stalk men on the internet
that they don't even know. They're
[ __ ] such losers.
They really really are.
I feel sorry for them.
I do feel sorry for them, you know.
S on YouTube every day. Ain't got a
life. Can't take a day off YouTube. Yeah.
[ __ ] ugly people.
Oh [ __ ] Oh man. And I can't get into that car.
Yeah. Won't be able to find you on
Reddit anywhere. Yeah.
Yeah. Just stop post on the thing and
you don't even let them know so they can
go on it to be prepared. They literally
sit on that all day refreshing their
homepage. So I could never imagine
being so obsessed and jealous the way
these people are. I I can't imagine it.
Like I know obviously they don't care
and they've got no shame and whatever,
but I just can't imagine it.
Cuz when I say that you are this and you
are that and you are this and you are
that, I'm not wasting my time on you. So
I'm not contradicting myself.
You know, I don't even go on free
channels anymore and I won't do for
probably never will ever go on it ever
again. So what I'm saying about you is
the truth. What you're saying about me
can't be the truth because you are the
one stalking every day. You are the one
wasting your life on me every day and
not getting paid for it. So anything you
say about me doesn't ring right,
you know. No, I'm just saying, bro, like
you know yesterday when you were saying
someone's done a video of me, I'm not on
their channel. I don't I'm not going on
their channel anymore. They can waste
their life away not getting paid for it.
I'm not bothered.
Like these people are actual stalkers.
Like they're actual stalkers. Like they
were stalking me on Reddit yesterday and
I didn't even tell them I was on Reddit.
They have to go on that dating advice
subreddit and have to keep refreshing
it. They're [ __ ] losers, bro. They're
actual losers. They their life is at the
pits. Really is. You know, their [ __ ]
lives are [ __ ] [ __ ] to be doing this.
Like I said, when I'm saying that you're
this, you're that, you're this, you're
that, then I'm not wasting my time on
you. You're wasting your time on me. You understand?
You know what I'm saying, bro? Like
[ __ ] weirdos on here, man.
You know, that's it.
You ain't got a life. None of you are
got a life. You all sat on YouTube
skinned every day. You know, I bet none
of you go out over this bank holiday cuz
you ain't got no money. You know,
they're just disabled people that call
you what they are themselves. You don't
get no no no logic arguing with them. You know,
they call you skin cuz they're skin. If
they weren't skin, they wouldn't be sat
stalking people on Reddit every day.
Um, simple. So, yeah.
Yeah, I think I'm chilling over this
bank holiday, man. I'm going out, but
I'm not going out drinking. It's no point.
I'm off soon anyways. I'm out of this
depressing country. No point wasting
money in this country anymore. It's
depressing being in it as well. I hate
this country. Hate being in it. I hate
the people. I hate the women. And I hate
the government, the [ __ ] gambling,
which I was reminded of 3 months later,
[ __ ] yesterday. I hate this country.
So, no, I won't be anywhere. I won't be
going. Well, I'll be going out, but not out drinking.
Just do something else.
Have to go drinking.
It's pointless. It's pointless in this
country. It's depressing.
It's a depressing country full of [ __ ]
To be honest with you, I don't even like
going out in it to be honest with you,
bro. Tell you the truth.
So, yeah. Finally broke the cycle,
didn't I? Finally broke the cycle.
This country annoys me in every way
possible. I hate it. Even when I went to
watch that cinema, the stupid man
yesterday in the cinema,
I wanted somebody to um start me
yesterday, bro, cuz I was saying like
stuff on the train cuz I was pissed off
from gambling. I wanted somebody to
start me. I would have slapped them up, bro.
Yeah, it is. This country is [ __ ]
bro. the women, the the gambling, the
[ __ ] people, the waiting around for
things, the weather. There's nothing in this country
for anyone, you know. It's depressing.
The country shitty women. I told you
once them numbers [ __ ] around, I'm not
going out again doing this again. I told you this.
Joker, you can't even leave the house,
mate. You're not approaching anyone. We
all know that's you, Joker. So I said,
"Yeah, once that happens, I'm not trying
again." Yeah, I said that. So,
and it and I was thinking of things like
um with that Polish bouncer and
um like the way things work in this
country and it just annoys me. There's
there there's no point even going out
dealing with [ __ ] and [ __ ]
women. There's literally no point even
going out dealing with it. I'd rather just leave,
you know. I don't know what I thought
about that yesterday as well.
So, yeah, just just little things like
that on top of it, you know.
So, I'm I I'm out of here so soon. So, yeah.
Yep. I'm beyond that now. I'm beyond the
going out numbers. I'm I'm over it now, bro.
I'm over it.
Yeah. Like I said, I've got about 300 approaches recorded,
you know? Like even like I was watching
some of them yesterday, like some my
really old ones from about two years
ago, and just watching them annoy me.
Just watching them just annoys me.
Oh, you're going to laugh at this. Yeah,
Nichol. I downloaded this Tinder
yesterday and um same old [ __ ] But
remember, go on Tinder. They said you
can get laid. They said
you can get laid. They [ __ ] said it's
a hookup culture.
Ah, I was watching some approaching
videos in America yesterday um on
Instagram. They were getting the same
old I have a boyfriend. I have a
boyfriend. Why is everyone getting the same [ __ ]
Why does it seem like every single
person that goes out doing this is
getting the same [ __ ] I've not even
done it in a while.
Cuz yeah, [ __ ] that.
Just chilling today, bro. Oh, [ __ ]
There's been loads of bank holidays in the past.
It's not changed then. It's not going to
change now. Simple. So,
it's just the same old It's just the
same It's just the same old [ __ ] I'm
watching. Just Just a younger me.
Nope. Nothing has It's the same. It's
the same. You're just younger.
Okay, bro. There's no point. There's no
point saying this stuff because we're
going to get into a whole conversation
that you can't back up.
So, am I going out today? I've literally
just said that I'm not going out again.
So, why are you asking me if I'm going
out when I've literally said I'm done
with it? We're over it now. And you're
still asking me if I'm going out. This
country [ __ ] annoys me. You know,
like like the way it used to be with
man. Okay, bro. There's no point writing
that stuff, Joe, because whatever I say
back, you're just you don't know. You're
not going to be able to say anything.
So, there's there's there's literally
not even any point writing that [ __ ]
bro. Come on, man. We've been through this before.
It's [ __ ] depressing. It's either you
leave this country or suicide. It's
between It's between two of them, bro.
It's that bad.
I see how Ant-Man feels now as well. I
can see it, bro.
No, I'm not. Listen, listen, listen,
Um yeah and okay Joe so any thoughts of
any thoughts on well maybe people are
approaching because dating apps are not
working maybe people are approaching because
um you don't get introduced to people by
friends. Do you think maybe that's why
people are approaching?
Do you think maybe that's why people are
approaching women? Maybe cuz the dating
apps are not working.
Maybe because you're not going to meet
anyone through friends. I don't know.
Maybe maybe a suggestion that's why
people do it. I mean, yeah, I downloaded
Tinder last night, Nicolo, and it's just
the same old boring.
I can't wait to leave. I really can't
wait to leave this [ __ ] This [ __ ] country.
Yeah, [ __ ] this, bro. There's no point
trying to like mock me or go me. I'm
done. Simple. I am done. Done. Done.
Done. D done. 100%. I'm done. So,
there's no point trying to say, "Oh, go
out." Or, "I'm done. I've proved my
point a million times. I've done it.
I've read the book and I I've wrote the
book and I've read it. So yeah. Well, no,
not at all. Because well, how else are
you going to meet someone? Think about
what you're saying, right? If dating
apps don't work and you're not going to
meet anyone through friends and no one's
going to approach you, how else are you
going to meet someone?
How else are you logically going to meet
or how else logically are you going to
try and meet someone?
But yeah, I've read I've wrote the book
and read it a million times. I've got
nothing left to prove, bro. I'm out of
here. You can go out if you want. I
won't be. It's the same [ __ ] every time
you [ __ ] go out, bro. If you don't
break the cycle, you're [ __ ]
Yeah, that's another thing, Nicolo.
Yeah, they complain that people don't
approach them and then when people do
approach them, they do this. And it's
not even just that. It's not even about
the approaching. It's how they [ __ ] with
you over WhatsApp as well. They
literally will will take the piss out of
you over WhatsApp as well.
Um, they'll actually play games over WhatsApp.
And it's just annoying. That's why I
don't want to try anymore. I want to leave.
I think it's a smart idea breaking the
cycle, you know. Yep.
I can't wait till I'm out of here, you know.
Yeah. Yeah, of course they do.
Well, I've never met anyone that way. I
can safely say.
Yeah, bars. Oh, people meet people in
bars. Well, what would you do if I told
you I went to them places, all of them
places that you've mentioned a million
times, and I've never met anyone? Funny
enough, I've approached people in every
single place that you've just mentioned.
Yeah. You know what's so funny? I've
approached them in every place that
you've just mentioned. I've I've
actually had a conversation with them.
Yeah. Restaurants. I've done
restaurants. I've done bars. I've done
trains a few times. I've done bus stops.
And I have done supermarkets as well.
And I've also done coffee shops. And guess what?
Yeah. It's me, bro. Yep. Yep. Like,
yeah. Yeah. You're right, bro. Like,
when I'm trying to speak to someone and
they pretended they've got a boyfriend.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's me, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. 100%. Yep. It's me, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. It's me and all of these
other guys that struggle. Yeah. Yep.
It's me. It's that person. It's that
person. It's Ant-Man. It's all of us.
Yeah. It's everyone, bro. Even all of
these videos that come up on Instagram,
all of these R channels that try to
speak to women and they get the same
[ __ ] Yeah. Yeah, it's everyone but
women. Didn't you know that? Yeah. So, so yeah.
Yeah. It's everyone, bro. It's everyone but women.
See, the thing is, I'd actually believe
that, right? But there's this guy that I
follow in England. He does it in London.
And there's another guy that does it,
and they get exactly the same [ __ ]
They get exactly the same [ __ ] as me and
they're completely different to me. Um,
and then um and then they're completely
different to me and also people in
America get the same [ __ ] So, [ __ ]
how could it? How could it be you?
How could it? If you're seeing all of
these people getting the same and don't
stop talking about people in
relationships because when you when you
start this [ __ ] you can never finish
it. How could it? I was watching it
yesterday for about 10 minutes and they
were getting the same [ __ ] Boyfriend,
boyfriend, boyfriend, boyfriend,
boyfriend. It's like your eyes see what
they want to see. I mean, to be honest
with you, them approaching videos that I
put up, it should have been enough.
Think about it, bro. No one's critiqued
them. All of the videos that I put up,
they can't be they can't be critiqued.
They can't even be critiqued cuz no
one's critiqued them.
Well, you should find them attractive
because there's nothing wrong with the
way that I look. And I'm not going to
get into a conversation about my look
again. About my my looks again. Well,
they should find you attractive because
you are objectively good-looking. And
I'm not going to get into a conversation
again about my looks anymore before. But
this ain't a conversation about my looks
because we all know that you're not
going to show your face. So, it's not
about whether they're not finding you
attractive. You are good-looking. You
are good-look. You've had [ __ ] women
before back two years ago. There's
nothing wrong with the way that you
look. You know, there's nothing not
attractive about you. So, at the end of
the [ __ ] day, there's nothing wrong
with the way that you look, just like
there's nothing wrong with the the way
these other people look as well. And I'm
not going to have a conversation about
my looks again, you know? You know.
Whoa. Whoa. No, no, no. Okay. Okay. Let
me put them Okay. Do you want me to put
No, no, no. Wait. You want me to You
want me to put myself in their shoes?
>> If a seven out of 10 woman approached
me, would I reject them? No. So, stop
twisting things because that's exactly
what it would be like, right? If if I
was in their shoes. A six out of 10
woman or a seven out of 10 woman
approaches me, I wouldn't reject them.
Stop twisting things, right? This is
what a lot of you people like to do. You
like to twist things and and and and
actually start making stuff up. So, at
the end of the day, right, if a six out
six, seven out of 10 women approached
me, yes, I wouldn't reject them. If I
was in their shoes and a six, seven out
of 10 guy approached me, I wouldn't
reject them. I definitely wouldn't
reject them. So, there you go. I put
myself in their shoes and I've answered
your question. But you try to twist it
by trying to say, "Oh, well, somebody
they don't find attractive." Anyone
would think I'm a [ __ ] two out of 10,
a three out of 10. So, now you're just
twisting things, aren't you? You know,
that's what you're doing. You're
twisting things, you know,
cuz Yeah. And we're not getting into my
looks again, bro. It's boring. None of
you show your face. It's boring now,
bro. Like, the only ones that are
insecure is you people that can't show
your face. Boring. Boring. Boring. All
you do is talk about men's looks. You're
boring, bro. You know,
and I am attractive. I'm [ __ ]
good-looking. And I [ __ ] know damn
well I am. I know damn well I'm I'm
objectively above average looking. I
know for a fact, bro. You know, at the
very least normal looking,
you know, there's just too many stuck up
[ __ ] in this country. That's that's
literally what it is.
That's literally what it is is they're
they're too stuck up. They think they're
better than everyone. That's what it is.
But no, like I said, no one will ever
tell you this [ __ ] They'll say, "Oh,
it's you. It's no no no." Then why am I
seeing everyone else get the same [ __ ] you know? So,
>> bro, you're not you're okay, but you're
not okay. Listen, bro, there's no point
having this conversation. Should we just
end it because you're I'm I'm going to
stop. We're going round and around in
circles, bro. I'm not going to answer
any of your more of your questions. You know,
you know, you're seeing it from their
point of view and you're not seeing it
from my point of view. So, there's no point.
yeah, there's no point, bro. We're just
going to go round and round and round in
circles and we're not going to get
anywhere. So there's there's just
literally no point in having this conversation.
There's no point of having this conversation.
They don't even give you a chance. They
literally don't even give you a chance.
But then you have people saying, "Oh, it
will happen. You'll meet someone."
Nothing ever changes. This is why I'm leaving, bro.
This exactly the same as [ __ ] Ant-Man.
You are right until you No, no, no, no,
no, no, no. You don't see it from my
side. What if you're somebody that
dating apps don't work? You can't get
anyone. You No, no, no. You are right
until you see it from someone else. No,
no. That's you. That is yourself. That's
no one else. That is yourself. What if
nothing works? Dating apps don't work.
You don't meet anyone through friends
because you don't meet anyone through
friends. Then what do you do? Then what
do you do? If you're not approaching
people, what do you do then?
So, no, I'm right because I see it from
both point of views and I'm right.
You're seeing it from one point of view,
not me. Yeah.
So, at the end of the day, yeah, dating
apps are not working. You're never going
to meet anyone through friends. I would
be a virgin. If I didn't approach, I'd
be a virgin, which is something you've
still not answered. You've still not
We're just going around and around in
circles. Let's just end the
conversation. We're going round and
round and round in circles. We've had
this conversation multiple times. I'm
right and you're wrong because I've got
evidence of what I' what I've
experienced. I've got messages of what
I've experienced. So, I'm right all the
time when I'm talking about this.
Otherwise, I wouldn't be talking about
it. If I wasn't right, if I wasn't
right, I wouldn't be talking about this.
I know I'm [ __ ] right. That's
why I'm leaving. That's exactly why I am
leaving and I'm not going out. I'm not
contradicting myself, you know? I'm
leaving. So, I know I'm right, you know.
And this is what I say to people on
Reddit as well. I said, "Hold on, hold
on. If I took your advice, I would be a
kissless, dateless virgin. You forgot to
put the dateless bit in there." And they
never seem to really answer that. They
seem to they sort of change the subject.
They sort of change the subject when you
say that. They say like, "Oh, um,
you you would be like Timmy if you
didn't approach. You would be like
nonsense. You'd be like [ __ ] Timmy.
You'd be like [ __ ] bombing Trump all that.
I'm not doing, bro. I'm doing the same
thing. When was the last time I went
out? When was the last time I tried?
When was the last time I went out? When
was the last time I tried?
No. No. I know I'm right. That's why I'm
leaving. And guess what? Even if I was
trying every week, guess what? I know
I'm leaving. So, at the end of the day,
bro, it doesn't bother me.
But I don't understand how they can say
that you're wrong when if you took their
advice, you would be a virgin. You would
be a kissless hungerless virgin.
It's crazy that, isn't it? I I don't
understand it. And no one's ever really
like went into that. You know what I mean?
Don't that is ex and what do you think
exactly what I'm doing? It's it's a bank
holiday. I'm done. It's over. You know,
that's that's the end of it. Like I
said, I've read I I've made the Superman
book and I've read it.
I've read the s
I've I've I've made the Superman book
and I've read it time and time again. You know,
I've made all the comic books and I've
read them all. So, there's nothing left
to see here. So, yeah,
I'm done anyways.
I mean, I tried with some numbers that I
got uh yesterday and they were just
giving me [ __ ] So, I was like, h
[ __ ] it. That was my last result. I will
not go out and waste any more time or
any more energy on it ever again.
Cuz what good is that? If you don't
break a cycle, what good is that, you know?
Well, no. There's If I If that was going
to If I was going to do that, I would do
it today. If I was going to do that, I
would go and do it today.
I would go out today. I'd go out
tomorrow. I've got the money to do it.
It's a bank holiday. I've got a nice
football bet for tomorrow as well. I
could easily go out today. I could
easily go out tomorrow. Nah, I'm good.
I'm all right. Thanks.
I should have left a long long long long long time.
[ __ ] a year, two years ago to be
honest with you,
not stayed in this [ __ ] thinking that
[ __ ] was going to change. But it's so
easy to [ __ ] get caught in the
moment, you know,
when you're out there [ __ ] living
life, you're not in reality. It's so
easy to think, oh, you know, one day
it's going to change. It will never change. Never.
No, cuz I've already booked it. But it
doesn't matter. Like it doesn't even if
you you could go out every week and keep
trying as long as you you know you know
you're leaving. It's not about trying
right or not trying. It's about you need
to leave. So as long as you know you're
leaving, you're all good. You know, you
can go out every Saturday or every
Friday. As long as you know you're
leaving every time you're, which I'm not
going to go out and try, but I'm saying
if you wanted to, say you're somebody
that didn't try as much as me, you'd be
like at the end of the night, "Oh [ __ ]
I know why I'm leaving now." And you're leaving.
No, listen to me, [ __ ] before I
talk. Yeah. Listen, before you butt your
mouth in, right, I am not trying again,
but I'm saying if you wanted to do that,
you could do that. I'm not doing that.
That's what Ant-Man used to do. I used
to say to Ant-Man like, "Why why don't
you just like shop this for shoplift for
a month and just leave?"
You know what I'm saying? Okay. When was
the last time I tried? Okay. When was
But I'm saying theoretically, you could
still do that. As long as you know
you're leaving, that's that's good cuz I
feel like you're leaving eventually. So,
you know you're leaving. If you don't
have anything booked and you're still
doing it, then you're just going to keep
going around in the same cycle. Bit like
I did with gambling.
Bit like what I did with gambling like
all of them months. You know, yesterday
it reminded me why I stopped for like
five months. Cuz if you don't break a
cycle, you're [ __ ]
If you don't break a cycle, you're screwed. So
with numbers. Yeah, but there were there
were numbers I already had. Yeah, I
tried with the numbers because I would
already had the numbers, you [ __ ]
idiot. But I'm not going to go out
wasting money and wasting time again,
you know, to get the same [ __ ]
to just annoy myself. Cuz you're just
going to get an escort at the end of the
night anyways. You're just going to have
a wank at the end of the night anyways.
So why why would you go out and even
waste your time?
Well, those were numbers I already had.
So, I thought, okay, I'll go out this
week if someone wants to meet. But,
you know, the maddest thing about this,
Nicolo, is that even as you get older,
even as you get older, right, it never
changes like the the games and the
immaturity. You think, "Oh, it's like 18, 19."
That's another thing I need to say to
Ant-Man, actually. He says, "Oh, you
know, sometimes you can be immature and
women don't like that." I mean, bro, no
one can be more immature than them. The
games that they play, the trolling. I
actually thought I was immature, but no
one can be as immature as them. I've
actually just thought of that now. You
know, they they they've actually got to
be the immature ones to be playing these
games and doing what they do.
No one can be as immature as them.
So, no one can be as immature as them.
Yeah, there were numbers I had got, man.
Yep. And I can watch other people. If I
if I like I said to you, if this guy in
London, he's a he's a black guy, by the
way, and he's not ugly either. Just a
normal black guy. if he got a different
result, right? Then I'd be like, "Oh,
okay. Well, you shouldn't compare
yourself to people, but he is in the
same position as you and you know, he's
doing the same thing as you. So, though
you can't compare, it might give you a
tiny bit of hope, but he gets the same
[ __ ] And watching him annoys me.
Watching it annoys me. Even watching it
annoys me. Even though I send them to
Ant-Man and laugh at him cuz it is
funny. It is funny. It's so [ __ ] up
that sometimes it actually is funny.
Like it is annoying though. It is annoying.
They're boring. They just They just say
the same [ __ ] They just got Tik Tok batteries in.
It's boring as [ __ ] Like even in
America. Yeah. You hear it in You hear
it in America, right? Yeah. They say in
America, "Oh, I've got a man or I'm
underage." They say the same [ __ ] there as well.
Because because it's a waste of because
it's I don't drink every week. I if I go
out I go out every two weeks. I don't
drink every week.
What's the [ __ ] It's just depressing.
This country is is just depressing. But
they call it a hookup culture.
They call it hookup culture.
They call it a [ __ ] hookup culture, bro. Yeah.
And then you got Timmy, right, saying
about how I'm going to hurt a woman. But
if I was Timmy, I would have already
hurted a woman. Like I said, if I was
any of these people like Timmy Bomb,
[ __ ] the the [ __ ] beds virgin boy,
you know, I I would have actually done
that because I would blame them for them
leaving me a virgin,
you know? You know what I'm saying? Probably.
Yeah, probably are. Maybe like if you
work with someone or something but
or maybe like if you're a big YouTuber
or I don't know like obviously there are
people are but it makes you wonder how
people actually are doing it. If you
can't even get a conversation with someone then
trying to think, bro. Yeah,
you can't even get dates anymore. when
you could actually go and get dates. You
can't even get that anymore.
Can't even get dates anymore, bro.
It's [ __ ] madness, isn't it? If I was
like people like Timmy and Virgin Boy
and Bomb and Trout, I would have I would
have done something, bro.
But then they
Yeah. They make it seem like getting a
relationship's hard, but getting sex is easy. Uh-huh.
Uh-huh. Yeah. They They make it seem
like getting sex is easy, but a
relationship is hard. That's what they
make it seem like.
Yeah. I downloaded this Tinder app
yesterday, bro, cuz I still logged on
it. And this is as dead as anything.
Women, I shall never know. I shall never
And like I keep saying, they're in a
worse position than you. Timmy, Virgin Boy, Bob,
but yet they still defend women.
This madness, is it? Autism to the max.
And they make it seem like you're the
one that's never had sex. You're the one
that's never been with a woman like them. Um, yep.
No, I would still feel exactly the same way.
And it's not negativity negativity
towards women. It's it's reality. See
the difference between positivity and
negativity. This is reality.
This is actually reality.
You know, so it's not even negativity.
It's actually reality. There's a big
difference. It's not negativity. It is
reality. I hate them,
you know. And I've got more than Timmy
and I've got more than [ __ ] Virgin
Boy and I've got more than Truman. I've
had more people than them. So that's why
I don't understand how they defend them, you know.
No, not at all.
Not at all.
Nah, not at all, mate. Not at all. You
don't understand that I'm different than
most people. I don't think you
understand. I'm different than most
people. I've tried more than anyone in
the world. You don't You don't
understand that I'm an exception.
I'm I'm an actual exception.
You not understand that?
It's just like that USA Izzy, bro. If I
ever see her, I'll slap her in her
[ __ ] face, in front of her [ __ ] boyfriend.
You know what I'm saying? You think I
give a [ __ ] if I've got [ __ ] 50k or
50 million, I'll slap her up in front of
her boyfriend and make him watch.
That's That's the [ __ ] That's That's
the madness thing about it.
I actually [ __ ] would, bro. Slap the
[ __ ] up in front of her [ __ ]
boyfriend. I'm giving you an example,
bro. It doesn't matter about [ __ ] money.
So either way, you know, that's an example.
I don't think I could I could even go
out [ __ ] nowadays. So, I just end
up glassing someone,
you know? I don't think I could even go
out nowadays and start dealing with
[ __ ] simps that try to defend
women. I just [ __ ] put one glass with their neck,
you know? I was I was waiting for
somebody to start on me yesterday. I was
in a dodgy area yesterday. I wanted I
wanted a perfect excuse to b someone up
yesterday. I was looking for that
excuse, bro. I was waiting for someone,
you know. I w I weren't in a good area
yesterday, so I was waiting for somebody. Yeah.
Over them properties. At least I know At
least I know why I quit. At least I know
why I stopped for five months.
Don't know how people And the reason I
didn't smash the shop up is cuz I ain't
got the energy.
I ain't got the energy. I I ain't
worried about being nicked or [ __ ]
But if I had kept doing it, I would have
ended up in prison.
I would have ended up in in prison from
for [ __ ] killing someone. I know for
a fact if I carried on doing it, I would
have ended up in prison for killing
someone if I kept doing it and doing it
and doing it 100%. Uh I was just bored.
I just come out the cinema and I was bored.
So, I was trying to win some money just
to try and get a buzz.
Yeah. Well, I've got this double. Both
teams to score no draw. Both score no
15 returns. 438. So, we
Yeah. They make you depressed. They
[ __ ] make you [ __ ] depressed. Yeah.
Frewood, old Coldchester, and Barrow.
Still can't get a bonus on that fishing frenzy.
I was saying to Adman, you win some, you lose some.
Gambling, win some, lose some. Do you?
You win some, you lose some. Do you
know? Yeah. [ __ ] bastard.
You know what? But he said, "Oh yeah,
with the football bet you couldn't hack
losing." But bro, the losing the
football bet, losing that 20 football
bet didn't make me angry or smashing
things. It just made me depressed. It
just stopped me going out. But it didn't
make me [ __ ] angry
cuz I was one goal off of 140. And even
though I didn't need a 140,
right? Even though I didn't need the
140, I could have done with it. Like how
anyone can do with extra money, I could
have done with that money to go out. And
because I was one goal off losing it and
I had went out the Thursday and I tried
the Thursday, there was just no point of
me going out, you know. I figured it was
just best to stay in and play Franklin. So
that Chinese escort was messaging me
yesterday. Um, Chinese is he? She said,
"I'll come to Manchester." I said, "Fuck that."
It's funny how Ant-Man's one to talk
about me being immature when they're the
most immature people [ __ ] going. But
I'm the immature one. I mean, I think
that's a good bet. Eventually, if I do
80 bets, it's going to start being on both SC.
The returns a lot harder. The returns a
lot um higher, but
I'm only going to do two teams.
Imagine having 500 on a on a treble.
Both score no draw. [ __ ] hell.
Could you imagine that? Jesus Christ. be
a [ __ ] That'd be a good You'd be set
probably for a couple of years.
Yeah, you'd be set for a couple of years, matey.
[ __ ] knows, mate. Cuz not last week, the
week before there was there was it was a
double both teams to score.
No, it'd be more than 1.5k, you idiot.
What a treble. Both score. No draw.
I can't be a lot more than that. That's
and that's that's a normal both teams to
score. Let me look it up. Hold on.
Yeah, I got a both score no draw [ __ ]
two weeks ago and I wish I had done a
both team no draw. I wish I had done it,
bro. It would have been a I would have
got about£600 instead of like 200 and something.
But it's getting the teams right, you know.
I'll look it up one second.
But obviously you can't do that because it's
what's the chance of you actually winning. Two seconds.
Yeah. 50 but not£500.
Yeah. 50. Yeah. [ __ ] sake.
Imagine you had 500 on it. Jeez.
So, say you put £500 on a double both
teams to score and you won £1,600.
How easy would it be getting that money,
do you think?
If they'll just pay it to you in cash
like or what?
Yeah, about 14K.
What? Yeah, about 14K. That's not even
really a big return to be honest.
That's not really a big return
because £500 a lot to put on something
that's so not likely.
Yeah, that's not really even a big
return though. 14K for that cuz Yeah,
that's not even that big though. 14K for
that. Three teams both score no draw.
how hard that would be to win. Very hard.
Yeah. The ones you need to be careful
with those casinos. They will do
anything not to pay you.
They'll find any excuse not to pay you.
The casinos are the dodgy ones.
They will find excuses not to pay you
out. And like I told you with a ticket
and that they can actually avoid
tickets. Yeah, they're dodgy. They are.
Nah, not really. I've done it all
before. going to cinos and
winning money and [ __ ] and [ __ ] going
out drinks. I've done it all before really. Nah,
but your mortal status never changes.
Your mortal status never changes. Nope.
It will never change, mate. Never change.
Yeah. See, if I if I got killed today,
bro, I wouldn't even give a [ __ ] I
wouldn't care, bro. I know I've lived
the life. I'd have no regrets.
I I I would literally would have no regrets.
I've done it a million times, bro. [ __ ] millions.
But yeah, I could have 50 million and if
I ever see that USA is I'll slap her up
in front of her boyfriend.
I'd love to slap her up in front of her
boyfriend, you know? It'd be a good
feeling. Not not not not with anyone but
her boyfriend. I wouldn't like to do it
by by herself because you know these men
always try to look good for women. These
little simps. I would literally slap her
up in front of her boyfriend. Bro, it's
not even a joke. You know
I like that one. That's good.
Yeah. That was a good one, bro.
Yeah, man. So, I'll be probably just
chilling playing GTA due d doing a bank
holiday to be honest.
Yep. During a bank holiday, I'll just be
sat chilling. Bro, I wake up late now.
Like 10:00. I used to wake up at like 8, 9.
I wake up really late.
You know, I wake up really late.
I think that's how you know you're
depressed. 8 10 is a is very late to wake up.
8 is the perfect time. But yeah,
you wake up at 10 when you're depressed, I think.
Nah, bro. Done it all before. What?
Going out drinking to hear I've got a
boyfriend? Nah. Wasting my 20ies. I've
lived a life. I think you've got Bro, I
think you've got memory loss. wasting my
20s. I've been out drinking probably
more times than you have and you're a
lot older than me.
[ __ ] hell. I think your you your
dementia is um kicking in again, lad.
Just like when you forgot that I've
shown money and all of these things that
you seem to forget cuz it doesn't suit
you. Bro, I would safely say I've
probably drunk more than you have and
and and I'm a lot younger than you
on a bank holiday here when I've got a
boyfriend. Nah, I'm good, thanks. That's
what stupid people do. Smart people save
money and leave.
Leave this [ __ ] out. Leave this depressing country.
But I would honestly say that I have I
have actually drunk more than you have.
And I'm and I'm not even just saying that.
Ah, trust me, bro. You've got no idea. I
used to drink three times a week, you know, like
waste of my 20s. Not at all. Not at all.
I probably I've probably been to cities
that you've not even ever been to. I've
gone out getting pissed in every city.
Bro, I don't think I've lived the life.
I know I've lived the life
in terms of this country,
bro. Because okay, okay, put it this
way, right? Okay, I I'll answer your
question. When I say that I've met more
women than anyone in the world, why why
do I say that? Because I've approached
I've gone to I I I used to do this
almost every day. I've got about 300
videos recorded. So, who else who else
has done it more than me? Who Who else
could have possibly done it more than
me? That's a B with the drinking, bro.
I've been I've been pissed in every city multiple times.
It's hard to imagine someone doing it
more than you.
Think of it. You've had to work. I
haven't had to work. So, what the [ __ ]
do you think I was getting up to in them
[ __ ] three and a half years staying
in [ __ ] bed? Come on, man.
So I mean with the approach and I know
I've tried more than anyone in the world.
Well so well it it works better than
dating apps. Well it works better than
He probably would to be honest.
Bro, you can have everyone's entitled to their opinion.
Everyone's entitled to their opinion. But
I mean, so you know these people,
Nicoia, that said that say you shouldn't
approach. Okay, so you shouldn't
approach. So what what does somebody do
if they want a child or they want sex or
they want a relationship? So let let's
just say that you take approaching out
of the equ the equation. Then what? Meet
people through friends. Meet people
through dating apps.
like, well, what what what's the
alternative? Because we never really get
into the alternative.
We never ever speak about the
alternative. We speak about a method not
working, but we never really we never
really think about the alternative, do
we? We never we never get to that bit.
We always just say, oh, like we
shouldn't approach, we shouldn't
approach, we shouldn't approach. But we
never ever understand. We never ever get
to the alternative.
because there is none.
How many people do you think I've
approached? Probably about 4,000 people.
Probably. I know that there was um New
Year's Eve. When was that? I think it
was 2 years ago.
You know, uh two years ago it was.
Okay. What is What is the alternative
then? You can say it. I would say
probably well I don't know man New Year's Eve
two years ago was was a banger bro. I
was out from 3 pm to about 2 a.m. and I
sent it hard. I was mad back then as
well. Thousands. I'd probably say thousands.
But that's this is what my other channel
was about. You know it's to show how bad
dating is in this country. how bad it is
when you try to speak to someone and stuff.
Probably 23 24.
Oh, right. Okay.
And then and then if I do that then then
what's going to happen? Oh, right. Interesting.
I think about 20
23 and a half 24.
So about 4 years
and no changes. No longlasting changes.
The only change there is a change. It's
just gotten worse.
any of their numbers reply back.
Nope. Not a sausage.
Not a sausage at all.
Well, we're still dealing with this in
our [ __ ] 20s. Late 20s. It's mad, isn't it?
This is why I like watching Oreo, man.
You know, I like watching them uh black
guys in America. Yeah. Yep. Yep. Mad.
Well, good for you, bro. I'm I'm happy.
I'm happy for you, bro. But I just like
watching this Oreo man, even though he's
still a virgin. I like watching negative
people like that. And to be honest, it's
not as negative as this community. You
know, you know how [ __ ] up this
community is is I'd rather sit there and
watch Oreo, man. You know what I mean? You know,
one second. You went out every other
week. So 26 weeks, that's people
approach every two weeks. Bro, I've I
pro when I go out, I probably approach
about 30 people.
I probably approach about 30 people when
I go out,
but I I watch I I you know, I'd rather
watch him than watch these people in this community.
Someone like them them them incel
people. I'd rather watch them than watch
these people. That's how bad this
community actually is.
He made a rap about himself. He said,
"I'm a He said I I I'm a no [ __ ] [ __ ] R.
I'm I'm just a [ __ ] that ain't [ __ ] I was dead.
I was dead, bro.
If I was like him or Virgin Boy or
Timmy, I would have I would have I would
have killed someone by now, bro. If I
was one of them,
I would have [ __ ] killed someone by
by now. if I was one of them people. Trust me,
it's bad enough now, you know, being in
this situation and then Yeah, but like I
said, they they defend them. So, they
defend women. Strange.
I wish that [ __ ] accepted my offer like
3 months ago, bro. It was like by the
last time I played roulette. I said,
"Let me come next Thursday and slap you
up in front of your boyfriend. Come on.
Oh, I really wanted to slap that [ __ ]
up in front of her boyfriend. Bro, you
don't even understand.
Really, man? Really?
Yeah. You ain't about [ __ ]
You ain't about that life. Yeah.
Yeah, there was a pub that I wanted to
go out to maybe this week, but that I
can't be asked. I ain't wasting money.
I need to be saving now anyways. So, boyfriends.
I heard you said Virgin Boy was still
making videos on me. So, well, that's a
shame cuz I'm not I have I haven't been
on that channel and I'm never going on
it again. And I'm never going on that
Red Star channel as well. I don't
entertain little [ __ ] keyboard warriors.
So, bro, that I I didn't even know, bro.
Sorry about that, man. I'd rather let
them waste their life away on me and
free a charge. I'd rather let them
embarrass themselves and not get paid for it.
>> He seems to He doesn't have no money.
All of the money he shows is his benefit
money that he's been showing for [ __ ]
years and years that [ __ ] not years.
It started off as £800. He doesn't have
no money. He's skinted. That's just his
benefit money. And it ain't my And it
ain't my 10 grand either. So, we're not
going to get into that again, remember.
But, you know, yeah, you don't have
cash. You you you don't have money at
all. You what you're showing is your
benefit money, your housing benefit
money, and you've been doing it
literally every month. So,
you know what we need to do, bro? Ask
Ask him to show his room
and that will prove that he lives in a
bed sit. Ask him to show his room and
show his bed. See what he says about that.
But you think what he is showing is
cash? Bro, please stop it. You've lost
the money game time and time and time
and time and time and time and time and
time again. And there's no point asking
me to show money again because I'm never
shown you nothing ever again. Not even
the videos of me in the hotel rooms
because whatever you get shown, you just
deny you've seen it. Which is one of the
reasons I don't go to [ __ ] this place
and that, you know? Listen, listen. It's
like going to meet someone on this
community, right? Like this um Smokeoky
B. If I went to Milton Kees and this guy
didn't show up. This is one of this is
why I stopped myself last time about was
it two months ago.
What happens is you you don't need to
know where I am. Uh
if I went there like do you remember two
months ago after the gym and I thought
I'm going to go there. I'm going to go
there. I stopped myself. Why did I stop
myself? Because I know exactly what's
going to happen when I go there. He's
not going to show up. Everyone's going
to stick up for him and everyone's going
to forget about it.
This is why sometimes like before you
even get angry, you need to actually
think about hold on what what's going to
happen if you actually do do this. Same
with the money. You show money, they
don't show nothing and then they show
you less and then they act like they've
won. You know, it's same when you show
you've had more women than them, they
still point black the night. So there's
literally no point in anything
when it comes to these semastics on this
community. waste of time, bro.
You know, the meeting, the money, the
showing the women. They'll just pretend
they ain't seen it. They'll just act
like they've not seen it. Cuz like I
said, if you're not fat and ugly like
these people, they will find a reason to
dislike you. If you're not the same as
these people, fat, ugly, ain't got a
life, you know, they they they find
reasons to not like you. So, if they
don't like you, they're not going to um
defend you. So,
but you don't need to know where I am
anyways. But let's let me tell you this.
I'm not in a bed sit in a room with no bed. So, yeah. Yeah.
Nope. I'm not showing you nothing.
I will never ever show money again. I
will never ever show anything again.
like in that in that way. So,
so I'm never shown anything ever again.
Not £10, not 20, not a million pound.
Nope. Because remember the last time we
played a money game, you all ran off. We
don't want a repeat of last time,
do we, Nicolo? We don't want a repeat of
last time. Nope. You've been shown money
multiple times and you all run away. Get
[ __ ] Go look at your own money. If
you've got all of this money, go look at
your own. If you want to see money, then
go look at your own money. If you got so
much, that's what I've started saying to
these people now.
Yeah. Just like every single time you
get beaten with a money game, you run
away. Yeah. I will never show you
nothing again. The only money you're
ever going to see is maybe things put on
a football bat. Maybe.
Nah, never. I'm never showing you money again. Ever.
I could pull out 2K. Not showing you nothing.
Well, you're going to put all £500 in a
[ __ ] in a in a in a fy, huh?
I used to do that when I was depressed
to be honest. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, I was thinking of going to
Liverpool actually, but I'm not going
to. Waste of time, waste of money. But I
was thinking of doing that as well cuz
I've only been once.
No, it wasn't 250. It was 150. But yeah, so yeah,
it was actually 150, but yeah.
Yeah, it was 150.
I don't know about 100 pound yesterday
on the property. So yeah,
do you remember Joe? I like Sho.
I see what you was trying to do there.
You was copying the copycat, weren't
you? You was mocking the copycat.
You was mocking the [ __ ] copycat, weren't you?
Yeah. Those were the good old days. Uh
you you copying the copycat, weren't you?
Yeah, you're a copycat.
Yep, definitely, bro. Definitely gay.
Yeah, 100%. Even though I've had more
women than him and I've never had to
resort to disabled. I know I'm the gay
one, bro. Of course. Yeah. You know the
drill. Definitely gay. You are
definitely definitely definitely
definitely definitely definitely gay.
Yeah. Even though you've slept with more
women than he has ever had. Been with
more women than he's ever had. One that
he probably tries stalking to this day.
But yeah, I'm gay, bro. 100%. And then you know
that is such that is such a trend. That
is copying bro.
He is copying. He's definitely copying
with that one. For [ __ ] sake. He tried
it with that USA and she rejected him.
You remember when she he was trying to
message her and [ __ ] trying to get into
her and she blocked him. She blocked
that [ __ ] virgin. Remember,
no one wants your virgin ass. No one
wants your creepy virgin ass, mate. [ __ ] hell.
No one wants your creepy virgin ass with
your little dick. That don't work.
You know what I'm saying?
[ __ ] hell. Yeah.
He was trying to message them. Do you
remember, Nicolo? We were trying to message them.
Proper virgin is it?
[ __ ] madness, isn't it?
Yeah. He He hates the fact that he's
still a virgin.
He hates the fact that he's he's going
to die a virgin. Yeah.
No, because what's there? Women. And the
women are [ __ ]
So why would I go to somewhere where the
There's [ __ ] here. The women, the
Romanian women are [ __ ] here. Yeah. is
it's cuz he's still a virgin.
That's what it is. He's He's still He's
still a virgin.
He He done it to Sig as well. He He sexy frustrated virgin.
Yeah. Because he's a virgin. Everyone
has to be like him in his head. Do you
not understand? It's it's it's part of
autism. It's part of his autism.
and he asks them in a certain way where
he knows he's going to get the answer
that he wants. It's because he hates the
fact that you've Don't forget this. This
this cunt's older than me by like two
and a half years
and I've got more money than him, proved
it many times. I've had more women than
him. I'm better looking than him. Think
about it. And and he's older than me.
So, this is where all of this YouTube
obsession comes from, which I don't
entertain. You don't see me writing
[ __ ] [ __ ] on my channel. That's where
it comes from. And you're older. But
you're also older than the virgin
and you've also got teeth.
I don't know. But but it's You know what
I find funny though? Like they're lying
on the floor, right? Like [ __ ] Big
Smoke and [ __ ] GTA San Andreas Grezy.
And when they've run out of options,
they've got nothing left in them. The
little losers. It's the boys in blue,
mate. It's time for the boys in blue.
That that that's mad to me. Like when
when when they failed everything, tried
to get a black man to do their dirty
work, put you on [ __ ] street drama,
when it all fails and there's nothing
left, then it's the boys in blue, mate.
That's the last resort.
The last resort is the boys in blue.
[ __ ] what a loser.
Imagine being owned so badly on YouTube
you need to run to the police.
Like these people have never ruined my
life. They ruined Monty's life. They've
not ruined my life. These people can't
even ruin their own life.
Nah, I'm good. Thank you, bro. I'm out
of here in a couple of months. I'm all right.
No, I'm good. Thank you. I already know the result.
It's like watching a film when you
already know when you already know the ending.
It's the same
beginning and the same ending. You
already know. You already know the
result. It's like me watching Superman
yesterday, right? But just with different actors.
It's pointless. It's like watching the same movie,
you know? Yeah.
It's like watching [ __ ] the same um
episode of [ __ ] Two and a Half Men,
right? But instead of Charlie Sheen,
it's Ashton Kutcher. You know,
it's like what Ant-Man says, Joe. It's
the same ending, the same beginning,
just different characters.
That's mad. It's just different characters. Grievy,
he doesn't even refer to them as people.
He refers them as as characters. Yeah.
You can see
you can see the westernity in their
eyes. They give you that westernized look.
He says it's the same old. He says
you're slow videos, but it's the same [ __ ] Yeah,
it is the same [ __ ] Just different characters, you know. >> Yeah.
Make myself a cup of [ __ ]
I had a cough yesterday. Grezy a nasty
cough. I had to drink milk to stop it. I
had to drink some milk.
So, Nikolai, what happened to um
what happened to USA? Is it what was the story there?
Well, at least I found at least I had s
it mean was a replacement it
was a replacement it. Yeah. Nicholas.
How do you know that?
That is that is definitely Yeah. Any mama
was never your mama.
When I was in the cinema, I was thinking
about you typing to what I write. When I
was watching Superman, it was making me
laugh, but I was just laughing in the
cinema. Someone looked at me. You
remember when I was asking you the
questions and you was answering and you
said, "Oh, so why didn't USA Izzy tell
me?" He's like she wanted to keep it a secret.
I was [ __ ] laughing in the ciney.
I was laughing, bro. You know
what I'm saying? Yeah.
Baby away from its mama.
Why you Why did you just copy my saying for?
Yeah, that account is definitely Joker.
That Nick account. You know too much. Yeah.
I got some cooking. M cookie.
Do you prefer do you prefer Superman or Spider-Man?
I Superman film was quite good,
but I've never really been into Marvel and [ __ ]
Maybe I'll stop getting into Marvel
and and whatnot, but uh I mean I said I
I prefer to Spider-Man, but maybe
I know that Superman was quite good.
There's even like sex scenes in that.
Well, obviously they don't have sex and
[ __ ] If only you could actually get
that in your life. You can't even watch
a [ __ ] movie with N P N P N P N P N P
N P N P N P N P N Piccolo without seeing it.
People hook it up and stuff. Especially
the horror films.
Especially the horror films,
you know. Oh, they they go into town
with that and it makes you think about
your situation. It's so cruel, isn't it? Very cruel.
satisfying but yet very cruel. Eh, you know,
no, the couples don't really bother me
anymore cuz I've seen it like a million times.
But yeah, that's
that bothers Ant-Man more than it
bothers me because I've seen it so many
times because I I I feel like
it's never going to be me. I don't
compare myself to other people and you
shouldn't compare yourself to other people.
Other guys do it.
They used to say my friends were [ __ ]
because I never ever met anyone through
friends. None of my friends have ever
been [ __ ] They're actually all right. I
got friends in the army. Um,
got friends in the army, [ __ ]
whatnot. Yeah, I got friends in the army
and [ __ ] So, and like friends like from
other places and they used to say that
my friends were [ __ ] because I never
made anyone through friends. And I used
to say, "Oh, but it's just everyone's
out for themselves."
And they'd say, "Oh, no, you need you
need to get better friends." I've never
met anyone [ __ ] through friends.
That's [ __ ] [ __ ] It doesn't
happen for everyone. Just because it
happened for [ __ ] a lot of people, it
doesn't mean it happened for everyone because
you not understand that. Let's just say
for argument sake it did happen, right?
Let's just say that it did happen. Yeah.
You you can get rejected. You can get
rejected that way. You can still get
rejected even if you meet someone
through a [ __ ] friend. You can still get rejected.
Like your chances aren't even they don't
even they're not even higher. Done.
I'll be in bed today. Probably
get McDonald's later.
What a [ __ ] life, eh?
life changes. They say
we say that
you never know what the future holds.
Um, life changes.
You can't predict the future, stuff like that.
You know what I'm saying? Um, other
people do it.
other guys do it. Watch out for the other guys.
That's the ones you need to be careful
of. The other guys,
the other guys do it. Yeah.
Always other guys not you.
It's not nice, is it? being compared
being compared to other people.
I am going to I am going to go out
tonight. I'm going out tonight to go to
McDonald's and then I'm coming straight back.
I'm going out and I'm coming straight back.
You get what I mean, Grooy?
No, I'm good. Thanks.
I'm all right. I've already said I've
already seen the same movie.
I've seen the same movie over and over
again with it. You know,
you have like the comic book um
you have comic books.
It it might it can have a million
approaching opportunities. I don't give
a [ __ ] I'm done with it. I'm leaving.
It's not my problem anymore.
It's not my problem anymore. You understand?
You think I could beat USA? Is his
boyfriend up? Nicolai 100%.
But I did like Superman. I don't like Batman though.
I might try that Smackdown versus Raw 2009 game.
I was watching like videos of its and it
reminds me of being an 11year-old me
sitting on the high chair playing it. I
was just thinking about getting an Xbox
360 and just getting the whole game again.
It's like the best game. That is the
best Smackdown game you would ever get.
Like trust me, 2009 and 2010
was the best. I could show you so many
glitches on that game, you know? I still
remember it now as a [ __ ] adult, you
know, as when I was a kid. So,
you could probably get from like CX
or if you get online, you probably have
to pay like 40 for it because it's an
old game. But that game, I'm telling
you, it's the best Smackdown game ever.
I stopped after about 2010. I outgrew
it. By 2010, I outgrown out grown the WWE.
But that game, bro,
I'm telling you, it was it was a one
[ __ ] good game. That was
2009 was the best.
2010 was still pretty good. Then after
2011 was just [ __ ] There were all the
good things. Then it started becoming
WWE 2K. Then it stopped. The Smackdown
versus Raw stopped. So yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. You can't with this one. You can't though
cuz you can't put a disc in my Xbox.
It's a digital one and you can't play it
on the store
for some crazy reason.
Yeah, for some reason you can't play it
on the store. I'm not sure why, but
but you can buy like GTA games on Xbox
One. You can play that. But you can't
play that Smackdown versus Raw.
Maybe I'll just get a Smackdown post as
well and try to stream it somehow.
[ __ ] I'm not sure how I'll do it, but that.
Did you ever play it?
I wish I was Superman. You know,
I was actually watching Superman
yesterday and I wish I was Superman.
I bet he gets all the pictures.
I wish I was Superman, you know,
cuz Superman's real, isn't it, Grezy?
Like all that stuff happens in real life
where people fly and [ __ ]
Yeah, that's the first game I got on
PlayStation 3 was Smackdown First World 2009.
There was so many glitches in that game
though. I bet you don't even know half
the glitches that was on that game, do
you? There was
there was a glitch where you could
freeze someone. So, if you playing
online, right, you pressed R1, X, and square,
and um they'd freeze. So, if you was if
you was in like um a tag team match,
yeah, and you froze one of the opponents,
then it's only it's two of you against
one, so you can actually freeze people.
Um whereas like you was playing Money in
the Bank or something. Yeah, you could
actually there's a glitch to freeze
someone. There is a glitch where you
could create a finisher and then when
you try to pin them, there's no way they
can get out of it. There's also a glitch
where you can choke someone to like [ __ ]
their full health up. You know, when you
choke them and they just can't get back up.
And then um and then um there's also a
glitch where you can choke the referee.
So when you choke the referee, obviously
what people would do is they'll choke the referee and then
obviously the match they can't they
can't do anything so they'd make you
leave. There was so many glitches on
that Smackdown game, bro. Like you don't
even know the core of it. Trust me, bro.
We used to rinse that game. How much did you lose?
God bless you then. God bless you Grezy
Jones. God bless.
Bless you if you on the off the little te then.
Yeah. I'd like to get the game again and show you.
So why are you saying So why you saying
that's you off? Oh, that's you off to the Yeah.
Well, do a do a little recorder in it,
man. And I can show you all of the I can
show you all of the glitches. I still
remember them now 15 16 years later.
So many. I don't know how there were so
many glitches in that game. Like, [ __ ]
me, bro. It was a banger that game.
And one of my friends I met on there
from America, he come here and saw me. I
still talk to him to this day. I was
like, "Bro, we was like well, he's a few
years older than me. I was like, bro, we
like almost kids when we was playing that."
But there was a and there was a kick
glitch where you could kick someone.
Like, there's so many, bro. Like, I
couldn't even explain like
how many glitches there was in that
game. And then after 2010, they there
was no more glitches. Yeah,
could just go see X by 360, buy the game.
I bet if I try and go online now, like
there's no one playing it. Imagine like
16 years later. Yeah. 17 years later,
you're back on it and then [ __ ] No,
to be fair, we did stop we did still
play it back in 2013.
me and some of the people in in 2013. It
was still like people still on it.
My order has been delivered. Can't have One second.
How can it be delivered? What? Oh,
I bet you're not ready for this. Are you grievy? Oh,
you're not ready for this, are you, matey? Oh,
are you ready?
Just got a little text at her. Yeah, I
got some stuff
and I didn't even show you what I got,
did you? Did I? So, yeah.
Oh, I don't think you're ready, bro.
Only took [ __ ] two weeks to come.
Are you sure you'll see? Oh, mate.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
You ready, Grezy? Right.
Got my little caps. So, maybe it is a
good idea today to go out cuz I got my little caps.
Right. Cap number one.
Well, not it must have took them [ __ ]
years to make this, bro.
That's my first cap.
Oh [ __ ] This is charging. My little
Chucky cap. Right. That's the first cap
I got. I told you I wasn't joking. Just
come through the face.
I saw you getting into Chucky.
Oh, this one's more of a uh
they just need a sort of reshaping, don't they? You know,
right? One second. And I've got another cat.
I got to wait [ __ ] two weeks for
these [ __ ] good guy cats.
Look, that's another one. I've got two
Chucky taps. He said get a Chucky Tap. Yeah,
you can go out and give it a whirl.
Greasy. One second.
>> Grezy, you can go out and give it a
whirl, but I won't be there.
You can if you want, but I won't be there.
>> You turn if you want, but I won't be there.
Yeah. Right. And I got some underpants.
Got some underpants.
You want to see my little underpants? Chucky.
You can if you want, but I won't be there.
Got some Chucky on the tank.
They're quite cute, aren't they? Yeah.
Now, this is what you're going to love. Now, Greavves. Right.
They went by weird sizes, bro.
My other underpants. And who cannot forget Stitch. Little Stitch.
I got the lot.
I got the [ __ ] lot, mate. Yep.
Do you like it? Yeah. I got some new underpants.
Yeah. Disney. You like him? Yeah.
Mhm. I really want to get that Smackdown game though.
Bless you then if you was into WWE then bless you
bless you then if you was into WWE
let's shoot if you was into WWE then
I got some lovely cats and some lovely boxing
want to play.
>> I'd love to give it a while, but I've
already seen this. I've already watched
this movie before. You understand? I've
already watched this movie before.
I've already watched this movie before.
Do you remember? I like this game. This
game is fun.
Remember with seaside moth? I like this game.
I like this game. This game is fun.
I like this game. You like my little You
like my little items?
Well, it's been predicting it for four years.
It's been predicting it for four years
with women. So,
who knows, eh? Yeah, that's what he says. Yeah,
this [ __ ] USA, this Chinese Izzy
keeps [ __ ] texting me, bro. Think he
is he? What the [ __ ] does she want?
Oh, do you think this Steven Howard is
actually putting these 80 on football
bets? Nico, I don't think he is. I think
he's trolling me.
Nah, there's no way in it.
Yeah, she's horny for money.
Yeah, I think it's Tom Woodwards as
well, but they're not they're not
actually do you actually think they're
doing the bet? Nah.
No, there's no point me going out. I
already know this movie. I've seen it before.
I've seen this film before.
Can you help me, Nicolola? I want to
give that USA a good [ __ ] hiding.
Do Do you remember Do you remember Do
you remember Scott? He was like, "Oh,
um, you're very successful at at doing
something to my daughter online." He
says, "You've been very successful as
slinging my daughter online."
Do you remember that one movie? He says,
"All I can ask is you have the same
energy towards me." You know, that's not
even funny, you know, bro. Like he he
probably he's at it's like what LT said.
He's You shouldn't do that to the old
Syrian man. You know, at his age, he
just wants, you know, peace in his life.
You know, at his age, he just wants a
bit of peace
at his time of life.
Yeah, he's time of time of life.
I just want you to have the same energy
towards me said that. That was funny,
man. It Yeah.
Yeah. I think that like that experience
in itself Yeah. is why I would say to
everyone, Yeah. don't even bother. Don't
even bother in the west.
You know what I'm saying, Grezy? Cuz
[ __ ] escalates like that and then people
can just end up getting killed
and then people just end up getting
killed. Could happen. Could escalate, can't it?
But I would love to smack that damn up,
bro. Oh, who does he think he is, bro?
some [ __ ] chubby mixed race guy, bro.
Yeah, he ain't about nothing.
Like, he ain't about [ __ ] all, bro.
That's what makes me laugh.
He said he was going to cut my dick off
and send it to my mom. Cut my dick off,
feed it. I think he said he was going to
He said he was going to cut my dick off,
feed it to my mom, and send it to my
mom. Feed it to me and then send it to
my mom. said,
"But he ain't about that life, bro. I
called him a fat I called him a fat homeless Simpson."
You know what I'm saying? They start Who
started all of this, Grezy? It wasn't
me, was it? I wasn't behind all of this.
They started it with me in it.
They [ __ ] started it with me.
Yeah, they [ __ ] started it with me, man.
I didn't start it, bro.
Yeah, but who start who started it though?
She'd thought, "Oh, let me go back to
America. No one knows my name. No one
knows anything about me."
And look what happened. You know,
you know what I'm saying?
I wish I said no. Now,
imagine that. You know, when being
offered the number, I wish I said no,
Reeves. I actually wish I said no.
Imagine all of that [ __ ] that could have
been saved that year by just saying no.
If I had just said no, then I would have
just been with these other people and
[ __ ] I would have been with these other people and
yeah I don't want one night stands you know
I want lovey
love and affection
you know what I'm saying yeah
now I want more
I want Oh yeah. Yeah.
You're my mama. No one else is. You're that one.
Once someone meets me, they're stuck
with me for life.
They're stuck with me for life, matey. Yeah,
>> they're stuck with me for life, lad.
God bless you then.
You keep putting them back. Yeah. Imagine
that, Nicolo. Me, USA, Izzy, in
Disneyland. Imagine Virgin Boy's reaction.
No, that's like [ __ ]
He'd kill He'd kill himself, isn't it?
He would kill himself.
He would actually kill himself. He'd be
like, "No, it's not a me and Britney
situation." Then he'd like stab probably
start stabbing himself.
He probably start stabbing himself. No,
it was uh it was um Michael Myers and
Halloween, I think it was.
No, it was Michael Myers and Pennywise.
Every time Penny Wise gets defeated,
Greasy, he keeps coming back.
That clown was a nasty bastard. It
Yeah, he was a nasty bastard. That um
that that clown was nasty, bro.
He was a nasty bastard. That clown.
See you in your dreams.
Do you ever want to see you in your dreams?
Let go. Be afraid.
Do you remember that one?
That's what the clown says, isn't it?
I'll drive you crazy and I'll kill you all. No.
Do you remember when he got defeated?
The clown got defeated.
So, how do you know it's my mama, Nicolola? Yeah.
Signal Peter Belly's mama.
These are the eyes and the hair. Yeah.
No, you can't get rid of me.
I don't know why I used to come out with
all these funny sayings like what's a
what a lovely sight taking a baby away
from its mother.
I was speaking to this woman from Brazil
but she's back in Brazil now. So
now I'll never know.
Now I'll never know.
Why do women in Brazil never say they've
got boyfriends? Um, Nicolola, you never
get that with um, Brazilians and you
never get it with Muslims. And I think
the reason is is because with Muslim
people, it's against their religion to lie.
In their religion, they can't lie.
They're they're supposed to um, respect
men. So, if you if you go out in London
and you approach someone that's Muslim
or they never say it. You never get it.
And that tells you how you know that
these people are full of [ __ ] Because
you would speak to someone from [ __ ]
India or a Muslim person or someone from
Brazil or Colombia or anywhere like that
and they never ever say it. You never
get it. Even though they say no, but you
never get that response. Yeah. Soon as
you speak to someone that's a westernized [ __ ]
I get a boyfriend. I'm sorry. I don't
think I could deal with that, bro. In
America, I don't think I could deal with
that cuz that's what they do in America.
That's how they say things in America.
You say I said it as well. They'll be
like, "Oh, I'm sorry." And it's like
it's like a patronizing thing. Like they
will say something and they'll say, "I'm
sorry." at the end of it in like a
patronizing kind of way. So, if he was
in America, they be like, "I've got a
boyfriend. I'm sorry." I don't think I'd
be able to like listen to that [ __ ]
bro. I [ __ ] that. You know what I mean?
Yeah. It's like a patch. It's sort of
patronizing in a way.
Does that make sense, Grezy? What I'm
trying to say,
oh, I just killed your dog. I'm sorry.
[ __ ] off, man. Yeah, you will be [ __ ]
sorry, you [ __ ]
Yeah, exactly. I I know, I know, I know,
I know, I know. But I'm just saying that
that boyfriend thing is [ __ ] It's
just a It's just a westernized MPC thing
that they say.
You know, it's just an NPC thing that
they say. You know what I mean, Grezy?
And I'm sick of people saying, "How do
you know that they're pretending?" How
do you know that they're pretending?
You know, they always say that, oh, how
Because it's obvious
their boyfriend's never with them. Most
of the people I know are single.
Um, you know, they're clubbing school
early hours, their boyfriend's not with
them. It's common sense. It is generally
generally generally common sense.
And if they really had a boyfriend, they
would just walk away.
Like some of them will sit there and
speak to you and then they'll say, "Oh,
I have a boyfriend." No, that's what
they'll say. They'll say that they have
a boyfriend. Which if they actually had
a boyfriend, they wouldn't sit there and
start talking to you. They would just walk off.
Do you understand what I'm saying? So
people that actually have boyfriends
probably wouldn't sit there and start
talking to you and then say it. They
just walk off or just say it and walk off.
So that's how you know them ones are certified bullshitters.
Them ones are certified bullshers
cuz you wouldn't entertain another
person if you was in a relationship.
You know, I had somebody say that they
were seeing someone. I said, "Oh, give
me a number anyways." Apparently,
they're seeing someone. They said they
were on holiday. I said, "Where you on
holiday to?" They didn't reply. It's
just the same [ __ ] And they they live
up the road from me as well.
It doesn't matter how many times you go
out in this country, how many times you
try in this country, it's always going
to be the same old.
It's always going to be the same old
boring. Once you've met one, you've met
them all. Once you've watched the film,
Once you've watched the film, you you've
seen the film a million times.
I'd rather not, lad.
That's why there was times I never used
to go out for like six weeks. Yeah, I
think that was my record. I didn't go
out for six, seven weeks. Done it a few
times. Six, seven weeks I would go out
because of it out drinking.
What about nightclubs, Nicolo, that you
pay like £30 to get in? Do you reckon
you'll hear it there? Like say you go to
Fabrics now and you
So you got fabrics and you pay £30 to uh um
to go in.
Do you reckon you'll still hear I've got
a boyfriend there as well?
Yeah, one second.
She said, "I'm at the airport. When I
get back to Brazil, we'll talk." Okay.
So it seems like the only ones you can
get slight interest from is Brazilian
people and [ __ ] Chinese people by the
sounds of it.
They're the only ones you can
sort of get anything from. One sec. I'll
answer your question in a minute.
That's the only ones you can get any
sort of thing out of.
What happened when when in um
boyfriend I think boyfriend boy I've
been fabrics a few times. I was going to
go like a month ago, but um they were
trying charge like £35 to get in and I
weren't paying that and I'd already got
like four or five members, but um he uh
I think it was boyfriend [ __ ] as always.
It would have been that. Yeah.
I don't know what happened to him. I
lost his number when my phone got stolen.
Yeah. Indian Ben, you know too much, don't you?
You know too much.
Why? What's your opinion, Nicolola? Why
these people stalk me every day? Like
Red Star, Jamie Thompson, the Virgin.
What? Why do you think it is? Like
what's your honest opinion? I think it's
it's jealousy. Like they even stalk me
on Reddit as well. Like they keep
refreshing like the page and like they
actually relentlessly stalk me on that as well.
And I'm thinking, bro, like I don't
understand it. If you was really ugly
and you were all of these things, then
would they just leave you alone?
That's that's what I I think makes
sense. Like I that's what I think makes
What else? Because what else could it
actually be? Like other than cuz they
don't they don't just they actually
stalk me on Reddit. Like like I said,
they they do it relentlessly. They don't
stop, bro. Like they will sit there all
day on Reddit refreshing that page,
right, until they see me post something
and then they'll start messaging me.
It's like, what the [ __ ] bro? Then they
they will sit on it all day. But you're
the ugly one. That's good. Doesn't make
sense. They say that you're all the
things that if you really was that, then
they would just move on with their life, you know?
Of course, it's jealousy, bro. 100%.
What else could it possibly [ __ ] be,
bro? They take stalking to the next
[ __ ] level, lad. Yeah.
I mean, look at that [ __ ] Jamie Thompson.
Have you seen his [ __ ] face?
But yeah, of course it is. Jennify 100%.
He hates the fact that he's still a [ __ ] virgin.
Dominates the fact that he's still a [ __ ] virgin.
Oh, but if he does this every day, how
is he ever going to lose it? How is he
ever going to get [ __ ] laid? If he
does this every day, bro, he's never
going to get laid, is he? You know,
I was so I felt so bad that I was going
to give him a football tip so we could
actually finally lose it. Finally lose
that V card
that's been favoring him andounding him
for 31 years.
You know, cuz I'm not, like I said, I'm
not a narcissist, bro. I can't sit there
and let somebody I've met seven times
die a virgin. It's not right.
You know, I was I was [ __ ] since the
[ __ ] age of 17, you know,
not a [ __ ] virgin like him.
I message USA is his friend on
Instagram. She's still not replied, but
she's put a story up.
It's mad at it.
I hate these ignorers. You know,
[ __ ] hate these ignorers.
You really want to know what I think?
Yeah, I hate these [ __ ] ignorers. No,
no, I don't remember that.
Oh yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah. I was
approaching the American right and I got
uh some American and I got some message
from Charles Ford Charles Edwin Ford.
And he's like uh yeah why I said are you
still with that Morgan?
And I said, um, and before I got to
reply back, he had blocked me. So,
something went on there, did it?
Something went on there. I said, "Oh,
you still with this Morgan character?"
Yeah, that's when I was at what when I
was approaching the American. Yeah.
That um that American said, "Oh, I'm not interested.
She she messaged me back saying, "Hi,
thanks for the offer, but sorry, I'm
just not interested."
Haven't we heard that a million times
before? People not interested. But
Reddit tells us that life changes.
Yeah, how could I forget that, bro? I
remember that. I exact I remember
exactly where that was as well.
But people on Reddit say that you just
never know. You just never know what
life can throw at you.
Well, I've got a pretty good idea.
Yep. Not interested.
Yeah, I remember that. Yeah, they were
going they were going back to America
the next day, I think, or something.
Where did they say they were from in
America? I forget. I think it was
Where was it now?
Maybe it was like Alaska or something.
They want they want people with a million subscribers.
A million subscribers on YouTube.
Yeah. Even if you have money, looks,
nice clothes, they're just not
interested in this country.
Yeah. They ain't interested in this country, lad.
Mad it. Yeah, I do remember that though.
I do remember that.
How could I not, bro?
But you never know what life throws at
you. Life changes.
That's what people Reddit say anyways.
Makes you wonder, doesn't it?
Maybe I'll just try and get this
Brazilian woman and let's [ __ ] [ __ ]
off to Brazil. You know,
that could be a shout.
Yep. You just have to keep trying, bro.
Just keep trying.
Now, my mom's been doing the lottery for
donkeys years. She's never won it,
but you never know. One day. You
probably got more chance of winning the
lottery to be honest. I should start do
I've never done the lottery before.
Maybe I should do it. You know,
you never Yeah, you got you've actually
got more chance of winning the lottery.
You've actually got more chance of
winning the lottery.
You actually have So yeah,
you remember the Chinese licked my ass,
Nico? She's so lucky I had a bath before
meeting her. No,
if I didn't have a bath, she'd be
licking [ __ ] [ __ ] off my ass. She is
so lucky that I had a bath
because no one's ass is always going to
stay clean [ __ ] hours after cleaning it. Yeah.
Yeah, I do.
I just put my approaches on my other channel.
What do you think will happen if I go
out today, Greasy? Do you think it's
worth a try?
Like, you need to you need to Let me ask
Greavvesy cuz I I know that Greavves is
not not a troll, right?
You need to really sell yourself to me
here, right? Pretend I'm a customer. So,
say we're in court, right? Let let me
let me give my let my brief speak first,
right? I don't want to go out anymore
because it's always the same [ __ ] It's
been the same [ __ ] for years and it's
always the same thing when I go out and
I've had bad experiences. Now, you need
to what what what defense does your brief have
to make me go out? You you need to try
to say say that like I'm say I'm um
say I'm a judge. You you need to
convince me. You need to really sell
yourself to me here.
then make me make me think that it's
going to be worth it me going out, you know,
cuz if you don't do it, then I I I I
can't go out. Simple.
What makes you so sure that the next
time I go out, all of the things that's
been happening for years stops?
What makes what would make you so sure
that this time is is is the time.
No. Come on.
Come on. You can.
They say they're just not interested in this country.
All of your prime being wasted. your prime years.
I was actually very disappointed today.
I woke up.
I didn't want to wake up today, man. I'm
I'm sad. I wanted to not wake up today,
but I always wake up. It's [ __ ]
It will never change. Never. Never it.
So, you're not going to sell yourself to me uh come on that [ __ ]
[ __ ] Right, I'm gone. I might be back
later with some McDonald's.
I need to watch some videos. So, what the [ __ ]
When you finally lose it, Virgin M.
Oh, my legs.
So, might be back later with some
McDonald's. I will be back later. So, yeah.