Well,
sorry. I just been talking to Morgan's
friend all day. So, I just been a bit
busy, you know, trying entertaining
these [ __ ] keyboard warriors.
Bro, one sec. [ __ ]
[ __ ] for that. Yeah, man.
This again, you've got memory loss.
You're telling me that I need to go to
this park. How many times have we done
this, bro? How many times have we gone?
I told a guy if he wants to meet me, he
can come to Stratford and go live. Let's
go on this now. Yeah. Mhm.
If he wants me, he can come to
Stratford. Why am I going to a park that
I've already been to two times? I'm not
doing it, bro. [ __ ] all this [ __ ]
If he wants me, he knows where I am.
Right. You can go live in Stratford. I
ain't going to no park. [ __ ] off, bro.
[ __ ] idiot. Um, why am I going to
that park? I've already been there two times before.
Again, selective memory. [ __ ]
disabled community. [ __ ] hell, bro. [ __ ] hell.
Oh. Oh, Franklin. Poor Franklin. Yeah.
But yeah, bro. I'm coming off this [ __ ]
as well after after today.
Oh, no. I just had to try these.
I'll be in bed, bro. Sleeping too.
Oh, be chilling tomorrow as well. I
think I left the house today.
But yeah, I'm not entertaining this keyboard warrior.
It's the same [ __ ] with him. come on
YouTube, everyone has to go to him. When
people go to him, he doesn't show up.
I'm not doing it anymore, bro. I'm not a
[ __ ] This is what retards do. So,
like when [ __ ] I find it offensive
when people are, oh, go, you know.
Yeah, I've already got a football bet.
I've already got a 50 double. I got both
teams to score draw.
But yeah, I'm not a [ __ ] bro, like these people.
Mr. depressing, bro. Come on.
Speaking to USA is his friend all day.
We're actually getting along, you know.
It's quite good. Yeah.
No, I'm just speaking to a friend, bro.
We're just talking. No,
I messaged them [ __ ] ages ago and
they replied back. So, I'm just speaking to them.
No, not at all. No.
Yeah, man. It's It's weird. Her friend
is like talking to me like normally and [ __ ]
We've been talking all day really like
sending voice notes.
What a [ __ ] Mazda.
I'm I've been speaking to USA is his
friend all day, Nicola.
I've been speaking to her day in and day out. Yeah.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah. I just been speaking to her friend
Nicolo and um
I said I said like we just been voice
noting each other and I said to her,
"Oh, is it is it a normal thing in
America to to before kissing someone say
that you're going to be their 25th?" And
she's like, "She did that? Really?" I
was like, "Yeah,
we're just having chats and [ __ ] is it?
Sending voice notes and [ __ ]
We've been talking all day.
That's why I've been um She's like, "She
really did that?" Oh, man. That's She
did. I said I I said, "Yeah,
I'm not sure, bro. Ask the Indonesian fella."
You know, I was laughing at you in a cinema, Nico.
I was laughing my ass off. Like you know
when I ask you questions and you go
along with it and you said oh USA was
your mama but she wanted to keep it a secret
cuz I can just imagine you yeah like
trolling like just sat there trolling
like oh it's funny as [ __ ]
It's just it's funny as [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
She wanted to keep it a secret. [ __ ] madness.
You know, it's what we do day in and day out. Yeah,
I actually saw it uh watching Superman.
Oh, I'm stuffed.
But yeah, I'm speak I'm speaking to a friend.
She said she might come to the UK.
I said this should have come to this,
you know, you saying all of this. It
should have this shouldn't have come to
all of this.
You know, you and [ __ ] dad and [ __ ]
Oh, this Scottish one replied saying,
"I'm not in
I'm not in London anymore, babes."
Well, duh. You're back in Scotland.
I'll say I'll come to school. Oh, I did
get I did get a reply.
No, I got a Chinese.
But yeah, friends, we've been messaging
all day, me and her friend. She says she
speaks to her every day. And that was
the one on the phone to her. You know,
when I was having when I was in the
restaurant with her. Yeah. Someone
called her and it was her. She's like,
"Oh, I I knew about you before she'd met
you. when she met you and after she met
you. It's like everyone knows about me.
She's like, "Oh, I'm surprised it took
you this long to find me." She was like,
"Oh, I've been expecting you."
She's like, "Yeah."
She's like, "Oh, I only knew about you."
And she was like, "Um,"
she was like, "Uh, yeah. Yeah, you told
me about all about you." And I said,
"Oh, what what did she say?" She's like,
"Oh, uh, she just said that she missed
she she she she met uh she said to me
she met this guy and she wasn't she
wasn't feeling him." I said, "Did did
she tell you all the things that she done?
They're coming on and she said, "Yeah,
she told me all that, you know.
Yeah, they all know. How do they all
know about me?"
She said, "Yeah, I knew about you."
He was just expecting to be in it. Yeah.
Yeah. It's a madness, bro. It
Yeah. That's who it was,
who it was. Yeah.
Do you want my number? Yeah.
Who's my mama? Nicolola
Lane is my mommy. Is it? Huh?
You wanted to keep it a secret. Tig not
Peter Belly's mama.
You're a troll. You are. You're a troll.
You're just a troll. Yeah. Signal Pet
No. [ __ ] that poor game of soldiers. I'm
leaving. [ __ ] that. Good luck to you,
mate. I'm leaving.
She sent me four voice notes. This USA
Izzy's friend. [ __ ] hell, bro. She
says they're best friends and they talk every day.
>> Oh, friend. Bren [Music]
No, she did know about me. She knew all
about me. You said I already knew about you
when um before you met. Um before you
met, when you met and after you met
Yeah, they knew she knew all about me.
She I was expecting you to message me.
It took you so long.
But she doesn't block. She actually
seems all right.
You seem like a pretty good [ __ ] I
think we'll get on just fine.
You know what? I'm I'm going to say that
to her. You know that. You seem like a
pretty good [ __ ]
I think we'll get on just fine. Yeah.
Yeah. I'll say you seem like a pretty
good [ __ ] You remember that one?
Do you remember? What? Okay. Okay,
Nicol, if you're if you're a long-term
fan. Yeah. What was Nons's and Nons
leg's dad's name? What was his real
Make love to her friend.
Her friend's mid, bro. Her friends Her
friend's mid, but she seems all right.
No, no, no. Sorry. What did he change
his name to?
What did he change his name to? Remember
he changed his name to try and hide them
crimes that he did. Dirty nons.
I don't know if you remember
taking a b M Jonathan Robinson.
Mick Jonathan Robinson.
He also immigrated to Australia
when he was on the run. Yeah.
Oh, Philip Campbell from Leads. That's
the one that had him up against the wall
and broke his arm. Yeah, it leads. Yeah. Oh, [ __ ]
Philip Campbell leads. Yeah.
His stepdad was from Leeds. Yeah. Philip Campbell.
What's his name? His name. Yeah.
I was speaking to her friend. That's
weird, is it, Nicola? I knew all about you.
I was like, "Oh, did you now?
Did you know? Um, Mick Gold. Mick Goldmith. Yeah,
Mick Jonathan Robinson.
But yeah, good luck for to you tomorrow, mate.
I won't be trying, but good luck to you.
Good luck to you, lad.
It's not your problem. It's It's not my
problem anymore. was yours.
No, I don't I don't watch any I don't
watch the Virgin.
I stopped watching The Virgin days ago
and Red Star. No, I'm not I'm not
interested in keyboard warriors, bro. I
don't even know why I started
entertaining them again, lad.
I'm not interested
in sad pathetic keyboard warriors that
do this every day and don't get paid for
it. They're just losers.
sad, deprived losers. I'm not interested.
Just like I'm not interested in this Arsenal Mark. >> Yeah,
I'm not interested in jealous people.
Well, it's easy. You go up and you
approach someone and you get a number.
Let me see what USA is friends saying. One sec.
If they seem uninterested, I just leave.
Yeah, I just leave. Yeah, I do the same.
One sec. One sec.
And I was speaking to Morgan's friend.
I've been speaking to Morgan's friend
all day, Grezy. She said, "Oh, what was
your body count?" And you said to
Morgan, "Free." I said, "Now it's five
excluding escorts." She's surprised.
Bro, you're lucky I've even had someone,
mate. [ __ ] me. They go on like you can
just go out and get laid.
She's like that anyone would think,
right? I I I was actually speaking to
someone earlier on Instagram from these
R channels and he's still a [ __ ] virgin.
I mean, you can't I mean, you if you if
you even at this age, if you had a body
count of [ __ ] three at this age,
you're lucky, bro. You're lucky to get
anything in this country.
It's [ __ ] impossible to get laid.
They don't understand because they can
just go out and get sex whenever they want.
They can go on Tinder whenever they want
and you can't just get laid greasy.
You can't even get a conversation out of
the [ __ ] let alone get a [ __ ] sex. Madness.
Like you can just go out and [ __ ]
just get laid madness.
Getting laid, man.
At least I got a reply from someone in it.
Is that not at all? Yeah.
Who? What? Her friend.
That's That combo's got to be so weird
cuz she's probably going to speak to her
later and be like, "Oh yeah, I've been
speaking to that guy you met like 3
years ago. We've been speaking all day. Yeah,
imagine that, bro. [ __ ] me.
Yeah, [ __ ] her. Give her a baby. And then
every time there No, no, no. You don't
understand. I I was supposed to [ __ ] her
sister and give her sister a baby. So
then she will be the auntie to the baby
and every time she's holding baby Peter,
she'll be thinking of me. [Laughter]
Isn't that right, baby?
Like a like like a cross name in it and [Music]
was funny, isn't it?
So you can baby it away from it.
You and your little ways.
[ __ ] hell, bro. Why is this [ __ ]
messaging me all day? [Laughter]
All right. Hey, listen. Listen, Joker.
Come on your real account, bro.
Come on your real account, you [ __ ]
Come on your real account. Come on now.
Come on. Come on.
She thinks she thinks it's USA's friend
thinks it's fun. She thinks it's
she thinks it's disgusting that I've used escorts.
That's not disgusting, man. So, wait.
They they don't give you sex and then
they go mad when you then use an escort
and get sex. They want you with nothing.
These women, I'm telling you, mate,
these bastard women.
Wow. She says she says she's never been told before. Yeah.
Oh, do you remember that one? Nicolo,
do you remember when I used to say that
in it? Yeah. Yeah. Do you remember that?
Do you remember the one in the park that
I was shouting at? [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] pair of [ __ ] Yeah.
Exactly. Well, yeah.
I'm going to tell I'm going to tell
Morgan I'm going to tell Morgan's friend
what I get from the escorts or
Yeah, man. Sorry, man. I'm just speaking
to her friend.
Yeah, I did say that, didn't I? Uh, Nicola,
she could give baby P a milk.
Yeah, I did say that. So, I'm talking to Morgan's friend.
Sorry, man. Hold on.
One sec. One sec, bro. Hold on. I'm
trying to speak to this [ __ ]
little Peter H straight. Oh, bless you. Oh, bless.
Oh, bless you. Yeah, I'm just talking to
um USA is his friend. She's like, "Oh,
she did that." I said, "Yep, she's a nasty bugger."
She's a nasty bugger. That one is itsy.
Oh, you're a nasty bugger.
Have you ever heard that saying? Have
you ever heard that saying,
"You nasty bugger."
She's like, "Oh my god, she really did that."
I said, "Yeah."
She said I'd be her 25th and she looked
at me like a serial killer. Yeah, you
nasty bugger. I'm a nasty bucker. Yeah,
these women are [ __ ] Nico like you can
give baby Peter milk.
When are you going to grow up? When are
When are you going to grow up, mate? Huh?
Let me reply to her. Hold up.
I know, bro.
Yeah, I was just speaking to her friend.
She could give baby Peter some milk.
Little Peter's child lounge put straight
on the roulette. Yeah,
that is jokes, bro. You can give baby Peter milk. Oh,
she was like, "Oh, she did that."
Yeah. She said, "What the fuck?" I said, "Yeah,
rape victims." A lot of him. You're
copycats, bro. I swear down.
You almost look like nonsense saying
Chev Cole's fit to fit in. Yeah.
If you don't like Shville Cole, you're
gay. That's exactly what a copycat would
say with no mind of their own.
I think this is immature, bro. Yeah. [Laughter]
Oh [ __ ] Yeah. [Applause]
>> Yeah. I hated me. I was just telling her
friend all about her boobies and stuff.
Oh, sound threatened.
Do you want my opinions if uh they're all guns?
They're all guns.
I'm telling her about her boobies and stuff.
Do you reckon I'll come up? Do you
reckon I'll come into the conversation? H
do you reckon I'll come in do the next
conversation of theirs? Yeah.
My friend had to go to Thailand because
of you. Oh yeah, I did say that, didn't
I? [ __ ] dirty chunks.
you sick. You're sick and twisted, [ __ ]
I'm sick of twisted for you. Yeah.
It's funny, isn't it?
Oh, the [ __ ] lot of them.
You need to grow up, Joker. Seriously.
Do remember this one. I love the [ __ ]
I love you all.
Do you remember Fraser and SL?
You remember Fraser and SL cuts, man. Cuts. Yeah.
Do you remember? Do you remember when he
come on? Yeah. And he was trying to
troll me and he thought I was never
going to find him and I said,
what did I say? I think I said
I think I said Somerset now sl. And I
put all this [ __ ] out there in it. Somerset now.
And he must have thought, "What the
fuck?" Yeah, we found that [ __ ]
bro. The [ __ ] dirty tri. Yeah. Somerset now.
He was like, "You're [ __ ] mad. You are slow. Some soul." Yeah.
Yeah, bro. Yeah.
But he had several ch, you know, him.
Yeah. He actually had several chances to
hit me. Like we was walking for like 15
minutes and he had a bite. I feel like
he had it in his head. Yeah. That he's
going to do me in that and then he just
he just bailed out
and he just bailed out it. Yeah. Yeah, man.
I had a lucky escape that day, though.
I had a lucky escape.
It was a [ __ ] [ __ ] trying to get
back. I had to get an Uber to Elen and
then Elen to Oxford, Turkish. And then
he said, "You you did me dirt day."
He said, "You done me dirty."
That's what he said. Yeah.
That's my mama. >> Mhm. >> Yeah.
So, what if I was black then? Would I
get the women if I was black? Nicola.
I if I was just black and not like white
and I cold approached. Do you reckon I'd
give up the goodies?
That's who they give the goods to, is it?
>> Yeah, bro.
>> Yep, exactly. That's who they give their
goodies to. Ain't it? Their goodies.
That's who give the goods to.
That's who they give the goods to. Is it? Yeah.
[ __ ] my friend keeps messaging me.
You say he's his friend. Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, [ __ ]
Yeah, she sent me like six voice notes, bro.
[ __ ] hell. I'm trying to stay alive
and [ __ ] I've got this [ __ ] stupid
woman messaging me. Yeah,
you remember Monty Nicola?
He He got ruined over [ __ ] social
media, didn't it? Yeah.
His life got ruined over social media.
I don't give a [ __ ] Like what?
Who wants to make love? I don't care
what nons posts or any of that, bro. I
don't really care. I just know that all
he needs to do is lose his virginity and
get laid. And when he finally loses it,
all of this [ __ ] will stop. Once he gets laid
and he loses his virginity.
Yeah. If that happened to me. Yeah.
Let's just say that somebody that I'm
not with that I've been with before.
Let's just say that USA Izzy went with um
went with Virgin Boy.
you know, and he finally lost his
virginity or whatever. I don't I
wouldn't let it lie.
I couldn't let it lie, bro. You saw the
whole Izzy thing and [ __ ] Mark
Samson. I couldn't let it lie,
you know? That's that's how it all
that's just how like that's just how it
happened, bro. With me being the whole
thing. I couldn't let it lie.
I remember, bro. I remember I remember
exactly when it was. It was September. I
woke up at 4:00 in the morning and them
them [ __ ] were laughing at us. I
remember, bro. Them them them [ __ ] were
laughing at us. And I saw I saw Izzy.
I saw Izzy, bro. I saw Izzy in the chat.
And they were laughing at us, you know.
There was a buildup to this and I
thought, "Fuck this, mate." The [ __ ]
next day I was like, "Right, come on
then, you [ __ ] You want Victoria
[ __ ] park? Let's have it. Let's have
it here and now. Come on, cunt." Didn't
show up. Then I went again. Didn't show
up. You know, [ __ ] that, bro. Hell no.
You know, they're evil. They are evil.
Someone ever done that to me, bro, then
nah. [ __ ] that. [ __ ] [ __ ] that, bro.
And that was the mob of his kids as well.
Yeah. And it's it's his enemy as well.
It's not even like it's not even like um
she's just gone with another man and
she's moved on with with her life. She's
gone with an enemy. She's gone with
Monty's enemy, Rice. And obviously my
enemy is [ __ ] Virgin Boy, you know,
and and a few others, but you know, like
[ __ ] that. Are you [ __ ] mad?
I think I'd be going to jail, bro. [ __ ]
that. You I would go to jail, bro. Trust me. Yeah,
that happened to me, bro. [ __ ] that. Are
you mad? I'm going to jail.
Yeah, they are evil schools. Yeah,
a [ __ ] lot of them.
the [ __ ] lot of them, mate.
Do you think the dad will ever forget me? Nah.
They [ __ ] with the wrong man, didn't they, Nicola?
Yeah. And I was speaking to her friend
about this earlier and her friend kind
of understood. I was like, "You want to
[ __ ] around? You take my money, I'll
[ __ ] take yours.
You You want to take my money, I'll
[ __ ] take yours."
Remember that one? I think that one's a
banger as well. You take my money, I'll take yours.
Remember when that man said that? Yeah. Yeah,
that's him in life.
He just wants peace at his time of life, bro. Yeah.
You see what I mean? Yeah. Yeah.
Exactly. Yeah. It's true though, is it?
Mhm. They [ __ ] come to you, mate.
It's just the same. It's just the same.
Just different characters. It's the same
film, just different characters.
Just different characters. Yeah.
It's the same ending and it's the same beginning.
Now, let me use this energy. It's like
watching the same film. You know that
you already know the the start and the ending.
Uh, I'm just talking to USA is his friend.
We've been talking all day, voice noting
and stuff. We're both Scorpios as well. So,
you know what I could do? I've got an
idea, Nicola. If I got with a friend,
started getting all this money and now
he's 32. If I got all this money and
started hitting the gym and [ __ ] and say
I go and meet her, think of how jealous
she will get.
She would she would get that that would
get the [ __ ] jealous, isn't it? Yeah.
Oh, no. Obviously, I haven't met her,
bro. She lives in America.
Yeah, I think that's what I need to do
next time I go out is get the [ __ ]
paint out then.
Yeah, that'll be a good idea though. Is it Nicolola?
He says we're best friends.
Yeah, Steven Howard, I don't think
you're actually putting these bets on. I
think you're trolling me.
Can you prove it? I'll show you my football bet.
Do you remember Rock and Roller when he
said that he had faults over gambling? Nicolola,
he said he said he had faults.
He said he had he had um thoughts over gambling.
Suicidal thoughts. He said he's had
faults in it.
He said, "I've had thoughts."
That's mad, isn't it?
No, you haven't. Put These are my This
is my football bet. Look,
that's my football bet.
He said they can really [ __ ] up your life. Yeah.
No, he said it could really [ __ ] up your life.
You can you can see the damage in his
face when he says that, ain't it?
There you go.
I don't think he's actually putting
these bets on.
Yeah, he said he had faults.
I miss my mama, Nicolo.
I think that's why I reached out to her
friend. I didn't even realize that was
her friend. I'm missing my mama. Is that
normal to miss your mama?
I'm miss I'm missing my mama.
You can't see it. Oh my god. Show us
yours. Show us your bet.
Come on. I don't think Stephen Albert's
doing these bets.
Yeah, I done both. I've done both teams
to score no draw
and I put 50 quid on it
and kisses. Nicolai,
I'm going to start telling her friend
about her boobs. I think we're pretty
open with each other.
I started telling her friend that like I
only like [ __ ] and [ __ ] Yeah.
You know what I'm going to say to her?
I'm going to say to her friend, Grezy,
you know what? You seem like a pretty
good [ __ ] I think we'll get on just
fine. You know, despite all of the beef
and all of that [ __ ] I think you're a
you seem like a pretty good [ __ ]
I think we're going. It's fine. That's
all I'm going to say to her. Yeah.
Um, it's Fleetwood versus Olden. Both
score no draw and Colchester and Barrow
both score no draw. I stuck 50 pound on it.
Yeah. To hear her little voice, her
friend sounds a bit like her as well
because they're from the same place. Oh.
Yeah, I want my mama back because
you know I'm going going on your
daughter to touch you.
She says she doesn't say anything. She
just says, "Oh, the people that messaged
him just block him."
Yeah. I said I said your friend just met
her match, isn't it? It happens. It'll
happen to me one day if I carried on
[ __ ] with people. You'll meet your
match one day.
You'll meet your match one day
and your and your friend's match with me.
Dad to say,
you know, it could have been anyone else
and they would have been like, "Oh, [ __ ]
this. I don't care." Peter Belly. Once
you meet Peter Belly, you can't get rid
of Peter Belly.
Is that right, Grezy? Oh,
she said she doesn't hate you anything.
She just wants to be left alone.
I said left alone. You didn't want to be
left alone when you was hoovering up all
my money on steak dinners and fancy wine.
was you? You didn't want to be left
alone then, did you? You [ __ ]
Did you? You [ __ ] Yeah.
[ __ ] dogs. [ __ ] off.
Taking a baby away from it. Mama,
what's your favorite saying of mine again? Nicolola.
Yeah, Grezy, they don't like you. L J
don't like you. Timmy don't like you.
They still don't answer my question. If
I'm so much of a ma that tremolo says
and Lord J why have I been seen with
women and none of them out and none of them have
that's what I don't understand Nicolo
I'm such a m I'm so ugly right?
Yeah, I moan at women because they're
[ __ ] and I don't need to s. Yes, but
hold on. Haven't I been seen with all these women?
And none of these people have.
But I'm the m
you got understand the greasy, right?
These people on here are biased. Like
I've said, if you're not fat and ugly
like them and you got a better life than
them, they'll find reasons to dislike
you. So, whatever you do, they will
choose to believe what suits themselves.
That's why I don't go to I don't show
money anymore. I don't [ __ ] with that
mark because they just choose they
believe what they they want to
they believe what they want to believe.
Who do you think's better looking
Nicolo? Me or Virgin boy. Yeah, basically.
I mean, I know that I'm better looking
than that virgin, but he calls he calls
me the Ma.
I need to try to get this USA easy to
[ __ ] meet me again.
A lot of things kill them.
They say that you're better looking than
them, you got more money than them, and
you got a better life than them. And it
kills them. That's what Ronald Pump
said. He said, "Get off of YouTube. Live
your life. They'll never leave you
alone." And come to think of it, he was
right. They never leave me alone.
They're not leaving me alone, bro. He's
actually right. I don't have loads and
loads and loads of money now, but you
know, it doesn't matter, you know. But
yeah, he's It's true though, isn't it?
If you think about it, because from that
time frame, they've not left me alone. So, yeah. So, yeah,
it's true that Yeah. the the the Brazilian kiss,
the [ __ ] other one, the Albanian.
But they say that I'm the M.
I'm the mate. I'm the m
I'm the [ __ ] M. Am I matey? So why is
it if I'm such a M?
Yeah, it's an account that's not on here anymore.
If I'm such a manta
such a manta,
why can I show my face and none of these people can?
That's what I'd love to know. If I'm
such a manta,
why could I show my face but these people can't?
One second. Let me listen to what her
friend said. Hold on.
Sorry about that, bro. I was speaking to a friend.
Yeah, I was just speaking to a friend.
Oh, you [ __ ] ignoring me now? make love.
Yeah, I think Greavesy would get with
USA to piss me off.
If anyone on this community got with
USA, I'd [ __ ] fill them in. No one
touches my mama.
No one touches my mommy.
You know, that's my mama.
I think Grezy would do it.
I think you would do it, wouldn't you, Grezy?
No one touches my mama. It
that's my mama.
So, what happened with the whole Britney
thing and and nons wey? What happened there?
Why was she doing all of these things to non legs?
What was she doing to
Why is she doing this [ __ ] to launch legs? You reckon? Crazy.
What happened there with Nex and and Britney Grizzy?
What? Just don't want to know him.
Just don't want to know.
Didn't want to know you. Huh?
No. What was the problem with with
Britney and Nons? Greavvesy. What was the story?
Bongbas. What was the story between
Britney and Britney and Nlex? Huh?
Someone going to answer me or what?
She rejected his ugly ass.
I can answer that.
She rejected his [ __ ] ugly ass, didn't she?
She did, didn't she? She did, didn't
Didn't she, mate? Didn't she? Didn't
She rejected your ugly ass, mate.
She rejected his ugly ass. Oh, losing. Bless you.
Bless you then. Where's Joan? Yep. Yeah.
My mama left me.
will grievy. Will my mommy ever come back?
I'm hoping my mommy comes back. Oh,
you reckon my mommy will ever come back one day? Mama,
>> you've got a better You're better
looking than them. You've got a better
life than them and you got more money
than them and it kills them.
That's what Ronald Pump said to me, Grezy.
I think he was right, wasn't he, Ronald Pump?
So, I'm going to take his advice and
live my life off YouTube.
That's what he said to me, Ronald Pump.
Cuz these people keep [ __ ] with me
online, is it?
You're better looking than them. You've
got a better life than them and you got
more money than them and it kills them. Oh,
it kills these people on YouTube. He's
right, isn't it?
You're telling me that there was never
some truth to that, Greavvesy. Come on.
You're an impartial party.
Come on. You're Let's let's let's let's
ask you, Greavves, because obviously
you're an impartial party.
You're trying to tell me there was not
some truth to to what that guy said.
Who that was?
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Listen. Better. Better life.
You know what about better life?
And also I was showing thousands in cash.
I was also showing thousands in cash as
well which no one else has actually done
but me. So
and it's not even just about money. It's
a better life as well cuz all of the
places that I've been. So yeah, I guess
he was right. Yeah.
Well, I was showing thousands in [ __ ]
cash for [ __ ] sake.
I showed 5.7 in cash. [ __ ] me.
I'm trying to know where she went. My mama.
Yeah. Let me see.
Well, I don't travel anymore, but I did travel.
No, I think what he meant by a better
life is like places I've been going out
drinking every week,
you know. That's what he meant by a
better life, you know. Yeah,
that's what I think he meant by that.
But yeah, I don't travel anymore, but I did. So, yeah. Yeah,
but I beat these people at the money game. Mhm.
I even got a back payment when I when I
spent that four or five grand. I I
remember getting a back payment. Yeah,
he's not on him anymore.
That Scottish woman replied to me
grievy. She was like, "Oh, um,
I'm not in London anymore, babes."
So, I was thinking of flying saying,
"Oh, if I come to Scotland, but what if
they say, "Yeah, what am I going to do?
Just go all the way to [ __ ] Scotland?"
[ __ ] that, right?
I [ __ ] long.
[ __ ] that for a game of soldiers. Grezy,
[ __ ] that for a game of soldiers. I
don't know about that, mate.
So, how do you know USA was my mama Greavvesy?
I'm going to have a shower soon and get
my little stitch boxes.
Speaking to her little friend. Oh,
my little sticks boxes.
She keeps messaging me. USA is his friend.
What does she Why does she keep
messaging me, bro?
She says she's going to hurt me worse.
She said, "You sound so hurt by this,
but I I'm not going to lie, I can hurt you worse,
which is why I'm surprised we're getting
along right now."
She said, "I can hurt you worse." I
said, "No, you can't hurt me worse than my mama.
That's why I'm going to reply back.
No, you can't hurt me worse cuz you're
not my mother. One second.
One second. Let me Let me Let me One
second. Hold on.
I was just speaking to her.
Gra. I think I found a name. Mama,
how do you feel about that?
How do how do you feel about that? How
do you feel about that? Grezy think I
found any mama.
Bro, that accent is [ __ ] horrible,
bro. That American accent is horrible.
She tried taking a piss out of my accent
earlier, Grezy. And do you know what I
said? She's like, "Oh, well, dead
things." I said, "Oh, you're trying to
talk take the piss out of the way that I
talk. At least I don't sound like this.
Hey, hey, you dead ass, Charlie. [ __ ]
you dead ass right now. Like, please
stop it. Like, we don't sound like that.
You Someone that sounds like that can't
even be took seriously.
Who the [ __ ] talks like that, bro?
Imagine imagine being an English teacher
and sounding like that,
you know? [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] You know
what I mean? They're all [ __ ]
Ah, taking a bubin.
Taking a taking a bubin away from it. Mama. Uh.
Sorry, bro. No, I'm talking to her.
I'm talking to my new mama.
How cute is that, though?
I'm talking to my new mommy.
She said that she'll be my new mama. Nicola,
you're my mama. Nobody else is.
She says, "I'm worse than Morgan."
That's what she said. She said, "Oh,
honey, I'm much worse." I said, "No, you're not."
I said, "Come on then." Yeah. She said
she's much worse and [ __ ] I said, "Come on then.
found you, mother. Yeah.
I just know she's going to be [ __ ]
she's going to be on the phone. Right.
Right. She's going to she's going to be
on the phone to her later having a good
old laughing it at me. They're going to
be laughing ass.
What's the trap then? What's the trap,
do you think?
Oh, she said I'm a lot worse than her. I
said, "Why don't Why don't you call me
after work? Give it a whirl." She said,
"Oh, I've got lots of weed to smoke
after work, so I'll call you." I said,
"Why not?" Yeah, why not give it a whirl?
Oh, [ __ ] me, bro. This is going to be
funny, isn't it?
Nah, it's not going to work. It's not
We're actually getting along quite quite fine.
But they're probably going to be on the
phone later in it. Nicolo laughing at
me, mocking me. Is it?
We've been like we've been sending voice
notes for about 10 hours.
Monty lost his he Monty's life got
ruined on the same website. You can
watch Chucky. Imagine that. Greasy
social services got involved over the
same website you can watch [ __ ]
Mickey Mouse on and Spongebob.
How [ __ ] mad is that?
That is a madness to think about, isn't
it? And I and I I almost died over this
website. If I was in that day, LT would
have killed me. And that's why I said
like me, LT, LJ J, and Mark Samson, we
all need to meet up because life short
and we we need to all laugh at the near
the near misses, you know, the things
that could have happened like me being
killed. [ __ ] we can all just sit and
have a good laugh at have a good laugh about it, you know.
But it's not really no laughing matter,
is it? Like someone almost getting killed, you know?
Someone almost getting [ __ ] killed
over YouTube. Is it? Yeah.
Ow. Why you doo?
What do you think of that, Grezy?
Hopefully this football bet wins tomorrow.
She said I said, "Oh, so are you and her
both addicted to weed?" She said, "Who
do you think God could smoke all that weed?"
Now, I know what you're trying to do.
You're trying to get me chat with my
mama. Is that right, Nicolo? That's what
they're trying to do. Get me involved
with their mama. Huh? Yeah.
Them [ __ ] are laughing at us. They're
laughing at us, Grezy.
Them [ __ ] are laughing at us. Yeah.
One second. What is she saying? [ __ ] sake.
Yeah, she she's told her she's she's she
she's been messaging my mama. She she
said um yeah, I've spoke to She's told
her that she's been speaking to me all
day, but she didn't say anything.
That's funny, is it, bro? Yeah.
She said, "Oh yeah, she texted her
saying that we've been talking all day,
but she didn't say much.
De [ __ ] are laughing at us." I know it, bro.
I know they
Yeah, it's shy
them all laughing us. Don't let them
Don't let them tell you otherwise.
One second. Let me listen to the rest of it.
Okay, one second. Let me let me message
her back. This is going to be all day,
mate. [ __ ] you.
[ __ ] sake, bro. Mhm.
This has been day in and day out. This is crazy.
Taking a baby away from it.
Taking a baby away from its mom.
>> Oh, [ __ ]
>> I blame the LT for this, you know. Yeah. Oh [ __ ]
I'm back. Sorry, mate. Taking a baby
away from it, SP.
I'm not trolling, bro. I'm not trolling.
I've been messaging a friend all day. Yep.
Them [ __ ] were laughing at us.
It's so weird like when you're actually
speaking to someone's best friend
Greavesy and they and they calls all of
this. How cowardly is it?
Like how how cowardly is that? Think
Think about that. Thinking about Think
about this right now, Greaves. You're
speaking to your enabler's best friend.
you like think of how mad that actually
is and they're speaking from like a a
third party. Oh yeah, I spoke to her and
I told us about how we're speaking. You
know how [ __ ] up that is? That is mental, bro.
I didn't even do anything to the [ __ ]
You know that is that that I don't care.
Honestly, I don't care. But I'm just
explaining how [ __ ] up it is, you know?
That is that is mad. Never laugh.
That is mental, bro. Mental.
Because he's already found
Because he's already found his mama.
Oh, load of old bell.
Yep. You know that when time's a bit
tough, it's the boys in blue, mate. Now,
Mark Taylor was trying to [ __ ] troll
me earlier. I said, "Listen, listen. You
bully me. I've made you and your little boyfriend.
You can't get women." I know, man. But
I've had I've had more women than you
and I've proven it on YouTube. Besie
will uh be my guest. Yeah.
I know. I've only showed more women than
you people. Are you people
gen Let me Let me ask this question. Are
you generally disabled or do you act
like this on purpose?
Like this is a serious not not to you
grievy. Like this is this is a genuine
question. Are you actually disabled or
you just or do you act like it? And
and like I said, bro, before you get on
to the you're almost 30, you've been
saying I'm almost 30 for 4 years and I'm
still not 30. They've been saying I'm
nearly 30, Nicolo, for ages
and I'm still not 30. So it can't have
been that near, can it? you know,
you know, and I've already had a woman,
plenty of women, but again, whatever you
show these people on here, they they
never um seem to remember if they don't
like you in it.
I think they are definitely disabled. I
done a video to L J ear earlier and he
done a video right [ __ ]
talking about something
like than what we were [ __ ] what we
on they they are proper disabled on here
bro you show more money than them they
call you skin you show more women than
them they say that you can't get women
they they're just they're just they're just disabled
they're they're just disabled you You know, you know,
and I'm speaking to a woman now,
actually. Yep. She's my mama's best friend.
No, you've not shown more money than me.
Not in cash. No one's shown more money
than me in cash. You've not shown
[ __ ] more than £5.7,000
in cash. No, you haven't.
No, you haven't, mate. And there was no
proof that that that was actually their
money. Like, that's not even me [ __ ]
saying that, lad. So,
um, no, they're still together.
And me saying showing you with women
mean [ __ ] all. Well, it does when you're
saying that I've never been with a woman
and I can't get women. So, actually, it does.
But I try not to get into debates with
these people because they're just disabled.
And there was no proof that money was
theirs as well.
Yeah. Exact. Yeah. This is what I mean
by they're disabled, right? They ask you
to show money. Show money. Show cash.
Show money. Show cash. And then when you
show them money, they And then when they
can't show anything, they're like, "Oh,
well, people don't carry cash." Well,
we're not supposed to carry cash.
They're disabled. It's cuz they ain't
got cash. They ain't got nothing. You
know, and now I'm skin. I'm nowhere near
skin. Again, you're talking about yourself.
Again, self projecting. You don't know
how much money I have.
You are the ones that spend all day
every day on YouTube. Can't get off it.
Like, you know, the skin ones. You
people are skin.
It's been the same three, four people
doing what you've been doing for [ __ ]
years, mate. Calling people what you are
yourselves. You don't get bored of it.
You don't think, "Fuck, let me just get
a life instead of coming on YouTube
every day calling people what I am."
Like, do not ever say that to yourself.
Do not get bored of it. Like, I was
asking Mark Samson this as well.
You call people skin cuz you are skin.
That's why you call people skin cuz you're skin. You know, you know. M
>> and people not showing more money than me, bro.
I'm speaking to my mommy.
I like my mommy's friend, Nicolo. Is that wrong?
Okay, bro. Well, if I'm skinn get off of
YouTube and live your life, then Mr.
I've got all of this money. If you if
you people have got all of this money,
why do you spend all day on YouTube
doing what you do?
If you've got all of this money, right?
You got all this money and everyone
else's skin. Get off of YouTube. Live
your life. Everyone's skin. We're skinn.
I'm skinn. Yeah. Yep. Yep. Get off of
YouTube and live your life. But you
can't do that because you are the people
that are on benefits that are skin.
That's my whole point is you're talking about yourselves.
That's the whole point I'm trying to make.
is you're actually talking about yourselves.
Yeah, you keep telling yourself that.
Anyways, bye-bye. Now, this is a proper
disabled community, bro.
It's actually a disabled community.
It actually is.
That Chinese was nice.
I'm starting to like my mommy's best
friend, Nicolola. Is that normal?
Do you remember Monty Greasy?
Why? When I used to ask him the question
and he would say the opposite. I would
say, "Why do they keep calling me skin?"
And he'd be like, "Because they are
skin." Like everything I'd ask him, he'd
say the opposite. And I'd be like, "Why
does Bomb keep calling me ugly?" And
he's like, "Because Bomb's ugly."
Do you remember? Do you remember that? I
don't know if you ever noticed. I used
to do it on purpose cuz it was funny. He
said, "Cuz ugly."
Like stuff like that. I don't know if
you ever noticed I done that.
Do you remember that one? Uh, Grezy,
why why did thingy Why did Nons call me
a virgin? Because he is a virgin. He is
a virgin. Do you remember that one?
All right, Nicolo, I've got a question.
Yeah, you still there? Tell me you're
there. And I'm I'm going to tell you
something that I find strange. You'll
get these women that take ages to reply.
Like no reply. And as soon as you give
them a little call, it changes. Like
they either block straight away or
they see the message straight away. All
from a little call. It's crazy, isn't it?
It's like they see it straight away.
It changes everything once you once you
press that call button. M
It just changes, you know. Mhm. Jesus.
She said that you've met your match with
me, not Morgan.
That's what she said.
She said, um, you think you've met your
match with Morgan? No, Morgan met her
match with me. That That's the
difference. She said, "You've met your
match with me now."
I love this [ __ ] though. I'm saying I
love this [ __ ] Yeah.
about that, bro. Yeah, their voice
notes. Their voice notes. We're sending
voice notes to each other. I know M I
didn't meet my match with Morgan. Morgan
met her match with me. That's the
difference, you know.
I love it.
One sec. One sec.
Hey bro, I'm not sorry man. I'm [ __ ]
nah. I'm speaking to a friend. We're
sending voice lights. Imagine it ended
up in death. Grezy,
imagine it ended up in death. I found a
new mama. Leave me alone, you know.
Tell her to come and do the chat.
Oh, you uh Chinese Izzy keeps texting
me. Steven Howard
[ __ ] Is he?
She keeps texting me saying, "Hi, dear."
She said, "Oh, I'm surprised to know I
was her best friend."
How the [ __ ] was I supposed to know you
was her best friend? and she doesn't
have you up on any social media. How was
I supposed to know that you're her best friend?
How was I supposed to know that?
It all changes when you press that call
button. Is it? It all changes.
This is Tom Woods. This
Steven Harvard account is Tom Wood. Yeah.
I just messaged her about her boobs and [ __ ] [Laughter]
I said to her friend like, "You don't
realize how crazy I am." But I was
saying, "I know you're Scorpio as well,
but you don't realize I am [ __ ]
crazy, bro." But trust me, that's what I
was saying to her. Yeah,
I'm a crazy [ __ ] One second.