go down. I'm down. [Music] Oh [ __ ] Oh. First down.
Let's knock it out.
But yeah, as I said, you need to um you
to pack the gambling in. You don't want
to end up like the skin bird yet.
Freaking hell, man. Trust me every month knowing
I'm um tomorrow as well. Who's that? Too much, man. Wow. [ __ ] B.
other people for [ __ ] that [ __ ] boyfriend [ __ ] Let's
go out here. I [ __ ]
is [ __ ] [ __ ] language. [ __ ] sake.
I happen to translate [ __ ] Portuguese.
They don't understand English. Oh, [ __ ]
Even they're displaying like
funny behavior now. Um,
my football bet um
my football bet never come in.
I'm just speaking to someone in Brazil
that I met like two weeks ago. I have
nothing to like translate Portuguese and
I mean even they're giving off like [ __ ] behavior.
They're giving off like [ __ ] behavior
as well like being [ __ ] like they are here.
Sad sad sad.
I was on the phone to Morgan's friend
for 5 hours. Joe.
Yeah. I've been speaking to her since
yesterday. We were just talking to each
other for like 5 hours on the phone earlier.
>> You miss out on the uh a lot of [ __ ]
You know that, right?
On the phone for like 5 hours.
I was like, "Oh [ __ ] we on the phone
for 5 hours, you know." But um
but yeah, this person's giving off like behavior.
Well, I told you, bro. Nothing happens
with them numbers. That's me, bro. I'm ded.
I was trying to help u our good friend
Kieran break the Gambon cycle earlier.
I was telling him about cycles and how
you need to break them and [ __ ] because
if you don't break a cycle then
you're screwed. Wait a minute.
Give me a bit of like friendly advice.
So that's what's happening. Come on.
It's what it is, bro.
If I went out yesterday
or today, I'd have less money
and I'll be in the same cycle again.
I have less money.
Nope. I had a both teams to score no draw.
Um, one was 1-1 and the other was 2-0.
At least I wouldn't have won it if I
just done a both teams to score as well
cuz obviously Colchester didn't score.
So the worst is when you do both teams
to score no draw, they both score cuz
you think, oh [ __ ]
just both team to score. I didn't pick
Swindon, but if I did, yeah,
I would have won, but I wouldn't have
won because obviously Colchester didn't
score, so I would have been [ __ ] So,
don't know why you say any luck to me.
Like, I gamble, bro. I don't [ __ ]
gamble. Only on a football every Saturday ever.
I'm glad I didn't go out yesterday. I'm
glad I didn't go out today.
you know, yeah, you might be a little
bit bored and whatever, but
um I care.
I care a lot cuz it's [ __ ] annoying.
So, I care. [Music]
stop talking about yourself. It's all
good for your mental health, man.
That's nice, bro.
But yeah, I'm glad I didn't go out
yesterday and I'm glad I didn't go out today cuz
my moods were right, man. If I went out
yesterday or today, I would have been mad, bro.
I would have been disappointed I'm going
around in the same cycle again.
If you don't break the cycle, you're [ __ ]
So it's like what I said to Kieran, if
you keep gambling doing this, he said,
"Oh, it needs to stop." I said, "It's
not going to stop until you stop."
Cuz I used to do the same thing with the
gambling, but I didn't end up skin, but
I'd end up with these mood swings and [ __ ]
And unless you break the cycle, you're
pretty much [ __ ]
Same thing with the women thing. This is
why I haven't been out this week, you know?
And you know, Antman said, yo, he says
that he left Thailand because the woman
he was seeing, he went in her daughter's
room and she he was touching the daughter up
and the daughter was like 15, 16. And
she and she ran out of the room saying,
"Mommy, mommy." That's why he's in
that's why he's in Cambodia.
Sounds like a certain person we know, ain't it?
Yeah. He went in he went in like the daughter's room.
So, what the [ __ ]
This is getting really weird now. It
But you know what? Let me let me tell
you one thing. As as mad as this as mad
as this is, right, and I'm not a yes
man. Yeah. At least he got off a YouTube
and got a life. That's that that's the
only thing that actually could be said
about him is he actually showed the
right thing to do.
Like, and that's not even me sticking up
for him. like that is at least he
actually got off a YouTube and actually
got a life and like these people like
and that's not even me sticking up for
him that I'll tell you about anyone who
does the same thing. So yeah, man
listen and I'm not going to try Thailand
for kids. I don't like kids. I'm going
cuz I'm I'm sick of these stuck up women.
I like these stuck up women. That's why
I'm [ __ ] going. Like
I hate the women in these westernized
countries. I hate them.
Like did you know that that Morgan
friend I was speaking to yesterday, Joe? Right.
No, we weren't arguing. We was talking.
We was talking on the phone and and everything. Right.
And you know, it started annoying me a
little bit when she's like, "Oh, if you
come here, yeah, we're just going to get
seven people to shoot you." And like I
was like I was about to like start some
madness, bro. And say, "Okay, do you
want do you want me to call your bluff?"
Like, but I was like, "It's just not
worth it." But I didn't even have to
hold myself from doing things. You know
what I mean? Um cuz
bro, no one's going somewhere to lose.
No one's traveling somewhere to lose.
But we was never arguing it. But it's
like, does she really know that? Like,
trust me, you would get yourself hurt.
People ain't going somewhere to lose.
I'm not anyways, you know. But yeah, we
was talking for like Yeah, we was
talking all day today about politics and [ __ ] but
bro, all I know is I would take one of
them out before they take me out, bro.
Even if it's just one of them, cuz they
actually thought I was
going to hurt the [ __ ] That's what
they No, I I I was just going to tell
the [ __ ] about herself to her face.
this [ __ ] to come out. But they they
actually thought like I was going to
like stop like they actually thought I
was going to kill the [ __ ]
You know what I mean? So yeah.
Yeah, I know.
But you don't have my temper.
You don't have my temper, bro.
when she says, "Oh, I know people in
prison." I mean, yeah, I know you know
people I know people in prison for
murder. You know, that could mean anything. Um,
so do you want to do you want to tell
Nicolo the story, Joe?
Yeah. Antman's in Cambodia because he
was touching up this woman's um
daughter. So, he had to go to Cambodia
and Yeah. So he was he was seeing a mom
which was 38 and then the kid
was like 15 16 and he was he was in her
room like he went in her room touching
her and she she she ran out the room
saying mommy mommy what's going on?
That's [ __ ] madness bro. I'm going to
have to block him, bro. I think Yeah.
I'm going to have to block him. I'm I'm
sorry, bro. That's that's very weird.
See, he lets himself down, bro, because
it was funny, you know, like the whole um
just different characters. But then he
does [ __ ] like that and Yeah.
Yeah, he told me he did. Yeah.
Yeah. Oh, I was on the phone to uh USA
is his friend for 5 hours. Nicolo,
we're both Scorpios. She's like, "Oh,
you've met your match with me." I was
like, "Trust." She's like, "I've been
expecting you. I've been waiting for you
to message me." I was like, "You do
realize I've not been looking for you.
You just come up. So I message you. And
trust me, no one's my match.
Believe that, bro. So it would take me a
very long time to meet my match.
Yeah, of course she was. Joker.
Yeah, I'm speaking to this Brazilian
woman. Even they're becoming [ __ ] now.
Like she's answering, but she's given
very boring answers. like not
uninterested answers, like boring answers.
So, I mean, it's even getting bad there now.
And I'm having to translate Portuguese
because you don't speak English. Like,
they're replying back, but what they're
saying is just boring.
Like, not one word answered. Like, just boring.
I'm so lucky I never have to try her
ever again. I'm a lucky bastard.
And you know, another thing, Joe, right?
You know this whole USA is his friend.
This is why I wait for you to come on
here. This in itself is one of the
reasons why you should never try here
again or any westernized country. Like
look at all of the [ __ ] that's already
happened. You know, all the things
that's gone on, the boyfriend [ __ ] the
piss taken, you know, it's like you you
you've done it more than enough now. You
know, you've gave it full of chances for
it to change and it hasn't. You you got
nothing left to prove now. And so
that's the way I see it. So,
and this is a big thing, you know. This
could have ended up people dying.
You know, it could have this could have
ended up with people actually dying, bro,
and all this [ __ ] And
she just said that. Oh. Oh, I I don't
care what she did.
No, because I'm speaking to her friend, bro.
So, I'm telling you, I'm speaking to her
friend, bro. So, but but it's still like
one of the reasons like it doesn't
matter where it is like Canada, America,
England. You just need to give up dating
in these countries, bro.
Just for your own sake, you need to just give up.
You know, you got all the [ __ ] that's
already happened, bro. you know, it
still counts as well, you know, and
we're older now as well. So,
[ __ ] that. [ __ ] these [ __ ]
And I want about her cuz I was speaking
to her friend.
She was telling me mad stuff about
Charles, like being an abuser. And I'm
not going to get into everything she was
telling me, but
yeah, she was telling me mad [ __ ] bro.
Mad stuff. Like, I'm not even going to
repeat. Obviously, you're on the phone
for 5 hours. You know what I'm saying? So, yeah.
Scorpios get along just fine, don't they, Joe?
Scorpios get along just fine.
I'm a Scorpio.
What star sign are you, boss?
So, what star sign are you?
But the thing is with these both teams
to score, Joe is that the only way you
can win big is you need to lump money on it.
Um, I'm not putting £500 on both teams
to score. [ __ ] that. So, you know,
I'm not putting £500 on both teams to score. Um, so
[ __ ] minimum, bro. You know what I mean?
Yeah, the bet loss.
I had um Fleetwood and Oldm and
Colchester and Ba. Colchester and Ba was
I had both teams to score no draw. So
Colchester was 2-0 and um
Fleetwood and uh and Olden was 1-1. But
at least Colchester didn't score because
then I'd be kicking myself saying, "Oh
[ __ ] I wish I just done a normal team
to score." But I feel like it was still
quite close. I don't know. Both score no draw.
[ __ ] Swindon [ __ ] was too [ __ ]
won. But it doesn't matter because I
would have never done Fleetwood and Swindon anyways.
I don't like to bet Shrewsbury because
they did score. though. I was No, I w I
weren't that far off, but
nope. I'm I told you I've given up with
it. I'm not doing any of it. I've tried
more than anyone in the world. I got
nothing left to prove, bro. I'm out of
here in a couple of months.
I don't need to do anything but leave
this country, which is what I'm doing.
That's the only thing I need to do is
get out of here. And that's exactly what I'm doing. Hey,
that's a smart idea. So, yeah,
it's so nice, you know,
you know, Joe, six weeks off. I had I
think before six, seven weeks. It was so
nice. Oh, it was lovely. Not hearing
that I've got a boyfriend.
not here at all. It was lovely. And the
only side effect was just slightly bor
bored. But I was fine.
Oh, I'm not
I've got a boyfriend. That's how you
know like Thailand is paradise.
I was going to gamble on the football
today, but I'm quitting the gambling now. But
it was so nice six weeks.
I'm not hearing it. Oh, it's lovely. I want
[ __ ] you just annoy the [ __ ] out of me, man.
Where the [ __ ] is he then? Your make
believe weapon. And the thing is like
the thing is it's like yo why do you why
are you going out to keep trying bro?
There's no one for you in this country.
You're only hurting yourself by trying.
You know it's not going to be different.
It hasn't been different ever. So why
are you if you want to self harm
yourself? Why don't you just get a knife
and stop slitting your wrists, bro? Like
why you don't
you going out doing this is actually
self harming yourself?
Yeah. Actually, you're just self harming
yourself if you go out and do this [ __ ] Seriously. Yeah. For real.
This Brazilian woman's being a [ __ ]
Yeah. I'm glad, bro. Made the right choice. that Five.
So yeah, it feels good, man. It does feel good.
I let you waste your
waste your time in this country. Waste your money.
I've done it enough times.
Time and time and time and time and time again.
I'm going to [ __ ] hate my
sucks. It broke bad. You right.
We need to stop talking about this, bro.
I'm not doing it ever again.
So, we need to stop talking about
approaching because it ain't ever
happening again, bro.
I am done.
I can't wait to leave.
I'll be in paradise. Paradise. Like
never hear when I have a boyfriend again.
Imagine that in a country where you
don't get a whole country where you're
never going to get that again. Yeah. westernized pumps.
No, I won't. No, I won't.
And even if I do, I'm not going to do it
cuz I already know the result.
So, I'm done with it. Like, listen. Read
my lips. I am done. I am leaving.
Simple. I am done. I am leaving. I am.
Well, I could have went out yesterday. I
could have went out today, but nah.
Nope. I've tried more than enough in this country. So,
Time to leave.
Remember, Nicolo, she can give baby
Peter some milk.
You're such a troll you are.
I'll just go back to SIG if I ever get
the chance again. Nicola, I'll just go
back to SIG, you know.
Yeah, I'll just go back to SIG.
Yeah, I was speaking to this woman in
Brazil. I said, "Oh, so
so I don't bring I said if I come to
Brazil, like I stay in your house and
shit." She don't bring men to my house.
You don't bring men to your house. So I
said, "Well, if you're dating a man,
where you going to where you going to
bring where you going to bring the man then?
If you if you if you say that stuff, why
are you giving a man your number? Why
are you texting back all day?"
Right? That doesn't make sense. You said
man and the way you say ma men is like
you hate men. So why are you why uh
why are you um giving men your number then?
Report him to the police. What police?
He's not in this country. What [ __ ] police?
But to be honest, yeah, he is something
to look up to in a way. He come off
YouTube. He's living his life. He's
living his best life. These little
mongos still can't get off YouTube all
these years later.
Like even as bad as he is, he's actually
like better than most of the people on here.
That's how sad it is. Like that's
generally how sad it is.
That's the sad thing about it.
Just think of it, right?
How comes a wrong and nons can get off a
YouTube and better their life and live
their life, but these little mongos
can't. These little mongos that can't
get off YouTube
when he come. He's never coming back here.
He's never coming back to England.
He said he couldn't help himself. Nicola,
he said he couldn't help himself.
He said he couldn't help himself. Madness, man.
He said he was in the bed with the mom
and he couldn't stop thinking of the she
come back from the night out.
He couldn't stop thinking about mad. I'm
not laughing but mad man. Oh [ __ ]
C is mad is it?
I've got a woman. I'm leaving the
country to get a woman.
I am. That's why I'm going to Thailand.
I That's why I'm going to Thailand to
get one and not deal with these stuck up
[ __ ] in this country.
I found the solution. Plan B works perfect.
Plan B works perfect. Leaving this
country works perfect. Yeah.
Why the [ __ ] would you even go out when
you even realize no one's interested in this country?
Yeah. Once you meet one, you meet them all, you know. Mhm.
Yeah, she she doesn't bring men to her house,
but yet she gives a man her number. Huh?
She still hasn't reply back. I said,
"Okay, well, if you don't bring a man,
you're going to be dating back to your
house. Where where would we go then?
This is one of the reasons." Yes. USA is
here last week, the week before that.
You need to think about all the things that's happening.
You need to put it together and realize that
you need to realize that you going out
trying is not an option. You're only
making you're only depressing yourself.
You're only frustrating yourself and
depressing and depressing depressing
yourself even more. You've got enough
numbers on your phone. You've tried more
than anyone in the world. You got
nothing left to prove. That's it.
Take the L. move on and leave this country. Simple, you know.
Well, mate, listen. Well, you don't need
to go to Thailand. You can use escorts.
You go Thailand. There's different
countries you can go to. It don't need
to be Asia.
It can be anywhere else. But whatever it
is, you need to stop trying in this
country. You know, even if people don't
even want to go to Asia, you need to
think of another thing cuz this ain't
happening in this country. You there's
even different countries you can try
that's not like Asia. It's different ones. Yeah.
Think of it. Even if it was like a six
month break. Imagine that. You don't
even need to move there. a month, two
months, just chilling, getting [ __ ]
No, it's a westernized country. I'm not interested.
It's a westernized country. I am not interested.
There's still some hope in South
America, some places like that. But you know
not I'm not interested in westernized
countries when it comes to dating. So Yeah.
To somewhere that's not a westernized
country, you know. Anyway,
I've found Asian women before.
There used to be an Asian
There used to be an Asian actor I liked
when I was a kid. I have liked Asian
Asian before. And it's better than
nothing. What are you going to do? Stay
here and get rejected your whole life.
That doesn't sound like a plan, does it?
Look at all the [ __ ] that's happened.
the boyfriend [ __ ] the trolling, the
[ __ ] the USA Izzy, that was quite
bad. That could have ended up in death.
You need to think, is it really worth
you pursuing this anymore? And the
answer is simply no. The answer is
simply no. So,
the answer is simply no. Yeah,
you got I still got numbers on my phone, you know. So,
still trying with a few of them, but I'm
not going out getting new numbers. I
can't be asked I can't be asked hearing
a boyfriend [ __ ] anymore. It's [ __ ] boring.
[ __ ] boring as [ __ ]
I hate it, bro. I [ __ ] hate it.
I hate it being a boyfriend. [ __ ]
[ __ ] hate it.
So I was like, "Oh, when are you
planning to go out again?" I told him a million times.
Um, so he the woman that he was dating,
he has a daughter and he went in the
daughter's room, started touching her up
and then she was screaming saying,
"What's happening? What's happening?" Yeah.
No, just in clubs.
Just in um No, some of them are really
good-looking. Some of them just give
their number and then they don't reply.
I normally get like one sober and the
rest like B and C and [ __ ]
You all right? Mhm.
Yeah, she she was writing to Ant-Man
saying the mom was saying you're a bastard.
Yeah, the mom was saying to him that
you're a bastard. She's like are you
bastard? I'm telling you right here,
whoever does this to me will never let
you be happy.
Stop it. I'm in Cambodia. I live here
now. She said where you are is your
business. I told you I'm going to scold
you every day. May you die there. You
don't have to come to my country again, you bastard.
That's a madness, bro.
That's That's something that [ __ ]
Virgin boy would do.
That's something Virgin boy would do to
try and lose his virginity cuz you can't get laid.
That's something the virgin would do.
You remember you talking about a 15y old boy
trying to lose his [ __ ] virginity. [ __ ] virgin. Yeah, bro.
Virgin there. I remember B that's
something B boy would do.
You remember when you tried saying that
Hannah sucked his willie? Hannah has
never sucked your willie.
You know she never sucked your Willie.
That's in your head. She was telling me
about Charles. Morgan's friend was
telling me about Charles and how she'd
not been with Charles for years and
Charles was abusive and [ __ ]
She was telling me like Charles is like abusive
and um he's delusional
and like he's a very scary bastard.
these nuts and
apparently he killed someone that
Charles apparently killed someone
where we're living and that's why he's
coming to America. [ __ ] madness, bro.
The [ __ ] I was hearing mad. Yeah.
Yeah. I already have. [ __ ] man.
When do you think Nicol boy is going to lose it?
Virgin Boy is going to [ __ ] lose that Von?
Yeah. He was saying that she he like
what used to like
abuse her and [ __ ] Um
and that he killed someone.
Yeah. But you got to understand though,
that's my mommy. I would I would have
done anything for my mommy. It doesn't
matter if the person's a murderer or a serial killer.
Um, you know, yeah, he might be nuts,
but obviously that's my mama.
So, well, I was prepared to die for my mama. Yeah.
Yeah. Apparently, he's killed someone
and he's psycho and that. And apparently
when he he typed back that he was with
her, he wasn't with her. It's in his
head. that it's in his head that he
still thinks he's with her. Like, it's
[ __ ] mental, bro. The [ __ ] I was hearing
like and other things I'm not going to
disclose as well. But yeah.
Yeah, it's magic. Madness, bro. Madness.
Why do you think the whole situation was
funny, Joe? I don't think it's funny, man.
I don't think it's funny.
The whole child situation and I don't
think it's funny. I don't even know how
anyone can find it funny. I don't find
it funny. Me.
Well, yeah. They said that if I went
there, they would
they knew I went there the first time,
they would have they would have shot me.
They would have found me and shot me.
That's madness, isn't it? [ __ ] soldier.
50 pound down the [ __ ] drain. Nice, man.
How many of the phone for five [ __ ] hours, John? That's mad.
Bet your virgin wife trying to hold a
conversation for that long.
She said you don't want to mess with
Scott. like he's a proper like badass
Boston dad apparently. Apparently. Yeah. Um
it's not funny, bro. It really ain't
funny. It was [ __ ] winding me up yesterday.
You do a [ __ ]
I find it funny, man.
I don't find it funny, man.
Yeah, I don't find that funny, man.
Yeah, it's fun to lose. What do you
reckon would have happened if I went out
today, Stephen? How would you reckon I
would have pulled? Should I just go to fabric today?
Should I just go out today and send it like [ __ ]
like [ __ ] will I?
Yeah. Right. But
nah, I've been through enough. with women.
You have lucky.
What makes you so sure?
that this this time will be the time and
all of them years?
What would make you so sure?
Show yourself to me, bro. Come on. You Sure.
So you sure they won't say they've got boyfriends. You sure? That's Joe.
Don't. We need you.
We need you here. Yo, lad. Reach purple.
One sec. I need to bought myself a drink. [Music]
Damn, we worked perfectly.
Of course she's [ __ ]
Of course he's going to be [ __ ] in
there playing the guitar. He's [ __ ] skin.
Where's he [ __ ] going? He's skinned
in a skin flint.
Where the [ __ ] is he going to be going, lad?
With his f with his [ __ ]
skin and a [ __ ] skin flint.
You know what I mean?
Where's that skin bastard going?
You get me?
Where's that [ __ ] skin bastard?
Skin bastard going.
You know what I mean? Hey Joe,
they look like him one day, mate. That
skin bastard in a bed sitting with no [ __ ] bed.
You really want to end up like that skin bastard? You know,
I said to her like, "Did Charles know
about all of this?" And she's like, "She thinks so. Yeah, Charles.
He's only had like two boyfriends apparently.
That's mad, isn't it? Unbelievable. [ __ ]
[ __ ] his cons are [ __ ] boring.
I lost bar's number.
Yeah, I lost ball quests number.
he needs to come back on YouTube,
doesn't he? I know he watches, Franklin
got seriously hurt. Franklin. Oh, Franklin.
Odds, Steven Howard, that Virgin boy is
going to lose his virginity by this year.
What's the odds? I'm thinking
5,000 to one. What do you think?
that Virgin boy is going to lose his
virginity this year?
5,000 to one. We should put a bet on it in it.
When do you think
5 million to one?
What about next year?
Maybe. What about next year? [ __ ] virgin.
Can't get it up. Can't attract anything
normal. It's why he's still a virgin.
It's why he's still a [ __ ] virgin Virgin can
[ __ ] hell. Need to get [ __ ] laid. Yeah. What's up?
Yeah, that's all made up, mate. It's all made up.
He made up some He made up a story.
Yeah, [ __ ] Greavvesy saves all his money. Deanie,
I'm going to nick I'm going to nick his telly.
I'm going to nick um Grezy's telly. Yep. Yeah.
It's the same. It's the same people
every day. You remember that one? Same people.
It's the same people every day. Yeah.
Right. Ask me why is it the same people
every day. Steven Howard,
ask me and I'll tell you.
But ask me why they call people skint. I
can answer you. Cuz they're skint.
They call people They call people skit
cuz they're skin.
Yeah, you you don't do any bets. Prove
it. Prove you do these bets, Tom Wood. Yeah,
you're very fraud. I like that one. Oh, [ __ ]
Oh, [ __ ] me.
Sorry, man. It's depressing, but I need
to stay in and save money. I can't
afford to be going out wasting money,
lad. I've got a holiday to be going on.
I've got a holiday to be going on, lad.
Can't be wasting money here anybody, lad.
[ __ ] wasting 200 [ __ ] pound. [ __ ] that. Yeah.
Do you think it's funny that I speak to
USA is his friend?
Imagine that. You're going to be like,
"Oh, yeah. I was speaking to uh
the person you had a one night stand
with for 5 hours.
Madness, isn't it?"
And she was telling me about how like
she's gone on these dates with these
guys and like she's not like them. She
doesn't like them the last dates before
me. And that's also another thing you
need to think of is that these women,
right, these people that go on dates,
which is something that I thought of before
is that they they want they're expecting
Mr. Perfect. When they go on these
dates, like they're they're they're not
liking you as, oh, they're not perfect.
Oh, they're not everything I want them
to be. So, they they've also got unrealistic expectations
when they actually go on these dates.
So, and obviously if people don't fit
that criteria, then they just don't like them.
You know, that's what I think it is.
It's they they have these unrealistic expectations
that if people don't fit, they don't
like them. I don't think it's
necessarily that, oh, I don't like them
because they've got a different
personality or because they've um
because they uh
or they just don't like the way that they look.
Remember when I went on that date when I
was limping on that date? It was
perfect. Perfect. I done everything I
could do. Perfect. the one a few months
ago, the one I was limping on, but yet
they claim they don't feel the vibe.
What are you supposed to do?
And it's not anything wrong with you or
all these other people. Why do you think
there's so many failed dates? Why do you
think so many people go on these dates
and cuz they're looking for something
that doesn't exist? you know. So
that's what it is. So yeah,
she said I can't meet you because I
can't go on the opposite team. She said
she's on Morgan's side. I said you
should be on my side.
I said to her, "You'll like it down
here. You'll never have to grow up."
I said, "Can't you just be on both of our sides?
You like it down here, son?
You'll like it down here, son. You'll
never have to grow up.
Whose side do you take, Steven Howard?
Side Peter Bellies or side USA? Izzies.
Which side do you take?
You'll like it down here, son. You'll
never have to grow up.
You'll never have to grow up. Yeah, I'm mad.
Uh, he's calling me a weasel.
Hang on a second.
Yeah. Sorry, mate.
Tell me to sort myself out. Why? Cuz I
said it's the same people on YouTube every day.
Buddy said the same [ __ ] that comes out
of my mouth.
But he said he's had enough of you. Yeah. Oh man.
You say you're still talking to me about YouTube. Yeah.
He's still watching. Bless
What is [ __ ] Yeah.
What's that? The lottery. Oops. Wait a second.
in the middle or something.
Converging boy will ever get laid.
I don't think the skinned virgin will
ever get laid.
I don't think the skint virgin will ever get laid.
It's such a shame. I don't think anyone should [ __ ]
you know die a virgin.
I don't I don't believe in it
because bang out of order. I don't think anyone
anyone should die of virgin.
You know what I mean?
Um, pick a number two. Number two. Oh, what?
what I mean. It's just same ended and
same beginning, just different
characters. These approaching videos,
it's just different characters. Yeah.
See what I mean? One sec.
Yeah, Greavvesy. Apparently, um, did you
hear about what, um, Ant-Man did?
What do you think? What's your opinion
on what Ant-Man did, Grevy?
So basically he was dating this um
uh basically he was dating this woman
um in Thailand and she has a daughter
that's 15 and he kept thinking about the
daughter. So he went in her room and
started touching her up. And then the
daughter come running out saying,
"Mommy, mommy, what's he doing? He said
he couldn't help himself."
He's like 15, 16. So that's why he's in
Cambodia now. And the mom like she
messaged him saying, "You bastard. I'm
going to do this. I'm going to do that to you." Yeah. Mhm.
That's mad, isn't it?
Yeah. He said he couldn't stop thinking
about her, so he went in her room. Yeah.
Yeah. I was on I was I was on the phone to um
Izzy's best friend for 5 hours, Grezy.
And yeah, she was telling me some mad stuff.
She said she can't be best friends with
me because that's ops. That's the opposite.
And she says that she loves USA. So yeah.
Yeah. But he's right about the women in
this country though. Agree with you that
they're all NPCs. They're all stuck up.
And he's right about that though, isn't he?
And when he says the only place you're
not going to get and he said and when he
says the only place
so what he was lying Grezy when he says
the only place you're not going to get
I've got a boyfriend is Asia Grezy he
wasn't lying though was he
when he said the only place you're not
going to get I've got a boyfriend is Asia.
He's right though, ain't he? We right.
That's the only place you're not going
to get it.
Was he Was he lying about that?
dog weed. He was lying about that when
he says the only place you're not going
to get that is Asia,
you know. Yeah. What [ __ ] What about
Virgin boy? These are rolling graves. You see?
[ __ ] virgin boys are [ __ ] nons.
You're never going to [ __ ] lose it.
The westernity in their eyes.
Greasy. You can see the westernity in
their eyes. They give you that dirty
look, you know. Hey.
I am a great guy. You should already know, man.
I'm sick of these [ __ ] videos.
I've watched different channels,
different approaches, and all I keep
seeing is e I've got a boyfriend. I'm
sick of watching it. It's [ __ ]
annoying. How the [ __ ] can I possibly
have hope when I can't even see
anybody else have hope? You know what
I'm saying, Grezy? Every time I go on
this Instagram, it's the same [ __ ] just
different people. Even different people approaching Griezy.
It's [ __ ] annoying.
It's horrible, bro.
[ __ ] hearing it.
Grezy, when is it ever going to change?
Like, I've been on Instagram seeing
different people approaching different
women and it's always the same [ __ ] I
have a boyfriend.
When is this going to change, Grezy?
When am I going to see a different [ __ ] video?
Like a different video, like a different
start and a different ending. That's all
I'm looking for is a change.
Grezy, when is it going to
when is it going to stop? You know,
when's it going to change? Grezy, I'm
sick of it now. You know, it's been
going on for years and years and years
and years and years.
You know, when's it going to change,
Grezy? For [ __ ] sake. Come on.
Cuz I keep seeing the same thing. Huh?
It will never change. Greedy. Never I said, right,
that I keep seeing these approaching
videos on Instagram,
different guys, different videos, and
all it is is the same [ __ ] I have a
boyfriend. I have a boyfriend. I have a
boyfriend. I'm too old for you. I'm too
young for you. I'm sick of it. I'm sick
of seeing the same [ __ ] videos. It's
boring. You know, how are you supposed
to have hope when you can't even see it
happening for other people that's
approaching trying to get out of that
position? Grievy, I've seen about
[ __ ] six different people today.
Grievy, when's it going to change?
Like, Grezy, when is this going to [ __ ] change?
No. When's it going to change? I'm
asking you a question. Don't be rude. Yeah.
Yeah. But it's not about a hobby. It's [ __ ]
Yeah. But greasy. I need sex. I need my toddra sucked.
You know, I need sex. I need my toddra sucked.
Well, I'm asking you a question. When is
it going to change?
When's it going to change? Huh?
When am I going to watch an approach
video that's different?
No. Like I mean generally when am I
going to watch an approach video where I
don't hear the [ __ ] I've got a
boyfriend? I'm sick of it.
You know adman's like I'm obsessed. Gre
man said I'm obsessed. You know
you know what I'm saying? He said is
that true? And man said, "I'm obsessed." Yeah.
He He says, "I'm obsessed." Crazy.
Bless you, Grezy. You're losing it, aren't you?
You're losing it here, aren't you, Greavves?
L Grez, I need to find as many women to
stop my willy Greavvesy. You know,
you know how it is.
It's pollution [ __ ]
Yeah. But crazy adman says I'm obsessed. Am I
[ __ ] sick of hearing it?
He said it's never going to change,
mate. Never going to change. He says you
need to leave the country.
That's what he said.
He said it's never going to change. Huh?
That's what he said, Grezy.
And I said to him, "But they told me to
go on dating apps." He says, "They tell
you lots of things." I said, "The dating
apps don't work." He's And that man's
like, "They say a lot of things. They
He says that they say a lot of things. Greavves. Yeah.
Is that true?
Oh, I'm I'm in my little nestles now, Grezy.
I still haven't had a shower for a
couple of days.
Yeah, Greavves is my friend.
I love Greavvesy.
Me and Greavvesy go way back. I'm the
only channel Greavvesy goes on.
Oh, bless you.
Is that right, Grezy? Yeah.
Yeah, but I feel like women was put on
this earth to satisfy my needs. Grezy,
how could I just forget?
Grezy, how could I just possibly forget? You know,
I think I'm falling for USA. Is his friend Greavvesy,
is that normal?
Greavvesy, I found a new mama.
A mama that will actually love me. Greavvesy.
Yeah, but you go on about women as well,
Grezy. You say that.
You say Izzy's is my mama.
You tell everyone she's my mama.
So that's [ __ ]
So that's you you you go on about them as well. Hi, Nicolo.
Where's my mama?
Where's my mama? Nicolo.
Oh, bless Charles then if he turned
insane and delusional. Well, yeah, he
lost his milk supply as well. I lost mine, too.
I said to this woman yesterday on
Instagram, "Can we have a baby?"
Yeah. Where is my mama?
Lane is my mama, isn't it, Nicola? Yeah,
Lane is my mommy, I guess.
Is that right? Gre
Steven Howard. That's not nice.
Not what nice way to talk about my mama.
You know lady's my mommy.
Isn't that right?
I can just imagine you, Nicolo, sat
there with your kids whilst trolling me on YouTube.
You sad bastard.
You're sat there. Yeah. With your little
kids just typing at me and laughing with
them when you're writing these comments.
What do you mean Laney was never my mama?
How can Laney How can Laney not be my mama?
Who is my mama then?
How can Laney not be my mama?
She's on my birth certificate. Huh?
So who is my mama then?
No one knows.
You're not my mama. Yuck. Yuck. You're
That's my mama.
You know that one they call though.
You're not my mommy. Yuck. Yuck.
That was funny. Is it? Really? Grezy? Why?
So, who's my mama then, Grezy?
Nicolo. Um, Greavvesy said I need to
forget about women, but I can't. They
were put on earth to to give me [ __ ]
and satisfy Peter Belly's needs. Nicolo,
how could I forget? You know,
they were put on this earth to give
Peter Belly [ __ ]
Is that right, Nicolo?
and make me sandwiches. I like Yeah, Steven Howard. That's jokes.
That's a good one. That one.
Who's my mama? Take aity.
Yeah, but how how can she be my mama,
Nicolo, when she's 2 years old? She's a
year and a half older than me.
She's a year and a half older than me.
So, how can she be my mama? You know,
her friend was trying to say that she
getsund and something grand a year. So
like 10k a month apparently. Really?
Yeah. Apparently she gets like 10,000 a month.
Yeah, but if she was my mommy, she
wouldn't have ghosted me if she was my
mommy though, right?
Your mommy wouldn't ghost you, would they? So yeah,
because I'm not there.
No one knows where I am and I'm going to
keep it that way. Yeah, mama.
Peter Belly can't get attached because
he's already found his mama. We've
Peter Bell's already found his mama.
Imagine I didn't I didn't have these
sayings, Grezy. Nobody would know.
No one would know. Hey,
because Peter belly found his mama. Oh, [Music] poor Franklin.
This woman was trying to beat up
Franklin earlier. You see?
Oh, poor Franklin.
Yeah, apparently Scott's a badass. her
friend was telling me like uh her friend
um no her dad like Scott
apparently he's he's a badass. He's a
proper badass apparently.
Yeah, he's a he's a badass. He's like a
proper like Boston dad. Yeah.
I said to her, "How about like we forget
this whole thing and Thanksgiving I come
over, you can like cook some food, me,
you, USA, Izzy, Scott, the whole family.
We can all sit around at the table like
a happy family and just and just just forget, you know,
forget about the past." Yeah.
She said that family never wants to see
you again. Crazy.
We could just all go and have like
dinner at Thanksgiving, you know?
What do you think about n that nic?
Do you remember? I'm part of the family now.
See, I kind of was a part of me was kind
of feeling bad when she was telling me
certain things about like that I didn't
know. But then the way I started with
Nicolo is that they don't give a [ __ ]
what they done to you. So why should you
give a [ __ ]
They don't give a [ __ ] about what they
done to you. So why would you care?
Think about it.
That's the way you got to think, blood. You know, one sec.
Do you want my opinions to be huh? Devil [ __ ]
Do you want my opinions to be? Uh uhhuh.
They're old [ __ ]
Sounds like they're like very old [ __ ] Yeah. Ah. Oh, Franklin.
Franklin, stop it.
All right. Do you remember uh Nicolo?
Let's Let's um let's end the night with
some lovely roulette.
Let's Yeah, let's end the night with
some lovely roulette. Let's
listen tonight with some lovely roulette. Yeah,
USA is he some lovely
lovely lovely Blue roulette. Hey,
I want somebody to suck my cheesy Willie.
I've not like had a shower for a couple days. So,
I want somebody to come and
suck my smelly willy breezy.
That'll be a lovely sight.
I don't know why she's best friend with
this USA Izzy Nicolo. She says that
she's known her for 11 years and she
loves her and [ __ ] I don't know how you
could love somebody that's evil. She does. All right.
I agree with you. I put up that all
women are evil and they said, "Yes, you
know our secret. Lock your doors and
your windows to get greasy. You know,
funny is it
You found out secret.
What was that?
Oh, bless you. And if you been on your little PlayStation, Grezy
Grezy is sick of me speaking about women.
Oh, bless you.
Me Greavvesy USA is the USA is his
friend having a Sunday roast. Oh,
how cute is that?
Do you remember Greavves? I'm like,
Chucky, you can't get rid of the [ __ ]
Once you've met me, I'm like Chucky. Is
it? You can't get rid of the [ __ ]
That made me laugh. You can't get rid of the [ __ ]
That's funny, is it? Yeah.
This was my dinner earlier.
I'm going to show you. I had it. It was yummy. Yeah.
them up. I see you tomorrow.