There we go.
Going to go live today, but I thought [ __ ] it.
There it goes. [Music]
These people on Reddit are so in denial.
You can show them all the proof in the
world about how like,
you know, they're such [ __ ] and
whatever. You can show them all the
evidence in the world and then still
point blank the night like it never happened.
It's a madness, bro. Ming
just playing some GTA.
But I can't wait to get out of here,
bro. Honestly can't wait.
Really can't. It's [ __ ] [ __ ] in it.
It's [ __ ] This country is the [ __ ] out
of me, lad.
Nah, mate. I don't want that, [ __ ] Why
pulled? I pulled more than anyone in
this community. Oh, probably shouldn't
say that because like I said, it is a
disabled community and you for and you
choose to forget what you see and
remember what you see. So yeah,
you choose to remember what you want to
remember. So yeah, waste time even
saying that to be fair. See what I'm
saying? You choose what you want to
choose to remember to see. [ __ ] pathetic. Yeah.
just play this [ __ ] game. Yeah.
Why are you talking about Jane, bro? No
one cares about her. Why are you talking about Jane?
Why you even talking about that?
Why are we talking about that, bro?
We're talking about how [ __ ] [ __ ] women are. my [ __ ] I mean
cuz I can well I can block you and
you're blocked. Bye-bye. Cuz I can
[ __ ] tell me about cuz you can. Are
you mad? Get the [ __ ] out of my chat,
bro. [ __ ] you talking to?
Yep, I remember him.
about cuz you can. Ain't no way you're
talking to me like that, [ __ ]
Ain't [ __ ] no way you're talking to
me about cuz you can. Not talking to me
like that, mate. Oh, okay.
I don't care about him, bro.
That's good. I guess I don't give a [ __ ]
about him, bro. Yeah. Interested.
She can do it, man. She can do it.
Ice cream van. Ice cream van
in your zone.
Live in your zone.
I feel sorry for these people that have
to deal with these westernized women
and people have to defend them. I I feel
bad for them, you know. I really do feel
bad for them. I really [ __ ] do.
[ __ ] sat there [ __ ] defending them punts.
[ __ ] madness, isn't it?
Madness, isn't it? Crazy, bro.
Sat there [ __ ] defending them.
Mad. It is mad.
Boring self projecting. Bye.
Boring self-reflecting. Bye-bye now. Disabled community.
Uh, no. It will never change. Never. Oh man. Self projecting. Self-reflector.
It was self-reflecting bastards.
These people self-reflect so much.
Crazy, isn't it?
talk about themselves so much. >> Yeah,
>> these people are the skinnest people
ever come across. You're probably
skinnier than a homeless person.
That's why they go on about like like I
always say, that's why they go on about
people being skinned cuz they are skinn.
Yeah, man. That's why they call people
skin because they're skin.
You know what I mean? 19 skin.
They call people skint cuz they're skin
and the skin flint though. That's the
thing. That's why they sit on YouTube
calling people skint every day cuz
they're skinn. That's why they're the
ones that are not sat there living life.
that's out there living life cuz they
ain't got a life. They ain't got a life to live.
They ain't got a life to live, mate. You know,
and that's it. [Applause] Oh [ __ ] No.
They call people skin because they're [ __ ] skin.
You don't understand matey.
Who's there? The skin flare
come out today by the way. [ __ ] 1499.
[ __ ] hell. Franklin killing us here, man.
[ __ ] killing us here.
Stop using that. You know, they don't
owe you [ __ ] That's getting really lame
now. Really boring.
Really lame and really boring. You know
that. Oh, like
they don't owe you [ __ ] That is so
boring. That is, you know, Yeah, man. Wait, man.
I'll wait to finally get out of here. What's that?
Bad it [ __ ] bad
by eight. Go tomorrow to be fair. Stay Monday.
Stay Monday. Is it?
Yeah. Do it tomorrow.
Nice shinies today. Pink. Yeah.
That's the [ __ ] out the mother. Yeah. [ __ ] Wait. madness.
Oh, I hate that guy, man. He's a [ __ ]
If I ever see him, I'll [ __ ] smash
his [ __ ] face in.
Yeah, I'll smash his [ __ ] face. And
if I ever see him, lad.
Nope. Someone yesterday. Hey, that's it.
Yeah, I hate women. They hate men.
[ __ ] hate [ __ ] men. I hate [ __ ]
women, not men.
Women are [ __ ]
And it Timmy Aldridge owns the drags of [ __ ] [ __ ] Bastard [ __ ]
I mean, I'm quitting the gambling. Me, I
had a nice take away yesterday. I mean,
I'm quitting the gambling.
I mean, I'm qu I mean, like I said, I'm
quitting the gambling. So
So, yeah, man.
Oh, the cinema. Yeah.
Yeah, the women are [ __ ] The people are
[ __ ] I've got to go work soon as well,
so I've got to be dealing with these
[ __ ] I've got to be dealing with them
again. So, yeah, it's depressing here in
England. Tell you that much.
Yeah, take away a bet. And the cinema is
pretty much your best bet when it comes
to this country.
Yeah, pretty much, man.
I'll be dealing with them again.
But yeah, that's basically where we're at.
That's where we're at basically.
Yeah. All them numbers never never were
no good. Timmy, the numbers that I got
the numbers I got to Eldridge was
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. They were all wank.
Nothing come out of any of them. So
nothing come out of any of them. Just
time wasters, trolls.
And would you believe it? I'm almost 28
and I'm still dealing with this [ __ ] Oh, [ __ ] Um,
one said she's in Spain and then I said,
"Oh, let's meet." And then when you come
back, no reply. And and then another one ignored. um
didn't ignore, but she's like, "Um,
I hate them, bro. I really hate them."
Like, you know what they're like as well. Um,
what did she say?
See, I'm not in London anymore. They
said no voice no reply. It's just it's
just the same [ __ ]
But even making money now, I don't even
think I'll go out every week, bro. even
like making money. I don't see the point.
I don't I don't generally see like the
point of it anymore. It's just the same
old. Once you've met one, you've met
them all. I was on that Instagram
yesterday. Do you know how many times I
was hearing I have a boyfriend? I have a
boyfriend. Do you know how many times I
was hearing it?
Do you know how many times I was hearing
that yesterday, bro, on that Instagram?
It's [ __ ] boring, bro.
Boring as [ __ ] It is. It's not even
funny. It's boring, mate. Bors me, bro.
[ __ ] bors me, lad. Yeah, they're not
normal. There's nothing normal about
them. They're just [ __ ] in this country.
Then I was speaking to Oh, oh, I tell
you one yesterday actually speaking
South America. I was speaking to one
yesterday that I met in England and
they're from Brazil and so obviously
they've gone back to Brazil and um
they were like um
yeah so I said oh when I come there so
what what can I stay with you? And she's
like oh I don't take men back to my
house. So I said okay well where where
am I going to go then? So why if you're
saying that [ __ ] like men why are you
giving a man your number? They're just
[ __ ] They're just they're even
becoming [ __ ] there as well, which
South America is not as is not as much.
South America is not far behind America
and all them other, you know, like
England and [ __ ] Asia is going to be
the same in 10 years. Everyone's going
to be the same in 10 years.
Everywhere. Yeah, it's going to be the
same. Everywhere is going to be the same
in 10 years, lad.
So yeah, she was just being a [ __ ]
But like all of them [ __ ]
I was speaking to USA Izzy's friend
yesterday for like 5 hours.
I was speaking to her friend Timmy
Aldridge for like 5 hours, man.
For 5 hours. Yeah.
Yeah. Bro, that they're just [ __ ] All
of them, bro.
Know what they're like. I know what
they're like. Sorry. So yeah, Yeah.
Why? Why are you talking about Australia, though? Uhhuh.
Yeah, man. But why why are you talking about Australia? H
Why are you talking about Australia though?
Why are you talking about Australia?
It's a bro, it's a westernized country.
Why are you Why are you talking about Australia?
They're the same as Americans. They're
the same as English. They're all [ __ ] You know,
they're all [ __ ]
How would I? Um,
yeah, bro. That's it's a westernized
country. They're [ __ ] there as
well. England, Australia, America,
[ __ ] all the Canada. Oh, I actually
got me approaching Canadian over there as well.
[ __ ] all stuck up. Maybe
Yeah. Oh, [ __ ]
I a [ __ ] lead as well.
New to sleep. Wish I could [ __ ] sleep, mate.
Don't know how they're going to be any
different. They're they're westernized
[ __ ] westernized [ __ ] Oh, [ __ ]
Where is I'm going?