Yeah, bro. I just watched a thing video.
Yeah, he's talking absolute
a lot of it made me laugh, you know,
bro. Anointed Belfast is not cheap. Yes,
the [ __ ] it is, bro. How How can you say
that to people that [ __ ] live in
London when London is like that? You
know, that's not even a [ __ ] That's
not even the most expensive place, right?
that like you know Dublin is more
expensive than Belfast. They're [ __ ]
fantasists and and another thing you
think of Yeah. is like why who the [ __ ]
would care about 200 whatever 250 if if they were
if they were all millionaires like these
people claim that they are and if
they're not skin but that they claim
that they're not skin. You didn't spend
no fortune in [ __ ] Belfast. That's
not even a [ __ ] Stop lying. Stop with
your lies. Trust me. I I live in [ __ ]
London, bro. Yeah. Honestly. And do you
know what? I had this conversation
before with people when I used to travel
and they'd say, "Oh, yeah, bro. You're
not going out by yourself drinking 200
pound away anywhere out of London. It's
not happening." Trust me, you are
talking [ __ ] Stop lying, bro. Listen.
And another thing is if you if you would
if you if you had all this money,
you wouldn't care about £200, you'd [ __ ]
yourself up every single time. You can't
say that a [ __ ] night out in Belfast
is not [ __ ] cheap. You're talking to
somebody that lives in London, bro. And
you won't you would not drink 200 pound
away by yourself. Trust me, you would
not. Even if you was play paying club
fees, you went out by your [ __ ] self.
You are talking absolute [ __ ] shite.
You're an absolute fantasist. I had this
conversation before like with this guy
in [ __ ] leads,
you know, and um you cannot drink
away£200 by yourself. You're an absolute
clown. You don't know anything. You're talking [ __ ]
Tell you what, the most I've spent
probably is probably about 120.
Probably about 120. You haven't spent
You haven't spent a fortune, bro. You're
talking absolute [ __ ] You're talking
absolute [ __ ] bollocks. Absolute a
load of old bollocks. Yeah, literally.
You talk [ __ ] man.
You did not spend no [ __ ] 250, bro.
And then and then you got your like
people commenting on your channel
saying, "Oh, that's why I don't go out
in Belfast." Let's just say that it did cost £200.
So why would you care about £200? You're
all millionaires. Everyone else is skin.
Why Why would you care about £200 if you
got all this money? You're all millionaires.
What the [ __ ] So So what if something
cost £200? So you're millionaires.
What's wrong with spending 200 pound
once in a while?
No, he never. Trust me, I've been out in
London numerous times and I've never The
only time I've spent 250 is when I was
buying everyone drinks. Trust me, he
probably never because London is more
exp more expensive than Belfast. And
I've never spent £200 just on myself.
I've spent like 120 125.
That was I was out out like seven
o'clock in the morning.
So you're talking a load of old [ __ ]
bollocks, mate. Trust me.
No, it wouldn't be 40 for the event. 40
for the event, bro. Even the events here
were not 40. [ __ ] hell.
And let's just say And let's just say
that it did cost £200.
Then who cares about 200 pound? You're all millionaires.
I mean, you're all millionaires. Why Why
would you care about 200 pound minimum?
Someone on your comments said they don't
go out anymore because of it. Why would
you go out every week? You're all millionaires.
Yeah, like what the [ __ ] What the So
what if it's 200 minimum? You're all
millionaires. Yeah, I know. It might be
unbelievable, but it's the truth.
You all spend all day on YouTube all day
every day because you've got all this
money. You're all rich.
Me, I don't even have a pound. Like, I
can't even eat. I can't even drink. I'm
going to die. Delayed.
Yep. Talking about yourself again. You
were on YouTube while you said that.
But me, I've got a pound, mate. I'm I'm
going to die soon. You know, I can't
eat. I'm I've literally got a pound. I'm
literally got a pound. I think maybe 99
p of that skin. Yeah. Right.
Is that why you really don't go out
anymore? Because the cost of it? I don't
go out because it's just the same [ __ ]
I don't I don't go out because it's the same bollocks.
Oh, [ __ ] Yeah. I don't go out because
it's just the same bollocks.
It's the same [ __ ]
That's why I don't [ __ ] go out.
It's not because of the [ __ ] cost of
it. It's cuz it's the same [ __ ]
It's the same [ __ ] every time. Same
people, same attitude, same every It's
like the night out you went on before
was a replica of the last one.
>> So that's why I don't [ __ ] go out.
Why the [ __ ] would you care about a
minimum of 200 pound? You got all this
money. Someone's lying. Someone said
Yeah, someone's lying. Yeah. Oh, [ __ ]
Aren't you a bit too old to be going on
nights out now, buddy?
I went out once this month. I think it
was last Thursday or the Thursday before
that, I think it was.
Probably won't be out again for forever.
So, I come back from my little holiday.
[ __ ] that. [ __ ] that. That's It was too
depressing. [ __ ] that.
Yep. Skin, bro. Bro, I'm skin. You're
the one saying about how [ __ ] Belfos
is this that and the other. Bro,
everybody knows that you are skin.
That's why you call people skinned
because you're skinn yourselves. Just
like your followers. Think about it,
bro. If you really had all this money,
you wouldn't think 200 a lot of money
for a night out. Listen, the only people
that are skinn is you and yourself
projecting followers. They're the only
ones that are skinned. That's why you
call people skinned, cuz you are skin.
What you say about other people is about
yourselves. Think about it. You spend
all day every day on YouTube cuz you are skiing.
That's Yeah, that's it. Yeah.
You spend an absolute fortune. You want
to know the most I spent on a night out before? £800.
And I was like, "Oh shit." And I thought
I think at that point, right, I have I
had the cheat to like say, "Okay, yeah,
that's a lot of money for that, bro."
And you spent not close to that
yesterday. And if the way you You just
give off skin vibes,
you know. You You just give off skimp
vibes. You really really You really are
skinn. Think about it, bro. I've proven
it time and time again. I've not been
skimp for three and a half years. The
only people that are skinn is you and
your gay followers.
They're the only ones that are skimp.
Don't leave. They don't even leave their
[ __ ] house. You know that good vibes
only, right? And you know, some of these
other people, they don't even leave
their house. They don't they probably
don't even have enough money to go to
the quarter shop. They're that skin.
That's that's the sad thing about it, you know. So, yeah,
I didn't do anything this bank holiday.
Yeah, I didn't do anything this bank holiday.
Waste of time.
Complete waste of time. Wow.
I know it's [ __ ] bro. Ain't it? Another
day in this [ __ ] Oh,
>> yeah. Another Yeah, I know, bro. Another
day. Another day in this annoying country.
I don't know what you done in I don't
know what you done. Did you go out bank
holiday or I just stayed in, bro? Well,
not literally. Like I went out for walks and [ __ ]
Yeah. It's a depressing country, bro. It
is a depressing country. It's a
depressing country to be in.
Yeah, it really is. It's an annoying
country as well to be in.
It annoys me being here every day, bro,
in this [ __ ] country.
So I can't leave until November. So
[ __ ] [ __ ] in it.
Horrible, isn't it? Horrible. Horrible. I mean,
still waiting for that change. Greavesy.
Remember we the the past don't dictate
the future. I was having this
conversation with someone yesterday.
So I said if the past doesn't dictate
the future, why is the same [ __ ] been
happening in 4 years?
If if the past don't dictate the future,
why has it been dictating it for 4
years? I think that's a good uh I think
that's a good question. Why does it
continue to keep dictating it year in
year out year in year out year in year
out year in year out for four years? If
the past really does not dictate, of
course, your past dictates your future.
Think of it now. Yeah. When you was when
you was 14, 15, maybe even younger, do
you feel any different than how you was
back then? I just went on Instagram.
There's some new approaching videos up.
I haven't watched them yet. Let me
guess. Is it the same old I have a
boyfriend, I'm married. Let me guess.
I've not even watched them yet. But it's
You've got They've got a very funny way
of showing that the past don't dictate
the future. You got a funny way of showing it, you know.
Stop talking about yourself. 40 plastic. So yeah,
LJ is still projecting his skintess onto
people. They will never learn these
people, will they be projecting their
skintess, loneliness? They will never
ever learn these people.
Never ever learn. But I'm so skinned.
Why are you the one that spend all day
every day on YouTube when you can't
leave your house if I'm the skin one?
Bit of a waste. But there's no point
getting into debates and arguments
because these people are disabled. So
why are you arguing with disabled people?
Yeah. And I realized that like that's
what it was in the end that you just
argued with disabled people. If you
argue with disabled people, you're just
going to fry your brains.
So there's no point arguing with [ __ ] disabled people.
Like it's even that Joe's a bit slow.
Not not disabled, but he's he's a bit
slow. like you'll have to explain [ __ ]
Like I'll be like I said, "Yeah, okay.
They might be trying to get a reaction
out of me." But then I'll be like, "Oh,
well, yeah, but they're they're reacting
to me." And then it's like then I was
like, "Yeah, yeah, I know." But I mean
like they're reacting to me and no
matter how many times you tell him, he
still wouldn't uh
he still wouldn't understand it. So he's
a bit slow as well, but not as disabled
as these people.
I like yeah they might be like for
example like yeah they might be do doing
stuff for reaction but
what I was explaining is they are
reacting to me so that just completely
misses the whole point
but he never understood that so there's no
And it took him it took a few times to
explain the money game to him as well,
which he didn't get
game. uh was had to explain to him about
a few times.
>> And then I just realized, oh, you
actually argue with disabled people. Oh [ __ ]
>> Yeah. You just argued with disabled people.
That's what that was.
Bro, there's no point talking about it
anymore. I'm not playing it with anyone ever again.
So, but yeah, generally that was the rule. Yeah.
Yeah. Germany. Yeah.
That's that's generally what the rule
was. Yeah. Like um you have to show
cash, but every single time I was
showing cash, people just went running
away. They all run away. That's why I
don't play the money game with them no
more. No £5 or£10 or £1,0003
4,000 because every time you show them
money, they run away.
Waste of time.
It was just invented by these skin
people to make themselves feel better
about the fact that they're skimp
another day in shitty old England either
I would have done myself in
million three years I I reckon 100% but
I didn't get that if I didn't have that
house and I wasn't getting money from
that house, it would have been like so
much worse like 3 years ago because you
wouldn't even be able to afford to go
out the way you did and you you wouldn't
be able to have lived some kind of life.
I don't know what the [ __ ] I would have
done. I don't know if I would have maybe
just adjusted to it, but I don't know
what I would have done, bro.
I would have been [ __ ] Like generally
generally I think I would have ended up
doing myself in 100%. I I think I must
have I I must I think I would have
you know it's not as bad now cuz
obviously I have savings and [ __ ] and
I'd already done it all but I'm saying
like them 3 years I don't know what I
would have done
you know back when you you still think
you had a chance in this country like oh
you know when you had Michael Jackson in
your head saying oh go out go out go out
it'll be different this time but
obviously if you didn't have the money
to keep doing it every week you would
have been [ __ ] then you'd have to
worry about getting money and horrible,
horrible, horrible life in this country.
It's a horrible life.
It really, really is.
I'm so glad I saw the light at the end
of the tunnel with the end though.
You know what I'm saying?
I'm still I've still got money. I've
still got savings and [ __ ] Greasy. But
I was thinking of other ways to get more
money, and there doesn't seem to be much out there.
there's this job I could do, but then
they were basically saying that uh they
were basically saying that a lot of
people were saying that they didn't get
paid. So, it's like they were saying
that they done the job and [ __ ] but
then they didn't get paid for it and
they had problems trying to get their
money. So, it's like it's a whole new
[ __ ] madness, you know?
Nope. I am staying in my bed.
I am staying in my bed. What carnival is
it? Is it the Notting Hill carnival every year?
It's got to be that one, right? Is that
I haven't heard of it, but I assume
that's the one you're talking about. No,
I'll be staying in my bed on Reddit.
I want to do I I think this is the best
you're going to get in this country.
Playing GTA, chilling in bed, nice bit of food.
No point going out. All the women are
the same. They're all [ __ ]
No, I've never been to that carnival in
my life. I know. I know what it is, though. Yeah.
I just want to be out of this country.
You know, I'm count I'm counting down
the [ __ ] days. So, I'm out of this depressing place.
It's like I told you anyway the other
day, Gio, when I was speaking to
Morgan's friend for 5 hours,
like we was talking about normal stuff
like politics and Trump and [ __ ] We was
on the phone, but even like cuz
obviously some of it got bought up. Even
that was annoying me. Like even that was
like winding me up. The whole thing, you
know, was just like cuz you think like
who the [ __ ] do they think they are? Not
that I care, but obviously we have to
talk about it because we're on the
phone, you know?
She wants to know why you've been
[ __ ] hyping at her best friend. You
know what I'm saying? So, you know, at
the end of the day, this all comes from
any of these countries, America, Australia, Canada.
You know what? Yeah. I don't even think
now, bro. And bear in mind, I used to
like be be obsessed with America and and
and [ __ ] cuz all the things come from
there and that. I generally don't think
you could pay me all the money in the
world to live there. Like, if someone
said, "Oh, yeah, you can you can live
there if you want." I wouldn't. She was
telling me things like, "Oh, the butt is
like $6, which is like [ __ ] five,
like5 pound4 pound something, which is
[ __ ] expensive." And how that people
need to earn like $66 minimum, which is
like over £50, which no one earns that
here to even be able to like live a
normal life over there. And then you got
all the entitled [ __ ] which I
personally think they're worse over here
than they are actually here.
I've seen some nasty videos, bro. I've
seen some nasty approaching videos.
[ __ ] that, bro.
If somebody says you could move to
another country, I'd say even Brazil, Poland, or
anywhere in Asia. I [ __ ] wouldn't
live there if you [ __ ] paid me a
million [ __ ] pound. [ __ ] that, bro.
I can't stand Americans, bro. I can't
stand them. I'm telling you, I can't,
bro. I hate them.
I really do hate them, bro.
So, that's how much people need to earn
over there. $66 minimum, which no one
earns £50 a [ __ ] hour here. So,
yeah, it's a madness, bro. She was
telling me and [ __ ] So, she was on the
phone for over 5 hours.
Yeah, she did make me want to actually
go there and like call her bluff when
she was saying, "Oh yeah, seven people
was going to shoot you." And
I was like, "Oh, really?" But we never argued once.
But it's it all it all adds up. All of
the [ __ ] adds up. Last week, two weeks
before that, the [ __ ] I've been putting
up with for years, the [ __ ] I had to
deal with with that [ __ ] [ __ ] and all
of these other people. Why would you
even try again here? Think about it,
man. We're not It's not like we're stupid.
It's not like we're dumb, you know? We
We know how to break a cycle. It's not
like we're stupid here. It's not like we
have disabilities that stop us knowing
right from right from wrong. You know
what I mean?
It's not like we're [ __ ] stupid, bro.
It's not like we're [ __ ] Monty, man.
Not like we're thick in the head. You
know what I'm saying?
Yeah. And it ain't money at all. I could
go out whenever I want to go out, you
know. I could go out today if I wanted
to get on the piss, but no interest.
But obviously like them three years,
three and a half years, I was doing it
more. So if I didn't have the money to
do it, I would have been [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
You'd probably have to try to gamble
every month to get more money and then
you'd probably end up skin and then you
basically be like Kieran.
And trust me, that's not a life. Trust
me, that's not a good life.
That is not a good life.
It's not a good life, bro. Trust me. I
done that back when I was like 21, 22
before my mom moved. I used to do the
same thing every month gamble and then
end up like skin if I didn't win. [ __ ]
that, bro. Like five years ago, I used
to do that same [ __ ]
Not a life, bro. It ain't a life. Trust me.
But there's less and less opportunities
here now. So, [ __ ] knows.
It's bad, isn't it?
It is really bad.
And you know, we was talking about Uber
as well, Gez. People people been banning
people's Uber accounts for no reason.
I've been looking up and they said, "Oh,
yeah, my account got banned." And no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's like the It's almost as if the
government wants people to get into bad stuff
like drug dealing and doing all of these
illegal things or even stuff like, you
know, gambling or whatever. It's like
the government is wants people to do
that. It's it's almost that the
government's actually against people and
that they want people to do the wrong things.
I don't know. It does. It seems that
way, doesn't it?
Does seem that way. But I would have
been [ __ ] for three and a half years.
Without that, I would have been screwed.
No, I was just saying to Grey if I
didn't have that house for three and a
half years, I probably would have end up
doing myself in
cuz that's where Michael I had that
[ __ ] [ __ ] Michael Jackson in my head.
Oh no. Go on. It'll be different. It
will be different this time. It will be
different. Go on. Go on PJ. Go on. Go on
And obviously it's like when you still
had some hope in your head. This is when
I was going out like three times a week,
bro. And if I didn't have the house, I
wouldn't be able to afford it. So, like
I would have definitely I think I would
have definitely either end up in prison
or I would have end up killing myself.
But then I realized it was [ __ ] and
then I already had the women and I had
savings. So it hasn't affected me now.
But it would have definitely affected me then
cuz how would have you went out you know
how would have you been living the life
if you don't have the money to do it you
can't do it.
So and yeah a lot of people's Uber
accounts have been getting banned as
well. So what ro
did I why they didn't lose gambling though?
Yeah, there's this [ __ ] app I've got.
You can work for them, but a lot of
people said that they worked for them
and they didn't get paid. So
that's what I would do if I was you,
Greasy. Work like 5 6 hours every other
day. Get like £300 extra a week. That
should be enough, shouldn't it?
But saying that, you're not going to
earn that where you live. So you're also
[ __ ] Cuz even if you get Uber, what
you're not going to earn, you're going
to earn like probably £3 an hour where you live.
No. No. No, it's something else. I'm not
going to get into it though in case I do
end up doing it. But
if I get like three 400 pound extra a
week, I'll be sorted, bro.
I'll be sweet. But
it could have been a lot worse. You
could be you could have been worried
about money then, you know, when you
actually wanted to go out and you
actually wanted to, you know, live the
life and [ __ ] like you would have been
[ __ ] You actually generally would
have been [ __ ] I mean, I guess you
maybe would have adjusted to it, but
I don't know, bro. I have no idea what
you would have what you would have done.
And by you, I mean me.
Don't forget, we used to spend like £700
on nights out. Like, well, I used to
mean that 19year-old and yeah, you would
have been [ __ ] You would have been
[ __ ] Trust me, you would have been
And it's like you
you don't want to end up like Kieran,
you know, gambling every month to try
and win more money and then ending up
skin cuz I done that [ __ ] when I like 5
years ago, five six years ago. I used to
just gamble to try and win more and then
if you're off skin then you are skin and
you are [ __ ] So it's not really good, is it?
It's not a good It's not a life you want
to live, you know.
And I said to him the other day like,
"You need to break the cycle." Cuz if
you don't break the cycle, you're [ __ ]
But I know cuz I used to be like that
six years ago. Gamble all my money and
then if I didn't win, then [ __ ] it. I'd be [ __ ]
It's not a good
It's not a good um ideally what you
[ __ ] want is to [ __ ] win a win a
big football and then you won't have
you'll be sorted for a couple of years
or even a year. That's ideally what you want. So
it ain't a good life, bro. It ain't a good life.
Yeah. Even when I was speaking to that
USA easy friend I was telling everyone
it was just annoying me even though like
we weren't arguing and we was cool and
that it was just annoying me
like the entitlement about oh yeah like
trust me you wouldn't come here you
don't need the energy bro I was like bro
I'd come there and I'd lap you in your
face like you you don't know me like a
part of me wanted to like really start
pulling their bluff and [ __ ] with
them but then I just like no cuz they
were all right with me
but the whole when we was getting when
we was talking about it. The whole thing
was winding me up. Just talking about it
was annoying me. Yeah,
just the whole thing was annoying me.
[ __ ] American. Oh, I hate them, bro.
I was just saying to my my man just now,
you could never pay me to to live there.
You couldn't pay me any money to live there.
Cuz I see these approaching videos and
they're all [ __ ] They're worse than
They're worse than They're worse than
English. I'd say they're even worse than
the people here.
I don't like Americans, bro.
Straight. I don't like them, you know.
So yeah, I'll be in bed today anyway. Still,
how the [ __ ] did we even get laid all them
years, Nicolo? I don't know how we done it.
How would have we done it, bro?
That's why you need to leave the
country. That That's why. Yeah, that's
why you need to leave the country.
And I know if I worked again, I'd have
to be dealing with these entitled
[ __ ] but obviously the way I see
it is you need to go out and earn money.
You know, it doesn't matter how people
act. You know, if that's how people
going to act, I mean, you're earning
money. So, I mean, you're earning money
at the end of the day. Who cares what
people are doing?
You know what I'm saying? Like, who
cares? Who cares what people are doing?
You know, you you know, you need to earn
money. You know, at the end of the day,
you can't change how people going to act.
It's not impossible to get a number.
It's easy to get a number.
And I would have been able to manage it
without the house as well. That's
another thing. How would you been able
to have managed it financially as well?
It's scary, bro. Is it crazy?
And then you get and then if you think
about how depressing it is and then we
actually look back on it, you realize I
never really had it that bad.
And then you get all of these people
that's had it worse than me and they
defend women. It's mad. All these people
that's had it worse than me, which is
probably most people that stick up for
them. It's crazy.
No, I can get one on the street. I had a
blonde one on the street I got a couple
of weeks ago. I've got a few on the street, bro.
But they just don't go anywhere.
They've had it worse than you and they
still defend them. It's funny, isn't it?
It's crazy. They they they defend them
the way they defend them. It's mad.
They defend them. >> Huh?
I dictate the future. Well, it's been
[ __ ] dictating it for the past four
[ __ ] years, son.
It's been dictating it for the past [ __ ]
you know what I mean? How many years?
But her friend was telling me things like
stuff about her and it made me feel bad.
But like I'm not going to tell you
exactly what it was cuz oh let's keep it
between us and [ __ ] in it. But yeah
well I don't know where you're going but
I'm going out I'm leaving this country
on [ __ ] in in November. I don't know
what you're doing.
I'm leaving the country in uh November.
I'll never have to hear it again.
I'll never have to hear it again. The
other boyfriend. Oh, I can't wait. I was
having I was having I was having um
Chinese Indie messaged me yesterday
said, "Oh, you should come, dear.
You should come." She messages me now
again. She said, "Hello, dear."
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
>> Yeah. I don't know how I used to do it.
Imagine trying to do it now. Imagine
three and a half years ago now having
less money trying to do it. Oh, you'd be [ __ ]
Yeah, that's what I said to That's what
I say to LT. Captain, why don't you pick
up your phone, Captain?
You know where I got that from? So, this
guy from Jamaica was doing like my
garden and [ __ ] paid him to do my
garden and he's like, "You all right, Captain?"
He says, "What's that you you're
cooking? I like the smell of that." I
said, "Oh, it's a burger. Do you want
one? I don't like to see people go hungry."
And he's like, "Yeah."
We used to just call each other captain. Captain. Hello, Captain.
I was telling um
I was telling USA Easyy's friend Grezy
about um the dessert thing. She said oh
she said oh she was like oh so so she
ordered herself dessert and obviously
dessert is a people have dessert here but
people don't normally
have it like that. Like some people have
it but it's not really a thing. Like I
don't really have it. I've not had it
that much in my life. Then she'd ordered
herself dessert saying, "Oh, do you want
any?" As if she was [ __ ] paying for
it. I said, "You're not having any
dessert?" And I was thinking in my head,
I said to her friend, it's like, "We're
not all [ __ ] bat [ __ ] like you.
Anyone would think she was [ __ ]
paying for it."
You know what I mean? Grievy. Her friend
was laughing at us. I couldn't believe
she didn't believe some of the things I
was telling her. Yeah.
Yeah. It was funny, bro.
But that's why I got the um She couldn't
believe it. She actually said that
and the laugh was so genuine. Gley.
Yeah. She was telling me like I said
that that Charles is like a bad guy and
[ __ ] like he's he's killed someone back
in his country and she was telling me
bad [ __ ] about him.
See, when you look at him, you just
think he's just like some some normal
guy, you know, that works. But, you
know, he was a bum before that job. She
was telling me, "Yeah, he was a bum. He
had no money. He always used to like
abuse her and shit." And yeah, mad [ __ ]
mad [ __ ] come out, you know.
I couldn't believe some of the [ __ ] I was hearing.
I'm right, Chucky. You can't get rid of the [ __ ]
I had some fried chicken yesterday, Grezy.
It was nice,
but well, it wasn't that nice. Yeah.
See, with fried chicken, you can only
really have it when it just comes out.
All right. It doesn't It doesn't taste
good. You need it when it's just come
out the oven.
Otherwise, it's it's no good.
You ever had like fried chicken when it
just comes out? Why the [ __ ] do you
think they make pizza [ __ ] fresh? Why
the [ __ ] do you think they make grilled
chicken fresh? Cuz it's supposed to be
that way. Them put that they put in that
thing that keeps it warm. It dries it out.
So it needs to like just come out.
Otherwise, if it don't just come out,
then it's dry and yuck.
I love some I like side breast and
middle breast. Greasy. Yeah.
But yeah, if you was trying to date now
with less money, oh [ __ ] you'd be
You would actually be you would be
[ __ ] You would be [ __ ] [ __ ]
I don't know what the [ __ ] you what we
would do. I don't generally don't know.
You'd have to deal with the stress,
money, women. Oh my god. I can do I can
deal with it, bro.
Now I don't need to deal with the women
cuz I know what they're like here. So yeah,
I know what they're like. I know what they're about.
They're just [ __ ]
you know. I only went to [ __ ] I only
went to Birmingham because Monty was
crying. And look at the thanks I got for
it, Greasy. Look at the thanks I got for it.
Is this the thanks I get?
[ __ ] done, you know. Done.
I only feel a bit better now cuz I took some cocon.
So yeah, it's nice cocoon more. Makes
you feel high. Man,
I'm depressed here, bro.
I feel isolated.
This person has not replied back. since Friday. Glad it
see I bet you thought I was going to go
out last week, didn't you, Grezy? No,
I'm dead serious, bro. I'm dead serious.
I've proved my point more than enough times now.
And I'm just okay. I might sound bad,
but I'm just okay.
But I know if I go out again,
I'm not going to be okay. And I'm going
to be mad at myself as well cuz I was
like, you knew what it was going to be
like. You know the s the the the the
story, the sad song story. And then you
done it again. So then I'd start
thinking, am I a [ __ ] [ __ ]
I'd start thinking I'm the [ __ ] you know?
And uh that's it.
They're just ignoring [ __ ]
It's like I said to you, Gres, I would
have went out last week if you convince
me that it's going to be different the
next time I go out. If you sell yourself
to me really good, I'll go out.
If you can really really like make me
believe that the next time I go out will
be different, I'll go out.
They're not going for anyone, but yeah,
you can't do that.
You can't do that.
I don't think anyone can.
I mean, what could anyone say, Grezy?
What could anyone really say, Captain? Yep,
pretty much. Yeah.
And don't you think I've been through
enough in my life? You know, with the
USA Izzy thing, the bullshitting, the
trolling. Do you not think that
someone's been through enough in their
life, you know, to to think that, oh, I
don't want to try him anymore?
You know what I mean?
Do do you not think that like
people have already been through enough
in their life? So that's
that's my take on it. That's my advice. Who's
there? You don't mess me. Oh,
once you've met one, you've met them all. Basically,
I said to Antman, "Are they all the
same?" He says, "Well, they say the same
stuff. They do the same stuff. They have
the same mannerisms. Yeah.
And like I said, it it winds me up just watching it
cuz how could it be you, right? If you
watch all of these other guys, [ __ ] the
people that say, "Oh, the other guys,
other guys do it. Other guys that might
have got lucky at work, might got lucky
on a dating app years ago. All of these
things that don't apply to you. So why
do you see all these different guys in
America and England get the same as you?
They're different than you. They look
different to you and they get exactly
the same [ __ ] None of them are ugly.
There's this African guy that goes out
in London. He sounds like English like
us. He was obviously born here and he's
no word of lie. He's not ugly. And this
guy, I've been watching the same [ __ ]
from him for ages now. I have a
boyfriend. I have a boyfriend. I have a
boyfriend. It seems the same.
It seems It seems the same [ __ ] that
he's getting. Then I said, "Okay, let me
watch some people in America." And then
they get the same [ __ ] as well.
It's funny how people don't bring that
up though, do they, Nikolai? They bring
up the other guys,
which they've got. No, it's no valid
argument because you are not other guys.
You are you you are in the position that
you are in.
So it's like whatever other people done.
Think about it. If I if I kept meeting
that person that I went on a date with
on that Bumble when I come back from
Belgium, I'd still be with them.
It doesn't matter if they're trolling,
bro. They're still getting the same [ __ ]
They Yeah, they're doing it for fun, but
they're still getting the same [ __ ] So,
it's it's not
just because other people do something,
they're not Tik Tok, they're Instagram
vids. Yeah, they might be trolling, but
they're that is generally what they're getting.
It doesn't matter if they're trolling or
not. They're they're, you know, they're,
you know, and some of them are trolling
as well, but it doesn't matter. It just
shows you what it's like here,
man. They're not staged. The ones that I
watch are not staged. You can tell when
they're staged. Trust me, I' I've been
approaching for years, bro, and you can
tell when they're staged. Some of them
are, but the ones I Some of the ones
I've seen are, but the ones that I watch aren't. So,
so that's where we're at.
That's where we're at, lad.
I don't watch him on Tik Tok. I watch
him on Instagram. Yeah.
So, yeah, it would never change though.
It would never change.
Do you remember? H They've all got boyfriends. Yeah.
When they've tried getting rude,
but I feel like a lot of people forget
Grezy. You'll show them all of this
stuff and they'll be, "Oh, you should go
out today." like, "Have you forgot what
I've just told you the the day before
and the day before before?" It's like
they seem to forget things because
they're so [ __ ] and then, "Oh, just
go out and try again." Like, no, we're
not doing that.
We're not doing that, bro.
So, if that westernity look in their
eyes, is it? You can see the westernity
in their eyes.
That's why I don't do it anymore.
But people on Reddit say, "No, you'll
find someone. You'll meet someone.
You'll find someone." I think you
actually have hope until you try again.
That's what I generally think it is. I
think you actually have hope and then
when you actually try again, you
realize, "Oh, there is no hope." And I
think that's what actually wind you up.
Yeah, you are just winding yourself up.
I mean, if you want to go for a drink,
just go for a drink and just do it when
you're drunk. I mean, it's a bit better,
but nah. But I wanted to go to a pub
last week. There's a pub I haven't been
to for a while, but I just couldn't be
bothered wasting money on it just to get
the same [ __ ] I've been getting for years. Yeah,
you are. You are winding yourself up
with it. You are.
Cuz once you've met one, you've met them all sadly. Yeah.
Yep. couple days, couple weeks, you
realize, oh [ __ ] it really is
impossible. That's what I No, but what I
do is I'll go out and think, okay, let
me do a couple of sober.
And then I'll be like, oh [ __ ] And it's
like, oh, damn, I really am going to be
alone forever. Well, my loan, I've been
single. And I thought, oh, and then what
and then what [ __ ] with my head is
then I realized that I don't look like
Timmy Aldridge. I realized that you're
probably above average looking and you
still can't get anything in your own
country and that's the bit that's hard
to accept. And then I just get on the
drink. But then I was going to get on a
drink anyways cuz did you notice you
remember them times I used to like go
out approach and I'd end up drinking and
[ __ ] even if I didn't plan to drink cuz
it was so depressing. You had to drink
like when I went to like read in and
remember when I went all them pl
remember when I went out the whole day
approaching I got smashed after bro
you know I got smashed after that's why
I used to like drink when I was out cuz
it was just too depressing you know
it's just too depressing
because there's no reason for it. You
don't look like Timmy Aldridge, you know,
because you don't look like Tim
Eldridge. There's literally no reason
for it. So then it's like there's
literally no reason for it at all. And
then you just wind yourself up and
that's that's all that happens when you try.
You know, like I said, we're beyond it
now. We're actually beyond it. Um,
then another thing that you got to look
at and you need to uh you need to
realize it's not even just that, right?
When I was on the phone with that uh US
uh USA is friend, yeah, she said that
she's gone on dates with people before
and she didn't like them and she's not feeling them.
And then I'm thinking, what the [ __ ] do
these [ __ ] actually expect? Like what
what do they actually expect? So, it's
like even before you go on a date. Even
when you go on a date, right? Even when
you go on a date with someone, put it
this way, even if you go on a date with someone. Yeah. Um,
think about it like this. Even if you go
on a date with someone, um,
you do realize that like in their head
they've got unrealistic expectations.
That's what they mean by, oh, they don't
like this person. Oh, they don't like
you. Oh, it's because in their head
they've got these these unrealistic
expectations like Romeo and Juliet and
they remain unfulfilled because they're
not realistic. So most of the guys that
they end up going on dates with, they're
just not going to end up liking them
because that's what they mean by they
don't feel the vibe or you know it's
generally because they're expecting
something in their head that don't
exist. Do you understand? Nothing wrong
with you. It's nothing wrong with me.
That's why even if you go on dates, it's
just a complete waste of time
because even if someone's genuinely
serious about it, you know, because
that's what they mean by they don't like
someone, you know, you understand? Or
they don't feel the vibe. That's what it
is. They're expecting some Romeo and
Juliet type of [ __ ] You understand? So
that's how that happened. You see,
which is strange to be honest. But
what do people on Reddit say though, Nicola?
I'd probably be able to go out and drink
and do it drunk, but I don't think I can
do it sober. Not cuz I'm scared to do it
sober, just because of the effects
after, but I wouldn't even do that
nowadays to be honest with you. Waste of time. Oh, yeah.
Do you remember Nicolai? She give baby
Peter some milk.
You're very funny, Joker. Very funny.
You can give baby Peter some milk.
You know what was making me You know
what was making me laugh? Yeah. When I
said to L that imagine you're an account
Yeah. that has kids and you're sat there
with your kids whilst you're sat on
YouTube trolling me.
You know, you know the one that used to
make me laugh is when I was asking
questions and I was typing back. I said,
"So why did my mommy not tell me that
she was my mommy?" And then you wrote,
"She wanted to keep it a secret.
Sig was never your mother, you know."
And I said, "Who was Sig?" And you was
like, "I forgettable one night stand."
It's like you're trying to patronize me in it. Yeah.
And you was trying to patronize me in it.
So then, so what if I was black then,
Nikolai? What if I was a black man?
Yeah, I am completely [ __ ]
I am completely completely [ __ ] Yeah,
completely. Completely [ __ ] I'm so glad
I don't go out anymore, though. I am so
glad. And it used to wind me up like
just a lot of the way the the things are
run in this country. Like apparently
you're not allowed to speak to people in
bars and clubs cuz the staff complain
about you. Just like little annoying
things like that. I'm glad I don't have
to put up with it anymore.
Yeah, I'm [ __ ] as well, bro. I'm completely [ __ ]
It could be worse. You could be a
skinned virgin in a bed suit.
Yeah. I mean, that in itself, I mean,
you need to think about little annoying
things like that before you go out. And
then when I was and then he and he
didn't want and then he didn't want any
of it. And then LJ was like, "Oh, well
maybe maybe he was um maybe he was uh
maybe he didn't want to do anything
because maybe he don't want to lose his
job and then he can't fend for his
kids." I said, "Well, then don't be a [ __ ]
If I if I was about say I was about to
and I knew that I couldn't do anything
to anyone because I'd lose my job or the
money, then I would just not be a
[ __ ] and I would never be in that
position because I'd never be a
[ __ ] Can't be a [ __ ] It's like
what is that? They were using the same
excuse for Kenji and they don't want to
do anything because uh because u they
don't want to lose their job even though
they're the ones that started it. What
the [ __ ] bro? It's not like you've
you've started it.
You know what I'm saying? Like Yeah. And
I told him, "Come and meet me after work."
Yeah. I was going to give it a good
shot, bro. A good good shot. Trust me. I
would have that, bro. [ __ ] that. I don't
care how big the [ __ ] is cuz I would
have just went back with a hammer. So,
I'm not ask me, bro. I don't give a [ __ ]
But I told him come around the corner
multiple times. He wouldn't. I got him
recorded. I said I'll meet him after
work. He weren't interested. So yeah,
like you're going to snatch the drink
out of my hand. Are you [ __ ] mad?
You're not talking to me like that, bro.
Especially not in my own country. Well,
I say it's my own country. I mean, whose
country is it anymore to be honest, you
know? And just little annoying things
like that and like them getting like the
order wrong and
um like the burger. I had to repeat
myself 20 times. Just little annoying
things like that is why it's just not
worth wasting your money in this country
anymore going out. You know, it weren't
just one thing. It was multiple things, you know,
just just things like that, you know.
It's depressing England. I hate it. I
hate going out in England, but I hate it
waiting around for things.
It's a [ __ ] country. It's designed to
annoy you. Like I said, the flag should
be replaced with a troll face. Have you
ever seen a troll face?
This country is designed to annoy you.
Women, gambling, waiting around for
things, government system. It's just a
country that's designed to annoy you.
Probably a bit like America and all them
other nice [ __ ] holes. >> Yeah. Oh, [ __ ] Yeah,
you'll be looking for that change until
the day you die, bro. And it still won't change.
How's it going to change?
How is it going to change?
And man was like, "It's not about them
anymore. It's about you. We know. We've
known what they're like for years." He
said, "It's not about them anymore. It's about you."
You know, he said, "It's not about them
anymore. It's about you.
You just keep watching the same videos.
We just keep watch. Just keep watching
the same videos." He says, "Yeah,
isn't it mad how Antman left before me,
way before me, and and I tried a hundred
times more than he did?"
I just I guess I was just listening to
people on Reddit. Like
I just guess I was expecting it to one
day just change like cuz that's what I
was told. You know, you never know what
the future holds.
The past don't dictate the future.
That's why I was just, you know,
I got one of these delivery jobs, but
I'm not sure if they pay if they
actually pay. So, obviously, I don't
want to go out and do it and then I make
money and then they don't [ __ ] pay me.
What if I go and make some money and
then they don't [ __ ] pay me?
You know what I'm saying?
Then I'll be [ __ ] up in it.
I don't even have a phone that's not blocked.
So I have to buy a [ __ ] new phone.
What if you do it and they don't pay
you? Then you're [ __ ] up in it.
Maybe you will be [ __ ] up.
I just want to lie in bed, bro, and chill.
Yeah, working [ __ ] But I'm sure you
could work five, six hours every other day, bro.
You know, sure you could do that, you know?
I'm sure you could work five six. Say
you got £10 an hour. Yeah.
Yeah. But I would do it for five hours
every other day. I would do it for 5
hours. What's that? 5060?
It's like 250300 a week for what? A
couple of [ __ ] hours. So
yeah, I would could do it for five, six
hours a day or every other day.
How do you know that six hours every
other day or every day
you have a nice paycheck at the end of
the week in it? Yeah.
Yeah. But bro, I'm I'm going in
November, so I know I'm out of here. So
I know in November
the suffering stops. So,
I've got that to look forward to.
I remember I worked like that 9 hours
for 88 pound. It was long, bro.
It was long.
I forgot to watch Oreo yesterday.
I supposed to auto, but I forgot.
Why does Reddit mods ban people? Nicola,
why do they ban people? Huh?
See, I knew I knew he was joker, bro.
I knew you was joker.
I knew he was joker. It's not on the internet. [ __ ]
I could be like that ski virgin in a
bedit. Oh, living with a disabled girl.
So, it could it could always be worse.
Imagine I was skinned like that virgin.
Oh, [ __ ] that, bro.
That skin bastard.
Show these how's the benefit of
pathetic. Anyone can show their [ __ ]
house benefit. How's the benefit up?
Yeah, could do.
So, where did you say easy go? Nicolola. Huh?
Where did she go?
It is depressing, bro.
So what I did with it anymore
so fast enough to to uh click on the
messages when you're negative,
you know, as soon as you write negative stuff,
funny you You speak of Chucky. It's
funny you're speaking of Chucky, right?
I'll show you something.
I'm wearing Chucky boxes. Look,
I'm wearing Chucky boxer shorts. Chucky boxes.
Just remember that.
I was thinking last night, how what's
the point of being bull without a dick
if you're not going to use it?
What's the point of being born with a
dick if you're not going to use it?
You might as well just not be born with
a dick and just pee for a bag or something.
What's the point of being born with
something you can't use?
Pointless, isn't it? It's crazy
just being frustrated every day thinking
about your situation.
How comes they they give you this
westernized look then
they you can see the westernity in their
eyes. Why is that? Is it because the Tik Tok
do you think?
Yep. That's pretty much
a horrible way to live, isn't it?
A horrible way to live.
The reckon virgin boy will lose his
virginity this this year. Huh?
Virgin boy will never lose his vility.
Why are we called a virgin boy?
Virgin boy. Virgin boy will never get laid.
He will do remember when he tried it on
with USA is he but she rejected his ugly ass.
I do you know what USA Izzy's friend was
telling me? She's like, "Oh, yeah. I
knew." As soon as you met her, she said,
"Oh, yeah. This this cute guy approached
me." I gave him my number because he was cute.
That's what she told her friend. She She
rang her friend up and said, "Oh, I
think I just done something bad." She
said, "What did you do?" She said, "Oh,
this guy just come and spoke to me and I
gave him my number because he was cute."
That was funny as [ __ ] it.
It's funny it joker. This piggy [ __ ] pretty [ __ ]
Uh, they would say they have a boyfriend
when they don't.
They would say they have a boyfriend,
but they but they don't. Yeah.
Do you remember the first Isabelle
Nicolo? The UK is about Oh. Oh.
You can, but I won't be there.
You can try, but I won't be there.
I'm out of here, mate. I don't go around
in circles. I'm not a [ __ ]
You can try, but I won't be there.
Easy loves edit. I'm counting the down
the the days down till November, boy. I can't wait.
[ __ ] never try again.
[ __ ] I've earned enough of it to last
me a [ __ ] lifetime. You can try, but
I won't be there.
Yeah. Run to the boys in blue. I don't
understand what it is with these people
running to the boys in blue. Yeah.
I don't know why they run to the boys in blue.
Bro, why am I going to go out and
approach people? They've all got
boyfriends. I don't want to be [ __ ]
[ __ ] up people's relationships.
They claim that they've all got
boyfriends, so they say,
right? So, why am I going to want to be
bothering people in relationships? Think
about it. Every single woman in this
country seems to have a boyfriend.
Makes you wonder, doesn't it? They all
seem to have boyfriends.
Why do they want to Why do they want to Um,
why do you want to uh bother people
that's got a boyfriend? They all seem to
have boyfriends. So, apparently, so
they all have boyfriends, so they say.
So, why would I want to bother people?
That's all got what that's got in the relationships.
Bit rude on me, is it?
But do you know the thing is people on
Reddit tell me to try like bars and
clubs and stuff. Nicola,
someone told me to go to pubs and approach lassis.
They said, "Have you tried the pub?" I
said, "Yeah, I've tried the pub loads of times."
They say, "Try like a pub or something.
But what what if you're approaching the public?
Yeah, they say the street is weird
trying to pub.
Well, I won't be doing it because I'm
going Thailand. So,
I'm not without any interaction because
I'm going Thailand. I'm getting away
from the [ __ ]
Should have done this [ __ ] years ago.
But yeah, anyways, I'm not doing it.
I'll get all what I want when I'm in Thailand
and I won't have to deal with any [ __ ] behavior.
What a life, eh?
I don't need interaction from anyone.
I'm good. I'm out of here in a couple of
months anyway. So,
I can't wait. Can't wait. I can't wait.
I got way. Yay.
None of this [ __ ] ever again.
I've tried everything,
bro. You're speaking to me here. You're
not speaking to anyone else. You're
speaking to me.
I have tried everything.
What's Saturday football saying?
Interesting. But yeah, I have tried
that. I've tried everything, bro.
Bro, what part of I'm done? Do you not
understand? Do you not understand? I am done.
I am finished. I am done. I am leaving.
I'm not interested. You know
I am not interested. You understand?
I'm not interested.
I am done. Uh no
two weeks in counting. I'm not interested.
I think we're going to break the record
this time, bro.
This is how fed up you get of it. This
is really how fed up you actually get of it.
Anyways, I need to watch some Instagram
videos, so I'll be back later. Anyways, see you.