Captain.
Oh, [ __ ] Captain,
that was yummy. Captain.
Oh, sorry, mate. I know I shouldn't
entertain Virgin Boy, but you know, you
have to mate. That vindaloo just brings
it all back. Oh, [ __ ]
Oh, [ __ ] hell, Grezy. That was yummy.
That was I am stuffed. So, we can't do a
Vindaloo video without mentioning Virgin Boy.
Feeling better. Of course, bro. I'm
feeling fine, bro. I'm out of here in a
couple of months.
I didn't go McDonald's.
I went uh I got a vinderoo.
Yeah, I'm fine, but I'm out of it in a
couple of months. Get the [ __ ] Yeah, I
done a video on the vindaloo. Did you see it?
So, a skin virgin in the bed. Won't get
into that, but yeah.
Yeah, I'm I'm fine, bro. I'm out of here
in a couple of months. Can't wait.
I can't wait. Rey, I can't [ __ ] wait. Yeah.
Oh, the [ __ ] tire's gone. [ __ ] sake.
I was watching some WWE videos, Grezy.
Yeah, I was watching some WWE videos.
Yeah, I've done that ages ago.
Yeah, for November. I done that ages
ago, bro. Get with the times, man. [ __ ] hell. Mhm.
There ain't no life here, bro, in this country.
There ain't no life for anyone in this country.
I'm going in November, like I just said. Yep.
This country. Are you proud of me,
Greasy? I wouldn't have been out for two
weeks now. You proud of me, lad? Yeah.
No, I didn't change that at all. It's
always been November.
Yeah, I know, man. I know. You should try it.
No, I didn't. No, I didn't change it.
cuz it's got to stop in this country,
bro. This is This has got to stop.
This has got to stop, bro. You know, put
an end to it. Otherwise, the [ __ ] is the
point if you can't break a cycle? We
need to put a stop to it. You know,
that's what I've done. Yeah.
Do you have McDonald's today?
Do you have McDonald? Bless you. Yes.
It was [ __ ] lush. It was.
Yeah. I'm not having another takeway now
until like Saturday
cuz I need to stop.
It's a day today. One day a [ __ ] Virgin. Whoa.
Yeah, that never lasted between me and USA
is his friend.
You randomly blocked me, Green Z.
I can officially say, bro, I've been put
off them for life, bro. I don't want any
dealings with them anymore, bro.
No [ __ ] Americans. No,
I mean, the whole thing is was just
[ __ ] up. The whole thing is just
[ __ ] up, bro.
But this is one of the reason why we're leaving.
Obviously, we're not in America, but I
mean, same same thing.
Western westernized. Yeah.
>> [ __ ] all of them, man. [Music] [Applause] It's nice.
I think like I said, it would only be
the once I've run out this month. I
think Grey, that's enough for me.
What's enough for me, mate?
I'm [ __ ] sick of it.
I'm [ __ ] sick to [ __ ] death of it.
It be a do my [ __ ] nut.
We should try that speed dating thing
for the LS actually. You know what?
Yeah, I I should try that speed dating
thing for the LS.
I think it would just be so hilarious.
I think it's like 30 pound.
The speed dating thing. I've never tried that before.
I can imagine what it would be like, but
I don't think you could knock something
until you've actually tried it. But
giving it give it a little whirl.
It'll probably be a bunch of people that aren't interested like always,
yet they would pay for a [ __ ] dating
thing. But who knows?
You know, the thing is, right, is I just
can't see how that would work.
I just can't see how speed a would work.
I would try it, but I just don't see how
it could possibly work.
It's on my channel
I just don't see
I don't see how it could work
cuz what woman can't get any man they
want nowadays with the amount of simps
there is? So why would they be speed dating?
So, you're going to try and convince me
that all of these men only wanted them
for one thing? I just can't see how it
would it would work.
I mean, surely they must get approached
on the street or something, you know?
So, I don't see how Bye-bye, Timmy.
Yeah, that's Timmy.
I can spot Timmy straight away. Yeah,
USA is his friend blocked me. Oh, no.
America's [ __ ] bro. America's [ __ ]
Oh, always, mate. Always, mate. We have
good curry houses here, lad. We're not
in some [ __ ] [ __ ] hole in Kent.
[ __ ] Little India, I call it.
That is a [ __ ] [ __ ] hole.
All Tim Romney is [ __ ] [ __ ] It is. I
know. I've been there enough times. An
absolute [ __ ] hole.
The [ __ ] out there, mate. [ __ ] [ __ ] out there. Yeah,
that's virgin lad.
That's [ __ ] virgin, man. It's where virgins live. Yes.
So, yeah. What do you think about the
speed dating thingy? I can't possibly
imagine how it would actually work.
Can't imagine it.
Yeah, that's cuz Timmy's has Has Timmy
been posting some videos or something?
Has he been posting some videos?
But listen, Karen,
if you're watching me, lad, I know watch
me bro, you need to on a on a serious
note now. Yeah,
you need to break the cycle,
you know, going out and
like gambling every month to try to win
more money and then you end up skin
because at the end of the day, lad,
unless you break a cycle, you're [ __ ]
And I know cuz I I used to do it 5 years ago.
used to just gamble and
you know saying you're
drinking a curry. Oh, is a stalker still
stalking me? That's nice. He's a proper
fat virgin, bro. The more he does this
[ __ ] every day stalking, you could just
tell he's some 40y old virgin his mom.
Um, so basically, yeah. So, yeah,
Kieran, you like me, I'll give you an
example. I broke the cycle. You know, I
booked Thailand. You know, I've not been
out for almost two weeks. And you know,
you get in your head saying, "Oh, yeah.
Go out, try again, try again." But you
already know the result. So, it's like I
said, unless you break the cycle, you're [ __ ] Bye-bye.
But yeah, unless you break the cycle,
you're screwed, bro.
That's why I broke the uh gambling cycle
here. Not that I end up skin, just
because of the mood swings and [ __ ] you
know, the mood swings it gives you and whatnot.
But still thing, it's still the same
thing. You break a cycle, you know?
That's why I'm leaving this depressing country.
It's [ __ ] depressing. The only time
it's sort of depressing is when you're
in your in your house, in it, Greasy. Yeah.
What in my what my situation when you go
out? Is that what you mean?
What? Like my what? In my situation,
Greg. Yeah, it is.
Yeah. And it's like what Antman says,
it's not them, it's me. You know what
they're like. You know what you need to
do. It's like what Ant-Man says. It's
like it's not about them anymore. You
know what they're like. We've been know
what they're like for years. You know,
we need to give up. We, you know, you
need to leave and [ __ ] It's not about them anymore. Yeah. Yeah, man.
Like I say, I should have gave up after
that USA thing to be honest. But
I'm pretty sure Greasy would have gave
up after the USA thing in it.
Well, no, cuz I was getting [ __ ] that
whole year. So,
I was getting [ __ ] that year. So, I mean,
not necessarily, but then they just got
bad the year after.
Where where it only really got bad
since last summer.
That's when it started getting bad. Something's changed.
I'm telling you, something's changed, Grezy.
Something's changed in them 18 months.
In the last 18 months or so, something's
changed, Grezy. I'm telling you. Cuz
now it's just [ __ ]
Oh, this one. You know what this one
woman said, Greasy? Right.
She said, "Oh, it's not practical to
meet me because I live in London and she
lives in Liverpool." You know what I
hate about these [ __ ] bro? Yeah.
What I hate about these [ __ ] right,
is as soon as they can use an excuse or
they feel they can use an excuse, they
do. That's what I hate about them. Like,
if I was living in Liverpool, you'd meet
me. Like, if you was living in London,
you'd meet me. They just use [ __ ]
excuses. And to be honest with you,
mate, the only time distance is is an
excuse if someone lives in [ __ ] America
or [ __ ] Australia. That's the only
time distance is is would would would
would be an issue.
They even use distance as an excuse.
They use excuses, bro.
They love using distance as an excuse.
Have you noticed that?
I can't believe she her friend spoke to
me on a phone. Uh,
and then she blocked me.
She actually thought I was actually
going to go over and hurt her friend.
That's mad, bro. It is [ __ ] bro.
They don't like people that are too short.
Well, saying that [ __ ] nonslegs is
like a 6' nothing cuz he's still a
virgin. So, who knows, mate. Yeah.
Yeah. Greasy. She was going to whoop her
friend's ass. Isn't it?
Why did it make you laugh, Greasy, when
she was getting me tempted to want to
start the whole thing again? When she
was like, "Oh yeah, I was going to get
seven people to shoot you." I was going
to start again, bro. Yeah.
Give it a whirl. Yeah.
>> Why did that make you laugh?
>> You laugh at very serious feelings, lad.
Lava things like that. One sec.
Mont is nowhere to be seen as
I can't believe this red star spends all
his life stalking me, bro.
Oh my god. He's a stalker. Mic.
He's a [ __ ] stalker, mate.
Why is he stalking me?
That scoop never comes on my channel
anymore. I saw him on LJ's the other
day. He never comes on my channel anymore. Scoop.
I thought I was making a new friend
there and then she blocked me. Greasy,
you think that's a madness? Greasy.
[ __ ] that, bro. Oh [ __ ] What's it?
So, yeah, no football bets on um
Saturday and uh I don't like the lineup. No,
no, I don't like the lineup. Uh, list
finally lose it.
And you finally lose it.
My bet should have come in [ __ ] on um
was it Saturday or Tuesday?
One of the two.
Yeah, I'm not betting on Saturday,
I don't think. No,
Stephen. Now, we should put 600 pound on
a double. Both teams to score. Why don't
we put 600 pound on a double? Both teams to score.
We should do that.
We should do them at 600 pound on two teams.
Nice little,200 m return. 1200 win.
What do you think? We give it a whirl.
600 pound on two teams. Oh, imagine that.
You'd be [ __ ] laughing, wouldn't you?
That coming, mate.
Would you do it? 600 on two teams. [ __ ] bro. Jesus Christ. Imagine that.
and then going and collecting the money
in the bookies. Breezy,
do you reckon I'd pay you Steven Howard
if you put 600 on two teams?
Do you reckon they would pay you?
If you won
If you put 600 on two teams, do you
reckon they would pay you if you won?
reckon I'd actually pay you like 17800 in
What in cash?
You're good though, ain't it?
Imagine that. Just collecting 17, 18,
100 pound casually
the next day.
You good at it? Yeah, true.
Why don't you do that, Greasy? Put put
um 600 pound on two teams.
You should do it.
600 pound both teams to score a double.
You'll be laughing if it wins, matey.
How much would you even get? Let me look it up.
Let me have a look.
So if you put £600 on it, we'd get $1890 back.
It's a good return, isn't it?
That is a good return, mate. [ __ ] hell.
Imagine that. Imagine going on a piss
share and knowing that you've won that
bet and you can just collect the money
the next day.
That would be ace, bro.
I should have done it when I had that
like when I won that money in the
casino. I should have put like
500 on a football bet.
Yeah, it' be nice, isn't it?
Would you ever put that kind of money on
the football Gene?
[ __ ] that, ain't it?
[ __ ] that. You'd be mad though, wouldn't
you? smashed the shop.
You'd smash the shop up though if they
didn't pay out.
Your mom never called me gay when I was
[ __ ] her last night.
And yo, another one. Don't talk [ __ ]
Yeah. Behind my [ __ ] behind my back if
you're never going to say to my face,
bro, about oh, imagine being scared of
PJ, bro. You're scared. You can't even
come in hangouts.
You can't even [ __ ]
come under a real account, bro. You You
How long have you been scared for?
Yeah, I'll do nothing, bro. You're
hiding behind a fake account. Shut up.
Come and meet me and you'll see what I'll do.
I'll do, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
Don't just start typing and actually
come and hang out. So, meet me, you silly [ __ ]
If I could get my hands on one of you
people, you Ricky Milling, I'd love just
like one minute with one of you.
Just one minute, bro. Like, honestly, I
swear down. Just one minute. You, Red
Star, Virgin Boy, that Ricky. Oh, just
one minute. I'd love with you, bro.
Really? Really, man.
Yeah, I'm not even joking.
Yeah, run away and cry again, bro. I
will never run away from you, you little [ __ ]
Never run away from you, bro. Never run
away from you. Why don't you join the hangouts?
You're not scared, are you?
You're not scared, are you, mate?
You're not scared.
You're not scared, are you?
Come on, Greasy. Let's do the bet, man.
mate. Yeah, I should have had, you know,
when I put 80 and I got it to 285, you
know, the first week of the football. I
wish I had [ __ ] 600 600 on it then,
mate. [ __ ] hell.
Uh, you are a virgin.
You are a virgin.
Yeah, I'm a virgin. Good joke, bro.
That's why there's like videos of me
having sex and [ __ ] Yeah. Good one,
bro. Good one. It almost made me laugh.
Yeah. That's why there's videos of me in
bed with women. Amigga, my dick sucks.
See, I'm a virgin. Uh-huh. Yeah. I'm a virgin, bro.
Proper proper virgin.
Uh-huh. Yeah. Proper one.
Like, imagine we had it on it then. [ __ ] Grezy.
But you would just spend on [ __ ]
McDonald, wouldn't you?
You would spend a£1,900 on McDonald's.
Wouldn't you agree with it? Bless you. God bless.
That's a [ __ ] big risk, bro.
Oh, [ __ ] me.
Am I insane? No.
You would [ __ ] cry. I think I'd smash
the shop up if I lost that, bro. I'm not
going to lie.
You smashed the shop up in it, Grezy.
I want that. I'd probably book another
holiday to be honest.
What about you, Greavvesy? I think I'd
book another holiday.
The first week of the football, I got I
got given good odds as well.
I got good I got given really good odds. [ __ ] hell.
That's scary, bro.
I guess it's good if you wanted like
quick money really fast, but
you lose then.
Yeah, it's not good, bro. are there. It's not.
You need to meet me, bro, so I can smash
your face in. Come on.
Come on, man. So I can smash your face in.
Imagine that. Greaves. Eh,
I put like 600 on it. Then I won and I
put all the winnings on um
by [ __ ] I put all the winnings on
for the next week. We imagine that
I would be loaded.
Imagine that. Greasy.
But [ __ ] hell. Would you imagine that?
Oh my [ __ ] god.
That be mad.
Greasy, we need to start betting, lad.
We need to start betting.
What do you think?
You think we
I can't believe I won two football bets
in a [ __ ] row, lad.
I can't believe that.
I actually can't believe that, bro. madness.
Oh, bless you then. If you're saving
£500 a month, then we
Oh, bless you then. Bless
That's so cute.
You wouldn't be able to say that much if
you was going out drinking, Greasy.
You wouldn't be able to save that amount
if you was [ __ ] going out drinking
[ __ ] every week or nah.
You'd be [ __ ] up. You would be [ __ ]
I ain't been out for like two weeks cuz
I just can't be bothered.
I've outgrown it, Grey. I've outgrown it.
I want to do that one time, you know,
put like500 on a double both teams to
score, but I don't think I've got the
nerves for it, bro.
I don't think I got the nerves for that. [ __ ] me.
But I can imagine the buzz like you're
drinking on a Saturday. Yeah, you've won
your bet, ready to collect in the
morning. Like that would be sick. Well,
you could do it there and then, but [ __ ]
be a lot of money to carry on you, in it. No, that's
that's insane, bro.
I lost £100 on the football bet. [ __ ]
Where was it?
Was that one last week? Was it £100? [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, if you lose a slip, you're [ __ ]
No, I'm sure there's a way. Like, if you
can prove what time you went in and
[ __ ] I'm sure there's a way around that.
Sure. Sure. away.
I kind of do want to put like a big bet
on like that, but
nope. Cuz then if you lose, you got to
start the savings all over again, don't you, Grezy?
You got to start all over again, don't you?
You'd have to start all over again, wouldn't you? [ __ ] that. Nah. Yeah.
Oh, is that man right though? Um,
Reevesy, he said, "I would have left a
long time ago if I had to put up with
the [ __ ] that you put up with."
He said, "I would have left a long time ago
if I had put up with the [ __ ] that you have.
That's what he said.
The [ __ ] that you put up with, he said. Yeah. These
are going a bit, bro.
I need to watch oil, man. I still got
round to watching them.
Yeah, I'm not doing any bets, bro. Let's
put 500 pound on two teams.
Come on, Stephen. Come on.
[ __ ] that, bro. Absolutely. [ __ ] that.
I don't feel I could do that, bro. 600
pound. I don't feel I could do that, man. Honestly,
no. Do 600.
Why not 600? [ __ ] Yeah.
What do you think of USA is friend? Um
Steven Howard blocking PJA
blocking Peter Belly.
[ __ ] Americans, bro. [ __ ] them.
[ __ ] their 911 asses.
Yeah, I think I'm up maybe still about 180.
I think I'm up about 180. Yeah,
[ __ ] their day.
[ __ ] their 9/11 trolling asses, bro. [ __ ] them. Yeah.
Why is it funny, Stephen? Now, that
she's a troll.
She was a truck.
No, they are mates. They are mates. They
are. I've seen pictures of them together.
She said she was going to shoot me.
That is jokes, bro.
Not me, matey.
Do you think you could date um
someone that lives in Liverpool, Steven
Howard? I think you can.
Yeah, you can date someone that lives in Liverpool.
Just another excuse, isn't it?
Yeah, she was trolling hard, bro.
Yeah, she had the accent as well. She
had a mad accent, bro.
We was talking for like 5 hours.
She's a Scorpio like me. She said her
dad died. I was like, "Oh, my dad died as well."
Yeah. She was telling me how like she's
been abused and that in the past
and [ __ ] And Yeah. Madness, bro.
[ __ ] America, bro. [ __ ] America. [ __ ]
Americans. [ __ ] American women.
Can't stand Yanks, bro. Yep. Maybe.
All right, Captain.
That's how I start my combo with LT. You right, Captain. Captain,
you are captain. [Music]
I wish I had [ __ ] put all my money on
that both teams to score, you know, the
first week and then the second week do
it all again cuz I won the first week,
Steven Hour, but then I won the second week.
I wish I put all my money on the first
one and the second one. Oh, I would have been rich.
I would have been rich, lad.
I would have been rich.
[ __ ] How did I win two in a row? We won
twice in a row.
What if I go out approaching Wedley?
What will happen if I go to the bars and clubs approaching? Um,
I don't know, bro. I don't bet that league.
So, I'm not sure
Yeah, I don't bet. That's what I mean. I
don't bet that. Yeah, that's what I
mean. I don't bet the cup thing. Know
what I mean?
But if I go out approaching the bars and clubs badly, Would
it be different? Huh?
What is the name? Anyways,
I'm gone. Yeah, I'll be back tomorrow.