Oh, [ __ ] it.
>> Nice to see my ass still being sed
every single day on YouTube. That's
nice, bro. What happened to this bed?
Oh my god, bro.
I feel sorry for these disabled people,
bro. Their disabilities are so bad that
they don't even they keep getting
themselves confused with me.
>> They are the skin virgins. Why do they
keep talking about themselves? Why do
they keep talking about themselves every day?
Now, do you know when I was like um
remember what I was saying um like from
like 3 days ago? Yeah. About how there's
no point showing these people anything?
Obviously, obviously they know the
truth, but I mean like they're never
going to like give you credit for it.
This is exactly what I'm talking about.
Like when I was speaking about with the
women with the money
because they're all 40-year-old virgins
[ __ ] sat on YouTube no life every
day. But I mean that's not the [ __ ]
point. like this is exactly what I mean
cuz like when I tried explaining this
stuff to this Joe right um
they you didn't understand it because
then I then I realized oh it's a
disabled community so then I realized oh
like there's no point. It's like you
know I just went on some [ __ ] thing
that popped up. I don't even know why
this shit's popped up and they're saying
I'm a virgin. I'm a virgin. I mean, how
many times have I shown me having sex
with people and they still try to call
me a virgin? Just like how I've tried to
meet people and people I've not met.
Just like I've shown more money than
everyone. Like I said, it's like I
continuously say, if you're not fat and
ugly and old like these people,
they get jealous and they find reasons
to dislike someone. So then when someone's disliked,
oh [ __ ] they will dismiss anything that they're shown.
>> It's just a disabled community really.
I mean, it's probably one of the only
communities you probably couldn't even
have a debate on because they're so [ __ ] disabled.
The [ __ ] is wrong with wearing Chucky boxes?
What's wrong with wearing Chucky boxes
that And you're saying I'm almost 28.
You've been saying I'm almost 30 for 5
years and I'm still knowing they're 30.
I'm telling you, bro, that's their
little safety net there.
That's their little thing that they use
to to to to make themselves feel better.
the fact that they're in their 40s.
They're in their 40s and their life is [ __ ] over.
Oh, [ __ ] Wrong thing. Their lives is
over. That's why they're sat on YouTube
every day stalking. Ain't got to lie,
bro. I could be 30 right [ __ ] now.
These people in their 40s.
[ __ ] sat on YouTube every [ __ ]
day. You know, you wouldn't be able to
tell me I'm near [ __ ] 40, would you?
There you go.
Yeah, man. They're jealous of anyone
that's got a better life than them, bro.
I'm telling you, these these little
mongos in this community, it's a proper [ __ ] community.
[ __ ] they're absolute losers. And you
you know it's jealousy because they all
fling to one person and they don't do it
for reaction. They don't do it for
reaction because I've proved many many
times what happens when you do not react
to these people. They still do it. They
do it because they're jealous. Someone
doing stuff for reaction is Yeah, I've
explained it a million times. I'm not
going to keep repeating myself, but
yeah, they don't do it for no [ __ ]
reaction, bro. [ __ ] do they?
Cuz like I said yesterday, what if you
just stopped and saying them for 10
years? What? So every every day for 10
years, they would they would have
stopped. They will never stop, bro. What
the [ __ ] Whether they got a reaction or
they didn't get a reaction,
I'm just explaining why it's pointless
showing this anything to these people anymore.
They're just fat, ugly losers in their
40s, ain't got a life who just able to
leave the house.
That's what it is. Um [Music] yeah,
it's not a funny reaction though, is You
don't get a funny reaction.
You don't get people braiding. You don't
get people smashing up things. So,
they're just sad, pathetic, jealous
bastards that ain't got a light. All of
them. Jamie Thompson, that Ricky
Milling, that Red Star, they're just
fat, ugly bastards that ain't got a
light. Why else would somebody sit on
YouTube reacting their life away free of
[ __ ] free of charge? and you don't
even get a response 99% of the [ __ ]
time. Who who in their right mind would
do that, bro? If they weren't skin and
they weren't a M and then it's
themselves that they're talking about.
You know what I'm saying? Everything
that they say is about their own bongo life.
Do you understand what I'm saying? Run over.
I want the [ __ ] over.
Yeah, they're proper bongos.
Proper proper bongos.
Proper disabled people.
You think the Mong You think the Mongols
would ever stop?
>> Nah, I don't think the Mongols and they
would ever stop. They're Mongos.
Nah, I don't think they will ever stop, bro.
They're [ __ ] disabled.
They are [ __ ] disabled, bro.
Disabled, fat, ugly people that hate the
world because their lives a [ __ ] up.
That's where all of this anger and this
whole keyboard warrior [ __ ] comes from.
You know, all of this anger and keyboard
warrior [ __ ] comes from. The fact that
they're fat, ugly, ain't got no life,
ain't got no money. That's where all of
this [ __ ] comes from with these ugly people
like Red Star. And it's fact. It's not
even reacting. It's it's speaking facts
about that them for them to do what they
do every day on YouTube. It's not It's
not reacting like facts. You can't. I'm
gonna do this. That's what you call an
actual funny reaction. What Timmy used
to do. It's just spewing facts. It's not
even reacting. It's spewing facts,
which is what we've been doing years
about these people, lad. You know what
I'm saying? Like
I just been like, so what? So what? Just
because someone's almost 28. I'm not
almost 28. Get married, right? What? So
you're not allowed to wear Chucky boxes? Says who?
Says who? some 40 odd duo that's sat on
YouTube stalking people that you're
jealous of every day for free. Is that
is that coming from you
and then you're writing comments trying
to call me a virgin? This is this is
what I mean. Yeah. This is what I'm
saying how with these people, right? You
should never show anything, money,
anything ever again. I know I will never
ever ever ever ever because like I said,
it's what you show what you show they
just dismiss it anyways. what you do,
they just dismiss it anyways, you know?
So, like it's it's it's just crazy, bro.
And I'm not reacting. I'm just I'm just
saying how it is.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
It's a it's a it's a disabled community
full of mongers that ain't got a life.
Ugly people that ain't got a life. Think
about it like this, bro. Let's let's
let's let's see what these people look like.
Let's start seeing what these people
look like. This red star, this other
Let's start seeing what they look like,
bro. They will never show their face cuz
they're fat, ugly montas. That they're
the ones that they're talking about
themselves every day. Fat, ugly montas
sat on YouTube every day. Ain't got to lie.
They're fat, ugly, and disabled. That's
why they do not show their face. And
every single person that has been on
here and has shown their face, they've
all been fat and ugly.
This is why they call you the manta.
This is why they call you that. Because
you're a million times better looking
than them. And if you're not a million
times better looking than them, then
they'd show their face.
Think about it, bro. I'm on a community,
right? Let's say I'm on an Oreo man
community. Yeah. It's a disabled
community as well, right?
Think of say I went on an Oreo man on
Oreo man's community, right? And let's
just say I started going on there. Let's
just say they didn't know me and I said,
"Oh, you're all [ __ ] ugly. You're all
monties. You're all this. You're all
that. You're all this." And then they
and they said, "Oh, then they turn
around and say, "Really? Well, why don't
you show your face?" The only reason
you'd be reluctant to show your face is
if you're a fat ugly bastard. Just like
Red Star, just like the bomb, just like
Jamie Thompson, just like all of these
fat, ugly, disabled mongos that can't
get up on YouTube. You know what I'm
saying? Like you that's the only reason
you wouldn't show your face cuz that cuz
that, bro, listen look at like I keep
saying, bro, look at the trend. Look at
all of the people that's done this in
the past and what happens when they've
been found out about their looks.
They're they're probably the ugliest
thing you've you've seen in the in the
world, right? or for at least many,
many, many, many years. This is why they
do all of this stalking. They hate the
fact that you're better looking than
them and you're younger than them. And
they can't do anything about it because,
bro, they're not going to come in your
door. They're not going to fight you.
They'll try to get the black man to do
the dirty work, but the black man's not
interested in their [ __ ] So, you
understand what I'm saying, bro? This is
where all of it comes from.
You know what I'm saying? And it's not a
reaction because they don't get a
reaction. They just get owned. So, it's
not a re a reaction is what Timmy gives.
You know what I'm saying? I'm sick of
people saying that they do it for
reaction because they don't do it for
reaction. They [ __ ] well don't do it
for reaction. And even if they did do
it, what the [ __ ] are they doing? This
is the bit I don't understand. If if
they're trying to get a reaction, what
are they doing? What the [ __ ] are they
doing? They are reacting. No. So, that's
the disabled part about it is the whole
thing is so disabled.
All of it is the most disabled thing you
never you never hear of. Bro,
I was on Instagram yesterday, bro, and
um some thing some Chevel Cole thing
come up and it reminded me of the Virgin boy
trying to fit in. I told you it was a
trend, bro. I was think I was going to
do a video on it. Um they said, "Oh,
Shit." I told you they all copy each
other, bro. I told you, bro. When do I
ever lie to you? I told you it's a
trend. They all copy each other to look good. Yeah.
They all copy each other.
They're like, "Oh, who's this?" Oh,
they're hot. Lover heart. Yeah, they're copycats.
Cuz isn't it funny, right, Nicolo? No
one says this about any any normal woman.
Any normal [ __ ] woman. No one says it
about any of them. You know, ones that
I've been with, ones that you've seen,
no one has ever said, "If you don't find
this person attractive, you're gay."
Have you noticed? You never ever hear
it. But as soon as it's cow, you're gay.
Homo. Literally, bro, do you remember?
Yeah. It's [ __ ] mad. Like,
they literally will say, "No, homo.
Homo. Okay. Okay." But yet all of the
other people that you've been with or
maybe people that you've seen on the
street, nobody would ever say this stuff.
It's cuz they're copying each other.
Just like the virgin boy. Virgin boy in
a bedsit. They're copycats.
They got no mind of their own.
You don't find attractive [ __ ] gay homo vibes.
Hi my vibes. Oh yeah, hot.
>> You remember that one? Nicolo [ __ ] virgin.
Where did that Joe account, bro?
Where's that [ __ ] Joe account?
I know. I'll be leaving soon. Greasy. I
can't wait. Oh, funny enough, I woke up
today and I saw yet another approach
video. You're not you're going to laugh
at this one, Grezy. So, um you they're
in Chicago, right? Cuz that's where the
guy was approaching. And there's this
woman from uh London and she said, "I'm
going to see my boyfriend." Oh, right.
So, you've come all the way to Chicago from England
um to see your boyfriend. Not Not sure
that. And And you're meeting him just
now. Well, I'm not I'm not sure that
really works though, does it? How the
[ __ ] can you date someone living [ __ ]
10 hours away on a [ __ ] plane? You
know, that's that is when distance is a
[ __ ] excuse when someone lives in
[ __ ] America. They're just [ __ ]
They're just [ __ ] [ __ ] Like, I
just I don't see any change. Like, even
when I'm not doing it, yeah, I'm never
I'm never seeing any change. There's no
there's nothing new about any of them.
It's just different characters.
No, I watch this guy in America. He does
approaches. He does them in like
different places like California, Chicago.
So, you're from London and you're just
meeting your boyfriend now in another country.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Uh-huh. So, why you not
with your boyfriend now? You're in
another country. Why would you be with
your boyfriend now? It's such [ __ ]
They say the same things. They do the
same stuff. Greasy, you know what I used
to say to the virgin virgin boy? Um,
that all women are the same. And you
say, "You don't know all women." And I I
used to say, "I know [ __ ] more than
you, [ __ ] The [ __ ] off, you virgin."
Um, I I I used to just say it because I
used to just say it.
I don't know why. I used to just say it
just for the sake of saying it. Now, if
you none of these videos are the are any
different than just different
characters. That's literally all it is.
Yeah. Oh, yeah. Someone Oh, yeah.
Somebody said to me on Instagram,
there's Oh, I said it will never change.
They said, "Yeah, never know though." I
said, "I know. I I know it won't. I know
it won't change." You said, "You never
know." I said, "I know." Because it
would have by now. It would have by now.
Think of the odds. Think of the odds,
bro. Think of the odds. If something
would have changed, it would have
already changed. It would have changed
now. We wouldn't be having this
conversation. It would have been
changed. You was going up and down the
country. It would have changed now. It
would have already changed by now if
something was going to change.
Things don't just change years later.
Like, it's it would have changed by now. 100%.
You've tried more than anyone in the
[ __ ] world. It will never change
ever. Even when I'm not Even when I'm
not doing it and I'm watching other people,
it will never I'll be waiting till the
I'll be waiting till I'm [ __ ] 90
years of age.
What if you write negative messages? Nicolola,
what if you write negative messages? How
fast are they to reply to negative messages? Nicolola,
how fast they to reply to negative messages?
I'm so glad I don't hear that anymore.
As much as I miss drinking Guinness and,
you know, having baby Guinnesses and
[ __ ] I'm so glad I've been off it, bro.
Like, I really am, you know.
Yeah. It will never ever ever change. Yeah,
what I was saying is um
yeah, [ __ ] I forgot what I was saying there. Um
Oh, virgin board in there. Yeah, they
respond to negativity. Yeah.
Funny that ain't it? They respond to negativity.
So, what's the chances that one in
Chicago had a boyfriend? Nah. None of
them are boyfriends.
None of them have boyfriends. [ __ ]
[ __ ] Maybe three out of 10. Like I
said, three out of 10 have boyfriends.
Three out of 10, maybe.
You know that boyfriends?
I've heard that one before. I'm going to
meet my boyfriend. Yeah. It's just an
NPC thing that they say. They say all
the same stuff.
Yeah. And then I And then I caught And
then I caught her out
and then she blocked me. Yeah. Yeah.
Bro, I've been dealing with these games
and this [ __ ] for [ __ ] years,
bro. I've had somebody from Liverpool
saying that the distance is too far when
it's not. I mean, Liverpool's it's not
that far in the ski in the scheme of
things, is it?
I don't know. Do you think it is? Not really.
I mean, I went to I plan to go Liverpool
and I went there the same day.
So, I mean, it's all excuses. And I hate
the fact that they reply when they think
they can use an excuse.
when they think that they can use an
excuse, that's when they reply. Like,
oh, I live in Liverpool or, "Oh, I live
in Birmingham or where." Like, as soon
as they think they've got an excuse,
um they use it. And then when you
counteract their excuse, then um
then um then they they don't reply. I
mean, and it's like people say, "Oh,
well, they might have gave their number
on the heat on the moment or ret." Well,
yeah, but then if they gave their
number, then they could explain in the
first message that they're not looking
today. But they don't do that. They
message a message and message maybe for
like a week, two weeks, or it might go
on for like a week, two weeks, and then
they finally say it.
They're just [ __ ] That's literally
who they are, is [ __ ] I'm glad I
don't deal with him no more
cuz it's just it's just depressing, bro.
So, what if I lived in Liverpool? You
would meet me if I lived in Liverpool.
And there, oh, well, it's not practical.
Well, it is. And why are you asking
where am I thinking? And why are you
saying that you're in Spain? Just say
that you you gave your number and you're
not looking today. It shouldn't have
that been the first message. That should
have literally been the first message
that you wrote back because I won't I
wouldn't say ignore because ignore is
just rude. But I mean that should have
been your first
or second message. As soon as someone's
asked you to meet, you should have then
explained that as soon as they asked you to meet. Um
and then we have another one that
messages all day every day and then says
that they're not looking to date. So I
mean for [ __ ] sake. And then you got
these people saying to you that one day
it's going to be different. [ __ ] hell.
They're crazy, bro.
They're [ __ ] insane.
What's up, man? So, yeah,
it's horrible, bro. It it really really
really is horrible, isn't it?
Yep. They're all They're all It's so mad
at 27 years of age cuz that's how I am.
27 or 28. I haven't found one that ain't
a [ __ ] yet.
I've not found one yet that's not a
complete [ __ ] How long is the
search going to go on for?
It's like police, right? if they were if
they were searching for a wanted man,
I'm pretty sure they would have gave up
the search by now.
And also not to mention that it also
happens as you get older as well.
Uh, bro, we don't do stupid rumors on uh
this channel, bro. We don't do immature
disabled voices on this channel.
So, don't don't bring it on here.
Don't bring your stupid rumors on my channel.
Back to large as you [ __ ] Bye-bye now. >> Yeah.
The people on Reddit say you never know.
You never know what the future holds.
Well, I've got a pretty good idea what
it's held so far. Yeah.
I don't know, man. And I've got a pretty good idea.
It's really bad, is it, bro? It's really
bad. And not to forget all of the other
[ __ ] experiences I've had like USA and
all of them because they're that you
need to still throw them in there as
well. You need to bring up the whole
thing like the Makebelie Boyfriends, the
Australian, what you just said, the one
in Liverpool, the distance as an excuse.
You need to use all of these. You need
to bring up all of these things, you know.
So, you give it up. You made the right choice.
Cuz think about this logically.
I bet you Yeah.
I didn't pump that chick. No one said I
pumped that chick. So, yeah.
Um, I bet you they told you, you know,
you know when LT, just put it this way,
right? You know when LT was telling me
to go out and drink and [ __ ] I bet you
the first week or the first month,
people told you, "Oh, you'll meet
someone. Oh, it will happen. You will
meet someone. It will happen."
And now, four years later, we're still
in the same boat. So, I bet you they
told you all them years ago as well, oh,
you don't know what the future holds.
Um, it might change. And it was easy
back then as well. So, I mean, I I bet
you them four years ago, people was
telling you the same thing as they're
telling you now.
And four years ago, nothing. Four years
later, not a sausage.
People was probably telling me back
then, oh, you you know, you'll um
you'll beat somebody, but nothing
happens. Nothing changes.
And yet they're still trying to tell you
that it's going to change. Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro.
Not interested, bro. Not interested.
Yeah. Bad advice. All right. You [ __ ] [Applause]
just [ __ ] throw that virgin. I could
throw that Kent virgin
my [ __ ] hand and put around his bloody neck.
You [ __ ] virgin.
You know what I mean? Yeah.
It's definitely rigged against men.
And it's like when you're watching these
guys get exactly the same [ __ ] as you
when I used to try. It's not It's not
good, is it?
You know, I think it's worse in America,
bro. I think it's worse in America,
believe it or not.
I generally think it is worse.
It's like if I was in America, I would
have called that USA Izzy's um friends bluff. You know,
you know what I'm saying? I would have I
would have literally called the [ __ ] bluff.
You know what I mean?
I'd hate to live there, man.
I'd hate to live there. I think I would
just end up [ __ ] shooting someone.
I know. I know what I'm like, bro. You
know what I'm saying? I would have just
end up shooting some [ __ ]
You know what I mean? It's all just a
bit of fun. I ain't gy.
She's telling me she's got like
relatives in prison. I know people in
prison. Is that like a flex?
Is that like a flex or something?
You know what I'm saying? Greasy. What
the [ __ ] Who doesn't know people in
prison? I was messaging LT yesterday
when I was at the carnival and he didn't
reply back. I said, "Captain."
All right, captain.
No reply though.
I love that little greeting, you know.
All right, Captain. Captain,
that's catchy, isn't it?
Well, I'll just have to find a new mama
now, won't I, Nick? I know.
My mommy and my auntie's abandoned me
now. Even my auntie's abandoned me.
Isn't it greasy? My mommy and my auntie
Still looking for that change. The only
one I've really got is that one in Scotland, but
she's not going to
We're screws, aren't we?
Aren't we? We're screws moods now.
Give baby Peter some milk. You need to
grow up, Joker. You really do need to
grow up. How old are you now, man? You
really need to grow up. Give baby Peter some milk.
I think he needs to grow up. Do you?
Come on, mate. We need to [ __ ] grow up. Yeah.
You need to grow up, son.
I need to go out today, but I can't be bothered, bro. Oh [ __ ] No.
I just bet my charger I think my phone's
going to die. Oh no.
It's [ __ ] bro. What the [ __ ] man? One second. No,
the lead's [ __ ] [ __ ] no, man. [ __ ]