Here we go. Funkman.
A day of Franklin again.
Got some awful taste in my mouth.
You on YouTube again, Bradley? I swear
some of you people just sit on here all
day waiting for someone to go live.
That's quite sad to be honest, bro. That
you come on straight away.
Not even like a minute, not even two minutes.
You know what they You know what they
call people like that, don't you? No.
Live at YouTube.
Don't pull a [ __ ] red store on me, bro.
I'm on YouTube. Yes, I'm on YouTube
going live and you come on my live
within like 1 second.
So, I mean I mean yeah, I'm live on
YouTube whilst playing GTA. I mean,
anybody can [ __ ] do that. A blind
person could do that.
Grievy, do you reckon Red Star can take
one day off of YouTube? Nah.
Like just one day? No [ __ ] way. It's
his whole life.
Do you reckon Do you reckon he could
grieves on this question? Nah. No way.
Not He can't even take a minute off
YouTube. That fat [ __ ]
What do you think, Greavves?
So, I'm going to call you from now on. Greavves.
I mean, I don't know, man. I mean, you
people are rich. I can take a day off
YouTube. I've took weeks off of YouTube.
What the [ __ ] Taking a day off of
YouTube, that's easy, bro.
Red Star can't cuz he's skinned. Just
like the Virgin, they can't take a day
off YouTube cuz they're skin. I can take
a day off YouTube. Day of YouTube's easy.
It's Thursday today, isn't it? I used to
go out approach on some Thursdays and I
agree with you if you remember correctly. Some days
um I repeat what I said cuz you didn't
hear. I've took weeks off of YouTube.
Oh yeah, it's Wednesday. Why do I think
it's Thursday? What the [ __ ] Feels like
a Thursday, don't it? I think it's cuz
the bank holiday. Yeah, it is. My bad. I
thought I thought it was Thursday. I
think it's the bank holiday, bro.
Yeah. You know, I don't watch Seaside
Mark. I went Well, I went on his channel
the other day. That was the first time in maybe
six months I went on his channel. I
don't watch him, bro.
Suicide Mark. I stopped watching him cuz
it was always the same [ __ ]
Maybe Virgin Boys finally got laid.
It's always been off YouTube, Grezy. You
know, there's always positives, isn't
it? Maybe the Skint Virgin finally got laid. We
uh what's happening, bro? Just chilling, man.
I was speaking to this woman on Reddit
yesterday, Joe. She's like, "Oh, I can't
relate because um I can't relate cuz uh
yeah, it's not e it's not hard for us to
uh get people get dates.
That's what she said.
Yeah. I'm just chilling, bro, on this GTA. [ __ ] knows.
You doing anything this week, uh,
Grievy? I'm doing [ __ ] all, bro.
Even if this football bet wins.
Yeah. It's so mad how like they can
literally get relationships. They can
literally get what they want. They they
can even they can be [ __ ] and get what
they want. And then genuine people like
men can't get nothing. It's [ __ ] up,
is it? It should be It should be
illegal. I reckon it should be illegal,
bro. What do you think?
It makes you hate them even more. You
know what I'm saying? It really, really does.
I actually hate them. I think that's one
of the reasons why I don't even bother
anymore, to be honest. I generally hate
them. I think they're [ __ ] Middle finger.
Put your little finger down.
having a bass on the Oh, I don't I don't
bother with them.
People would People call me I don't give
a [ __ ] what they call me, bro.
Misogynist. That's That's overused, bro.
No one cares, bro. It's It's like being
called an incel. No one cares,
you know. They are [ __ ]
I generally think they are [ __ ] I
[ __ ] hate them, bro. I actually [ __ ] do.
They want to call me a misogynist. They
can call me misogynist all they like.
It's the truth. They're [ __ ] [ __ ] I
hate them, bro.
They really are.
[ __ ] They're absolute They're actual [ __ ]
That's what they are. They're actual
That's the only word you can really
describe them in it is [ __ ]
What do you think, Joe? Yeah, they're actual [ __ ]
Nah, I do have that much hate, bro.
Sign that USA is his friend. I was going
to start on her the other day and start
all again about, oh, she was going to
shoot me with seven people. Bro, I
slapped the gun out your [ __ ] hand,
bro. What the [ __ ] Are you mad?
It's little things like that about them
annoy me, bro. They wouldn't know what
they're getting themselves into.
That's what you would call a [ __ ]
jackpot, mate. Yeah,
they are [ __ ] though. They are
[ __ ] He was even talking on Reddit
yesterday how they go on dates to waste
people's time as well. That's another
thing that they do.
Yep, I can imagine it. Yeah,
probably in like Camden Town they would
do it as well. Yeah, they are [ __ ]
though. They are proper proper
[ __ ] Stuck up [ __ ] Why I
don't bother with them? Two weeks now
I've not been out. I don't bother with
the [ __ ] They're [ __ ] [ __ ]
I hate English women. And I hate
American women. I hate all of them. I
hate anything West women. I hate them. Bye-bye now.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah. I put on a bet Saturday. Hopefully it wins.
Do you think it's got a good chance of winning Griezy?
Um, not Griezy. Joe, Barnett, Colchester and
Cambridge and Newport. Both teams to score. Yeah.
Yeah. Cuz that's what only Yeah. Cuz
they're only good for their body. Yeah.
Cuz they're good for their body. They're
not good for anything else.
That's all they're good for is a is is
is their body.
Nothing else. If you if you watch all
these videos, right, they are literally
all the same. They say the same stuff.
They do the same thing. They have the
same mannerisms. They literally are all the same.
They actually are all the same. They do
all the same stuff.
Like, no joke. Like, not even
bullshitting. They actually are all the same.
They're just non-playing characters.
Yeah, I put 90 pound on that football
bet. I don't know why this time I done
90. I told you I'm not skinned, Joe. I
just don't show skin people money cuz
they ain't got no money. I don't show
skin projectors money. I won that game a
long time ago. Did I agree?
That's what made me laugh yesterday when
you was like, "Oh, have you forgot what
you've done on it?" I said, "Coming from you.
Have I forgot what I've done on here?
Coming from [ __ ] you that [ __ ]
pretends I've not gone to meet [ __ ]
people and pretend I ain't [ __ ] show
money a million [ __ ] times. Jesus
Christ. The [ __ ] cheek on it.
Grievesy. Oh, Jesus Christ.
And actually, I don't pay them for sex.
I actually pay them for their mouth most
of the time. I actually don't even pay
them for sex. I pay them for their [ __ ] mouth.
You understand we
smells nice. Is that Is that bleach or
something? Smells like bleach. You know
the smell of bleach.
Yeah. Well, yeah, cuz that's all they're good for.
That's all they're [ __ ] good for.
Nothing else. They're all [ __ ]
Why I don't go out anymore?
I mean, yeah, I could go out and
approach every day and [ __ ] with them
and use them for their body, but
you know, and use them for their body, but
yeah, that's just a waste of my time. I
mean, I could do it. I was thinking of
doing that to get my own back on them,
just like [ __ ] with them and trying
to use them for their body, but I just
don't have the time to do that, bro. I'm
not sad like them. I was actually
thinking of doing something like that.
Just humiliating them, you know, like
all the [ __ ] that they've caused me in
the past and that they've caused me so much [ __ ]
And that [ __ ] USA is his friend was
winding me up as well. And we weren't
even arguing. We weren't even like
arguing or swearing at each other.
Oh, I've got relatives in jail, bro. I
know people in prison. I know people in
[ __ ] jail. The [ __ ] saying [ __ ]
go to [ __ ] jail now.
Just stuff like that annoys me, bro.
Like with them, you know what I mean? I
hate them, bro. I swear down. I really
do hate them.
The ones that use distance, they do they
all do the same [ __ ] like using distance
as an excuse. They all say the same
[ __ ] They're all the [ __ ] same.
And that one in Liverpool, I think she's
like 31, 32. And and they still they do
you know what? I forgot to say this to
[ __ ] Ant-Man. Yeah. He says that I'm
immature, right? Which yeah, I am
immature a lot of the time, but they're
[ __ ] more immature than me. And that
same [ __ ] something. They all do the
same [ __ ] They all play the same games.
They all They all They're all the
[ __ ] same. They literally are all the Bum.
They are all the [ __ ] same, bro. They
all do the same stuff and say the same thing.
They all reply to negativity. Like just
little things like that. They all do the
same [ __ ] Why do they all do the same
[ __ ] if they're not all the same? That's
what I don't understand. If they're not
all the same.
I was reading again yesterday agree with
you why people gave up on dating. A lot
of people said they just can't be
bothered with it.
And that's like me, bro. I'm just I feel
like I'm a hundred years old. I can't be
asked with it, bro. I'm too tired.
I'm [ __ ] retired from the dating
game, bro. [ __ ] hell. It's about [ __ ] time.
And even when these people say, "Oh
yeah, we go on dates. We go on dates."
Yeah, but you go on dates with
unrealistic expectations. That's why you
don't find anybody. There's no point
going on a date with someone.
It's like that one from Italy. Oh,
whipped whoop. You tried to kiss them.
Oh, wow. Oh, wow. Do you know what I'm
saying? Wow. Don't call the [ __ ]
police on me. Do you know what I mean?
Bro, it's a good thing, man. You all the
only word they know is they have a
boyfriend. I see on Instagram all the
time. So, I mean, it's that's a good thing, bro.
cuz all all they all they'll say to you
is how they have a boyfriend. So I mean
that's the only conversation that they have. So
you know how it is bro.
Just [ __ ] give up with the [ __ ] thing.
All right, captain.
I'm doing good, Captain. How are you
doing, captain? I don't gamble anymore,
captain. Do you gamble, captain?
[ __ ] same old same old, bro. Don't
really gamble anymore. [ __ ] the
football. But yeah, hope you It seems
you haven't packed it in, have you, Michael? Michael,
it seems you haven't packed it up, have
you, bro? Packed it in.
You can ask money Mike. We used to speak
to like all we used to speak to each
other all the time there and he would
tell you how I used to be skinned and
[ __ ] No, I'm never skinned, bro. I just
don't show these people money cuz every
time you show them money, they don't
show you nothing.
You know, Michael Mike will tell you,
bro, what I used to be like, you know,
when I was on like 700 pound a month
like them years ago, man.
You know what I'm saying? But yeah, it
is. I just don't [ __ ] bother, bro,
cuz this the same [ __ ]
You know what I mean? Like, if some
[ __ ] little skint virgin in a bedset
wants to show [ __ ] money, good on
you, bro. I ain't showing you [ __ ] all.
I just put 90 on the [ __ ] football
bet. I spent one [ __ ] 40 walking up
the road yesterday, bro. I told you this already.
You know what I'm saying? So yeah. Yeah, man.
Yeah. They want you to show their money.
But listen, here's the thing is that
even if you show them money, bro, they
don't show you nothing. I've shown like
different amounts of money, bro. Like
[ __ ] yeah. I've shown six Well, no. I I
I try to be real. Yeah. I've shown 5.7
grand in 50s. I've shown £900. I've
shown £700. I've shown £2,000. I've
shown £3,000. And they always run away.
They just want people to show them what
they ain't got and I'm not doing it. Um
I don't Cambridge and Newport both teams
to score and Barney and Colchester both
seems to score.
Bro, I won two football bets in a
[ __ ] row, man.
uh the start of the season and then the
second one after that and then I lost
last week and I lost on another Tuesday
as well. But one of them was only 20
pound bets. But yeah, hopefully this
[ __ ] wins, bro.
I don't play the roulette and [ __ ] anymore.
I just put 90 on it. I normally put 80
pound on it. It's just a thing. But I
just put 90, bro. [ __ ] it. Yeah.
Did you go Liverpool?
Did you go Liverpool, Mike? I see a
video. Was you in Liverpool?
I was like, what is this geyser doing?
What did you think of it? Did you like
it? I've been meaning to go back up
there, but I ain't got round to doing it
to be honest. Did you like it?
I've already been there once, bro.
[ __ ] few years ago, but I said I was
always going to go back, but just never bothered, man.
Did you like it? Yeah.
You need to get yourself to Newcastle, bro.
You know, you need to get yourself to Newcastle, man.
That's where the batches are at. Next
time you go out, I haven't heard from
Monty. He's probably with [ __ ] Natalie
having sex every day.
We might do London. Yeah.
Yeah, I would give it a whirl.
Yeah, that's why I won that four grand
in the hip drone, bro. Imagine that.
Yeah, it was a Wednesday. I was [ __ ]
drunk as [ __ ] I put 150 on the roulette
and I walked out with four grand, bro.
Cash. Imagine that.
Oh, [ __ ] me, bro. It was a Wednesday as
well, which is today. I actually remember it.
Yeah, the madness, bro.
Yeah, it was good, bro. I used to rin
You know, I used to rinse them [ __ ]
every week, bro. You know what I used to
tell you on Facebook? I wasn't joking.
Every Thursday I used to [ __ ] rinse them bastards.
I used to take them to the cleaners, bro.
Well, not literally cuz I mean they've
got millions, bro. But you know what I mean?
I'm saying they got [ __ ] Did you Did
you Did you gamble in Liverpool?
One sec, bro.
You gamble there or no?
Yeah. I've never Bro, I've never show
money ever again. I've said it straight.
I've never I've never I've never said
it. I I I've said it, bro. Cuz the thing
is is that when you show these people
money, all they're going to do is run away.
They ask you to show money,
but then like when you show money, they
all run away. It's like we got some
[ __ ] virgin in a bed sit showing
£1,000. I was like, "Are you [ __ ] serious?"
So yeah, just say them. Just say this to
them, right? Just say this to them.
Anyone that says this to you, bro, just
say this, right? You want to see money,
go look at your own money. If you've got
all of this money, yeah, this is what I
say. Yeah. If you you got all of this
money, go look at your own money if you
have so much of it. That's that's what I
say. You got all this money. I don't
need to show you what you already have
apparently. That's all you got to say,
bro. That's what I say. You know,
well, bless you then if you went blackp. Bless you,
bro. I had to block you on Facebook,
bro, cuz you was you was trolling too bad, man.
Yeah, I went to Birmingham to see Monty
like a month ago, bro. I I hate the bro
the bouncers are [ __ ] [ __ ]
there, man. Yeah, that's the first time
in Birmingham for like two and a half years.
You hear that?
You know, like that was the first time
in like two years.
Two and a half years,
bro. Is a [ __ ] Birmingham. Yeah, bro.
I'm not going to lie though, there was
some place I went to. Yeah,
but I forget what it was called. It was um [ __ ] um
it was some breakfast place. Yeah. Need
it was right next to the station kind
of. It's quite it's next to New Street station
by the [ __ ] um
what's that shop called?
Um and they done like an omelette and it
was really nice. What's that breakfast
place called? It was something Canada. I
need to look up to see if there's anyone
in London. It was next to a [ __ ] I
don't know if it was Oh, what? It's like
two seconds away from the [ __ ] train station.
You must know what I'm talking about. It
was Southern Canada and it's just like
some breakfast place.
You know what I'm talking about? Yeah.
By New Street by the station.
Literally like you go to the station,
you walk up that little hill and then
you turn left and then it's southern
Canada, bro. I got an omelette, bro. is
[ __ ] nice, man.
You know what it's called? Cuz I don't
think we have one of them in London.
Is that what it's called?
It's next to like, you know, not Co-op.
It might have been a Tesco. I think it's
next to Tesco.
I think it's next to a Tesco.
I ain't been That was the first time in
Birmingham for [ __ ] years, bro. So, I mean, yeah.
You know, I've been Birmingham like six
times, but just a been in ages.
Yeah, the bouncers there were [ __ ]
bro. They're [ __ ]
Like [ __ ] was like, "Oh, you
can't come in with trainers." Said no
one in London. Said, "Oh, you need to go
in with a group of girls." Said no one
in London. They're [ __ ] the bouncing
on. Why is it in these places he's
bouncing off [ __ ]
I had to get Monty off like one of the
bouncers, bro. He was going to bat the
bouncer, bro. I had to stop Monty.
They're [ __ ] [ __ ]
Oh, you're from Kidd Minister, Mike.
You're from You're from Kitty Minister,
aren't you? Aren't you, Michael? Michael,
you're from Kitty Minister, aren't you, Michael? Michael,
>> I met some guy, bro, and his friend and
his friend was from Birmingham and he is
from Kitty Minister. They were in
London, bro. That accent, bro. Oh my
[ __ ] god. That [ __ ] accent,
Michael. Oh my [ __ ] god, bro. It was
so mad. It was It was It was crazy. I
said, "This gezer sounds mad."
And the other one just sounds like
[ __ ] Provident Loans. The one from
Birmingham just sounds like Provident Loans.
That [ __ ] mad act, bro. It's got they
got a mad accent, you know, bro.
Lisa, they had the aa bit to it, bro.
It's [ __ ] mental. But yeah, Michael,
you're a kid. You're a kid minister,
chat. You are
kidding. Kidding Minister.
You're a You're a Wolver Hampton boy.
That's M. That's me and Michael's little banter.
Yeah, with me and Michael it's banter.
It's always been banner, is it? Michael,
you W boy. [Laughter]
I love it, bro. I love it. [Music] Oh, [ __ ]
I'll be back later anyways. See you.