I think I'm going to have
Yeah. McDonald's. I think
[ __ ] Second, bro. [Music] I'm [ __ ]
Yeah, I think we're going to see Don't they
realize you're just wasting your time
with these disabled people in this
community? Is it for real?
like money or [ __ ] anymore.
Any for anything?
You get me?
£14 for just some nuggets. [ __ ] me.
That is insane.
Talking about yourself. What have I told
you about talking about yourself, bro?
That's not nice, bro. Don't talk about
yourself like that.
Don't talk about yourself like that.
That's not nice.
What have I told you about talking about
yourself? Please stop it. Don't put
yourself down like that. You know,
calling yourself skint, saying that you
got no woman, no money. Don't talk about
yourself like that. You're better than
that. Don't put yourself down like that.
It's not nice calling yourself all of
these things. It's horrible. You're
better than that. Come on, man. Don't
talk about yourself like that. Come on. You know,
I know you go clubbing by yourself at
41, but you're you're better than that.
You're better than that, man. Come on.
Come on. You're better than that. Don't
talk about yourself like that. Calling
yourself skin no woman. It's not nice to
talk about yourself like that, bro.
It's bad enough that you simp [ __ ]
every single woman on [ __ ] YouTube.
You shouldn't put yourself down like
that. It's like when you project your
anxiety onto people. You shouldn't put
yourself down like that, man.
It's not nice to talk about yourself.
You know, it is what it is, bro. Don't
worry. Things can get better for you,
bro. You don't need to talk about
yourself like that.
Jesus Christ. I feel bad. Huh?
Come on, man. We need to stop with the
money thing, bro. Please stop it. You
run away every time you're shown money.
Stop it. Come on. You You've been
embarrassed several times before, bro.
Come on now. Come on. Stop it. You're
the one that has to convince people that
you've got all of this money when you
literally have nothing. Just like Virgin
Bar, you generally have to come online
and convince people that you've got
money when you literally have [ __ ] all.
I ain't doing that, bro. We come on my
my channel talking about normal things.
We don't really mention money. Only you
skin people talking about money cuz you
ain't got none. That's why you bring it
up. Cuz you ain't got none. You ain't
got no money. Cuz you are skin. Ah.
You understand, bro?
You talk about money cuz you ain't got
no money. It's reverse psychology.
Remember last year when you got owned
several times, you couldn't show [ __ ]
all, bro. Take that L, [ __ ]
Take that L.
Take that [ __ ] L.
Which makes me laugh when Joe tries to
say to me, have I forgot what I'm shown?
Have I Have I forgot what I've um done?
I don't forget anything, bro. I know. I
showed you all, buddy. You ran away.
I remember that. I remember that. All
made you run away when you couldn't
match my money, which is why people
don't show you anything anymore.
You know what I mean, bro?
Yeah. It was trying to prove it was
trying to prove a point, but yeah, I I I
realize you're just wasting your time
with with with people on here. Like, I
shouldn't have even done that video back
to be honest. But cuz it doesn't matter
what you tell these people. It doesn't
matter what you show them what they are.
They're never ever going to stop.
Like I said, if you're not fat and ugly
like these people, they'll find a reason
to dislike you. So, once they dislike
you, they're always just going to do
this. So, there was no point me even
doing a video about to be honest. I just ordered McDonald's.
So yeah. Oh, this person's from England.
So yeah, I just ordered McDonald's, bro. Yeah,
that's not nice for you to talk about
yourself though, LJ. No money, no woman.
That's that's you're talking about
yourself, especially with the money
thing. All you do is talk about
yourselves. This is why people don't
show you money because that's what you
want. You want to be shown money so you
can run away again. And it's not
happening, matey. Nice try.
You know, you're you're the one that
forgets things on here, not me. I found
that very offensive yesterday, Joe, when
you were saying uh about I forgot things
I've done in here. I've never forgot
anything. You are the ones that choose
to forget things like being shown money,
like being shown women. You are the one
that chooses to forget things, not me.
What the [ __ ] have I forgot about, you know?
So, when you're arguing with fat, ugly,
jealous people, you're never ever going to win. You know,
when you're when you're with arguing
with these fat, ugly, jealous people,
you're never ever ever going to win.
Like if you go on Virgin's [ __ ]
Virgin boy's video, you see all of these
comments, right? You know what I'm
saying? You get all of these comments
and you just know you're never going to
win. Whether you're right or whether
you're wrong arguing with these spastics
like these Ricky Milling didn't account,
you're never going to win. No matter
what you show them, you're literally
wasting your time. Uh you know what I mean?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I do take it literal because because it
annoys me, which is why I don't do it.
It annoys me, which is why I don't do
it. You You shouldn't You can't tell me
how I should take things or not because
you get given No, no, no. Cuz you get
given advice, right? You get given
advice on the internet. Oh, you're going
to find someone. Oh, you're going to
find someone. No, no, no, no. Yet, no
one's interested. So, think about what
you're saying. I I do take it personal.
So, which is why I gave up. you know, I
mean, I I can't help the way I see things, you know?
Yeah. That's why I stopped that's why I
stopped doing it. That's one of the
reasons why I stopped doing it.
That is one of the reasons why I
actually stopped doing it.
I mean, I didn't contradict myself, did
I? I have stopped doing it. So, yeah.
But I I I take it. It annoys me with me.
cuz Yeah, it just annoys which is why I
don't do it anymore. But they are all
the same. The point of the video was
they are all the same.
Well, those guys back to bad personality.
Nope. You don't need to work on that.
You need to leave the country cuz the
whole point of the video you you missed
the whole point of the video. I think
you missed the whole point of the video,
bro. There's no point getting into
debates with me, bro, because you can't
finish it. So, there's no point. You
know, they don't care about personality.
I'm not having the same conversation
again, bro, with you. I've just shown
you a video that was almost 10 minutes
long and you you're just going to
disregard. You're going to disregard
everything that you're shown. So, what's
the point? You're going to disregard.
I've shown you stuck up [ __ ] that are
pretending that they've got boyfriends
to different kinds of people. All
different kinds of people. And you're
going on about something completely
different. Just wasting my time, bro.
You know, and I and it's like when that
video back to nonslegs. I'm just wasting my time.
You understand? It's just just a waste
of time because you're not going to win
with these people. So, they're never
ever going to stop. They're never ever
going to stop. even if they didn't get a
reaction, mind you, Joe. So, it's the
whole thing is just pointless, isn't it?
Really, all of it is just pointless if
you think about it. Sorry, bro. So, yeah.
Why? One second, bro. Um,
and why do they say that boyfriends, you
know, they man or not? Why can't you
accept that they have no interest in
you? Uh, you're missing the whole point
again. You're you're missing the whole
point again. You people are telling
people that the past don't predict
predict the future. I was showing you a
video of people rejecting people,
you know. So when is it ever going to
change then? Okay. Okay. Let's go by
your logic. Okay. So we know what it is.
Okay. So we know what it is. So when is
it going to change then?
So when Okay. So when is it going to
change? Are you just going to wake up
one day and it's going to change then?
You know, why do I have no interest?
Because there's nothing wrong with you.
There's nothing wrong with the way that
you look. So, why do I have no interest?
This is the the the problem that I have,
which is why I gave up. I gave up
winding myself up based on terrible
looks. Yeah. That's why I've had more
women than you and you have to simp over
women, which I don't even know why I'm
saying all of this stuff, bro. You
forget everything you're shown. It's a
waste of time me saying that. You forget
anything you're shown when you lose the
money game, when you lose the looks
game, when you lose. You've lost all of
these games and you still pretend it
never happened. I don't even know why
I'm saying this [ __ ] to you, bro. It's
like when you still ask me to show you
money. It's laughable. You call people
skinned cuz you are skin. It's perverse
psychology. They call you what they are.
That's how that's how it goes on this
community. They call people skint
because they are skinned. That's why
they're sat on YouTube every day. They
call people ugly because they're ugly.
You know, everything they say is about
their own lives.
Shown this, shown that. [ __ ]
You know what I mean?
No, I'm not comparing myself to others.
I'm saying what other people get that
are in the same situation as me. Yeah.
And you're the first guy. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Yep. Yeah. So, why have I had all these
women and I've never had to simp like
you? Then ask me that question. Why have
I never had to resort to sing like you,
you loser? And I've had more women than
you. Think about that, bro. This is This
is why I always say to Virgin Boy. If
I'm so ugly, why have I had all these
women and you can't get none? That's why
you resort to Simp. What does that say
about you that an ugly person has had
more women than you? And don't say where
are they now? You've been shown women.
You've been shown sex. You've been shown
money multiple times. Why is an ugly
person got more women than you then?
See, it doesn't make sense. And then you
realize, hold on, reverse it. It's back
to these people. Do you understand, bro?
You know what I'm saying?
I'm not okay looking Joe. I'm better
looking than you. I'm better looking
than L Joe. L J. Yeah. I'm better
looking than all of you on here, bro. Do
you want me to put the link up again and
and and and let you people show your
face then? Okay. Okay. Are you going to
show me your face? If you're going to
talk about my looks, show your face. At
least have the balls to show your face.
I'm better looking at all of you on
here. Multiple people on here. Yeah.
You know, but he's right. It doesn't
matter if I'm a bro. Listen, listen.
He's right. Listen. Someone that stalked
more women. Listen, listen, listen.
That's what I'm saying. This is why I
don't bother because you're always going
to take their side. This is why I don't
waste my time arguing. I don't show
money cuz I know what you people do.
This is why I don't do this [ __ ] anymore
with you. Oh, show money when you
project. This is why I don't do this
with you anymore.
That's why I don't bother. I let you
crack on because everything. It's like
what you were saying to me the other
day, Joe. Well, you forget what you're
shown on here. I've shown money. I've
shown [ __ ] thousands and you forget
everything. That's why I don't bother
with you. I don't bother with it
anymore. Do you understand? I don't
bother anymore. And I'm not okay
looking. I'm better looking than all of
you. Jealousy again with you people and
looks. That's another thing you people
like to do. It's already proven that I'm
better looking than all of you. So, if
I'm better looking than you, how the
[ __ ] could you say I'm okay looking when
I'm better looking than you? I'm I'm
comparing myself to you. I'm better
looking than Joe and Log. Yeah. I'm
better looking than all of you. So, that
must mean I'm better than okay if I'm
better than you. That that Do you understand?
You know what I'm saying? Where's the
thousands now? In my bank account. Where
was your thousands when you was being
shown all of that money? Hold on a
minute. One minute. Same conversation.
This is why I don't waste my time on you
anymore, Mike. Cuz it's the same
convers. When you're arguing with
disabled people, you're never ever going
to win. When you're arguing, bro,
listen, listen, listen to me, bro. When
you're arguing with these disabled
people, you're never ever going to win
cuz they're disabled. Do you understand,
bro? You know, like when you're arguing
with disabled people that ain't got a
life, bro, like it's where was my
thousands? Where was your thousands that
year and a half? Where was all of your money?
Listen, listen. Mike, never ever show
these people, right? No, no, no. Sean
has a disabled Mrs. Okay. Okay. Sean has
a disabled Mrs. Like I said, right? He's
He has I would never want a disabled MS.
I don't target disabled people. I don't
care about somebody with a disabled
girl. Think of it like this. If he was
really happy with his disabled girl, why
is he trying to get him with all of my
women that I've been with? Okay. Okay.
Let's go by your logic, right? Okay.
It's like I was saying in my other
video, he has all of these women. Why is
he stalking all my sloppy seconds? Cuz
he's a [ __ ] Cuz it makes sense, bro.
You know what I mean?
This is what I'm saying, Joe. And this
is exactly why I would never show you
money. I don't get into it with you
people. This is why I don't get into it
with you people anymore. Because
whatever you're shown, you ignore.
That's why I don't bother with you
anymore. When you sit there and you say,
"Oh, you're skimp. you're this. I just
say yep because we know what you all do.
We all know what you people do. This is
why we don't waste our time, bro. I
don't waste my I don't get into with
disabled people. Like that's one of the
things that that's probably one of the
thing I learned on this [ __ ] Yeah. He
can keep it, bro. He's winning. He lives
in a bedsit. He has to resort to
disabled girls that ain't winning. And
this is why I don't waste my time with
you people. Like, bro, getting into it
with disabled people, you never win.
Like you're never ever going to win. It
doesn't matter what they're shown,
whatever, they'll just pretend they've
not seen it. Like there's no point
getting into it with these people. Like
there's no point. You know, bro, if I
had a long-term relationship, you would
still tell me I was single. Whatever
you're shown, you deny. I think there's
been evidence on that. Like, you know,
at the end of the day, right, you don't
know where I live.
Yeah, I've never had a disabled girl.
But I've had normal women though. I've
had sex with normal women though. And
you don't know where I live. And I'd
rather live with my mom than live in a
[ __ ] shitty bedit. Cancelled bedsit
with no bed in it. How many times we
going to keep going over this, bro? You
don't know where I live. And I don't
even live with my mom. But I'd rather
live with my mom than live in a shitty
bed sit with no bed in it. Skint like
nonsleads. I've said it a million times.
I'd rather have that than be in a skint
bedsit with no bed in it and no money
like him. I've with a disabled
girlfriend. I've said it a million times.
I' I've literally said it. I'd rather
that than being in a [ __ ] shitty bed
suit with no bed in it that the council
owns. I think I've said that about a
million times. I'm literally put my
hands up to it. You know
what? What? You know what I'm saying? Like,
so yeah, Joe, I've shown me with better
women, better money, but you all dismiss
it. This is why we don't get into it
with you anymore. You're a waste of our
time. You know, I said the same thing to
LT. You're a waste of our time.
Yeah, this is why we don't get into it
with you people, bro.
Yo, this is why we don't get into it
with you people, cuz it's boring, bro.
Listen, listen listen, bro. Come on now,
man. It's getting pathetic. You get
shown money, you will run away. You get
shown women, you will run away. You get
shown whatever, you will run away. Bro,
you've been doing it for years. No one
cares. You know what I'm saying? People
just don't just don't get into it with
these disabled people. They believe what
they want to believe and choose what
they want to believe. It's pointless.
It's pointless as [ __ ]
There's no point, bro.
Nah, he's not worth it, bro. He's not worth it.
You know what I'm saying, mate? Listen,
listen, listen, listen. This you've also
shown money, but where they from, you
can't hold on to either. I've shown you
me with plenty of women. Again, I'm not
getting into it with you, bro. I'm not
getting into it with you. I'm not
explaining myself. You choose what you
want to choose to believe and that's it.
You've been doing it for years anyway.
So, just keep on doing what you're
doing. You know, you get showed money,
women, thousands, and you still say you
ain't seen nothing. I'm done. I knew I'm
wasting my time with these mongos, bro.
You know, these self-p projecting people
that talk about their ugly skin lives. I
knew I was wasting my time. That's why I
don't waste my time with them. I don't
get into it, bro. Look at Okay, let me
let me give you an example, right? Nons.
I've had normal women. I've got money
than him. I'm better looking than him.
I've actually been in a relationship and
he still comes on like he owns me. I
know I'm wasting my time with these people.
You know, you're wasting your time with
these people. I said the same thing with LT.
You're wasting your time on these people.
You know what I mean? You're wasting
your [ __ ] time getting into it with these people.
They choose what they want to choose to believe.
Doesn't matter what they've shown, they
all dismiss it.
Yep. Okay. I've never been in a
relationship. Okay. I'm just going to
start agreeing with these people now.
Yep. I'm skin. I've never been seen with
women. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Okay.
Happy now. That's how it gets that
angry. You just you disagree with them
because whatever you show them, they're
just going to dismiss it anyways.
You know, I've been shown better looking
women than than Virgin Boy. He stalked
my sloppy seconds cuz he was that
jealous, which everyone forgets about,
by the way. Everyone forgets about how
this guy in a relationship,
bro. I've already been in a
relationship. Bro, you're 47 and you're
still a virgin. Look closer to home.
You're 47 and you've never been laid,
you [ __ ] virgin. Stop talking about
yourself. 47, never been laid. This is
what a lot of these people are like on
this micro. They're talking about my
age. They're [ __ ] old, 20 years older
than me. They ain't even got a life.
They're sat there [ __ ] skin. No life
on YouTube every day. And they're trying
to talk about my age. [ __ ] 47 [ __ ]
sat on YouTube. Ain't got a life.
[ __ ] skin. Like these people, bro.
They're [ __ ] 47y old [ __ ] Disabled
people that can't get off of YouTube.
Yeah, I know he owns me. Yep. Yep. But
guess what? No one's ever made me run to
the police on YouTube.
Uhhuh. Yep. No one's ever made owned me.
No, I've never been so I've never been
owned so hard that I've had to run to
the police over YouTube. I mean, I can
safely say that.
I can safely say that I've never been
owned so hard that I've had to run to
the police on YouTube. Same can't be
said about Virgin Boy. I think that says
it all, mate. And you're banned. Bye-bye.
Yeah. I've never run to the police. Look
at you, bro, in a club at 41. No money,
no hair, no driving license. You ain't
[ __ ] traveled anywhere. You're 41.
Skinny [ __ ] no friends. And you're
coming on here talking about me. So, you
was clubbing on your own. You [ __ ]
socially awkward autistic [ __ ] How the
[ __ ] are you talking about anyone else?
41, [ __ ] barely traveled, never been
to Asia, [ __ ] skinn as [ __ ] Listen,
let me tell you something right here,
right now, [ __ ] Yeah, if you've
got all of this money, why did you run
away when you get show every time you
get show money? Why do you run away?
Why do you run away? Listen, if you're
not skin, answer me this. Answer me
this. Oh [ __ ] that's hot. Every time
you get shown money, you skin bastard.
Why do you run away? Why do you run
away? Answer me. Why do you run away
when you can't show anything? Because
you're better. And you know the thing is Yeah.
He has to come on here like he's got money.
He comes on here like he's got money.
He coming on. He actually thinks he's
got money. The thing is Mike,
you know, listen. Yeah.
Him and nonsense.
They actually think they've got money,
but their [ __ ] skin. The skin is I've
never known so so desperate, such desperation.
They literally think they've got money.
And that's the funniest thing about it.
They actually think, but they've got
nothing. Like the try hardness in it, it
makes me die. But you got someone
showing 800 pound in the bedit thinking
that they got money. You got a [ __ ]
stupid [ __ ] in Ireland pretending that
he gets three half grand a month and he
gets nothing. He gets [ __ ] all. You know
what I'm saying? Nothing. about benefits, mate.
I'm telling you,
this [ __ ] is on £700 a month. He's not
on that £300 a month. He literally he literally is on
He's on 700 pound a month.
He ain't got no [ __ ] 30 a month.
You know what I mean?
late 20s, I have had a girlfriend and
I've already proved I've been in a
relationship. You're 47 and you can't
even get a woman. That's even more
shocking. You know what's even more shocking?
You people in your 40s and you're still
virgins and you ain't got a life. You
can't get off of YouTube. That's even
more shocking. That's even more shocking
that you're in your 40s and you can't
get off of YouTube cuz you ain't got no
money. You ain't got no life. And you're banned. Bye-bye.
And this is what I'm saying. It's a This
is why I'm coming off this [ __ ] Um,
Mike, this is why I'm coming off this
[ __ ] because you're never going to win
with these losers. These jealous fat
losers. And they're disabled as well. I
don't even think a lot of them actually.
They're they're fat disabled losers that
ignore everything they show. You're
wasting your time with them. You're
literally wasting your time, guys.
You're wasting your time with these
people. I've shown more money, more
women that I'm better looking and they
still work for me. Like, bro, you're
wasting your time with them. You're
literally wasting your time arguing right now. You know,
these fat ugly people ain't got nothing
but YouTube. Remember that when you
leave, bro. Remember that [ __ ] Oh, man.
Yeah, I'm nearly Yeah. You said I was
near 30 four years ago, bro. I'm still
nowhere near 30.
Bro, no one cares about him going to
Vegas. Everyone's been to Vegas. No one
cares about Vegas, bro.
No one cares about Vegas, bro.
[ __ ] me. Everyone's been Vegas. [ __ ] hell.
These nuggets are very nice.
So why are you simp?
Yeah, you've been saying I'm near 30 for
four years. Like I said, you've been
saying it for four years.
You've been saying
you've been saying I'm almost But you
people put in your late 40s and you
ain't even got a life. Start on YouTube.
Never mind my [ __ ] age, bro. You
know, never mind my [ __ ] age.
I'm not skinn like nons. I'm not skint
like L. Who's shown the most money on
here? I have. I'm the winner.
You and non-slates can never show that
money. You ain't got it. You're scented.
You're You ain't got no money. You can't
even show me nothing cuz you're scented.
The evidence is there. You know,
why do you simp over women every day?
Why do you Why do you and Virgin Boy simp? Huh?
begging women on YouTube. [ __ ]
Yep. If your life is so better than
mine, get off of YouTube.
Yeah. Get off of YouTube then.
Get off of YouTube then. How can you be
41, never been to Asia, don't have a
driving license, ain't got a penny to
your name, and try and talk about me,
bro. No driving license, no money, skinn
as [ __ ] And you're trying to talk about
me? [ __ ] hell. You people [ __ ] You
got no shame, bro.
You got no shame.
[ __ ] scared as [ __ ]
I'm just ignoring these people now, bro.
Let them embarrass themselves.
Do you know what makes me laugh is
there's this guy called Smokey Be saying
that I'm below the poverty line. You
don't know how much money how much money
do I have. You don't know how much money
I get. You don't know how much money I
have. You don't know how much money I
got last month and you don't know how
much money I have. So yeah,
think about like that, bro. I let you
keep talking about yourself. It's amazing.
No, you don't know what I've got.
You don't know that. You don't know what I've got.
You don't know what I have. I tell you
what I want this earth and I haven't
told you anything recently. You don't
know what I have.
Sorry, bro. So, um, yeah, you don't
know. I have Yep. Talking about yourself
again, bro. Yep. That's all of them
things you're describing. You're talking
about yourself, bro. Just like Ricky
Milling, you were talking about
yourself. Think of it. You're all past
your sell by date and you got nothing
but YouTube. Don't even try to [ __ ]
say anything about me, bro. You're all
past your [ __ ] sell by date and
you're still on YouTube with nothing.
You can't talk about no [ __ ]
Bro, he wasn't laughing when he was
running to the police crying, was he?
This is what I'm saying, bro. You can
say someone owns me all they want, but
listen. Yeah, I made him run to the
police crying. I had him not leaving his
house for 3 weeks. Laugh at what you
want, bro. That's fine. I was laughing
when I had you running to the police and screaming
and didn't leave your house for 3 weeks.
Did you forget about that one? Probably.
So, laugh all you want. I'm glad I can
entertain you. But you wasn't laughing
then. You wasn't laughing when I made
you leave YouTube for 3 weeks.
You wasn't laughing then. So, I mean,
laugh at me all you want, bro. And you
should also laugh at the fact that I'm
better looking than you. I got more
money than you and I had Morgan and you
will never get Morgan and I had her body
and her [ __ ] and your ugly face.
Couldn't get any of these women. You
should laugh at yourself. Look at all of
these women you tried with. Izzy,
[ __ ] Morgan, and he got rejected.
There's nothing to laugh at but but
yourself. There's nothing to laugh at about yourself.
But like I said,
you forget all of these things. Just
like the bomb to be,
you forgot. You forget all of these things.
That's why I said to my man, it's a
waste of time arguing with any of these people.
It is a waste of time arguing with any
of these people when it is back and forth.
It is back and forth with these people.
Like think of I I own him in every
aspect. I'm better looking. I've had the
women that he wished he could get that
follows him for the rest of his life,
you know. But did you forget about that
one judge when he stalked all of these
women that I got with? You seem to
forgot about that one, didn't you?
Typical [ __ ] northerner remembers
what you want to remember. That's why I
don't waste my time with you. Do you
know when I see all of these comments?
Yeah. I don't even waste my time on them
like making videos because I know I'm
wasting my time cuz you believe what you
what suits yourself. So I don't I don't
I don't waste my time. You people are
not laughing at anything. I'm better
looking than you. I've got more money
than you. I've shown more women than
you. How can you laugh at someone like
when you people in your 40s, fat and
ugly, can't get off of YouTube? Like
let's get in it right now. that you're
fat, ugly, 40-year-old losers that can't
get off of YouTube. You can't laugh at
[ __ ] no one, bro. Especially someone
that younger than you. You know,
I'm not a [ __ ] disabled that has to
resort to disabled. That's against the
law. Yeah. I have never never had to
resort to a disabled girl cuz I'm too
ugly to attract anything normal. The
same can't be said about someone else.
I have never ever had to go for a
disabled woman because I'm too ugly to
get anything normal. That's not me, bro.
That's someone else. That ain't [ __ ]
me. It's not [ __ ] funny either, you know,
bro. Laugh at yourselves.
Sat on YouTube in your 40s skin. Laugh
at yourselves. Laugh at you for listen.
Laugh at yourself. FLJ 41, no money, no
woman, no driving license, barely been
to any countries. Like, laugh at
yourself. Don't laugh at me. Don't laugh
at someone that's got a chance. That's
not 41. That That's not like you. You
even have a provisional. Laugh at
yourself. You're 41. You're a loser.
You're an old man. You got back problems.
Never traveled hardly anywhere at your
age. Like, laugh at your [ __ ] self.
How? You've ended up a 41y old loser.
How did you end up like that? At least a
27y old has a chance.
You haven't even been to Asia. No. [ __ ]
Claim P. I don't claim Pip.
I don't claim Pip. Oh, you don't like
him when the truth is um SP, do you?
You don't like them when the um tooth is
smooth, do you?
You don't like when
you don't like it, do you? Do you think
somebody in a bedit Yeah. Do you think
somebody in a bedshit that could only
that could only [ __ ] get a disabled
girlfriend could laugh at me? Do you
think some skinned [ __ ] with a disabled
fat ugly girlfriend could ever laugh at
me who I had run into the police?
Do you think a fat a a a lanky ugly [ __ ]
with a rat face that could only get an
ugly girlfriend that don't give him sex
could ever laugh at a man like me? Never, bro.
Bro, you keep saying that I'm forgetting
these things when you're the ones that's
forgetting these things, not me,
you know. So, yeah.
Joe, I don't forget things. You're the
one that forgets things. I've shown more
money than all of you. You forget. I've
shown I'm better looking than all of
you. You forget. I've shown that I can
get women that aren't disabled. You
forget. You forget everything. I don't
forget anything. You forget things, not
me. Well, you choose to forget things.
Rather, not that you actually forget
things, bro. Come on now.
I forget things. Are you forgetting that
I've shown Okay. Okay. Are you
forgetting that I've beat all of you at
the money game? Are you forgetting that
I've showed I'm better looking than all
of you? Are you forgetting I've shown
more women than all of you? Did that Did
that pass your mind? Did you forget
Virgin Boy stalking all my sloppy
seconds? Did you forget that? You seem
to forget a lot of things for somebody
that tells other people they forget. Did
you forget all of that when when I
played the money game and I had you all
running? Uh, show me 10 grand in cash.
Yes. Same conversation again. Same
balling again. Uh, I'm not at my mom's.
You don't know where I am.
And you live in a bed sit in your 40s.
Who the [ __ ] are you talking about who
they're with? You know what, mate? I
would rather listen listen. I've I've
said this right a million million million times.
I would rather be with my mom than be in
a shitty bedsit. What you people are in.
I've said it a million times. And you
don't know where I live. That's another
thing. Keep Bro, listen. You don't know
where I live. Simple. That's it.
Nope. You You got show you got asked to
show money all of them times.
No. Ask me [ __ ] Well, when are you
going to stop all of this [ __ ]
When are you going to stop all of this [ __ ]
I'm not speaking about kids.
You're wasting your time, Michael.
You're wasting your time with these ugly
freaks, bro. [ __ ] damn.
So, why do you simp over women, Lger?
Anyways, why do you s Why do you do that?
When do you and when will you and Virgin
Boy realize it's never going to get you laid?
Women don't like you and Simp is not
going to get you laid. When are you ever
And I know you're autistic and that, but
do you not understand? It's never going
to get you laid.
Women don't write to you.
Ask [ __ ] You have to end up with a
[ __ ] disabled girl. When are you
going to learn it's never going to get
you laid? Come on, man. You already
thought you [ __ ] won. Jesus Christ.
[ __ ] simp. Simps everywhere. These
are quite spicy.
Yeah, I'm jealous. Okay, bro. Uh-huh.
Cuz I still I tried to get with all of these.
Yeah, I tried to get with all of the
women that he got with and he never
tried to get with any of the women that
I got with. Yeah, I'm very very jealous.
Huh? Yep. I'm the jealous one, bro. Oh,
damn. You caught me. [ __ ] Uh-huh.
Yeah. That's why I tried to get with all
of the women he got with and he didn't
try to get with all of the women that I
got with. Uh-huh. It was definitely the
other way around. Damn, you got me, bro.
[ __ ] You caught me, Grezy.
Yeah. I wasn't the one messaging Morgan.
I wasn't the one messaging Izzy. I
wasn't the one messaging Sig. Uh-huh.
Nah. That that Nah, that was No, that
was me. That weren't him. That was me.
Huh? That was me, bro. [ __ ] How did you
know it was jealousy? Damn it.
I thought you'd never know. Oh, man.
I warned them. I already had them. I'd
already slept with them. So, no, he
literally tried it on with them. How did
you know I was jealous? Oh, damn. Caught
me out, bro. Uh-huh. Yeah.
Yeah, but I stalked all of you sloppy
seconds. He did stalk any of mine.
That's definitely the way around it was.
Oh, yeah. Damn.
Who the [ __ ] is that? Yeah.
And he is a virgin.
He is a virgin. That's not sing. That's
just a compliment. No, no, no, no, no.
That's not what sing means. Anybody can
give somebody a compliment. That's not
That's not what sing means.
That's not, bro. Anyone can give. So if
you if I went downstairs and
I love my sisters and said, "Oh, I think
you look really beautiful. That's simp."
That's not sing. That's called a
compliment. There's a there's a fine
line between the two.
You actually should know what sing means.
That's not what means. Anyone can give
someone a s right is
basically people that will lick women's asses,
defend them even though women don't like
them. Like Virgin Boy, RoJ, they will
literally sit there and defend them even
though women don't like them. You can compliment anybody.
So that's what simp means
like what what Virgin Boy does in Lord Jim.
So like I was saying about how all women
are the same which is not even offensive
and then you get these little simps
like coming to their rescue like man
saying oh no you don't know women that's
singing that's what you call sing
and the things weren't even offensive.
So what they do is they simp cuz they
think that if they simp and they defend
women it's going to get them laid jokes
on them but
that's why they do it. It's bad really.
They defend women, but women don't like
them. And they make it seem like you're
the one that's never been with women
and [ __ ] That's what they do. They
defend That's how they That's what they
do. And they try to make it seem like
you're the one that's never been with
one when they're the ones that's never
been with one. Do you understand?
That's how the whole singing thing works.
You know what I mean? Yeah,
think about it. I'm not even joking with
with what I'm saying, bro. You know,
I'm not even joking what I'm saying.
Like, I'm saying that he's a virgin
because he he is a virgin.
He is a virgin. I'm telling you he's a
virgin because he is a virgin.
You know, like there's actual evidence
of me having sex, having [ __ ] and
people still try to call me. Like, like
I said, bro, you know, when you're not
liked on here, Michael, no matter what
you do or what you show, they're still
going to just say, "Oh, no, you didn't
show." Like, you you don't understand
that. This is what I'm trying to explain
to you, Michael.
My good friend. I've more women than
Virgin Boy, more money, better looks,
and they still go at me. So you're
wasting your time really.
You can show these people a million
pound and they'd still say, "Nah, mate, you're scared." Oh,
cuz they self project stuff.
But I don't understand why like I wasn't
saying like I said it cuz I was
genuinely getting fed up with it.
like the whole um
I was getting fed up with the whole like
women [ __ ] with a boyfriend [ __ ] and
cuz I'm getting fed up with it,
you know, cuz it's boring, bro. Yeah,
that's why I stopped doing it cuz it's annoying.
So, I learned something about it and I
stopped doing it and because I wanted to
say all women are the same. I get
attacked by all of these people that's
had less women than me. Put it get this
in your mind, Michael. Yeah.
these women that I used to be get with,
this guy used to stalk them. He used to
message them and then they had to block
him. So, could you imagine I done that
with any of your exes and then he wants
to try and do a video
um he's and then they're trying to do a
video on me. That's what I find weird.
You You just Yeah, just just do what you
do. Just put your videos up and just
don't get into it with any of them. Yeah,
it don't matter what you show.
But the things that I was saying is not
offensive. I generally think that they
are all the same. Like
the same like mannerisms, the same
games, the same [ __ ] that they do. I
think they're all the same. I generally
do. I don't think that's offensive.
You don't know where I live. You will
never know where I live. So, keep blessing. Bye-bye.
So, it doesn't matter with these disabled people.
Let the games begin. You don't know
where I live. Keep blessing. But yeah.
Yeah, bro. Just put the um just put
whatever you want to put up. Just don't
get into any of it. As soon as you
realize it's going to get into an
argument. Yeah. Just just just just cut it, bro.
Just cut it. Just cut the [ __ ] Just
don't argue. Just go on to something
else, you know?
Like I said, when you're not liked on
here, then it doesn't matter what you do.
I don't think that's offensive saying
all women are the same. I generally
believe they are.
And then I get called to incel like I've
never like you've not stalked my sloppy seconds.
Do you actually know what a [ __ ]
incel means? Have you have you have you
actually watched any of these incel
videos? They don't have x sloppy
seconds. You do realize that
crazy, isn't it?
Madness. Time wasting. Wasting my time, bro.
Michael, I've got another channel, by the way.
You don't know where I am and you're
banned again. Bye-bye.
Ain't got a life.
So, the thing is Yeah. Um
I forgot what I was saying. I Yeah.
Yeah. But did Elliot Roger ever get Did
Elliot Roger ever get laid?
So, but did ever did did Elliot Roger
ever get laid like I did? Did Elliot
Roger get his sloppy seconds stalked
like I did?
Don't think so. So, anybody that is not
a s is is an incel. So, if I don't lick
women's asses, I'm I'm an insult.
Is that what you've made up? So, because
I I'm not scared to say the truth, I'm
an insult even though I've been with women. Okay.
I'm trying to I'm trying to understand
it because it doesn't make um
I don't like them. I think they're [ __ ]
up [ __ ] and I stand by what I say and I
don't contradict everything anything I
say about them.
It's my choice, you know.
How can I've already answered that question,
right? It's crazy. Unless you lick that like
they're [ __ ] disabled, bro. Um, so
unless you looked at, and the thing is
is like I keep saying, if I was virgin,
boy, I I'd be mad, bro. If I was virgin
boy, I'd [ __ ] be mad at the world.
But I had to end up with something
disabled and I and I never got laid at
31. But they they prefer to defend women.
Strange, is it? They prefer to defend women.
That's crazy. It's got to be all of
them. Got to be.
Oh, for [ __ ] sake. Oh, [ __ ] me, bro.
Sorry about this, bro. Yeah,
they're [ __ ] disabled on here, bro.
Yeah, really. No one No one cares.
Nobody cares about your letters, bro.
Literally, everybody knows what you've
done now. No one cares.
Uh-huh. Yeah, bro. You keep thinking that,
bro. Everybody knows what you people do.
Everyone's been informed and you don't
even know where I live anyway. So, back
on. Bye-bye now. Anyways, back to what I was doing. Um,
yeah, I wasn't want
nobody cares and you don't even know
where I live anyways. Come on.
They're [ __ ] disabled, bro. They're
absolutely [ __ ] disabled on here.
They're [ __ ] mongos, bro. You know,
you need to show your um your um nieces, Mike. Yeah.
You need to show them these people, bro.
And to not end up like these people.
I'm like, you got nieces? Yeah. Or a
niece. You need to show them these
people. This is not what you want to be
like when you're 40.
Like these mongos,
ain't going to lie, on YouTube every day. [ __ ] disabled.
Probably why Monty doesn't
f with anymore. I'm Yeah.
Um, where is that?
Where was that [ __ ] thing?
Oh, your sister knows about it. Yeah.
Uh, what's my other channel? If you
message me on Facebook, I'll give it
you, bro. But don't give it to any of these mongos.
It's like where I've done all my like
approaches and [ __ ]
Are these people really threatening to
send [ __ ] letters, bro? No one cares
about your letters. Didn't you do that
again? No one cares.
It's like what what I used to say to
Trouble. You can only get so far with
being a coward
and then your options are you have no
options after that. Like no one cares
about your [ __ ] ass. Send me what you
want, bro. No one cares. Nobody cares.
It just shows how you ain't got a life.
You're the one that's going to be
wasting your time, wasting your money.
You know what you should do? You know
that money that you're going to waste,
right? trying to get people killed or
whatever it is you're whatever the [ __ ]
it is you're trying to do. You know what
you need to do with that money? Get
yourself a gym. Get yourself to the gym.
Get yourself a gym membership. Get off
your fat ugly skin tes and [ __ ] lose
some of that weight. Yeah. And you might
be able to actually like fit into
society. Like you should actually do
something better with that money. Cuz
I'm telling you right now, like nobody
cares what you do. That's why I'm
telling you to do it. No one cares about
what you fat, ugly, low lives do. That's
why I'm saying like I would I'd be all
right along. Get off of YouTube. Get off
your fat ugly ass. You're not bothering
anyone. Yeah. And sort your [ __ ] life out.
So, what did you think of the videos
anyways? [ __ ] Did you like them or what
did you think of them? Ah, [ __ ]
Yeah, it got to a point where it was
annoying me just watching them.
They say that they're not all the same,
but they have the same mannerisms. They
do the same stuff and say the same
stuff, but they're not all the same.
Strange, isn't it?
They all say what what what man think
about like this, right? What man does
the same thing as another man? None.
If you if you want to see it like that.
Yeah. What man does the same thing as
another man? None.
But these women do the same as each other,
but they're not all the same.
Cuz I feel like when I was watching
these videos, I'm just seeing same [ __ ]
just different people.
But they're not the same.
Strange, isn't it? They are definitely
definitely definitely the same. 100%
they're the same, bro. They're NPCs.
Like Like we say, they're NPCs.
Yeah. NPCs, non-playing characters. [Music]
No one cares about your shitty little letters.
I wish I could tell you that and make
you actually believe it. No one cares.
If anything, you're just [ __ ] with
the neighbors. Really, you're not
[ __ ] with anyone else.
You're just [ __ ] with the neighbors
and you're just like [ __ ] with their
life. Happen to read it. You're not
messing anyone else's life up. Well, now
you're not actually cuz they all know
about you. But at the start, maybe even
the second time, but third time now,
everyone knows what you're about, bro.
Letters, letters, letters.
You know, that's why I was waiting for
you to send letters at like 90
when I was in Stratford. Like I wanted
you I was waiting for you to send them
letters cuz no one cared because
everyone knows me. So like nobody cares.
I was actually waiting for it. I was
saying you come on come on do it. Do it
cuz you're only wasting your time and
your money. You're not bothering no one
else. Everyone knows what I'm Everyone
knows everyone knows me in different areas. So
even kids talk to me for [ __ ] sake. Uh yeah, Yeah, man.
Getting triggered. Nah, none of you
people trigger anyone.
You people are the triggered ones.
Remember, you come on YouTube every day
trying to [ __ ] with people. I would say
that's pretty triggered. You people are
triggered. Look what you do every day.
You can't take one day off of doing it.
I'd say that's pretty triggered. Do you
have a whole channel dedicated to
someone? That's pretty triggered if you ask me. [ __ ] Yeah, man.
Nope. It's Saturday, man. Saturday, bro.
saying you know the Oh [ __ ] Hold on.
One second. They live in my head. Yeah,
I know, bro. Yeah. You live in my head.
Yeah. Uh-huh. I know, bro. That's why
you got a whole channel dedicated to me,
cuz you live in my head. Yeah.
All right, Mike. I'm going to come off
this [ __ ] um later, bro. So, I don't
know if you still got me on Facebook and
want to do like the football and that,
but yeah, I don't think I'm going to be on here
uh for a little while after today, bro.
It's It's getting weird again.
It's getting [ __ ] weird again, bro. I
can't lie to you. It's getting it's
getting disabled again. So, um yeah, I'm
going to come off after like later, bro.
So, you got my Facebook anyways if you
want to talk.
But it's getting weird again, bro.
Like, how long was you off of YouTube?
Like [ __ ] a year, bro.
You probably noticed like when you come
back, it's it kind of fries your brain
because they're [ __ ] disabled
after like the third day or something. Yeah,
this guy on Instagram is really starting
to annoy me, but I'm going to get him to
accept my follow and put all these [ __ ]
on YouTube. He's annoying me, Mike.
Yeah, he's like undercover like trying
to troll me. And he's uh he's um
you don't bully anyone.
You bully yourselves.
That's all you bully. You bully yourselves.
But remember, if you stay here for it,
mate, just don't argue with these people.
And I've seen you on L J's a few times
as well. You need to stop going on that [ __ ] cuz
there you're not you're not going to
win, bro. You're not going to win with
these fat ugly low lives. Ain't got a life
yet. But remember I said that to you. Yeah.
But yeah, I'm going to get this guy. I'm
going to put all this [ __ ] on you on
like another community cuz he's trying
to like troll me and be funny and I'm
accept and I'm like trying to follow him
and he's not accepting it. So I'm going
to put all these [ __ ] all over some
[ __ ] mad thing, bro. When he finally
accepts, I'm going to make like a woman
account and then follow him. Yeah,
I don't like people
that try to do it discreetly, you know.
Yeah, but the the problem is I get I get
what you're saying, but you know, you
probably said all of this stuff like 4
years ago. So, do you understand how no
one could take anything you say serious?
Because the advice that you're given,
you've gave this like probably four years ago.
Yeah, I'm running off because you found
where I am. Yeah, you don't know where I
am. You don't know where I live. But you
keep telling yourself that.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Bro, why would I run
off if you found where I live? If you
found where I lived, you wouldn't What
would you do? Send posters? No one cares
about your posters. You know where I You
knew where I lived for like [ __ ]
eight months and you done nothing.
No, I'm coming off because you're all
[ __ ] disabled and it pisses me off
just [ __ ] seeing you [ __ ] type
like little and that the fact that
you're never going to win with these
people on here which is what I listen
what I should have like
listened to like um you're never ever
going to stop your jealousy towards me.
So there's no point me being on here.
You know what I'm saying? That's you're
never ever going to you're clearly
jealous of something. You clearly ain't
got a life for you to do what you sat
when you're sat on here doing what you
do every single day jealous of people
that you don't know. People just rather
leave you to it. We'd rather leave the
mongos to it.
We'd rather just leave the mongos to it.
You know, it's just easier that way.
And you're all biased as well. Yet you
start arguments with people, you know.
It's not even worth entertaining.
Like that's that's it.
found out where I live. You don't know
Even if you knew where I live, you
wouldn't do anything.
Where are we now? Okay.
Well, I'll be back later, Mike. Anyways, that's it.