And you
bro, this is going to be my last live
stream. I'm probably going to do like a
a video, but yeah, I've been thinking
about this, bro, like for the past hour.
And yeah, I don't want to be associated
with these mongos anymore. these jealous
mongos that's never going to stop. I had
like a really really long think about it
and I was just thinking about like
earlier like what the [ __ ] I'll just
save it for the video anyways but I'm
done after this anyways. So yeah [ __ ]
indigestion. I'm done bro. I'm done
after this. Well, I'm probably going to
do a video. And I said all of this [ __ ]
before you even started mentioning
posters. So, don't even try and say,
"Oh, I've run you off of YouTube."
Because, bro, you don't even know where
I live. And posters don't scare me,
right? Because, bro, you was begged like
for 10 months when you actually knew
where I live to actually send posters
and you never like, bro, that doesn't
bother me one little bit.
How who will I talk to every day? I've
got friends on like you people. You
people are just never ever going to
stop. I' I I've realized this now. I've
actually realized this guy was actually
right. Like you people are never ever
ever ever going to stop it. Like you're
never ever going to stop. You're never
ever going to stop. You jealous fat ugly
people. Like you're never ever going to
stop your [ __ ] are you? It's it's
obvious, bro. Like I'm done anyways, bro. But
yeah, so you can have your shitty little
YouTube, you know, because that's all
you have clearly, you know?
Keep defending women. Keep licking their
asses. Keep calling people what you are.
Um, you know, you can keep you can keep
doing that cuz that's all you have in
your life, bro. No one cares about
posters. You don't even know where I
live. And even if you did know where I
live, I don't care about posters. I
literally do not care. You don't understand. So, yeah.
But yeah, you people ain't got nothing
in your life but YouTube. It's clear as
day. You're never ever ever ever ever
ever going to stop.
You're never ever ever ever ever
going to stop because you're fat, ugly
people ain't got a life. Fat, ugly,
jealous people ain't got a life. Carry
on coming on YouTube every day talking about yourself.
Yeah, would they really? No, they
wouldn't. And it just shows like you
don't even know where I live, right? And
just the fact that you're trying to do
it again, it just goes to show you
people really are jealous of something
in your life. Fat, ugly, can't leave the
house. These people, do you know
actually the analogy I come to yet is
that they're probably so skinn and
disabled they probably can't even go to
the pub. These people sat on you. This
is why why they do all of this [ __ ]
Like the whole belly thing, the whole
It's cuz they're fat, ugly bully victims
that ain't got a life. That's why they
do all of this, bro. Come on. It's it's
laughable. It's laugh a ball. Think of
how much money it costs out of their
benefits as well.
You know, I'm just sick of these self-p
projecting fat ugly people slim.
It gets boring, bro. These these skin
fat, ugly projecting little weirdos,
lad. That's all it is is, bro. You know
what I mean? Yeah. But I'm going because
I want to come off because of you
people. Cuz you're fat, ugly losers that
ain't got a life.
biased, ugly, slow people. Yeah, I'm
leaving cuz I want to leave, bro. It I'm
leaving because I want to leave, you
know, not because you people got me off
here. You can never get me off here,
bro. Never. Never ever ever ever get me
off here, you know? But if you want to
keep saying that, then, bro, keep
telling yourself that. It's not going to
keep me on here. So, you know what I
mean? You don't even know where I live.
You know what I'm saying? So, you keep
you keep telling yourself that. You keep
telling yourself that. You don't even
know where I live. So you're just sad,
ugly, jealous of something in life,
losers. You ain't got a life. Simple,
bro. You ain't got a life. You ain't got
a life. Jealous, fat, ugly people. They
ain't got a life. You know, look at this
comment. He's latest. Women are all the
same. Yeah. All the same Tim. He doesn't
get it. He creeps him out with the cold
project. He will forever be a virgin.
And even this Nicolo. Yeah. You know,
with these people on here. Yeah. It
doesn't matter what you show them. You
got more money than them. You're better
looking. every game.
I've beat them at every game going. Like
every game you can think of going, I've
beat them and they still talk [ __ ]
You're never going to win with these fat
ugly people. That's why I'm coming off
of it. That's why exactly I'm coming off
of it. You know, they try to still call
me all the things that they [ __ ] are.
I don't know, bro. I don't live with my sister.
I've beat them at the money game. Yes, I
have. I've beat them at the better
looking game. I've beat them at the
weight game. I've beat them at the women
game. every game east I beat them at I
beat them at every single game and they
still come here and they still try to
talk [ __ ] You know what I'm saying?
Like it's pointless with this with this
now. You know I don't mind the laughs.
You know the you trying to troll and
rare. Do you know what I'm saying bro?
Like I don't mind that but this is
getting too weird now bro with these people.
And then it's like why what I don't
understand. Why do these simps keep
defending women when I've had more women
than them? Why do they keep doing this?
Trying to say that I'm the virgin and I
creep women out when I've had more women
than them. This is what I don't I I I
don't understand these people. Have they
Are they being dumb on purpose? Are they
just that [ __ ]
I didn't give anyone's address. And they
don't even know where I live. That's
another thing. They don't even know
where I [ __ ] live. None of them do.
And I wouldn't care if they [ __ ] did.
You know what I'm saying, bro? They're
sat fat fat ugly people that ain't got a
life that can't get off of YouTube.
Leave them to it, bro. I'm done. L
literally done, bro. What the [ __ ] was I
even doing earlier doing a [ __ ]
video, bro? What the [ __ ] Madness, bro.
They're [ __ ] They're [ __ ]
Bro, listen. I'm coming off because I
want to come off. You're not You do not
run me off of nothing. Yeah, I have been
on here for years. Yeah. I don't want to
entertain you [ __ ] mongos anymore.
That's my choice. You don't know where I
live. If you knew where I lived, I would
say that you knew where I lived. How can
you run me off and you don't even know
where I live? How can you run me off
when you don't even know where I live?
And I can swear on anything you don't
know where I live. Anything you want, I
can swear on. Yeah. Stop talking about
yourself, you [ __ ] mongos. Get off of
YouTube and go get laid, you [ __ ]
mong. Yeah. Stop talking about yourself,
you fat, ugly loser. So, yeah.
Yeah. These people, you know what it is
with these people, Nicolo? Their lives
are ruined. Their lives are [ __ ]
They're old. They got no hope. They're
fat and ugly people. Disabled, fat, ugly
people. This is why why do you think
they've done all of this [ __ ] to like
rice? And it is funny. It is funny. But
you need to also think of why they do
this [ __ ] why they done this [ __ ] to
why they're trying to [ __ ] um why
they try to um
[ __ ] my life up even though they don't
know where I live. And I'm telling you
now on my [ __ ] dead dad they don't
know where I live. I swear to God on my
life they don't know where I live. You
got to understand Yeah. at the end at
the end of the day. No, no, no, no, no.
It's not about people's mouth. you do
this stuff, you know, is because you are
jealous. Now, bear No, no, no, no, no.
Let's let's get to the real point.
You're jealous of something for you.
Well, you probably won't understand to
be honest with you, bro. You probably
won't understand it due to your
disabilities, but you are jealous of
something. Like, you have been on here
doing this for years and and you don't
stop and you don't stop. You're clearly
jealous of something. You know, you keep
telling yourself you're not, bro, but
you are. Come on, bro. Come on, bro.
Listen, you're lying to yourself at this
point. You know, you are jealous of
something. And it's obvious. No [ __ ]
men, double your age, sit online every
day stalking you, unless they're jealous
of something. And you can ask any
psychiatrist this and they'll tell you
exactly the same thing. What it is with
you people is your fat old skin, ugly.
You got nothing in your life. Let me let
me let me let me talk. You got nothing
but YouTube. You got [ __ ] all. And the
only way you can try and make yourself
feel good is coming online every day
saying that people are this and people
are that and people are this to escape
the fact that you are all of these ugly
things. You are these things that can't
get off of YouTube. You are all of these
things. That's why you're sat on here
every single day, YouTube ridden, never
been seen with a woman, can't show your
[ __ ] face, lose at every [ __ ] game
that you [ __ ] invented. How can you
invent games? How the [ __ ] can you,
[ __ ] invent games and lose
every single one of them and pretend it
never happened? Bro, I've shown I'm
better looking than all of you. I've
shown I've got more money than you. I've
shown I've had more women than you, bro.
I've done a video of me guessing my dick
sucked. I've done a video of me showing
women in a bed. Have any of you people
done that? Come on, bro. Has has any of
Let's Let's Let's really talk about it
right now. What have you shown? You've
shown [ __ ] all. Yeah. You You've shown
that you can only come on YouTube every
day doing what you do because you're fat
skinned, ugly people that ain't got a
life. That's all you have shown in all
of these years. Year in, year out, year
in, year out, year in, year out, year
in, year out. You do this [ __ ] all the
time. Yeah, that's it. Yeah. And
I am going to explain this one more
[ __ ] time because [ __ ] Monty said
this, but I thought I'm not going to
[ __ ] say anything because of
whatever. Yeah. You do not do this for a
reaction. Yeah. There's a f there's a
fair line between someone being jealous
and people doing stuff for a reaction.
People used to write stuff at Timmy for
two seconds to get a reaction. Yeah, you
people will do this [ __ ] even if you
don't get a reaction. Even if you never
ever get a reaction, you never ever get
mentioned, you will still do it all your
life. The extent that you do Yeah. to to
to to get a reaction. What you claim to
do it to get a reaction, bro. It says
everything about your life, you know.
Think about it, bro. You got nothing.
You got nothing in your life but [ __ ]
YouTube. Why don't you all come on
camera? Let's show what you're really
about. Come on. Why don't you all come
on camera? Come on. Come on. And you're
trying to say that I'm below this. I'm
below that. Listen, Smokey. You don't
know what I have. You don't know what I
get. You don't know me. Yeah. You do not
know me. I've seen your stupid little
comments. You don't know me, bro. Yeah.
That's a [ __ ] other thing.
Yeah. You don't [ __ ] know me. And
you're trying to say that, "Oh, I've
seen you before. I've never I've never
seen you before. I've never [ __ ] seen
you before on WhatsApp. Why don't you
put your camera on? How about I put the
link up? Let's Let's talk in Hangouts.
Yeah, let's discuss this. Let's show our
face while we do it as well. You're not
scared, are you, Smokey? What you scared
of? Come on. Come on. What are you
scared of? You're not a manta, are you?
You're not a manta. Come on. I'm the
mantra. I'm ugly. I'm this. I'm that.
I've heard it all from you [ __ ]
self-reflectors. So, why don't you come
in the hangouts? Why don't you put your
camera on and let's have a talk. Come
on. Yeah. Come on.
Yeah. Well, I said fair line cuz I want
to say fair line. So, bro, listen. I'm
the mon. I'm this. I'm all that. I'm all
this. I'm all that. Come on, bro. Join
the hangouts. Put your camera on and
let's and let's discuss this. Yeah.
Come on. Well, you not scared, are you?
I'll put the link out for you. I'll show
my face. You show your face. We can
talk. You won't do that, bro. You won't
do that, though, will you? Come on. Just
tell everyone you won't do it. Yeah.
>> [ __ ] idiot, bro.
>> You people are clearly jealous of life, bro.
Why? Listen, why do you
need to even waste your time on this
[ __ ] bro? Like, why? You got all this
money, so you claim you have this, you
have that, you're better looking, but
bro, then you wouldn't be wasting your
time [ __ ] hating on people every day
on YouTube. You're clearly jealous of
something. You clearly clearly are
jealous of something.
You clearly clearly are, bro. It's
obvious. It's obvious, man. You know,
it's you you you show yourselves up, you
know, just like that Red Star, you show
your fuckingelves up and and at the end
of the day, bro, it's just like earlier.
What the [ __ ] was I doing even doing a
video? What? What the [ __ ] You know,
there's people No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no. You do this even when you don't
get a reaction. You do this. Okay. Okay.
So, and I'm telling you that you do this
even if you do not get a reaction. Yeah.
Do you want me Do you want me to give
you an example? Okay. And I'm going to
give you an example now. Yeah. It is
what you do. Yeah. You listen listen.
You do not do this for reacting. And
another thing is, bro, it's like, what
the [ __ ] was I even doing earlier doing
a video? Arguing with some [ __ ] skin
[ __ ] in a bedsit with a disabled
girlfriend. I'm [ __ ] better than
that. I'm like, what the [ __ ] am I even doing replying?
Replying to somebody that meant run into
the police like a [ __ ] and act like
they won. I think we we we actually
forget a lot of these things. I think we
generally actually forget a lot of these
things. Or in your case, you actually
choose to actually forget a lot of these
things. Arguing with some [ __ ] in a
skinned bed suit. You're [ __ ] better
than that. You're better than somebody
that you had crying to the [ __ ]
police. Why the [ __ ] would you even
[ __ ] be wasting your time on that? [ __ ] hell.
And you do all of this stuff even if you
don't get a reaction. Bro, you want me
you want me to you want me to give you
an analogy here? Listen, bro. Bro, he's
never bullied anybody off again. Memory
loss, bro. Memory loss. You have got
memory loss. Nobody has ever bullied me
on here. Virgin boy has never bullied
me. I want to come off because I want to
come off because you I want to leave you
people to your jealousy. I want you
people to keep embarrassing yourselves
on YouTube. That's what it is. That
[ __ ] nons in a [ __ ] bed sit with a
disabled girlfriend and [ __ ] bullying
no one. And no, they haven't found my
address. They don't know where I live.
Again, I'll repeat that about a million
times. And no, you don't do it for a
reaction. Do you know what? I'm I'm
going to save that for the video.
Actually, [ __ ] it. So you can actually
go back and actually understand that
this whole reaction [ __ ] is [ __ ]
You don't do it for reaction. [ __ ] off. Yeah,
bro. Like, bro, what about when I showed
you money? Where was you then? When I
showed you all money? When I when I
showed you money? Where was you? Where
was all of you when I showed you money?
Yeah. Go on. Go on. Go on. Go on. Go on.
So, why you keep leaving on him? Stand
up for yourself. Um, are you forgetting
that I had him go running to the police
crying? Did Did you forget that one? Did
Did you forget that bit?
Uh, bro, you people just want to go back
and forth on YouTube like the keyboard
warriors you are cuz you ain't got a
life. Some of us actually have a life. I
can't keep going back and forth with a
keyboard warrior skin in a [ __ ]
bedsit. That ain't my life, bro. If you
want to do that for the rest of your
life, you you you can take my place if
you want. And you think I'm going to go
back and forth with somebody in a bedsit
with no money? That ain't my life, bro.
If you want to do that, you can do it.
You will do this cuz you're jealous. So
actually ignoring you is actually the
best thing to do. You do it cuz you're
jealous of something. Deeply, deeply
jealous of something. And you only know
what that is. I'm not going to start
guessing things, bro. You know what it
is. I don't know what it is, bro. You
know what I mean?
Well, the past is very, very relevant to now.
You know, so that's it.
Who is that, bro? Me.
Oh, what's that? What?
I'm not [ __ ] aware of myself, lad.
>> No. So, that's how it is. like you you
I'll just let you keep coming on and
being jealous because we can argue all
day long if you want. But I mean at the
end of the day, you none of you are ever
going to meet me,
bro. Yeah. Do you remember that, Slim? I
showed them money and this is why I
don't show them money anymore because
they don't show me money. Not because I
don't have money. I don't have money,
bro. Come on now. You don't know what I
have, you know?
And yeah, I can sit on here and go back
and forth all day long, but for what?
I'm wasting my life on people that are
jealous. Do you know how stupid that
sounds? I'm going to sit here and argue
with a bunch of jealous people that
ain't got a life when none of them are
going to meet anyone. And when Okay. And then what?
You know what I mean?
Like, think about it, bro. What are you
going to do? Like, meet like you're
never going to meet anyone. You've shown
all what you're about when you got shown
[ __ ] It weren't even six grand.
You've been shown different amounts of
money, bro. You've been shown different
amounts of money. It's not even just six
grand. You've been shown different
amounts. You've been shown 700, 1,000,
2,000. You've been shown 3,000. You've
been shown different amounts of money
over the years. Yeah.
And so that's where we're at. You know
what I'm saying? So, it's like you've
lost every single game you've actually invented.
You know, you want to sit here and argue
all your life. That's on you, bro.
You're never going to meet anyone. You
know, what's the point? I know the
stupid skinned little virgin is never
going to meet anyone. He does what he
does cuz he's jealous. So, it makes me
look stupid me replying to him. He does
what he does cuz he is jealous. Yeah.
Listen, it's like earlier. Oh, I've
never had problems attracting women.
Bro, you're with a [ __ ] disabled
girl. You stalked every single woman
that I got with that people seem to have
forgot. You stalked Morgan. You stalked
Izzy. You stalked [ __ ]
Stig. You stalked You tried to stalk all
of these other women. Are we forgetting
all of this [ __ ] What this little
virgin's done in the past? And he wants
to try to call other people, oh, they're
an incel. Oh, they're all this. Are we
like literally forgetting, bro? Like,
you know what I mean?
Yeah. People think I'm skinn. Yeah.
Cool, bro. Whatever, man. Was I skinn
when I showed you all money and you all
ran away? Was I skinned that time? Was I
skinn when I showed you money a million
times and you all ran away? I weren't I
weren't skinned that time, was I? No.
But you were. You definitely were, but I
wasn't. You know,
I married an absolute 10 out of 10. So,
are we actually forgetting right what
this [ __ ] has actually done? What am I
to be jealous of, bro? I've been with
normal [ __ ] women, you know? I would
rather actually sit there and say I've
actually been with normal women. I've
got teeth in my [ __ ] head. I've I'm
not bored. I don't look like a rat.
What's to be jealous of an ugly bastard
like that? I don't have a [ __ ]
channel dedicated to someone. They have
a channel dedicated to me cuz they hate me. Simple.
You know what I'm saying?
Jen is having 6K at 27 is skin. Oh,
really? Is it? Well,
it could it could be worse. It could be
like you older than 27 and you don't
even have anything. That could be worse.
Yeah, whatever Jane, whatever you say.
So, like what is there to actually be
jealous of somebody with a dis? Like I
could I could safely say to you right
now, I could I could drink 30 Guinnesses
and I still wouldn't get with that
disabled disabled Sarah,
you know? You know, you know. So,
bro, what's there to me to be jealous
of? I'm younger. Don't forget I'm 2
years younger, better looking. I got
teeth. Had more [ __ ] than him. Ones
that he's actually stalked. Are we
actually forgetting that this [ __ ] has
actually tried it on with my sloppy
seconds? This is why I don't understand
why he defends women when he literally
women don't like him. Women hate him. I
have one [ __ ] opinion and they all go
for me. I have one opinion which I I
don't think I'm wrong in saying they're
all the same. And I get all of these
[ __ ] go at me. Like I'm the one that's
never had a [ __ ] woman. Simp.
But I mean that's social media for you.
I don't think that's ever going to change.
Do do you remember that time Slim since
you're the only one that doesn't seem
that you've got selective memory? Do you
remember when he was messaging that
[ __ ] USA Izzy? He was messaging that
Izzy. He was messaging that Stig. He was
even trying to find other women that
I've been with trying it on with them.
Do you remember all of that [ __ ]
Like, bro, do you remember all of that
[ __ ] And I'm the incel. What? Bro, this
doesn't even make sense.
Do you understand what I'm saying? It
Travels abroad. Travels abroad. Um,
bro, he can't play the guitar. Secondly,
he has no friends. That's why he had to
stalk my friends and meet my friends.
Um, I've been with normal women, not a
disabled woman. And I've been abroad
more times than he ever has. And I'm
younger than him. So, I think I'm doing
a lot better than him. And I've got
teeth in my mouth. He doesn't travel
abroad. He's been abroad once at 31
years of age. Let me let me let me put
this into perspective, right? Um, you
know, when he went abroad at 31, you
know that trip that he done? Do you know
how old I was when I done that? You know
when I done that? I went abroad. Do you
know how how old I was when I went
abroad twice the first time? Do you know
how old I was? Do you remember? Don't
know how long you've been watching me.
23. Yep. So what he was doing at 31
I done it at uh 23.
Imagine imagine that.
lives with a disabled girl when I
brought her was 30. Okay bro. Funny is
it? Nice try though man. Yeah.
Yeah. He was stalking um all of my um
sloppy seconds. Let's just call them
that cuz people don't want to call them
exes. So, he's been stalking all of my sloppy seconds.
Cause trouble, bro. You ain't caused no
trouble. You don't even know where I
live. You don't even know where I'm
telling you right now on my mom's life.
Yeah, because maybe you'll believe me
more. You do not know where I live. On
my mother's life. No question included.
that, bro, you're wasting your money and
your time because a I'm telling you
straight, you don't know where I live. I
promise you, you don't know where I
live. Firstly, and second of all, even
if you did know where I live, bro, I'd
tell you to go and do it cuz when you
actually did know where I lived, you
remember when I was telling you to
actually do it. So, yeah.
So anyway, Slim, you know, I'm not
trying to get you on my side cuz I see
that you go on Lorre's, but you
obviously have you obviously don't have
selective memory. So we remember when he
was singing all over my sloppy seconds,
stalking my sloppy seconds cuz he is the
one that is jealous. You know, he is a
he is jealous. That's what it is. I
don't need to go with a disabled woman.
I have had more chances to be in relationships.
You know what is all of this [ __ ] about?
Because I say that what? Because I say
that all women are the same. Okay. And what?
That's my You know what I'm saying?
That's my um that's my choice.
You know what I'm saying? That's my
choice to [ __ ] say that.
You know what I'm saying, bro? So, it's
like, what? What? What did you say
that's actually offensive? This is the
same dude that stalked all of my sloppy
seconds. Think about this, bro. Yeah.
You say that I'm ugly and I'm this and
I'm that. So why did I get all of these
normal women that you can't get out of
your [ __ ] head? Think about it, bro.
Think a [ __ ] about it. And actually,
I actually have been in a relationship
pretty much and I've also had chances to
be in a relationship. But bro, even if
somebody was in a relationship, you'd
still tell them they weren't in a
relationship. Cuz what it is with you
people on here, you self-reflect. So it
doesn't matter what people [ __ ] show you.
So you know what I mean?
You don't like it that people are better
looking than you and got a better life
than you. That's why you do all of this
[ __ ] That's why you do all of this
[ __ ] [ __ ] online every day. You know,
cuz you're jealous of [ __ ] something, bro.
you know, you're prepared to spend money
on posters even though you don't even
know where I live, right? And I'm
telling you, you don't know where I
live. You're you're you're prepared to,
you know, I mean, it says a lot about
your lives. Maybe a lot of people don't
understand it because they're they're
disabled or but or maybe they're thick,
but you don't realize how much you show
yourself up every time you do this. You know,
let's look at Red Star, right? How
long's he been doing this for? Four
years? 5 years? All day every day? Even
when he's not had even though even when
he's not got a reaction from the time
he's woke up to the time he's gone bed.
But he ain't going on anyone's door.
He's begging the black man to do it.
They're all begging the black man to do
everything. But then they'll still come
online and still do what they do all day
every day. But I'm the one that's I'm
the one that's the [ __ ] m.
Well, bro, this is what I say. This is
exactly what I say, right? I mean I
mean, yeah. No, no, you you've got a
solid point. I I'm not going to dismiss
what you've just said, but you've also
got to ask yourself this. If I know I'm
better looking than someone, and I don't
I know they're a skid bun, I wouldn't
waste my time on them. You go well and
beyond to stalk me every single day
doing what you do every single [ __ ]
day. So, you got to be jealous of
something. I don't know what you're what
the [ __ ] you're jealous of, but it's got
it's got to be something. It has to be
something. I mean, because because you
you sit on it all day, every day, years
and years, and and I I couldn't do that.
I couldn't do that. So, it the only
thing it points to is is jealousy. That
is the only thing it can actually be.
And I hate using the word um jealous,
greasy. I hate using that word jealous,
but it's so lazy, you know? It's such a
l But you generally are jealous of
something. I don't know what the [ __ ]
you're jealous of. You're the ones that
are doing it. You know,
you know what I mean?
Oh, yeah. Listen, listen, bro. Okay.
Yeah. I might I might Okay. Okay. Okay.
Bro, listen. Listen, listen, bro. Come
on. Here's the thing, right? It doesn't
matter if I'm if I'm saying, "Oh, I want
to kill myself. I want to do this. I
want to do that." Think about this, bro.
I'm young. I'm better looking than these
people, you know? I' I've got a life
unlike these people. Something that
these people don't have. Think about
these people. They're not normal people.
You know, they're fat, ugly, they ain't
got no life. They can probably They
can't even probably leave the house for
[ __ ] sake. And then you see me, I'm
better looking than them. I've got a
better life than them. I've showed a
better life than them. And if I'm wrong,
get off of YouTube and leave people alone then.
Cuz the thing is,
if you weren't jealous, you wouldn't
waste your time doing this every day.
Think about it. Like, look at this red
star, right? He's no different than
Bomb. You know, he's been doing Yeah,
exactly, Slim. That's what I'm saying.
You're jealous of It doesn't need to be
a lot of [ __ ] things. You're probably
jealous cuz I probably got better looks
than you and I'm young and I can and
I've actually got a life.
So, I mean that something that you don't
have. Even though it's the basics for a
lot of people, for a lot of normal
people that are not on here, you know,
bro, but you people don't bully anyone.
You show yourselves up. You don't bully
no one. Listen, listen to me, bro. The
only people that get bullied is you
people. You've been bullied your whole
life. You're the ones that come on
YouTube every day angry, angry, but not
willing to do anything. Like, all of
this stalking and all of this, you bully
yourselves. You show yourselves up. All
you do is bully yourselves. You get
angry, but you can't do anything. You
beg the black man to do it. I'm a lying,
LT. You get angry, you get mad, but you
can't do [ __ ] so you beg the black man
to do it. Who do you bully, bro? Who Who
do you actually bully? And I'm not
saying anything about like just cuz
you're black, LT. But it is that they
beg the black man to do it. They beg the
black man to do this [ __ ] I can assure
you people, right? any one of you, bro.
You wouldn't even look at me in real
life. You'd walk the other way. Yeah.
Like, we've all seen a lot of you people
when you get exposed, you're nothing to
look at. You people are the ones being
bullied every day on YouTube, angry, but
not willing to do nothing. Cuz let me
let me let me tell you something. Yeah.
LT. Yeah. If I was doing this
religiously, I would drive myself mad
and I would have to go and do something.
You know what I'm saying, bro? I would
have to actually go I would have to
actually go and do something. Think of
this LT. Yeah. Say you was doing this
[ __ ] every day like Red Star or these
other people. You would have to go and
do something eventually in it. Like
you'd have to just go on someone's door,
pack it up in it. Like that's what a
normal person would do. But you come on
here every day, bro. Put your camera on.
Go on. Put your camera on. Simple.
But I'm just saying, bro. It It's facts, isn't it?
Did you see that thing that happened to
Rice? Yeah, Rice. Did Did you see the
video? And also, Bell's been nicked as well.
I'm just saying they beg the black man
to do [ __ ] It's just It's It is true
though. They do beg the black man
because it's not the [ __ ] white man
they're begging, are they? Are they Are
they Are they begging Mark Samson?
Are they begging Mark Samson? Are they
begging Mark Samson? No. So, they're
begging the black man. Yeah, I'm not
going to mention every name they've
begged on here, man. You know,
now they won't see him. They won't do
anything to anyone on here, bro.
Yeah, they won't do anything to anyone
on here, bro. They They were saying that
they were going to send posters again,
bro. They don't know where I live.
They don't know where I live, lad.
Yeah. Listen, bro. They were saying that
they're going to send posters to where I
live. Bro, they don't know where I live.
Yeah. No, Jane. I won't leave Mark out
of it. I'll mention him as much as I
[ __ ] want to mention him. Yeah. Cuz
listen here, [ __ ] I've been to his area
two times. He ain't ever been on my
door. He ain't ever been on my door, bro.
You know? No, I'm not Irish.
Yeah. So, I'll talk about [ __ ] Mark
Samson. Mark Samson is a baldy [ __ ] bastard.
Yeah, he is a [ __ ] nons as well cuz
he tried, you know, he was flirting with
Izzy. I'll say what I want about Mark.
I'll say what I want and I'll do what I
want. Yeah, you're another one with
[ __ ] memory loss who went to his area
two times three years ago in September.
Oh, [ __ ] Did you Did you forget about
that as well? You know,
yeah, I know he's everyone knows what
that mark is, bro. You know, it's so
bad. Yeah. You know how these people
have got selective memory, LT? Yeah.
They even know what Mark's like now.
Well, they knew from the start. Well,
they Well, they know what they're like,
LT. They know what these people are
like, but they've they've all admitted
it. So, that's how you know that that
guy's down bad, bro. When everyone's
admitting it that don't like us. They're
actually admitting now what he is. They
knew what he was. Don't get it wrong.
Them times I went to his area, them
times, they knew what he was about,
nothing. But now they're just saying it
now because that's how you know that
like the guy's down bad, bro. Think of
it. Cuz in the first six months, the
first year of him doing this, no one
said nothing. They knew what he was.
They knew what he was. No one said
nothing. Now everyone's saying stuff
that don't like us.
Think of it, bro.
No, we can't all be wrong, bro.
Cuz people deny everything like I've
show money. I've gone to see bomb. I've
you know people just deny things because
it that that's what winds me up about
this this place. The only thing that
annoys me the most about this [ __ ] LT is
the biasness. Like how many times have I
told you oh don't waste your money.
Don't go back up there.
If it doesn't matter how these people
wind you up again. I said don't waste
your money. Don't do it. Even when we
wasn't talking even when we was arguing
I said listen don't do it. you know, do
you not do it, bro? Because, and I used
to even defend you even when we weren't
even talking cuz it's annoying, bro. It
annoys me cuz they do it they do it with
me as well. I hate that. I hate that
[ __ ] bro. You don't understand. I hate it.
You know what I mean? It it annoys me,
bro. Like, when people are biased like
that, I hate it. That's one thing I
can't stand. Like, that's even when I'm,
you know what I mean? So,
but now everyone everyone knows about
Mark. They, like I said, they already
knew about him, but they've only just
come forward saying.
No one likes [ __ ] Mark, bro. No one.
That's That's saying something, bro. And
don't forget, we're not liked on here.
Not to like not to put you on here, bro.
Like, not to try and get you involved,
but you know, like when you was back on
here and [ __ ] ain't it, bro? But
people, this is what I'm trying to say.
People knew he was [ __ ] the first
two, three times. When did I Okay,
listen. Listen. When did I ever get
credit for going to Mark's Mark's area?
LT, when did I get credit for going to
his area? Never. Never. Before you done
all of that [ __ ] going to his house or
whatever, did I get credit? No one even
talks about that. That never You know
what? That never gets mentioned. And
that was like one of the biggest [ __ ]
ownages. Yeah. Like they can try and
say, "Oh, yeah. Well, you done a
pre-recorded video with Bomb the first
time." Bro, this was done to a tea. Two
times I went to this guy's [ __ ] area.
Yeah. And no one's ever said anything to
this day. Do Do you know Do you know how
mad that is? Not to this day. No one has
said anything about it. That's why I
say, bro, you never ever get into it
with any of these people cuz you're
going to lose. Like, you're going to
lose, bro. They're just biased. They're
just [ __ ] retards.
Just give it up, bro. Just just give it
up. Yeah. [ __ ]
To be fair, you even tried to draw out
LT in a beef with me. P. No, you were
saying stuff about LT. You and him had
your own problems. Yeah. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no. You and LT had your
own problems. I'm sure you did. No, you
did. You did have your own problems. He
even said that some of your comments was
winding him up. That's why I got him
involved. Yeah, that's why I got him
Yeah, but they don't know. This is what
Bro, well, you said you must have said
something because something that you've
said before has wowled him up because
otherwise I wouldn't have said it. I
don't need people fighting my battles. I
don't need no one fighting my battles.
Was LT fighting my battles when I was
[ __ ] when I was in Manchester? No.
Was he fighting my battles when I went
to [ __ ] meet Terry? No. Was he
fighting my battles when I [ __ ] went
to Mark's area two times? No. I don't
need people to fight my battles, bro.
There was obviously a reason for it.
Something must have happened cuz I
wouldn't have just got someone involved like that.
I don't know, bro. But I'm sure you did
mention him, bro. I'm sure you did. I'm
sure you did mention him.
I'm sure you did.
You know, I I know Jimmy Jazz, but I'm
sure you did, bro. I'm sure you did
because why would I get you involved
with someone that's like that doesn't make sense?
I didn't need you all them other times,
did I? And the only reason with the L
thing is cuz you had your own problems
with him. But if he ever comes back
here, I'm not even going to message you.
I'm not going to tell you anything. I'm
just going to fill him in. So there's
not going to be no messaging you. If you
want him, you go get him your [ __ ] self, bro.
You know what I'm saying?
But I don't know what it is with that
Smokeoky Bee. I'm sure you did mention
him. I'm sure I'm sure you did, lad.
But I didn't I don't need no one to
fight my battles, bro, at all.
You know the [ __ ] The reason with that
L J cuz I thought that you wanted to
meet him. If he ever comes back to
London, I'll meet him. Simple. I'll [ __ ]
him up. It's It doesn't matter, man.
There'll be no messaging you. I just
thought you wanted you wanted him yourself.
But saying that, I mean, I guess that
would be a waste of time. But why is
none of you said why is not But do you
not think it's weird out here? None of
these people have said anything about me
going to Mark's area twice. I beat him
fair and square twice.
Twice. And now you're all And now you're
only [ __ ] Now you're only And still
people don't back me up for that. People
don't People don't seem to remember
that, did they? Is it mad how people
don't seem to remember that, Altie?
Never ever got mentioned. It never ever
got mentioned that, did it? I mean, I
should have known all them years ago I
was wasting my time.
Yeah. I I should have known all them
years I was wasting my time with these.
Like it's like earlier, bro, when I was
responding to that [ __ ] nods legs,
like I'm thinking, bro, now later, what
what the [ __ ] am I doing, bro? Arguing
with some [ __ ] idiot in a [ __ ] bed
sit that goes running to the police.
Like, at the end of the day, bro, these
people can act like this [ __ ] has won
like they done with Mark Samson for many
years. But I know the truth, you know? I
know what you people [ __ ] do. You
ain't got a life, bro.
That's why they can't say nothing to me,
cuz it's it's the truth.
Think about it, bro.
Think the [ __ ] about it, you know? Yeah. Simple.
So, no one's going to talk about that
Mark thing. No.
Yeah. No one's meeting anyone. No one's
meeting anyone. It ain't never happening.
It's never [ __ ] happened.
But why am I arguing with some [ __ ]
that run to the police?
Think about this, Lt. Yeah, you might
want to say that I called the police. I
didn't even call the police on you half
the time. And what do you remember what
you done? This little [ __ ] idiot, bro.
And I'm going to sit there and start
arguing with someone like that. Are you
[ __ ] mad? Imagine that, bro. Like you
know when these little biased people try
to sit there and say, "Oh, you're being
owned. Oh, he's got you, bro." Are we
forgetting that this guy couldn't leave
his house for three weeks because of me?
Are we all forgetting that? Cuz we like
to forget certain things. Are we
forgetting that this [ __ ] was hounding
the police cuz he couldn't take the heat
on YouTube? Did we all forget about that [ __ ]
Cuz it seems that people like to forget
things on here
clearly, bro. Like and and you're just
they're never ever going to stop, bro.
Like they're never ever ever going to
stop. Never ever ever going to stop,
bro. They're never ever going to stop.
You know, listen, you've called a police
on me and died snits to your mom about
me breaking in. But here's the thing,
bro. Yeah. Here's the thing. If I was to
have called the police on you, that's
because you actually done something in
real life that could have killed
someone. And half the time I It wasn't
even me calling the police. It was I
don't know who it was, but it wasn't me.
Yeah, I was just saying that it wasn't
it wasn't even me. Half the time, bro.
It wasn't even me.
Just like the last time. So,
and Okay. Okay. So, you're saying that
I've called the police on you, right?
Okay. So, you're you're saying that I'm
I called the police on you. Okay. So,
that's what you're saying. Okay. Am I
doing videos to you every day calling
you out? Am I doing videos calling you,
oh, you're this, you're black this,
you're black that, you're this, you're
that. Am I doing that, bro? No. So, I
mean, there's a big difference. I mean,
bro, am I the one doing videos on you
trying to draw you out every day? No,
I'm not. Am I the one that's got a whole
channel on you and won't leave you
alone? No, I'm not. So, that's the
difference, bro. I think you know when
you've called the police, you know your
place, bro. You took the L.
You took the [ __ ] L. Simple as that,
bro. Like, if you took the police, then
you know you you
It's not m It doesn't matter how they've
done it, whether it was real life or it
was just YouTube. If you do something
like that, then I mean, you take the L,
bro. Is it simple?
Unless you then unless you actually want
to meet someone, unless I actually
wanted to meet you now, then obviously
it' be a different story. But like, you
can't run to the police like a [ __ ]
cry like the [ __ ] that you are, and
then think you can come back on it like
nothing's happened. Just like what Mark
Samson does. No, [ __ ] that, bro. Yeah,
we need to really start like getting
into this [ __ ] again, bro. When these
people want to like,
you know what I mean?
Think of it, bro. Do you know what he
said on his video earlier? Oh, I I can
attract women, bro. How many sloppy
seconds has this [ __ ] stole of
mine? Like you said you was messaging
people to warn them. Okay, whatever. How
many times, you know, of all people,
bro, how many [ __ ] women has this guy
tried getting with that I've been with
and he's going to sit there and try and
call me a [ __ ] incel, bro? How does
that even make [ __ ] sense?
You know, you know yourself, bro. You've
seen it yourself, bro. You know
what I'm saying, bro?
So, it's just silly, bro. All of it is
just really silly. Very, very silly. All of it.
But yeah, I do find it strange.
cuz I don't think the marking ever's been mentioned.
No, I don't think so.
So, think of it four years ago. I bet if
I wish I knew this [ __ ] four years ago,
bro, before wasting my time [ __ ]
going and meeting these people. But it
weren't that bad to be fair cuz I mean
bomb did get me laid.
Bomb did get me laid,
you know? So, I mean, but you you get
what I'm saying, bro. Like how much
money do you think we've wasted between
us all and both of us? And how and how
much money do you think we've actually
uh how much time do you think we've
spent traveling to these places to try
to meet these people? Think about it,
bro. Even [ __ ] Triple H couldn't come
out, you know, if you want to get that
deep into it, bro. He even he couldn't
come out three times.
So like, come on now, man.
It's just silly, bro. Really? It's just very silly.
[ __ ] up, bro. It is [ __ ] up.
It's mad madness. But yeah, that's two
in one week. LT, you all right, Captain?
And you know what? As much as I find it
funny like the whole Rice situation and
that, bro, I don't like the [ __ ] like
the grassing and [ __ ] like especially
when they know where he lives. And
obviously I never had a problem with
Rice. I said this to Monty earlier, like
I've never argued with him um and [ __ ]
but even though Okay, yeah, it is funny, [ __ ]
you know what I mean?
Listen, LT, I I was in a carnival as
well, Captain. You're right, Captain.
You were right, Captain. But yeah, the
rise thing was funny, but it's not.
I think they must have sent letters and
[ __ ] [ __ ] madness.
That's [ __ ] bro.
Who donkey? Huh? Yeah.
But it's all cowardness though because
they know where they know where the guy lives,
right? And what no one done anything.
It's cowardness. It's It is funny. Like
obviously the drama is funny, but bro,
like it would have been more
entertaining if actually somebody
actually done something other than grass.
It's just it's not good, bro. Is it?
It's not good.
Yeah, he is in Glasgow and everyone knew
where he lived and there's loads of
people on here that live in Scotland. So
why couldn't somebody just went on his door, you know, is cowardness.
And they don't realize that if it's a
family house, the only people they're
affected is everyone but that person.
And they don't even realize that.
Why couldn't someone win on his door?
Like think about it, bro. We we hear
this all the time. Oh, you won't come
Scotland. You won't come here. Oh, we're
all about it. Why has no one gone on
this guy's door? They resorted to
snitching when they knew where he lived. You know,
it's [ __ ] up, bro. It's mad cuz it all
goes quiet and people think they're safe
and then madness like that happens.
It's bad, bro. Bad.
Bro, there's loads of nonses on here.
Nons. And this is what I say. I was
saying this to Monty earlier. Why don't
no one go for [ __ ] nonsexs? They know
he's a [ __ ] nons.
They know he's a [ __ ] nons.
Am I lying?
But no one goes for that [ __ ]
You would have thought they would have
went more for him than Rice. You understand?
[ __ ] virgin boy, you know. Yep.
If these people actually put more effort
into fixing their life, they wouldn't
have to be doing this. Do you know what
I said? Yeah. I said like
basically, bro, like instead of sending
them posters out to where you think I
live, cuz you don't even know where I
live. Why don't you get yourself to the
gym and actually get yourself a life,
you know? Like, cuz they don't know
where I live. Well, trust me, and I'll
tell you this on the phone anytime you
want, they don't know where I live.
And when they did know where I lived, I
was asking them to send them cuz
everyone knows everyone knows me. So
like, you understand, bro? Like the thing is
they spent more time [ __ ] trying to
fix their ugly [ __ ] up life,
you know, then they wouldn't feel the
need to be doing this [ __ ]
Like they're jealous of something, bro.
I don't care what anyone says. Anyone says.
I don't care what anyone says. You show
it every day, bro. You know,
you show it every day of your life. You
show it, you know.
And if Monty man tries getting me back
on here after, I'll tell him [ __ ]
himself, bro. Cuz I ain't [ __ ] cuz
don't even try to get me back on here, bro.
[ __ ] annoys me, bro. I swear.
So, what do you think of what they done
with Rice? Do you think they should have
done it another way or what?
You know what I mean?
It's not good, bro. It's not good.
I can't believe that. I thought they
were chatting [ __ ] with that rice thing, bro.
So, Rice is gone and is gone. Yep. That's mad.
See, people always um No, my bet's on
Saturday, bro. I told you,
bro. He can spend £300, but that's Bro,
that's not where I live. Like, they
don't know where I live.
Trust me. I'm I'm coming off this [ __ ]
because I want to come off this [ __ ]
because of how weird it is. I'll leave
you jealous people to it, bro. I'll
leave you jealous people to be obsessed
every day of your life. And you know
what I'm saying?
It's [ __ ] up, bro.
Yeah. Well, I blocked Antman anyways.
Yeah, I blocked Ant-Man anyways. So, yeah.
See, this is what like not like I
blocked him anyway, so I'll say this
[ __ ] to his face. Like this is what I
always thought with him like, "Oh, the
women thing was him because he's like
weird and some of the shit." Like I
always put it down to him, but then I
class myself as normal and then I was
getting exactly the same [ __ ] So
yeah, I had to block him cuz it was too weird.
Yeah, he's living in Thailand now. He's
never coming back.
So that's why I just thought, oh, like
he's weird or maybe they find him ugly
or that I thought it was him that was a
problem. And then I started getting the
same [ __ ] with these women.
Even I was I was speaking to [ __ ] um
USA Izzy's friend um
LT, bro. And it was it was whining it
was winding me up, bro. We was on the
phone for like 5 hours, bro. No [ __ ]
And there was no arguing. There was no
nothing. But it's like she was winding
me up, bro. Like the whole Oh, yeah. if
you if you was going to come here, I've
got seven siblings somewhere in prison
and I would have shot you. I was like,
bro, you wouldn't do [ __ ] And it was
winding me up so bad that, bro, like I
was going to start it again, bro. But I
was just like, "Oh, just leave it."
Like, don't I don't know who you're
[ __ ] talking to, bro, but you ain't
shooting no one. I don't care who the
[ __ ] you are, bro.
You know what I'm saying? Like, I don't
care if you know people that's been
prison. Like every everyone knows people
that's been prison, bro.
You know what I'm saying, bro? Like it
was annoying, bro. You're not going to
do anything to anybody.
Like, you're not going to do nothing to
nobody, bro. It was annoying me, bro.
And there was no argument. There was no
argument to be had
like in any of it. Like, there was no
argument. There was But just the whole
thing is like, bro, you would get hurt.
Like, you don't understand. I'm not even
joking. Who in their right mind, bro?
Bro, listen, let me let me tell you this. Yeah.
Who in their right [ __ ] mind goes
somewhere to lose? Go on. Go on. Go,
bro. You ask me. You ask me. You You
answer this question. Who goes some all
all the way to lose to to know they're
going to lose, bro? And they did go to
the old bill as well, LT. Bro, I forgot
to tell you that. They dab not five
times, but they did go.
Her best friend told me. Yeah. [ __ ]
it's all madness, bro. I don't I can't,
man. I can't. It's [ __ ] Well,
and I didn't actively search for the
person. I don't you you understand? I
don't actively stalk people out here.
I'll type someone's name like once a
month. Like when I'm really bored. I
don't do what Red Sword does all day
every day from the time he wakes up to
the time he goes to bed.
Like I don't do that [ __ ] bro. I don't
[ __ ] sit on there
cuz I I don't You know what I'm saying?
Like this is You understand, bro? Like
I don't what you think I do. I don't
know what you think I do, but I don't. You know, yeah.
And you know when I was like speaking to
them, we were just talking about
politics and life and [ __ ] And even
though I was just speaking to them, the
the whole thing was just annoying me.
It was just annoying me, bro. Like it
was the whole thing was just annoying
me. It's like, bro, should you really be
dealing with these westernized [ __ ]
Look at all of this [ __ ] that that that
that's happened, bro. Like all of this
like amalgamations. You need to really
think what you're [ __ ] doing. You
know what I'm saying, bro? That's what,
you know, it's just the whole thing was
just annoying me. Even though there was
no arguing or anything.
And that's it, bro.
Just can't be bothered, bro. It's [ __ ]
But yeah, my bets for um my bets for Saturday, bro.
So yeah, I put 90 on it. Returns 324. So
it's a good return.
Might have to hit up Fabrics, you know.
But yeah, that's like not not to be like
weird or anything, but that's what I
thought the problem was like,
oh, like Ant-Man's weird, like people
think he's ugly, like people think he's
a n and [ __ ] and that's why people
didn't go for him. But then it started
happening to me and I'm like [ __ ]
normal. So it's like it's got to be these [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying? Like like it's
mad. Yeah. He told me a [ __ ] up thing,
you know, LT.
I had to block him, bro. I had to block
him. It was too weird.
It It was too weird.
Very very very very weird, bro.
See, I'm not biased, bro. See, I block
people people if I need to block people and [ __ ]
But if a nons can come off of YouTube
and live a life, why can't any of you?
You know what I'm saying? LT if think
about it like this. If a nons if a
weirdo nons can come off of YouTube and
live a life, why can't any of you?
That's that's more of a shame. That's
that that that that's shameful, isn't it? Really?
So, think about it.
If somebody was a nons if someone's a
nons and all of this [ __ ] why can't
they come off of [ __ ] YouTube, you know?
If someone could do it like that, why
can't any of you,
you know what he told me, LT?
Like me? What about me?
He told me he was with this woman. Yeah,
LT. And then he went in like the the
child's woman room and started touching
the child up
and then she was saying, "What are you
doing? What are you doing? It's quite
sick actually, bro. I had to block him.
It was quite [ __ ] sick. It's [ __ ]
bro. Listen, I'm coming off of this
[ __ ] Anyways, I was just talking about
you little mongos. But yeah, I had to
block him after that, bro. It was getting weird.
I actually thought all of this [ __ ] was
just like talking and that, but nah.
basically, right? He was with this woman
that was 38, right? And um
her her child was in the room and he
went in the child's room. He couldn't
stop thinking about the child and he was
like touching the child up and that and
the child went up screaming. So that's
why he left like Thailand and [ __ ] and
then the mom like messages him abuse and
[ __ ] See, I don't think that shit's
funny. I I generally thought like cuz
I've said some [ __ ] up things. Yeah.
But and that's why I always thought he
was the problem with the women and [ __ ]
I always thought it was him. But then
the same [ __ ] started happening to me
cuz I'm not a [ __ ] nons. I'm not a
[ __ ] weirdo and I get the same [ __ ]
Like he's still done the right thing
going Thailand. But I had to block him
after that. Bro, that's [ __ ]
I've defended him when I've Well, I've
never defended him
when I actually knew he was an actual
[ __ ] nons. No, I didn't defend him. You know,
it's bad, bro. It's bad. [ __ ] off, Joe.
You [ __ ] defend nonses trying to
[ __ ] sit there and try and say uh
trying to sit there and [ __ ] say, "Oh, um
you know, nonslegs own me when you know
and I've owned them a million times."
Which is what I was saying to Joe. You
you was what I was saying to LT is you
people are biased. Like you keep doing
this [ __ ] cuz you're jealous every
single day, bro. I'm done with all of
you, you know.
Um Yeah, but it wasn't actual child porn, obviously.
It was just some animated thing. Yeah,
when he went in the ladies toilet. Yeah,
because women are [ __ ] Women are
[ __ ] Yeah, that's funny. That's
funny as [ __ ] Him going in the ladies
toilets. Yeah, that's funny as [ __ ]
We're not touching up a kid. There
there's a there's a there's a fine line
between both of them. I mean, yeah, it
is funny as [ __ ] Like some of these
Snapchats used to used to make me die, bro. You know,
it is funny. That is funny as [ __ ] Like
him running into like girls toilets and [ __ ]
you know? No, it couldn't have kids in
it. It was in a pub, you idiot.
It was in a [ __ ] pub.
So obviously there was no kids in it. It
was in a pub. Yeah, that is funny as
[ __ ] bro. Some of these snaps did used
to be funny.
But that just goes to show that like it
is women that are the problem cuz you
got a weirdo like him. Yeah. Struggles
and then you get a normal person like me struggles.
Like I was saying to you, Ali, just the
whole the whole USA Izzy thing when I
was speaking to a friend, the whole
thing was just annoying me. Who the [ __ ]
do they think they are? No, they can't.
Not in central London, they can't. No,
they can't. And I tell you how I know
this because I was in a pub two weeks
ago and there was these kids that tried
to come in with their parents and they
weren't allowed in. Not in central
London or not. Unless it's a Weather Spoons. Uhhuh. So,
it is women that are the problem here.
Of course, it's women that are the
problem here, bro.
It is funny as [ __ ] but women are [ __ ]
here. Nothing he ever said about them were wrong.
Nothing he ever said about them are
wrong. Like, they're not interested. They're [ __ ]
Nothing he ever said was wrong, though.
That's the difference. Apart from all
the weirdo [ __ ] and the nons [ __ ]
nothing he ever said was wrong, though.
He's, "Oh, you know what? You you know
what they were like for years." It's true, though.
Yeah, true. But I doubt there was going
to be kids in the toilet by themselves.
Come on, man. It's not a thing that's
aimed at kids. So, yeah, it's mad.
But you have a different opinion on
women, Joe. And then all the simps come
to their rescue.
They come to their rescue like Superman, Stimp.
They all come and treat you like you're
the one that's not had women. Like even [ __ ] nonslegs
[ __ ] earlier doing a [ __ ] 10
minute 30se secondond video.
What the [ __ ] doing a 10 minute 30
second video when the [ __ ] cunt's
still a virgin with a disabled girl and
he's singing. [ __ ] hell. But to be
fair, he is diagnosed autistic.
So, I mean, you know. Yeah.
But yeah, you basically you saw the
approaching videos I sent you, Joe, in
America. Doesn't seem like it's any
different over there either. Sadly,
don't that doesn't it depress you like
watching that [ __ ] It [ __ ] annoys me, bro.
20 minute vig.
No, I didn't.
Yeah. And it wasn't sing over women.
And I think you've got memory loss as well.
Yo, because this guy was actually trying
to get with all of my sloppy seconds,
but I'm the incel. Mhm. I'm the incel
cuz I don't lick women's asses. Yes, I'm
an incel. Yes. And this incel had women
that you wish you could get. I love how
uh in the past and that's why he doesn't
reply to any of the [ __ ] because he
knows I'm right. But I'm the incel. I'm
the incel cuz I say what? Women pretend
they've got boyfriends. you actually
know the definition of um you I would
actually be more closer to a misogynist
than an actual incel. I'd actually be
classed as a misogynist, but I'm not
even that. I'm just saying I think
they're all the same and they pretend
they got boyfriends.
I mean, that's not really misogynist.
That's just facts.
I mean, that's that's what you'd be
closer to. How could I be how Think of
it, bro. If someone's an incel.
Nah, he's a s. He's been doing it for
years, bro. Even when I used to meet
him. He's a [ __ ] s. He's an actual s.
No, he's an actual s.
Well, how do you know they don't know,
boy? He's an actual s.
They simp women, but women don't like
them. You know, me and Ant-Man used to
talk about this all the time. You know,
you know, like they they defend women,
but they can't get women and they don't
get women and women don't like them. And
yet you have an opinion on someone
that's actually been with women.
Do you know what? You know when if I
ever saw that USA Izzy here with her
friend, I would think I actually won. I
would think, "Yep, this is the jackpot."
I would I would smash that [ __ ] face
in front of any man. Bro, you know when
you thought that you got me that day,
LT, you know when you thought you hit
the jackpot, I'd be like, I hit the
[ __ ] I would be like, I hit the
jackpot here, boy. I would be like 777.
Oh, mate. I would have a filled day. [ __ ] hell.
I would have a filled [ __ ] day, bro.
[ __ ] Americans, bro. Yeah.
So you'd actually call me a misogynist,
not an incel. Cuz if I was an incel, why
are you begging incel sloppy seconds?
Why are you trying to get with incel sloppy seconds?
[ __ ] trying to get a [ __ ] with an
incel [ __ ] sloppy seconds. But
anyways, you're all low lines, bro. Like
this whole thing, you you're never ever
going to stop, bro. You're never you're
never going to stop your [ __ ] Mhm.
>> You're never going to stop your
jealousy, bro. What's going on in your
lives? Honestly, man. Come on.
But you you you do all of this stuff,
Joe. Cuz you're jealous. You don't do it
for reaction. You do it cuz you're jealous.
You do it cuz you do it cuz you're
jealous of something. And only you know
what that is. No one else. Cuz
I mean it's you have to be pretty
dedicated to do this every day on YouTube.
Stalking from the time you wake up to
the time you go to bed and you don't
think you're jealous or something and
you don't think that you're the skin
one. Please, bro, have a word with yourself.
See, let me tell you something with that
USA thing. You see how I never done it
every day, every other day, every week,
every two weeks. If you want to use that
as an example, you see how I don't
bother them every day, bother them,
bother their family every day
or and I gave up in the end. Isn't that a madness?
And it but these people never give up
and they do it all day every day. So it
can only be that you're jealous of
something. You can say you're not, but
you know, you wouldn't waste your time
doing this. Reaction, no reaction. Even
if you don't get a reaction, you still
do it. So, at the end of the day, I
mean, something's not right there, bro.
You say you're not jealous, but you have
to be. You literally have to be
cuz there's no reason why other reason
why you would do it.
And it's what you do. [ __ ] it, bro. Even
if you got even like I was saying, even
if you got Sorry for repeating myself,
LT, these people don't really understand
these things. So, say I done it for
react. Say you do it for reaction. Yeah. Okay.
So you stalk every day, you react every
day to get a reaction. Okay. So you get
a reaction 6 months later. Okay. And and
and and what? Okay. You get a reaction
and what? So 6 months later you get a
reaction. Okay. Do you want a round of applause?
So it just doesn't really add up to
anything. You know, you you No, you are
the ones reacting. You've got a whole
channel on me. You've got a whole
channel dedicated to [ __ ] reacting to
me and being triggered by me.
Even if they don't get a reaction, they
still do it, which is what I've
explained a million times, you know?
So, even if you you don't do it for a
reaction. People used to troll Timmy for
reaction. No, no, no. You don't do it
for a reaction. You definitely
definitely don't do it for reaction.
Like I said, [ __ ] I could
ignore you for 10 years and you'd still
be doing it every day.
You'd still be doing it every day. I
could come back 10 years later and you'd
still be doing it and you would have not
got any replies in them 10 years. I'm
not reacting. I'm telling people why
you're doing it. You know, there's
there's a there's a there's a big difference.
You know, you say that I'm skin and I'm
this and I'm that, yet you're the one
stalking all day every day. make it make
sense because none of it does, you know.
So, and that's not even reacting. That's
me telling you why you're doing it.
Timmy is what you call reacting.
You do it cuz you're jealous of
something in life, bro. And only you
know what that is. No one else does.
You know, man,
I mean, what is it, bro?
But, um, for you to do this dedication
every single day, you got to be jealous
of something. Obviously, a lot of people
in here were disabled, so they don't really understand.
That's probably why they don't get what
you mean. But you have to be
you have to be jealous of something.
You after me,
>> but you say you still do it for reactions.
Right. Let me let me go now.
See, if you look on this Red Star
account, he's been doing this for years.
Sat on YouTube years stalking me all
day, every day. It's got to be jealous
of something. You've got to be for you
to be coming online all day every day
doing it. You got to be jealous of something, bro.
You got to be because they wouldn't
waste their time on you. You you
understand? Like people like Steven
Howard, they wouldn't waste their time
um if if they were better than you. If
they were better than you, it'd be a
case of oh, I'm not going to give you my time and
but they do it every day and they never
ever stop. You see with with most
stalkers, right, they stop. Or someone
that's been [ __ ] with someone,
eventually they stop. I mean, like even
a few people on here stop, but these
people never stop. So, they're clearly
jealous of something. They clearly
clearly are cuz they wouldn't give you
they wouldn't give you their precious
time if there wasn't.
They wouldn't they wouldn't waste their
time on you.
She looked and they're still doing it.
And they never they never stop. Never
stop. That Oh, that's coach went through my belly.
>> Bit of nuggets.
You look, Virgin Boys posted another
video. They never ever stop. It's so mad
how they put all of this time and energy
into somebody that they're better now,
is it? It make it makes you wonder
how they say that you're this and you're
that and [ __ ] bro. And you're this, but
they sit there and waste every day of
their life on you. It's mad, isn't it?
It's mad, isn't it, doggy? How these
people claim that I'm this and I'm that
and they're none of these things, but
yet they spend all day every day
stalking me and being obsessed with me.
Makes you wonder, doesn't it? Makes me
[ __ ] wonder. I never even know that
when I used to be in love.
Makes you wonder, doesn't it? It makes
you wonder what these people really look
like, you know? Um,
crazy, is it, bro? Crazy.
Yeah, I'm skinn. Yep, I'm skin, bro.
Yeah, I disagree to everything you say.
Yeah, cuz whatever people show you,
you're just going to deny anyways.
Um, like I said, I beat you at every
single game and you still say I'm skinn
and I'm this and I'm that and I'm this.
Yeah, bro. No one no one cares what
you've got to say, you know,
bro. I don't want to see your [ __ ]
face. I don't care what you look like.
Yeah, you people asking.
Do you have any new thing, bro?
Yeah. Look at him, bro. Like even when
you see his face, he's such an ugly
bastard. I was actually seeing I was
actually seeing Yeah, I was just looked
at that video and yeah, this explains
why he does this. Look how ugly he is.
Like actually in the [ __ ] light, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. These these jealous people are
never going to stop.
I think that's why I've literally come
to this conclusion. But honestly, yeah.
These jealous, ugly people are never
ever going to stop
it. Life must it must suck being these
people. Really, it must really really
suck being these people.
I feel I feel bad for them, you know. I
genuinely feel bad.
I do feel bad, bro.
Because I I I cuz bro because I'm not a [ __ ] narcissist,
you know? I'm not a narcissist, bro.
Like, I I couldn't imagine being
obsessed and jealous of somebody every
day of my life on YouTube. Like, you'd
be a narcissist if you didn't feel bad.
I'm not I'm not a narcissist like these
people. Like I couldn't imagine living
in someone's head rentree.
Um someone living in my head rent free
every single day. I have to do videos. I
feel bad. I do feel bad for them, bro.
Like it doesn't matter if I don't like
them. They literally have nothing in
life but a Peterbelly addiction.
Why do they never ever stop? I stopped
with this whole Morgan thing. I messaged
a friend like weeks ago.
You know, I actually messaged a friend
weeks ago because I just typed her name randomly.
So, you got to understand that these
these things that these people do, you
only do it to people that you're in love
with or people you're jealous of. I
mean, it could be that either,
especially if it's a man. So, I mean, it
just says everything about their life, you know?
It says everything about their life when
they come on air all day. It just shows
that they're jealous of you. He did.
Honestly, bro, I wouldn't say it if I
didn't believe it, you know,
and then they defend.
Strange people, bro. Very, very strange people.
But how he can try to call anyone an
insult when he's [ __ ] in a bed with a
[ __ ] disabled girl, still a virgin,
is beyond me. Even when he's not trying
to talk about me.
Yeah, these people will never ever stop,
bro. I should have took that guy's
advice [ __ ] years ago.
Maybe it was like two years ago. They're
never ever going to stop. They're
clearly jealous of something. And I'm
not here to answer what you're [ __ ]
jealous of. You know what I mean?
But it's clearly clearly something.
Clearly is something.
And if you're too disabled to understand
it, bro, then that's on you.
So, so why do these people keep
defending women anyways, Joe? When do
they realize that simp is never going to
get them laid?
When when are they going to realize that?
Can't show money. I I I mean, how how
much are you going to show me?
I mean, you can do. Yeah, if you want.
How much are you going to show me?
Sure, man. How much you showing me here?
I can put the link on.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. It is It
is jealousy. It is jealousy. I mean, you
can show two grand, but
I mean, I don't care cuz I've showed
more than that. It is No, it is it is it
is it is jealousy.
Think of it. You've been doing this for
years and years and years and years and
years and years and years. And here's
the thing. You're using that horrible
stuff as an excuse. Have you noticed no
one else cares about that all of this
all of these thing, right? All of this
[ __ ] And you've also been at people
before they've said any of these things
as well. So, at the end of the day, um,
no one cares about that stuff but you.
It's because it's it's an excuse for you
to be jealous. Because, think about it,
bro. It's not because of what you said.
Cuz no one else cares about it but you.
It's jealousy. If I had to come on
YouTube every day wasting my life on
someone, I'd know I'm jealous. I would
know deep down I'm jealous. If I if I
was given one life by God and I had to
be such a loser where I had to come on
YouTube doing this all day every day and
not get paid for it, I know I'm jealous
to someone. I know I'm I'm jealous or
I'm in love. There's there's no other
thing that can that can uh that would
that would that would um explain it
other than you're jealous. And I'm
someone that hates using the word
jealousy cuz it would only
that's the only thing that would make
sense. That's generally the only thing
that would make sense unless you're in
love with someone. I mean, you could be
in love with someone, but I mean I mean,
are you gay or like what is it? Because
you don't care about stuff people said.
Nobody cares about that [ __ ] Nobody
cares about that [ __ ] But you obsess
people, you use it as an excuse cuz
you're jealous. That's the excuse that
you use. You're narcissist. That's
that's one of the excuses that you use
um to justify why you've done this
and you can [ __ ] off. So, bro, you show
me and then back to you, Joe. Sorry,
bro. I don't want you show me 2K. I'm not interested.
I'm I mean, are you are you trying to
play the money game with me? I told you
I'm never playing the money game with
any of you other people again.
You're biased. You forget what you're shown.
So yeah, it's not because of what people have said.
Um, was I uh jealous? No, I was in love,
which is what I said. You could either
be in love or you could be jealous. And
I didn't stalk her every single day and
I gave up. And I didn't stalk her every
single day. And that's cuz I was
actually in love. So, I mean, yeah. I
mean, I admit it. So, that's what I'm
saying. You're either in love with
someone or you're jealous of someone.
That's that's the whole point I'm making. So yeah,
and I didn't do it every day and I gave
up. Like I literally gave up.
So I mean you do it because you are
jealous. You would do it to anyone.
Anyone that comes on here that's 21, 22,
better looking than you, got a better
life than you, you will you will [ __ ]
with them until they react to you. And
then when they react to you, you will
use it against them because you are narcissists.
You know what it is with you people? You
hate anyone that's better looking than
you, got a better life than you. You
don't like anyone that's better than
you. So that's why you [ __ ] with them on
the internet. Cuz I'm sure there's
people that said worse stuff than me on here, you know?
So, and I never used to stalk her every
day. And listen, the reason I done what
I done is because I asked the [ __ ]
numerous times to say sorry and she kept
trying to mock me. So I thought, okay,
you want to [ __ ] with me, I'll [ __ ] with you.
So I didn't go straight to like doing
that. But I stopped. Are you people ever
going to stop? Never. You're never going
to stop. You're never ever ever ever
going to stop.
So And it's not because of what people
have said. It's cuz you're jealous.
Simple. You're jealous, bro. No one
gives a [ __ ] about what people said
years ago. You're all jealous. Look at
what Pat Mustard ended up looking like.
Look at what Pat Mustard ended up
looking like. Look at what [ __ ] Bomb
ended up looking like. Isn't that a
madness how all of these people that do
this for revenge have all been fat and
ugly? Ain't that a thing?
Ain't that a thing? Huh?
Isn't that a thing though? Huh?
You selfject. It's because you are jealous. You know,
so yeah, you you you are jealous. It's
not because of what people have said at
all. You would [ __ ] with anyone even if
they did say anything. You know, even
Red Star even said it in a roundabout
way because I flashed money and I won
money. He hates the fact I'm better
looking and I got more money than him.
Like he even admitted half of it. When
people say, "Why are you doing this?" He
even said, "Oh, cuz he like he doesn't
like the fact that I'm better looking
than him and I got more money than him."
This is where all of this YouTube
[ __ ] comes from. It's deep down
jealousy. They don't stop. They never
[ __ ] stop. You know, you want to talk
about USA [ __ ] Izzy and I and I and I
done that thing to USA cuz she was also
being a [ __ ] as well. So, there's a few
things that like went into that and I
gave the [ __ ] a chance a million times.
You know, cuz who's the one that's
suffering? Like, you're the ones that
have to sit on here being obsessed every
day and you don't get paid for it. I'm
not the one suffering.
Like, that's that's what I'm saying.
You know, I'm not the one suffering. You
are the ones you're the ones that have
to sit on YouTube every day doing all of
this weirdness cuz you ain't got a life.
I ain't suffering, bro. You are.
show that you're not skin Joe suffering.
Not cuz of you people. You people don't
bully me. You people don't bully me at
all, bro. Cuz we all know what most of
you people look like. Fat, ugly, sad
with your lives. You don't You don't
make anyone suffer cuz I wouldn't be on
here. You don't make anyone suffer. You
just embarrass yourselves. Like it
doesn't matter like how many times
people tell you this. You don't
understand. Like you just you just bully
yourselves basically. You don't bully anyone else.
You just show yourselves up, you know?
And why do you people like,
"Yeah, you can say I'm getting ran off
from YouTube all you want, bro. That's
not going to keep me back on here. So, yeah.
How do I know what anyone looks like? Um,
because I've seen Bombs looks, I've seen
Pat's looks, I've seen Graycat's looks,
and they all used to come on there doing
the same thing as you people used to do. So,
okay, tell tell Red Star to put his
camera on them.
Okay, I might be wrong then. Well, if
you weren't fat and ugly, you would show
your faces just like I would. If I went
on a new community and I said, "Oh, [ __ ]
you. You're this. You're that. You're
this. You're that." And I'd be like,
"Fuck." They'd be like, "Oh, [ __ ] Show
your face." I'd show my face. There's no
there's nothing to it. But you people
can't show your face, which doesn't look
good, does it? And then when you do get
shown what you look like, you all fat and ugly.
So, and you've been [ __ ] with people
for years. You know what I'm saying? So,
that's the that's the madness about it.
It's just like that red star. He
probably looks like Pat. He probably is
Pat, to be honest. And if he's not Pat,
he probably looks like Pat.
Cuz isn't it funny how it's no young
people that are better than you doing
this? You don't notice that all of these
people that are doing this are old, ugly
people. It's not even young people that
are the same as you.
Like you're clearly clearly
maybe you don't realize it, I don't
know, but you are clearly jealous for
something, bro. Cuz I wouldn't be
wasting my life all day every day on someone, you know?
I stopped that USA easy [ __ ] ages ago, you know?
And that was somebody that I actually
met and actually [ __ ]
You know what I mean?
What would you class me as? Greaves.
Yeah. Misogynist or an incel. I don't
think, bro, I don't agree with these
little sayings. You know, you should be
able to have your own opinion on women.
You know, you should definitely be able
to have your own opinion on them.
I mean, there's a difference, right?
Yeah. I'm an incel.
So, I've never had sex. No. I never show
me with women that weren't escorts. No.
Oh, okay. I'm an incel. Uh-huh. So, cuz
I don't lick women's asses, I'm an incel.
So, anyone that doesn't lick women's
asses, they're an insy.
All right. So, people remember, you're
not allowed a different opinion. If you
don't lick women's asses, you're an
insult. Not really fair, is it? Everyone
should be entitled to their own opinion.
So, even though I've had sex, I've been
with women. Just cuz I don't lick
women's asses, I'm an incel. Oh, man.
What happened to [ __ ] freedom of speech?
That is literally like
that is literally
that is you not even allowed a different opinion.
Why are you forced to have these
opinions, bro? You know, I don't like
women. I think they're evil. I think
that's like I'm allowed to say that
[ __ ] I think they're evil. I hate all
of them. I'd say that's I that's just
the way I see it, bro.
I think they're all evil. I think
they're all scum of the earth and I
think they're all [ __ ]
You know, you're allowed your own opinion
and I generally feel like they're all
like that. I've met more women than
probably anyone on YouTube and I don't
think I'd be lying and saying that.
They're all [ __ ] They're all
[ __ ] They're all evil. I hate them. I generally do. So
I do I do generally feel that way.
They're all [ __ ] They're all
[ __ ] They keep people single.
They're they're the reason why these
people are incelss. Them they're the
reason why the there's virgins and
incelss and ret. They are the cause of
it. Now, I know my opinion is very
unpopular and probably no one is ever
going to agree with me, even though
probably a lot of people know it's right
deep down, but they are the cause of it
being [ __ ] The [ __ ] they do, [ __ ]
hating, bro. That's why I don't bother
with them anymore.
They're [ __ ] They're all the same.
They're all [ __ ] you know. And I was
mature about it, you know, for a very
long time, you know. I gave them the
benefit of the doubt and they're all
just the same.
They're the ones that ruin people's
confidence. They're the ones that get
people down. No one else. And yes, I am
blaming them as a whole. You know,
I am blaming them as a whole.
They're evil. They're [ __ ]
But yeah, stuck up time wasters. They
[ __ ] with people on purpose.
Well, I don't do that anymore.
I don't do that anymore, do I? And what
they do via text and they're just
[ __ ] That's why I don't um bother
with them anymore. All stuck up [ __ ]
I generally hate them, bro. I couldn't
even tell you what I would do if I saw
that USA Izzy. I can't even tell you
what I would do to her,
bro. Like, Greasy. I'm not even joking.
I would knock the absolute [ __ ] out of
her, bro. I'm not even joking.
It's not nice. It's not nice, bro.
Yeah, absolutely nothing. Well, if she
comes here again with her friend, you'll
see exactly what I'll do to her. I'll
knock the [ __ ] out of her.
So, yeah, I do hate them. I I think
they're, you know, these people like
Ario, man, and [ __ ] I think they're the
bl I I think they're to blame for it all.
They're all the same.
They're all the same [ __ ] but no
one ever mentions that on Reddit, do they?
I mean, I shouldn't even I shouldn't
even really be getting into these
debates anymore cuz that's a waste of time.
I if USA comes back here, I would smash
her face and 100%. I would smash her
face and I don't give a [ __ ] if she's a
woman. I would smash her face and and
her friends facing and I would do it in
front of any man. I would do it in front
Like I said a couple of months ago, I
was saying, "Let me come next Thursday
and slap you up in front of your
boyfriend." And I do in front of your
boyfriend as well
because I would slap her up in front of
her [ __ ] boyfriend, bro. I don't give a [ __ ] didn't reply.
So, I mean, yeah, I would do it 100%.
They're [ __ ] They're [ __ ] I
think a lot of people should start
talking about it instead of pretending
it's not a thing. Like when I was in
Birmingham and I was texting them and
their [ __ ] behavior and their [ __ ]
and I hating me. I [ __ ] can't stand him, bro.
You know what I mean? Yeah.
Um, I can do, but I think you forgot
when I told you I'm never showing money again.
Did you seem to forget? I literally told
you I'm never ever showing money ever again.
And how much did you show me,
bro? I told you I'm never ever showing
you money ever again. Doesn't matter
what you show.
Why is that? Because I don't need to
show you money. Why do you want me to
show you money?
Every time I played a money game before,
you've all ran away. Why? Why do I need
to show you money? You think I'm skin?
Oh, that's nice. If you think I'm a
skin, that's good, bro. That's not going
to change my life. I know I'm not. I
know I've got more than enough money to
do what I want to do. So, if you think
I'm a skin, that's on you, bro. Good for
you. I don't What have I got from
showing you people money in the past?
What have I got from showing you money
in the past?
What have I got from showing you people
money in the past? [ __ ] all. What have I
got from trying to meet all of you
people? [ __ ] all, bro. I'm not wasting
my time getting into it with you. You
can show what you want when you want.
I'm not interested. So, so yeah,
I mean in most incelss are virgins
greasy. So why would I be an incel and
not a misogynist?
But yeah, I would slap that [ __ ] USA
up, bro. 100%.
I don't care about hitting women. Do I
give a [ __ ] about hitting women? They
ruin people's lives.
Women ruin people's lives, bro. Who
gives a [ __ ] about hitting them? They're
not exactly supposed to defend themselves,
right? Yeah. They can't defend
themselves. They're not exactly supposed
to. Who said they were supposed to
defend themselves, lad?
Oh, I called the police. Good. Nice
excuse, bro. Nice excuse. Yeah, good one.
Good one. Well, Joe, I can tow you under
the same um actually I can tow you under
the same brush because when I showed you
money all them times you showed me
nothing. So that proves that you are skinned.
So what was you all skinned for? What 18
months? Was you all skinned for 18 Huh?
I mean you pretty much do grieves. I
mean most incels are virgins.
Most incelss are virgins.
It doesn't matter. Yeah, it's just my
experience. I hate them. I'm not saying
it's everyone's experience. I'm saying
it's my experiences and I hate them. Simple.
But I I feel like sometimes going out,
getting some of them, and just using
them for their body, like just keep
approaching until I can [ __ ] with one of
them and get the last laugh. But I don't
have the time to do that, bro.
I generally hate them. Like I don't
think you understand. I hate them.
[ __ ] hate them a lot. You know, so yeah,
you know what I'm saying? But I don't
have the time to keep doing that, bro.
I'll just use one for their body and
just [ __ ] him off. To be honest, I used
to do that to be honest with them. I
have done it a few times. The one in
Nottingham [ __ ] them off, went to the
toilet, never come back. It's my It's my
turn to be a [ __ ] now. You know, it's my
turn to be a [ __ ] to these women.
They're [ __ ] evil, bro.
You should see what some of them do via text,
acting [ __ ] all their life.
Don't know. Don't care. Bye-bye. So, yeah.
See you later.
So that's where we're at. You know,
I don't understand how people can't hate
them. They are generally evil, Grezy.
And it's not like I've not gave people the chance
to prove me wrong.
I gave people the chance to prove me
wrong, Grezy. You know, but they're all the same.
They all do the same stuff. They say the same [ __ ]
You've never had problem with women? Of
course you haven't, bro. Of course you
haven't. None of you people seem to have
problems with women. Just everyone that
I see, everyone that I meet, all of you
people don't have no problems with women.
I [ __ ] can't stand them. Yo, I don't
think I'm contradicting myself, bro.
Like, you know, I don't go out anymore.
I don't go out anymore because of them.
They're just evil scum and they got off
on hurting people and [ __ ] That's why I
don't bother with them anymore.
giving their numbers, wasting people's
times, being all toxic, [ __ ] being
the [ __ ] that they are, you know,
and certain things that you you can't
even explain. Certain things that they do.
Do you know what I'm saying?
Like giving people's numbers, wasting
their time. They're just [ __ ] I'm
surprised people don't say anything
about it. Must be scared of the truth. But knows madness.
Like the numbers I got from Birmingham
Griezer. Like what the [ __ ]
it's like they get off on hurting people
and wasting people's times. This is what
I This is what I've sort of gathered from them.
They're not normal. They're all the
same. I'm yet to be proven wrong.
Otherwise, I would say I've been proven
wrong if I had.
Does it matter what everyone says?
I've already got a new channel, bro. I'm
going to go back onto that channel no
one knows about
cuz it's just getting [ __ ] weird.
and they're clearly never ever going to stop.
I don't know how people can like women.
They're [ __ ] evil.
I don't know how people can like them.
They're just evil and they make people
depressed. I don't know how anyone can like them.
You know, even talking about it winds me
up. I can't even lie. I mean,
did you see that rice thing? Um, Greavvesy,
That was [ __ ] funny, is it?
See, they all think they're safe staying
on this YouTube, but none of these
people are safe. [ __ ]
See, I would have ran at that angry mob.
I would have I would have said something
at least to that angry mob.
Can't believe he actually got evicted.
[ __ ] hell, bro. I never had a problem with Rice.
was always all right with me. Yeah.
And you know what I hate about women as
well, Grezy? How they seem to want to
try and give people advice, but they can
get sex whenever they want. They can get
dates whenever they want.
I think they're evil. I hate them.
I think everyone's entitled to their own
opinion, you know, like
I generally generally do. I feel like
you think there's people that's met more
women in the world than me. Nah,
I personally can't imagine it. As
delusional as that sounds, I know that
sounds mad, but I generally don't think anyone's met
more women than I have.
How could they, bro? How many people I
used to approach?
There's not one good one I found. So, it
doesn't really matter what people say
it, does it? I guess
they used to be It used to be worse when
I was an actual virgin.
It used to be worse. So, how can they
give people advice, Greavesy,
when they're the ones that can get a
relationship or get sex whenever they want?
I wish it wasn't like that, you know,
Greavves. I don't think I would ever
moan. You know that. Um
I generally think I would never moan if
they if they like
had it right just as bad as we did.
Um then I'd be like, "Okay, fair enough."
I just don't like how they get to be
evil and they can get whatever they want
when they want.
Um, and we have to suffer.
You know what I mean?
I'm just like a big baby, aren't I?
I'm just like a big spoiled brat in it.
I'm just like a spoiled brat, aren't I, lad?
Yeah. 100, bro.
I buy a spoiled rat. Yeah.
[ __ ] funny, is it?
Oh, women not the same.
How are they not the same? They say the
same stuff. They've got the same
mannerisms. They do the same stuff. How
are they not the same?
How are these women not the same?
They're all [ __ ]
They're all [ __ ] [ __ ] you know. Whoa. Franklin,
do you think all women are [ __ ] I
think they are. I think they keep men
single. They keep them alone. And they
can get anyone that they want.
I hate it. I hate how they'd ever have
to go through hard times. Doesn't that
annoy you? Like the dating game, Grezy?
Like how it's so rigged against men?
How it's so rigged against men and they
have it on easy mode? Does it not Does
that not annoy you? It [ __ ] annoys me.
Yeah, I know about that Charlie, bro. I
know about him.
You know what I mean, bro? Like, does
that not annoy you? That that bit of the
dating game, Grezy, how they can get
what they want when they want and other men suffer?
I don't know, man. Maybe I've got an unpopular opinion.
I think they're the root of all evil. I
don't think money is. I think women are.
the way they take the piss, they troll
people, and it's not even in a funny way
either, the way they do it, you know,
wasting people's time leading people on.
I could tell you everything in the past
what these [ __ ] have done.
Well, you know, you should be proud of
me, though, Greavvesy. People should be
proud of me. I've gave up. I finally
gave up in the end. finally
saw what they actually are like and I
actually lost hope.
Yeah. Oh, bro, I told you straight. If I
ever see USA, I'm smashing her face in.
Like, hypothetically, I would smash her
face in in front of any man. Um,
I just wish they never had like life on
not not like that. Obviously, they're
always going to have it a bit easier
because I mean, they're not going to
approach people, but I wish like there
was no simps, there was no dating apps.
Um, I wish they struggled as much as
like these normal men do. Then then I'd
say, "Okay, it's fair, you know.
I mean, it depends what they Yeah. Like
that USA is I would smash her face and
if I saw her, she wouldn't even need to
hit me, bro. She could be walking the
other way. I'd smash her face and
yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] You're not
supposed to defend yourself.
But um it's like when I went to
Birmingham and I got them numbers, I was
just led on Grezy.
Just led on and took the piss out of.
But people don't think women are evil.
No, they are evil. Every single one of them.
And the reason I'm not going to go out
and approach to just use them for their
body, which is what I could do, cuz I'm
not sad like them. I'm not a low life
like these women, you know?
And if somebody tells me they've got a
boyfriend one more time, I will throttle
them. Like, I'm not even joking. If I
hear that one more time, I will throttle them.
Well, I could just keep approaching
people just use one of them for their body
because I would just approach every
single day and I would I would get them
for their body, one of them. And then I
would just mock them and take the piss
out of them.
That's what I used to I used to when I
used to meet these women greavves, I
used to treat these [ __ ]
How I was treating the past.
Yeah, I'll treat them how I was treating
the past. Does that make sense?
Bro, nobody cares,
bro. Listen, I'm going to I'm not even
going to explain the rules to you again.
You know, I know how you have to prove
yourself still to this day, though. You
can call me skin. I know I'm not skin.
You can try and call me skin. I know I'm not skin,
but I mean, yeah, like I was about I
could approach women every day and get
one and use them for their body and then
just mock them and be a [ __ ] to them,
you know? But I'm not a so like them, bro.
I'm not a so like one of these [ __ ]
cuz that's what I generally would do. I
wouldn't even I don't even think I would
even give up if I done it again. I would
keep doing it and doing it until one
eventually said yes and I would mock
them and ruin their life like all of
these other [ __ ] have done,
you know. So
why I used to walk out on people on
dates and [ __ ] [ __ ] them. But I hate them,
you know. [ __ ] hate them [ __ ] Evil bastards. [ __ ] [ __ ]
That's why I don't bother with them no more.
That's why I don't Well, okay.
If you're not skin, why did it take you
18 months to show money?
Why did it take all of you 18 months to
show money? Was you all skinned for 18 months?
Answer me that. Was every single one of
of you here skinned for 18 months?
You know what did somebody wrote to me
on Reddit? One of the mods like PJ
you've been a loser himself for like a
decade. This isn't new. Do you know
what's so funny? Yeah. Let me use this
analogy. So you know this moderate Yeah. on like
on Reddit that calls me an incel. You
know what's probably the maddest thing
about this? I've probably been doing
this for years.
And how many women do you think I've
been with in these years? And how many
women do you think he's been with in these years? So,
like I said, they defend women even
though they don't get women. It's mad. I
hate them cuz I generally [ __ ] hate
them. They've wasted my [ __ ] time. Oh, [ __ ]
They [ __ ] with people on purpose as
well. Do none of these things happen,
Joe? Am I lying? Am I lying or no?
Nah, I'm not lying, man.
Just like when I went to Birmingham,
time wasters, piss takers.
And you don't know how better you
actually feel when you give up.
You just don't realize how nice it is to
just give up. You know,
I hate them.
[ __ ] it. I really hate them, bro. I
would never do something like Antman
done, Joe, cuz I I wouldn't go to prison for them.
I wouldn't go to prison for these these
scum scum women. Scum of the earth, you
know what I mean? I wouldn't do time for them.
Unless it was USA, then I would give her
a little slap.
Slap across her face.
[ __ ] mad. I hate it, bro. Really do.
Does anyone else hate them?
[ __ ] evil bastards.
They're [ __ ] evil [ __ ] in they
women. Yeah, but he wasn't wrong with
the women cuz like I said, I thought
women didn't like him cuz he was ugly
and he was this and he was that. But
then I got the same [ __ ] and I'm normal.
He's right about everything he says
about women though.
They are scum of the earth. They really are scum.
You know what? I might try and meet a
woman in this [ __ ] over. Give some of
them [ __ ] some back. I know I've
ditched a few over like
time and stuff, but I feel like really
like maybe just degrading one
just like degrading one. I mean, I have
[ __ ] a few over in my time, but I kind
of really want to get the last laugh on them, you know?
I really really want to get a last laugh
on some of them, bro.
I never talked someone's daughter. What the [ __ ]
I wish that [ __ ] got [ __ ] pregnant
in America, bro. So then she could have
been carrying baby pee and then she
would be [ __ ]
Something like that. Like we need to
find a woman to [ __ ] over. Should we
start trying to [ __ ] women over, Joe?
Like I'll approach one, they're going to
say they've got a boyfriend, but I I'll
hold it and I'll eventually find someone
and [ __ ] them over. Do you think I
should do it?
And I'm going to have to deal with the
I've got a boyfriend [ __ ] because
I'm going to have to keep getting that
until I meet one of them and then just
[ __ ] one over royally. Like, what do you think?
Yeah, be nice, bro.
Yeah, you shouldn't take out on kids.
You should take out on women. [ __ ] women
over, but not kids.
Kids are innocent. Women aren't. Women are evil.
I don't know why people defend them.
Women are scum of the earth. But kids
are innocent, you know.
Kids are innocent, bro. You know, but
women, they're not innocent. They're [ __ ] [ __ ]
I want them to really struggle with the dating game.
I want them to be left with no one. You
know, I see so many good guys out there
still virgins. You know, people can't
get anyone and you get these evil women
being able to meet people.
I just can't stand it, bro. I wish I
just I just hate them.
Sharp on it. But yeah,
like I said, I'm glad I broke the cycle, you know.
I'm glad I broke the cycle, Joe. You
should be proud of me, man.
I guess I always thought it would have been different
cuz, you know, Virgin Boy always used to
say to me, "Women aren't all the same. I
don't know all women." Yeah. I used to
be what, 17?
16, 17, I think. And the [ __ ] used to
say, "Oh, you don't know all women." But
I've met loads of women and they are
generally all the same. So I didn't know
many people back then. [ __ ] me
[ __ ] today [ __ ] put people through.
You know what I mean?
How could they ruin our life and we
can't even hit them? So yeah,
you still there Joe?
But yeah, I do think they're all evil.
They go on like they're all innocent on Reddit, Joe.
They go on like these women are all
innocent. I [ __ ] hate him, bro.
Why do people defend them like they're innocent?
They're not [ __ ] innocent. There's
nothing innocent about them. They [ __ ]
with people on purpose. They give people
their numbers and they [ __ ] with them on
purpose. No one on Reddit ever talked
about this. You know what I mean?
But do I really have time to go out
approaching every day just to [ __ ] with
something? Just to [ __ ] with someone? Not really.
[ __ ] hate women. Yeah.
>> So why do these people keep defending
women anyways? Um, Joe,
did you think the videos were [ __ ] up?
I have a boyfriend. Oh, don't it didn't
it annoy you watching it? It actually
annoyed me watching it. Even watching
that annoyed me. Like, I'd wake up in
the morning, see it, cuz it'd pop up.
[ __ ] hell, that's annoying, bro.
So, how how is it going to change?
How is it going to change?
How is it going to change, Joe?
What? One day you're going to wake up
and it's not going and it's going to change.
That's funny, bro. 300 pound and 15 out.
Well, you didn't answer any of my questions.
You didn't answer any of my questions,
bro. Where are you going?
You're at work in the morning. You're
not answering any of my questions. Why is that?
We need to find a way to [ __ ] with women, bro.
[ __ ] put £300 in a [ __ ] property. Jesus Christ. Crazy you.
Bet you wish you had more on that bet,
didn't you, Joe? That 20 pound bet that
returned £100. I bet you wish you had
more on it. That's what I always find. You know
that whenever you'd win a football bet,
you wish you had more in it.
What do you think, Greaves? Do you
reckon I should approach every day and
just start [ __ ] with women?
and try and use one of them for their
bodies or something.
What do you think?
You think it'll be a laugh?
I think it would be a laugh to hear.
Don't mind I can give up with like I
could die tomorrow greasy and I can say
that I've been to more places than you.
See I know I could die and I wouldn't
regret anything cuz I've been where I've
wanted to go. I've traveled. I've done
what I've wanted to do. I generally
wouldn't care if I died. But I bet you
you would care if you died. Greasy.
You would care if you [ __ ] died.
How we wouldn't give a [ __ ] if I died, bro.
Don't know about you. Yeah.
I really want to mess with some women. Grezy,
what do you think? I really want to just
[ __ ] with some women.
Just mess with them. [ __ ] with their heads.
You know what I mean?
I really really want to [ __ ] with some of them.
What do you think, Grezy?
What do you think?
You know, I've been to prison before,
Grezy. I've been to prison before.
Yeah, I've been to prison.
Yeah, I have actually been to prison.
Grezy, you're so funny. Yeah. Heat.
I'm just going to start on some of my WhatsApp contacts.
I'm going to start on um
WhatsApp contacts that are women. I'm
just going to start on them.
Does that sound lost to you?
Does that sound lost to you, boss?
Sounds [ __ ] lost in here.
Why? I think it's lush.
Wonder how quickly they reply back to negativity.
I wonder how quick they reply to negativity. Okay.
Yeah. [ __ ] hate me.
I bet they reply to negativity though. Erezy,
I bet they'll reply straight away to that.
I'll soon reply to that.
Won't they grieve? I'll soon reply to
negativity. I'm sure of it.
They love negativity.
Do you want my opinion, Grezy? Uh. Uh-huh. Daryl [ __ ]
Well, maybe we can try and get one on the Hangouts.
Maybe we can try and get one on the Hangouts.
We could try. I could try.
She said, "Oh, I've told you I'm seeing
someone which you seem to respect, so
please don't message me anymore."
Bro, listen. I'm saying all of you.
I hate all of you, bro. You're all the [ __ ] same.
I'm just going to start on all of these
[ __ ] bro, on my on my phone.
And you know what they're going to do
now, Greavvesy? You know, you know what
they're going to do right now? They're
going to they're going to reverse the psychology.
That's what they're going to do on here.
They're going to, you know, they're
going to reverse the psychology. Now,
you do realize that.
So, what I mean
So what they'll do is they'll probably
reply back saying, "Oh, this is why they
meet you or this is why this and this is
why that." So they'll they'll reverse
the psychology. This is this is
something that they all do. Yet none of
them are the same apparently.
You know, but they're not all the same,
Greasy. But they just do all the same
stuff. Reversing that psychology is one
of them. Replying to negativity is
another one of them. But they're not all the same.
Isn't that mad that they're not all the
same, but they seem to do all the same stuff?
Doesn't that make sense? Does that seem
weird to you, Grezy,
that they all do the same stuff,
but not all the same?
It's mad, ain't it? Yeah,
but they're not the same.
Yeah, they're not they're not all the same.
It's mad how they're forced enough to
reply back to negativity. Hey,
is it mad how they
I I had two of them, three of them say
they were on holiday. We
It's mad, isn't it? They all do the same
stuff and say the same stuff,
but they're not all the same.
Well, they still reply back to
negativity, don't they?
Makes you wonder, doesn't it?
Makes me wonder.
any kind of negativity they reply to.
But they're not all the same.
Say the same stuff, do the same stuff,
act the same way,
but they're not all the same.
Strange, eh? Strange women, eh?
So why are women all the same anyways?
Bradley since Grezy's not talking.
Three of them said they were on holiday.
They even have the same lies, the same
mannerisms, the same everything.
But women are not all the same.
They're such [ __ ] aren't they?
Such [ __ ] such [ __ ]
Yeah. See, they all played the victim.
See, look. They're doing the same thing again.
the same stuff.
Grievy, I'm trying to be in the middle
here. Yeah. Is that they say that women
aren't all the same. They all do the
same stuff. They all have the same
excuses. They all play the victim. They
all do all the same stuff.
But apparently they're not all the same.
Really? But apparently they're not all
the same. They do the same stuff. They
act the same way. They have the same
excuses. They all say the same excuses
and act like a victim. But they're not
all the same.
But they're not all the same. Really,
bro? Am I missing something? Or
See, look. Here we go. And they're all
reversing the psychology.
They all reply back to negativity.
Look, replying away. Replying away. It's
the same you don't get uh these replies
when you're normal and nice, isn't it, Grezy?
But when you're negative, you seem to
get a load of them. Yep.
Bro, I feel like really getting one over
on these [ __ ]
I really feel like getting one over on
these [ __ ] bro. I swear to [ __ ] God
I do, lad. Yeah.
Oh, here we go. Another one that's gone
on holiday. They all say exactly the
same stuff. They all do the same stuff,
but apparently they're not all the same.
Another one that's gone on holiday. I've
never known so many people to go on
holiday in my life all at once. Isn't
that a funny thing, Grezy?
They all reply back to negativity. Wow.
At 28, you 27, you still kind of have a
different experience. What a life, eh?
They truly truly are all the [ __ ] same.
Yeah, they're on holiday, aren't they?
Yeah, of course they are. Of course they
are, mate. Of course they are. Yeah.
I feel like we need to do something to
give us the last laugh.
You know what I'm saying? Like really
really just [ __ ] have one over on them.
I just get one and just come all over
their face and just [ __ ] him off, bro.
You know what I mean?
What do you think, Grezy? Yeah.
Yeah. She's saying she saw my voice
though and then she thought, "Oh, I'm
not going to bother." You weren't going
to bother to begin with. Why do they
always play the victim and try to
reverse the psychology?
Why do they do this? Why do they always
do this, Greasy? If they're not the
same, why do they do the same [ __ ] Why
do they act the same and say the same [ __ ]
I swear to God, bro, some of these
people, they make me really want to hit them.
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. Yeah,
I [ __ ] I really do generally hate
them. Grezy, do you think I should go
out and just start [ __ ] with people?
Do you think I should really go out and
start [ __ ] with people, bro?
But I have to run it by you first. Is
that okay with you, boss?
just go out and approach a 100 people
day and just [ __ ] with them, bro. Anyone
that I can just just be a [ __ ] to them.
See what's like the shoe being on the
other foot. Huh?
You know, is that okay with you, [ __ ]
So, did Reese get a evicted on the same
website you can watch Spongebob Reevesy?
Oh, there I'm getting so many messages
from people when when negativity is involved.
Whoa, I got three messages. Why are they
always somewhere to be seen when there's negativity?
They're always somewhere to be seen when
there's negativity involved. Have you
noticed that, Grezy?
Makes you wonder.
Somebody before I was waiting for a
month and they replied, as soon as I
said something negative, they're there.
They're all the [ __ ] same.
I'm just going to start being a [ __ ]
now. That's what I'm going to be. I'm
just going to stop being the biggest
[ __ ] you'll ever meet. You know,
one second. Let me message these [ __ ]
back. One sec.
got more uh got more replies. Greavves,
it's mad. They all reply to uh negativity.
They they're there to be seen when when
uh when there's negative messages. Yeah,
they all respond to negativity, don't
they? Agree with me, [ __ ] [ __ ]
You know what? I'm going to end up
[ __ ] with these [ __ ]
I [ __ ] hate them. You really think we
see that they're not [ __ ] [ __ ]
I think they're [ __ ] [ __ ]
It's just the same [ __ ] They all reply
to [ __ ] negativity.
Nah, I think they're all the same me. I
might just go I might go out and start
[ __ ] with him, bro. I'm not even
joking. I might just start like
approaching and just try to use one and
[ __ ] them over.
Maybe even rob one. You remember when I
robbed that Somalian?
Yeah, I robbed that [ __ ] Yeah.
It's mad how they all reply back to
negativity but ignore positivity.
I might do a video on this.
Yeah, I might You like my little videos,
don't you, Grezy?
It's all the same thing. It's all
exactly the same thing. Grievesy, the
conversations that I've been having here
like from them years till now, it's been
exactly the same thing.
But apparently they're not all the
[ __ ] same. So why do they do all the
[ __ ] same thing then if they're not
the [ __ ] same.
And also when you message me a woman and
then a guy like gets involved and [ __ ]