Yo,
I don't expect anyone to be a [ __ ] weight, but
yeah, I'm getting these [ __ ] mood
swings again, bro. I swear that I can't
[ __ ] sleep. I'm going [ __ ] mad.
Like getting these jumps and [ __ ] bro.
I swear to God, bro. Like someone with [ __ ] Tourette's.
These [ __ ] are [ __ ] pissing me off.
Oh, that never got a tick, did it, Zippy?
>> Yeah, bro. I swear if I knew where one
of these women lives, I'd lock it on the
[ __ ] door, bro. I [ __ ] hate it,
bro. I swear to God.
[ __ ] madness. I know it's going to be
awake. I [ __ ] watch one.
Oh my god, bro. [ __ ] hell.
They're [ __ ] all the [ __ ] same,
bro. You know, I was speaking to my
friend about this, but to be fair, yeah,
he's still in like the whole like where
he thinks I like, bro, you should know
more than anyone how this is. And he's
like, oh yeah, one day. And bear in
mind, I've been out with him a couple of
times and he seems to think it's going
to change. He seems to, how the [ __ ] is
it going to [ __ ] change? You you know
as well as I do, right? It's never going
to change in this country with these
women, these [ __ ] You know, I was
having exactly the same conversation as
I've had before with a lot of with a lot
of people. It will never change.
Do you know that?
You know, it will never change with
these [ __ ] women. It's been going on for years.
They're [ __ ] absolute [ __ ] lad.
I hate him, bro. There was one American,
she was pissing me off, bro. I swear to
God I was just speaking to a [ __ ] on
WhatsApp. I swear I really want to hurt
one of them, bro. I'm not even joking.
Like I generally generally just want to
like really hurt them, bro. I'm not even
joking. They're [ __ ] annoying me now,
bro. I swear.
They [ __ ] annoy me. I [ __ ] hate
the [ __ ] You know what I mean?
They all reply back to and they all have
the same attitude, the same [ __ ]
behavior as the last one. They're all
the [ __ ] same. How can anyone sit
there and say they're not all the
[ __ ] same, bro? I told that American
one to go get You know what?
Obviously, I know that she can't report
me cuz she's in America, so I thought [ __ ] it. Same, bro.
I told her about herself.
I told her to go get, you know, Yeah.
via SMS. [ __ ] pissing me off, you
little [ __ ] Don't you think it's so mad
that they're fast enough to reply back to negativity
straight away with the same [ __ ]
attitude? Same [ __ ] [ __ ]
You know, they're all the [ __ ] same.
They literally are, bro. I swear down
these [ __ ] are all the same.
I swear down.
And look, she send trolling me, sending
me monkeys and [ __ ] I [ __ ] hate them, bro.
You know, I don't say half the [ __ ] on
here that I actually say to them because
of, you know, these grasses and [ __ ]
but trust me, it's bad, bro.
They're [ __ ] That's what they are.
[ __ ] I know what they're like. You
I'm so glad
[ __ ] And my friend, I can't believe
he thinks it's going to change.
I was like, "Bro, you've been out with
me. We've been out together."
Um, you know, and he thinks what one day
it's going to change. How? Like, let's
let's be real. How How is it going to
change, bro? Come on. It will never
change. It would always be the same old
sad song in this country. That's why I'm leaving.
That's exactly why I'm leaving.
You know, I even had somebody start
asking me for money and [ __ ] I'm
definitely leaving, bro. Bye, douches.
[ __ ] [ __ ] this ball game of [ __ ] shoulders soldiers.
You know what I mean? [ __ ] this ball
game of soldiers, mate. You mad? this
same old [ __ ] I've been [ __ ] putting
up with with these [ __ ]
You know, and I know what I'm like with
my temper, bro.
You know, I'm so glad I gave up. I said
to my friend as well, "Good luck to you,
Rod. Good luck to you.
Good luck to you, mate. It's your
problem now, not mine.
Even though I'm still here, I've given
up with it. So, good luck to you, mate.
You're going to need it.
Hope you had more luck than I did in
four years. Yep. And they've done that
before as well, like the trolling,
asking for money. Isn't it mad they do
all the same [ __ ] but they're not all
the same? All reply to negativity, all
be a [ __ ] all pretend they got
boyfriends. Isn't it mad how people that
aren't all the same do exactly the same
thing? Huh? Who would have thought, you know?
But they're not all the same, yet they
do all similar things.
Mad, isn't it?
I swear down, bro. They were pissing me
off, mate. Bro, I swear down, bro. If I
knew where one of these live, I would
have filled them in today, bro. I'm not even joking.
I swear down. I'm not joking, bro. They
are [ __ ] I swear to God, bro. There's
this one in America that was pissing me
off just now. Like, you should try it,
bro. I don't know how many numbers you
got or what contacts. If you write
negative stuff to them, they all reply.
I swear, bro, I'm going to end up
[ __ ] killing one of these people one
day, bro. I I swear down it ain't even
nice to say, bro. I swear it ain't even
nice. But I will, bro. I told a [ __ ] to
go get [ __ ] to and go suck her dad's dick. Yeah.
You know what I mean?
Yeah. I'm going to go message her now
saying that. I'm going to say that.
Yeah, I'm just I just text her out. I
said, "Pe, you didn't have the same
energy when you weren't behind the Yeah,
you Yeah. All you can do is troll behind the keyboard
trying to be a dickhead." But we all
know face to face, but I'll smack you up
in front of any man, bro. You know what
I mean? Who the [ __ ] do they think they are, bro?
You know what I mean? Yeah, I will, bro.
She lives in America, so it's not like
they can report me. They're in America anyways.
Yeah. Yeah. [ __ ] replying to
negativity, you [ __ ] stupid. Talk
about 911 and everything, bro. No, it's
annoying, bro. It is annoying. And then
you got ones trying to ask you for money
and [ __ ] Like, it's like when you have
once you've met one mic, you've met them
all. They all do exactly the same thing.
They say exactly the same thing. And
then you got some [ __ ] virgin, some
little skint virgin in a shitty council
bed suit with a fat ugly disabled
girlfriend trying to tell me how the
[ __ ] it is. He's going to [ __ ] sit there
in his [ __ ] virgin [ __ ] hole with no
bed in it and try and [ __ ] tell me
with his ugly rat face. Him and his no
teeth ugly virgin rat face is going to
[ __ ] try and tell me, "Bro, [ __ ] out
of here, bro. Are you mad?" Nah,
I told her I was going to get [ __ ] by
daddy and [ __ ] bro. Yeah, [ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
No, like it's one of them, bro. Like,
you know, you just get in a mood for it,
bro. You know what I mean? I swear if I
knew where one of these live, I'd be
there now, bro. I'd be in that taxi right now.
I hate that me, bro. I [ __ ] hate them.
I'm surprised you never battered that
Natalie G, bro. I'm surprised you never
batted the [ __ ] out of her.
I'm really really really [ __ ] surprised, bro.
I'm surprised you didn't you didn't bro.
You I'm surprised you didn't do that
coming in. I'm I'm I'm actually being
dead. You serious, bro?
She said, "Okay, old man." Huh? That's
not what your mom said. That's what I'm
going to say. Hey, that's not what your
mom said. Yeah,
I said that's not what your mom said
last night. Bro, you should have slapped
the [ __ ] out of her, bro. You know, if I
if if if I Bro, if I ever see that USA
Izzy and I ever see her friend, I'll
slap the [ __ ] out of them in front of
every man. You're right. You're in your
rights to defend yourself, bro. Don't you know?
>> I would have snuck that up.
>> You should have. [ __ ] it in it. I know
what you mean though. It's like hard
when you're with the person and that
you know what I mean, bro. But but
[ __ ] they're they're [ __ ]
They're actual [ __ ] mate. Bro,
they are actual [ __ ] bro.
So yeah, man. I hate them me, man. I
[ __ ] hate them me, bro. Are you with
anyone at the minute or [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. I know. She never ever had um a
personality to be fair.
This [ __ ] [ __ ] is sick in the head, bro. You know. Uh Damn.
I find bro.
But yeah, I do hate them, bro. I
actually hate women, bro. I don't know
about you. I'm not telling you to go
through the avenue that I'm going down,
but you know, [ __ ]
[ __ ] me, bro. I actually hate them, bro.
They're [ __ ] winding me up. You I
just told her to go get [ __ ] by her dad's dick. Super [ __ ] Pretty
much. Yeah, pretty much. They all do the
same stuff. They've all got the same
attitude. They all pretend they got
boyfriends, even via text. I would love
to just slap one up there, bro.
I would just love to just It's like that
American one, bro. I said like two
months ago, let me come down on
Thursday, slap you up in front of your
boyfriend. I was being serious, bro. I
was being serious, bro. I was going to
slap her up in front of her boyfriend,
bro. I'm not even joking.
Yeah, I [ __ ] with that [ __ ] for Oh,
bro, God knows how long. Yeah, they turn
you like this. They They turn you like
this. These [ __ ] turn you like this.
You don't understand. They're the ones
that turn people like this. Them
Thailand in November, lad.
Yeah, I'm I'm off Thailand in November,
bro. I can't do this no more.
Yeah, I'm out of it, lad. You're more
than welcome to come with me. I'm not
doing this no more. This ain't no life.
This ain't no life for anyone, bro.
Like, I'm not living out there, but I'll
be visiting. So, if you want to come,
bro, you're more than welcome. I'm not
doing this [ __ ] no more, bro. You know,
[ __ ] this. And I already know what the
difference is going to be, bro. [ __ ]
this, bro. not staying in this [ __ ]
annoying country for the rest of my [ __ ] life.
I don't know, bro. It's mad, is it?
Well, it doesn't Yeah, but like I said
to you, bro, it's a waste of time
getting into it with these [ __ ]
Just don't argue with them, bro. Yes,
but I'm only on here cuz I'm not going
out anymore. I don't think I'll be be
going out in this country anymore, bro.
Like, it's that I'm that fed up with it,
bro. Like, I'm that fed up with it.
Like, there's been times before where
I've not gone out for like six, seven
weeks. Obviously, I've left the house
and that, but like not drinking. But
normally, it's like winter. You get so
fed up with the [ __ ] you just stop going out. Yep.
Yep. They don't have money, bro. None of
these people have money.
I mean, I'm basically on it cuz I've
give up with life, bro. I ain't skin at
all. I can do what I want when I want.
I'm not a millionaire, but
You know what I'm saying? I can do what
I want when I want. I just basically
just give up a life, bro. It's just It's
just [ __ ] hanging, bro.
It's actually hanging, lad.
Yeah, I called that prime out when I was
in Birmingham. He didn't want none of it, bro.
When I was in Birmingham, I actually
called that prime out.
Yeah, I'll never try again in this
country. I don't think
I can't see it happening, bro. I swear
that I can't. They're [ __ ]
bro. I felt sorry for him, bro. Like, to
be honest with you, I won a football
bet. It was only 200 pound and I felt
sorry for him and I hadn't been out for
like two weeks and I hadn't been
birthing him in ages so I thought it was
just something to do. I had nothing to
lose by doing it sort of thing
and I felt sorry for him bro um but yeah
so I just sort of had nothing to lose
sort of thing.
One second, bro. One sec.
Hold on. One sec, bro.
One second. I'm trying to [ __ ] do
something. It can.
Uh, one second. Do you want the link? Monty.
Okay. Monty wants the link. Okay.
Monty wants the link, bro.
Who the [ __ ] is Money Mike? Money Mike,
I'm back in Birmingham, you fit [ __ ] Yeah,
>> if you want to meet me with it, Money Mike.
>> Oh no, my phone's [ __ ] cuz I can't hear you.
>> Yeah, Money Mike back in Birmingham. So
if you want to meet me now, Money Mike,
you really can. Yeah. Calling me all
this and all that. But in real life,
you're a [ __ ] [ __ ] >> Yeah. >> Me?
>> No. Money Mike,
man. I'm in Birmingham now. I live in
Birmingham. Money Mike.
>> Yeah. Go on. I meet you and Timmy.
Wherever the [ __ ] you want in Money Mike,
>> just you two. Just stop it. Yeah.
[ __ ] hell, bro. Just pack it in both
of you, man.
>> No, man. Watch Money M's face get washed
up. Come on, M. What do you want to meet, lad?
Sick of this little clown running his
mouth. The same as Jim. [ __ ] Timmy Eldridge.
So, where do you want to meet money,
Mike? Cuz I'm getting sick of this sort
of run around with you on [ __ ] Timmy.
Why the [ __ ] I'm going to tell you
where the [ __ ] I am. I'm in Birmingham
and that's all of what you need to know.
So, where the [ __ ] do you want to meet,
Money, Mike? I can literally meet you
right now. Rightly second.
Name a plate. It could be anywhere near
your location. If you want me to come
near your location, I'm more than
welcome to come near your location.
Money m second. Instead of running your
mouth on YouTube, come and meet me. >> Yeah.
>> Oh, what was it? A couple of days ago,
money Mike, a couple of days ago, you
was up on someone's panel giving it all
this and that because I left Birmingham.
But when I was in Birmingham, you were
like, "Oh, I ain't got no problems with
with multi. I ain't got no problems with
him." Well, I've got a problem with you,
Money Mike. Anyways, one threatening
women. You know what I'm about, Money
Mike. That's only what you can do.
Threaten women. I'm meeting now, Money
Mike. Just get this over and done with
literally. You think I'm some soft ass
in this community? Let's meet now.
You want it, Money Mike?
Where do you want to meet me then, Money
Mike? I come now. I ain't got nothing to
lose. So where where do you want to meet me?
I can like literally get you now. Right
near your location.
I can go near your mommy's house if you
want me to. Money Mike and just get that
that Natalie where your mommy live. I
can go up near your mommy's address if
you want me to money Mike. I will make
you come out. Won't it?
Where does Where does money Mike live?
His mom live.
Where does money Mike's mom live?
Don't worry, I'll mute my mic.
Yeah, money. Mike, I can meet you in that location.
Natalie, just give it me.
Please move you. I can meet you in that
that location if you want. Normally, M
clown in this community. Sorry, PK
[ __ ] up your channel.
You two got beef in it. It's
>> a [ __ ] idiot. It's another [ __ ]
[ __ ] just like [ __ ] Timmy Eldridge.
What? What kind of team?
>> You never You've never Monty, you've
never had a problem with um
>> Well, give me one second.
>> You've never had a problem with that
tiger. A tiger, have you? Nah.
>> No, not really. No. So, where are you
now? Money. Give me your location where
you are then. I'll come to you now. No
[ __ ] I swear down there on my kids
lives. Come now
you [ __ ] ugly little dwarf little
Yeah, money Mark. I won't forget Tim. I
want you. I want you. Money m you Tim's
relevant to me. It's a lot plastic.
You're not. You're not. But where are
you now when Mike if you think you about it?
Where are you now?
Where does he hang about? He's lo What's
the best pub he goes to now?
So you won't even give me the location
where he is. So
that's how much of a bushes they have in
this community PJ. They won't give you
the location where to go. The oldest guy
come now. Where do you want me to go
about the streets? Yeah.
>> You show us what they like the [ __ ]
bags. PJ, these are [ __ ] bags in this community.
>> What is he saying to me in PJ? >> Um,
get an Uber. Uh, Chamsy Wood.
>> Chamsy Wood. What's up? No.
>> Why Mike? Have you ever been Have you
ever been to Kitty Minister?
>> It's not worth it.
>> I'm going to smash his face in, man. I'm
going to grab him by the throat and pick him up.
>> I am. I am. I'm going to smash him up,
man. Where is Where's that wood? Where is it?
Literally, I'm going to strangle him. 101 >> 108
PJ I'm going to jump off here weasel in
this community. You're welcome threaten
to cut it off for women. You weasel man
weasel. See you later PJ. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Oh wow. Yeah, bro.
[ __ ] sick of these [ __ ]
What a [ __ ] life, eh?
Have you ever been to Kitty Minister?
Yeah, I met some guy from there, bro. He's [ __ ]
You ever been there before?
He talks a bit like this from the black
country. Like that. My mom said that's
how they sound a bit like that.
>> They sound a bit like this.
That's how they sound a bit. They sound
a bit like this.
That's how they sound, is it? Like,
>> yo, PJ, unblock this account. Yeah, cuz
I can't write on this account on my D egg account
cuz you got me blocked and block from
writing. Money max. No one's running
away, you little clown.
Who's going to run away from you? You
[ __ ] ugly man. A man with a little small dick.
You can't even satisfy your woman. Come
on, man. You and Timmy belong together.
Two gay couple.
Old dick money. Mike.
Yeah. Unblock me account.
One second, bro. What account?
Morning Mike. I reach every side on on
Natalie. I I reach every [ __ ] inch of
her. You even go all the way up to the belly button.
All the way up there to the belly button.
Where do you go to the [ __ ] fanny
flaps? That's it. That's only where your
dick can reach up to is the fanny flap. Reach that >> weeny big man.
>> There you go.
My teeny weeny small man. We knew we knew. Yeah. sex and
>> he's still fue. So he's not >> watch
I mean you had a nons