Woke up late today to be
fair. Probably from [ __ ] trying to find
my trying to find my My power coming.
Almost shot my [ __ ] phone there.
n Yeah. N said that you're two out of
10. Lord J, how does that make you
feel? How does that make you feel, Lord
J? She gave you two out of 10. And I
don't It's Tuesday. Football today. I
don't like doing the football on
Tuesdays. I like doing it on
Saturday. Let me see who's playing actually.
Well, to be fair, it's quite a few teams [Music] playing.
Um, yeah, I think
that is way too
hard. Is way too hard.
Yeah, that both teams to score no draw
is way too hard,
bro. There's a lot of teams
playing. Almost got it
though. What's that? Yeah. Oh,
dogs. I fell asleep, mate. I fell [ __ ]
sleep to be honest with you, bro. Yeah,
I forget to go on the Celtic
forms. I'm trying to find my dad
Samuel. Yeah, I could do a football bet
today, but then that means dipping into
my favorite if it loses, and I'm not
dipping into that for as long as possible, bro.
But it's going to have to be
Saturday. I can put 20 quid on a double
both team score, but they're too hard to come in,
bro. And I can do a double both teams to
score, but then it means lump like 80
quid on it. And I don't want to put 80 football
pointless. I'm saying it's [ __ ] pointless, lad.
No, I'm not paying him for a month, lad.
I'm not paying him for a month. That was
me done for the month, bro. Sorry,
man. What's the day tomorrow the 5th?
It's not too
long. A bit long. Well, not too
long. Nah. No, I'm good. Thanks. Yeah,
you'll get over three grand. No, thank you.
log woke up. I was looking for Tam last
night and I couldn't find him. The one
from Glasgow, my dada. I was looking for
my daddy, but I couldn't find him. I
already found my
mama. But I can't find my daddy anywhere. Strange.
I was thinking of doing a football bet today,
but all those people back.
Yeah, you people trying to encourage me to play
Frankie. No, I'm good, bro. Them days
are done, man.
If I was to gamble again, it would be on
the multiply roulette and it's not going
to be for a while.
Bro, I'm trying to find a Celtic fan.
Tamjang. Well, I'm not going anywhere
now until my passport comes. Says
they've not even received it. Well, send
it to the right place. Maybe just takes
a day or so. You have to go through a
lot of passports. for
listen. You need a new gambling video,
mate. Well, go and do one
yourself. That's the wrong one, man. You
got to do one yourself. I need a
gambling video as well.
Nah, it's a waste of time and money bend
this gambling [ __ ] mate.
It's okay if you bump or whatever, but nah,
bro. I'm not gambling, bro. I'm good. I
lost 350 this month, but only 50 pound
of it was my own money. 300 was was a
loan that I have to pay back, bro.
Yeah, I have had an email back, but I
I'm waiting for them to receive it to
say that they've actually received the passport.
Yeah, I've had an email. Yeah, and I can
track it, but it still says they haven't
received it when I sent it.
No. Yeah, you got fire rather you than
me, mate. [ __ ]
that. [ __ ] that [ __ ] It's actually very
easy to stop gambling if you just want
to stop doing
it. It is actually very
easy. Really is.
Yeah, you can be £310 up, bro. I don't
care. I've got money saved. I'm good. I
don't need to win any more money. I'm all right,
guys. Sorry. I'm all right, bro. Um
Yeah. I wonder how long it's going to
take them for them to say they've
received it, Joe. Maybe the end of
tomorrow cuz I've definitely sent it.
Obviously, I've got a receipt.
Um I would do a football. Both teams
just got no dry. I used I almost got it
last week, but that's too hard to get.
It's too hard to get,
bro. I feel like if you got a B of
football, you're best off just doing a
both teams to
score. But again, that means lumping on it, right?
So that's the risk. You
see, what do you think?
Um, no. That's the risk though, isn't
it? That's the
risk. That's the risk. Even,
bro. You got some terrible plans here,
lad. What happen?
What is the actual easiest thing to win
on? Do you know why I don't like that
online anymore, Ben? Is because it shows
up as euros and it puts me off. I don't like
euros. Yeah, it puts it comes up as
euros and I don't like it coming up as euros.
Yeah, that might be coming up as you as
see. That's why I don't
Yeah. Yeah, I'm just chilling today. But
like I said, I'm having a quiet month. Hello. Very
boring. One sec.
You gamble every day, Ben. It's not good for you,
bro. You gamble every day,
Ben. Every day you gamble, Ben. It's not nice, man.
No, no, no, no, no, no,
no. Yeah, there's no point doing a
football bet, is
there? What do you think, Ben? 20 pound
football. No 20 football
bat. What do you think?
Nah, we'll do one on
Saturday. Yeah, we'll do one on
Yeah, Saturday. We get money every
Saturday as well,
sir. I'll do one on Saturday, Ben. I get
money every Saturday,
sir. I do one
day. Is that okay with you,
boss? to be
forever. But yeah, you was right
yesterday about my race. That's what I
think it is as well. It's funny how you
picked up on that as well because it
doesn't make any sense cuz how how does
a white person do better than me when
he's the same looks range as me?
the same look range like whatever it is six
seven that's what I'm trying to say it doesn't make
sense it's true it doesn't make sense
it speak to my friend about this
yesterday before you even mentioned it makes no
sense so you get a lot of racist people
in London back.
Yeah, they're actually racist. There's
nothing wrong with the way that you look and other
people. It's like my friend. Yeah. He's
Indian. Yeah. Some guy I go out with.
Yeah. And he's like 5'4. Now we know the
chances of him ever getting anything in this country
is pretty slim to them. Indian
5'4. I don't think it's happening in
this country, Ben. But you know, like
you said, they're never going to admit
it. That's what I'm saying.
And then the other guy I know, he's from
um Indonesia. You got no chance,
bro. These are like the least desired
races because they're racist. You
understand? So it's like they're not
It's not going to happen, bro. It's not
lad. Cuz I have people say to me, "Oh,
um, you know, you look,
uh, German and you look this," but you
obviously don't because if you look
white, you would have more success if you looked
white. And that's the fact anyways. But
anyways, I'm going now. Anyways,
so good stuff. So, see you later, bro.
Yeah, see you, man.