Jesus Christ. [ __ ]
Crazy though, is it?
I've never known so many people reply to negativity.
It's like that Twitter thing. Hey. Yeah,
it's like that whole Twitter thing all
over again. Really,
how they reply so fast to negativity.
Those how [ __ ] up they are. Why
somebody would reply to negativity to
ignore positive messages, but they like positivity apparently.
So the simp say.
So the simp say. Yeah, I am leaving,
bro. But I just wanted to rant about
this one more time. Am I just like
ranting about this [ __ ] cuz it blows my
mind, bro. How like people can reply to
negativity uh ignore negative uh
response ignore positivity and and reply
to negativity straight away. >> Yeah.
It's crazy, isn't it? No, it's not hard
to leave this place at all.
It's not hard to leave this place at all.
I've come off of it for weeks. Nothing
hard about it. It's just full of repeating people. No,
I mean I've I've come off of it for
weeks, but you probably forgot that cuz
you got selected memories. So
So yeah. Well, you you have got
selective memory on here. So you
probably forgot about that just like you
forgot about the times of showing money.
Just like you forgot about the times
I've showing women. You probably forgot
about that because you do have selective
memory. Just like you forgot about when
I went to Mark's area two times and he
didn't come out. Just the usual. I mean,
you have got selected memory on there,
so you probably did. You probably did
forget to be honest.
You only remembers what you only
remember what suits yourself.
It's so mad how many people reply when
you write something negative.
Yeah. Well, you can't even take a day
off of YouTube, so you should be talking
about anyone going live. You know,
you know what I'm saying? You people
can't even take a [ __ ] minute off
YouTube, so I wouldn't be talking about
anyone else, lad. Oh, [ __ ] So, yeah.
Oh, same old [ __ ] [ __ ] hell. Oh, X's now.
the X thing again. I've not heard that
one in a while. Another same
conversation I've had. Isn't it mad?
Right. I'm not Isn't it mad how they all
say exactly the same stuff, but they
don't know each other? They do all the
same stuff. They act exactly the same
way. They don't know each other, but
they're they're not all the same. Isn't
that a madness for people that aren't
all the same? Let me tell you this.
Well, they've got very similar traits to
people that aren't all the same. Let me
tell you that. For people that aren't
all the same, they've got very, very
similar traits from people that don't
know each other. Tell you that for
nothing. They all reply to negativity.
They all have the same [ __ ]
behavior. They all say the same [ __ ] in
the same way. that X thing I've heard a
million times before. Been asked for
money million times before. All of these
things. I think I've had these
conversations with a million other
people. Is that mad for people that
aren't all the same? Makes you wonder, doesn't it?
[ __ ] makes you wonder, doesn't it? Yeah. Yep.
Is this the same conversation? Yep. You
are still on YouTube. You're on YouTube
right now. Tell yourself that you're on
YouTube right now. That's how you type
that uh [ __ ] That's how you type that
message. I didn't go to bed until 6:00
in the morning last night.
Yeah. All of these people that was
ignoring me, I was sending them
dickpicks and all sorts like people from abroad. Uh
that's not my credit score. We're not
talking about that. So yeah. Um, people
from like abroad and [ __ ] cuz a lot of
them are tourists. I just started
sending them pictures on my dick.
[ __ ] if you want to [ __ ] troll me,
I'll [ __ ] troll you, you [ __ ]
You know what?
I just sending them like piss on my dick
and [ __ ] [ __ ] pissing me off.
[ __ ] think you're going to sit and
[ __ ] troll me, you [ __ ] silly little [ __ ] Yeah,
you're gone. Bye-bye. I just told you
we're not talking about this. So,
bye-bye now. I told you we're not
talking about something. We're not
Don't know. Don't care.
Simple. [ __ ] 6 o'clock in the
morning. How did I go to bed until 6:00
in the [ __ ] morning?
Yeah. Well, that was then. That's not now.
Used to not now
cuz of these [ __ ] women pissing me
the [ __ ] off. I feel like I'm having the
same conversation with with different
people for people that aren't the same.
I'm sick of it. I'm [ __ ] sick of it.
You know? I can't be I can't wait until
November. I really really [ __ ] can't.
You know what I'm saying? I'm literally
literally literally I can't wait.
Like you don't understand. I am I can't
wait to get out of here. You know what
I'm saying? I've never been so excited
in my life now. You know what I'm
saying? Like all of this [ __ ] You know,
[ __ ] responding to negativity grievy
yesterday again. Oh, I'm having the same
conversation with different people. But
people that aren't all the same, they
don't know each other. They do a lot of
the same stuff. That's all I'm saying,
bro. They do a lot of the same stuff.
For people that aren't um
for people that aren't the same, they do
a lot of the same [ __ ] Don't you think
that Don't you think that's quite
strange? They do a lot of the same [ __ ]
So yeah, I was sending them like
pictures of my dick and [ __ ] like people
from a different country. They were
[ __ ] annoying me. So I was just
sending them pictures of my dick, the
numbers I got. Yeah. Troll them. Troll
them [ __ ] Give these [ __ ] some back
over what they've gave you over the
[ __ ] years. [ __ ] You know what I'm
saying? Give them some [ __ ] Give them something back.
Give them some [ __ ] behavior back. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] Only
replying that to negativity. [ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
And yeah, I I started it. Did I? Why? By
by saying one thing. Okay, I'll finish it then.
Okay, I'll finish it then. I did start
it and I'll finish it then and I won't
be the one [ __ ] running away. All the
same [ __ ] behavior I've dealt with
with it in the past, Gres, I've dealt
with this [ __ ] [ __ ] in the past.
It's just the same old [ __ ] and I ain't
dealing with it no more. These aren't
new. These aren't new approaches. These
are old numbers, bro.
Like like I say old like past couple
weeks and [ __ ] when I last went out again. Simple.
They all reply back to negativity.
Whilst enough to reply back to
negativity, but the normal nice
messages, oh, they they get ignored.
They get lost in transit.
They get lost in the Afghanistani
transit. But oh, the the the the the
negative messages, Jesus Christ, they
reply to them straight away.
Makes you wonder on it how [ __ ] up
they actually are in the headlessness.
Yeah, I can't wait now, bro. I can't
wait to get out of here. Gy can't wait
now. I can't wait, bro. But I'd rather
be sat there like say I was just saving
now and I had nothing. I'd rather be sat
there bored out of my head for 6 months
knowing I was going to leave this this
place. I'd rather sit there bored,
depressed out of my head for 6 months
and knowing I could s and leave than
stay here. You know what I'm saying?
That's how bad it is.
Like I' i'd rather do that. I'd rather
take that off than have to deal with any
of this [ __ ] ever again. I shouldn't be
dealing with this [ __ ] at my age, bro.
I'm [ __ ] I'm 2 [ __ ] seven. I'm not [ __ ] 17,
you You know, I'm not [ __ ] 17 months.
You understand, bro? I shouldn't be
dealing with this [ __ ] at my age. You know,
>> with these [ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
>> I messaged that dam yesterday at
Greavves. I said, "Oh, fatty." Boom
boom. Where'd you run off to fatty?
You [ __ ] fat [ __ ] That's what I said
to him. Fatty boom boom.
Cuz they're sick in the head. And
they're all the same. Cuz they're sick
in the head. [ __ ] that are all the same.
They say all the same stuff about their
ex asking for money. They do exactly the
same [ __ ] Why? You never see me out
anymore cuz they're all the same.
There's no point in me speaking to
people that are all the same. Wasting my
time. Might as well get a [ __ ]
parrot. You might as well get a [ __ ]
parrot. Do you know what I might do? I
might get parrot. A parrot and call it
Pete the Parrot.
You know what? That's what I might
actually do. I might get a parrot. Yeah,
I might get a parrot. You know, like a
pet parrot. Peter the parrot. [ __ ]
might as well.
If you if you're going to get someone
that says all the same things, you might
as well get a parrot.
You know, I'll name it Peter the parrot
and just look at that every Friday,
Saturday, and it's what they are. You
know what I'm saying? Yeah.
They [ __ ] they [ __ ] annoy me. They
do, bro. They [ __ ] annoy me.
They annoy me. I can't wait to leave,
Reeves. I really really can't wait to
leave now. Seriously,
talking about their ex asking for money,
trying to be they they just are all the
same, man. They're all the same.
And [ __ ] Virgin Boy a [ __ ]
community post last night [ __ ]
defending them. I said, I can't even be
bothered to respond to this simp
anymore. You're never going to get
through to these simps. So, there's no
there's not even no [ __ ] point even
there's not even no point me even responding anymore
cuz what he's doing he's like he was
projecting and he's clearly just trying
to get me to waste my time doing a video
on him. I said it's not going to work.
When he says, "Oh, you need to learn to
talk to women and stuff." Like all he
wrote was about himself. So, I just
didn't bother replying to it. He's just
he's just self pagan and you're never
going to get it. You're never going to
get through to simps. So just waste of
time. Once a s always a simp.
It's like when you're aw the wolf you're
always going to be a dwarf. You
understand Greavesy. If you're a dwarf,
you're always going to be a dwarf. It
doesn't matter what you do. You're a dwarf.
You was born with the wolfism. So if
you're born with the simple is, you're
always going to be a s. It don't matter
how you explain to them, they're always
going to defend women. So, so yeah,
I send dick pictures to like people that
was abroad just in case they could call
the police and obviously they can't when
they're in another country. So, that's a
lovely picture to wake up to, is it? An
ugly dick just like their ugly behavior.
just like their [ __ ] stinky ugly [ __ ] behavior.
Now, I said to one, if you are going to
write paragraphs, I had to SMS one G we
uh if you're going to write paragraphs,
at least let people um at least don't
block people and let people actually
defend themselves before you block. [ __ ] cowards.
And they all think they're smart and
they're not smart.
They're not smart. They're just
[ __ ] So that that I hope they
they're having breakfast and they open
that message. A nasty dick with a bush
on it. [ __ ] be sick. [ __ ] dirty
[ __ ] Dirty shitty bastards.
They know that
[ __ ] [ __ ] See, I'm smart. I'm not
like [ __ ] man. I know I'm going to
[ __ ] leave. So I'm not going to do
anything to jeopardize my my freedom.
You know what I mean?
You think if I didn't know where one of
these [ __ ] lived yesterday, I would
have went on I would have would have
went on their [ __ ] door. you [ __ ]
mad [ __ ] winding me up. I was
speaking to this [ __ ] [ __ ] in
California. They were [ __ ] winding me
up, pissing me the [ __ ] off. Who the
[ __ ] do they think they are, bro? Told
him from a [ __ ] cross the sea. I
said, "You're a little [ __ ] You weren't
saying anything face to face, just like
all of you [ __ ] You don't say anything
face to face. You're just at the [ __ ]
when you're [ __ ] back home and you're
stupid little [ __ ] emojis.
What are you sending me stupid emojis
for, you stupid [ __ ]
What you sending me stupid [ __ ] for? You [ __ ] Huh? [ __ ] idiot.
You still I'm just going to send a
picture of me. I'm just going to send a
video of me having a wank. That's what
I'm going to do.
Boom. A lovely video of me having a lovely wank.
Yeah. And I'm going to send it around
tea time so when they open it they can
be sick. Yeah. [ __ ] just like their
dirty sickening behavior. [ __ ] [ __ ]
They reply so fast to negativity
so fasty. like they're on that message
as soon as you write
something negative. It's it's insane
that you wouldn't even believe it. You
wouldn't believe it.
They are they are generally all the
same. They say all the same stuff. They
do all the same stuff. They have exactly
the same mannerisms. Am I lying about
that? They generally are all the same
scum. I get nothing out of saying this,
bro. I don't get paid to say this. I
wouldn't say it if I didn't believe it.
And I would be out if I didn't believe
if I didn't believe it. You know what I'm saying?
So, yeah. And I figured that I would
already had enough numbers on my phone. So,
there's no uh is they
Yeah, I had one call me a [ __ ] old man.
I had one call me an old man. Yeah. I
said I had one yesterday call me a
[ __ ] old man. There was this [ __ ] in California, right?
Yeah. Uh and she never ever replied to
any of my messages even though I gave
the [ __ ] recommendation. So she was one
of the one that I wrote the negative
thing to and she replied straight away.
I don't know how old she was. I never
ever got her age. I don't know how old
she was. She was obviously of age. I
don't I don't know. Maybe 19. Maybe 18
19. And as soon as I wrote that negative message,
um she she replied
replied straight away. Um then replied
again, then blocked me. Then I gave her
some um over SMS and um yeah, she was
sending me like [ __ ] monkey emojis
and just like roses and [ __ ] like
trying to be a top [ __ ] tier [ __ ]
troll. I said, "Well, I hope you get
[ __ ] by your daddy." That's what I
said to her. Yeah.
I said I said that um I said uh yeah I
hope you get you know what and and I
hope you get it by your daddy. Obviously
they can't do anything because they're
in America. And I sent some of them dick
pictures as well. Nicola ones that were
uh they don't live here. So obviously
they can't run to the boys in blue cuz
they don't live here. So yeah.
Yeah, man. Let them open that in the
morning. The lovely dick in the morning. [ __ ] [ __ ]
If I knew where one of them lived
yesterday, I would have went on their
door. Then I messaged that dam saying,
"Oi, fatty." Oi, fatty boom boom, you
talk a big game, fatty boom boom. Yeah.
Yeah. [ __ ] fatty boom boom.
That's what I said to him. [ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
I [ __ ] Nicolola. I really really hate
them, bro. I don't think you understand.
I really, really hate them. I can't wait
until November, bro. I'm more determined
now than ever. You know, I was thinking
about this until 6:00 in the morning
yesterday, right? And I was like, you
know, you know how much patience you
actually have. I I didn't know I had
this much patience. I always thought I
was an impatient person, but I I knew
dealing with all of this [ __ ] and
still dealing with it, you have got to
have some patience. I'm surprised no one
ever gave me credit for that.
If anyone was in my shoes, Grezy, they
would have either gave up, ended up in
prison, or would have seriously hurt
someone. I'm telling you, one of them
three things would have happened. So, I
mean, like, yeah, people can sit there
and talk about [ __ ] other people,
bro. Yeah, but no one has got as much
patience as me. And I didn't even know I
had patience. I always thought I was an
impatient person, but clearly not
because I was thinking about this six
o'clock in the morning. Yeah. before I
went to sleep, I was like, "This ain't
this is never going to change it, is it?
This is this is never ever going to
change it, is it?" I'm having the same
conversation, you know, with people like
when I was in like Scotland. I'm having
the same conversation with people, bro.
You know, they're not winning, bro.
They're not [ __ ] winning.
These little [ __ ] aren't winning.
These little [ __ ] aren't [ __ ] winning, bro.
That's the thing.
But I I would never try here again, bro.
I can safely say that
cuz think of Ant-Man. Yeah. He didn't
even try 10% of what I tried before he
left. And he's more patient than me.
He's actually a laid-back person.
I'm [ __ ] I'm not laidback.
Look, is it matter? I don't like losing,
right? I do not like losing.
I don't like [ __ ] losing
and all of this [ __ ]
I don't like losing and all of this
[ __ ] But you seem to have had a lot
of patience surprising me.
Well, I have a lot of patience for
someone surprising me. I had I've only
just started losing my patience [ __ ]
four years later, you know.
No, I just said, "Oh, I think I just
said I hate women."
I just said, "I hate women."
And they all reply back.
No, they weren't voice notes. Yeah.
My mom was trying to say, "Oh, you don't
like it when women say no to you." No,
no, no, no, no, no, no. They're just all [ __ ]
I really really hate them. Like I don't
think you understand. I really really
hate them, bro.
They're all the same cuz think about it
like this, Nicolo. They do a lot of the
same [ __ ] as one another, yet they don't
know each other in it. Don't they do a
lot of the same stuff?
They do exactly. You never ever meet
someone. Isn't it funny how you never
ever meet someone
that would say, "Okay, well, I don't
like uh I'm not interested." And here's
some feedback and this and that. And for
example, when they say no, and if they
say, "Yeah, you never meet any of these people."
Three pound overdraft.
If only you knew how much money I had,
bro. If only you knew. Three pound
overdraft. If only you knew how much
money I had, simp boy. So, you never
ever meet anyone that's different. You
never ever meet anyone that's that
doesn't do the same as each other. But
they're not all the same, says Virgin
Boy. Makes you wonder, don't it?
Like, you never even meet anyone that
says no and say, "Oh, you could have
done this better or you could have done
that better." They all do exactly the
same stuff. Have you Have you noticed that?
You know, it's never they're never going
to change ever.
They're never ever going to change, bro.
Never. And they say that men have got no
personality. Yeah. I have all of these
friends. Okay, bro. You know.
Yeah. But that's but that's social
media, bro. Yeah. They got no social
skills. It's like Virgin Boy. He says
that I need to learn to speak to them
when I've spoke to all of these women.
You should know that you've you've tried
getting with my sloppy seconds enough [ __ ] times.
All of what he writes is just clearly
projection for reaction. There's
literally no even there's no point even
like doing videos anymore because they
just they just project and they just
want you to give them attention. Oh [ __ ]
You can't even get a combo out of them though.
But they blame the man.
So yeah, bro. like,
"Oh yeah, you can get in big trouble for
sending your dick." I was like, "No, you
can't because I live in a complete
different country than them." I knew
exactly what I was doing, bro. You think
I do that to someone here? No. [ __ ]
that, bro. You know, they'd run to the
boys in [ __ ] blue for someone that
lives in a different country. Look, look
what Look at all that [ __ ] I done to
USA. Is he? And the police never ever
ever bothered me. They say, "Oh, we
can't do anything because he lives in a different um
he lives in a different country, but
we're just going to watch out for him."
That's what they said. Like they they
can't do anything if you're in a
different country. So if somebody lives
in a different country, knock yourself out, bro.
Knock your [ __ ] self the [ __ ] out.
You think I'm stupid, bro? I know what
I'm doing. You know what I mean?
picture somebody that lives in England.
Are you [ __ ] mad or somebody that's
from England? No, cuz we know what it
is. It's the boys in blue. Yeah. I was
saying to some of them, "Oh, I hate
women and I mean that's not enough to
get someone arrested,
you know. Very calculated. I know what
these cubs do, bro."
Yep. It's all about blaming a man.
Some of them lived in Italy, one lived
in America. When I said to that [ __ ] in
America, go get you know what. She
obviously lives in California. So
obviously the police aren't going to do anything
cuz the whole court case would be [ __ ]
up. So I know exactly what I'm doing,
bro. I know exactly what I'm doing. When
there's people that live here, I'm very
calculated and I know exactly what I'm
doing, you know?
But if someone lives in America, like
the police are never going to do
anything. Knock yourself out literally.
Like if I if I if I if that USA is for
example lived in England, I probably
would be in prison now.
I generally would probably be in court.
I'm not even joking. But obviously cuz I
don't live in America, which is a good
way. It was a good thing in a way to be
honest. Like you can do what you want
and they're not going to do anything cuz
you don't live in a you don't live in
live in their country.
Yeah. It's a good thing, is it? You can
give them a bit back and they they can't
go to the boys in blue. You understand?
I've been dealing with the same [ __ ] for
4 years, the same women, the same [ __ ]
But somehow one day it's going to change apparently.
But I'm not dealing with it no more. I'm leaving.
Oh, I was speaking to my uh my friend
yesterday, Nicolo. You don't know this
guy. Uh he's a bit like the Indonesian
guy, right? He's a
he's a but he's Italian and he actually
does approaches. He's a bit older than
me. And he says, "Oh, one day you're
going to you're going to find someone."
I was like, "Huh?" I was like, "You of
all people think it's going to change.
You of all people think one day you're
just it's you're you've been out with me
[ __ ] like five times. You should
know. But to be honest with you, what it
is with a lot of these people is they
probably have hope in their mind.
Obviously, he's a he's older than me,
but he's probably not tried as much as
me. So, you know, I used to get this
where like you think, "Oh, yeah, it is
going to change." You don't know. You
know, you never know what the future
holds cuz your mind plays tricks on you.
But you'll know when you're ready
because my my mind's like, "Nah, get out
of there. Leave. It's never going to
change, you know.
So you you you you'll know when you're
ready, bro." You know, it will happen eventually.
Oh, another one who's in love with her
ex. Oh, Jesus Christ.
Ah, do you know what? This is exactly
why you don't you shouldn't [ __ ] with
Muslim women. They just use their
religion as an excuse. This is boring. I
can't wait. November, come on. Come
quicker. I can't wait to get out of here.
I can't [ __ ] wait to get out of this
Oh my god, bro.
I literally can't wait to get out of
here. Yeah, I sent a dick picture to
someone in Brazil, someone in America.
But yeah, knock yourself out if they
don't live here.
I can't wait to leave. I think I'm ready, bro.
I'm ready. I really am, bro.
No, she's never blocked me.
I can't wait to leave.
Can't believe Ant-Man left before me. Jesus Christ.
I just can't wait. You know, I used to
be a lot more confident, you know, when
I was younger. Yeah. You know, I used to
be a lot more uh
You know, I used to be a lot more
confident than I am now.
No, she didn't.
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Oh, that one did. Yeah.
You speaking about the You know, I used
to be a lot more confident, but then I
sort of was like, "Oh, it doesn't work."
And I sort of lost confidence. I used to
be a lot more confident, you know, like
a lot more. But
um then I sort of just gave up cuz I
realized people don't care about confidence. So So
what women do you hate the the most?
I hate American women.
So, I want to send this French one a
picture of my dick, but uh
I can't do that cuz she lives in England
and I ain't getting in trouble. So, I
can't do that one
cuz if they didn't live in England, then
I'll do what I want. Like, you know, Yeah.
Yeah. That's what Well, yeah. Yeah. You
know. Yeah. Basically that Nicola
I said I welcome Yeah. I showed them
Peter the penis
I showed them Peter the penis Nikolai
cuz I already know the result. Yeah. I
feel like I don't know about you. Yeah.
From 24 23 to 27 I feel like I'm 100
years old. I generally feel like I'm 100
years [ __ ] old.
I generally feel like I'm a hundred
years old. I walked like two miles the
other day. I was like, "Fucking hell,
bro. All my feet feel [ __ ] weird and
shit." I was like, "Bro, I feel old as
[ __ ] I feel like a 100red years old, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Good luck for you. You're going to
need it." Just like I said to myal
Italian friend, I said, "Good luck to
you." Good luck to you. You're going to need it.
Good luck to you. That's what I say to
everyone now. Good luck to you. You're
going to need it in this country.
Good luck. You're going to need it. I
think that's the right thing to say to
these people, is it? I would love for
people to be able to beat this and and
it work for them. I'd love to hear
success stories because I couldn't do it,
you know. I mean, Grey, I couldn't do it. So,
do you remember Peter the Strawberry?
They don't even give you a chance.
They don't even give you a chance. I
mean, you can't even get a date. I mean,
there's there's literally no point in
even trying in this country anymore. You
can't even get a [ __ ] date,
Grezy. So, I mean, there's no point. I'm
just going to get a parrot. Peter the
parrot. I'm going to get a parrot and
call it Peter the parrot.
I don't know what women you hate the
most, but I hate American women. Defer,
I hate them, mate. I hate them.
You know, I've met a few of them [ __ ]
I [ __ ] hate them. You remember that
one of the O'Neals when I told her about
I told her about herself in front of her
[ __ ] father and they done [ __ ] nothing.
You know what I'm saying? I told her
about herself in front of her [ __ ]
father, bro. Imagine that. her sister
and her father. Yeah,
I was going to discipline the little [ __ ] Yeah, [ __ ] [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying, bro? Yeah, I
was going to discipline the the little [ __ ]
It used to be fun. You know what? I kind
of missed that O'Neals. I know I'm never
going to be able to get in there again,
but I do miss it.
I have tried. Yeah, it doesn't matter if
you if you give up or not. They're not interested.
So, it doesn't matter if you
even if I have tried that before, bro.
I've I've approached four 5,000 people.
I've tried everything you're saying.
Carry on with a boyfriend [ __ ] It's
just an excuse that they're always going
to use. Even if they give you their
number, it's pointless.
I mean, you can keep going, but it's not
going to work cuz I've done it before.
I was speaking to this American guy
yesterday. He's like, "Oh, maybe
Australians are different." I was like,
"Oh, boy. Maybe Australians are different."
Yeah. I used to say, "I'm your boyfriend."
boyfriend. Let's get a new one." I said,
"I've got a boyfriend as well, but they
don't need to know. It's just me and
you." What doesn't know don't hurt them?
And they used to actually believe it.
They said, "Do you?" And they actually
being serious. That's how dumb they are.
They'd be like, "Oh, do you?" I said,
"I've got a boyfriend as well."
Yeah, bro. I told you. I thought
they're just not interested in this country.
So, I've just wasted all of my time
getting all of them numbers for
absolutely no reason.
For absolutely no reason. What I was
thinking of doing, Nicolo, is uh just
approaching women every day, like a 100
women a day, and just ruin one of their lives.
Give them some back of what they gave
you over the years. But then I realized
I don't really have the time. I can't be
bothered. And the I've got a boyfriend
won't bother me because I'll just keep
doing it until I find someone that says,
"Yeah, I'll do it for a whole month if I
have to." and I just [ __ ] wreck their
life emotionally, you know, just a random person. So,
but I don't really have the time or
energy to do that anymore. Yeah,
they turn people into a nasty person,
don't they? They really turn people
nasty, don't they?
Because they're [ __ ] bro. That's why.
Nah, I'm not trying it for a week, bro.
I'm ready to leave.
So, yeah, I just sent it to people that
basically don't live here.
So it will never change. Never.
Yeah. This Brazilian woman was trying to
troll me. So I sent her a picture of my
dick. I wonder what they what what they
feel like in that situation when they
know they can't run to the old bill.
They must be [ __ ] in it. Like say
you're owning them over text cuz
obviously in England they can run to the
old bill but obviously when they're not
in this country they can't run to the
boys in blue.
They must be really [ __ ] in it. You've
hit the jackpot with that one. You know
it doesn't matter what country they live
in because they can't run to the boys in
blue cuz they don't live here. I mean
they can call the police their country
but they got to tell them they don't
care cuz you don't live here. So
cuz that's the first thing they do when
they lose. is they run to the boys in
blue. But obviously if they can't run to
the boys in blue,
then they're [ __ ]
Cuz that's the first thing that they do.
They run to the boys in blue.
They love the boys in blue, mate.
[ __ ] hell. They love them boys in blue.
This will never ever change. Never
No, I never. I only said it once.
No, I've only said it like once or twice.
Antman said it more times than me. I
only said it twice.
Yeah, like that simp American that said,
"Oh, don't talk to her." I said, "I'll
talk to the [ __ ] I want." He soon shut
his [ __ ] mouth, didn't he? The
[ __ ] yank [ __ ] I [ __ ] hate
Americans. Oh, I hate them. I do, bro.
You know, I used to love that country
when I was when I was younger, you know.
Um, but just meeting so many people from
there just put me off it. and the way it
is and the way it's run by Trump. I hate
I don't think you can even pay me to live there.
That's how bad it is. I I hate America.
I hate Americans.
I generally generally generally do. I hate them.
Yeah. And I said, "I'll talk to the [ __ ]
I want." And he was like, "Oh, get out."
He said, "Oh, you're a big man." I said,
"Yeah, I'm a big man when I'm talking to
you." And he said, "Get out of my face."
I told them to [ __ ] move me. Yeah,
trust me, them Yanks are not about
nothing. They used to get [ __ ] up
every week in that O'Neal. They had to
stop letting people in in the army because
people in the army used to come and they
used to fight with the Americans
obviously the war and [ __ ] Um, so the
people from the army used to try on with
their women and then they used to fight.
It happened every week. They had to stop
letting people in the army for like six
months. But them Americans are not about
nothing. Trust me, they're not. They're weak.
Think about it, bro. Look at that USA.
Izzy, she went to the police how many
times? And they don't even live in the same country.
Like, what the [ __ ] bro?
That just goes to show they're fast
enough to run to the boys in blue. These
[ __ ] You know what I mean?
When I was starting on that damning
yesterday as well, I said, "Oh, fatty
boom boom. You fat Homer Simpson.
You [ __ ] fat Puerto Rico looking
[ __ ] Homer Simpson [ __ ]
Yeah, I'll talk to the [ __ ] I want.
That's what I said to him. Yeah,
you're not going to come here with your
9/11 ass and try and tell people who
they can and can't talk to. You're in my
country, [ __ ] Yeah. I don't know
how many times I I had to [ __ ] try
and tell them that.
Good old O'Neal's Water Street.
Good old O'Neal's Water Street, lad. Eh,
good old O'Neal.
It was fun there.
That's why I met all the army people.
And they were actually all right. You know,
there's some guy I met for the army.
He's actually all right. Like he's got
tattoos and he is actually an all right
guy. He was with me. That was the guy
that was with me when I won the four
grand. He said, "Oh, do you want to go
for a drink?" It was a Wednesday. And I
said, "Oh, [ __ ] it. Why not?" And I
remember saying to him like at the end
of the night, do you want to come in
casino? I'm going to go casino before I
go home. And then I want that's when I
won the four grand. I bet you he wish
he'd come now, is it? I bet he wish he'd
come now, ain't it?
Yeah. That was the day like I went out
with him and we was dealing with the
same [ __ ] from them.
Yeah, we went out together and we went
for like a drink of that. So
he's actually he's actually all right,
bro. actually a cool guy.
But um yeah, we just stopped talking and
[ __ ] So yeah. Well, that's the day I
won that four grand in the casino that Wednesday.
You couldn't believe I said, "Bro, I
just won four [ __ ] grand. What the fuck?" So yeah.
So I got all of them numbers for no reason.
I got all of those numbers for no reason.
All of them numbers for no [ __ ]
reason. [ __ ] it.
Respect to the ones that didn't reply
though, regardless, you know.
So, yeah, my situation, I just need to
leave now. So, I roll on November. I
mean, I don't get as much money as I
used to, but bro, I'll make it I'll
still make it work. You know,
I can't wait. I'd rather sit I'd rather
sit in bed. I'd rather stay in depressed
for 4 months and leave. Save money and
leave than then try here.
Do you know what I mean?
Than than actually like leave than I'd
rather just sit there and save money
greasy for like four or five months
knowing that I'll be in paradise,
you know, than than
um then then try here.
Yeah. Okay. You're not going to be able
to go out as much cuz obviously you
don't get as much money now. But I'll
still make it work. Easy. Easy, bro.
You know, even £1,100 a month, I can I
could I could start from scratch. 5
months I can get out and go out there
five, six months.
It's not a problem. Yeah,
virgin boy says I don't know how to
speak to women yet he stalked all of my sloppy seconds.
USA Izzy Izzy Sig isn't mad but he's
never had problems attracting women.
Not like you didn't stalk a girl in
Canada for 3 years when she rejected
you. Yeah. You've never struggled with
women? Nah. What would why would anyone
think you would struggle with women?
What would make you think that you
struggle with women?
It's not like you only date disabled
girls and [ __ ] you know?
What do you think of the whole rice
thing? That was actually quite funny, wasn't it?
It will never change.
I think I'm going to beat the record,
Grezy, of not going out. I think I done
six or seven weeks.
I think I done six or seven weeks.
I think I'm going to beat the record.
Yeah. I always used to stop for like um
6 weeks in the winter or February and
thinking that like when I go out again
it's going to change, but it will never change.
It will never change. I was still under
the impression that it was actually
going to change. But if this football
bet wins on Saturday, I'll probably just
get an escort
and put put it towards the spending
money. I'm that done.
Why is it so far away? cuz I've had to save obviously
for the spending money. So, I just
probably just and then just put some of
the money away to be honest.
I I I can't see me trying ever again,
bro. I proved my point nous times. It
ain't changing it.
No, I can't remember that. So yeah,
I can't see it, bro.
I can't see it.
I generally generally can't see it, bro.
Cuz I've got money. I've got money. I've
got clothes. I can go out whenever I
want. and I'm just not interested in it.
I know the result.
You might as well just sit and play Franklin.
You know, you know what I mean, Grezy?
You might as well just sit down and just play Franklin,
you know? It's [ __ ] It's ridiculous, bro.
You know what I mean, bro? Like, um,
it's like that time I didn't I I only
went out once this month, you know? And
it wasn't because of money. Like you
might think it's because of money. It's
not because of money.
When I won when I lost that, you know,
when I lost that football on that
Saturday, when I went out that th prior,
it was obviously cuz I lost the but a
lot of it was like, "Oh, well, hold on.
You've already tried. You went out
Thursday. You got enough numbers. You
don't need to go out again.
You already tried. You I was dressed up
and anything. If I hadn't gone out that
month, I would have still went out. I
would have been annoyed, but I would
have still went out. But then I was
like, "Oh, well, you've already been out
once this month. You don't need to go out again."
What happens when you get older, your
feet start hurting, your legs start
hurting. I don't have as much energy as
I used to have, especially when I know I
know more than anyone how it is.
I've approached more than anyone.
So it's like
I generally think I am, bro. I think I'm
going to hit the million before I die if
I carry on. Yep.
Generally feel like Yeah, they all say
no. That's another thing I used to think
of is I can't see that happening. But yeah,
and just think about it, right?
It's been going on for four years.
Right. And I get I bet you they told you
four years ago it was going to change.
I bet you they told you four years ago
it was going to change
like they're telling you now, you know. So
it's horrible. It's horrible, bro.
You know, it's a horrible way. Just no
way to live. So,
cuz think of it, you're 20, what, 27?
You're going to be 28. You can do so
much [ __ ] in your 20s, but you're not
going to be able to do any things in
your last, but your 20s if you keep
trying in this country. This is what I'm
trying to say to you. You've already
wasted enough time. You've proven your
point more than, you know, multiple times.
There's no one for you here.
you know, that wasn't four years ago.
There's nothing for me here, you know. So, that's it.
Do you remember Nicolo? Michael
Jackson's in uh Michael Jackson's in Manchester tonight.
I'm not falling for your [ __ ] Michael Jackson.
I'm not falling in for your [ __ ] Michael Jackson.
Yeah, Michael Jackson's in Manchester tonight. Yeah.
So, do you think this football bet has
got a good chance?
So, at least I broke the cycle because
unless you break you break the cycle, you're [ __ ]
If you don't break that cycle, you're [ __ ] you know,
which is what Kira needs to do.
See, I've broke the cycle with the whole women thing.
It was a long time coming. It was hard,
but you know, I just realized it's never
ever going to change her.
So, you know, I had to learn in the end
it will never change.
>> No, I'm not even doing that now, bro.
Even if I win,
you know. Yeah, but I used to do that
even when I had the house. It's not
about money. I have money. I can go out
when I want. I have money. I've got my
own money, you know, and you know, and I
tell you why I I do that is because if I
don't feel like I'm being paid to do it,
I'm not wasting my time. That's why I'm
not It's not cuz I need the [ __ ]
money to go out. I just don't want to
waste my time if I'm not being paid for
it. That's that sounds bizarre to you,
but that's how it got, you know, even
from 8 months ago. So, if I if I don't
win, I'm not going out cuz I'm not
wasting my time.
So don't forget it used to happen all
all stage of my life. If I didn't win, I
wouldn't want to go out.
So it's not cuz I need, you know, if I
win, I'm only getting an escort. I'm not going out.
Say that I want to go out that
Indonesian guy, but I want to go out
just cuz I want to go out. I I don't
give a [ __ ] about the women and [ __ ]
Well, obviously I would approach if I'm
out, but I I just want to go and have a
drink with him.
Not cuz I want these these [ __ ] Like
cuz obviously if I want a [ __ ] I just
go by myself cuz he's no use. But you
know I just want to go for a drink with
someone maybe. But I probably won't even
do that to be honest with you. I'll
probably just get an escort and put it towards
um savings or something. I probably
won't ever try here again to be fair, bro.
No, no, no. But that's the whole point.
I'm not interested in this country
anymore. That's why I would That's why I
would go out with him
is cuz I'm not interested. They've shown
what they're about year after year after
year. I have no interest. That's one of
the reasons why I'll go out with him
now. I never before cuz I was actually
trying to pull. But now I'm not asked
cuz I know it's the same and it will
never change. So that's why I just
probably just go out with someone else I
think. But I won't even go out anyways
to be honest. hypothetically was
speaking because I wouldn't even I
wouldn't even go out and try again anyway. So,
I've tried more than anyone in the world. So,
take that L.
Take that [ __ ] L, bro.
What do you think of the whole USA
thing, Niko? Like
And no one deserves this, you know. I
don't care who you are. No one deserves
this [ __ ] you know. No one deserves the
[ __ ] that Ant-Man's been through and no
one deserves the [ __ ] that I've been
through. Near tenfold of what he's been
through. He is like minor compared to
me. No one deserves it. I don't care who
you are. No one deserves the [ __ ] that
I've been putting up with for years with them. You know,
so no one deserves it. It ain't no more, you know. Yeah. pretty much.
I don't think I can get fat.
I can gain weight, but only a certain
amount. But yeah,
I wish I could die, you know, my sleep
cuz you know a lot of the people that
die. Like what if you just passed away
and you ended up um
what if you just ended up in heaven with
them people? So you just ended up in
heaven with them people.
That'd be a good life, bro. Think of all
of the people that's died.
You know, you'd be you'd be with them.
Not this hell life that you can't change.
It's a failed society, you know.
It's a failed society, bro.
Um, so yeah,
now I just message people on Instagram.
I think that's that's as far as I go now, bro.
I just don't have the energy for it anymore. So yeah,
it's one of them it goes.
I've been [ __ ] with this woman on Reddit
um since yesterday. I made like seven
accounts to keep messaging her. I said,
"You [ __ ] coward." I said, "You're
never going to get rid of me. I'm your
baby." I said, "You're my mommy now and
I'm your baby and I'm going to keep
messaging you." I said, "You can't give
birth to me and then leave me."
That's why I said, "Yeah."
I said, "You're my mom."
You're my mama.
[ __ ] blocking coward."
No, she's not a mod. It's just someone on Reddit.
I said, "Trust me, you're not going to
get rid of me." I'm like, "Chucky. You
can't get rid of the [ __ ]
Trust me, once Peter belly sets his eyes
on you, it's it's it's over. You can't
get rid of me.
I'm like, Chucky, you can't get rid of
the [ __ ] you know." So, yeah.
I'm like, Charles Lee Ray, you can't get
rid of the [ __ ] Yeah,
let me make another Reddit account.
Yeah, well, you've stolen enough of my sayings.
So what happens when you send them Peter
Peter the strawberry
USA is she couldn't get rid of me.
I'm stuck in her life for [ __ ] forever.
So I wouldn't have [ __ ] with her
again. But because her friend blocked me
after speaking to me for 5 hours, then
yeah, these coward Americans bring on themselves. One second.
She wanted to do a post on me, but she couldn't cuz um
she didn't know my name.
Oh, Scooby. I love Scooby. Scooby's cute.
What do you think USA thinks now, Nicolo?
Like about meeting me,
you doing sitting outside by yourself, mama? Oh,
what do you think she thinks?
Oh, nope. But when you send a picture,
they they want it straight away.
Jamie Hag has just uploaded a video.
I can't believe. Do you know what? I
never ever argued with Rice. Me and Rice
was actually all right. Never argued
with the dude. So, I don't really have
anything against him. Stupid dude.
She was sending me monkey emojis. She
was just trolling me. Stupid [ __ ] I'll
come to [ __ ] California and whoop your ass.
I made that 19year-old swallow my sperm. Greasy.
Yeah, I made her swallow my sperm grooves here. Stupid [ __ ]
All different things.
USA is the [ __ ] I've got sig.
Um stuff I've done in clubs.
All different kinds of things. They're
just things that I've been just people
that I've been with in the past. Yeah.
Just different kinds of things.
Sometimes I wank off to getting like USA
is he pregnant and [ __ ] like that. All
different kind of things.
We got plenty in the rank bank.
You get a lot of that stuff. in four
years of constantly trying.
I tell you one thing you do get out of
it. You get a big wank bank. Reevesy,
we need to make these women pay. I said
to this guy on uh Instagram, he's 23.
He's a virgin. He lives in America. I
said, "These women need to pay, mate."
What they've done.
It's funny how you remember by saying
rape victims. There's a lot of them.
[ __ ] hell. I'm surprised you remember
that. That's an old one. Didn't used to
like that one.
The [ __ ] lot of them.
A lot of them. Yeah. So, I just think of
all different kinds of things.
Sometimes the one in Nottingham
Yeah, you [ __ ] take my money, I
[ __ ] take yours. Do that one, Grezy.
You want to take my money, I'll [ __ ] take yours.
See, the old house was good cuz I had
people around me. I don't have people
around me here.
Yep. You want to take my [ __ ] money?
I'll take [ __ ] yours.
Bad man's not so loser. If he loses,
he's like whatever.
I don't like losing. I'm I'm I'm
completely different than him. I don't
like losing. I don't like the I've got a
boyfriend [ __ ] He said, "Oh, you're obsessed
with the boyfriend [ __ ] you are. You
keep sending me these videos.
Yeah. I said cuz it's [ __ ] depressing.
[ __ ] that. It's [ __ ] depressing, isn't it?
Yeah, she keeps blocking.
Yeah. Yeah. I feel like I feel like
Yeah. I feel like when I've lost I feel
like I've been degraded.
I feel like I'm I've I feel like
I'm a I'm a West Ham fan and we're
playing Mir and they're laughing at us.
That's what I feel like. I feel like
losing and then being laughed at, you
know, by the crowd. It's a degrading
feeling losing. It's It feels like
you've been degraded.
Yep. That's It actually feels like you
have like I'm not even joking. It
actually feels like you've actually been
raped. It's It's horrible.
It's horrible. It's a horrible feeling, man. Degrading,
you know. That's why I stopped doing it.
Hopefully this football bet comes in.
Be good if these football bets come in. Lad,
what do you think? 90 to return 324.
What do you reckon the chances are? It's
going to win.
Be nice to get like over 300 pound pay.
That would be good. Yep.
Do you know what I don't see much about
anymore? Many pregnant people
the other guy.
But you don't really see many pregnant
people anymore, do you?
You don't really see a lot of people get
spunked up nowadays.
what I used to call it.
You don't see a lot of people. You see
some, but it's quite rare now, isn't it?
Watch out for the other guys.
Other guys. I can't believe my friend,
my Italian friend thinks it's going to change
when he's actually he's actually been
out with me and we've actually tried together.
I've actually got a picture of me and
him together. You know,
like you didn't know about him, but
yeah. And I said, "What you think it's
going to change?" You know? Yep.
[ __ ] hell. USA is is a [ __ ]
I I would have thought I'd hit the
jackpot if I see her and her friend
together in it.
Yep, they are doing it on purpose.
It's the whole part of It's the whole
point of the vendetta.
They reject you and then get rid of
other people. Yeah,
they do do it. They do do it to push it
in your face.
Just like that. USA is she'll be
pregnant in about maybe a year. Say a year maybe.
Yeah, probably a year
or something. Yeah, they do do it. They're evil.
I wish people told me this when I was
[ __ ] younger, bro.
I have to find out for myself.
They do do it, bro.
If you're black, they come to you.
Yeah. You can't get anything.
Yeah. And you can't get anything. So,
you can't get nothing. You can't even
get a relationship.
You can't get anything. Yeah.
Imagine we was a virgin, Nicolola.
Imagine how much worse it would be if we
was actually a virgin.
What would you actually do if you was a
virgin? Like say say we're a virgin now.
Just let's just say we're a virgin boy,
right? And we're a virgin now. What
would we do? What do you think the first
thing you would do is Jesus Christ?
I think escort and you'd have to go
Thailand is it?
Um, no. It's It would never be
different. It would never change.
You would actually be [ __ ] cuz you'd
get less money. Society's worse now.
You'd probably have to get an escort to
go to Thailand probably.
I don't know what you do.
There used to be some hope. You know,
you used to go on dates, used to get the
odd one night stand. Now you can't get nothing.
I think it's that Tik Tok app. More
people started using it.
That's what I But I'm sure people
something has changed. I know something's changed.
But then people's using it back then,
but I know something has changed because
why is it all of a sudden impossible to
get anything now?
Not like before.
Maybe it's got to be tiptop because
why is it all of a sudden just become impossible, you know? Yeah.
[ __ ] mad. It's got to be that Tik Tok thing
cuz I I remember you used to actually be
able to get dates. I used to go lots of
dates and I used to tell them about USA is
I wish I just stayed with that [ __ ]
Portuguese one now, you know?
There was literally nothing wrong with
her as well.
She wasn't a time waster. And I I wish I
just stayed with that [ __ ] now.
If I knew it was going to get If I knew
it was going to be like this, right,
then I would have just done it. Just
would have stay with him.
I could have had a baby by now. Yep.
Then the next year I just had more money
and less [ __ ]
Now got less money and no [ __ ] So
yeah, it gets worse every year.
It was the best year.
The USA is a year was the best year.
I almost had people throwing themselves
at me in a way when you look at it, but
I just [ __ ] up cuz I used to just tell
them about USA.
So I just [ __ ] it all up. But you
know, and it doesn't matter about the
money cuz I still had money coming in.
So it doesn't matter how much money I
had. So that was the best year and the
year after was still decentish. Now it's
just impossible. So if you look at them
two years, it has actually gotten worse. You know,
We can't get nothing now.
It's horrible. It
It's no way to live.
There ain't no way to live, mate.
So, you think the bet's got a good chance, Nikolai?
What would you say at 100%?
Charge is golf coming in.
Good luck, captain. Captain,
good luck, Captain.
That's a good return of 90. That's good odds, bro.
That is some good odds off of um 90 quid.
That's a good return, right? Yeah,
that's probably the best you're going to
get for both teams as well. Yeah, captain.
You all right, Captain? I got that from
that Jamaican guy.
Yeah, he come to the house and done the
garden for me. I cooked for him. Yeah.
So, what if I was black?
Nah, it wasn't. So, what if I was black,
Nicolo? Do you reckon that woman from
Liverpool would have the one that lives
in Liverpool would have used that as an excuse?
Do you reckon she would have used that
as an excuse?
If I was black, do you reckon she would
have used distance as an excuse if I was black?
Yeah. He said that's he said that food
smells good. And obviously I don't like
um I don't like to see people go hungry.
So I said, "Oh, I can cook you up a
burger if you want. Why not?" And yeah,
he liked it.
I said, "You're welcome, Captain.
So what if I was black? Would you use
this as an excuse?
So if I was black, USA Izzy would have
you would have blocked me if I was black.
Her friend was like, "Oh, she doesn't
hate you or anything. She just wants to
be left alone." Tough [ __ ] You don't
want to be left alone when you was using
me for my little Wonga. When you was
using me for steak and wine. Maybe I
wanted to be left alone.
Maybe I wanted to be left alone when I
we finished dinner and I and I didn't
want dessert. Maybe I wanted to be left
alone. Tough [ __ ] You don't get the
[ __ ] say around here when you want to
be left alone.
You don't have a say in the matter. I
don't know how these [ __ ]
I don't know how these [ __ ]
uh think they've got a saying when they
want to be left alone.
You ain't got a say in the matter. My
mommy told me not to listen to [ __ ]
She did block Charles.
Charles used to [ __ ] abuse her and
[ __ ] My friend was telling me
he's a he's a he's a crazy guy. Charles.
Oh, Franklin, you died.
no. She did block Charles.
Oh, yeah. No, she didn't.
Do you reckon she ever had sex with
Charles Nicolo? Probably not. Is it?
Do you reckon she ever gave Charles a little [ __ ] Yeah.
Oh, Monty said box. Nah.
I didn't know Monty wanted a box. Nah.
Do you remember, Nicolo? Your mama left you.
Yeah. Monty said he wants the box.
No, I don't I don't imagine it. But I'm asking,
do you reckon she did like have sex with
him and [ __ ]
Do you remember when B was pretending to be [ __ ]
her for like 2 months?
He played a good game, you know, but
quite sad how somebody has that much
time on their hands.
imagine it actually was real.
You can't get off of YouTube like that,
Nicolo. If that [ __ ] was actually real, you know?
Yeah. Like um
it's the um
you can't get off of YouTube like that.
You're too deep in it. You can't get off
of YouTube like that when you're too
deep in it.
Nah, it don't work, mate. Nah.
It's like that USA is uh it's like the
normal Izzy and Craig Goodston. You
remember Izzy and Craig Goodson? You
can't get off of YouTube like that. Not
when you're too deep in it like that.
Cuz if you try to get off of it, you'll
just come back on it cuz you're too deep
in it. Once you're too deep in it, you're [ __ ]
You all right, Captain?
>> How you doing, Captain?
>> I'm good. I'm good.
>> That's good, man. Any any news on Rice?
All what I can say is that only what
I've been but I think it's trying to
chuck everybody off track
is that the
supposed to be moving back to Plymouth apparently.
>> [ __ ] me.
>> I think that's to everybody up rice
living at flat now. Yeah,
>> that's where Rice is the second. He's at Cavis. >> Yeah,
>> talking about that [ __ ] anyways, but you
know, I thought I put that up obviously
because Rice mentioned about being in
the safe house out yesterday
that the police put him in.
>> I think I think I think you and Rice I
think me, you and Rice should just go
for a night out and forget about all this [ __ ]
>> I think we should be smashing Rice. He
said in helping mate what he said about my kids.
>> Yeah, but I we've argued and stuff before, Monty.
>> Oh yeah, but you're different. You're
nipp and rice. I know you. I've known
you for what? A long long long time. Or
even [ __ ] YouTube. For [ __ ] sake.
>> You know me. You know me when I was a
little You know me. You know me since I
was a kid.
>> Not a kid. Been here.
>> Yeah, but I ended up at 16 now. You know
what I mean? You know, it
>> No. No. Yeah, of course. You know what I
mean? But I've known you for a long time
where you're different and [ __ ]
amped. Do you know what I mean?
>> You know, you've known me since before I
had facial hair. >> No,
>> I didn't have facial when I was 16. I
was only little. Do you remember how
little and skinny I was?
Yeah. No, I don't. I don't even remember
back. That was Yeah. And years ago.
That was years. That was like what?
[ __ ] knows. Yeah.
>> Well, you was never you was never into
the um WWE games, was you? Like the actual games.
>> WWE is fake in it. It's not really.
>> No, the games. The games though.
>> Oh, the games.
Not really. They're not really into fighting games.
>> Oh man, them games were the best in
2009. The wrest ones.
>> No, games are the best.
Donkey Kong and [ __ ]
Mario and all that. They were the best.
>> No, Monty. No, Monty didn't groom me,
you sick bastards.
>> Is that only what you people think about
is grooming? Is that all what comes out
of your mouth and brains?
>> If anything, if anything, Monty, if
anything, Monty protected me from
groomers, isn't it, Monty?
>> [ __ ] no. >> No.
>> Yeah, you protected me from that old
man. He was creepy, man. [ __ ] off.
>> It's [ __ ] creepy, bro. It
>> were creepy.
>> That [ __ ] old man, bro.
>> What? You being in there with him or
that old man hitting on me?
>> All of it. It's just creepy, bro. Is it?
>> He fell in love with me, didn't he? >> Yeah.
>> You [ __ ] fell in love with me in the
old man. Little [ __ ] weird one. It's
all right to be gay, Jamie. >> Yeah.
>> It's not a choice, Jamie. It's not a
choice. It's not a choice. Yeah, man.
>> He's He's Canadian. Uh
>> he's Canadian. You You'll never forget
him, is it?
>> No. No. Give me nightmares like that. I
still have nightmares of him now. I
still remember him. Skinny, a grayish
[ __ ] kind of alcohol look alike kind of guy.
>> Well, you you know how we went out in
Birmingham drinking. Yeah.
you know, around the city center. You
You never done that in Manchester ever
in it. Around the city center, is it? Nah, I've
>> never Yeah, of course. I went out
clubbing when I did my film, when I did
>> Okay. So, what's Okay, so what's better
then, Manchester or Birmingham for drinking?
>> Well, obviously I don't know because
they haven't been out proper in
Manchester, you know what I mean?
>> I'd say Manchester is was good.
>> I don't I'm not really I don't really go
out clubbing, do I? Nah,
it was fun though getting pissed in it.
We done I can't believe we done it on an
empty stomach. [ __ ] hell.
>> We're crazy, bro. It
>> We did it.
>> Yeah. I'm surprised we didn't vomit.
>> No, cuz I think it's cuz your belly was
empty and it was just beer on it. So
when you got food in your belly and
that's when you vomit, think about it.
>> You need to eat before you drink because
you know you you you know what I'm
saying? And you puke.
>> No. No. Because I realized I realized if you drink
>> before you I mean when you eat you're
going to be sick.
>> Monty too old for club club. Nah, not
really. Not so
man. I was still a young man.
Still a young ass man. I said the only
thing Yeah. lines.
>> The only the only Monty the only [ __ ]
thing that I regret about [ __ ]
meeting you is obviously the [ __ ] I
met the virgin cuz of you. >> What?
>> Obviously the only bad thing about
meeting you is obviously I've met that
virgin because of you. I tell you this
all the time. Is it?
>> You didn't meet that virgin because of
me. You met him through the community. I
got you in on PlayStation.
>> Yeah, but it was all through
>> it through me because you weren't
talking to me at that time. We're through.
>> I don't remember that game Joe from Leads. >> Yeah. >> Ah,
>> well, you know that you know that Aaron
Cox, he always used to give it the big
end to me. Do you remember
>> that? That Luke guy weren't really gay, you know.
>> Of course he was.
>> No, he wasn't. He weren't gay. He only
said he were gay so he could watch Anna
get undressed all the time at night.
Well, he sounded Listen, listen though,
Monty, you remember when Aan used to
give it the big to me.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> I bet you I could [ __ ] beat him up
now, though. I bet you I could have him
now. It Yeah.
>> Go to him. This um uh
>> Bristol is it?
>> Yeah, Bristol. Yeah,
>> I bet you you know I could have him now, buddy. Yeah,
>> go to him if you want.
I've not seen him for a long time to be
honest with you. He always speak like a
like a piger like a bit like that.
That's how we talked about it. >> Yeah.
>> Sounds a bit like you.
>> I met him through my brothers. That's
how I met him.
>> Have you seen that? Have you seen that
Red Star channel?
>> Was back on PlayStation. I was in a big
group. I I was in a boosting group.
>> Monty, have you seen that Red Star channel?
>> Red? Yeah, Red Star. Yeah. He stalks me
every day and he's been doing it for
years, bro. He doesn't stop.
>> Don't you fancy, Red? >> Huh?
>> Don't you fancy him?
>> No, he he fancies me. Why does he stalk
me all day every day, Jamie?
>> Don't they all do that on here?
>> Yeah, but he does it to me like
specifically and he's been doing it for years.
>> Aren't they all been doing it for years?
>> True. But this this is the way I see it,
Jamie. Yeah. If if if we're the skinned
ones, why are they on here every day
doing this if they if they weren't
skinned? That's what I say. That's what
I always say.
>> Oh, not even mentioning it. There's no
point repeating to him.
>> Yeah, it's the truth though, is it? It
is the truth, though.
>> It is the truth. It is, but don't repeat
what they what what that
you just do it back as well as them. You
know what I mean?
It's just weird what they do on here. I
don't think you understand.
>> You got a brain like [ __ ] they call
me [ __ ] but they maybe they can read or write
the big by having no [ __ ] social life
or anything like that. You know what I
mean? They they can't go out there and
and start a conversation with any
randomized people. They can't sit there.
How was how was I in real life?
>> No, you're not bad.
>> Yeah, we're the same. We're the same
behind it. Yeah.
>> You don't act like you do on YouTube.
>> What do you mean?
>> You don't do all this [ __ ] you do. You
don't do this [ __ ]
>> Yeah, but I would if I was fighting if I
was fighting someone. If I was meeting
someone for a fight, I would. Wouldn't you?
What's the point of fighting these
people? Yeah, Pete. Yeah. Yeah. I'm
going to say one thing. Yeah. When they
give you locations to go to.
>> Yeah. You go to that location. This is
why you don't show up anymore. You won't show up.
>> Like I like I said last night, I'm back in Birmingham.
Like I said last night, I'm not lying
about that, but I'm not saying why I am
in Birmingham. No one's going to know
>> either way.
I can would be
I think I think some of these accounts
are Pat Mustard.
>> Yes. Yeah. Some of them. One is Pat
Mustard. Pat Mustard's never left
YouTube. He's always been watching. >> Yeah.
>> He's always been watching.
He's always been sat on Discord
writing away on Discord with all these lot. >> Mhm.
>> Do you not remember when he got me onto
Discord with him? ages and ages ago.
>> Yeah. When you when you went against me.
>> Yeah. Then then [ __ ] that motion left
back then, didn't he? He left you.
>> That time they made you the time they
made you climb into a fish tank.
>> I've never climbed into a fish tank.
>> Well, they made you do something, didn't they?
>> They don't make me do nothing. I do [ __ ]
on my own world. I got me brain. I got
my own [ __ ]
>> It's just content I do in it. It's
content. Like I said, buddy, maybe one
day these people will stop.
>> They don't understand what I do on
YouTube is just content. It's not really
me. If they don't know me, they don't
know the real me on here. They never
will do. Natalie knows real me.
>> Money, but maybe one day they'll stop it.
>> PJ, they ain't got the mentality to stop.
>> You know,
>> PJ, if these people were going to stop
what they were doing. Yeah, come on.
They would have stopped it a long time
ago. Like instead of telling everybody
else he got off YouTube when these are
still stuck on YouTube. These are the
people who have got a life and
self-reflect on other people's lives on
social media and that's all they what it
is. They haven't got no content. All
they what content these have got is
bullying and that's it. That's all the content.
>> Yeah, but they don't bully me.
>> No, they don't bully me either. But that
they like to think only what they good
at is is toxic and that's it. And that's
it. It's [ __ ] people's lives on when
they get their address and that's only
what they can do. But these don't
understand that these are basically sat
the same situation as us.
>> Look at look at her dress as being rock
star already. Rock, you know, I know
where the [ __ ] she lives. She know you
know 55 in TV in your room. It's It's
big enough, isn't it?
>> It's still good, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's still good.
Yeah. Why? That's what I play. That's
what I play Franklin on.
>> You know, it's same as Pat Mos address.
It's been docks. It's the same as my all
my addresses and all that. Look, being
docks. It's YouTube. >> Yeah.
>> YouTube's not a good place to do because
soon as they got older your address,
you're [ __ ] You can [ __ ] your life up through that.
>> You know what I mean?
>> Rice, is it?
>> No. Yeah. Of course, to look at rice, he
got dragged out of his house by the
police and everything yesterday. Do you
know what I mean?
>> Is it funny?
>> No, it's not funny cuz it's [ __ ] up.
It's [ __ ] people's lives up in it.
It's just a messed up community on
YouTube and it's just mental. It's just
[ __ ] up. They ain't got no life. sat there
putting their own lives on other people
>> cuz they sad with their lives and they
blame other people for whatever. >> Yeah.
>> They put all allegations on people. They
do whatever they do,
>> you know. And that's only what we can
do. And this is why I've left. This is
why I don't go live anymore. I don't
mind jumping up and up on people's
panels. That's different.
>> But I will not be going live anymore.
>> Yeah. Obviously been thinking about it
now and saying tonight I'm going to go
live. But think about it.
What's the point?
>> Same repeating people in it.
>> Exactly. You're just sat here with the
same people talking about the same [ __ ]
going around in a big circle. There's
nothing being said. There's nothing
changing. All what what's changing is
these videos of people getting kicked
out of the houses. What what's been
happening for the last [ __ ]
>> Why do they Why did it take so long for
them to do that to Rice? Do you think things?
>> Um I think they only done that is
because Kayie will uh
>> they only done that is cuz Kaye was at
the property and they don't want Kaye to
be in a relationship or they want to but
Kay don't understand that.
You feel sorry for Kaye?
>> I don't feel sorry for Kayie, do I?
How the [ __ ] am I going to build
something for that rat for?
>> But it's weird how people knew where he
lived for so long. But
>> yeah, of course, of course.
>> Strange strange all of a sudden. You know,
>> I'm happy with the woman I'm with now. Believe. Trust.
She's a really good woman. A really good
woman. I've landed on my feet good. I I
don't want to [ __ ] this relationship up
cuz yeah, I've got a fantastic woman. You know. >> Yeah.
>> And if you all think that I'm going to run back,
you all can suck my dick first.
>> How you how you going to make money now,
Monty? Like get rich. How you going to get rich?
>> What do you mean get rich?
>> How you want to get the money on the side?
>> I don't want to be rich. >> No.
>> No. Why the [ __ ] do I want to be rich
for? Right. What breeds happiness, PJ? >> Money.
>> Money. There you go. You got you got
your priorities right, wrong, right
there. What makes happiness is being in
a [ __ ] having someone around you,
being in a relationship, having your own
[ __ ] family, and that's it. It's only
what you need. Why the [ __ ] do you need
money? Money don't make you happy. You
can ask any celebrity, does money make
you happy? No, it doesn't.
>> Hopefully you don't end up Hopefully you
don't end up skinned again. Is it? That
was bad. That was
>> Monty bad. I'm always skin PJ. You just
come down on the wrong time. You know
what I mean. I'm always skin. Not
always, but not meaning it like in a bad
way or whatever. I don't like money PJ.
I can't stand money,
>> you know? Like all these people can sit
on YouTube and say, "Oh yeah, we go out
with more money." You Oh yeah. Yeah.
Your skin. Oh yeah. Look at this. Oh
yeah. Money's just [ __ ] money. Everybody get
>> But these people Yeah. But Monty, these people asking.
>> Yeah. That's why they talk about money
every day. And
>> it's cuz they ain't got none. >> [ __ ]
>> Cuz think about it, Monty. Yeah. Say I
had £2,000 now. Yeah. 1.5,000. Listen.
Listen, Monty. Yeah. Say I had 1.5,000
or 2,000. That's enough for me as a
single person. You know, PJ
in the tent. Look, people definitely not
in a tent. Hang on one sec.
Let me guard my backyard camera.
Definitely not in a tent, peeps.
Definitely not in a tent. Definitely not.
>> Well, poor Franklin. He got run over.
Franklin got run over.
>> Oh, cheated.
>> Yeah, Monty. What I was saying is, yeah,
if I had 1.5,000 or 2,000, whatever like
a single person, that's enough for me.
So why do these people keep going on about money?
>> Because ain't got PJ, it doesn't matter
if they got money or if they haven't got
money. They're just so obsessed with money,
>> you know, like people have got
addictions with like smoking weed, um,
drinking and all that lot.
>> You know,
do you know, hey Monty, do you know
another thing what they do? Yeah. is
they ask you to show money and then when
you show money they don't show you
nothing. Do you remember that?
>> Some people do, some people don't. Or
>> they never show they never showed me
money when I showed 6,000 cash.
>> Like like Jimmy Eldridge. No, he only
show yours when he's got it and I rare.
>> What I'm saying is what I'm saying is
when I showed £6,000, right? No one none
of these could show nothing.
It doesn't matter if they can show
[ __ ] Listen, having one PE is
nothing. A grand nothing. How long do
you reckon a grand would last your PJ?
>> Three weeks, a month?
>> Three week a last me, lad. A grand only
lasts me what? Four days? Three days?
>> Four days. Three days. Really?
>> Yeah. And it's gone. And it's gone. And
it's [ __ ] baboom gone.
That's no [ __ ]
>> Yeah, but Monty, that's cuz you're rich, man.
>> I'm not rich. I'm not rich at all. It's
just because I keep going on Tik Tok
getting loads of [ __ ] off Tik Tok. What
I don't even [ __ ] need. I keep
getting son panels. I got a big old
obsession at the moment with [ __ ]
sono panels for some reason.
>> The solo panels come in handy. [ __ ] in
the world. It does turn off me solo
panels charging my phone up when all use can't
>> you know
>> madness has zero savings
I've got zero savings
but they think that bothers me pia but
they don't understand I can get s and
put like what
say about 400 quid in one saving and
then spend the rest and so that money left over.
>> So that's what I can do like once a
month. So you
>> I get paid the same amount every day twice over.
>> I'm I'm poor money.
Yeah. I tell you how much I get paid PJ.
I'm not as I get paid. I get uh 900. Yeah. And
no 700. I get 700 and 90. >> Yeah.
>> And I get 790 on my other payment as
well. So I come out with 700 on one and
700 on the other.
>> I'm poor Monty. I
Can you ask Jamie to wish me luck approaching today?
>> I'm not I don't approach. I'm not I
didn't I didn't even approach in Birmingham.
I weren't even approaching in
Birmingham. I talked to him.
I talked to people.
>> Yeah, I done it. How many times you see
me do it, Molly? Not much.
>> Not much.
>> I I [ __ ] did, mate.
>> No. No.
You only did it about I say about seven times.
>> Yeah. Which is [ __ ] a lot. What the
[ __ ] What the [ __ ] Which is a lot.
>> Seven times isn't really a lot.
>> Well, it is.
I went up to someone me and PJ told me
to call approach him.
>> Remember I approached the one with her mom
>> and the dad? Yeah, that was the first
one. That was the first one.
>> No, the first one was outside Monty
sober. No, I done one outside sober
before I remember
when I first met you.
No, I only can remember the [ __ ]
>> No, when I first met you outside the
outside the pub. Do you remember the
first one I done when we walked up the road?
>> We didn't go to the pub. You met me at
the train station.
>> Yes. And then we went outside a club,
the pub club. And I done one outside
Soar. Do you remember the first one I done?
>> Right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> You remember now? Yeah.
Oh, these people are weird. Anyway, so
I'm just going to see what Natalie wants
me to do. >> Yeah.
Obviously, you got to treat a woman
happy in it. One sec.
One second. I'm going to go back live.
One second. Yeah, someone's calling me. Hold on.