Yeah, sorry about that. I was doing something.
Oh, the dick picture seem to got a
reply. Strange. That's not being
insulting though, is it? That's just
pure negativity with somebody that you
don't know. That's just pure pure negativity.
I was, "Oh [ __ ] there's actually a
video of me getting a [ __ ] Let me
send them a video of me getting a blowjob."
Oh yeah, I forgot that. I actually have
a two videos of me getting a [ __ ]
Lo and behold, the penis picture got a
reply back. Wadley, they love
negativity, don't they? For people that
sit there and say that they they go for
positive. You're on YouTube. Yes, it is
your life. Yes, you're on YouTube as
well. YouTube is your life. You're the
one there talking to me. So, I sent a
dick picture and then um it got a reply
back. Wow. I thought they like
positivity and not negativity. So, I
thought, "Oh, that's not that's not as
good." So, I sent them a video of me
getting a [ __ ]
Yeah. Sticking their mind. These sick
[ __ ] Give them some back what they've
put me through all of these years. [ __ ] scumbags.
Yeah, I've still got their videos. I
just sent them. Yeah.
No, she was like, I thought it would be
big or so small. I'm a little
disappointed. I was like, h, it wasn't
even erect. So then I sent her a video
of me getting a [ __ ]
It's so mad how they're so quick to
reply back to nastiness, but they ignore
positivity. [ __ ] hell. Oh, it's like
the other way around, isn't it?
Crazy, isn't it?
I'm so glad I gave up.
I'm so glad I'm so glad I gave up. I'm
so glad. I feel like I'm free, you know?
I'm so glad I g I wish I'd gave up sooner.
I'm I wish I gave up with these [ __ ]
sooner, bro. I swear to God. I wish I
gave up with these [ __ ] sooner.
You know, I wish I generally did.
I wish I gave up sooner with these
[ __ ] these [ __ ] scumbag women.
I'd send other people it, but obviously
a lot of them live in England, and you
know what they're going to do? They'll
call the police. So, we can only do it
to people that are like out the country.
Yeah, the weather can be good all at
once. I don't give a [ __ ] I'm staying
in bed. I give up a life. Roll on November.
Roll on November. Yes. Get the [ __ ] in there.
Can be good all at once. It can be [ __ ]
all at once. I'm I'm not bothered. I'm
not going out in it.
So yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] Should
have gave up a long time ago.
[ __ ] hell. What the [ __ ] was I
thinking? Thinking it was ever going to change here.
[ __ ] want to be [ __ ] to me, I'll be
a [ __ ] to you. Simple.
It's not letting me back on Reddit. Why?
Yeah, the French one replied to the uh
dick picture saying, "I thought it was
bigger. So small. I'm a little disappointed."
Nope. I don't I told you a million times
I don't gamble anymore.
There's no point in explaining it to you
disabled people cuz you don't listen to
anything any anyone says anyways. She
says, "Uh, yeah, so small. I'm a little
disappointed." I said, "Ah, it's bigger.
It just wasn't hard." So then I sent her
a picture of me getting a [ __ ] I
forgot I had this [ __ ] video. I start
sending it out to people that uh live in
France and Italy and Poland. I got a lot
of contacts. I'll just start sending
them videos of me getting a [ __ ]
Yeah. Just just [ __ ] with their head.
Bit like how they [ __ ] with other people's heads.
Yeah. I've had a bad loss gambling when
I've literally said that I don't gamble
anymore on anything but the football
brain damage. This is why we call it a
disabled community, bro.
This is why I warn fellow people to not
get into it with you people,
you know, because you're just [ __ ] disabled.
Yep. Trolling, bro. They are such
trolls. the French, aren't they? Such
I can't log on to Reddit. It's not
letting me back on Reddit, man. [ __ ] sake.
It's not letting me back on Reddit, man.
Let me message this one.
So, yeah, we've had a lot of replies
when you say you hate them. We've had a
lot of replies.
Yeah, I would send it to Mo, but
obviously they live a lot of them live
in England. There's one that lives in Ireland.
I could do it with that one because they
can't go to the police, but I don't
know. That's a bit dodge, isn't it?
Yeah, it's a bit dodge.
So, some of it could come under the UK.
So, no. Let's Let's make sure they're
out of Europe when we're doing this [ __ ]
Oh, I know this one. This one's American.
I can send I can send this one. Yeah. Hold on.
I'm going to say, "Look what your mom
gave me last night and send a blow your
video." That'll get a response, won't
it? That'll get a response.
That'll get a response, won't it? Yeah.
Sure it will. Sure that will get a
response, won't it, Nicolo? Anything negative,
anything disgusting, anything that they
can argue against, they're there.
They're there before you can say [ __ ]
Jack Robinson. They're [ __ ] there, bro.
They're there in your life. As soon as
something negative is said, makes you
wonder, doesn't it, who we're really dealing with.
It makes you wonder who we're actually dealing with
what kind of scum we're actually dealing
with here. You know
the kind of scum we're actually dealing
with, bro, in this uh thing.
Yeah. never never never going to change.
It's never going to change.
And then you you explain to these
people, Joker, a million times that you
don't gamble anymore and they think that
you've lost gambling when I've literally
explained about a million times I don't
gamble anymore. And by I don't gamble,
you know what I mean by not gamble, I
mean like machines and roulette. You know,
it's not small. It's just part of their
trolling, trying to knock people's confidence.
And the reason I started sending is is
to see how fast they are to reply to negativity
because they don't reply to positivity.
So, let's see how quick they are. Um,
they're just [ __ ] They're just
[ __ ] in this country. I hate all of them.
I got a lot of numbers to [ __ ] with today.
And why would you say about a gambling
loss when I've literally said, "I don't
gamble anymore." Are you disabled? Like,
no offense. Are you a bit slow in your head?
When someone says they don't do anything
anymore, that means they don't do
anything anymore. You got have you got
brain damage? Cuz for people that come
on here every day and call people
spazzers or whatever, you sure are one
[ __ ] selves. Like I don't know how
many times people have to explain stuff to you.
Are you generally disabled?
Like it is generally a disabled
community, isn't it? you know,
generally think like a lot of you on
here are actually disabled. Like, no joke,
[ __ ] hell. Jesus Christ. You can't
have a different opinion without being
called an incel. You can't have a
different opinion without being told
that you've lost a lot of money
gambling. What the [ __ ] What's the
[ __ ] world come to, Joker?
Why the [ __ ] would I have a big gambling
loss? Gambled on [ __ ] what?
the [ __ ] bro.
But yeah, I that's like I said, that's
why I tell people to never get into it
with these people like LJ and these
disabled people and [ __ ] There's just no point.
There's just there's just no point.
So yeah, there's no point getting into
it with these people, bro.
You'll develop brain damage,
bro. There's a lot of hills on GTA
[ __ ] five, isn't there?
But then I realized you're just arguing
with [ __ ] disabled people. So, I
mean, what the [ __ ] do you expect?
This life doesn't change, does it?
Despite any advice given on the
internet, it's bad, isn't it, bro?
Really bad. Nicolo
aka Joker. It's so so bad, bro.
So bad, lad.
[ __ ] can't sleep until 6:00 in the morning.
You wake up angry and you go to bed
angry. But you don't go to bed angry cuz
you can't even sleep. You can't even
keep still. And then you wake up and
same [ __ ] again and again and again and
again and again and again and again. All
to just die in the end anyways.
All to just die in the end anyways.
You just die in the end anyways. You
live, you get bad experiences, and you die.
What a [ __ ] troll. You know,
you get people give you the same advice for years.
Nah, I'm done, bro. I don't I'm not
interested in nothing.
I'm probably not even going to go to to
the um thing today, to be honest. I'm
probably not even going to go
um outside, to be fair. Yeah,
you get bad experiences with women and
you die. What kind of life is that, lad?
Yeah, bro. I've been defeated from a
long time ago.
I've been defeated by a [ __ ] from a
long time ago, bro. [Music] Yeah,
this life is wank. It doesn't change.
No matter the effort that you put, no
matter the effort you put into it, it doesn't change.
Probably just get like some
chicken today, I think. Maybe.
Nah, my head's down. It's so far down.
It's up my ass.
My head's up my ass at the minute.
That's how down it is. This life is
[ __ ] It's boring. I want out of it.
Generally, it's [ __ ] donkey. It's
[ __ ] donkey [ __ ] It's pig [ __ ] It's
not even donkey [ __ ] It's pig [ __ ]
It's pig [ __ ] It doesn't change, bro. I
want to die, bro. I pray yesterday I
[ __ ] die in my sleep. This life ain't
the one, bro.
It really, really ain't the one.
It ain't the one, bro. There's a lot of
things that are the one, but this ain't for 100%.
Someone was like, "Oh, um, yeah, so you
approach more than a thousand every
year." Well, basically, yeah, cuz I've
got on my phone,
but it doesn't say the contacts anymore,
but it's about 200 contacts. And
obviously, that's not including the ones
that haven't gave me their number. So, I
probably would say I clear I'd clear
about a thousand approaches in probably
about five months.
You can probably do about a thousand in
So yeah, I have could probably do over a
thousand in a year to be honest. So yeah,
that's easy, bro. I don't know how many
do you approach when you go out. Maybe 20, 30.
So maybe like five, six months, you
could do about a thousand. So yeah, thanks
happened to rice.
Don't know yet. Don't care. Don't know.
I'll probably just go back to sleep to be honest.
It's not letting me back on [ __ ] Reddit.
Maybe I won't eat today. I'm not even hungry.
You lose your appetite when you're
depressed. I think
Reddit. I'm not sure why.
Yeah, things will get better in another
lifetime, maybe, but not this lifetime.
It will in another lifetime, but not
this lifetime, mate.
That's for sure.
That's for damn sure. It Greasy.
in another lifetime maybe. But show as
hell not this one.
This has been going on for years.
Creepy. This has been going on for
years, lad. [ __ ] years with these
[ __ ] you know.
Nope. Negative outcome equals negative
thinking. Four years of negative
experiences equals negative thinking.
Because if that way, if that wasn't the
case, then people would No one's born
negative. No one's born positive. Why
would you be negative for no reason? Let
me let me let me ask you this question,
Grezy. Why would someone be negative for
no reason? Seems like a waste of time.
You want you just wake up one day and
you're negative. You're probably
negative because of your negative
experiences with women
and your experiences with women. That's
probably why you're negative because
that's the only thing that would make
sense because you wouldn't be negative
for no reason. What a waste of time that
would be. No one's positive for no
reason and no one's negative for no
reason. You are what you've been through
and you're a byproduct of what you've
been through in your life. Negative outcome
equals negative experiences.
Just like when we'd go out every week.
Just like when I went out three weeks
ago, it was all negative. Yeah. I'm
pretty sure he wasn't thinking of anything.
So that's why he's just best not giving
up with life.
So which is basically what I've done and
I'm sticking to it this time. Like all
the other times where I got out of it
and [ __ ] that. [ __ ] that for a game of soldiers.
You know what I mean? Greasy. [ __ ] that
for a game of [ __ ] soldiers, lad.
Just the same old [ __ ] that never
changes. [ __ ] boring. It is [ __ ] Yeah,
literally. Yeah, I give up with everything.
I mean, I'm not leaving until [ __ ]
November, so I mean Yeah.
Literally just give up with everything. Yeah, bro.
No point tormenting yourself anymore,
thinking that shit's going to change
when it's never going to change cuz it
would have changed by now.
Yeah, but he was trolling at Dusty.
I'm going Thailand.
I'm going Thailand. It's right after my birthday.
I'm out of here.
[ __ ] my back is hurting. Does that ever
hurt happen to you, Greg? When you lie
around for so long, your body starts aching.
When you're not proactive, you just Yeah,
I'm depressed because of these these women, bro.
They're [ __ ] It's just the same [ __ ]
with them year in year out, year in,
year out, year in, year out. I'd rather
be sat here [ __ ] depressed for them
months knowing that I've saved money
than going out thinking that it's going
to change here somewhere somehow.
Somehow you're going to meet someone
that's different. Yeah. You got more
chance of meeting the [ __ ] elephant man.
You got more chance of [ __ ] Stitch
being real. You got more chance of of
going out and pulling Stitch.
That's how that's how rare it is. Like
you got more chance of Stitch being a real character, you know? So
you got more chance of pulling Stitch,
mate. And he's not even real, you know.
Yeah, my back and arms hurting, bro. Cuz
I'm not proactive anymore.
What happens when you give up your life?
Same old [ __ ] I mean, what I'm saying
is right. I mean, who you only you know
what you've been through, right,
Greavves? Only you know your experiences.
Only you know.
And by you, I mean me. Only you know,
like I said, by you, I mean me. So yeah,
no one else can tell you anything. So yeah,
my back is [ __ ] hurting me, bro. Hey,
my [ __ ] back.
Oh man, my shoulder hurts.
Yeah. And like I said, in another lifetime.
In another lifetime.