That was lush. [ __ ]
That is the last one. slow motion. Yeah.
This just kills the time, eh?
Thanks for the two thumbs up of the
video, by the way. Yeah, man.
Yeah, that was good.
That's mad. You literally can't get rid
of the [ __ ]
Literally, mate. Literally.
A [ __ ] lot of them. A
Oh, Franklin's drowning. Dead,
isn't it? Yeah.
Nah, I'm not trolling him. He's trolling
me. Bro, what the [ __ ] You said I need
to find God. I said there is no God.
the [ __ ] lot of him.
I was thinking of some of your sayings.
Yeah. Well, they're my sayings that
you're repeating as I was eating and
it's funny. I'm like, Chucky, you can't
get rid of the [ __ ]
Yeah. I'm not trolling, bro.
I knew that' make you laugh, is it? Yeah.
Yeah, that's why they quickly broke up.
So they thought I weren't going to find
out in it. They thought I weren't going
to find out.
They thought I weren't going to find out in it.
Fight god. You said I should fight God. A not. [Laughter]
It's funny, is it?
No, I'm not. I was on [ __ ] Reddit,
man, arguing with these [ __ ] sing
[ __ ] Some of the people I sent a dick
picture to, they reply back.
The Brazil was, "Oh, why did you show
that was very ugly of you? Just do
that." I said cuz I wanted to do it.
Yeah, I just been [ __ ] I got so many
numbers. I could just I just just been
[ __ ] with them, bro.
Yeah, I've just been [ __ ] with them legit
cuz you got so many of them. So
yeah, just been on Reddit all day. I
order some food, but yeah. Yeah, man.
[ __ ] a lot of them. [ __ ] a lot of you,
you know. That's what I said in the end.
Really, ain't it? You know, [ __ ] a lot
of you. I was messaging LT, you know,
saying, "Listen, we can go tonight if you want.
I got nothing to lose, bro." I was messaging him.
Yeah. I said, "Bro, I want to show
everyone on YouTube who's boss."
H I ain't even [ __ ] around, bro.
Literally, I got nothing to lose.
So, just show them. Show him who's boss in it.
I said I'll show everyone on YouTube who's boss.
Would you like to see that?
I just felt like going out today just
doing something daft
like really really daft. You ever get
them days? I want to do something d know.
Don't know why
it's on a video. So
money is back on YouTube.