Yo yo Um,
I think I went to bed at like 4
yesterday. I don't think I went to bed as late.
Definitely [ __ ] not. No,
you mean I might just like tired of it
now. I don't know how [ __ ] Red Star
does this every day. He really has got
no life. I'm telling you, he's a fat
ugly virgin living in his mom's
basement. Don't let him tell you
otherwise. That coward that's been doing
this for years. So, I just brought him
up cuz like obviously I was doing a bit
of that [ __ ] for like two days and I'm
actually tired, bro. Talking about
yourself again. No money is you. No
girlfriend is you. Yep. You're talking about yourself.
Yep. You are on YouTube talking about
yourself. I've shown more money than you
and I've shown more women than you. Get
real, kid. Think before typing.
Oh, [ __ ] Yep. You're talking about
yourself. Stop talking about yourself
like that. I've told you this a million
times. It's not nice to talk about
yourself like that. Your mental health
is probably very bad as it is.
No money, no girlfriend. That's
literally you. Especially the no money
part. Why are you talking about yourselves? [ __ ] hell.
You can't even take a day off of
YouTube. Why do you go mad when people
go live like three, four times a day?
You can't even take a [ __ ] hour off of YouTube. Self-reflector.
It's all self-reflectctors on this
community, bro. I'm telling you. They
can't even take a day off of YouTube.
Not even one day. And then they try and
tell people how many times they're live
when they're sat there on YouTube all
day. Every day can't leave the house.
And they tell you how
[ __ ] How many times you're on YouTube?
And they can't even take a day off of
YouTube ever. They never have. And they
want to try and tell you how many times
you're alive. Interesting.
Stop talking about yourselves. And uh
another thing is right
I I forgot to reply to Greavves
yesterday. You know when Greavves says,
"Oh yeah, you should see a specialist
and meet a woman and then own the
trolls." Bro, come on. These people have
been owned multiple times, but they
forget what they've shown. They know
deep down they've been owned. Like, they
know deep down I got more money than
them. I've shown more money than them.
I've show more women than them. I'm
better looking than them. Bro, they
already know all of this [ __ ] that's
already happened. But they're never
going to admit it. Which is why I said
there's no point getting into it with
these disabled people. That's the whole point.
Cuz no matter what you show them, they
pretend it never happened. That's what I'm saying.
That's the whole point of them being disabled.
Just like I've said a million times
before, when you go to meet people and
they pretend it never happened. You're
wasting your time.
Look as it is now. I'm younger than
these people. I'm better looking than
them. I got more money than them. And um
my life is not perfect. And they still
tried to call me. So I mean, [ __ ]
hell, bro. Come on now. Could you
imagine if you really was any better?
They're just sad, depressed people that
can't live that can't take a day off of
YouTube. [ __ ] how many times people
going [ __ ] how many times someone's gone
live, bro. [ __ ] all that.
The fat, ugly people that never made it.
These people should be shown in
classrooms, bro. What people don't want
to end up like.
These people that can't get off of YouTube. [ __ ]
Oh [ __ ] the vibrator
self-reflecting every day.
[ __ ] I can go [ __ ] live a h 100
times in a day if I want to. You people
can't even take a day off of [ __ ] YouTube. So yeah,
that's what I mean. Can't even take a
day off on YouTube.
Keep calling you things that they are
themselves. They'll never stop.
Never ever ever stop.
Just like I was saying with the whole
Mark Samson thing. You remember when I
went to Mark Samson's area two times and
no one brings it up?
They never got to admit that I'm better
looking than them. I've got more money
than them. I've got better life than
them. Whoever I do or I didn't. So it's
everyone knows what they
everyone knows what the you people do, you know. Could
go out today if I wanted to. Could get
pissed today. What's day? Friday.
Could go out today if I wanted to. Not interested. Simple.
Do a video last night, but I didn't like
two channels, but then I just didn't. So
these people can't even leave the house.
[ __ ] s on YouTube day in day out
every day. Can't get off it. Trying to
talk about other people.
I was speaking to someone yesterday and
then they've uh disappeared all of a sudden.
Oh, that's strange. People disappearing.
People disappearing, eh?
Well, it's happened a lot of times
before, hasn't it? People disappearing.
So, here today, gone tomorrow. That's
what I say. That's a good saying, you know.
Go out today, I could go out tomorrow.
So all of this [ __ ] where people say you
got no money, they're just talking about
their own lives,
the self-reflection of their own skin
vibes like they always do on here.
It's okay to come on here and rant and
take the piss of that, but there's no
point in getting into it with any of
these disabled people.
There's there's literally no point in
getting into any of it with these people.
No point. Why does no one speak about
that Mark Samson thing as well? That's
how you knew you was losing from the
start. You knew, you know, with these
disabled people in here, you knew he was
losing from the start.
Why has no one ever mentioned that Mark
Samson thing when he got a bigger ownage
than [ __ ] um
when he when he got a bigger ownage than
[ __ ] uh Bob? What the [ __ ] I mean,
yeah, people are going at him now. What?
Four years [ __ ] later. They already
knew what he was [ __ ] about. And it
doesn't even matter if they're going at
him or not. They never ever bring that
up. I noticed that.
Yeah. You don't want to remember things
that you're that you don't want to
remember, do you? No. Like when people
shown you six grand and you will run
away multiple times. Um when people have
gone to people's areas. Yeah. You never
remember these things, do you?
Yeah. You never remember these things, do you? Wow.
Is it? Hey, what do you mean? Is it the
time? You remember exactly what time it
was, you know? You remember all of the
L's that I [ __ ] took very very very vividly.
Like everybody knows exactly what
happened and no one's ever mentioned it.
Like literally no one's ever mentioned
it. That's how you know from the start
you was losing with these people,
you know? That's how you knew you was
losing with these people cuz no one ever
Yeah. They say that he's an idiot and
he's not about it after what 20 years
later. But that that doesn't [ __ ]
they should they knew that [ __ ] years ago
when I've made people go running to the police.
You know, you could be a millionaire.
You could show a video of you having sex
right now. They still tell you that
you're skinn and you got no one because
they're talking about themselves. Not
understand theirelves. That's what these
losers do. Talk about theirelves every
day on YouTube. [ __ ] me.
That's their life. YouTube
and that's it.
Like I said, I went to bed at 4
yesterday, so it wasn't that late.
I was speaking to someone and now
they're gone. So, typical westernized experience, eh?
Typical westernized experience.
Yep. Never changes. I heard yesterday,
bro. A double eye of a bl and a [ __ ]
approach. I was watching it. Well,
yeah. I was thinking of doing a video,
but just never.
It's not even like you can you can be
positive about it cuz you know what it
is. You know what happens. you know the
result. It's not even like you could,
like I said, you could be positive about
it cuz you know the response. You know
the [ __ ] You know they've been
being [ __ ] and [ __ ] for years. So,
it's not even like you don't know.
It's not even like you have any hope now
because of all of what's happened, you know. Yeah.
So I think um
[ __ ] Tik Tok [ __ ] everything up
when people started going on that app.
It [ __ ] everything up.
Do you remember when dating apps used to
work back like four or five years ago?
You remember when they actually used to workish?
Even back in 2015 when I was like um 18
17 18 back then there was actually like
real profiles because there's no Tik Tok
then you see so people could actually date. Yeah.
Something's changed in them years, bro.
Tick tock. Tick [ __ ] tick tock. Tick
[ __ ] what, bro? Yeah.
Yeah. Today, gone tomorrow.
I just fancy doing a little video just
to rant, you know, because I don't ever
do like videos about dating much. So
yeah, probably just go for a walk later maybe, but
that's probably about it. I probably
won't do anything else.
Roll on November.
Jeez, do you remember when it was
[ __ ] roll on Christmas
or roll on a day or roll on, you know,
you ever heard the saying?
I don't have the energy to keep going on
Reddit for now, bro. That's crazy. How
the [ __ ] does a Red Star do this all
day, every day for years?
Some fat, ugly bongo. Like, I I get I
get it. I've been there, bro. Like,
[ __ ] a reaction and [ __ ] [ __ ] I
was doing it for like a day and a half
and I was like, "Oh boy, I can't do it
anymore." I'm telling you, he's some fat
ugly virgin living in his mommy's
basement. Don't let him tell you any different.
Don't let that coward tell you any different.
Cuz bro, that's I can actually say like
I was kind of that [ __ ] for like a day
and I was like, "Bro, you need to be
very very sad to to keep up with this
all day every day for years.
You have to be very sad. Very, very sad.
It depends where people are in their
life, I guess. Like, you know this. Oh,
[ __ ] Whoa. Like this red star, he's
probably very ugly in real life.
Probably been bullied, probably never
been laid. So, he comes on YouTube and
takes it out on people, you know.
But like a lot of these people, you know
what they doing here?
Yeah, I was got a I was going to do a
video saying uh title uh a video titled
I was going to do a video titled No
Chance of Finding Mrs. Right. I think
that's a good that's a good title, is it?
Yeah, I was going to.
Yeah, Peter Belly can't find Mrs. Right.
That's what I was going to type it as. Miss, right?
Nah, not even that. You need to have
loads and loads of money. You need to be
a Tik Tocker. It's not about just being
6'4. There's a lot of people that are
very tall that struggle.
That's why I don't go out. That's why
I'm not going out today, cuz I already
know the result.
I already know the result before I even
tried. So there's no point doing
something you already know the result.
You already know the outcome.
Friday is a good drinking day as well to
be fair. It will never change.
So there's no point wasting time and
money on something that's never going to
change. It never changed all them other
years. So it's not going to change now. Simple.
It was not changed all them other years.
It's not going to change now. It's just
common sense, isn't it?
>> I think so. Yeah. Listen to it. >> Yeah.
Horrible, isn't it?
I can't be angry for [ __ ]
more than like two days, bro. I just
like, "Oh [ __ ] I don't have the energy. Yeah.
SP it up. Horrible at Oh [ __ ]
I might do a video. Um,
just stay in bed, maybe go for a walk.
Yeah, we woke up again sadly.
It's horrible. Is it, bro?
When's it going to change? Greasy. [ __ ] hell.
when you're going to change, bro. [Music]
Yeah, I might do a dating video. Greasy.
Yeah, I might do a little dating video
titled Peter Belly will never find Mrs. Right.
You know what I mean? Yeah.
I might do I might do a video, man. send
it to some people. I have a lot of
people that follow me on here
with a with a with a with a quiet emoji.
So what if I went out today approaching Grezy
went to the pub?
Yeah, of course she did.
Of course she did. Yeah, of course she
What if I go to the pub today and and do some approaches?
What if I went to the pub and done some
approaches today? Groovsy,
why? I could meet someone. Wooy.
Why is it a waste of time?
Why is it a waste of time though? could
meet someone moves.
Yeah, I was just saying that like I
don't have the energy to keep doing this
Reddit [ __ ] all day, every day. That's
how you know that Red Star is just a
jealous loser and he's been bullied all
his life. Cuz say you're pissed off.
Yeah. You go on Reddit for like a
reaction and you go on Reddit to vent,
right? For what, like a day and a day
and a half and he's like, "Oh, bro, I
can't do this anymore." Think of this
disabled bastard has been doing this for
years on YouTube all day, every day. It
It just goes to show that he's a bully victim,
right? It goes more to show that he's
just some disabled bully victim that's
sed with jealousy. Cuz bro, it's hard to
have that kind of energy every day, you
know, bro. Especially when you're not
even getting paid for it.
Think about it, bro. It's, you know,
it's it's effort to do that every day.
Sat sit on YouTube from the time you
wake up to the time you go to bed like
that loser does. You know, it takes it's
it's energy, bro. I mean,
that's mad, bro. What the [ __ ]
I want to try and do a video at some point.
You remember what I was saying to Damon
Grevy? Why did you and mommy break up?
That's funny, isn't it?
Only God can save you.
Yeah, I asked I said to him, "Why did
you and mommy break up?
Is that cute?" Greasy.
Mommy said you were [ __ ] in bed. That's
funny, isn't it? That's funny, is it?
I ain't showered for days, bro. I'm
very, very smelly.
What happens when you give up your life? You know,
that Red Star is such a coward. Whoever
is behind that account, that cowardly [ __ ]
little [ __ ] begging the [ __ ] black
man to do his dirty work, but sat on
YouTube being a [ __ ] every day, too
scared to show where he is. What a [ __ ] coward.
Isn't that right, Grezy?
Isn't that right?
What happens when you give up a life, you know?
That's what happens when you like I said
that's what happens when you give up the life. Grezy
got a football tomorrow. Yeah.
So, I might just get So, I don't know.
Might go to the Chinese today.
Do something like that.
I think I want to do a data video.
Why did you say it's a waste of time,
Grey? How is it a waste of time if I
could meet someone?
How is it a waste of time if I could meet someone?
Why would it be a waste of time if a
[ __ ] guy meet someone?
>> No. Well, but what what if they're not
all the same? Maybe they're all different, you know? Well,
are you suggesting that they are different?
Are you suggesting that they are different? No.
I I never said that. I I don't know if
they're all the same. I mean, they do
the same stuff. They say the same stuff.
They have the same mannerisms.
They lead people on the same way. I
mean, they do a lot of the same stuff
for people that are not all the same. I
mean, that's that's what I said. They do
a lot of similar stuff for people that
aren't all the same. I'll give I'll give them that.
I mean, you be the judge. You know,
they all pretend they got boyfriends.
They all give the same excuse in exactly
the same way, like they're speaking to
someone or they've got a man. They do
exactly the same as one another does.
They literally do. So, yeah.
So, are you suggesting that they're not
all the same?
Is that what Are you suggesting that
they're not all the same? They seem all
the same to me.
I mean, they say they seem all the same
to me, bro. Don't know about you.
Well, I never found anyone in four years. So,
I mean, bear in mind, I have got
experience with this. I can find decent
people out there. Well, I didn't find
anyone in 4 years. So,
um I don't know how true that is. I
didn't find anyone traveling up and down
the country for 4 years. So, I don't
know, man. It's hard to believe you when
I've got this much experience. If you
could find decent people out there, why
haven't I found one by now? It's been four years.
That's always going to [ __ ] your
argument up. That is literally always
going to [ __ ] your argument up.
We're not stuck in our ways. I'm telling
you what I'm experiencing.
You know, when every time I go out and I
try to speak to someone, which is why we
don't do it anymore. Um, and by we, I
mean me. I mean, if there was really
decent people out there, you would have
found someone in 4 years, you know? I
think that's I think that's a fair
point. If there was actual decent women
out there, you would have found someone.
And what what argument do you do you
have to that? What? You can't say I
didn't try hard enough. You can't say it
wasn't long enough. So that's why you
your argument would always come to an end. You know,
if there was truly decent people out
there, you would have found someone by now.
Simple. What does anyone have to say to
that? you know.
Yeah, I think I'm going to do a dating
video. I think,
you know. Yeah, I'm going to do a dating video. Definitely.
Yeah. Why did you and mommy split up?
So if there's decent people out there,
then you would have found someone by
now. No, four years up and down the
country, all that money that you went
through, all of that, you know what I
mean? I mean, surely to god, you would
have found someone. I'm guessing you
would have. I'm guessing you would have.
We went to a lot of different cities,
Grezy. We we met a lot of different
people and they all turned out to be
exactly the same as one another. So,
which is why
I'm not going out today. I'm not going out tomorrow. So, yeah.
So, yeah. And besides, why would you
even want to go out and disturb people
today? They've all got boyfriends,
remember? We Why the [ __ ] you would you
want to disturb people in relationships?
They've all got boyfriends, so they say. So
why would you want to disturb pe disturb
I don't want to go disturb people with boyfriends?
You know, how do you know they don't
have boyfriends? Oh, [ __ ] hell. I
used to hate that one, you know, when
they used to say, "Oh, how do you know
that they don't?"
because it's pretty obvious that they don't.
I mean, it's pretty obvious. So, Greg,
you didn't answer my question. If
there's decent people out there, will
have I met one by now,
you know? When have you met when have
you met someone by now?
Because that's that's what separates me
from Oreo man and all of these other
people is that I'm sure you would have
found someone by now. If there was if
there was decent people out there, I am sure you
Yeah. I've given up looking for Mrs.
Wright in this country cuz she's nowhere
to be found. Nicolo,
and this is another thing you need to
realize. I've tried more than anyone in
the world when we're having this
conversation. Whereas most these people
complain, I don't think they've even
done one approach. Um, yeah.
I'm not a decent person. Well, I pretty
much am. Oh, so you're blaming me now?
Oh, I'm not a decent person.
I'm not a decent person. Oh, Jesus
Christ. I've never heard that one before.
All right. Is that the excuse? [Laughter]
Good one. Is that the excuse you're
going with now? It It took you It took
you a long time to think of that. I'm
not I'm not um
Okay, what things have I come out with then?
And yeah, even if I wasn't a decent
person, which I am. Yeah, they go with
um drug dealers and thugs and people
that degrade them and [ __ ]
Yeah, that's another thing. What? What
the [ __ ] makes me not decent? Hold on.
What? Because I've reacted to people on YouTube.
Is that what makes me not decent?
What do I come out with, bro? What do I
come out with? Come on, let's hear it.
Well, then these fat ugly people ain't
got a life on YouTube. Yeah, they don't.
That they self-reflect. Yeah, that spoke
about their kids in retaliation. Yeah.
What else have you got, man? Come on.
I'd love to hear it.
Nah, but they got in relationship with
Montes, bro. They don't count.
You know, you would be day in day out. What?
Not at all. Not at all. What about all
of the [ __ ] that they do? Like replying
back to negativity and like only
replying back to negativity and [ __ ]
So, no, they're they're not the they're
the ones that are not decent. They're So,
I mean, they're always going to blame
the man no matter
no matter what you um no matter what you
no matter what you uh what you show,
you know. They're always they're always
going to blame you
no matter what you show.
bit like when I went to Mark Sumpson's
area two times. No one ever brings that up,
you know? They No one ever brings that up,
which I know by doing this video I'm
going to get trolled the [ __ ] out of,
but it's just to show people on like
different platforms and [ __ ]
Don't know what I'm not going to eat
until later. I only eat once a day. So yeah,
that Red Star is a sad [ __ ] Nicolo. I
don't even have the energy to go back on
Reddit today. All day, bro. You know
what I've I done for like a day and a
half. He does this all day, every day.
Think about it, bro. Which Well, it's
it's a po
It's a waste of [ __ ] time just saying
this [ __ ] to be honest with you. It's a
it's a waste of time saying all of this
[ __ ] to be fair cuz you you're not going
to understand it anyways just like when
you're showing things. So that's it's
just I mean it's just a waste of time
telling you how sad these people are
because you don't I don't think you
understand the extent of it. So that's
that's even a waste of time now.
We was talking about earlier how I went
to Mark Samson's area twice and no one
ever brings it up.
It was that moment you would know you
was wasting your time with these losers.
Have you ever heard that meme? That's
how you kind of know like don't get into
it with any of these people. Don't show
them money. Don't show them women. Don't
try and meet any of them because they
will do all the same [ __ ]
They would do all the same. They they do
all the same [ __ ]
You know, find that mad joke how no one
ever brings up when I went to Mark's
area two times and he bottled it.
That's how you know. in here, they have
their favorites. So, there's no point.
It's just a disabled community. There's
there's nothing better. There's nothing
you can do on here but rant.
Literally, I I knew then I was wasting
my time cuz you know these pe when these
people go for Mark Samson and they say,
"Oh, he's a bullshitter." Yeah. Four
years later. Yeah. Isn't it funny how no
one ever brings up the time I went to
his area twice and he didn't show up?
You not find that weird? I'm sure you
I'm sure you remember that.
Do you not find that strange?
So yeah, I was speaking to some woman
from Canada yesterday, but she's
disappeared. Here today, gone tomorrow.
Here today, gone tomorrow. I like to
say, you know,
So yeah, that's that's where we're at
basically. That's where we're at, mate. So yeah,
they were mocking you, laughing at you
when you was traveling up and down the
country. They were taking a piss.
How long is it going to take to find
Mrs. Right, Nicolola?
I don't think she's anywhere to be se
anywhere to be found.
Yep. They were mocking you, laughing at you.
That's funny as [ __ ] is it? Yeah. So yeah.
Um yeah, uh being gay is um
um being gay is is a choice is is not a choice. You know,
you have you do have problems. If you
went out approaching women, you would
have problems. If someone 27 like me
that's decent looking is having
problems, you would have problems as
well. Go out today and approach women,
you will have problems,
you would have problems. If I'm having
problems, I can imagine and other people
are having problems. I can imagine you
are having problems as well
in before I'm married. Oh, [ __ ] sake.
Probably say, let's say I'm married or something.
Um, but I mean, if I'm having problems
and all of these other people seem to be
having [ __ ] problems from what I'm
seeing, then how wouldn't you have problems?
So, yeah, that's exactly what a s would say.
That's exactly what a s would say. I
know how to treat a woman. That's That's
exactly what a s would say. Yeah.
I guess this video is going to be Do you
know what? I might not even do the video
on this channel. I might do it on my
other channel to be honest.
There's no point a bunch of [ __ ] disabled people
listening to it. But I would want Joe to
listen to it cuz I feel like he has got
some sort of sense. But I mean it's just
a bunch of disabled people that's going
to be watching it. So I don't think
they'll really understand.
And why would you say go gay when being
gay is not a choice?
Why do people always use that joke, oh
you should go gay? Why why would someone
go gay and just not give up? Why would
they go to the other side when they're not gay?
It's that doesn't make someone gay. You
won't just turn gay cuz you had [ __ ]
with women all your life. You're not
just going to go gay. You know what I mean?
>> You said you know how to treat a woman
when most women are entitled and stuck
up. just come across a simp.
Yeah, it just it just come across a
simp. That's all. Otherwise,
I'll be back later.