[ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] Newport of all [ __ ] teams.
People didn't [ __ ] score. It wasn't
even [ __ ] Bonnet. It's [ __ ] fixed
as [ __ ] Honestly, it is. It's fixed as
[ __ ] bro. And the [ __ ] didn't they
score? We was expecting [ __ ] Bonnet
not to [ __ ] score. How the [ __ ] did
they not score? It's [ __ ] Bollocks.
Absolute [ __ ] A one to one and they
didn't even [ __ ] score. It's
[ __ ] bro. It's [ __ ] bollocks. Yep.
What's this on five 7%.
I done that [ __ ] bet days ago as well.
Yeah, days ago. I done that bit [ __ ]
days ago as well. Absolute [ __ ]
It really is. It is absolute [ __ ]
reason I didn't Yeah.
[ __ ] horrible is it?
How they never scored is beyond me. We
was expecting Barnett to have not [ __ ] scored,
you know. I was expecting Bordick to
have not [ __ ] scored.
Well, how did they not score?
How the [ __ ] did they not score?
How did they score? H They had enough
time to score, you know.
That's depressing. And it doesn't even
feel like a money loss as well cuz I've
done it days ago. It's [ __ ] I
really really should gamble. I shouldn't
gamble me, bro. I really really shouldn't.
Really, really, really, really
shouldn't. You know, even though we only
do the football, I I don't like losing
to [ __ ] You know what I'm saying? I
do not like losing to [ __ ] a load of old [ __ ]
[ __ ] one goal. [ __ ] off. You know,
for the ones I [ __ ] want. You know, yeah.
Yep. They're bastards. I feel like I've
been [ __ ] raped. It's disgusting. I
actually feel like I've been raped. It's horrible.
That's that honestly that is the only
way you can actually put it in it.
That's the only way you can put it.
There's no other way to put it. You
actually feel like you've been [ __ ] raped.
It actually is the truth. I done this
bet days ago as well, bro. And this was
days ago. I done this bet for today.
Yep. They've always got one that ruins it.
Yep. I could have done with that money.
I think anyone could have done with
extra money. You know what I'm saying? I
could have done with that money, you
know? I could have really done with that money, bro.
Cuz it's [ __ ] free money off 90
[ __ ] quid. You know what I'm saying?
I could have done with it. So yeah. Yep.
Sounds about right. just 90
a few days ago. It's [ __ ] [ __ ]
bro. Now I don't even want to go out. I
was going to go out and get some food
from the shop, but now I don't even want
to go out now. It's [ __ ] depressing. Yeah,
it's too depressing, bro. It's [ __ ]
depressing. I hate losing. You know, I
could have done with that [ __ ] 300
and odd pound cuz it's [ __ ] free
money. You know what I mean? What the
[ __ ] You know what I'm saying?
It's depression, bro. It's [ __ ] depressing.
Absolutely [ __ ] depressing.
So now I can't even go out now and get
food. Too depressing, bro. Too depressing.
I didn't. I lost 90 on a double both
teams to score. [ __ ]
It's absolute [ __ ]
That makes you suicidal, bro. It's annoying, bro.
No, I done it a few days ago. It's not
about the money. It's not like 90. I
could have done with the extra money.
No, it's not a lot to lose. It's not
even about the money. It's just I needed
I needed the extra money
kind of. Well, not needed it, but you
know what I mean. Could have done with
it. I think that's that's that's better
word. Not about the 90. I don't give a
[ __ ] about that.
It's [ __ ] depressing, bro.
[ __ ] now. I can't even go out now,
you know? Get some food. It's too
depressing, bro. It [ __ ] feels like
you've been [ __ ] raped. It's horrible, bro.
It's [ __ ] horrible.
It's [ __ ] horrible, mate. [ __ ] horrible.
Don't know how they didn't score, you
know? I don't know how they did not [ __ ] score. No.
Makes you suicidal and [ __ ] don't it? Horrible, bro.
Secular is a bullshitter.
He's a [ __ ] bullshitter. And that's
his footballer. He's a [ __ ] bullshitting [ __ ]
I was going to, but I'm too depressed
now. I can't even do anything. Just that football bet. Yeah.
That's what I was going to get, but
atom simple law J's channel saying that
um oh I need done to me what was done to
rice showing I'm a danger to women I was
like you [ __ ] you coward I went on
his channel I said you what you [ __ ]
coward come and meet me now you cowardly bastard
you cowardly little [ __ ] come and meet
me now you little coward
even writing [ __ ] like that you [ __ ]
coward [ __ ] [ __ ] off, you cowardly little [ __ ]
I'm waiting for a [ __ ] response back.
All that [ __ ] is cowardness. What they
do on here? Cowardness.
I'll be a danger to your [ __ ] mom.
I'll finger the [ __ ] in front of you,
you silly [ __ ] I'll [ __ ] finger the
[ __ ] in [ __ ] in front of you, you silly
You know what I'm saying? I'll be a
danger to your mother who's a woman.
I'll do it in front of you, you silly
[ __ ] I fingered a [ __ ] [ __ ] with
[ __ ] all five fingers.
[ __ ] stupid bastard. Cy little [ __ ] So yeah,
someone commented on L J's.
It makes you want to give up.
It [ __ ] um it makes you want to give
up with life, is it? When you lose a
football bet, it's degrading. It's so
degrading. Like I can't I can't explain
it, bro. I honestly can't explain it.
And I didn't even feel like I lost any
money cuz I'd done this days ago. It It
makes you not want to go out. It makes
you not want to do anything. Even if
it's money you can afford to lose. Mind
you, obviously it's money I can afford
to lose. That's why I put it on there, bro. Annoying, bro.
It's so annoying, bro. I swear to God,
it makes you want to just kill yourself.
You know, I can't even leave the house.
I can't even leave the [ __ ] house, bro.
Seriously, I would I want to smash this
[ __ ] TV up, bro. I'm not even joking.
I want to [ __ ] smash this [ __ ] TV
up. It's [ __ ] annoying, bro. Losing
to one [ __ ] goal. I need I could have
done with that money, bro. Do you know
what I'm saying? What the [ __ ] It's
It's [ __ ] [ __ ] horrible.
No, it just makes you depressed. It
doesn't make you angry cuz this makes
you [ __ ] depressed.
It makes you [ __ ] depressed.
It actually makes you [ __ ] depressed.
It's annoying as [ __ ] You know,
it's annoying as [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, it makes you want to kill
yourself. That's how it gets me like, bro.
Oh my god. Is Virgin Boy showing a £850
holiday? Bro, I done that exact same
holiday when I was 23 years of age.
Get rid of Times, Virgin Boy.
Get rid of [ __ ] Times, Virgin Boy.
What the [ __ ] I done all that [ __ ] when
I was 20 [ __ ] three. That virgin's
just doing it now.
That is insane, lad. What the [ __ ] That
virgin is just do just doing it now.
And I need to come off this [ __ ] as
well. That's another thing I need to
come off this [ __ ] as well. What better
thing you to be arguing with these
[ __ ] fat, ugly, self-reflecting low lives.
That's another thing I was thinking of.
No, I can't even leave the house. I'm too depressed.
I'm too depressed because of it, man.
It's depressing as [ __ ] It's horrible.
I can't even leave the house.
You can't even keep still. You can't do
anything. It controls your whole body
and your whole mind. I wish someone told
me that before gambling.
Your whole body, your whole mind. Is that right?
Your whole body and your whole mind.
your whole body and your whole [ __ ] mind. Yeah. Literally. And it
[ __ ] loos ruining it. Ruining the
fun. You always got one ruin in the [ __ ] fun. Horrible, man.
I know it's a madness in it.
But you you understand what I'm saying
about why I don't get into it with these
people anymore, Nicolola. You
understand? You understand, right?
You know what I mean? It's cuz there's
no point getting into it with these little weirdos.
When you take W's, they like to not
remember it. This is why I don't get
into it with these little mongos
anymore. These little low lives that
live to do this cuz it's pointless. You
know, they like to forget things. You
remember what I said earlier on the Joe
video? They like to forget things. So,
there's no point getting into it with these people.
[ __ ] bro. Absolute [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] it is. Yep.
That'll be the last I ever do a football
bet for sure. You know, the longest I I
stopped doing them was about a year.
But secularist says, as long as you've
got your bills paid, it's all right.
It's not all right. It's not all right.
There's nothing all right about it at all.
You know what's what's all right about
losing to [ __ ] What's all What's
all right about that? You know,
I just want to go back there with a
hammer, bro. I swear to God, I just want
to go back there with a hammer. It's annoying.
Yeah, cuz I'm done in this country. I'm
saving. I'm leaving.
Yeah, I'm done. When I say I'm done, I'm
done. I'm done. I'm leaving.
Can't afford to be going out drinking it
every every week if I'm leaving here.
You know what I mean?
Not interested in it.
I actually feel like going back there
with a hammer, bro. I swear to God. But
I'm not even near one.
I swear to God. Yeah.
I think if I was near one, I actually
would go back with a hammer. Bro, I
swear to God, it's annoying as [ __ ]
Yeah. And I won't be going on a drink
for ages. Even if I wanted, I wouldn't have.
Nah. Can't be asked. Same [ __ ]
Same [ __ ] Same cycle. Is it right, Boozy?
like just going outside and just doing
something in. Bro, I don't like that. I
don't like to be around people. I don't
like to be around people like on the
street. I just want to [ __ ] hurt
someone, bro. I swear to God.
I want to hurt someone. Yeah.
Or a weight bar. Or a metal weight bar
is probably better than a hammer.
You want to take my [ __ ] money? I'll
[ __ ] take yours and I'll send it to
I'll send it to Ant-Man. Yeah. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Horrible. It is [ __ ] horrible. It is.
I don't give a [ __ ] if it's only money.
It's [ __ ] annoying. I don't give a
[ __ ] It's [ __ ] annoying as [ __ ] I
swear to God if I was near a bookies,
bro. I swear to God I would be going
back with a [ __ ] weight, bro. I swear
to God, bro. If I was back in the old
house, I'm surrounded by bookies. I
would just go back to any one of them
and smash it up. I swear to God, it's
annoying. I don't give a [ __ ] you know? So yeah,
I would bro 100%.
Cuz it's annoying,
is it, bro? It's annoying as [ __ ]
It is so [ __ ] annoying. Oh my god, it
is annoying, bro.
So [ __ ] [ __ ] and annoying, bro. Is it?
Why the [ __ ] didn't they score? Huh? Why
Say I could just get an Uber there and
smash it up and then come back
to be honest.
Don't know if I have a hammer though to be honest.
I don't think I do
this. Do I? No.
You You allowed to go with a hammer. You
have to go with a weight bar as well.
Cuz if you go with a hammer, you get in
serious trouble cuz it's a pointy thing in it.
I want to go back there and smash it up,
bro. I'm not going to lie.
Yeah, I want to go back there and smash
it up. It's [ __ ] annoying, bro.
So yeah, I can't even go out now. I
can't even go to your shop. It's that depressing.
So [ __ ] depressing, bro.
[ __ ] horrible it is.
I don't want to go out.
[ __ ] go out now.
Happened like last week, bro. Or the
week before that. It happened the week
before last, I think.