Yeah.
Well, when that [ __ ] comes back, he'll
be getting it as well.
I don't know how these fat ugly people
on here can try to call anybody a moment
when we've actually seen what these
people actually look like. We've
actually seen these people and they are
the biggest mters of all time. I don't
know how these people of all people,
bro, of all people can come on here and
try to call me a MTO when I'm better
looking than all of these fat ugly
people, bro. But tell them to put their
[ __ ] camera on. Tell them to put
their [ __ ] camera on.
Tell them to put their [ __ ] camera on.
Tell them to put their camera on.
[ __ ] their car, bro. These people, I
don't know how they think they can call
anyone a M. That's what makes me laugh,
bro. It's amusing to be fair.
It's amusing in a way how they can try
how they think they can call anyone a manta.
I think this has got to be the first day
in the whole
in years. I ain't ate. You know, some
people can go a day without eating. I
can't. That just put me right off my
appetite. That football bet put me right
off my appetite, bro.
I'm thinking of ordering stuff
something, but then
what's the time? I said, I probably
won't even eat today. I never go in
there without eating, bro. I know that's
normal for some people. That's [ __ ] depressing, bro.
I was near bookies. One of them would it
would have got it today, bro. I swear to
God it would have got it. Any one of
them. Any [ __ ] one of them.
I'll give you just gambling. You win
some. You [ __ ] lose some. You [ __ ]
I'll [ __ ] give you a [ __ ] You win
some, you [ __ ] lose some.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] All right. Yeah.
I eat today. [ __ ] that. can't e
and I would say that is pretty much
gambling responsibly. That is
That is pretty much Ging responsibility
responsibly. 90 a couple of days ago.
Yeah, that's fine, bro.
We're still up. I just [ __ ] hate
losing. I can't stand losing to
[ __ ] You know what I'm saying? I
can't stand losing to [ __ ] You
don't even know the [ __ ] I [ __ ] done today, bro.
Bang up. My mom starting on her starting
on people and [ __ ] Yeah, [ __ ] damn
[ __ ] right, bro. Damn [ __ ] right.
Form of entertainment. My [ __ ] ass.
[ __ ] stupid little [ __ ] You're lucky
I'm nowhere near a [ __ ] bookies.
So anyway, since you like to come on
here and you keep calling people Ma, why
don't you all show your faces? I'll put
a link up there when um uh
I'll put a link up when more people
join. Let's see your faces.
Let's see your faces, bro. You should
put your faces up there, bro.
because I lost the football bet. It was
annoying. I started some mad [ __ ] today, bro.
That was like the final [ __ ] straw.
Yeah, I started some mad [ __ ] bro. I
ain't going to lie. [ __ ] annoying.
Annoying as [ __ ] it is. Yeah.
Remember people, it's just a form of entertainment.
Just a form of entertainment. So they
say, "Fuck off, you silly [ __ ] I can't
even go and get food now. I have to
starve today. I can't even get food. I'm
agitated cuz of it. It's [ __ ] annoying.
Oh my god, it is so [ __ ] bastard annoying.
So lucky I'm not near bookies, bro. Like
I was back at the old house. Trust me,
they would have been smashed up today.
I'm not even joking.
No, I didn't didn't get it. I can't eat.
I can't eat. I probably won't eat today,
to be honest, cuz of that football bet.
It's [ __ ] depressing, bro. Nah, I
can't I'm not even in the mood to go up
the road and get it. Nah.
Nah. It affects you so bad, man. Secular
SW told me this [ __ ]
but he says once you've got all your
bills paid and [ __ ] it's fine.
Nothing's fine about it at all.
I think it's [ __ ] depressing. I don't
understand how he can think it's fine.
I just rang up people and started on
them and [ __ ]
And I was getting on with them as well,
like family and [ __ ] but I just started
on him because it's annoying. You know
what I mean?
Lucky I'm not smashing this [ __ ] TV.
I've smashed the house up before a few
times. It's annoying, bro. [ __ ] It is [ __ ] annoying.
I hate it, bro. I swear to God, I
[ __ ] hate it.
Should I have to starve today?
I can't eat like that, bro.
I can't eat like that.
I've had to take some cocoon more as well.
So, yeah, I'll starve today. I think
I'm not in the mood. Not in the [ __ ]
mood, lad. Not in the [ __ ] mood at
all. [ __ ] that. Absolutely [ __ ] that.
Yep. So now it seems I can't even do
football bets. Wow.
I can't even do football bets now.
How depressing is that?
Oh yeah. So, when that doggy comes in,
I'm going to start on him, by the way,
cuz I've caught him being two-faced,
which is what a lot of these people do
on here, they they lick your ass on here
and then they talk [ __ ] on L. I don't
know how they can try to call me a manta
when I'm better looking than all of
these old men, these old wrinkly men
that ain't got a life. How they try to
talk about the way I look, bro, is
beyond me. It's up up and [ __ ] beyond me, bro.
You know? Yep. pretty much
and I'll just end up starting on someone
in the shop,
you know? So
up up and [ __ ] beyond me, bro. I'm
telling you. These fat, ugly people on
here trying to talk about other people's looks.
Come on, bro. It's embarrassing. Now, we
all know that these people are the
absolute munters, you know? It's been
proven multiple multiple times with the
bomb, with Pat Mustard, with [ __ ] gay
cat, you know, they're all fat and ugly
how they talk about tried to talk about
anyone else, bro. It's crazy.
Really, really, really, really crazy.
It's madness. It's actually madness. I'm
better looking at all of them and then
they tried to call me a ma. It's [ __ ]
madness, bro. [ __ ] crazy, bro. Look at it.
They are the alltime hunters.
They are the actual alltime hunters.
Trust me, bro. They are. Yeah. No,
no, I'll just be like abrupt.
I would just be abrupt. That's what I
would do. I would just be abrupt.
I already started on my mom, so
over the phone and [ __ ] So, yeah. Yeah,
if I live near bookies today, bro, I'm
telling you. I'm telling you, I would
have went. You have my words, but I
would have went.
cuz it's annoying. But I could have done
with that money, you know, wherever it was.
No, obviously not
Yeah, it's [ __ ] depressing, isn't it?
I probably won't eat today. Yay.
Football put me off my food. Yeah.
cuz you're already pissed off as it is
with life and [ __ ] women and [ __ ]
and then you got that [ __ ] pissing
you off. You know what I mean?
[ __ ] depressing, isn't it, bro? Yep. [Laughter] Yeah.
Yeah. I start on everyone.
Yeah. I thought I don't even have cloaking either.
Yeah, I started on everyone, bro.
I need to come off this YouTube thing
soon, but honestly,
all jokes aside,
don't need to know where I live, but I
started on everyone. So, this whole
community is so weird. You got these
fat, ugly, disabled people, right, sat online stalking,
going at people every day that they
don't even [ __ ] know. They're [ __ ]
weirdos, bro. Anyone would think you've
actually met these [ __ ] people in this community.
Fat ugly people sat skinned ain't got a
life on YouTube every day trying to talk
about other people, trying to preach
about other people, bro. It's a madness.
How do these [ __ ] fat ugly people?
Yeah. I started on my mom and
everything, bro. I said I'm going to
smash her [ __ ] faces and [ __ ]
I said, "You're not getting your [ __ ]
um you're not getting your birthday card now. Yeah,
there's nothing too smash up of it on my
own things. Like I said, if I live near
if I live near a bookies, no.
See, it makes you bully people losing
the bet and [ __ ] It makes you turn you
a nasty person, these women and
gambling. It's horrible. It's horrible.
But secular slot says it's a form of entertainment.
I couldn't sm if I if I had been here
bookish I would have smashed the bookies
up bro 100%.
100% I would have you know not smashing
my own things. Why am I going to smash
my own things?
Why am I going to smash my own things up?
No, I've done that before. Smashed up
mugs and [ __ ] but I knew I could just
replace it. I'm not going to go smash a
[ __ ] 500 lb TV, am I? You know,
it just makes you start on people for no
reason. It's horrible.
You win some, you lose some. That's what
I was going to do. Go back back there
with a [ __ ] weight ball, bro, and
jump on the table saying, "Wins some,
lose some." Well, it's my lucky day now
because your whole [ __ ] shop smashed
up. Win some, lose some, win some, lose
some. That's what I would have done. Yeah.
Win some loss. Winam lam winam lam winam lam.
You know what I'd love to do if USA Izzy
was in front of me? Do you know what? I
wouldn't even smash her up. Do you know
what I'll do? I'll just do this squeezy
and spit in her mouth and make her
swallow it. That's what I do. I'd spit
in the [ __ ]
That's what I do. I'd spit on the
[ __ ] [ __ ] Just spit on the [ __ ]
Nothing else. Just a big fat spit. spit
through her throat. He sent it to her
[ __ ] dad. Yeah.
I don't have any new numbers. I have
numbers. Obviously, I've got numbers, but
you know, there's no point.
Oh, I know where you live. I'm going to
call the police. I said, "Call the
police. I'll smash the police up today.
I don't give a [ __ ] Call the police all
you want and you see what will be
happening. Call the police all you want
and you'll see what happened." Yeah. Simple. No.
I've spat on one person. Yeah. In
Nottingham. Yeah. Cuz she was being a
[ __ ] So I spat at her. Yes.
Can't believe that bet never Um, [Laughter] this man,
>> I'm just being back in [ __ ]
Stratford. I prefer that area.
I'd prefer that [ __ ] area than here.
It's a depressing life. It sure is.
Sure is a depressing life.
No, I got no reason to go there. I miss
it there. I miss all the people and
all the people that live there and I
knew all the neighbors and [ __ ] I miss it there.
It's the best thing. My mom um
chucking me out that time.
It all worked out in the end because I
became stronger from it. You know, I
become a stronger person because of it.
And yeah, I was forced to do things I
might have not done.
So yeah, it won't be now. I ain't got no
money to go there.
Not now, mate. I ain't got no money to
[ __ ] go there.
I like that area more, I think.
I like that area because I don't know,
it was more for me.
I think it, like I said earlier, I think
it was better for your mental health that area.
That wasn't my f. I never went drinking
there. I'd always go central London. I
might have had one or two, but that
weren't my favorite pub. I'd never I'd
never stay there till it closed.
My favorite pub was the O'Neal and Water Street. Yeah.
No, I like that O'Neal's Water Street.
That was my favorite.
You know the manager in O'Neal? He lives
on my road. Like when I was in
Stratford, I said, "Oh, you're O'Neils,
isn't it?" Like he literally lives in
Mer he actually lives in Maryland.
even though it's in central London. He
lives in Maryland. Um
I was like, "Oh, oh, I've seen you."
When I saw him again, I was like, "Oh,
he lives on my road."
Um well, put it this way, their staff
never change. That bouncer's been there
for about 15 years, and one of the
manager never changes. So,
I mean, I could go in there at about
5:00 p.m. and stay there for like 5 6 hours, but
I could stay there until, but obviously
I'd have to stay in the toilets until
like the bounces and [ __ ] come. So, I
mean, I could probably, but it's just
not worth it.
Um, yeah, we used to rinse that place, bro.
I'm B from one of the weather spoons. Yeah.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. What are
you going to do? Yeah. You remember when
I when I sneaked in, he said, "Oh, you
can come back in 3 months." I tried
sneaking in. The [ __ ] just as I opened
the toilet to the toilet door to get out
of it, he opened it to get in it.
I cost you £50. I cost myself almost
£100. You stupid [ __ ]
Uh, I cost myself [ __ ] 100 [ __ ]
pound, you stupid bastard. About [ __ ]
50 [ __ ] quid. I'm [ __ ] leaving in [ __ ] November. Um, yeah,
Simmons and other pubs.
There's another one I wanted to hit up.
There was a brewery I wanted to hit up,
but I don't go anywhere now. I drink now. So,
I feel bad for bullying Laney Grezy.
I could have done with that money.
I could have done with that [ __ ]
money, bro. Yeah. Okay. I might have
14,500, but I could have still done with
that £300 extra. Bro, what the [ __ ]
Where else am I [ __ ] getting it? I
could have done with that extra bit of
money. You don't understand. It doesn't matter. Yep.
I don't need to go there anymore.
I could have done with that extra bit of
money, bro. It doesn't matter how much I
have. I could have done with that extra
bit of money.
Yeah, no point going to them places.
What's the point? You just get I've got
a boyfriend. I've got a boyfriend. I've
But in a way, I'm not.
In a way, I'm glad I tried cuz I know
the truth. At least I now I've gave up.
At least I can say I've actually tried.
So like that's once you know you've tried,
you know, you can retire in peace and
just leave, you know.
So I know I know how it is. Yeah.
I [ __ ] hate women. One second. So yeah.
No, it will never happen in London,
mate. It will never happen in London, you know.
>> Yeah, I got banned from one of the
Simmons, but I'm allowed back in it now,
bro. They That's what I'm saying. They changed staff.
They change management and they change staff.
So they'll ban you for like a week and
then you go back and then you're allowed in.
I could probably go back to that one now
with that Polish bouncer. Which to be
honest, it wasn't even his fault. It was
them complaining to him. I didn't even
do anything wrong. What? Trying to
change my mutral status? That's a
[ __ ] crime. You know what I mean?
What the [ __ ]
So what? Me trying to change my mal
status? That's a crime.
And obviously they snitched the bouncer
and then [ __ ] obviously the bouncer
has to do what they say. So it's
actually the management in there. So
what? Me trying to change my mal status?
No, it's not him. He's all right. It was
the other one that [ __ ] found me.
Jamie his name is and I had a go at him.
I did tell him about himself. I've
already told him about himself months ago.
I said that [ __ ] started on me [ __ ]
first. I said yeah. Walk away cuz you
know I'm right. I've started on him already.
Yeah. His name is Jamie.
Found his Facebook. I was going to
message him some [ __ ] but there's no point.
And they're never changing staffing at
O'Neil's. They're never changing
staffing at O'Neals, mate. Never.
Never changing stuff.
Never in a million years.
I remember when I used to go there
January and no one was there.
No one was there. So I had to stop going.
because people don't collide with me.
Do you think that's bad bullying? Laney Grezy.
I could I could [ __ ] own Laney with one finger.
It's that bad.
I know. I kept them in business for for
a very very long time.
No one did. I always kept them in
business. Only me and the army lads used
to go in there continuously.
I kept them in business, bro. Even in
January and they wanted to ban me.
I said, "All right, your loss."
I had to deal with, do you know how many
[ __ ] I had to deal with in that place?
You know, the first time I was supposed
to go to America and obviously I had to
be careful what I was doing and saying
in case it got nicked and a lot of times
I felt like punching one of them in the
[ __ ] face. I had to deal with their
[ __ ] for a very long time, you know. And
yeah, it's mad. I might message him on
Facebook, you know. I should say you you
you should give me a medal, bro.
You should give me a [ __ ] medal, bro.
You know, I I had to go through a lot of [ __ ]
with people in that place. But I got I
got friends with like all the people and
all the security knew me and Oh yeah,
I could have done with that 3 320. I
could have done with it, mate.
Could have done with it.
I'm surprised I didn't go back to them
roulette days. I can't, bro. So, if I
went back to them roulette days, I'd be [ __ ] now.
I don't get the extra money, so I'd be
[ __ ] Oh, man.
Yeah, I would have went out. I wouldn't
I wouldn't have went out at all regardless. Nah.
No point going out. No,
just to hear I've got a boyfriend. I've [ __ ] off.
[ __ ] off, mate.
You can't even win big now, can you? On
in the UK sites cuz they ask you for
proof of everything's gone [ __ ] You
can't win money gambling. You can't pull
women. You can't do [ __ ] all. It's
[ __ ] [ __ ] isn't it?
You know, if you Let me tell you
something about these places like
O'Neal's and all of these places. If it
wasn't for foreigners, they would have
gone bust a long time ago. You know
that? Cuz most people in this country
are broke. You know, most people in this
country are broke. You know that. So the
only people that are keeping them in
business are actual foreigners that come
from another country. America,
Australia, they're the ones that are
keeping them in business. If they didn't
have them people, they would have gone
bust because most people here are skin.
They don't even go out drinking. It's
people from other countries bringing the money in.
Do you know what I'm saying?
Very uh a lot of people are very most
people are skinn here. So
it's money coming from abroad, you see.
Could have done with that money, mate.
Could have done with that money.
Because who wouldn't? You know what I'm saying?
What do you think of the Uber pay,
Nicola? Was it good money? Uber Eats money. Yeah.
I don't want a Chinese. I don't want an
Indian. I want a Chinese.
What do you think of the Uber Eats money?
But if you don't see me come back on
here one day, don't don't say I didn't
tell you, bro, that I'm going to be done
with this [ __ ] soon
cuz it's just weird. Very weird. Very biased. Um
pointless being on here really. [ __ ]
fat, ugly old people calling you what
they are themselves.
Yeah, you got to use a VPN.
What do you think of the Uber Eats money?
Uber Eats pays good. I remember one time
it took me [ __ ] 8 hours to make 50 quid.
Uh he got banned cuz he's got a criminal record.
He's got a criminal record. So,
yeah. So, I can't make extra money now.
I can't even make extra money now. What a life.
It's a [ __ ] life, ain't it?
Yeah, that was only one day, though.
Normally, it's it's £10 an hour, but it
was just it was just bad that day
because he probably saw it for what it
is. It's a it's it's a weirdo site full
of [ __ ] fat ugly people that ain't
got a life, bro.
But he did leave.
Yeah, that was a Sunday. I don't know
why it was bad that day, but normally
it's £10 an hour. So, it's better than
nothing, could it?
If you done six hours a day, every other
day a week, you know, you'll get
don't know why it was so bad. I don't
It's the orders or something.
I need to order some [ __ ] Chinese somehow.
Yes. It's not supposed to be a main job.
Yeah. It's not a main job. It's a side
hustle, which is what a lot of people don't understand.
It's a side hustle. It's not a main job. So, yeah.
I'll just go and read it later. [ __ ] it.
Yeah, it's not a main job.
It's a side hustle.
That's what it's supposed to be used as.
It's not a main job. So, yeah, if you
done six, five, six hours every other
day, you'll be laughing at the end of the week. So, yeah.
But or if you put mad hours in, then
obviously it would pay out in it. So yeah.
No, cuz local areas you're not going to
I done it in I done it in Leicester
Square cuz if I done it in Stratford,
you're not going to make any money. So,
I can't believe Virgin Boy want is so
desperate to like
make people con to convince people that
he's got money and he's got he's got
nothing, bro. He's got absolutely [ __ ]
all. He used to always be the same. Used
to think that he had money. Even when I
met him, he literally got nothing. It's funny, bro.
Oh, looks nice.
He literally has got not a [ __ ] pot
to piss in. And he thinks he's got
money. Oh, man. Chicken balls.
Where's the chicken balls? I can't find
these chicken balls anywhere. It's also
Okay, you can choose the hot on here.
Why can't you choose? I want these
chicken balls, bro.
Why don't they have them?
And they don't even have coke either.
This is a joke today, ain't it? Trying
to order this.
So Jo trying to order this. I'm not
going out. I'm not going out.
Yeah, I had ice. I'm not going out. I
just won't have anything.
I'm not going out. I should have to go
I'm [ __ ] starving here. You know what
I'm saying? I'm not going out. I'm not
in the mood to go around waiting waiting
around for things.
And I don't want a And I don't want an Indian either.
I want like a [ __ ] beef name, bro.
You know what I'm saying? Nope.
Hope I die in my sleep, bro. This life
is [ __ ] man. It never changes. I'm
[ __ ] done with it.
Done with this life, bro. It's boring as [ __ ]
I hate this life, bro. Feels
like torment being alive every day. Does
it feel like that for anyone else? Like
torment. Like someone's laughing at you.
I hate it. Know what I'm saying?
You can't find these chicken wings to
save these chicken balls to save your
life. You can't find the [ __ ]
to save your [ __ ] life.
These chicken boards to save your life, mate. One second.
It's [ __ ] horrible, bro. I'm not
going out. I need to go out to this
[ __ ] Chinese and I'm not going out, bro.
Ain't going out.
I ain't going out. [ __ ] that.
I'll just starve.
I'm not in a mood to go out. I'll end up
punching someone, bro. I'll end up
smashing someone in their [ __ ] face. Trust me.
I end up smashing someone in the [ __ ]
face. Trust me. You don't know what I'm
not in a mood, bro.
[ __ ] rape victims. A lot of them. No,
I ain't got We got We ain't got I ain't
got nothing. I got [ __ ] all in the
fridge. I don't do food shopping. I just eat out.
I got nothing, bro. I I ain't been shopping.
too depressed to go shopping, too
frustrated to go shopping.
I don't do anything anymore. So
yeah, I don't do anything anymore, bro.
I'll just be having tea today by the
looks of it.
[ __ ] I wish I could die, bro. Eating
once today I didn't eat today.
I didn't eat at all today. Too frustrated.
If I drop dead, I wouldn't care. I
if I dropped dead. I really wouldn't care, bro.
I hate living, bro. That's comment.
Why don't you [ __ ] Chinese, bro?
I wouldn't care if I died, bro.
At least I've been to a lot of places,
isn't it? Um, Nola. Yeah,
I went to a Chinese buffet with the virgin.
I went with the virgin.
I remember that. I went to a Chinese
buffet with virgin boy. Yeah,
I could have just got escort. to travel the world
if I was
Well, I'm still talking to this one in Canada. So,
if she's serious, then I'll just go Canada. Simple.
I don't give a [ __ ]
Where are we speaking? Yep.
What would you say USA is out of 10, Nicolola?
Nah, she's not even average, bro. She's
below average. She's [ __ ] below
I don't miss that [ __ ] virgin.
go out with [ __ ]
Right. I'm going to go have to I'm going
to go have to get this Chinese, bro. So,
I'll I'll be back. [ __ ] sake.