See that [ __ ] [ __ ] heat. Oh, go ahead.
Mhm. Next. Playing the money game. Sure.
Show me two
grand. Yeah, sure. Show me two grand.
showed you 1K the other day.
Yeah. Yeah. But I'll play the money
game. Don't rip out two grand like you
were supposed to on Friday. Was it
Friday? Yeah, it was
Friday. Yeah, I'll play the money game with
you. Yeah, sure. Two
grand. Oh my god. Not all not this
[ __ ] autistic conversation again. [ __ ] hell,
bro. Let me ask you this question. Why
are you people on there so obsessed with
money? Like I don't understand what what
would you do right now? Let me ask you this
question. If it What would you do right
now if you had
money? Answer me, bro. Like you people
come on here every day. Yeah. You don't
even leave your houses. What would you
do if you actually had money? You're not
going anywhere, but you're not doing anything with
it. That's what makes me think it's
autism because people with autism get
obsessed with things like that. Money
and and [ __ ] where
money still you still can't show
up. It's a bad
man. It really really
is. It is
bro. I'm sorry. I'm going to sleep. just
watch some YouTube there to be fair.
Exactly. You win again. Oh dear. Well, I
haven't seen you show 12 grand yet. So, yeah.
into the fourth of
March. Uh, really? Bye-bye
now. [ __ ] sake. I could have done that.
I don't have a possible do it.
Yeah, I would have done that. Got any more
passport? What is it anyways, bro? Yes.
[ __ ] What was that? Yeah.
Yeah, such [ __ ] simps is absolutely unbelievable.
That shot simps. I swear
down. I've not had much to say about
women. [ __ ] hell. Who's the biggest
s? Um, well, there's only one sim really that I've seen. L
J. I actually done a video for LJ J, but
I haven't uploaded it yet. Um, the only
one that does it is L J.
Really? Yeah. From what I've seen. Yeah.
It's so bad how like Oh yeah, Timmy as
well. Yeah, obviously. But LJ is the the
proper s. He is like the biggest s ever. It's
crazy. It's so mad though. Honey on
money. Like you try to explain to these
people that you're negative towards
women because of your negative
experiences. And no matter how many
times you explain it, it doesn't seem to
grasp in their brain. They've got
short-term memory loss. It's like they
forget. It's like, I don't know how many
times common sense can be explained to
someone. I don't know how many times common
sense can't be explained to can be
explained to someone. They say, "Oh,
maybe you're not working on your
appearance or your approach." You see
what I'm saying? It's always the man's
fault. This is exactly what I'm saying
to you. It's always the man's fault for
their stuck upness and their unrealistic
standards. This is exactly what I'm
talking about. And I'm sure it's not
just Reddit. I'm sure it's other places,
too. They always blame the
man. They've always blamed the man
that's tried everything. I've noticed
that. And they and they said to me um
probably or maybe you know women
apparently women don't have it any
easier. Women don't have it any easier
apparently. Okay, I'm wrong. Women don't
have it any easier. No. No. Women do not
have dating any easier.
No. No, they don't have um No, they
don't have dating any easier. No, I'm
completely wrong. Yeah. Okay.
Yeah, women don't have dating any
easier. I mean, it's it's already been
proven that they that they do. It's
already been proven that they that they
do have it easier, but these people on
Reddit say that they don't have it
easier. But it's actually been proven
that they actually already do. They
literally have dating like a hundred
times easier. But apparently they don't.
And apparently it's my attitude. Okay,
I'm completely wrong. I don't know what
these people want you to say to them,
bro. I really don't know. You
know, [ __ ] me, bro.
I can't do anything without that passport.
They just don't have no bad words to say about
women. Like, tell me, bro. Tell me if
I'm if if I'm wrong here, lad. Yeah,
I've had to send it off for renewal. I
could have made money on that, bro,
today. You know, I could have made money
on that, but I need a passport to verify
myself in this
thing. Reddit scratch were trying to say
that women don't have the don't have it
any easier dating. And it's my
attitude. So, women do not have any dating
easier. Okay. So, they don't have dating
any easier than Yeah, I was thinking of
Tam today actually.
Yeah, but they don't have dating any
easier. Interesting, eh? Yeah. Must be
all in my
head. No, you
don't. No, you don't. Yeah. Apparently,
women don't have dating any
easier. No. Why do I have any news? I
don't care about her. You're the only
one that's obsessed with her, Harry. Not
me. I don't give a [ __ ] about that
[ __ ] slag. Why do you keep going on about
it? Girls don't like people on YouTube.
Yeah, it's always something in it. It's
never It's never the woman's fault, is
it? It's never the woman's fault, is it?
It's always a man's fault. I had
somebody on it on Reddit say, "Oh, maybe
you're not working on your appearance enough.
maybe you're not um approaching in the
right way. I was like, "Oh
boy, these people on Reddit really have
got no life experience, do
they?" Yeah. Apparently dating women
don't have dating any easier.
Apparently, this guy said to me,
"Apparently, it's my attitude and women
don't have it any
easier." Really? So, women don't have
the dating game any easier? Is that what
you're going to really sit there and try
and say to me? Yeah.
So, if I made a dating profile as a
woman right now, I'm not going to get
5,000 likes in an
hour. Yeah. You're going to try and tell
me that I'm not going to get nothing
pretending to be a woman.
But these people really are twisting
applied. Well, Google's wrong. Google is very, very wrong. Yeah.
They just don't have any bad words to
say about women. Where does this come
from? It's It's got to be a disease.
It's got to be a disease. I'm not
disabled. No, but you are.
Bye-bye. It's got to be a disease. It's
got to be some sort of
disease. Yeah, I was on the Celtic
thing, but I couldn't find them. Samuel,
it doesn't let me look at all the
followers. I would have went through a
million of them. It says that the Celtic
FC has got a million followers, but it
didn't let me scroll under a million. I
would have went through every single
million one of them to find that
C. He's got to be with them in that million. Is
it? He's got to be in that
million. They also like lad with jobs. Yeah.
Yeah. They also don't like people that
live with their mom, do they? Don't
forget about that excuse.
that excuse for women, Mr. Fry Cook.
They also don't like and you know what I
said to these um people um boasting,
don't judge a man until you've walked a
mile in these shoes. And they can't say
anything to that because it's the truth.
Don't judge someone unless you walked in
their [ __ ] shoes,
lad. Unless you walked a mile in their
shoes. That's the truth, though.
Yeah, they also don't like people that
live with their mom.
No, I'm not going speed dating. Antman's
already tried speed
dating. Yeah, you keep telling yourself that,
Ghost. Yeah, just that one day in it.
Just that one day your time will come. Yeah.
I don't need you don't need you don't
need 10k, bro. I could go to Thailand
right now if I wanted to and live out
live off the money that I
get, you know, and live off the money I
get. But yeah, speed dating wouldn't be
a bad idea because I mean, you have
technically not tried it. I mean, you
could have, but I I feel like doing it
in London would just be a waste of
time, but yeah, I feel like Yeah, you
might as well. I think it cost like 30
quid. I mean, I can't knock it cuz I've never tried
it. Yeah, it will happen when you least
expect it. Yeah, you never know till you
try. Really, I should have like 20k
saved up already.
No, no, but I could go try right now if
I wanted to and live out the live off
the money I get whilst being out
there if I wanted
to. But I don't know, man. I mean, the
way I see it, Ben, is let me tell you
what the reason the thing that I see is.
Why would a woman need to go speed
dating when she can get any man she
wants? Now, I know these people say that
dating is not any easier for women, but
it is. It is easier for women. Don't let
anyone tell you that it's not, cuz it
is. But why would a woman have to go
speed a she wants?
My out goes are nowhere near 1k. But
when you go out drinking, you spend a
lot. I want to try and save like 2k this month.
Yeah, 20k saved up. Bro, you're [ __ ]
dreaming. Money goes when you spend when
you go out drinking every [ __ ]
week. I don't know why. Why would a
woman I'll try it. I will try it, Ben. I
will try it because I've never tried it.
So, I will try it. But what I'm saying,
yeah, you can't spend fruit. Yes, you
can. Very easy. Yes, you can. Very, very
easy, mate. I spend £700 in a day before
in the summer. Yes, you can. When you
live my lifestyle, yes, you can. Very
easy. Not every month. Yeah. Not every
month, but you can. You can. Yeah.
Yeah, I got loads of disposable,
bro. I've got loads of
disposable. It does make sense. When
you're young, going out is very
expensive. It does make sense. It does.
It makes perfect sense cuz I'm living
proof of it. So, what I'm saying is,
Ben, anyway, is why would a
woman need to go on a date when she can
get um why would she go to speed dating
when she can get any man she wants? It
just doesn't make
sense. But it be it'll be fun for a
laugh. It'll be fun for a laugh.
Anyways, it does make sense. I spent
£600 last week. Passport, haircut,
drinking. It doesn't matter how I have
so much disposable, bro. I'm not getting
into my personal
life. It doesn't matter. But just know that I
do. Yeah, I know. I'm lucky and life
still sucks without [ __ ]
sex. Well, I don't really No, not
really. I don't really have a sex drive
much anymore to be honest. I don't even
waste money on their thought.
So, yeah, I know I'm lucky. E lucky than
probably 80% of
people. Yeah, obviously I don't pay
rent, do I? Yeah, I know it's but I
don't pay rent. So
yeah. But yeah, we're not getting into
my bloody finances anyways. You believe
it? You don't believe it, bro. It I'm
not going out drinking for a
month. I'm not going out drinking for a So
yeah, doesn't matter, bro. It doesn't matter.
It's something called um housing
benefits. Anyways, we're not talking
about my finances anyways. This is not
what this is
about. There we
go. Sorry, man. You
know, Yeah. Lucky. Yeah.
But to be honest, realistically, I'm
probably going to save like 1,500 this
month. Already got that saved. But
yeah, but I'm not going out drinking for
a month or anything. So, I mean,
yeah. Yeah, lad. Well, unless this
person wants to meet next week, this
bartender, but she's probably got a
flake just like always. Yeah.
I lost 300 pound [ __ ] on Friday. No,
Thursday. It was, was it? Yeah,
Thursday. Yeah. Bye-bye, Peter
Griffin. I tell you what, you are
jealous of my looks. I'm not fat and
ugly like you. You loser. Now get
yourself gone, you fat, ugly
loser. Fat, ugly loser. Stalker.
Loser. Fat ugly JB.
It's not in I don't think it's inventory
anymore, but I've already set it
off. I already set it off. So, but
yeah. Yeah, you got a fast track one.
You know, I didn't need it a bit extra.
I just done it normal. So, I'm not going
out for anyways. Bye-bye, Peter
Griffin. How much do you get a month? Ghosting.
H I'm going to have to go a whole month
without drinking and going out. [ __ ]
hell. It's going to be hard again.
It's going to be hard,
man. Going to be [ __ ] hard, isn't it?
Yeah. So, you basically might as well be on benefits
then. Okay. and all those. So yeah, that
[ __ ] bro. You might as well be on
benefits. Yeah, you might
benefits. Yeah, you might as well be on
benefits for real life.
So, somebody is saying that I'm negative
because I'm saying that uh dating is easier for
women. Yeah, probably is. Yeah, I'm
not. Life in benefits is no real life.
Well, if you're only having a grand left
a month after you've paid everything,
then I mean, it's better than working,
is it? Really?
Yeah. Time's a we Scottish [ __ ]
Yeah, I know you
mean. Yes, I know what you mean.
I've got about 2K at the moment. It's
all to myself. Everything's
paid. 2K and everything's
paid. Yeah. Tam's getting [ __ ]
whilst we're sat here getting nothing. I
don't actually know what to do in this
country ghosting because you go out, you
send it, they pretend they got
boyfriends. Dating apps don't work, but
then people wonder why you're
negative. It's crazy, isn't it, bro?
Changing the subject
slightly. What do they expect you to be
like? I'm trying to understand it.
So, they don't like anyone disagreeing with
them. No, no, I know what you're saying.
Yes. Yes, you're right. I need I need I
need to go to the gym, bro. I'm going
[ __ ] I'm doing some madnesses this
year. Yes, I know. But I'm just saying
that what what else are you supposed to be,
bro? Especially if you got needs. I
spent like500 on escorts last
month. You know what I'm
saying? Not the point, bro.
I didn't go out last Friday to get
women, but hearing the make believe
boyfriends was just pissing me off. And
I didn't even just go out for that
purpose. I felt like having a beer today,
actually. Obviously, I'm not going
to. Yeah. Good luck trying to find a
side hustle in this day and age,
mate. Good luck trying to find a side
hustle in this day and age.
Yeah, good luck,
bro. There is no side
hustle. You can't even make money from Deliveroo
anymore. You know, or anything like
that. This person said, "Go to a club
and find someone to hook up
with. Go to go for dating." Yeah.
Doesn't matter. Women can still get sex.
It doesn't matter. Most of the men on
dating apps don't give two shits about
women. They're just in it for sex. Yeah.
Even still, they can still get
more. You know, you can they can still
they can still get more [ __ ] they can
still get more than what any guy can can
get. So, it doesn't matter. You know
what I mean?
Let me put it this way. I guarantee
you a woman has got way more chance of
finding a man that actually wants to
date them than a man that just wants sex
with a woman. I guarantee you, bro. I
guarantee you right now. You know that a
woman can find a
relationship way more easier than a man
can find sex. And that and that is
saying something. That is speaking
volume. So what does that say, bro? You
know, how many women do you know that's
never been in a relationship? Ask
yourself that question. It's
[ __ ] Woman can get a man anytime
she [ __ ] wants. Stop sugar coating
They always have to sugarcoat [ __ ] It's [ __ ] annoying,
bro. Stop [ __ ] sugar coating
[ __ ] But but they're trying to make out
like they don't have it easier. Oh yeah,
but the men that they go with just want
sex, so sex is better than
anything. Yeah, but they like this kind
of men. Yeah, but but the women like
these kind of men. No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. Because the women like
these kind of men and also the women
will not give a nice guy a chance.
See, the difference is when we
generalize all women, it's because we've
never been shown any different. When
women generalize men, that's the men
that they choose. That's the men that
they go for. You know, there's a big
difference. That's the men that's the
women that that's the men that they exclude themselves
to. So, they are the actual ones that
like these people, but they compare
everyone to the people that like me.
I've never been shown any different. In
27 years, I can't ever tell you I found
a woman that weren't
different. I can't generally tell you I ever have, you
know, so they
have there's literally nothing you can
do. I mean, you can go out and approach,
but I mean, they're just going to
pretend they got boyfriends, as you
know, or ghost you. So yeah, there's
nothing you can do. You're just forced
to be single and you're forced to be
sexist. But then they wonder why people
are in sales. Then they wonder why
people are negative. They're negative
because of the way things are and that's
what they have to go off by. But they
don't ever want to admit any fault. They
just like blaming
men, you know? It's the same old bro.
It's been going for [ __ ] years. They
don't want to take no
responsibility, you know.
It's a madness, isn't
it? Yeah, they have it way more easier.
I'll message this person.
You see what I'm saying? Like they they
don't want to
um they don't want to take no
responsibility. They just want to blame
all men. This is this is what I'm trying
to say. They don't think the dating game
is easier for them. They don't want to
admit that they're any fault of
anything. They just want to be seen as
innocent and men are the ones to blame.
Look, I just said, "Yeah, look, the
dating game is rigged against men. They
won't have it." Even though we've done
studies to prove it, they won't have it, you
know, and that's why I'm so bitter and I
hate it that the dating a game is rigged
against you and there's nothing you can do about
it. That's that's the [ __ ] that pisses
me off. It's not even just so much about
the experiences. It's the fact that
there's nothing you can do. And if you
try to do anything, you're just going to become more
frustrated. You know, even if you go out
and you keep trying, it's just going to
make you worse.
So, there's nothing you can do to change
your situation unless you go to [ __ ]
Thailand. There's nothing you can do to
make it better. That's the [ __ ] up thing, bro.
You know, I can go out this Saturday and
approach it and it would be the same
thing. I've got a boyfriend. I've got a
boyfriend. I'm too old for you. I'm too
young for you. Or I'm lesbian. You know,
we've heard it all before, bro. It's
boring. You know what I'm saying?
So they don't go through all the wies
and the druggies. They generally choose
them people. They will only
go for them
people. You know what I'm saying, bro?
And it's not just a London thing. So
they like them kind of people.
They're either drug dealers, black men,
or white guys with tattoos. That's the
only see people they they seem to have
this type that they go for that they specifically go
for. So, don't try to give them any
sympathy or anything cuz they're the
ones that choose these people, bro. Cuz
they've got with them in the first
place, you know?
You get what I mean? So
yeah, I don't like talking about it to
be honest. You just wiped me up, bro.
Let's change the subject. [ __ ] whip
me up, man. [Music]
This guy ain't talking about it, bro. Yeah.
Never been a s in my life, mate. Never
have, never will. You know these people
that s like L J, they they never get no
women. They they think by defending
women, women will like them, but they
they don't. Women don't like these
people, but yet they don't have a bad
word to say about women. But here's the
point, okay? Let me tell you this for
example. Yeah, maybe it's harder for
women to find relationships, but guess
what? They can still get sex. They can
still get way more than a man can
get. So a woman, it would be easier for
a woman to find a relationship than a
guy to find just sex. That speaks
volume. So stop talking
[ __ ] So stop talking [ __ ]
[ __ ] It's [ __ ] What they're
saying is [ __ ] We know the dating
game is rigged against men. Why are they trying to
front? Trying to make all these excuses.
Oh, but they only just want us for sex,
mate. I done a I done a dating profile
of this Morgan, right, with filtered
photos. Three filtered photos of an
average looking person and I got 5,000 likes. [ __ ]
off. Simple. Stop trying to And I wasn't
told. See, with with with these with
these men, right? I tell you what it is.
This is what they they tell these men.
They need to work on themselves. They
need to get a good job. They need to be
this. They need to be that. They need to
eat three times a day. They need to wash
their ass 13 times a [ __ ] day.
They've got all these requirements for a
man, but a woman has to jump on a dating
app and has the most shittiest filtered
pictures and she can get any man she
wants. [ __ ] off, bro. Even like that
thing with the dating app. The dating
app thing. Oh. Um, the dating app thing.
What was it with the dating apps? She
was They were like, "Oh, um, yeah, you
need better pictures of you with hobbies
or you with friends. Do you think a
woman needs dating apps with friends or
hobbies? She would only need two [ __ ]
pictures of her [ __ ]
face." So, that's the point I'm trying
to make. It's rigged against you. Dating
is rigged against
you. And and and it doesn't even stop
there because even if you meet someone
then when you get ghosted, it's probably
because they found someone better. When
you get ghosted by these women, what it
probably is is because they found
somebody better, so they don't care.
So, the only thing you can Yeah. The
only thing you can do is go to a [ __ ]
town where everyone looks like
crackheads. You know, you might think to
yourself, well, why have I go why is
this person spoken? They haven't met me
when they were supposed to meet me.
Yeah, ghosting should be criminal.
Yeah, people need their feet chopped off
for [ __ ] ghosting, bro. I believe
that. Yeah, for
real. For real,
lad. Doesn't matter if I'm a virgin or
not. It's annoying, mate. I might as
well look like
slug. Still skin and single. Never been
skint, mate. I showed a load of money on
Friday. You didn't show me any
money. I showed you. You You've always
been skinting single and you're still a
virgin. Go self-reflect on another
channel, little virgin loser. Got
nothing going for
yourself? Nah, it shouldn't be that
though. It shouldn't be like
that, you know. It shouldn't be like
that. I don't agree with it, you know.
So that's why I'm [ __ ] probably not
going to try for a long last time to be
honest. But I might as well look like
Timmy Aldridge to be
honest. Why don't they want to admit
that they've got the upper
hand? I don't understand why they don't
want to admit they've got the upper hand
in dating. Okay. Okay. Okay. I I'll tell
you again. I went out with my friend
about two months ago who's a girl. We I
approached people. She approached
people. Guess what? She never got
rejected once. She never got rejected
once. I got rejected I think every
time. Um maybe I got one number. I can't
remember. But I remember she didn't get
rejected once. And she also had men
approach her. But a dating game rigged
against men. That's all in our head.
We're negative. Even though you've seen
it with your own eyes, you've
experimented it with your own eyes. It's
all in your head. Well, what do you know, Daz?
You know, maybe these things I'm
dreaming. Maybe I'm Maybe I'm dreaming,
lad. And why would you want to play a
game that's rigged against you? That's
the way I see it, lad. Why would you
want to play a game that is rigged against
you? Think about it. Dayton is rigged
against you, lad.
It doesn't make sense.
Yeah. So, yeah.
What makes me laugh is that they give
sex to these men. You're saying that
these men only want sex, but you give
sex to these
men. You know, this country annoys me,
bro. This country really annoys me. I'm
not going to lie to you, bro. It [ __ ] annoys me. You
know, so what if they're just looking
for sex? You give sex to these people.
No one said nothing about the videos I sent
them. Yeah. The only way we can take
back control is if we stop giving these
people attention and simp stop sing.
Then you'll get the control back. That's
the only way you're going to get the
control back. if people stop sing and stop white
knighting and stop giving them
attention, you know, that's the only
way. But that's never going to happen.
The social ma media has made it too easy for simps, you
know. It's made it too easy for simps to
go on their little keyboard and lick women's
asses. Just being alpha. Try that. They
have boyfriends apparently.
Yeah, you should try that in London,
bro. Maybe they won't tell you they got
boyfriends. Yeah, they've all got make
believe. They've all got invisible
boyfriends. They've all got invisible
boyfriends. Invisible boyfriends,
demanding for you.
It's like alter ego. What do you think
is realistically going to happen if I go
out Saturday approaching? What do you think is
realistically going to
happen? Tell me what do you think
realistically is going to happen.
Whether we think this or whether we
think that, what do you think
realistically is going to
happen? Uh, no,
no. Exactly. So, but then when we say
these things, we're told that we're
negative. But when you speak the truth,
you're told that you're negative. So I I
I don't understand what what you speak
the truth, you're
negative, you know. So what do you want
me to do? Be a liar. No one likes a
liar. It's like they won't have any
truth spoke about women. If if it's in a
negative way, they they won't have it.
I've been told to delete my YouTube
videos. I've been told to, you know, do
this and that. They just don't have no
[ __ ] bad words to say about
them. It's It's crazy, bro. It's crazy.
They don't even want to admit they've
got the upper hand in the dating game.
Oh, no. Uh men just look for sex. Oh,
no. No, no. That's [ __ ] There's
plenty of men that want
relationships. I'm sure you could find a
man that wants a relationship within a
week that would date you. Stop being
foolish, you know.
But and it's also down to your race as
well. They're very racist women in London. Um you
know in London they either like really
white people or black people cuz I'm
don't obviously look white. So that's
why I don't really get
anything because of your
look. Sorry. Because I look I don't look white. Sorry. One sec. So
yeah, you're at a bad age though. I
think younger or even older would be
okay, but mid late 20s is the worst. I
think so, too. Yeah. If you was probably
like 14, 15 where people haven't discovered Instagram
yet or any of these things, but saying
that they probably have nowadays
or Yeah. Oh, you're in your like mid30s.
Yeah, I reckon so.
Maybe. Cuz the thing is with women in
their 20s, they look they want the
perfect man. They want the perfect man
that don't exist. They're looking for
this perfect man that does not exist.
Don't let them tell you otherwise. They
look for this perfect man that don't
exist. And then even if they did exist,
um they wouldn't want them. So they go
through their whole 20s realizing,
"Fuck, I didn't find this person." And
then by the time they're like 32, 33, 35
onwards, then they want to settle down
when they've had a child by somebody
that's used them and abused them.
They're scum. Women are scumbags. You
know, I have I've had I've had way more
women than LJ, way more women than Nex.
And I hate them. I actually hate them.
Like, I'm not I'm not even joking. I
generally hate them, bro. You
know? Yeah. They want They would rather
have nothing than No less than
perfect. No less than perfect. They'd rather have
nothing. Look, you saw me. I went out on
Friday with my Stone Island jumper. The
as of hissing it up. I didn't get [ __ ] all. Four
numbers. Three replied and stopped. The
bartender said she's going to meet me
next week. We'll see. Yeah. Fat chance
of that happening. I think out of them
four numbers, only one didn't
reply and then Yeah, they just [ __ ] you
around and lead you on. They're evil,
lad. They're [ __ ] evil. You
know, they can call me in all they [ __ ] want,
lad. It would have to be Yeah. They'd
have to stop
sing cuz these sibs could actually get
what they want if they stop sing. Simp
is never going to get them laid.
Defending women is never going to get
them laid, but they still do it.
But they still
defending. It's crazy, isn't it?
Yeah. It's a mental illness. 100, bro.
100% it is. I wasn't born born of it.
What do you think's going to happen
there if I go out approaching on
Saturday? Ah, they've all got
boyfriends. I might meet USA Izzy again.
Who's an evil
[ __ ] USA Izzy the evil [ __ ] Hey.
Yeah, but I am I am actually done for a month,
lad. I am actually done for a month.
Yeah, they all have boyfriends, but they're in
nightclubs. It's mad, isn't it? Oh,
ego. They've all got boyfriends,
apparently. Why would they say that?
Why? They say that they can't find any
nice men. Um, alter ego, but then when
somebody approaches them, they don't
even give you a chance. So, I
mean, what I just don't understand it.
It just doesn't make any
sense. You know, they they collect they
complain about it doesn't make sense.
It's like they hate men, right? And they
generalize men and they don't think any
but then when men approaches them, they reject them.
So, I don't really really get it. You
know, if I had nice women approach me,
but there is no nice women because they
don't exist all the time. My opinion would be
different. Yeah. But they should find
you attractive cuz I'm decent looking.
No homo obviously about myself and that ain't it.
Like, but they should find you
attractive because there's nothing wrong
with the way that I look. Just like
there's nothing wrong with the way that other people
look. So this is what makes me think
that they're racist. I mean if somebody
was on to something because it's like
there's nothing wrong with the way that
I look. You know, especially when I've
had a trim and that I had a trim on
Friday, you know, there's nothing wrong
with the way that you look, but they
want white people that s 6'5 tattoos.
That's that's what they find attractive.
So yes, technically they don't find you
attractive because they've got this
perfect man in their head that they will
go for and anything other than is not
attractive to them, you
know, and being like fully white helps a lot as
well because my friend, he's like the
same looks range as me. He's got tattoos
and he cleans up all cuz he looks like
white. He looks like proper proper
white. Obviously, I look Mediterranean,
so I don't really get anything. So, race
is a big thing as well. Race is a big
thing, you know. It is. It is, bro.
So, but then they wonder why they can't
find good men. So,
it's doesn't make any sense.
But why do why would they find you
attractive? Because there's nothing
wrong with the way that you look. You
know what I'm saying? There's nothing
know, like you know what I'm saying, bro? Sorry.
That's what I'm saying. Yeah, I agree
with you. I would I would agree with you
as well. Like it's either black or
white. And that's what was making me
think all the time that I know I'm ugly,
bro. I know I'm decent looking. I've got
a beard. I've got hair. I've got nice
eyebrows. But obviously because I'm I
look Mediterranean, but I don't have it
the worst. There's Indian people that
have it worse than me. Chinese people,
they have got it worse.
They've got it
worse than [ __ ] than anyone, bro. But
so with me, I'm stuck in the middle of not getting
nothing. Obviously, I don't look pretty
white, do I? So, not cuz you're ugly.
It's cuz of your [ __ ] race cuz I've
done experiments like this before even
like black people and they didn't even get any
matches. They want 6'5 white men with tattoos.
That's their standards. That's their
type. And even other races like them as
well. But when but when we say these
things narrow, when we say these things,
alter ego, we're told that we're an
incel. Any any evidence, any facts that
you tell them, you're an
incel. Why do you think I got with that
Morgan? Because we're similar heritage.
That [ __ ] Who's the other
one? Well, there's another one I got
with as well.
Portuguese, Italian, you don't
understand the the the the pattern
here, you know? It's more for people
that look like
you. So that's the kind of people you
should be going
for, not people that are
like I mean, yeah, you understand?
I wonder if I was approached in Glasgow,
would would they be like, "Oh, I've got
a boyfriend." Nah. They'd be like, "Oh,
you from London. You're cute." I
guarantee you that's what they'd say.
Just like they do in
Newcastle. You went anywhere like that
area, bro. I swear to God, they'd be
like, "Oh, you're from London." Cuz you
stand out and they know that you look
good and you look good and there's no
competition. This is what these things
are meily down to. You know what I'm saying?
You you even went to Glasgow, bro. I
swear I don't think you'd have these
problems, bro. I swear I don't think you
would cuz you don't get it in
Newcastle. Not like you do in London.
Not like you do in London,
bro. Not like you do in
London, you know.
So I I think it is London, bro. As well as like
Yeah. Chinese Indians. They're [ __ ]
Why do you think that Indonesian guy
could never get
anyone? I tell you what, bro. I
approached this woman before. Yeah. He
was with her friend. They were from
Ireland. You know, the Irish one. It was
me and the Chinese. It was me and the uh
the Thai guy, right?
And uh he was saying and she liked me,
who was kissing and [ __ ] but her friend
didn't like my friend just because of
his race. Yeah. And then she went with
the army guy that was white who was in a
[ __ ] relationship. They're racist
[ __ ] That's what they are, bro. They
wouldn't get with my friend all because
he was [ __ ]
Asian. Believe it, bro. Trust me. Cuz
he's not ugly for a [ __ ] Asian guy.
He looks [ __ ] normal. He had his
teeth done as well. Yeah. So, you get
the gist of these racist [ __ ] And that
white guy, he didn't even look much
better. He didn't, bro. I think he was
like 5'8, normal, average looking
person, but she chose him over my
friend. Huh? Why do you think that is,
you know? So,
yeah. Hello, Goon. Are you okay, boss?
How does it how does it feel that I get
more money than you? Oh, you got to get
Kitty and the Caliban in the
valleys. Kitty and the Caliban in the bies.
Oh, I can't take you serious with that
accent, Gona. Please stop
it. Yeah, I still can't find [ __ ]
Tam. This is why I don't want to go to
Glasgow, cuz it would just make me think
of Tam, my daddy.
Ah, really? No, it's not. No, it's [Laughter]
not. Yeah, we were just talking about
women being [ __ ]
Guna. And I've had more women than your
S friend, Lord
J. It was fine, thanks. Do you know why,
Duna? Because you're bored alone and
you'll die alone. You only have yourself
in this world. You understand that in
this world you only have
yourself, you know, and that's exactly
how you'll die by yourself. So, it felt
pretty good to be honest. How does it
feel that I get more money than you and
I don't have to work? That's
lush. I think that's the easiest saying
to do with a Welsh
accent. Yeah. Kitty in the calibad. Oh,
the you cuz he actually said that once. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. They don't want to admit
that the dating game is rigged against
men. [ __ ] hell, bro. I give up,
lad. I give up with these [ __ ] people on Reddit.
I [ __ ] give up,
mate. Where are you, Tammy? Come out.
Come out, wherever you [Laughter]
are. Yeah. And the things I have got
from trying. Yeah. It's not even been
made. It's not even It's not even been worth
it. Bro, I'll go for a good oldfashioned
piss up in a month on Saturday and we'll call
it. I'm alone. I'm not crying on Reddit.
I'm just being real
lad. Yeah, you have a wonder. Okay, good
for you. Do you want a
medal? My And the reason I spent alone
Christmas is because my family don't
even live in this country. Tam lives in
Scotland and my mommy lives in America.
Mhm. They left Peter Belly alone whilst
they flew out the country. I seek
validation from strangers. Good. I'm
just saying that the it's rigged against
men. I think I need to go to Thailand,
bro. For real. Like, all jokes aside, I
you know what? I I don't want to live in
an I don't want to live in an in an unfair world.
I don't want to live in an unfair world
because it annoys me, bro. It annoys me.
I don't want to live somewhere where it's unfair, you
know. Yeah, but that's my
mama, you know. I got a mommy and
daddy. Imagine we all take a picture
together. Samuel, I didn't I didn't lie
about going to her [ __ ]
country. Yeah. You're the one You're the
same one that said she owned me. She
didn't owe me, mate. I got her [ __ ]
body. I made her change her number. I
made her go to the police on me. And
when I went to her [ __ ] country and
when I went to her [ __ ] country, she
[ __ ] um she avoided me. She's a
[ __ ] man. [ __ ] didn't [ __ ] owe
me. [ __ ] pair of
[ __ ] She's banned from [ __ ]
England. She's banned from the
UK. I'll give her a
slap. A slap. I didn't lie about go to
her country, mate. But
yeah, she made me fake on today, bro. I
made her change her number. I made her
go to the police on me. I made her split
up with her boyfriend. Oh, that's
another thing. I made her split up with
her boyfriend. Yeah, good for you, bro.
I'm the reason she spit up with her
boyfriend. Who's the one that really got
affected? Not me,
lad. So, try again, lad.
Try again, please.
Let me tell you, it's so good. I get I
have more disposable cash than you every
month. Even if you get more money than
me, I get I have more disposable cash
than you every month. Believe
that. No, it won't. The reason I didn't
put up videos when I was in America is
because I didn't want these people
harassing. You [ __ ] [ __ ] That's
why. You know, it's a pity you didn't
have this [ __ ] attitude when I was in
Cardiff, did you, Huna? You
know, [ __ ] Cardiff. I still remember
the first time I went to Cardiff. It was [ __ ] house.
Little [ __ ] house, mate. That's what you are. [ __ ] [Laughter]
house. You [ __ ] [ __ ] house,
mate. I'll never forget that day. Um,
Samuel, they they installed the
Elizabeth line. It was a couple of years
ago is when I was going to the gym and
pumping the iron. I was like, "What the
[ __ ] I've been to Scotland two times.
I've never been to Wales." So then they
installed the Elizabeth line. So I put
my little duffel bag over my back,
coddled off and went to
Wales. It was lovely, you
know. I was like, "Well, I've been to
Scotland two times. I've never been to
Wales." So I p I I I I p I I puddled off
to Wales and Guna shot himself.
Yeah, it was a lovely sight, mate. Those
were the good days,
Gona. Those were the good days,
lad. Those were the good
days. I've been to Wales three times.
No, I went to Wales a few years ago
before that as
well. Yeah, I went the next week again.
I went three years ago. I think it was
three years ago. Then I went one Friday,
then I went the next
Friday. Didn't really get anything
there. I didn't get anything in Wales.
No, the first time I did, but not the other
times. Yeah, I don't think I'm going
Wells again. I'm going to Glasgow to see my daddy. Samuel.
Yeah. To be fair though, the Welsh
people are friendly to be to be honest
with you. They are nice people, but this
is just a
[ __ ] Yeah, I remember I saw the
video, you know.
No, I don't forget what I say. No, I
don't forget what I say at all.
I'm going to see my daddy next week, Samuel.
I want to see my daddy. [Music]
I don't like you. I think you're mocking me,
bro. I actually think you're [ __ ]
mocking me, lad. Yeah.
Yeah. Samuel, I'll be going to Glasgow
and and um Tam will be waiting for you
at the station. Ah, what a lovely
sight. What a lovely
sight. What a lovely sight.
Hey, what a lovely [ __ ]
sight. What a lovely [ __ ] sight. But
here's the thing, Gona. You say about
that American owned me. That's fine. But
I own you in your country. That's the
funniest thing. I owned you in your
country, you little
[ __ ] I owned you in your country,
mate. With a dragon flag, so [ __ ] off. And
Yeah, you're worse than that [ __ ]
virgin Sean you are,
mate. L didn't owe me in my country
though, did he? Cuz I opened the door. I
told him to [ __ ] off and then when I was
in the same location as him, he wouldn't
turn his camera on. He didn't owe no
one. He didn't owe no one in their own
country, mate. I told him to [ __ ] off. I
was standing in front of my mom. Yeah.
He had several chances to to kick that
door in my face. A B even if he did win.
Um I tried to meet him whilst he was
still in the same location and he would
turn his camera on. Hey B, when I went
to Tererry's area last time, he didn't
show up. Stop talking [ __ ] mate. I
think you've got memory loss. It must be
from old age.
Goona Terry told me to go to his area
last time. I went live in his area. He
didn't come out. Yeah.
Literally, he literally did not come
out. Yes. I went to his area in London
and the [ __ ] did not come out. When he
was telling me to go to his area, so no,
Gona, you're the one that got owned in
your country. Yeah, bro. I I didn't What
else? Yeah, I opened the door and I told
him to [ __ ] off. I didn't need to. What
do you want me to do? Go outside and
kill someone? Bro, stop imbalance. Stop
embarrassing yourself, Gona. You know,
please stop embarrassing yourself, lad.
It's not good for your mental
health. And that's
it. So, you didn't you didn't react when
I was in your country though, did you?
You little [ __ ] You didn't react when
I was in your country though, did you? So,
Oh, shut up. Shut up. Shut up. Shut up.
Don't tell us how much money you get a
month then, you
[ __ ] You're only grand a
month. You're 100 grand a month, mate. Press the button. The
Okay. £275 a day. You're on a grand a month
sha. I can't live on a grand a month.
I've explained to you why I can't live
on a grand a month. Who's going to pay
for the little stonies? Who's going to
pay for the little stony baby bros and
the little nights out?
He's going to pay for all of them
tricks. Just can't do it on a grand a month,
mate. I can't I can't do it on a grand a
month, mate. Nah, not on a grand a
month. [ __ ] a grand a month,
eh? You could live on it, but it
wouldn't be a good life. No drinking, no
stone iring, no baby,
nothing. You'd be [ __ ]
No America, no nothing. You
know, you want to grind them up. So, you
want to grind the month,
mate. You want to grind them up. You
know, you want to grind them up, son. [ __ ]
I don't have so much
money. I I don't have so much money. Do
you know I spent £500 last week? I had
to get my passport renewed and everything,
mate. You know, I'm just saying who's
going to pay for the little Stone [Laughter]
Islands. Oh, [ __ ]
me. I'm not depressed.
Luna, you you're saying that I'm lonely,
but you're the one who's on YouTube
every single day. You're the one who's
on YouTube every single day, bud. Not me. You
know, you're the one who's on YouTube
every [ __ ] single [ __ ] day, mate. No,
bro. You're on YouTube. You're on £275 a day.
So, and how many day? So, you work five
days a week? Yeah. Fine.
Yeah. What should I get my mommy for Mother's Day? Yeah.
So, five days a week. Okay. So, you
probably got like four grand a month.
Okay. But you don't have as much
disposable money as me every month. I'll
tell you that for nothing.
Yeah. You know. Okay. So, what? 4K.
Okay. Good for you. I bet you don't have
as much disposable money as me. You
know what should I get my mama say? Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Good
enough. Well, I told you this. If you
really want to fight, I'll be in Glasgow next
Saturday. If you really want to do this,
I'll be in Glasgow next
Saturday trying to find my
father. Get what? She wants you dead.
Hey, that's not
nice. That's not very nice, buddy. Well,
I'll meet you in Glasgow next
Saturday. I'll be
there. I'll be there, son.
I'll be there, Gona. I'll be there,
lad. You know, I'll be in Glasggo, ready
to fill you
in. You're a loser, Gula.
Yeah, you know, I won't prove American.
Why would my mommy want me dead? Why
would Laney want me dead? That's not very
nice. Just because you're a fat, ugly
old man don't have to tear down Peter Belly. You
know that's not nice, is it,
buddy? No. No. No. No. When's it
possible going to [ __ ] hurry up,
man? Something here. One sec. Yep.
have all had the passport by now. What
the [ __ ] is going
on? Come my emails.
but I'll be back later anyways. Peace.