Yeah. M. Yes. Mhm. What's so It's nice.
It's spicy though.
The nicest is [ __ ]
Yeah, I had some some Chinese here. Oh, mate.
Oh, lovely. It is
You reckon Virgin boy will ever get laid?
Steven Howard, honestly, you reckon
they'll ever lose it? Never die once.
Sorry about that, bro. It is M
as much proof as we have. I do want him
to get laid.
I do want him to get laid. I don't It's
not like seeing anyone be 30 when
they're still virgin.
I'm not a narcissist like these people.
Yeah, we could have.
We needed to win that football bet,
didn't we? Really?
We needed to win that football bet.
Really, didn't we,
didn't we? Oh, B,
that was lovely.
We needed to win that football bet.
Definitely needed to win that football back, bro.
[ __ ] [ __ ] me almost for [ __ ] £100.
90 is a lot of money, you know, bro on a football bet.
Should have went on the [ __ ] piss with that. Yeah.
[ __ ] 90 [ __ ] football. [ __ ] hell.
It's not good, is it, mate? It's not good. No. Yeah.
I'm not doing it again, bro.
It's too [ __ ] depressing. I'm not
doing it again.
How much do you think you'd spend on a
night out just drinking Steven Hour?
How much do you reckon you you'd spend? 100 maybe.
Yep, pretty much.
I can't believe Paul [ __ ] us, bro.
Why don't you go out? Did you out there
going out drinking and [ __ ]
What did you grow it on?
This community is so weird, bro.
It's so weird. Yeah.
What do you mean the same crap? Like the
same music and Yeah. That's why I don't go out much anymore. Very much
Yeah, USA is he bs me.
That [ __ ] bs me, mate. USA [ __ ] Izzy.
She [ __ ] balls the [ __ ] out of me.
Yeah, I don't go out anymore either.
I rinsed it, bro.
I used to go out all the time, go
casino, then go drinking and
Yeah, good times, bro.
There were good times.
Never do it again. I don't think, bro. No.
It's going all the time. Go casino. Get pissed.
Just good times, bro.
Why is it just start off in the casino?
I did. I did.
Yeah. But for real, I am coming off this
community soon though. For real. For
real. But all jokes aside,
I want to leave these low lives to it.
this little red star and
[ __ ] like this little [ __ ] and that sad
pathetic YouTube losers. They ain't got
a life. You know what I mean? I want to
leave them too at some point, bro.
For real. I'm being deadly serious now.
This is me talking on a real Yeah. [ __ ]
It's mad, isn't it?
I got a delivery bag. I'm going to start
delivering some food again soon. I got a
delivery bag that I bought.
So, obviously at some point I'm going to
have to sort of do some work or
something. I think, bro,
cuz I'm not always going to win a
football bet. You see what I mean? And I
can't keep doing these mood swings every
single time I lose. So
that's the thing.
Yeah, I bought a food bag. I bought a
food bag, bro.
The other day.
So make some money soon, I think.
Wow, they've made like posters of me on Reddit. But
these people need to get their life.
They seriously seriously need to go alive.
I I do feel bad for these people.
See, they can't do what they done to me
with rice to me cuz people know me in
every area. So that's why like when I
was in Strapford, I was saying, "Okay,
send them, send them, send them."
Because everybody knows me in the area.
They know what I'm about and [ __ ] So,
like at the end of the day, it's not
going to work because people know who I
am. Do you understand? They've known me
since I was a kid.
People know me around my sister's area
and people know me around my mom's area. So,
you know what I'm saying? So, I mean, if
they do that, I mean, they can, but it's
not going to work cuz they know me. They
might have not known Rice and whatever,
but people know me. So, and they know
that I'm like not into kids and [ __ ]
So, no one no one cares.
Like when I went back to um my mom's
that time a few times um when I used to
stay over like the kids would talk to me
and [ __ ] They were like, "You all
right?" And that like the actual
children would would speak to me, bro.
People know about me. People know who I
am. They know what I'm about. They've
seen me with women. So
it's just a waste of£3400
which I did try saying to them but they you know
people know who I am in all these areas
so it's not going to work. [Music]
Yeah, there's a lot of stalkers on here,
bro. That Red Star one's the worst. Oh
my god, he is such a loser.
How he does this all day, every day. He
is a proper proper loser. But the thing
is, Stephen Howard, when you explain
stuff to these people where they don't
understand it because they're disabled.
So that's why they don't see it as like
they don't see it as a big deal cuz they're disabled.
So like like it's like Joe like they
don't understand things that's explained
to them because they've got a dose of retardation.
So, like there's no telling these people
cuz any normal person would understand
what this red star does. He's a creep.
He's a weirdo. How he does this all day,
every day for years is is mental, bro.
Like on that Reddit thing when I was on
Reddit, I could do it for like two days
and I was like, "Oh, I ain't got the
energy." But this guy is consistent with
this all day, every day. And I think if
people wasn't as disabled as they are on
here, they would actually understand the
severity of it.
You know, it's very very sad. You know,
and people don't don't understand it.
You know what I mean?
I need to just get off this [ __ ] and
live my life, bro. And end end of story.
You know what I mean? Cuz of they're all
biased on here. They're never going to
stop their [ __ ] And it's just weird.
Just leave them to it. They're obviously
low lives. They ain't got a life. So
you understand what I'm saying?
>> Oh yeah. Oh [ __ ]
Reckon you're going to lose it. Reckon
you're going to lose it. Lose it. Reckon
Going to lose it, Virgin boy. You're
going to lose it. So yeah,
that's where we're at, lad.
And I need to do this job thing soon as
well cuz I need to try and make some money. I mean,
they're such weirdos on here, bro. That
it's just a [ __ ] disabled community.
It's like that Joe trying to show his
pension, bro. Nobody cares what you
have. If you have all of this money, get
off of YouTube and live your life. Have
a better life. Live up to like they're
they're they're [ __ ] they're [ __ ]
disabled, bro, on here. Like really really disabled.
They're really disabled on it, bro. Even that
What age do you reckon you outgrow the
going out? Thinking I'm thinking maybe
What age do you reckon you outgrow it?
Maybe 26, 27. maybe 27.
Yeah, I had it, bro. Yeah,
I was just saying that this, you know,
that red star, what he does every day,
it's really, really sad. And if these
people, the reason when you when you say
this stuff, oh, it's it's sad what he
does and no one says anything, bro, is
because they're too disabled to understand.
They're too disabled to understand. They
don't understand because they're disabled.
That's why they don't understand things
and they're all biased as well. You understand? So
Mhm. They had a beef shade.
These people, I don't know how they do
it for for years, Nicolola.
I don't know how they sit here every day
and do this for years.
I get bored off for like two days on Reddit
ranting and [ __ ] They they never give
up. These people
[ __ ] mad, isn't it? It's mad, isn't it, bro?
They've got to be disabled in it.
Got to be disabled.
Yeah, I'm getting old. That's why I
don't really go out drinking anymore, bro. Just boring. So boring.
Nope. I'm not [ __ ] that old. [ __ ] hell.
I'm not that old, you [ __ ]
Do you remember when I used to go up and
down the country? Nicolola.
Uh, I was a lot younger back then, mate.
A lot younger back then.
Well, I just like to chill in bed.
Do you reckon that Red Star will stop in
5 years? Nicolo,
do you reckon he will stop in 5 years? No, no, never, never, butter,
they will never leave me alone. No,
they never leave me alone, bro. What the [ __ ]
They were laughing at you, mocking you.
It's the same atmosphere, isn't it? Yeah.
If that Red Star's got all of this money
and [ __ ] why does he sit online
stalking me every day? Just Red Star.
He's a fat 40y old disabled loser.
No one has that time in their hand to
sit online every day
stalking someone. Bro, it's like that
pat. Do you remember what we always used
to say about that pat? It's some fat
ugly bastard. They're all the same, bro.
They're all the same. Fat, ugly,
disabled. [ __ ] sat there trying to
call me a m. Yeah, these people are
scared to show their face.
How mad is that, bro?
I sure do. Yeah. [Music]
>> But bro, they they sit there and say,
"Oh, you're this, you're that, you're
this, you're that." But you're better
looking than them.
Better looking than them. Better looking,
better life. Yeah.
Bit like what that Ronald Pump said,
better life, better more money, better
looking, better life. And it kills them.
True though, ain't it? Cuz why would no
one none of these people show their face?
It is true though if you think about it,
bro. Because most of these people are
fat and ugly
and their [ __ ] skin as well, you know.
So if I meet this woman from Canada, we
could have a baby and call it baby Peter from Canada.
Imagine that. Baby Peter from Canada.
That'll get that'll get the virgin, won't it? Virgin boy. Virgin born.
[ __ ] virgin [ __ ]
You're [ __ ] virgin.
I mean, bro.
Can't believe we put 90 on a [ __ ] football bet. Yeah, man.
It will never change. That's why I don't
go out anymore
doing this [ __ ] I can't be asked.
Uber Eats. Uber Eats. Uber Eats. [ __ ] knows.
could do. Nicolo could do.
You [ __ ] virgin, can't you? Yeah.
Yeah, I didn't like her. [ __ ] that.
Isn't it greasy? Yeah.
These women are NPCs. Yeah.
One second. I'll be right back. Yeah.