Okay, so I just wanted to um do a little
live stream. Yeah. Talking about this
[ __ ] sad [ __ ] self-reflecting lowlight community. A second.
Yeah. One sec.
Let's talk about this [ __ ]
spasticated low life immunity. These
hungry people ain't got a life. You
know, I was actually thinking about
this. Yeah. Before I went to bed and
also like when I woke up like these
people truly truly have got no life.
Like it come out of [ __ ] nowhere like
when I was thinking about it. It's like
bro what the [ __ ] bro? These fat, ugly
people sat on YouTube every day trying
to call people that they don't even
[ __ ] know. They waste all their life
away stalking and harassing people that
they don't even [ __ ] know. Think
about that for a second. These these
[ __ ] fat, ugly, lowife people trying,
>> you know, when we're talking about these
people, you might as well let these
people look so they can at least offend.
>> You know what I mean? You might as well
They Well, they don't Well, they don't
defend themselves, do they? Cuz they're
too scared to
>> Yeah, but they're more welcome to come
up on a panel to offend theelves either
way, EJ. Do you know what I mean?
>> Well, they don't join the hangouts ever. >> Okay.
>> So, yeah. So, basically, why why do you
people do this? Anyways, this is what
this is what I'm going to ask these
people. You know, they can type, they
can come to hangouts. I want to know why
they do what they do every day.
And that's the answer what I've been
asking myself for the last [ __ ] six
years. What what
>> you know they don't know you. They don't
know you in [ __ ] real life, you know.
>> No, they don't know your life. They
don't know nothing about you or what you
give them or or what they of other
people. But it's not true either way.
>> And all they do is stalk and harass
people every day. It's crazy, bro.
>> And then put people nons on kidos when
they're the ones who go around doing
this [ __ ] themselves. Yeah.
Well, what what can you do? What can you
say? Oh, your skin. We've heard it a
million times, you know.
>> Yeah. Many times. Do
>> you know another thing that happens on
Montre is when you do something they
they never like admit it. Like, you
know, when you've shown money in the
past or when you've gone to like meet
someone or anything, they never you have
you noticed that?
>> Yeah. like they won't bring it up or
they lying or
>> they're [ __ ] mongos. They're [ __ ] mongos, bro.
>> Yeah. That's their content. From the
time they wake up, from the time they go
to sleep, they ain't got nothing. These
people ain't got nothing in life. >> Yeah.
>> So, they come on YouTube. I'm not being
funny. Half of you people, no offense on
you, I said half of you are fat [ __ ]
in this community.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> And that's not [ __ ] And they're
trying to call And they're trying to
call me a MTO and I'm better looking
than all of them.
Yeah. No, no. And these are monts. These
are ugly ass people. This is why they
sat on YouTube and putting people up
play as pedophiles and stuff like that
to make these look better than what you
are. And that's only what it is.
>> And that's only what it is with these.
You put people up play what they are. >> Yeah.
>> That's what it is.
These are the ones who are actual
leedophiles. These are the ones who
putting on innocent people.
Obviously is a 100% is a nons. >> Yeah,
>> but I'm on about like normal regular
people in natural.
>> His wife a natural nons.
Yeah, he's a [ __ ] fo. Yeah, of course he is. >> Yeah,
>> that that is the same as that letter.
What what got what what fell put up rice
saying that it's ricees. All that's
being done by that computer,
>> not my head.
>> You know what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> His one because barely hasn't got the
[ __ ] brain to go to like
>> your hands. Your hands covering your mic
a little bit, I think.
>> Is it?
>> Yeah, it's better now. Yeah, it's better now. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> I don't know why they do this on the
>> It's weird. All of it. It's just weird
how they they don't Have you noticed
it's not even that money. It's like they
never like they never stop. Have you noticed that?
>> No. No. They they can't stop. It's only
It's only the content these can do. They
can't go out and make content. They got
to sit on YouTube, call people, or get
content of other people
>> or out of other people and that's it.
>> That's all like like I've been watching
Lord J. All what he does and does is
talk about other YouTubers what what
they do in their life. Like
like with you calling you beautiful.
Call look at PJ. Lorna Lorna. But look
at Lord J. Lorna. >> Lorn.
>> I'm not being funny. And I'm not being
funny. Monty. Yeah. They tried to call
you skin, right? How many times has
these people been showing money and they
can't show anything? How many times
Monty? This is why I don't I don't I
don't um get into it with these people
anymore. This is why I don't waste my
time with them anymore.
>> No, there's no point racing your time
with these people. There's no point.
This is why This is why I don't go live
no more. This is why Natalie doesn't go
live no more because it's boring. >> Yeah.
>> They haven't won. They haven't won us
off YouTube. Have you seen the state of these people? >> Yeah.
>> [ __ ] hell. Timmy Elders is more
better in looking.
>> Look, look at this money. You know that
you know that Red Star account? >> Yeah.
>> He said he tries to say that I'm
triggered. He's the one on YouTube every
day stalking me every day.
>> Wait, how about we triggered? Yeah. When
users are on YouTube with no life,
nothing go and
why don't you come up on the panel. If
we're the one who's triggered,
>> why don't you come up on this panel, Red Star Triggered
on YouTube every all day, every day
stalking. Yeah. Making videos, Monty.
And I'm the one that's triggered.
Apparently, you're the one who's
triggered. You are all triggered.
user on YouTube repeating the same [ __ ]
every day. How about you going to get
anybody trigger triggered? Only what you
can do is trigger yourselves and that's it. >> Literally.
>> That's it.
>> Why did you make Why did you make a new account?
>> Cuz you had to reset my [ __ ] phone. I
put a fus on my phone.
>> Why do you do you like the color purple?
>> What do you No, purple lack.
Would you wear No, would you wear like a
Would you wear a purple t-shirt or a purple tracksuit?
>> No. What the [ __ ] No.
>> Well, you don't like purple? Why?
>> No. Purple's for girls, mate.
>> No, I Bro, I wear pink, you know. I wear
I wear like a light pink t-shirt. Like a
baby pink. Nah,
>> I like I like how you turned I like I
like how you turned the conversation on
to you, Pia.
>> Well, yeah, cuz you said it's girls and
I wear and I'm a girl. That's
>> No, I'm not about that. You just turn
the co You just turn the
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. What we were saying is
anyways like any any of you just come
and join and and just say why you do
what you do. Anyways, anyways.
>> Yeah. Just just join and say and just
explain why you do it. Is it
>> the thing is PJ? Yeah. These people are
sat on YouTube from the time they go to
sleep. That's what probably about 7 6:00
in the morning. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> They don't want to miss out,
you know. But they don't want to miss
out on all the content or whatever. But
what is content? What just people
sitting on YouTube arguing with other
people who they don't know?
>> Who they don't know. Yeah. And they
don't and and they're never going to
meet either. That's the thing.
>> No. Yeah. Yeah. They're sitting there
arguing over [ __ ] and watching
>> and that's it.
>> That's why it all comes to jealousy on
this Monty because think about it. Yeah.
Look look at this. Yeah. If they're
trying to call you you're this, you're
that, you're skinn, you're that, then
they would just leave you alone and live
their life. No. If that was the case,
they wouldn't be wasting their life on
you every day. But they do cuz they
ain't got a life.
>> The same ugliness as Lee. Yeah. If
you're the same ugliness as Lee, they
put you on their side.
>> Yeah. That's what I'm saying. Yeah.
>> But if you're better in the They don't
like it. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Exactly. That's why they go for
me. That's why they got I have like all
these people go for me, bro. >> Yeah.
You know, cuz I'm I'm [ __ ] way better
looking than these [ __ ] people.
>> So, who's coming up on the hangout then? Explain yourselves.
>> Yeah, come on. The link's there.
>> Let them all up. Yeah,
>> I'll let all I'll let them all up. I'll
>> Let them all up.
>> And then you get weirdo like [ __ ] nonso.
>> Only what he can bring up is this with
me. Yeah. He's teen dating up from Pat
Muster's kid, but he's all forgetting
what Pat must Muster did to Lola Lola
back in the day.
>> Also, another thing, Monty, you know
this this whole Monty, listen. You know,
um this whole thing about what you what
they try and say that I've said and you
said, you do realize it's just any
excuse, isn't it?
>> They know what it is, PJ. Yeah. If they
come up on the paddle, start putting
pictures up your daughter or your sister's kids.
>> Yeah. And when you react to that and you
start back on them, they won't put them
up what they done to you. They put you
up what you doing to them. And that's
it. And that's it. And that's only what they
>> What I'm saying is what I'm saying is
even if you didn't say that stuff all
them times ago, what I'm saying is they
would still go for you.
>> They still go for you. But they're going
for you for what reasons? For what they cost.
>> Yeah, that's what I'm saying. That's
what I'm saying. But I'm saying even if
you didn't do any of that stuff, they
would still be trying to like troll you
and trying to make you say [ __ ] That's
what I'm saying.
>> I mean,
>> no, of course. Of course. No, that's
what they do, Lord. That's what they do.
They put you up at something what you're
not through something what they cause
for something what they said.
>> I remember I remember when you said
that, Monty, that it's the same
atmosphere every day.
>> It is the same atmosphere. These people
haven't even got a IQ to change your
[ __ ] underpants. Never mind. [ __ ] words.
>> Yeah, it's true though. It is true.
>> You know what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> This is why they repeat theelves every
day cuz they think it's pissing you off,
but it's not. It's pissing them off not
knowing that they knowing that they've
got the same words coming out the mouth every day. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> I can sit here and call these [ __ ]
all different [ __ ] [ __ ] Go on.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Someone asked you why do
they call people skin?
>> Because at the end of the day, if you're
watching from the the time they wake up,
from the time they they wait for the
people, they wait for the money benefits
or whatever. They get paid come through
the door. Then they go out and they
spend it on gambling. They go gambling
for [ __ ] sake. They grab the beer.
They grab the drugs and they go gambling.
>> I don't know why nonslegs always cause me skin.
Yeah, I'm not talking about him. He's
he's irrelevant here at this time of
moment, Pete. Yeah.
>> Well, I mean, I know what I'm saying is
someone asked you why do they call
people skin. That's what I mean.
>> Yeah. Yeah. It's because these people
when these, like as I said, when these
people get paid,
>> they go out gambling, they go out
drinking, they waste their money on all
that what two two days they skin,
they're broke, they're back on YouTube.
Well, they're on YouTube either way.
They can't get off YouTube. YouTube is live. >> Yeah,
>> they're live.
>> I'm not being funny, Money. I'm not
being funny. Yeah. Listen, listen. I've
been I've been off of YouTube for a
week, two weeks, three weeks before.
Yeah. And as soon as I come on, they're
like, "Oh, oh, you're on YouTube again."
I was like, "Hang on. You can't even
take a day off of YouTube and you're
trying to talk about me."
>> No. Exactly. Exactly. And they tell you
you to go and get a job. Just think
about it. Why don't you work now? Oh
[ __ ] Yeah. It's Sunday. Any excuse? >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean?
>> Yeah. I'm saying. Yeah. >> Okay.
>> I call people skin cuz they're skin basically.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Basically. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Do you remember when Bob Do you
remember Bob used to say that I was a virgin? Monty.
>> Bob's a virgin. I'm not being funny, but
half the lead in this community are
[ __ ] virgins, PJ. And that's no
>> Yeah. Yeah, they only come on you and
write about you is because that's what
they can do. It's selfreflecting and
that's all what they do is selfrelect on other people.
>> It's true. It is true.
>> They haven't got nothing going. They sat
there [ __ ] what? Talking themselves
off on camera, showing their dicks on
cameras and [ __ ] like that
>> on YouTube. >> Yeah.
>> And they call other people. I'm not
being funny, but there's kids on this app.
>> Yeah. There's [ __ ] trolling on this
app. It's [ __ ] YouTube. >> Yeah,
>> it's teenagers on this app. And then you
get all used in the background flashing
your dicks on camera and [ __ ] like that. >> Weirdos.
>> And I've shown me I've shown me Monty
with money and women and stuff and they
they pretended like they haven't seen it.
>> Yeah. They pretend because they don't
want to see. They're not bothered about
what you show. They bothered about what
comes out of their mouth. That's it.
>> They're not bothered about you. you
really they're not bothered about you.
They're bothered about the own being.
Basically, they want to [ __ ] go at
you to make themselves look better. Look
at this. I'm going for someone who you
don't like. Oh yeah. Okay. You're on my side now.
>> And that's what it is.
>> Of course. Of course.
>> You know what I mean? These all these
are not that clever because if they were
that clever, they find out where I live
now, won't they? But they can't. And I'm
not doctoring myself. Am I [ __ ]
I've I've only docked myself once in my
life and that was at my old address. The
other times were being docked which no bed. >> Yeah.
>> So I haven't really docked myself.
>> They're like Monty with the same
repeating comments and [ __ ] They're
like robots. They're not even like
humans. They're like robots.
>> No, they just that's how they write
because think about it PJ. Yeah.
>> These people are stinking like cosmic
kitties. Yeah. Yeah,
>> these people are stinking. And I mean
stinking. I'm not They are.
>> Yeah, they are.
>> They [ __ ] fat and ugly.
>> [ __ ] sake. Some of them in the [ __ ]
40s for [ __ ] sake on YouTube arguing
with people younger than them.
>> They don't know as well.
>> They don't know as well. Yeah.
>> Yeah. They don't know. And these are
supposed to be more [ __ ] mature. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? supposed to be
more on YouTube. Where's the content on these people?
>> You know, but you know nonsex's channel, isn't it?
>> I don't want to. Do you like nons
like do you like him? Cuz you know Yeah.
Because the way you bring him up every
day on your video like Sean Longlegs. No
wonder going to you all the time, bro.
He does it even if I don't say anything, bro.
Listen, if you go and do you even know
the channel, Monty?
Yeah, but it's not even about I don't
even follow them people. I don't I don't
even follow any of the in this
community. I don't even follow
I don't follow fe I don't follow
any of them. I follow he go someone
someone's trying to come in.
>> Put yourself on big. Yeah.
>> Hello Mango. Can I ask you a question?
And this is what I'm all about with the
gay little boys. No, keep up. That's
voice of reason.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Keep them up. Keep voice of
reason up. Little [ __ ] r. >> Okay.
>> Come on, boys. A reason. Grow the [ __ ]
up. Use your real voice. Yeah.
>> Instead of using that little [ __ ]
fake voice of yours, you little weasel.
>> Okay. [ __ ] can I ask you a question?
>> Grow up first. Yeah.
>> Okay. Do you think that people who show
their bits on YouTube are nonsers?
>> Uh, basically. Well, um, what who goes
on this uh map? Who who goes onto this app?
>> Children do.
>> Exactly. There you go. So, yeah, I do
think it's wrong. So, I do think it's
>> Okay. So, I think one of them
>> called you just called Natalie a nons.
>> Natalie's not a nons. Natalie's not
>> showing a bit on YouTube, but good boy mango.
>> See what I mean? See what I mean, buddy?
>> Yeah. Yeah, of course. And that's what
what what they change it to. Do you know
what I mean? And that's what they do.
>> You know what I mean?
>> Don't forget Voice of Reason pretended
to be that girl in America for [ __ ]
two months. What a sad bastard.
>> Yeah, I know. I know. I know. They have
sad and that's what they have said.
>> Is he wrong though? Well, if he wasn't
wrong, Grezy, why did he leave? He
didn't give Monty a chance to defend
himself. So, yeah, he is wrong because he left.
>> Ah [ __ ]
>> Yeah, he is wrong because why did he
leave? He didn't even
>> Hold on a minute. Well, we weren't
talking about Natalie. We're talking
about you splashing your dicks and that.
Not not Natalie. You know, he just
brings it on to Natalie because that's
what they do. You know what I mean? Cuz
you're talking about them. So, they
bring someone else up like someone who
you wish like Natalie or your mom or
whatever else like that cuz you're
putting whatever up there. So, they will
go up in Natalie or that. And that's
what they do with
>> Monty. Let me tell you something here. I
don't know why these people sit there.
Hear me out. Yeah, they try and say,
"Oh, these people do it for a reaction."
But I I explained to them, yeah, that
even if you didn't give them a reaction,
they're still going to do it. So,
>> right. Sorry. Sorry, PE. Yeah.
>> And if you want my opinion on Natalie on
that Yeah. It's not my fault that you
people are paying for Natalie's beer to
get it pissed out of her face so she
doesn't know what she's doing. So, no,
that's not Natalie's fault. That's all
your fault, not Natalie. True or not
true? You are the only ones getting her
piss out of her face or she's at the
point where she doesn't know what what
she's doing. But when you are getting
your dick kiss out on YouTube on
people's panels, you all know what
you're doing. You all sober. But you got
to get a woman to do that.
>> That's the difference. It's the same as that um
>> that Natalie [ __ ] that other Natalie
who lives in Manara the karaoke one.
>> Yeah. It's the same as her. She only
does what she does is because you all
know you all donate for that [ __ ] Yeah.
But with Natalie, my my Natalie is
completely different. You had to get
>> [ __ ] drinky. That's what I need. A
[ __ ] drink, mate.
>> But that's the difference.
>> She knew exactly what she was doing.
>> No, she were pissed.
>> I need a [ __ ] drink at some point,
mate. [ __ ] Don't you know what you are
doing when you are getting your bobbies
out on camera and [ __ ] like that? Don't
you people know what you're doing?
>> Why won't you fancy going for a piss up
again some point?
>> Not yet. Not yet.
>> It was fun in it.
>> It was all right.
>> You enjoyed it, ain't it?
>> Yeah, it was all It was all right night
actually. It was good.
>> Them [ __ ] clowns off you off YouTube
didn't want to meet us. Did they when we
knew we was in Brumtown? >> No. >> Bastards.
>> I was thinking more of like Guinness.
Greasy. Some lovely Guinness.
You like Guinness, don't you, Monty?
>> Yeah, but I didn't till that day with you.
>> Oh, it was like the baby Guinness was
nice, isn't it? Little shots in it.
>> Them shots. Yeah.
>> Monty not financially. money not
financially recovered from the mess that
Natalie put him into. Laugh my ass off.
>> I'm over that. I'm living with N. I'm
back with that. So I ain't got nothing
to worry about.
You are the ones who sat on YouTube. I'm
the one who's laughing at you cuz you
the one on YouTube not even in a
relationship and you are thinking I'm
not all for that. It's you who are not
all for that. I am. That's the difference.
That is a big difference. You said you
will always be on YouTube no matter
what. No life, no nothing.
>> No girlfriend,
>> [ __ ] always be the fat [ __ ]
loneliness [ __ ] you would always be.
>> That's funny, isn't it?
>> It's not. It's sad to tell you the truth, PJ.
>> It is pretty sad that full grown men
can't even make content videos. You've
got to sit there and make content videos
of other people's lives, not their home life
>> or not what they can do.
Content to me is this. Yeah.
>> And also,
>> also, have you noticed that? Have you
noticed that with these people, they're
proper nerds as well?
>> No, no, no, no. Nerds have got more
[ __ ] brains on these. A nerd wants
>> but they but they use like nerdy words.
>> Yeah, they will. Yeah, they [ __ ]
[ __ ] These are the people who've
been bulliing school. PJ
>> Monty, you've left and come back about
30 million times. You can't leave either.
>> I'm not back. I've I'm only here. It's
cuz I I I've been thinking about making
that video what I made about you people.
I've been thinking it and I'm not
backing now. We're just here now talking
about what you people do and then blame
other people for your own [ __ ] >> Yeah.
>> And that's sick.
>> And that's only the reason why I'm here
now is to talk about what you people do
to save other people's asses. It's the
same as when you send letters out to
people's neighbors. Some people think it's
>> some people think that they're real.
>> But no, but the thing is Monty Monty,
listen. Yeah. They've been threatening
to um do that to me. But again, but
listen Monty. A listen to me. A they
don't know where I live and b it. All of
them all of them addresses that they say
they're going to send it to. Everybody
knows me. So it's not it wouldn't work
cuz they all
>> Okay. The best thing to do, PJ. Yeah. Is
go on to all these websites where they
put you up. Yeah. Leave a big [ __ ]
essay yourself about what this community does.
>> So when the post does go up, play
>> Yeah. If nobody can see that it's a fake post.
>> Do you know with rice? Yeah. You know
what they done with rice? >> Yeah.
>> They couldn't do it to me because
everybody knows me in all of the areas.
They all know me.
>> So it's it wouldn't be like that.
>> Rice. Everybody knows rice.
>> So why do they all Well,
>> Rice is a wrong.
>> That's what I mean. But they know they
know that I'm not. That's what I'm
saying. So that's why like they post it. >> Yeah.
>> And it was the same when I lived in
Plymouth. I lived on my street for ages.
You know what I mean? Everyone knows me
>> and that's what they pick on when you're
known in places. It's the same as
Roxdale when they when they tried
putting me up as a pedo in Rodale. I'm
well known in Rodale.
>> Do you remember? Do you remember they
sent posters to your neighbors that was hanging it?
>> Yeah, it was hanging. But my neighbors
knew before was going to get the thing
about these people is like they're going
to tell you they're going to do it.
>> Yeah. And that's the worst thing they
can do is tell you you're going to that
that they're going to do it. Then only
what you have to do is screenshot that
and then that proves that these people
put malicious stuff up online
>> about other people
>> and that's it. It's a
>> like where I was living in in Stratford
Mont I said to them okay post it post it
post I was telling them to do it because
they all know me there so they'd be
wasting their time >> really.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Of course. Of course. Of
>> You know what I'm saying? Because the
whole they all know me. You know when
you're known for so long, people know
you're you're not that. You know that.
>> Like even you know when I go back you
know when I go back to my mom sometimes
Monty. Yeah. The the kids talk to me.
Even the actual kids talk to me.
>> Yeah. Yeah. No.
>> No. No one believe it because they know it's [ __ ]
>> No. They know you're not in this
community. They know why I'm not in this
community. They just pop you up like
[ __ ] and [ __ ] your life up.
>> No. But I'm saying I'm saying what I'm
saying is the neighbors even knew I
wasn't. That's what I'm saying.
>> Yeah. Your neighbors know you. Come on P.
>> Only what's not looking good for your or
for you is when you're sitting there
saying what what what you said. But it's
the same with me.
>> It's not looking good on this [ __ ] what
I've said either. Do you know what I mean?
>> But it's also not looking good for these
people either when they got pictures of
other people's kids on the phones and
putting pictures up there. Yeah.
>> And he can't just say that was F because
it wasn't just F20 who's done that.
>> You was all right. You was all right
with weren't you?
>> No. Melly.
>> No, but I swear you and Vy was on
talking terms at one stage.
>> No, no, no. Melly, me and Melly was talking terms,
>> you know.
And that's the truth that I don't know
why they do it anyway. I don't know what
content they get from it or they sit
there and say, "What a night last night.
Did you see the argument last night?
What people you don't know who's arguing get alive?" >> Yeah.
>> It used to be [ __ ] fun when you used
to put your red out the window
and then your next door neighbors used
to argue. They were the best days when
your neighbors used to argue. Not on YouTube,
>> not random.
>> But don't lie. Yeah, but don't lie,
Monty. You did find Timmy funny at one
point, didn't it?
>> Timy's just stupid. He's fake.
>> Yeah, but it was funny, isn't it?
>> No, not really. He's Timmy's No, I don't
find Jimmy Timmy funny.
>> Monty, why do they keep saying that I've
got a big nose? I don't have a big nose.
I wouldn't even read their comments, PJ.
>> No, I mean in the past. Are they trying
to make me like insecure or something?
Because it's never going to work.
>> They're not worth the PJ. [ __ ] hell,
man. I these people like today I didn't
even know this guy. I was watching one
of his videos cuz he left a comment on
my finger and he's put his thumb up and
I called him a fat [ __ ]
>> They're not the greatest, Grezy. They're
not the greatest. Hey, the great guys
when you give up.
>> It's what happens when you give up. Is
it Grezy? I had a nice I had a nice Chinese yesterday.
>> How's your teeth PJ?
>> Yeah, they're all right.
>> that was all that was all.
>> Are you Are you Are you Are you
financially suffering, Monty?
>> Financially suffering from what? No, I
mean like are you you got money in that
ain't it? You're okay now, right?
>> Me and
never struggle when we're together.
>> Yeah, it's good, isn't it?
>> Yeah, it is. It's all right.
>> Yeah. So, I'm going to jump PJ. Yeah, I said >> about
you don't see any of them coming up and
joining about it anyway. No,
>> I know it's true.
>> Yeah, it is. >> Cab,
>> but yeah.
>> Oh, Franklin sticking his middle finger up.
Bless you, Franklin.
Yeah. Oh [ __ ]
>> Yeah, man.
>> I was thinking of getting a breakfast
like a breakfast.
>> This ain't my point.
>> I was just talking.
>> No, in fact, this ain't my point. This is [ __ ]
not at this point.
Um, she does. I was talking about
[ __ ] I said about me showing the
sales that the dicks off on this
community and Nat just jumped on to
Natalie bring Natalie up and Natalie
turned around and said yeah they will do
it's because these are not in the
relationships theelves they just want me
and you are you
>> and that's it.
>> So they will bring that up. They will
bring that they will bring I already
said that a minute ago or didn't I? So >> yeah,
>> [ __ ] it TJ. Tell them to come up. You
tell them to
>> tell them to the link's there. The
>> Put another one up. Pick another one up.
Let's actually [ __ ]
>> Just show them now. That that
just let them just embarrass theelves,
PJ. Best option. I think all these will
tell you as well. The good people in
here. Just let them embarrass themselves.
>> Yeah. One second. Hold on. I'll post a
link. Hold on.
>> You know what? Yeah, you have to do is
just keep the video up.
Come on, Pete.
>> No, no. Go on. Go on.
>> Yeah, I'll put a link up.
>> Yeah, man.
>> Oh, [ __ ] Have a left. >> No.
Hey, Monty, are you there?
[ __ ] disabled community.
>> I'm on I sent you something on face I
sent you something on Facebook.
>> Yeah, I'm not taking anything just yet.
She just kicks me off.
>> Yeah, that Red Star just talk he stalks
me every day. No, Red Sn is Red Star you
know now. Yeah.
>> No, but he's watching cuz he always
watches. He stalks me from the time he
wakes up to the time he goes to bed.
>> I think he fes, you know, DJ,
>> maybe. Yeah.
>> Why don't you ask him on a date or something?
>> He says that I'm triggered, but I says
you're the one that's triggered. You
must be triggered to be online every day
doing what you do. You must be the
triggered one. Did he say a day? No,
>> he puts on his channel that I'm I'm
triggered and stuff.
>> Oh my god.
These people are triggered, huh?
>> No, no, they are. They are triggered.
That's why they want to come on up on
the panel now because they're the ones
who are triggered, not us. This is why
the the [ __ ] Where's the three great
guys anyways? Where are they?
>> They're wanking each other off. who
gums gorgeous Natalie. Now,
>> when do you reckon these was the last
time these people left their house?
>> Uh, I don't know. I don't know. I think
soon I think from when they left school.
They've never left around. >> Yeah.
I think you and Timmy should go for a pine.
We still [ __ ] Timmy, I call you
Timmy now. Yeah. >> What?
What you calling? I'm going to start
calling you Timmy now. >> Okay.
No, I think you No, but I The only No,
Monty. The only reason I bring up
[ __ ] nonsense is because I always say
this to you, bro. Because I met him through you.
I met that [ __ ] weirdo through you. You know,
>> I can't hear you, bro. You put your hand.
>> Yeah. No, no, I know. I know. I'm just
giving that a kiss.
>> No, I was just saying it's cuz I met
that weirdo through you.
>> No, not through me. Through the
community on PlayStation.
>> Through you.
>> How's it through me? Come on then.
It was the same because it was the same
[ __ ] chat room.
>> The same chat room. >> Yeah.
>> Who who did you meet?
>> It was me. It was me, you, him, and one
other person. And he kept going on about
[ __ ] Britney. Don't you remember?
That's how I met you.
>> No. No. I met you in that gay man's
[ __ ] chat room.
That's how I met you in that gay man's
[ __ ] chat. That [ __ ] old man's
It's okay to be gay, Jamie. It's okay to be gay.
>> No, it's not okay to be gay.
>> He said, Jamie, you got nice eyes.
>> [ __ ] off, DJ.
>> Remember that though? He said it.
>> Yeah. He freaking me out.
>> You were there sat there with him
enjoying it. you. >> Nah,
not at all.
>> No, you I give me I got you into the
community, didn't I? With Brew Girls.
>> You used to have a You used to have your
eye on her.
>> Never had me on R girl. >> You
never remember. I remember when I was
walking into the house with Izzy and
then she and and and and Ken, you looked
at me for like the fre. You knew
straight. How did you know straight away
that it was the freom eye? What?
>> How did you know straight away that when
he looked at me, he was thinking recent?
How did you know?
>> Obviously, you know what men think of?
>> When you gave me the eye, is it?
>> Yeah. All men think like that though.
That's why [ __ ]
He It's not just men. Women are the same.
Women are the same to be honest with you. Yeah,
>> because if it's one man and two women,
one of them women are going to be
expecting or thinking about a freeway. >> Yeah.
>> Either way. >> Jesus
is free, mate. Yeah. So,
what else should I do? PJ
call people skin when they're skin. Um,
they call people ugly when they're ugly.
Um, they call you for what they are.
>> Um, they try to get other people to
fight their battles.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
cuz you can't part their own battles. >> Yeah.
>> Are we going out today? >> No.
>> Well, bless you then. If you're going
out then, you can go out to the pub,
Jamie. Bless you.
>> No, we're not going out today.
>> Oh, bless.
>> We're going out next week.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah, I know. We're going next week. [ __ ]
Want to see some dolphins.
We see some dark things next week.
>> I didn't I didn't even think that
Britney was that good-look. >> What?
>> I didn't think Britney was good-looking. >> Britney. >> Yeah.
>> Who knows?
>> I don't know why he was so obsessed with
[ __ ] Britney. So, sorry to bring it
up and [ __ ] but I used I used to have
to hear about it like cuz I used to have
to hear about it all the time cuz
>> she was a child. PJ. >> Yeah,
>> that's funny. [Laughter]
>> That's funny. Anybody?
>> No, not really. M.
>> Oh [ __ ]
>> [ __ ] hell.
Remember everyone used to bully him on PlayStation?
>> Yeah. Everybody.
>> Everyone. Aaron Cox [ __ ] I know he's
on YouTube but he doesn't get bullied. >> Huh?
>> I know he's on YouTube.
>> No, no, no, no. But do you know why? No,
no, Monty. But do you know why? The
reason he doesn't is because people
don't like me and he goes for me. As
soon as I come, say me and you come off
now. Yeah. For a week, they'll all go for him.
You get it?
>> Yeah. Of course. Of course. But
>> yeah, that's exactly what happens.
>> I don't get that. I don't get that. No.
Can I tell you something only? Why they
don't go for him? Really, you need
because they like Sean better than they
like you. And that's what it is. >> Yeah.
>> Sean's a [ __ ] actual [ __ ] pedo.
And they like that. And they like them
people. And that's what
>> if we come off if we come off, they will
go for him. You know what I mean?
>> But not really. Not really.
>> Well, L does and people in L chat do.
They a lot of people do.
>> Will do. But you won't see these go up
on his handouts or his [ __ ] thing.
All watches he gets is about one or two
watches and that's it.
>> But that's it. The most he will ever get
on his channel is one or two watches and
that's about it. >> Yeah.
>> He gets loads of thumbs up when he when
he does videos of you.
>> Yeah. He's obsessed with it.
or buying from that.
>> Think of it, Monty. These people are so
skinn and disabled, they probably can't
even go to the pub and have a drink.
>> See, again with the skintess PJ with them, >> huh?
>> Again with the skint, man. You're doing
it exactly the same as what they do.
>> Well, they're so disabled they they they
can't go to even go to the pub and
afford a drink. How about that?
>> They can't. They can't. They can't even
have bought a [ __ ] packet from the shop. >> Yeah.
I don't understand when people say they
do it for reaction because even if you
don't react to them, they'll still do
it. Even if you don't watch them,
they'll still do it.
>> Yeah. It's all because you have on their
mind. Yeah. Their content is
>> and that's what it is. They want content
and they're all here because they're
laughing at what? They're laughing at
us, but they're laughing at theelves.
They're laughing at themselves included
cuz they're the ones sat there watching
us. So, it's me laughing at them really
boring content. What's not even worth
what a couple of people arguing when you
could be watching [ __ ] people,
you know, [ __ ]
what knows? Could be watching porno and
having a wank for [ __ ] sake. >> Yeah,
>> obviously. Obviously, I don't need to.
>> I watch some new approaching videos
today, Grezy. It come up on Instagram.
Someone's videos come up on Instagram
and I was watching them. It was just the
same [ __ ] Same old, is it?
>> So, why do I get Why do I pull? >> Huh?
>> Why do I pull?
>> Yeah, you pulled when you was with me,
isn't it? You know, I thought football
when I was with you.
>> Yeah, you did. That the one that only
likes bald people.
>> Oh, the one the one who was striking me for ages.
>> Yeah, you fingered her in the corner.
>> Yeah, I [ __ ] finger anyone in the corner.
>> [ __ ] You're going to get rec.
>> I'm joking. I'm joking, man. [ __ ]
Monty has had different experiences to
pee as well, Greavvesy. Monty has had
different experiences to pee.
point that out.
>> What is that? Scared. What?
>> We're too scared to leave that the house
in case we miss content. >> Yeah.
>> Molly, look what I sent you on Facebook.
[ __ ] sake, please. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> You see what I mean? This is This is
every day, Monty. Every [ __ ] day.
Red Star got content to
>> n people. Let me ask you all a question. Yeah.
What is content to you people? Actual
like and I'm not on about like sitting
there arguing or calling people on
YouTube. What is content to you people?
Because repeating in content it's like
[ __ ] is it? >> No.
What content? What content can you
people do? What people explain content
to me? Come on. Cuz I can explain
perfect content to you people now. Like literally. >> Yeah. >> Content
going um going on adventures, going for walks, countryides,
going out country sides. Um that's like
fuse and all that. what country what
some people are into. Um, what else?
What else? Um,
underground tunnels like I do. Like
second world war bunkers, all that.
Yeah, that's content.
Um, content. Content. What else is Come
on, PJ. Give name some content. Yeah.
>> Go to the pictures.
>> Not exactly because we recording there,
PJ. That's not content. Not really.
That's just copyrighting.
See, content is sitting there doing
Lego, making houses out of Lego or
[ __ ] doing jigsaw puzzles or doing
coloring books and [ __ ] like that.
That's all sort of content.
Doing worse searches content.
Make a game out of a word search.
All content what you do on this
community is nowhere near their content
is basically okay. It's not even
bullying. It's childish
and that's it. What what what content do
you people get out of sitting on YouTube
targeting people who you don't know?
What's the content in that? You're
laughing at [ __ ] other people who you
don't know. And that was [ __ ] bad on
my behalf to be honest with you all that
you all actually I feel sorry for you to be honest.
Feel so sorry for you like you all sat
on YouTube and you you can't do actual content like literally
no I'm actually being serious PG but I
do feel sorry for these people. Sorry.
Sorry about that, but I was on the I was
listening to something. What you saying?
>> Oh, just saying that I feel sorry for Le
because these people can't do content or
they can't make content. They've got to
stay on YouTube and argue with people
who they don't know and laugh at people
who they don't know just going to own
content just to make them feel a little
bit more happier in life.
>> Yeah, that's them. You know what I mean?
If you see content and actually [ __ ]
dumb videos, I'm not being
>> I might pop to the chicken shop soon, Grezy.
>> Pop into the chicken shop. It's nice to
pop to the chicken shop, isn't it, Grezy?
>> I'm a bit peckish.
>> What you getting from the chicken shop?
>> Some chicken.
>> What are you getting from the chicken
shop? Some chicken.
That's cute, isn't it?
>> That's cute, is it? Monty,
>> I'm going to go to the shop and get some
[ __ ] chicken. Yeah. So, be back later.
>> TJ, can I tell you something about the chicken?
>> Before you go and get it, you know, you
eating chicken from last night's
chicken. Yesterday's chicken.
>> No, cuz I make them No, cuz I make them
make it fresh. I'm not stupid, bro. I
make I always make them make it fresh
because if not, it's dry. So, no,
I'm not stupid.
>> It has to You have to have chicken when
it's been out for like 10 minutes
maximum. Otherwise, it just dries out.
>> Sometimes Sometimes they give it you
[ __ ] cold and that sometimes.
>> No, they put it in like a thing, but
that keeps it warm, but it dries it out.
If it dries it out, it's no good.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> So, it's [ __ ] But it's just open so it
should be all right. Anyways, I'll be
back later anyways. Yeah.