and from Cornwall at the foot of England.
>> I've never I've been Bris I've been
Bristol. I've been to Cardiff. >> Yeah.
The the country accent is very crazy.
Yeah, but you know what I'm talking
about. I got a friend from Bristol and
he sounds like a right car by the way. >> Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I need to go for scope. I never never
Few places I've not been to.
Some people don't. Yeah.
I've been I've been to Bournemouth,
which is It's nice. It's nice though.
>> Yeah. Right. Yeah, >> yeah,
>> yeah, yeah, yeah.
>> It's what? Yeah, of course it is. [ __ ]
>> you ever been to uh you ever been to
Middlesbrough? [ __ ] [ __ ]
about two places good.
Every every I've been there. It's been a
good [ __ ] class. Yeah,
>> I've been there three times. Three
times. [ __ ] class, man.
>> You know the leads.
I that. So I've been most places. The
only the only places I've not been is Blackpool,
Glasgow. I've been to Scotland but not
Glasgow. Glasgow and Cornwall, Plymouth,
Satan lead them bouncers, they hate
Southerners. They [ __ ] like you as
soon as they here, you're from down
south. They have a [ __ ]
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> I used to do like every
every every every week I used to [ __ ]
off to another city like cuz I had a
rail card like so I just go leave Newcastle [ __ ] off.
>> I've been there four times. I've not
been to Swansea. I've been to Scard. I
can't card if Do you know what though?
I've been to Manchester
10 times. I've only been to Liverpool
once and I've always been meaning to go
back up, but it's never a couple. >> Okay.
Uh you Manchester just >> Yeah.
some money. Okay. >> Yeah.
>> You want to You want to go You want to
go back to
>> I I was in B I was in Birmingham, mate.
I was in I was in Birmingham last month
and it was so I've been five times but
the time before last month I hadn't been
there about two years but I went to meet
my friend and he was having like a bad
time and a breakup so I thought [ __ ] it
let me go there but feel a sh Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yes.
One thing about leads, it's expensive
though. It's [ __ ] the hotel. I was
saying that 170 cost me 40 quid to get
my [ __ ] haircut. It's expensive
though. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Have you ever been to Hull? I've never been there. No.
>> Have you been to Have you been
>> What school is that? That's That's I would say,
>> you know what I love about Scotland?
Yeah. You come out the train station and
next to the train station, it's just
full of like open weather spoons where
people are like just getting pissed
right next to the train station. And
even on the train, people was [ __ ]
offering me drinks. I was like, >> "Yeah,
yeah." And literally, but I should have
went to Glasgow as well.
I heard it's dangerous, but
>> Yeah. Yeah. But
>> yeah, Liverpool I definitely miss. I was
thinking of like this. Yeah. So going on
a night out in a different city on a
Friday, Saturday. So I need to pick two
cities. One for the Friday and one for
the Saturday. But obviously I'd have to
stick to beer. If I if I drink [ __ ]
spirits, I'll be [ __ ] I can't do the
second day. If I if I drink spirits, I'm
[ __ ] for like two three days. I can't
drink the next day. So I stick to beer.
So I was thinking maybe like
Liverpool and party for Glasgow or just Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> But even like say you don't like maybe
you could do Liverpool in Glasgow. That
would be that would be [ __ ] >> Yeah.
I just met I literally just met a woman
about like 30 minutes ago from [ __ ]
from abroad said that she was doing
English and talking got her number and
[ __ ] but she's like she couldn't
pronounce it like yeah
>> I've been I've been to Bristol but I've
not been on a night out in Bristol.
I went there. I went I went to Bristol,
you know, when the co [ __ ] was going on
and they just just opening the pubs and
that was the time I was supposed to go
to Wales, but if you went to Wales, you
couldn't come back. They weren't letting
people travel from Wales. So, I had to
go to Bristol and [ __ ]
>> You just
You're never too old, man. You're You're
as old. You're as old as you can. [Laughter] >> Yeah. >> 60.
How old would you say you are when
getting old? How how old do you is
getting old? For me, I would say 50.
You know what? I listen. You're
going to you're going to laugh at this. So,
you're going to laugh at this. So, I'm
I'm I'm right.
And compared to 3 4 years ago when I was
23 24 I feel like I'm [ __ ] 100 years
old man. I feel so like I don't know. I
just feel 100 years [ __ ] old and
>> Yeah. I feel like I'm [ __ ] 100. Don't get
>> Yeah, literally I'm I'm [ __ ] I'm 28
in two months. I'm 28 in two months and
I was like I've got to do [ __ ] I've got
to do [ __ ] There's no point in No. No way.
It's like this is you'll laugh at this
though cuz my my mom is be five in three
days and she wishes she was 40 again. So
I think [ __ ] like you see what I
mean? Like it depends how old you are to
how you consider old. You know what I mean? >> Yeah. My friend,
>> my friend. >> Yeah.
>> Oh no. Yeah.
They were laughing at you. They were mocking you.
>> They were mocking you. That's what they
were doing. Horrible bastards, man. Horrible.
>> But my friends moved to Thailand. He My
friends moved to Thailand. He loves
Thailand. He moved like he he's been
there three times in a year. And the
first time he's not coming back. Said he
loves it. He [ __ ] loves it. He said
it's too depressing here. You said it's too [ __ ]
>> 10 years
I was in Mexico before that was the
expression in Mexico
and eventually I been eaten Thailand.
Yeah. Wonderful the winter sunless summer.
See me, I I I hate I hate the winter. I
hate the summer. So here, my favorite
month is probably April
>> cuz it's like in between. It's not cold
and it's not hot. >> Hate. >> Yeah.
>> I hate the heat. I hate it when it's
too. I'll just sit in my room. [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah, I just like it in between. But
yeah, like today's just right. Just it's
just right. But I hate it. I hate the
cold and I hate the heat. I like it like Yeah. [Music] >> Yeah.
>> Of course. Yeah.
You're not uh you're not drinking today.
to be honest I'm not drunk in about 3
weeks another thing as you get older
even now 23 27 you don't do it as much you like you know
23 24 and Right
now, if I stick to beer today, tomorrow
I'll be fine. I'll get a bit be a bit
tired, but fine. If I drink spirits,
which I probably will do later,
I'm going to be [ __ ] like those.
That's the thing. That's the That's the problem. >> Yeah.