Yeah. You know what? Funny.
>> The dichotomy was mad.
>> Funny. Funny you used to say Islington,
right? That's where you know, that's
where one of the first five guys was.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Yeah. So, I went there. I remember going
there. It was opposite the super dry.
You know the super dry. You know that
the little shop bit
>> in the >> Yeah.
>> In isn't opposite it was the Five Guys.
>> So, before it comes to the cup big, one
of the first ones was in Islington. So,
I thought, "Oh, [ __ ] it." Like heard
people like going there.
Let me let me just spend it and go there.
>> Yeah. So, yeah, that's and I don't think
I've been there since. I think I might
have been through there, but >> yeah.
>> Don't think I've actually been there now.
>> I would say
Angel is back in the day. >> Yeah.
>> Used to be very like London, right? >> Yeah.
>> Now, like all them media types, that's
they're doing, you know, they're making
money. Good for them, whatever. the
media types, actors, you know, wealthy creatives
>> are living there. >> Yeah.
>> With children
and the children being rich.
>> So they're putting on this performance
in year eight
>> and then next year, next summer in >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? That's not how you talk. >> 100%.
Yeah, you're not too far. No. No.
You're like Wolfen Wolf and S. If you
keep going from Wolf and Sophi way [ __ ]
>> when I when I work here
I work with like live in Tottenham.
>> Yeah. So like
the thing is when you when you meet
people when you meet people here a lot
of the time they'll say they're from
like south or they're from west
obviously because we're in west London.
So when you say when somebody says
they're from east you just know they're
near you like me cuz east ain't that
big. I met some I've met people from
Mland which is where I live now as Mland
or up the road or Wolfen like you know I
was born in Lenstone but I was born in
Leighton stone then I moved to Leighton
then I moved to Strapford so I've always
been like it's London so I hate West I
hate like shepherd I don't know anyone
there I feel like I don't know anyone
>> an old person's game then >> what
do you mean an old person's I like
>> Yeah, I like
I like coming to Soho. I like, you know, small
been before man house.
>> Yeah. I've never been,
>> you know, walking.
>> Oh, bless you. Yeah. Yeah. I I don't
know about I don't know. I've been to
Yeah. I've never been. >> Yeah.
>> You know what? You know what? You know
one place I hate street. It's full of so
many sucked up people. I don't like it.
They're so Have you been there?
>> It's good for the restaurants and cuz I
love I love Indians.
>> You're not a vegetarian, are you? >> No.
>> A lot of the people I meet, they're
vegetarians and it's kind of like,
>> you know what?
>> It's hard to relate. for ethical
reasons. Ag 12 to 19 I was right. >> Yeah.
>> For eical reasons. I was like I wouldn't
want someone to kill me else. But now I
understand. Then I got really sick. I
tried carnival. Best of my life
>> and I I started feeling alive again.
Literally I did you know I start feeling
if you if you meet someone that's uh
vegetarian where you going to go to eat
man? Like when you when you take them
like for a nice restaurant on like your
anniversary or whatever, what are you taking there?
>> I mean like you know sushi and steak. Easy.
>> I love steak. Love steak.
>> steak's my favorite.
>> My f like I like
>> What's your favorite thing to say?
>> You know what I like any steak for like
calorie reasons. If I'm cutting one but like what?
>> Obviously fatty. Obviously
>> No, no, no, no, no. But like
>> I like fatty with salt.
>> No, no, but there's different like
Yeah. What kind
>> is like [Music]
I love my my favorite is T-bone
>> then it's spill it then it's sirloin.
>> I've not had much t-bone in my life.
>> Never had never had t-bone.
>> The only thing at home
>> the problem no you go to the butchers
and get a t-bone but it's a lot harder
nowadays. But the reason I prefer T-bone
than like fillet is because T-bone is
half sirloin with the fat and then half filling.
>> So obviously the F don't have the fat.
So you've got the best of both. T-bone is
>> T-bone is banging. T-bone.
>> Let me let me guess. You have yours bloody. Yeah.
>> You like it? What? Not completely wrong.
>> I do sometimes when I'm hungry. I can't
like get you.
I'll get my lamb chop out the fridge.
>> So, will you
>> Well, you just eat it. Well, you just
eat the steak without it being good.
>> It is good.
>> You eat it raw?
>> [ __ ] I know you could I know you can
eat it raw, but I I know I like
>> I love it.
>> I like mine like this. A a tiny bit
pink, but no blood. Like pink cuz
obviously if you overdo it, you rub it
there. But I can't have any blood, man. No way.
>> So yeah,
>> let me tell you something.
>> And it's tender.
>> Come on.
>> I cook. Yeah, you're not you're not
going to laugh at this. Yeah, but I cook
very good pork chops.
>> I can cook you some pork chops. I'm I'm
so good at it. But it's going to it's Huh.
>> Lamb chops might
>> Yeah, obviously you're going to prefer
lamb over pork. But I'm saying with pork
I can do bang and p but it's going to say
>> just cook them really slowly in it.
>> But it's going to take about 45 minutes. >> Interesting.
>> Once they're done there,
6 a.m. 5 a.m. Yeah. I'm like