Oh, what?
I'm back. Back.
Exactly, bro. [ __ ]
I'm [ __ ] wasted, bro.
[ __ ] hell, bro. I'm [ __ ] more
racing than [ __ ] thank them.
Have to try and make this bed somehow. Easy. Yeah.
Coming home. I'm pissed. again getting
into some nice fresh coffee. Oh, [ __ ]
Oh [ __ ] that's got some [ __ ]
Where am I,
man? Sent it. I got four numbers for
Sunday. Give me some credit, bro. been
out the game for like three weeks.
Oh, [ __ ] me. Try and make this [ __ ]
bed somehow, bro. Yeah, I went out, bro.
[ __ ] uh we might have a we might have
a Finnish Izzy.
Yeah, we might have a Finnish Izzy.
Yeah, m to
Yeah, we got a Finnish Izzy on our
hands. Boss, is that okay with you, boss?
Seems to be the [ __ ] seems to be the
same in me.
Making this bed [ __ ] stealing.
Yeah. Seems to be okay. [ __ ] bro.
I just have a nice pizza
video to come.
Oh man. Give me two seconds. Let me make
this hunting bed.
Yeah. Oh, [ __ ]
numbers. I went out on the piss, bro. I
was [ __ ] [ __ ] wavy to [ __ ]
I was born this. I thought, [ __ ] it, let
me just get on the piss. It Sunday for
a very long time.
Bro, you can't get into bedding that
ain't fresh. It has to be a fresh bed.
Let me make this bed. Give me a second.
I'm not looking at
two seconds, bro.
Not damp, is it? But even if it is damp.
Oh, abandoned escort. I say abandoned
escort, bro. [ __ ]
in a [ __ ] mouth and
yeah, I comes in a [ __ ] mouth, bro.
Throat as well. But yeah, to be honest,
to be honest with you,
one second, please. I need to do this properly.
To be honest with you, today I wasn't
even pissed off. Nah, I don't. One
second. Right. I'll talk to you in a
bit. Let me do this. I'm in bed.
Sorry. Hold on.
Few seconds. Few seconds.
B is getting old, mate. I can't be doing
this [ __ ] forever.
Needs to become rich.
[ __ ] I can't be that skinned virgin in Kent.
[ __ ] with a disabled girlfriend.
[ __ ] I'm getting too old for this
[ __ ] man. I'm getting too old for this
One second. Where's the
This is probably the only time I Okay.
Two seconds, bro. Two minutes. A
Right. At least it's a [ __ ] sit,
mate. Had a roast dinner, got pissed.
I got I got roast dinner, got pissed,
and got a pizza at the end of the night,
mate. What you want?
Where's this [ __ ]
dip thing there? Oh, lovely. One sec. God. [Applause] Um, okay.
You going or what? One sec.
Why is it not blowing up?
One second, bro.
Why is that not going up?
Is it C or anything?
Oh, it's [ __ ]
It is actually [ __ ]
The ship is actually [ __ ]
I'm sorry, bro. I'm not ignoring you. I
just need to I can see you in the back
of my head. ign
your text now. I went out today setting
it, bro. [ __ ] me. I don't know about
petty sober, bro. No word of a lie.
We was the same old [ __ ] I have a
boyfriend. and I have my boyfriend
[ __ ] got one number. I ended up
getting four numbers in the end.
Ended up meeting somebody from [ __ ] uh Finland.
It reminded me of you a little bit. So,
I got four numbers in the end, but
[ __ ] it was [ __ ] hard, bro. It's
why I don't go out here anymore. I went
out today cuz I was bored. It didn't
even piss me off to be fair cuz it
didn't piss me off cuz I know it's
always going to be like that here.
So, I played at my own risk. I went out
cuz I was bored and I paid a price for
it. So, it doesn't even piss me off cuz
it will always be that way. Yeah.
Nothing to be pissed off about. It's
always going to be the same same old
I have a boyfriend and no [ __ ] So, I
didn't get pissed off to be fair, but I
got four numbers.
Give me a minute.
Two seconds, lad.
That's kind of a lot, though. Four on a
Sunday is a lot, bro. I never go out on
Sundays. I just fancied getting drunk
today, bro. I don't know why.
I just fancied getting pissed.
One second, man.
I just absolutely knew.
It was hard, man.
One second, bro. I'm going to mute the
mic for two seconds, bro. Hold on.
Do you want to see who I met today?
Steven Howard, I've got a little video
if you want.
Two sex, lad. Bye-bye.
Got self reflect on uh the one in the video. No.
Bro, no one's autistic like you. Fat ugly [ __ ]
Bro, you you sit on YouTube every day
cuz you're autistic. Fat ugly bastards.
Don't self-reflect your [ __ ] onto me,
bro. Why is these [ __ ] plus five?
You people are autistic. Stop talking about yourselves. Uhhuh.
Wait, hold on, bro.
What a [ __ ] day I've had. Literally,
bro. It's a madness, bro. I swear to God.
So basically, right, I [ __ ] What the
How has that happened? One second.
>> Right. Listen, listen, listen.
Hey, bro. I met this person. I'm sure
they were [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Oh man, I need to change my boxes. I
have to change my Chucky boxes.
[ __ ] hell. Listen, one sec. One sec.
Oh my god. I just made my bed as well.
Um, basically right, I went out today
cuz [ __ ] it, why not? Oh, Stitchboxes.
Lovely. Changing to these ones.
Uh, basically right, I went out today, Nicolola. And uh
basically what happened was I
had a roast in so I done I done 10
approaches sober. I got one number.
She's like, "Oh, I'm seeing someone." I
said, "How long you been seeing them
for?" Said, "Oh, 3 months." The first
one I said, "Oh, do you need a new
boyfriend?" She said, "Oh, I got a
boyfriend." I said, "Do you want a new
one?" That's the first one I done. I was
like, "Oh, you could do with a new
boyfriend, is it?" So, I know about 10
of them, bro. I know. Well, I don't know
about 10 of them. Yeah. [ __ ] one
said, "Oh, she's with someone for three
months." I said, "Yeah, really." I said,
"Give me give me your number in it.
Let's change that in it." So, I got I
got one number.
I got one number out of them. 10, bro. I
sent it sober, bro. I don't give a [ __ ]
I don't need alcohol, bro. I sent 10
sober, bro. I got one [ __ ] number
sober. Yeah. And then I got four numbers
all in all, but obviously the rest of
them were [ __ ] tipsy slash drunk cuz
I could be [ __ ] doing any more sober
after that. I met somebody from Finland.
I think I found a new mama. I'm going to
I met this person as well. I'm going to
put it up. I'm going to put it up on my
YouTube channel right now. But in the
end, she was kind of being a bit of a
[ __ ] But I got four numbers on a
Sunday. I mean, [ __ ] it ain't bad, is
it? But bro, I sent it hard, bro.
[ __ ] hard. And to be honest with you,
it didn't piss me off. And I got an
escort in that, but it didn't piss me
off because I know that it's nothing to
be pissed off about. It's never going to
change here. It's never going to change.
So why are you going to get pissed off,
bro? It's never going to change in this country.
One second. Let me put it Let me put it
up, bro. Let me put it up.
I'm uploading it. I'm uploading it. No,
this is another one. But you understand?
Yeah. Like I don't get pissed off about
it anymore, Nico, because it will always
be the same old here.
Well, upload her. Yeah.
Yeah. I'll show you her if you want to
see what she looks like.
Nicolola, I'll never stop my craziness.
You know what I'm like, K. I mean, you
know what I'm like, mate.
You know what I'm like, mate. But she
was being a [ __ ] in the end. I'm not
going to get into it, but I got four
numbers in the end anyway. So,
which doesn't I mean, that's still good
for us on there, ain't it? [ __ ]
I was just bored, bro. I was just wanted
to I just wanted to [ __ ]
They're all [ __ ] NPCs.
They're all [ __ ] NPCs, bro.
Obviously, I [ __ ] bro. I was [ __ ]
out all [ __ ] day. Just like [ __ ] 3 p.m.
It will never change.
It won't change, never, will it? It will never change.
There you go. She's a bit of a [ __ ] [ __ ] though.
She's a [ __ ]
I'm in my little nesticles now.
It made me think of LT the whole time. Oh, mate.
Yeah, I went in the the the place that
that old [ __ ] was in last time.
I'm saying, bro. Yeah.
Just what I was saying, bro. Yeah,
was never your mama.
Don't try and patronize me. Don't try to
[ __ ] patronize me.
Don't you [ __ ] try and patronize me.
I know what you're like, Nicolo. You're
trying to make me think that you're one
of mine. No, she's not the Finnish one.
You're trying to make me think that I'm [ __ ]
you're you're my friend and [ __ ] You're
not my [ __ ] friend.
You're trying to [ __ ] patronize me
about Oh, Sig was never your mama.
Stig not Peter Belly's mama.
Sig not Peter Belly's mama. Oh, bless you.
I bet you're sat there with all your
little mates when you're typing that
out, in it. Don't try and [ __ ] fool
me. I know what you've been doing for a
[ __ ] long ass time.
Stig not Peter Belly's mama.
You know what I'm saying? Signal Peter
Belly's mama. Ha, where's my mama?
Nicolo, I met some guy today from
Chicago and I told him all about all
about USA is
they were laughing at us.
Now, I'm not giving you her number. She
turned out to be a [ __ ] in in a way kind
of. I'm not going to get into it, but
yeah, England is just the same old England,
you know. It will never change.
But I'd always be out there
looking for that change. I thought, you
know what? Let me go out and look for that change.
Looking for that change. You know what I
mean? I will always be out there looking
for that change.
You know what I'm saying,
bro? What the [ __ ] man? I need to try
to get with that one that said she's
seen someone for 3 months. She needs to
[ __ ] see me, bro. That's what she
needs to do. [ __ ] see me, mate. Not
that other [ __ ] I mean, yeah. I'll
always be looking for that change. No, I
didn't tell everyone. I just told him.
Oh, they were mocking you. They were
laughing at you. Did you hear what I
said to the guy in the pub today? I told
him that as well. They were mocking you.
They were laughing at you.
That's what I said to him. Yeah.
They were mocking you. They were
laughing at you. Go back to my Go back
to my [ __ ] first live stream earlier.
I did say that.
They're mocking you. They were laughing at you.
He agreed. Yeah.
Yeah. She's [ __ ] bro. Nikolai
Virgin boy can't do that. He's still a
virgin. He's going to die a virgin.
Isn't that right, Nicolai?
He's going to die a [ __ ] virgin. He's
going to die a virgin.
He will never change. Yeah. [ __ ]
Do you want my opinion to be? Ah,
they're all [ __ ] They're all [ __ ]
Do you want my opinion? Zipp.
I need to make a cup of [ __ ] mate. Let's go.
I know what you're doing, Nicolo. You're
mocking me when you're writing these
little Do you remember? Why didn't USA
tell me she was my mommy? Cuz she wanted
to keep it a secret. Yeah, I know all
about them days, mate. What you trying
to [ __ ] do? Sign not Peter Belly's mama.
Then Peter Belly's mother
not Peter Bell. You're trying to
patronize me. I know what you're trying to do. Yeah.
Not Peter Bell's mother. [Laughter]
Not Peter Bell's mama.
my opinion to be.
What a [ __ ] day I man. I'm wearing my
[ __ ] I'm wearing my [ __ ]
[ __ ] stitch boxes and [ __ ] all
sorts. What a [ __ ] day I seriously
put a [ __ ] day like that.
Do you reckon Virgin boy is going to lose it?
Steven Albert, you reckon Virgin boy is
going to get laid or he's going to die a
virgin skin on the fans of B?
Anyway, I'm I'm [ __ ] I'm I'm crazy
enough, bro. Even when I'm not [ __ ]
even I'm not drinking. Yeah, s my [ __ ]
that will never get laid. It's why he's
still a virgin.
[ __ ] Kent skin version in a [ __ ]
bedit with a few cheapy cheap [ __ ]
guitars. Shitty guitars with [ __ ] no
money. What a [ __ ] life that is, son.
Sat in a bedit [ __ ] skint as [ __ ]
[ __ ] still a virgin.
See? See why people can't pick on me,
Stephen? Now, cuz I'm I'm a grown man,
mate. You understand? I'm a I'm a grown
[ __ ] man, mate. You think some little
skinny lanky little virgin [ __ ] with no
bed is going to [ __ ] step to someone
like me? Come on, let's let's talk here.
Do you think some scrawny little no
muscle virgin [ __ ] in Kent is going to
ever [ __ ] step to a man like me with
his little no muscle and his little
broken dick that he's never stuck
anything in? You think someone could
step like that to me, sir? [ __ ] now.
[ __ ] now, mate. Speaker
never said to me his fat ugly disabled
girlfriend that can't talk him or that
fat [ __ ] donkey he's working with
mate [ __ ] virgin [ __ ] you know
I'm I'm a [ __ ] mad [ __ ] baby
I mean I'm [ __ ] mad [ __ ]
I need to take some coal
USA is his friend said you shouldn't take cacodamol
even even after [ __ ] drinking
because he said she said that it still
rip the line of stomach but you know
what I've got to say to that [ __ ] a lot
of you know what I'm saying [ __ ] a lot yeah
[ __ ] a lot of you
that's all I've got to
[ __ ] a lot of you, you know.
Oh, he's already got
[ __ ] I wonder how Fraser is doing now.
Always wanted your frame. Even if it was
only up to stand. Always wanted you.
Always liked you.
Always wanted your brain.
Even if it was only at the pun.
Always wondered your phrase.
Even if it was only at the page.
Even if it was only at the pain. You
know what I mean? Always like
I'm going to be [ __ ] for [ __ ] like
three days now on that nasty run, mate. Yeah.
The other one I approached
it was sexy.
What a [ __ ] [ __ ] man.
I got her number, man. She had to go
back to work, but I got her number.
I got a few people's numbers.
Oh my god. [ __ ] mo move
my little stitch boxes. Oh [ __ ] Good
old man. I had a pizza, man. I had a
pizza. I had roast beef today and I had a pizza.
A bit gobby. Yeah, she's an horrible old [ __ ]
Yeah. Oh, Franklin. No, I can't play
Franklin. I'm too drunk. Yeah.
[ __ ] horrible old [ __ ] You should
saw the other numbers I got. [ __ ]
horrible old [ __ ]
Horrible old [ __ ] mate. Yeah.
>> Oh man, that will get that will grind
LJ's [ __ ] uh that will grind LJ's gears
in he and and also the Virgin as well
cuz obviously he's never going to lose
it. So [ __ ] what I mean, mate.
You know a main son he's never ever ever
lose that ray go. Ah.
Oh, it's just someone I met, Mr. B. I've
been out all [ __ ] day, mate, on the piss.
I've been out all day, mate, on the [ __ ] piss.
Let me know. Let me know. Oh [ __ ] I've
been out all day on a [ __ ] piss,
mate. Oh, I was drunk. I'm drunk. I was
drunk as [ __ ] bro. I got four numbers
today. I got I Bro, I've done 10
approaches sober. I was just bored, so I
thought, "Fuck it. Let me just go out. I
won't be out now for like another two
weeks or so." Um,
oh, [ __ ] steaming, bro. Yeah. Yeah,
she is a
she's a horrible old [ __ ] And then Mr.
B, did you see earlier when I was live
speaking to that guy?
He looked like a Barry.
That old man, did you see Did you see
Did you hear that old man speaking? He
sound He looked like a Barry, didn't he?
He looked like a Barry.
He looked like a Hey. Hey, Mr. B. Didn't
he look like a Barry, bro? Or is it just
me? You didn't see him,
bro? That guy was so weird, man. I was speaking to
I was speaking to him. [Laughter]
I said they were laughing at you. They
were mocking you. That's what I said. Oh, mate.
Yeah, that did you hear him earlier? The
old man, Mr. B, who said, "Put the cam
on." Yeah, we was having a lovely chat. Lovely combo.
We was having a lovely conversation.
I don't like old people. They smell [Laughter]
old people seem to smell. I don't know why. Yeah.
Barry. What a [ __ ] name, mate. Barry.
I think he said his name was Barry.
Barry, wasn't it? He said, "I need to
visit Cornwall sometime."
[ __ ] Barry, bro.
What the [ __ ] Yeah.
Somerset now slow. You remember when
that [ __ ] Fraser kept [ __ ] with
me, Nicolo? Yeah. I said, listen, I was
keeping it quiet. Yeah. Me and LT had
this [ __ ] behind the scenes. I was like,
let him join the hang. Let him join the
live stream. And I said, Somerset now,
slow cuz he was he was from Somerset.
Somerset. Somerset. Then he moved to
slow. I said, "Somerset now slow." He
said, "You're [ __ ] mad." I said,
"Yeah, that's what you get for [ __ ]
with me, son. Somerset now slam."
He was like, "You [ __ ] what?" I said,
"Yeah, we all know. We know all about
you, Bossy. We know all about you, son." Yeah.
And I said, "Do you reckon the trolls do
you reckon you privatize your Instagram
just in time, Fraser?" He said, "Nah,
mate. They got what they wanted." He
said, "Them people on YouTube, they got
what they wanted, mate." That's what he
said. He said them people on YouTube got
what they wanted, mate.
That's what he said.
They would have got what they wanted,
mate. That's what he said.
They would go what they wanted me
Nah, they would have got what they
wanted, mate. Trust me, eh? They would have.
Oh, I got a [ __ ] nice [ __ ] Mr. B.
It cost me 70, bro. I come in the
bitch's mouth, bro. I was fingerling her
and everything, bro. I was fingerling
her and kissing her as well [ __ ]
earlier, mate. [ __ ] bro. Swear. >> Yeah.
[ __ ] I come in her throat and
everything, bro. And I was fingerling
her and kissing her. It was an escort, mate. Yeah.
Yeah. Monty Monty's dad's name is Barry.
Hey, that's a Barry. What a name, eh? Why? >> What?
>> Your your dad's name is Barry, isn't it?
>> No. Is it [ __ ]
>> I swear it is Barry.
>> My dad's name's not Barry, you dick.
>> Yeah, but you don't even know that was a
name, did you?
>> Yeah, Barry's a name. Yeah.
>> But I met an old man today. His name was Barry. PGF.
>> Yeah, man.
>> What was the [ __ ] like, PGF? Um,
it was nice.
>> It was a nice way you pay for it, did you?
>> Only a little bit.
>> How much did you pay?
>> Whatever you mind. It's our little secret.
>> I'm going to get 70 quid. Yeah.
>> Bit less.
>> So, about 60 50.
Nah, bit less, bro.
>> About 30.
To be honest with you, Nicolo, I went
out today, bro, cuz I was bored. I
hadn't been out for three weeks. I just
wanted to get drunk, man.
>> Like, you remember like when I do, hey,
I was, you know, I was telling a few I
was telling a few people, Monty, I was
telling a few people about you um today.
Like, I went to Birmingham last month
because my friend was crying over a
bird, so I had to go and pick up the pieces.
>> Why bring me or what you bring?
>> Because I said like the last time I left
London was [ __ ] a month ago. I had to
go to Birmingham to [ __ ] pick up the
pieces for some [ __ ] [ __ ] crying over a bird.
>> You know what I mean, bro?
>> Who's that? Who's that? Jamie,
>> I've never cried over a
>> Who's this?
>> Who's he?
>> Please don't tell me this is Timmy.
>> Hello, PJ.
>> Oh no, it's Timmy. Monty, it's me.
>> I've been watching your background
videos. You've been skinned out of your
head this week, haven't you?
>> One second. One second. Hey, Monty. One
second. Why don't Hey, Timmy. Yeah. Why
don't me, you, and Monty meet up for a pint?
>> I don't like Monty, man. He's a nons.
>> Timmy. Yeah.
He's been with He's been with teenage
dating apps. Doesn't that
>> Listen, listen. Timmy. Timmy. Timmy. You
talk about people being a nonch
listen you you support nonslegs and he
actually is the
>> I support the English whites and
bringing England to how it is and
getting rid of all you bacons in prison.
All you bacons get away with murder. You
do [ __ ] foul [ __ ] Innocent person.
He needs he needs to grow up.
>> 3 months suspended sentence. Our
government needs to be ashamed.
>> Monty, I think he I think he needs to grow up.
>> I don't mate. The only reason why you
get let off cuz new labours in they love.
>> I have to kick him Monty. He needs to
grow up bro. It's ridiculous at his age
now. Come on.
And you laugh at him, Monty. I don't
know how you laugh at it. Right, money?
Yeah, I done 10 sober. Me, I done 10
sober, bro. I don't give a [ __ ] bro. I
do. I do. Easy, man. Easy to do with me.
I'm not scared.
Yeah, I done [ __ ] 10 sober, man.
It was about 10. I'm sure it was about 9
or 10. I done
I think I done one at a train station as
well, bro. I don't give a [ __ ] mate.
You don't understand. I don't give a
[ __ ] I'll do some more tomorrow. I
don't give a [ __ ] I'll keep doing it
until I find Mrs. Right. I will keep
doing it until I find Mrs. Right. You understand?
Yeah. That's what I was saying. That's
what I was saying to myself. Everyone is chilling crazy.
>> Yeah. Too [ __ ] right.
Yeah. I was saying that to myself as
well. I won't stop until I find a new mama.
I won't stop until I find a new mama,
you know. I will not stop until I find
until I find a new mama.
I won't stop. Yeah.
Yeah. Virgin boy. Virgin boy will never ever ever
be able to do that. Which is why he's
still a virgin. Do you not understand?
Do you not understand? That's why he's
still a virgin.
No, I'll never know. Yeah, that one
today, she looked British. Yeah. And uh
I thought it was her mom. I said, "Oh, I
didn't want to like um interrupt you.
Obviously, you're with your mom." and it
was her [ __ ] sister. But she was all
nice about it and that we were speaking
for like 10 minutes and [ __ ] and I was
like, I have to do this because if I
don't, I'll never know, you know? I
don't want to ever be, you know, put in
that position where no, I'll never know.
You know, it's you never want to be in
that position, you know,
where you say to yourself, no, I'm
never. No, no, it's not even funny, bro.
It's horrible. I thought it was her
[ __ ] mom, bro. She looked a lot
older, but she was nice about it as
well, you know.
The first number I got was [ __ ] Oh,
man. She was [ __ ] lame, man. She
said, "Oh, oh yeah, I'm seeing someone."
I said, "Oh, yeah. How long you been
with them? 3 months." I said, "Listen,
let me give give me your number in it."
And then what? You know, I'll message
you anyway. See what happens.
I want to do it tomorrow, but I'll
probably be too hung over.
I'll probably be too hung over. I don't
even have loads of loads of money, bro.
This is the problem now is the
affordability of it all as well. Now, I
still have money and [ __ ] but I'm
leaving in [ __ ] November, bro. I got
to be careful.
I [ __ ] spent I got roast dinner
today. I got [ __ ] Then I got pizza at
the end of the night.
I need to kind of be a bit, you know,
I don't have loads and loads and loads
and loads and loads and loads of money
anymore, bro. But [ __ ] I need to
leave in November, so you know.
But yeah, it didn't even bother me. I've
done so many yesterday and it never
bothered me cuz I know what it is in
this country now. So, I'm playing it at
my own risk.
I just know what it's always going to be
like. So, I mean, it didn't it didn't
even bother me, bro. To be honest, it
was a tiny bit depressing, but I just
got over it cuz,
you know, you're playing at your own
risk. When you go out and you try, it's
at your own risk,
you know, and that's that's the problem,
you know. It will never change here,
but there might be a slim 1% chance. And
if you got nothing better to do then,
you know, I just really fancy getting
pissed today, bro. That's why I done it.
Just trying to look for a new mama. A
mama that will love me. I got a Norway
number. I got Brazilian number. And I
got two English numbers. So four on a
Sunday ain't bad.
Sweating. Why the [ __ ] would I be
sweating, bro? I'm not scared to do them.
Why would I be sweating?
They don't bother me, bro. I'm not
scared to do approaches.
No, they don't bother me.
I ain't scared. I've never been scared
to do them since I was 19.
I done it like [ __ ] I ain't done it
in like 3 weeks and I still weren't
scared to do it. Tiny tiny bit nervous
at the first one, but I'm not scared, bro.
Yeah, I got her as well.
And I don't give a [ __ ] bro. I'll go
Finland. Wherever I need to go after
this Thailand thing, I'll go. I don't
give a [ __ ] If this person in Canada
turns out to be real, I'll go Canada. I don't care
if it means getting a better life than
here, mate. Like, [ __ ] So, yeah.
If I'm not out tomorrow, I'll be out on
[ __ ] W. I'll be out on uh
um probably Tuesday, bro. I'm going to
be [ __ ] tomorrow.
I got a really nice [ __ ] bro. I come
in her mouth.
She said I swallowed a little bit as
well. I liked it.
But it didn't bother me, bro.
Cuz it would always be the same here. So
why, you know, it's it is what it is
and I hope it stays that way.
I did get a boy I did get I got a
boyfriend a few times. Not in the sober
ones, right? I think I got it like three
times, which I believe they generally
did, but some of them just walked away.
Some of them just weren't even trying to speak.
You know what I mean?
Some of them didn't even want to speak.
Some of them just like walk past. So
then I kind of felt like if you can't
even get a conversation out of them,
then how are you going to date, you know? obviously,
but it is what it is, bro. Tuesday,
maybe. Maybe. Yeah.
I'll always be looking for that change,
bro. You know what I mean?
So, what? You actually like that person
in the video, Steven Howard? She was
okay. I mean, I done it because there
was there was no one else to do, but I
wouldn't say they're really really my type.
Yeah. Virgin boy can never approach
anyone. He's That's why he's still a
virgin. That's why he would die a
That one that I approached, oh my god,
she was sexy, bro.
The first one that I approached was
sexy, bro. But she's been with somebody
for 3 months, but I weren't going to let
that stop me, bro. Cuz I the way I see
it is a number's better than nothing.
You know, even if they say they're
seeing someone for 3 months, a number's
better than nothing. That's the way I
see it. That's the way I saw it in the
end. Like, I just don't give a [ __ ] One second. Yeah.
Yeah. One second, bro.
No, not really.
No, the whole net wouldn't go mad. They
would just pretend they didn't see it.
I've gone off with I got off with nicer
women than her before. They won't. They
won't. They would just pretend they've
never seen it. They would just pretend
they didn't see it.
That's what would happen. Like they
always do. Like when I've shown them
thousands and they all run away. No,
they would just pretend they didn't see it.
Is that right, Nicolo? Just like when I
went to Mark's area two times. Like
they'll just pretend they've never seen it.
Let's put that like on here, bro. It
doesn't matter what you show them. You
could show them you
[ __ ] shovel cole and they'd still
say, "Nah, never happened, mate." Well,
you know what they're like on here?
You could show you [ __ ] literally
shovel cole and they'd still say, "Nah,
mate. Never had a bird." That's what
they're like on here, bro. It doesn't
matter what you show them.
But no, she didn't really have boobies.
No, but I don't need boobies. I just
need [ __ ] I just need I just need a
mouth. If someone has a mouth, that's
good enough for me.
I just need somebody with a mouth.
No, I just need someone that's got a
mouth. You know what I mean? Nicolo,
if you don't find Cheryl Co attractive,
you're gay. I'm not gay.
No, we can't. We can't let that [ __ ]
virgin find out about anyone.
All I was thinking about when I was
weighing up a mouth was how far my
dick's going to go in it. Nicolo, that's
what I was thinking about that one. I
was uh thinking about how far my dick's
going to go up it. Yeah,
I'm not gay. Why does Virgin Boy call me
gay for not liking Cheryl Cole? I don't
like the [ __ ] I'm not [ __ ] gay,
Nicolo. Why does he say you're gay if
you don't find her attractive? I
generally don't find her attractive. I'm
not [ __ ] gay. I've never been with a
man or anything.
No. I was drunk by this point.
No, I was drunk.
Why does Virgin Boy say that I'm [ __ ]
I'm [ __ ] gay? Cuz I don't like Cheryl
Cole. Nicola, I'm not [ __ ] gay.
I swear to God I'm not gay. What the [ __ ]
He said if you don't like Cheryl Cole, you're gay.
Yeah. Yeah. I used to say I said to you,
Monty, why do these people call me skin?
He says, "Cuz these are skin." They're
Yeah. I said, "Why does Bomb call me
ugly?" He said, "Because Bomb's ugly."
It's just like reverse, isn't it? Yeah.
Yeah. That Chevil Cole thing is a tread.
Literally a [ __ ] tread, mate. Copycat. Copycat virgin.
Yeah, he's a copycat virgin. And he
needs to get laid. He needs to lose his
virginity. [ __ ] virgin
telling people they live with their
[ __ ] mom or live with their dad. You
live in a [ __ ] bedshit, you [ __ ]
[ __ ] All of these little [ __ ]
holidays that you're going on, I done
all that when I was 23, mate. You're
about 8 years too late. You [ __ ] skin
virgin. It took you to the [ __ ] age
of [ __ ] 31
to [ __ ] finally
to finally um afford a [ __ ] holiday.
He's [ __ ] virgin.
You know what I'm saying? What a [ __ ] virgin, bro.
Do you remember Kenji Nicolo? The free
eyes. Free some of [ __ ] eyes.
Yeah, she's [ __ ]
I'm on Ebox.
Have I been her? You know, why would I
been her, bro?
And yeah, she has got no tits, but I
don't give a [ __ ] about her.
As long as she's got a mouth and she got
a [ __ ] it's it's good enough for now.
You know what I mean?
So, who is USA is he to me?
Who is USA is he to me, Nicolola?
Yeah, I was holding her hand and [ __ ] I
didn't kiss her or anything yet, but I
was holding her hand. She almost beat me
in a [ __ ] arm wrestle. I said, "Bro,
I'm I'm [ __ ] weak. I need to go back
to the gym, bro." She almost beat me in
a [ __ ] arm wrestle. You know that?
She actually almost beat me in a [ __ ] arm wrestle.
I was like, "What the fuck?" I swear to
God she almost beat me, bro. In an arm wrestle.
Yeah, but how is she my mama, Nicolo? If
she left me, if she was my mommy, she
wouldn't have left me, would she?
Yeah, the one in the video, bro. She
almost beat me in an arm wrestle. I was
holding her hands with her and that. We
was holding hands. It was cute.
I was touching her legs.
I didn't want to go for the kiss just
yet, you know. Yeah.
He's speaking to the old man earlier. Nicolo Yeah.
What do you reckon would have happened
if I was in Canada? Do you reckon I
would have met someone by now if I was in Canada? Yeah,
I think we would. I think so. I think
Tool [ __ ] in it. Yeah, that's what an
old man used to say to me up the road.
There used to be an old man I used to
when I used to live in Stratford, we
used to speak and he used to say, "Yeah,
have you seen the new uh new manager?
He's [ __ ] tall [ __ ] ain't he?" Yeah.
Tall [ __ ] isn't he? tall [ __ ]
What do you reckon would have happened
if I was in Canada, Nicolo? Do you
reckon I would have found someone by now?
The only remembrance that I have with a
Canadian is just one that I fingered. Um,
have I ever been with another I don't
think I have. Canadian?
No, I don't think I've come across many of them.
the only one I know is that I fingered.
Yeah, I don't think I have. But Canada
is another westernized country. It's
going to be hard there as well. But I
still think London is the hardest place.
I don't know, man.
Yeah, they give you that dirty westernized look.
westernized look, bro.
That dirty westernized look. I was
speaking to some guy in Chicago. He said
that he's not had sex in 2 years. He
said he's been single for 2 years. He's
not had sex for 2 years. is I said
you've not had sex for 2 years. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, he says that he's not had sex for
[ __ ] 2 years.
Okay. What the [ __ ] Crazy, bro.
He said he lives in Chicago. Chicago.
[ __ ] that, bro.
Yeah, it's kind of a dodgy place.
No, that's dangerous there, bro. Not not
having sex for two years. [ __ ] that.
No. [ __ ] that.
That's crazy. He seemed right though. He
said, "Yeah, the dating game is [ __ ]
there as well." I told him, "I'm never
going to America again." I told him,
"Never." Cuz of like the the people
there and that. Like he knew what I
meant. He said I said, "Nah, no way."
I always see them approaching videos and
it's just the same old [ __ ] I have a
boyfriend and that same westernized
[ __ ] I don't I don't I'm not into it, bro.
[ __ ] that, bro. [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] way, bro. No way.
They give you that dirty [ __ ] westernized look. Yeah, the NPCs.
It will never change.
It will never change. Yeah. Antman said
I'll never change. He said you'll never
That's what he said to me. He said
you'll never change.
You said it would never change and
neither will you.
He said you will never change. Yeah.
Taking the baby away from its mama.
Remember that one, Nicolo? Yeah.
Yeah, but I'll be back Some money.