Oh, Franklin
and his little hands were real wheels. Oh, bless. Franklin,
it was nice to see you again, Franklin.
Stop sticking your middle finger up. Bye. Yeah. Oh [ __ ]
Hey Monty, how you doing man? [ __ ]
did you see who I was on a call to yesterday?
You know they're actually real. I was I
was speaking to them on the uh
one second. Need to put this up. One sec.
They're from Canada. Who else is from Canada?
Do you know who else is from Canada, Monty?
You know, we're not going to we're not
we're not going to mention the name, are we? Yeah. Oh, well.
See, the thing is money. Yeah. I I can
go out whenever I want, you know. I I I
can go out wherever I want whenever I
want. I have I have I have money to go
out whenever I want. Do you understand,
Monty? It's Johnny Long Legs ex
>> It's not It's not his ex. She didn't want him.
>> She didn't want him, Monty.
>> No, they were going out together, you
>> never met They never met though.
>> No, they never met each other. Oh,
>> but then uh yeah, see I can go out
whenever I want money. I have money to
like go out whenever I want. I just
don't show these people money when they
ask me to. I I don't I don't play I
>> I don't play their silly skin I don't
play their silly games anymore.
>> No, there's no point in every time they
call you just block them. Just get rid
of them every time they make your letters.
>> Yeah. I just say I just say to them,
stop talking about yourself. That's what I say.
>> That's what they do every [ __ ] day. Peel
every day, man.
>> Yeah, man.
>> I'm not [ __ ] around on this. I'll
just walk up. So, I'm serious when I'm cut. >> Yeah. >> Seriously
>> Remember when you always used to laugh
at silly things?
>> No. Never.
>> Never ever. Never ever
dush is [ __ ] idiots by waking up at
9:00. I need that [ __ ]
>> The what?
>> You're not writing. There's no writing.
>> I know there's seven people here.
>> Seven people. >> Yeah.
>> Just woke up, mate. You're [ __ ] so tired.
>> Well, bless you.
I [ __ ] drunk yesterday, man. Rubbing
that out. But I don't feel too bad today.
>> Not really now. Just feel tired. Like you
>> feel I feel like I've got a yang over. >> Really?
>> Yeah. That's how tired I am.
>> Yeah. I'm [ __ ] bro. I'm so tired. But
there's no hangover for some reason. I
was drinking white rum and [ __ ] everything.
That nice that we knew we were drinking.
>> Yeah, it was lovely, wasn't it, boss?
>> We should do it again sometime.
>> You were talking to a bird all last
night, weren't you?
>> I was talking to a few.
>> Did you get any numbers?
>> Yeah, four numbers. I've not text them
yet, though. I texted them later.
>> I text them. And it was a Sunday
yesterday as well. Don't forget, it
weren't like a Saturday, you know what I
mean? Or Friday. It was a Sunday. I
don't know why I went out yesterday. I
was just bored, you know. Yeah.
>> No, not too bad. Not too bad.
>> You got six numbers when you was with me.
>> I got no numbers when I was with you.
>> Oh, what was I saying? What was I
saying? Um, you know where Rice is now?
>> Yeah, Rice is at Kay's
name back on YouTube.
That's why he's That's why they've been
showing the floor and who's been at K's
house who knows the basic the outlay.
>> Wait, wait, wait. Have they been back on
Have they been back on YouTube? Because
I don't know any of their channels.
>> Yeah, Rice has. Yeah.
>> See, I always forget his channel. It's some some
>> Yeah, R has made a new channel. So, if
no one doesn't know that, Rice has made
a new channel and he makes a video
saying you're not getting rid of this
gangster that easily. And then they took
a picture of some food.
>> Yeah. And that food was on the kitchen side unit
>> and it show the floor and next to the
floor is the fridge freezer. >> Yeah.
>> And well on the floor it's a fridge
freezer next to the unit where his food
done. That's how I know he's at K's
house cuz the where the fridge freezer
is and the freezer is
>> 100% under. I can even
he got he got [ __ ] owned in it.
It's going to get owned again once he
find out the he is at K is. >> Yeah.
See with me money I'm too smart. See
Monty I'm too smart for these people.
>> That's where it is. Even tell you where we
>> I'm too smart for them in it. Monty.
>> Are you sure? Are you sure? >> 100%.
No, we talk to now.
>> Yeah. Now we'll even tell you
R's got a new YouTube channel. >> Yeah.
>> What this YouTube channel called?
>> Right. The same as last time. Ryzen
Extraordinary Rising K.
>> Extraordinary Rice and K.
>> Oh, bless you Natalie with your little
black country accent. Oh,
>> what the [ __ ]
>> Good morning, PJ. Good morning.
>> Bless you with your little black fancy accent then.
>> Bless you with your London accent.
>> I actually don't have a London accent.
>> Yeah, you do, please. Yeah, you do.
>> Yeah, but not everyone guesses I'm from
London when when I ask them. Some people
say different things.
>> Oh, man. I'm just wait. You know, do you
know some people, you know, do you know
some people, Monty? Yeah. They used to
say to me, "Oh, you sound like you're
from Birmingham." I said, "No, I [ __ ] do not."
>> Are you [ __ ] mad?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You do sound
like you're from um No, you sound like
from Scotland. Liverpool. You sound Liverpool,
>> bro. Wherever they said I was from, the
only one I took offense was [ __ ]
Birmingham. I don't sound like them.
What the [ __ ]
>> man? I think the Birmingham on the
woman's play. All right. I don't like it
on a man. Yeah, but you've not heard a
Birmingham accent on a woman. A proper Birmingham accent.
>> Yeah, we have.
>> Yeah, we have. Yeah, we have. I [ __ ]
live in Birmingham in my head.
>> Oh, yeah. I went on a date with a woman with Birmingham.
>> Natalie's got a
>> I think this is um Timmy.
>> Hello, PJ. Good [ __ ]
>> Yeah, I told I told you. Has the
gambling been going?
>> Timmy, stop yourself. I'm not talking to Mongol.
>> Go on. Go on, Jimmy. I mean, shut up.
I'm having a [ __ ] game. One second.
>> You need to stay off them machines, bro.
>> I don't go in there. I don't go in
>> Don't lie, PJ. Including me, PJ. I lost
a fair bit last week, PJ. But I I I
don't go in the machines.
>> I'm not full of [ __ ] PJ. I've got the videos going.
>> I don't go on the machines.
>> Okay. Anyway, PJ,
>> the only talking
come to me.
>> I'm kicking him, man. He's He's talking
over me. He's giving me a headache.
>> Yeah. Yeah, he does. He does. He just
talks over you. That's only what he can do.
>> What the [ __ ] man?
>> Yeah. Why don't you meet me then, Timmy?
Now. Me and you meet now, Timmy. Tell
him to meet me.
[ __ ] hell, man. Why is he shouting people?
>> Because that's what he thought he can do
because he gets on. Because that because
he gets on. That's what it is.
>> Is Timmy get on so he's got to shout over people. >> Yeah.
>> Is it?
>> Yeah. I don't know why he's saying that.
When was the last time I was I gamble
and I don't even play the machines. He
must have me mixed up with himself. What the [ __ ]
>> Yeah, I know. He gambles. I gamble on
the football. Yeah, sometimes. But I
[ __ ] gamble on them [ __ ] machines
or online. No,
>> did you stop them? The machines or something?
>> Yeah, I stopped them ages ago, bro. Like
6 months, seven months. What the [ __ ]
There's an account called PJ Sisters,
bro. If you I'm at my sisters. Okay. Yeah.
>> Don't be add to it. Is it okay about my
sisters? That's it. >> Yeah.
Like I said, man, I'm just saying this
one more time. The posters thing, what
you done to Rice, it's not going to work
with me. And I've already explained why
it's not going to work. Because
everybody in all the areas know about
me. They know who I am. Hang on a
minute. One minute, PJ. If I If Jimmy
owns me, why did Timmy not want to talk
to me? Why did he just want to talk to
[ __ ] PJ? And if Timmy wants to get
owned this second, I would meet Timmy
now. And that's just me owning him with
one word. I would meet him now.
Hey, my money mic.
>> Scottish people about One second. One
second. Scottish people about it.
England people aren't Scottish people
aren't [ __ ] about it more than English people.
>> What the [ __ ] Are you funny?
>> Are you mad?
>> Are you [ __ ] [ __ ] up? Why don't you
Google what people do in Manchester with grenades?
>> One second. One second. One second. One
second. Hold on a minute. Yeah. One
second. Money. If Scottish people about
it so much. Yeah. Why? Why is it that
there's so many Scottish people in this
community, right, including Shagger and
they didn't even go on Rice's Do ever
and they all live near each other if
they're all about it. Go on.
>> No. Yeah. No, that's true. And if you're
on about it, I was watching this series
about all you lot. Yeah. And if you all
about it, why the [ __ ] do you all carry
knives around and you look like scrubbers? >> Yeah.
>> You all about it. If you ever, why do
you all carry knives and weapons around
with you? You clowns.
>> Yeah, cuz you know people say to me,
"Yeah, oh, you wouldn't like Glasgow."
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. Bro, I wouldn't [ __ ] be scared of
Glasgow, man. What the [ __ ]
>> I'm not even scared of [ __ ] Glasgow.
I'm a man union. I'm a man.
>> Yeah, but it's not just There's other
It's not just There's other Scottish
people on here. Obviously there's other
Scottish people, isn't it? >> Manchester
is a lot worse and uh and so is London.
>> Yeah, Liverpool, London, and Manchester
is the worst. >> Yeah.
Only what they do is copy up there and
just carry knives and stab.
>> You know, you know, with London. Yeah. I
don't know why people always think, "Oh
yeah, you're going to go out in London,
someone's going to stab you." You're not
going to get stabbed. You're going to
get your phone snatched. That's what's
going to happen.
phone snatched or moped snatched.
>> Yeah, you'll get your phone snatched by
a moped thief. That's what definitely will happen.
>> Well, in Birmingham, you get kicked off
more you get kicked off mopeds.
Obviously the same in London and you get
your back robbed as well in Birmingham. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Watching it happen in front of me
when bank get throw some money out and
this guy got booted off his bike. Three
teenagers drive up his moped off him
with his motor bike off him.
What a bless.
I got I got Scooby-Doo. I've got a Scooby-Doo toy.
>> Which one have you got? Shaggy.
>> Well, I got Scooby and the little baby.
>> Baby Scooby.
>> Yeah, but that baby Scooby's not a baby
Scooby. He's a booger or an adult. He's
a dwarf Scooby. That one.
>> Imagine you as a dwarf. You look funny in it.
All give me hands about me without the dwarves.
>> You would kill You'd kill yourself if
you was a dwarf, wouldn't it?
>> Of course I would. Of course I [ __ ]
>> Nah, you wouldn't kill yourself, would it?
>> Timmy, why would the [ __ ] I called you?
What the [ __ ]
>> Yeah. What? Yeah, but you wouldn't kill yourself.
>> Why the [ __ ] would I want to be about 2
in off the
>> Cuz you can join other little clubs with
other dwarfs with the same condition as you.
More guns in Birmingham. Yeah, there's
more guns in Birmingham.
Imagine trying to pause at the wolf.
>> There's more guns in Manchester as well. Manchester, Birmingham. Um,
>> yeah, but Monty, could you imagine
trying Could you imagine trying to pull
as a dwarf? It
>> be hard. You had to go to the dwarf clubs.
>> That's what I mean. Yeah, that's where
thingy found uh that's where nons found
his girlfriend in the wolf club.
>> The wolf club. Yeah,
>> I've met every I've met everyone on
YouTube but um Natalie I've even met
I've even met Laur.
>> Yeah, but it's technically you know what
I mean? Like you know what I mean? Yeah.
>> I've seen Tiger, I've seen Timmy, I've
seen unworthy clock. I've seen Mike.
I've seen you
[ __ ] every pretty much everyone, bro.
>> Yeah, same as me. I've seen who have I
met up here. I've met Tim.
Who else have I met? >> Um,
>> Cosmic Kitty.
>> Oh, but yeah, I've never met her. I've
>> Yeah, I've met Cosmic Kitty. I've met uh
I don't know who else I've met.
>> Um me. Yeah, I've met you. I've met
someone else as well. Trixie.
Someone else. I've met someone.
>> That That Trixie was a little weasel though.
>> Yeah, he was a weasel. He was a weasel.
>> Little weasel. He was
>> He had to get back up. >> Yeah.
I'm wearing Stitch boxes. Monty,
>> you're wearing skid markers.
>> No stitch boxes.
>> Oh, [ __ ] hell. I thought you said
skid mark boxes. Monty stayed a night at
Fat Dans. Nah,
>> I'm a [ __ ] stay at Fat Dans. Would I [ __ ] away?
>> I remember you used to bully Alen on
PlayStation, isn't it?
>> Yeah, I still bully him last night. He
was shouting his head off last night.
>> Why does he do this like all his life
coming like online doing this, bro? Only
in it. He ain't got no one to say
look like Daniel Sullivan.
>> But I don't understand how he come on
this community. Did you know it was a
lean straight away?
>> Yeah. You know it's him cuz he's always
got his camera on and you know him with his eyes. >> Yeah.
Do you remember when he said on
PlayStation some [ __ ] had that away? I
was dead, bro.
>> Oh, I remember him talking about kids a
lot on there.
>> Yeah. He's got a vagina in it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. He's got a Yeah.
>> You're not coming into me.
>> Just let him up. Just let him up. Just
let him up. He's just
>> Yeah. Yeah. Just let me say one thing to
him. Timmy, why don't you meet me now?
>> Jimmy, why don't you meet me now?
>> Why are you so wacky?
>> Why don't you meet me, Jimmy? Now,
you've been taking the piss out of you. Letting yourself
keeps on giving.
>> Oh, see what I mean?
>> You never [ __ ] grow up, lad. Just get
rid of him. Just get rid of him. He's
>> Timmy. I was near you, Timmy. I was
Timmy. I was near you. I was near you
last week. Now, make sure you answer the
door. I'm going to put the window.
>> Listen, I was
kicking the pig. You're not running away
from me this time. Sunshine.
>> One second.
>> Just kick him. Just kick him. Just give
kick him. Kick him. One second.
>> Timmy, I was near you. Timmy, I was near
Oh, for [ __ ] sake. I'm kicking him, bro.
>> Kicking for a second.
>> No, he can't. What?
>> Yeah. And I'm not shouting, bro. What
the [ __ ] Timmy, you don't know where I
live. And even when you did, you done
absolutely nothing. You let Tiger do the
do the fighting. You done nothing. So,
shut up, stupid [ __ ] You couldn't even
kick me. You couldn't even hit.
>> Oh, no. He can't kick. He can't kick. He
can't punch. He can't do any of that. He
kicked like a circus clown for [ __ ] sake.
>> Money, I think, yeah, if you had if you
had the choice to pick somewhere to
live. Yeah. Birmingham or Liverpool, I
think you would choose Liverpool in it. 100%.
>> No, Birmingham. Birmingham. I mean,
Timmy's town. What the [ __ ] Jimmy
going to do about it?
>> Yeah. I said the same thing to Prime. We
I called Prime as well when I was there.
He didn't do anything about it.
>> None of them do when you're with me. I
said, "I'm in your city and you're not I
said I'm in your city and you're not
going to move me.
Have you not noticed that when you're
with me? No one turns up.
When you when you're on, they turn up.
When you're with me, they don't turn up.
>> Would I shagger the wolf escort? That's
a stupid question.
>> Yeah, they are stupid. Can you not get
better with your questions in this
community or you've all got the right [ __ ]
>> Money, I had a hamburger the other day
from a shop and it was really nasty. You
know when you have like a a beef burger
and it just tastes fake, but I can't
explain it. Like plasticky [ __ ]
>> Plastic like um dried up thing like it means plastic.
>> Yeah, cuz you know when you you know if
you make like a homemade burger like
with mints and then you make it, it's so
nice. Like you can just taste the
difference like pure beef, you know?
>> And then you go like to [ __ ] It's not
even just McDonald's. There's other places.
cheap looking burgers and they don't
taste of anything kind of. >> Yeah. Can't even
>> Why would I shag? Why would I shagger
the wolf? That's a silly question.
>> Pick them up. P. Yeah, you can [ __ ]
swing the bastards around.
>> Saying that virgin boy [ __ ] is with a
dwarf, ain't he? But
>> no, I think you'll be able to do a lot
more with a dwarf to tell you the truth.
I think you'll be able to do a lot more
with a war.
>> Explain how it's because why would I why
would I a normal person?
>> Why would I a normal person? Shaggy the wolf.
>> So what you're saying is that the
dwarves not a normal person. Yeah.
>> Well, they aren't they're a normal
person, but they're not they're not
>> because they're little people.
>> No, he's disability PJ. >> Yeah.
Have you ever seen that? Do you know who
that Warick Davis is? Do you know him?
The dwarf. Um, he was in Star Wars. Do
you know him?
>> We've got a couple of dwarves in this
community. We've got We've got money, Mike.
>> I used to like I used to like Harry Potter, man.
>> But I used to like Dobby. I only like I
only like Dobby cuz you know Dobby
Monty. He reminds me of you, Dobby. >> Okay.
>> He's cute, isn't it? Dobby. All right then,
>> why don't you meet me then outside 71
Brford Lane Garden? Why don't you meet
me later now, Timmy?
>> Why would you rather Why would you
rather live in Birmingham than
Liverpool? What What if Timmy didn't
live in Birmingham anymore? >> Because
Timmy, why most of these YouTubers live
in Birmingham? That's why I'm staying in Birmingham.
>> Yeah, but they're never going to meet you.
It just ruins the point then, don't it?
>> Yeah, but a lot of these people, a lot
of these people probably live in London as well.
>> Yeah, of course he is. Of course,
there's a couple live in London. It's a couple. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Of course. Of course. Even if you
went to Manchester, they still won't meet you.
>> You know, I don't know why, but I'm sure
you told me before your dad's name was
Barry. That's why I said it to you yesterday. Hey, Barry.
>> Yeah, your dad's name is Barry, isn't it?
>> No, my dad's name is not Barry. Wrong
thing, PJ. What I'm not doing is putting
my dad's name up on YouTube. So, [ __ ]
off. And it's not Barry.
>> I thought it was, buddy.
>> No. Is it for Barry? But I'm not putting
my dad's name up on YouTube.
>> Yeah. Yeah. It's fine, man. I don't want you to.
>> I don't I don't want you to.
>> They know my mom, but they don't know my
dad. They haven't found my dad. Your dad
probably not even Your dad's probably
not even on social media.
>> My dad is on social media.
Just put it this way. Yeah, my real name
is not even egg. [ __ ] sake.
So all these on YouTube become a I'm not
even a [ __ ]
>> You told me you told me your dad's like
[ __ ] um Frank Gallagher in it from
Sheamus basically. Is it?
>> He's a piss edge.
My dad My dad's My dad's pretty solid.
My dad My real dad anyways. My dad My
stepdad guy [ __ ] J.
>> I don't I don't I don't [ __ ] I don't
believe in stepdads. Do you? Nah.
>> My real dad's solid as [ __ ] My real dad.
>> But do you believe in stepad? Do you
believe in stepdads?
>> It depends how long he's been in your
life for. If he's been in your life
since [ __ ] birth, since you was born
or since you was a baby or whatever, then yeah,
>> I I would just see I I would just see it
as like it's weird how someone that's
not your real dad bringing you up and
like shagging shagging shagging your mom
and [ __ ] That's how I
>> It's normal. It's just normal. But a
woman with kids, that's it.
>> Yeah, I know. But it would just seem a bit
>> Oh, yeah. Put it this way. people. Rice
will never ever ever be the stepdad to
Lord of Pre. He will never see them kids. Never.
My mom's already told me like only
person who can see them kids is me and
Kerry and that's it.
No one else can see them. So if Rice
thinks if Kay thinks that can bring Rice
to see them kids, that's a no no.
>> Oh, bless you.
>> Bless you then.
>> If you want to know where Rice is. Yeah.
All the trolls. Yeah. Why don't you get
working on Rice? Who's that Kay's house?
Who's that Kay's flat in Leicester?
So Kay stood in Leicester and and Rice
is now living at K's flat.
>> Do you reckon um do you reckon will ever
get a life? I don't think so.
>> No. None of these will get alive on this
committee here. None of them got a life
[ __ ] all of them. I'm not being
funny, but they all sit there and pay
pedophiles. They all give money to pedos.
You call that normal people pedos.
That's not [ __ ] They sit there and
pay actual nons money.
Just think about it. Yeah. When me and
you first joined into this community,
well, when I first joined into this
community, all these people were calling
fairly, weren't they? Yeah.
called him apping him this calling him
that. Yeah. And then since um the
governor and Mrs. Brown source and all
them lot left YouTube.
>> Ah you remember you remember them.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And then they started
and then they started licking F's ass
after when all them gone. >> Yeah.
>> So for me
>> this community is a pedophile loping
community. These people love in this
community. They [ __ ] love them.
>> They do. They do.
>> Yeah. I got you all now, aren't they? Your local.
>> Yeah. But why do you all pay pedophiles money anyways?
>> You like it?
>> I don't like it. I don't like pedos.
>> No, not like pedos, but obviously not.
I mean, but they call me a pedo for
having the teen dating. I'm like, I give a [ __ ]
These people are pedos.
>> Don't make you appealed having a teen
dating app. It makes you appeed if you
go on to a teen dating app and meet up
with children and talk to kids just like did
>> Is still backstage? No.
I meet Jimmy now if you wanted to meet
me with money. M come in the news.
What do you think would happen if I went to Chicago? >> Huh?
>> Watch Chicago Bulls.
>> Yeah. Like if I went to the to the to
the state will happen.
>> Nothing will happen. Just keep away from
certain areas. Yeah, but you could get
killed in it. >> Huh?
>> You can get killed in your own fing. It
doesn't matter to work you got.
>> I love GTA 5, Monty. I love Franklin. I
think he's such a lovely little character.
>> No, Franklin. No, Trevor.
>> No, I like Franklin.
>> Trevor's the best.
>> Why do you like No. No. Come on. Come
on. I've got a good one for Timmy. Uncle Lester. [Laughter]
Did you get it? >> No.
>> Right. One minute. Don't end your life.
Just give me a second. Let me go get
this picture. Give me a second. One
second. Cuz this is funny. Hey,
>> Bugs Bunny. I've got a question. Yeah.
What would happen if I went to Chicago
to go approach him?
Anyone who's watching, what do what do
you think the outcome would be if I if I
went to Chicago and I went approach him?
I would like to think, mate,
what do you think would happen?
What do you think would happen if I if I
went to Chicago and I went approaching?
Um, I don't have no opinion on it.
Different uh different culture.
And what do you mean?
Did you see that woman I was with
yesterday? Grievously she was a nutter. different game.
Well, the dating game is the same there,
I'm guessing, from what I've seen on videos. Yeah.
Right. Here's [ __ ] Timmy PJ. Let's see.
Here's Timmy Eldridge on my picture.
>> That's Uncle Lester. That's Lester.
>> I was on the piss yesterday, Grezy. Did
you know I went out on the piss?
That's Uncle Lester, the child of molester.
>> Oh, damn.
>> Yeah, that's who that's who he's called. Uncle Lester.
>> He's a child. He's a child of molester
on GTA 5.
>> Did you not know that?
>> I didn't know that.
>> No. Yeah. Lester is a child molester on GTA 5.
>> Any stake update? Nope. One second.
Who the [ __ ] is messaging me?
>> Yeah, not anymore, bro. bus.
Is that the real boss or another bass?
>> I'm not sure, bro. One sec.
Hold Oh, hold up.
>> Where do you Where do you find that um
about TJ Hook on the old man online?
What's his name again?
>> I don't know his name.
>> But do you remember if I put a picture
up of him, would you remember?
>> Yeah, I remember him. Yeah.
Well, you know, straight away from the
picture, is it?
>> No, I caused on the picture. Yeah. From
>> Don't play more, man. He scares me,
mate. He's [ __ ] man who actually
scares me to [ __ ]
>> He was
scared of anybody in this community, but
that man scared of that man.
>> He wanted to come to um he wanted to
come to um Manchester and see you,
Jamie. [ __ ] off.
>> Why? He used to hit on you. It's true though.
>> Yeah, I know. I know he did. [Laughter]
>> [ __ ] funny, man. >> Huh?
>> I'm scared of that guy.
>> He was going to come and be your new daddy.
>> Everybody raped me. P. I was already
young back then as well.
I think his name was Terry the Berry or
some [ __ ] was it?
>> Oh, Terry. I remember it being Terry or
Tony or something like that.
>> Do you still remember like the the
picture where he's wearing the red? You know,
>> come on, man.
>> You remember
sleeping with his mom, didn't he?
Something like that. Yeah.
>> You know, Virgin Boy was put into care
up until he was 18. You probably didn't
know that, did you?
>> This virgin boy.
>> You know who?
>> Johnny Long Legs.
>> He was put into care. Did you know that?
>> So, what was he doing back at his mom's house then?
>> He He wasn't back at his mom's house. He
was put into care. Then he went to his
dad's and then he got a new um like a
house, you know, when he was living by
himself when he was 19.
He was put into care at a very young age.
>> That's good. That's good. That >> Yeah.
>> And he got bullied off his stepmom.
>> Stepdad. Yeah.
>> Well, his dad's a ped anyway. >> Yeah.
You used to say your dad's bull is it?
Do you remember? You used to say that
your dad's bald.
>> Yeah. Yeah, it did. Didn't it? >> Yeah, definitely did.
That's funny, isn't it?
>> Life's not funny when you think about it. >> Huh?
>> I think it's quite funny.
I just feel sorry for our police on this
committee if we're not having a life.
>> Yeah, we've got a life in it.
>> I can just get off YouTube now, man, and
just stay off YouTube. You know what I mean?
>> These people can't take a day off of YouTube.
>> No, they can't. They can't. They can't.
They literally [ __ ] can't. So, when
they tell you, "Oh, you get off YouTube
and you say, "I've already been off
YouTube." Why don't you get off YouTube now? all your >> Yeah,
>> I've already been off and on YouTube. >> Yeah,
>> I'm the one who's got a live and you are
the one who's you the one set on YouTube.
>> It's true. It's true.
This community will never change, will it?
>> So, did you call the person get on last night?
Yeah, like I said, it was all right. I
got poor numbers. I'm going to text them
later. It was a Sunday. Don't forget. >> Yeah.
>> You know, so I'll text them later.
>> We do. Yeah, we do a bet. I tell you how
many. He's going to text you back.
>> How many?
>> I say about I say about one of them.
One. He's going to text you back
>> and after a couple of days he's just
going to drop.
>> Oh, we'll see it. But in Birmingham they
all in Birmingham they all reply back.
>> Yeah, they all do. Did that girl come
back? Did Did she come? >> No.
>> Do you still talk to her?
>> No, bro. They used um one one said was
using an excuse they lived in Liverpool
and the other stopped replying and then
the other one just said, "Oh, they're
not looking to date." So, I thought,
"Fuck them." And just drop them, bro. Yeah.
Same [ __ ] in it, bro. Is what it is.
>> Oh my god. >> Yeah. >> It's
to be Monty. It's to be expected. You
know what I mean?
>> Yeah. I'm so glad that I've got Nat.
>> Publish it.
>> No. [ __ ] hell. Nat's been watching me
since day one of my being on YouTube. Oh,
>> so she knew knows everything what's
going on and what's going on. So she
knows that I'm not n cuz she's been
there from the beginning of it all.
>> Yeah. Yes, she did.
>> All right.
Go on. I'll leave you to your life for a
bit. Yeah. I'm going spending time with N.
>> Okie do.
>> Yeah. I'll be back on a bit.
>> Okie dokie then.
See you later.
See you later, alligator.
No, I think it's starting to hit me now. The alcohol. Oh [ __ ] See, We done.
I want to get that picture of the old
man to show on, but I can't find him anywhere.
I can't find him, mate.
Um, yesterday I had a roast dinner.
Oh [ __ ] I've actually got a video to
show you. We see
what I got last night.
That reminds me. I'd done a little video.
I done a little video. Oh
>> yeah. I can't find the old man. Monty, >> what?
>> I'm still trying to find the old man. I
can't find him.
>> Is it T? No, it's not Tony.
>> Terry. It was Terry. Huh?
>> Dude, what was his second name?
>> I don't know. Terry Berry, was it?
>> No, it wasn't
>> Terry Jerry. I think it was Terry Jerry
or something. Hold on. Terry Jerry Canada. No. Why not?
>> You know Canada's next to [ __ ] Russia?
>> No, it's next to Manchester.
>> Is it? No way.
Don't you know?
>> No. No. I didn't know that. PJ.
>> Yeah. You can just get a bus from Manchester.
>> It's near Russia. Did you know that? >> No.
>> Let's put PJ up to the test. Who is
closer to America, the Russian or the UK?
>> What? Who's closer to um who's closer to America?
Russia or UK? >> UK.
>> No, Russia.
>> I've done a video for you, Grezy. Are you sure?
>> Yeah, I'm sure. Russia's closer. Russia.
Russia is basically next door to
America. You can walk basically on a
sunny day and that you can walk to
America from Russia.
>> Well, bless you then if you can walk.
>> Right. Okay. If you go into Google Maps. Yes. >> M.
>> And then go over to Russia and then keep
moving across, you see America right
next to it. >> Well,
no. UK is not near America. Russia is.
>> Well, bless you then.
>> Did not know that. PJ. >> No.
>> Yeah. Russia's next door neighbor to America.
I don't know that.
>> What? Why is this Grey account on
YouTube every day?
>> Cuz Grimby hasn't got a live. >> Really?
>> Really? No. Come on. All these people
have been awake since what 30 hours
later this morning, go to sleep
>> and then jump back online first thing in the morning. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? That's what lily
have got. And they check on YouTube.
>> Even even even [ __ ] even Virgin boy
ain't got a life if you think of it.
None of them do. >> Nobody
on here. See, even even Ginsby even says
it. Nobody's got a life on here. >> Well,
not exactly. What? Well, going out
clubbing and watching.
>> He said he said he said he said he said
we love the content watching Mongo's
family breaking down. It's lush.
>> We love watching
my My family's not brought down. Why do
you all think that I've lost my family?
>> They say the same. They say the same to
me. They think my family hates me and I
talk to my family all the time.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I do. I talk to my mom all the time.
>> They say that to me as well.
Yeah. No, my mom just rings me up and
tells me to get off YouTube cuz she
knows that it's [ __ ] for the weirdos.
So, you got all that wrong. One, you all
think that I've lost my kids. I have
lost my kids when my kids are living
with my mom.
True. I haven't I'm not a belly. I
haven't lost my kids. I still see my kids, you know.
I've still I'm with a woman off YouTube
knows me well been with her what five
months six months wor about the rat
traps in the assessment center trap.
>> There's nothing even to say about a rat
trap. What the [ __ ]
No, it's just someone put a rat trap in
their baby's pram and got blamed for it.
YouTube's these people's life, isn't it?
>> Yeah, YouTube is their life.
>> Well, you think it's funny, though.
>> I think that the idiots, PJ, that's what I think.
>> Complete Mongos.
>> True. They call people Mongos cuz these
are the Mongos themselves, man. I'm not
being funny, but they are. >> Yeah.
A rat trap in
hilly belly. Definitely not.
Yeah, someone put a rat trap in a brown.
I'm not a [ __ ] Wednesday, you
[ __ ] I'm not a Wednesday of Adam's family.
DJ, I have you dick.
>> No, I haven't sent Grezy a dick picture,
but I sent your mom one.
>> I'm cheeky, aren't I, Monty?
>> Did you watch the little video, Grezy?
Did you watch it?
I done a little video for you.
Is it obsessed with you? >> No.
>> Obsessed with you.
>> All of these people are obsessed with me.
>> Why did you get me into this [ __ ] Community pedia.
>> I thought you would have liked it.
>> No, these are not people with no money.
I'm surprised you didn't beat me up when
um we met because I sent you me getting
a [ __ ] video.
>> What do you mean?
>> When I sent you me getting a [ __ ] >> Yeah.
>> Did you like it?
>> No. Did a [ __ ] I should have slightly actually.
>> You watched it, didn't you?
>> No, not all of it. I turned it off.
>> Why? It was hot in it.
>> Sean [ __ ] Kelly.
I bet she was she was liking it in it.
>> Don't know probably. [Laughter]
>> I've said that to a few people.
I'm surprised you didn't I'm surprised
you got pissed off at that. It was only
a [ __ ] [ __ ] video.
>> Yeah, you. >> So,
why the [ __ ] do I want to see one of my
mates getting a blow for
it? That's basically me and you standing
next to each other in a hotel shagging
two birds and giving each other high five.
>> Well, you liked it.
>> Of course.
>> Did you see that person I was with
yesterday, Grey? Did you see the little
video? She was a right She was a right looney.
>> You were the one you were talking to?
>> She She was a right looney.
>> Yeah, I think I think you were suited with that.
No, she was crazy.
>> In what way?
>> In a good way.
>> There you go. Did she tickle your pier? >> Yeah.
>> You places where you never been tickled before. Yeah.
>> Damn. Right.
>> I'm waiting for [ __ ] mail me, man.
I've got [ __ ] mail coming.
>> Oh, bless you. Yeah, you got mail coming. She's
Billy only what you you're shagging
Billy is a granny next to you. Sort yourself out.
That's only what you're shagging his
granny's. Sort yourself out lad. That's not a cox.
Iron Cox is record.
>> Yeah, it's proper fun, isn't it? >> Yeah.
Billy Granny Billy, your misses is 100%
not a mil. If you think she's a milk,
she's a granny, not a milk.
PJ, would you shag in a bit his girlfriend wife?
Would you shag in a bit his wife, PJ?
>> Yeah, totally.
>> Would you?
>> Totally, man.
>> No, man. She's stinking, mate. She's stinking.
Monty gets £40,000 a month. It was
>> you get £40,000 a month.
>> I got to get £100 a month. You dick?
>> Same man. £100. Yeah.
>> 100 pound a month. I get
>> my girl is better than that. Well, the
wells that you harpoon Monty
definitely not better than Natalie.
Definitely not better than Natalie now.
It Billy, didn't you want to meet Natalie?
I'm sure that Billy wanted to meet that >> baby.
>> Yeah. You know what Billy does? Yeah. He
goes out on his bike here and he picks
and he tries picking up younger women to
take them to hotels and that. Where does he live?
>> Near rice. >> Really?
>> Yeah, it is near Shagger and Rice and
that in Scotland.
>> The Scot. It's really all weird, aren't they?
>> Yeah, they are weird.
>> Yeah, he's from Scotland.
>> You know the new conjur out soon?
>> Is it? >> Uh-huh.
You take a wobble.
>> Yo, every time you go [ __ ] ride your
bike, you old fart. You're always
robbling. Sort yourself out.
>> God bless.
>> I'm Welsh. You donut.
>> Well, Wales. Wales.
Don't say a [ __ ] thing. You all sound
the same. Well, in Scotland.
>> Yeah, pretty much.
>> I'm not a mong.
I think if we come back on this
community in 15 years, it would have
changed, isn't it?
>> Come back in 15 years. No, mostly. Yeah,
it would actually. Cuz half of these be
dead. Ity belly be dead.
Half of these. Yeah, half of these be dead.
>> don't forget I'm not being funny PJ
because if you actually look at these
when they put pictures up and you look
at the fingers and the thumbs and [ __ ]
like that, they're fat [ __ ] Half of
them are fat bastards. John West is a
skinny skinny bastard. I mean, John West
got like [ __ ] rice. That's no
>> Why Why do they try to Why do they try
to call me ugly? Because they ugly. They
are ugly. So they trying to make
themselves look better. And if they call
you ugly, tell them to come up on camera
to prove it.
>> That's what I say. And they can't. I
say, "Why don't you come come up on
camera then? If you're trying to call me
a M, why don't you show your faces?"
Can I ask Monty what three times four
is? No, I can't.
>> Three times four.
I was only want to do I not notice it's
repeating as well. Like I don't answer
them questions anyways anymore cuz it's repeating questions. >> Yeah.
>> Any questions like adding or [ __ ] I
won't do it anyways cuz it's just
repeating. So they just don't cuz I'm
not doing it. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean?
I'm going to sit here and do times
tables but not back at school. That's
what I mean. They do peed all jokes as
well. That was when I've like back at school. Oh [ __ ] You >> Yeah.
>> I just popped up my live thing. One sec.
I'm back on. I'm back on. Can you hear me? The
>> two biggest Mongs on one panel. Uh it's
lost. No, you're There's a third one as
well. You you're the Mong, but the
reason you don't come on The reason you
don't come on a panel is because you
you're too disabled to you are the Mong.
>> Yeah, they are Mong. So you only 24
hours every day on different people's
panels. You [ __ ] mongos.
>> You put yourself up on your own joke on that one.
>> Projecting bastard isn't it?
>> Yeah, that's only what they are. Rejecting.
>> Sorry LJ. Sorry LJ. Why you beating me
up bro? That's boring now. I was in
Birmingham last month and Prime was
nowhere to be seen. So, I mean, you
can't even use that anymore. So, nice try though.
>> Yo, peeps, tell Prime to come and meet
me. Tell him to meet me. Yeah,
>> he won't even meet me. I called him out
when I was in Birmingham. He won't even
meet me, bro.
>> He was with me. That's why you didn't show up.
>> He wouldn't have met me even if I was by myself.
Someone's asking for your link, DJ.
>> Yeah. One second. I'm doing something. Hold on.
few seconds. We need to do something. Um,
hold on, bro.
Why do they call the Why do they call
themselves Mongs anyways?
Because they are mons.
I won't kick you. Come up hilly billy.
Have a pint your old fart. Come on. Show
us all your stuff. Filly Billy.
Why don't you come up Billy? Link link.
>> Yeah, let me do it later. I'm going to
send the link now. One sec. Sorry. I doing something.
>> No, you're right, PJ.
>> One sec. Sorry for a grandad. Anyways,
anyways, I want to ask Billy a question.
>> Bill is a pedal. Did you know that PJ?
>> Why is it not coming up? What's What's
the title? What's it called? I'm scared
to put the link up. One second. Just
>> stick it up.
>> Yeah, give me a second. But I was doing something.
>> No, no. I thought you were scared to put
the link up.
I'm not scared of any of these [ __ ]
guys over here, bro. There you go. Let's join.
Where's your Where's your
Yeah, there's a link. He just put a link
up already. Link said, "Yeah.
There you go.
There we go.
Hey, why the [ __ ] are you being kicked
out of Russia? I haven't been kicked out
of Rodale. Why don't you go on to
Scotland grief and find out you little
clown and come back to Rodale and smash
your face in because I know where the
[ __ ] you live. Why don't you go on grave spot grieve?
Why don't you ask someone called Why
don't Why don't you ask someone called right in
his mic is [ __ ]
>> One minute. One minute, PJ. Just let me
sort this out. Do not talk. Yeah.
>> Yeah, but his mic is [ __ ] bro. You
can't barely hear anything.
>> Yeah, just let me get rid of the phone.
Just let me prove this fat company. I'm
being kicked out of Manchester.
>> One sec. One sec,
>> PG. Why are you a virgin?
I'm virgin. One second. Monty, are you
going to let me talk or are you going to
keep talking over me? I've had more I've
I've had more women than you've had on
dinner. You Ant and Dex sounding [ __ ] >> You
[ __ ] I'm a virgin, bro. I've had more
women. You've had no You haven't had
[ __ ] since [ __ ] had you. You little
jie [ __ ] When I man when I man don't
even try and [ __ ] don't even don't
>> Bro I can't Bro sort your [ __ ] mic
out before [ __ ] coming on here trying
to call people things bro you you can't
even a [ __ ] afford a decent [ __ ]
phone you [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] you
[ __ ] Jordy [ __ ]
>> You [ __ ] ant and deck sounding
[ __ ] [ __ ] off you [ __ ] One
sec. One sec. One sec. Let me get the
proof I'm being kicked out of Rodale. Go
[ __ ] reset your [ __ ] phone before
I try to come back on it. You know what I mean?
>> One sec, PJ. One sec.
>> This is what I mean, bro. It's a waste
of time that you these people call you
what they are.
Pointless, bro. Is it?
>> Yeah, it's pointless. It is pointless. Come on.
One sec, PJ. I'm going to jump on on a
different account. Let me just get your YouTube channel. >> Okay.
>> Yeah, because I'm going to prove these
little clowns that I haven't been kicked
out of Rodale. One sec.
Thinking of being kicked out of Rodale,
bad man. I go back to Rodale now and
smash your face in you little [ __ ] fat [ __ ]
and tell your mom to stop getting naked on camera.
One sec, PJ. Yeah, I'm coming to you now. >> Yep.
Pull your [ __ ] mic out before I try
to come back on here. [ __ ] stupid com. Yeah. Yeah, man.
>> On the box. Yeah.
>> Why are these people [ __ ] making
diesel accounts? They're [ __ ] weirdos.
>> Yeah, because they think it they think
I'm a g. They think I'm going to cry
over it. Oh, diesel. [ __ ] diesel. Diesel's gone
>> here. Let me back up. This is me, PV
trying to prove a [ __ ] point.
>> I've kicked myself anyways. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> One sec. Don't talk.
was classed as an old age pensioner. Fat dad,
these people are weirdos.
>> Yeah, man.
It's not picking up what
spy with my kids.
>> I'm getting a bit hungry now, Monty. Are you?
>> Yeah. here. [ __ ] this. Yeah, I just So,
why do I talk to people from Manchester
if I'm being kicked out of Manchester?
Why is my best mate? Who's my best mate? PJ
>> um I know.
>> Yeah. Where where is my best mate from? >> Watch.
>> Yeah, exactly.
>> You know,
you know that video I sent you the other
day, the N Hunter. Yeah. Um, you know,
the the launch hunters, bro, where they
dragged [ __ ] um dragged them out the
car. You didn't find that funny?
>> I don't find any of that P [ __ ] funny.
>> Yeah, but they dragged funny. >> Huh?
>> What's going to be funny is when I go
back to Rodale, when I go back on to
grief and this guy who just come up,
he's going to be [ __ ] it.
>> Yeah. But listen, but Monty, listen.
Yeah. Didn't you see it when he got
dragged out the car? Huh?
>> No, cuz I turned him up. I don't I don't
really watch him.
>> But it's funny, isn't it?
>> I turn them off.
>> I think it's funny. Me.
Get this information.
You've got you've got a stomach bug. >> Huh?
>> Have you ever had a stomach bug? I have.
>> Yeah, I've had a Yeah. >> virgin
>> cuz he's a [ __ ] virgin. Ask him about
his misses going around shagging um
every Tom can off YouTube.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Ask him about that.
And I know where he liv [ __ ] golf
course. That's where he lives. >> Yeah.
>> So I know where he lives.
So I can easily easily get get some
people. Who knows? Who knows his
address? Yeah. because he thinks I've been k
watch what happens to his house today.
Cuz watch what happens if he's been
kicked out of if he thinks I've been
kicked out of Manchester. Watch how many
people turn up to his door today. He's
got his address.
>> Listen. Listen. All right, money. I just
sent you something on um Facebook. [Laughter]
Yeah, I'm going to it now.
Is it David's address? Yeah. I don't
give a [ __ ] about Sean. [ __ ] off that
[ __ ] Now you see what you send me [ __ ]
David get smashed up.
>> Oh my David's address.
>> One second. One second. Hold on. He's
trying to get back in. Hold on.
>> What's your address? You little clown.
>> You think I can get out of jail? Watch
how many people I can get to your house.
You little clown.
>> You've got no me.
>> So, what's your address? And
>> you've got no mate.
When I was in Newcastle, big man
of you while you were in Newcastle. Are
you [ __ ] real?
>> You were in Newcastle years ago. Listen,
>> I've seen videos of you crying when
[ __ ] people get sorry you do. You
[ __ ] run. You run around a bus stop.
Well, where should I come to Russia and
get on YouTube?
>> Excuses. Excuses again. You're full of excuses.
>> Excuses. He's angry. He's angry on YouTube.
>> Why do you go around filming women?
>> Cuz I can do what you want. What are you
going to do?
>> Why does
men Why does his gogging?
>> Listen. Shut the [ __ ] up, Mos in the corner. [ __ ]
>> listen PJ
yourself. Where's your meat? I've had PJ
and I'll answer you. I'll answer
question. You don't let me answer.
>> Yeah. Where's Where's your
Let me talk.
>> Not even from my mate. You've seen my
mates. You've seen my money. You've seen
my women. But we've never seen you with
mates. We've never seen you with money.
mates. Where's your mates?
>> I've never I've never seen you, mates.
Every time you go out, you're always
with You're always by yourself. You've
seen me from the game.
>> Where's your mates? Where's your
>> So why So why are you [ __ ] Why are
you by yourself?
>> Why do you bite your nails down to the [ __ ]
Why do you sound like a [ __ ] Jordy down syndrome?
>> Why do you sound like a Why are you
bringing down syndrome into it?
>> Why do you sound like a Jord?
>> Down syndrome. Got nothing to do with
it. What we're talking about whatsoever.
maximal mentality whatsoever
what we talking about about your
mentality you down syndrome
>> why your words
>> why is your cons so big
>> well I man
hang on a minute
yeah when you were in this you got arrested
>> what you doing what you doing like like
you get arrested when you in Newcastle. PG.
>> Didn't you get arrested when you were in Newcastle? >> Yes,
>> the first time I went.
>> Yeah, you got arrested cuz you're a [ __ ] nons.
>> Oh, listen. Listen. If I'm a nons, why
didn't you meet me when I was in
Newcastle then? Why did you let a nons
come to your city? Why did you let your
city and you don't absolutely do nothing?
>> I didn't even know you were in Newcastle
till a couple of days ago. >> Newcastle.
>> I'm not even sub to your channel, you
[ __ ] I'm not even your channel, mate.
>> Full of excuses. No excuses
weasels. They put up excuses. There's no
point with it. You go around filming
women. You go by yourself. You got no me.
>> And I do what I want. You
engage [ __ ] anxiety. You got serious issues.
>> I've never had anxiety. You people never
had anxiety like
that. You know, when you go all over the
place, you listen, bro. Your anxiety is
so bad you can't even leave your house.
>> You're paranoid and death.
>> Let me kick you, Monty, cuz you keep
listen. Did I have anxiety when I was in your city?
>> Around your city. Did I have anxiety
when you done nothing about it? When you
could listen when I was younger,
>> you run away like a little [ __ ]
>> Run away, bro. Why didn't you meet me?
I've been to Newcastle three times.
You're a little funny.
>> I was in Newcastle. Why wasn't you
saying any of this [ __ ] then?
>> Well, get get yourself back to Newcastle.
>> I can't get myself back say mate. I was
there three times [ __ ] about big.
>> Just like ever done anything. Just like
none of you do anything.
>> You're [ __ ] funny. Listen, we got no
female interaction whatsoever.
>> Why can you not get a female
interaction? I' I've had more women.
You're a virgin. You're a virgin with no
friends. Not me.
>> A virgin.
>> You're a virgin with no friends. Not me.
How virgin when I got
>> I've been seen with women and friends. You haven't.
>> You haven't got any seen with women and
friends. But you haven't.
>> You haven't got any women on.
>> No woman. I know I have.
>> No women on this planet wants a big nose mate.
>> Listen. Listen.
>> I'm better looking, bro. Do you know
it's funny that you say that stupid?
>> I'm better looking than all of you. I'm
all of you. That's why you can't put
your camera on cuz you are ugly. You are the ugly.
>> Oh my god. Put your camera on.
>> That's why listen listen. Do you not
find it a bit strange how all you fat
ugly people your face? You've never been
seen with women. You don't leave your
house. You sit on YouTube all day.
>> Yeah, I'm the ugly one. Literally, bro.
>> What do you mean never been seen with
women? I've got [ __ ] kids.
>> You will see the m You will see the
jewel down syndrome m you will see. You
won't see that.
>> This is how sick you are. Listen female
interaction in your life, right?
>> Why don't you put your camera?
>> You go around filming women. You go by
yourself ugly face. Show everyone your
fat ugly face.
>> Why do you want to see me face?
>> Why are you scared to show your face? M.
>> Show yours.
>> M. Are you scared to show your face? You ugly jewel.
>> Oh, you you are thick.
>> Come on. It's not me and Monkey now.
It's It's me and you.
>> You are really thick.
>> Show your ugly face. You virgin. You've
never been seen with a woman, you
[ __ ] Jordi virgin. I went to your
[ __ ] I went to your city and I had
women all over me
>> to in your
bastard like you live in one of
>> How many women did you [ __ ] How many
How many women did you film when you
were in Newcastle?
>> You're a [ __ ] Listen, this is how
weird you are. You offered a [ __ ]
woman £500 to spend a day with you. you
offered a woman £500 to spend a day with
you. You woke up with a random woman and
you went, "Oh, hello. I just think
you're lovely. Um, I'm just wondering if
you want to spend a day with us if I
give you £500."
>> So, you're not So, you're not going to
show your face, man.
>> What sort of You're not going to show your face?
>> What sort of man does that? You're a
>> So, you're not going to show your face?
No. You're not going to show your face.
>> Listen, you've got to show
>> You've got to pay for sex. That's how much.
>> So you're not going to show your face.
>> Why would I want to show a big nose mother?
>> Cuz you're a fat ugly bastard. Just like
the bomb. You see? Let me let me let me
tell you right now. Let me tell you.
>> What you going to do? Go punch your mother.
>> The reason you don't show your punch
about [ __ ] That's why because anyone
that wasn't showed he's getting
>> anybody would show their face if they
wasn't. You can't show your face cuz
you're as [ __ ] You're an ugly mother.
That's why you can't show your face cuz
you're bro. You've got nothing going for you.
>> Everybody in the community. That's why
none of you show your face. It's
embarrassment cuz your ugliness. Look at
how big is your nose.
>> Do you remember how big your nose? You remember Pat?
>> How How big is your answer? You all You
all turn out to be fat and ugly. Isn't that funny?
>> Answer the question. How How big? Did
you not find that funny?
>> Yeah. I found it hilarious.
>> Yeah. And it's like even when you're
shown things, you deny it. This is why
people don't waste their time on you anymore.
>> Show more money, better looks, more
women, and you
>> Oh my god. Wasting time on you. That's
why it's a waste of time.
>> This is where you're going wrong. This
is where you're going wrong in life. You
think [ __ ] your life revolves
revolves about around money. It doesn't.
This is You're going wrong, man. You're
[ __ ] a weird guy, man. Can you not
see it? How weird you are.
>> Weird guy. Okay.
>> Yeah, you are. Who? Why do you go around filming women?
>> Just cuz you Because I do what I want.
Have you got a problem with it?
>> It's weird as [ __ ] Do you not find it weird?
>> Have you got a problem with it?
>> Do you not find it weird?
>> Have you do? No, I don't find it weird. Weird.
>> Weird. Speak. If you're going to talk,
talk English. I don't know what weird
find it [ __ ] weird, mate.
>> Like, what the [ __ ] is that? That's not
the queen. That's what the queen's English.
>> You [ __ ] big nose monk. Listen, like
I say, you got your face cuz you're a
virgin. Listen, you're so hard to bastard.
>> How How can I be a [ __ ] virgin? I've
got kids in a [ __ ] mom. How can I be
a [ __ ] virgin?
>> Got kids.
>> That's how thick you are.
>> Anyone can say they've got kids.
>> Everybody can Anyone can say they've got
kids, mate. [ __ ] wrong, man. It
doesn't mean anything.
>> Look, there's [ __ ] Mongol crying in the back.
>> Have I proved to you I've had sex?
>> What the [ __ ]
>> You haven't proved [ __ ] all. You haven't prove nothing.
>> [ __ ] all. Listen, I'm I'm I'm [ __ ]
inside a [ __ ] arguing this [ __ ]
Yeah. Leave him to me, PJ. Leave him to me. Yeah.
Ro for you, David. Roale
out on camera, lad.
your mom, David.
>> Let us know. Let us know your mom and
let us know and I'll punch [ __ ] out. How
about that? Yeah. >> Wass
[ __ ] know what I'm saying?
Your mom's picture of all over your
mom's titties on that picture, David.
>> He left.
>> Listen, you need Yeah. And another thing
is let me tell Yeah, he did leave.
Listen, let me tell you something as
well, man. You you people can try to
speak about people's looks all you want,
but guess what? You are the fat ugly
ones. That's why you can't show your
faces and you get proven to be ugly
every single time. I didn't kick you,
you little [ __ ] I never kicked you at all.
>> Well, let him back up. Let let him back.
>> No one kicked you at all.
>> Get him back up.
>> Put the link back up. No one kicked you.
You [ __ ] liar.
>> One second.
>> Back up. Yeah, cuz he thinks I'm being
kicked out of Natalie. I mean, he thinks
that I'm being kicked out of Manchester.
Yeah, Natalie's met my mates from Manchester.
>> What can I handle, bro? What can't I handle?
>> What can't I handle, bro? I asked you a
million times to show your face and you
couldn't do it. I asked you a million
times. How am I triggered about what,
bro? You started.
>> Yeah, get him back up.
>> Yeah, the link's there. What? Bro, you
start stuff and you can't finish it. You jy [ __ ]
>> No, I am going Raleigh. This needs to
get dealt with, man.
getting smashed up if he thinks I'm
being kicked out of Manchester listening.
>> I thought he lived in Rox.
>> He's a [ __ ] Jordy [ __ ]
>> Yeah, but I thought he was going out
with that [ __ ]
whoever his name is.
>> I don't I find it amusing how these fat
ugly people try to talk about how other
people look. That's what I
>> He's ugly. He's ugly. He's ugly as seen.
He's a fat bastard.
>> I love I just love how they tried to
call someone that better looking than
all of them. I find it funny, bro. I
don't even find it triggering. I find it funny.
>> The fact there on YouTube doesn't even
know anybody and thinks that being
kicked out of Manchester says so on YouTube.
>> I'm not I'm not saying I'm [ __ ]
good-looking or anything, bro. I'm not
saying none of that [ __ ] but I know I'm
better looking than every [ __ ] [ __ ]
on here. Damn right, bro. Of course I
am. Have we seen these people?
Think of it. Think of it, Monty. Yeah.
If you went on a community, right,
calling people ugly and someone asked
you to show your face, would you make a
million and one excuses why you can't
show your face or would you just show
it? You would just show it in it.
>> Is that that David guy?
>> But obviously these people can't show
their face cuz they're ugly. Well, David
lives though. That David guy, he liv
>> bro. He's mad. This guy is mad, bro.
>> Life gets more women than PJ. Yeah, of
course he does. See, the thing is with
these these these people, Monty, it
doesn't matter what you show them,
they're just going to deny it anyways.
This is what I'm trying to say to you.
>> No, obviously that's because they like
to deny things. They like
>> That's always what they're going to do.
Like I've shown me getting [ __ ]
[ __ ] sex, me in bed with women,
money, friends, and they still sit there
and pretend I've not shown nothing, bro.
They're always going to do this.
>> Oh, what they bring up is universal
credit. I could give a [ __ ] but the
people give a [ __ ] what the money they own.
>> You know what I'm saying?
>> [ __ ] Anyway, is he not coming back up? No.
>> No, the link's there.
>> Well, he's the [ __ ] bag. He's the one
who ran away. PJ kicked me.
Yeah, I kicked you cuz I was trying to
cuz you was pissing me off, bro. And you
was all talking over each other. >> Yeah.
>> No, man. You need to stop letting little
weasels up on a panel like that, man.
>> Yeah, man.
>> Yeah, they're [ __ ] just disabled,
bro. That's all they are.
>> Yeah, they are disabled. I'm going back
to Roxdale anyway.
>> Rodale, man. I'm going to I'm going to
kick [ __ ] out of him when I get back to
Rodale anyway. So, >> Rodale. >> [ __ ] >> Yeah.
I'm going to shoot off anywhere, PGA.
>> Yeah, man. I'm going to come off in a
bit anyways. Yeah. All right.
>> Okay. In a bit.
>> [ __ ] My eyes are [ __ ] now, bro.
>> But yeah, this is what I mean with these
people, bro. They sit there and [ __ ]
try to call [ __ ] you.
One second, buddy. You still there?
No job, no life. Yeah, that's you
people. You ain't got no job. You ain't
got no life.
Like obviously I know like they know
deep down the truth. Obviously, we know
that. But obviously, if they never are
going to admit stuff, that's obviously
the whole point where people why people
just don't waste their time on these people anymore.
you know, money game, showing this,
showing that, showing this, showing
that. It goes back to the Mark Samson
thing every time.
You know, they they remember what they
want to remember with these little mongos,
but they're very reluctant to show their
face, which is strange because if they
really weren't ugly, they would show their face.
They would actually show their face.
If they weren't ugly, they would show
their face, bro.
It's It's straight. It's literally just
what do I get from showing my face? What
do you get from being on here every day
being a keyboard warrior? You know, same
question. What do you get off? And you
don't get money for it. So they just all
of these excuses, right, we've heard and
you know, we've heard it from different
people, right, for ages. We've heard
these excuses and then every time they
get put out there, they're always fat
and they're always ugly.
Isn't that a madness? We've heard so
many different excuses. Oh, I don't want
people to find out who I am. No, no, no,
no. You hear all of these excuses to
hide up the fact that they're ugly.
That's what it is, bro. They, you know,
they don't show their face cuz they're ugly bastards.
Skinn ugly bastards ain't got a life.
That's it, brother.
Yeah, I've got no friends, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, I know, man. You keep
telling yourself that, bro, cuz all of
the things that you say that I don't
have, I've already shown before. So,
yeah, you keep telling yourself that. If
it if it makes you feel better about the
fact that you don't have any friends.
Keep saying it, bro. You know, if I' if
I've helped one person, even one person,
I feel like I've done my uh job. You
know, if them projecting their [ __ ] life
onto me helps them feel better, I feel
like, you know what, let them do it. You know, you know,
it's strange, isn't it? It is strange
what these people do on here. Anyone
would think these people actually know
each other, Reevesy,
you know. Cuz if I went on a community
right now and I called every [ __ ] ugly
and they said, "Oh, why don't you show
your face?" I'll show my face. I'll put
my camera on
cuz I know that that way I could own
them. I know that way they would never
have that. They would never ever ever
um have that over me. See, that's
something that you have over someone.
You know what I'm saying? Grievy, it's
what I had over Pat Mustard for many
years. It's what I had over bomb for
many years is the fact they could never
show their face. And when their face did
get out there, lo and behold, they were
fat and ugly.
So, I mean, the proof is in the pudding.
If you get me, bro.
Call one now. Prove it. Listen, bro. I'm
not playing your projecting games.
I'm not here to entertain you. I'm not
here to for your projecting games. You
know, you've seen me with friends,
you've seen me with women, you've seen
me with money. So, keep projecting, bro.
If it helps you feel better about your your life. Yeah.
And honestly, Greavves, that is why I
don't waste my time on them anymore. The
money game. Do you how much money I spent yesterday?
This is exactly why I don't waste my
time on him, bro. Cuz they're all the
same on here. All of them are the same.
Fat ugly people that ain't got a life
that self project hating on people that
they don't even know. been doing it for [ __ ] years.
He's [ __ ] ugly, bro. Yeah, I've seen
him. I've seen them. I've seen them.
He's a [ __ ] ugly bastard.
How he tries to [ __ ] talk about
anyone is [ __ ] beyond me.
[ __ ] way better looking than him,
bro. You mad?
You think that annoys me? It doesn't
annoy me. It just shows how insecure
these people are when they keep calling
you. It shows how insecure they are and
that's why they don't show their face.
Like bomb, Pat. It just goes to show how
insecure they are when they keep talking
about other people's looks.
It shows that they want to be you.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
Yeah. They need to grow up. [ __ ]
Virgin boy needs to get laid. He needs
to [ __ ] lose his virginity. Um,
yeah. It was funny yesterday, ain't it, Nicolola?
Yeah, I got a lot of I got a boyfriend
yesterday, Nicolo. But it was more so
when I was drinking, not the sober ones
as such. more so when I was drinking.
Bro, I'm done in this country, bro. I
don't care for dating in this country.
I'm leaving in November.
I'm not interested in it anymore, bro. I
only went out yesterday cuz I was [ __ ] bored.
I am done in this country. Like, I don't
care about it, bro. That's why it it
didn't piss me off yesterday, cuz I
expected it. It didn't annoy me at all yesterday.
because it's just I don't expect it to
ever change here. It will always be the same.
I'm not interested in this country, bro.
Obviously, I don't have hope. I just
went out cuz I was bored. Think about
it. How could you have hope? How could
you possibly have hope if you you
already got out a million times and
there was no hope then? So there's not
going to be no hope now, is there?
Things don't just suddenly change over
years. You know what I'm saying? If it's
been happening for years like it has,
God knows how many people I approached.
If things ever change then, it's not
going to change now. It's just logical,
isn't it? Like it's how it is. It's not
just one day going to change. What the [ __ ]
But you know, it was something to do, you know? So yeah,
and that's what I done yesterday.
Yeah. And that's what I'm going to do
every two to three weeks.
Every two to three weeks, I'm going to
do that. And that's what I done yesterday.
That's what I do. But not every [ __ ]
week. A, I can't [ __ ] afford it. Um,
by afford it, I mean I wouldn't be able
to do it and still be able to go on the
holiday that I'm going on cuz it would
just rinse all my money. And B, I don't
enjoy it as much if I do it every week.
Well, I could do it every week if I
really wanted to, but
it's more about I'd rather keep that
money for when I leave.
That's what I mean by afford it. Not
that I would run out of money. You know
what I'm saying? So, so yeah.
And yeah, it's not good drinking every week.
Yeah, she was being a [ __ ] in the end
anyways. The one that I met, she was
being a [ __ ] in the end anyways. And
that man's like, "Oh, maybe it's what
you said." And no, it's not what I've
said. Listen, I know people that I have
[ __ ] up with.
People that I have [ __ ] up with, I
know every single one of them. And I
know every single one of them that
wasted my time
cuz I've had people I know people I've
[ __ ] up with and there's been loads of
them and I know people that have just
wasted my time, you know? I know the
difference. Like, bro, I've been doing
this for many years now, man. I'm not
new to the game.
Nah, I'm never getting rid of my beard.
It needs to be trimmed. But yeah,
but um but then I'd say to him like, "Well,
how about um
how about the women that you kissed and
then ghosted you? What about that one then, Nicolo?
What about the ones that you kiss and
then they ghost you?
That's a bit odd, isn't it? How they
going to talk their way out of that one?
But this [ __ ] was trying to friend zone me. Um,
she was trying to friend zone me
in a way, but I think I can get myself
out of it.
So even like okay so say cuz these women
they will find stupid reasons why they
don't like someone. It's not a case of
oh they don't like you. It's a case of
they expect something that's not even realistic
which is why a lot of them never fight
oh I had an I had I had an I had one
with an attitude yesterday.
She was like oh I'm not interested and
no. I said oh that's a bit rude is it?
Like you should give people a chance.
And uh I didn't say anything cuz it was
negative. And then she was like, "Oh,
like walk on." I said, "I'll walk on
when I'm [ __ ] ready. You don't tell
me when to walk on." Um
and I said, "Don't moan and winge when
you're in your 30s and you can't find
anyone." Which I weren't even being
disrespectful. I was being real. And um
I mean they were quite they were a bit
younger than me sort of thing. Um which
I feel like is to give some advice, you
know, like don't don't moan in the wind
when you're in your 30s and you can't
find no one.
don't moan to us cuz we don't want to hear it.
You know what I'm saying? And I said,
"You don't tell me to walk on. I will
walk on when I want to walk on." I made
a point of that. You don't tell me what
what to do. And it was right in the
middle of Leicester Square as well. And
I said, "You can bring any man over here
and I'll say it in front of them as
well." We were in a public place. He was
with her friend as well. There was two
of them. I said, "I'll wait here for any
guy you bring."
And I'll say it in front of any man,
bro. Like, like it's not about that.
So, we let I'll step away. You get put
the guy in the middle and I'll say the
same thing. But I don't know. You got to understand like
don't do this [ __ ] like
being a [ __ ] or even like leading
somebody and use leading someone on and
use them like regardless of what they're
doing. And then cry like a [ __ ] when
when you meet your match.
There's there's no point in that. Like
there's no point crying when you meet your match
because it's just ridiculous, you know,
like and it could be anyway like
attitude or they could just use someone
or, you know, could be don't don't don't
play the victim when you meet your match
then. Simple. Like it's just silly. It's
like if I go around [ __ ] on the if I
go around [ __ ] with people on the
street, I'm going to get my ass whooped eventually.
I had one as well. I sat down. I tried
to speak to them and they just stood up
and walked away. Yep.
There's been a lot of those. There's
been a lot of those. With this one, I
never because I'm just used to it now
that their attitude and that. So, it
never really wound me up. But, I made a
point of saying that like, you're not
talking to me like that. Like, you don't
tell me what to do. Um,
I don't think I was being rude either.
Like when you're in your 30s, you will
you'll be winging and moaning that you
can't find someone. That's not being
rude. That's what actually will happen. Um,
but it's funny cuz a lot of these people
on Reddit, where do people on Reddit get
it so easy? Cuz it is not easy in
America. And I know most people on
Reddit live in America. And trust me,
it's not easy in America. Trust me, it's
not. All you got to do is look at the
attitude over there as well. Like, it's
not, bro. Especially [ __ ] North
America. I would say that's the worst
place to try dating in.
I mean, London's pretty bad. I mean, UK
is [ __ ] bad, but I mean, like, I
think America is is even harder.
I mean, all the toxic people come from
there. So, I don't know where people on
Reddit go on like it's so easy. It's mad.
I'm surprised, bro. Like, they they go
on like it's so I might do a video on this.
You like my little videos, Nicolo?
I might do a little video talking about
this. I feel like it needs to be a
Yep. She didn't even look at me as well.
You didn't even look at my face. Um,
he didn't even look at me, I don't think.
But then there was ones that were nicer
and so it depends. But yeah,
no one tells you that on Reddit cuz it's
like what Ant-Man says. It's It's not
about them. It's about you now. It's not
about them. It's about you.
It is about you. It's not about them.
They're not the problem. You're the
problem. you're the problem because
you're staying in this country
knowing what it's always going to be.
Then you can leave and which I am doing.
You can leave or you can give up. So at
the end of the day, it's actually you
that's the problem now because you know
what they're like. You know what they've
been like for years. And you know, as
much as we say it's not going to change,
it's not going to change. So at the end
of the day it's like
um at the end of the day like it's not
about them it's about you and what you do
you know obviously leaving or you know
moving forward so it is actually you now
that's the problem
which obviously I knew yesterday I was
playing at my own risk so it didn't
bother me at all really cuz
I like to think I know what it's always
going to be like here now.
I really hope it's that and not the fact
that it's not cuz I went I didn't go out
for 3 weeks.
But it pop up in my it did pop up in my
mind a few times. Oh, if you can't even
get a conversation out of someone, how
are you going to date? But it didn't
annoy me. Like nothing about it annoyed
me. I was just happy just to go out and
not be bored. But obviously it does it
does obviously pop in your mind
obviously cuz it's normal. You know, you
get people that say, you know, life
changes. You don't know what's going to happen. But
I don't know, man. It doesn't look good, does it?
Let's put it that way. But people still
say seem to think that. And it's not
easy in America either. So I don't know
where they get this [ __ ] from
because it's not easy in America.
They're horrible people in America. You
know, all you got to do is look at some
of them videos, bro. Like it's
I can't believe that guy said he's not
had sex for two years. Wow.
How the [ __ ] did he cope for 2 years not
getting sex? He said, "Yeah, he broke up
with somebody two years ago. He's not
had sex or Yeah, it's
I'm used to it, bro. Like, it is what
it's always going to be like here.
I have patience that I never knew I had.
That's what I'm trying to say, bro. So,
people shouldn't be People should
actually be biggering me up. They
shouldn't be bringing me down. They
should be bringing me up.
Yeah, but it's just
it's the way it is, isn't it, bro?
Then they call you an incel when when
you don't lick their asses. Strange, is
it, bro? Strange.
But the Norwegian the the Norwegian one
was the Finnish one was nice. Um and the
one sitting down was nice as well. And I
generally believe she actually was in a
relationship. Like you can actually
generally tell when they are when they're not
because the way they word it, you know.
So, I think the people that said they
were in relationships actually were not
the clubs, not the bars and the clubs.
They're full of [ __ ] But I feel like
the ones that I spoke to on the street,
I think they were I think they were
generally genuine, bro. I'm not going to
lie. Cuz three out of 10 said they were
in relationships. And
no, I generally think they were genuine,
bro. You just know when they're genuine.
You just know when they're genuine. Like
the first one I done, I remember, she
said, "I have a boyfriend." And I said,
"Oh, where you from?" She said, "I had a
boyfriend again." I said, "Do you want a new one?
I know. I never said that. I said, "Do
you want another boyfriend?" That's what
I said to her. I said, "Do you want another boyfriend?"
He said, "No, she's full of shit." That
woman was full of [ __ ]
So, maybe. No, I think I got Yeah, that
No. So, two of them were genuine, but
she was obviously full of [ __ ] You just
know when they're full of [ __ ] But the
other two, I think they were genuine,
but the way they worded it, you know,
some people are in relationships. Yeah.
Yeah, I am.
I generally think they were in
relationships, bro. The the the other
two, I think they generally were. Just
the way they worded it, like they're
talking about their partner. I generally
think they were, bro. I generally think
they were. Not them ones where you go
into a club and they're Indian and they
say straight away they've got a
boyfriend. They don't have no [ __ ]
They don't have no boyfriend.
This is [ __ ] bro. But some of them
I think they actually did. You can read
between the lines, bro.
But um yeah, if you go to like a club
like a Simmons
and like they say it straight away or
Yeah, they're full of [ __ ]
They're full of [ __ ]
They really are full of [ __ ]
But yeah, she said she was with someone
for two months. I got one appro I got
one number sober and I just got the
number anyways cuz it's better than
nothing, you know. It's better than
nothing. She's only been with the [ __ ] 3
months. So it's better than nothing.
That's the way I saw it. So
yeah, it's bad, man. I'm going to do a
video on this later, man.
I done a video by Big Ben. I just never uploaded it.
Not Peter Belly's mama. Yeah.
I said, "Do you want a new boyfriend?" I
said, "No." I said, "You want another one?" Am
I virgin with his ugly virgin face?
Yeah. Yeah, I done a video about Big Ben
talking about the dating game, but I
didn't like some of the things I said,
so I didn't upload it.
Yeah. So, I didn't upload it.
That's where they blocked the road off
so I couldn't do deliveries and stuff.
I'm not your [ __ ] mate.
But yeah, I do.
Yeah. I said, "How about this? You just
give me your number and then um you
know, text me and I'll text you and if
you reply back, you do. If you don't, you don't."
I kind of persuaded her cuz I just
wanted a number cuz nothing sober. So,
so what? 3 months is nothing. If she
said like 3 years, if she said 3 years,
then I would have [ __ ] with it.
Personally, I wouldn't have [ __ ] with it. But yep,
I done a lot of walking yesterday, mate.
Nah, 3 months is nothing, bro. What if
they break up tomorrow? You got to
understand with these things, right? Not
not three years, though. somebody was
with someone for 3 years, then
I just I would rather disrespect it.
But, you know, 3 months is a is not a
long time. And you know what? If he
cheats on her one day or you know,
whatever. Like, you know what I'm
saying? So, 3 months is is [ __ ] all, bro.
Look what happened to Monty and [ __ ] Natalie.
Yeah, she was nice. She was standing on
by the grass and I just [ __ ]
approached her. I thought, "Fuck it.
Yeah. Yeah. I don't get fat. I do a lot
of walking, matey.
Had a nice roast dinner yesterday at the brewery.
[ __ ] spent about 200 pound yesterday.
[ __ ] me, man.
Bad, bad, bad.
Yeah, I was speaking to Barry. It was a nice chap.
It was a nice chat, Barry. I done some
approaches in the Weather Spoons as well.
Yeah, there were a lot of approaches yesterday, but
No, I don't remember that.
Maybe vaguely. Yeah, [ __ ] me.
Yeah, I got in a piss uh yesterday, Mike.
Yeah, I done some approaches. I done 10
approaches sober and uh yeah,
I was speaking to Barry yesterday, man.
I was telling him I had [ __ ] I feel
100 years [ __ ] old.
Oh, [ __ ] knows, bro. I can't remember.
There's been so many of them.
I was on the ramicals yesterday, but
funny enough, I don't feel that bad.
Going out's too expensive now, man. [ __ ]
Yeah, I got an escort at the end of the
night. She swallowed my [ __ ] bro. And
then she started kissing me and [ __ ]
which was quite nice.
Just went out and about, bro. Just
approaching and drinking and [ __ ]
Why do these people say I've got
anxiety? Nicolo David UFC said that I've got anxiety.
I've got [ __ ] anxiety.
What the [ __ ]
Why do these people say I've got
anxiety? I might have to ask Monty.
Monty would know. Monty would know the answer. No.
Because these people have got anxiety.
I don't [ __ ] suffer with [ __ ]
anxiety. What the [ __ ]
Nah, mate. I can't I can't suffer from
anxiety because I've been through like
hell and back and [ __ ] So, what what
doesn't kill you makes you stronger,
right? So, how can I have anxiety, bro?
7 8 months of living in that house, bro.
You you can't be you can't have anxiety after that,
you know? So,
I don't have
I don't have anxiety like these people, bro.
What should I eat, man? I'm [ __ ]
hungry. I don't want to eat because I'm
going to eat. I have to eat again. So, I
might just get like a big Chinese later.
Oh, that'd be lovely. A nice Chinese.
Some nice chicken balls. Money, mic. Oh, mate.
But yeah, I'll do a video later on the
dating game and [ __ ] Nah, it's too
greasy, bro. When I've had rum, I can't
have greasy [ __ ] the next day.
You know what I'm saying? I can't have any grease.
Um, I don't know about you, but if it's
greasy, I can't have it. It makes me feel sick.
Something to do with the rum or
something. So, it'd have to be like a
curry or some nice chicken fried rice or something.
I had a pizza yesterday as well. Pizza.
But yeah, the dating game here is
impossible, Mike. Like, bro, it is proper impossible.
But I went out cuz I wanted to go out
and I realized it's not about them
anymore. It's about me cuz I need to
leave, which is what I'm doing. So, I
love bacon, bro. But I tell you what's
good after drinking an omelette.
I'm telling you. I tell you what's good
after drinking is an omelette.
Omelette, bro. Like a nice piggy and
mushroom omelette. I don't think that
gets enough rating, bro. I honestly
don't think that gets enough rating.
Like a nice omelette.
It is impossible, bro. And I'm decent
looking as well. And I'm confident, like
somewhat, but I haven't done it for a
while. But yeah, you can't you can't get nothing, bro.
It is impossible. [ __ ]
It is impossible, bro. Obviously it is cuz Yeah,
cuz obviously the number one thing is
obviously the time frame it's been going on for
and obviously if something was really
going to change it it's not just going
to change now.
You know what I'm saying? It's not stuff
don't just change like that. You know
what I'm saying, bro?
If it was leading up to change, like
date, date, kiss, date, kiss, then we
could, okay, well, we can work something
out here. But they uh
they um there's no leadup to it. So,
just seems [ __ ] isn't it?
But I think what was good yesterday is I
never really tried. I just dress
casually. I think if I dress casually,
may maybe if I actually put a lot of
effort into it, I think it would have
wound me up.
Like if I got like a haircut and [ __ ]
and dress good and that even though I
still look all right, but like I think
that would have just like annoyed me more.
But I don't know. I don't think so, bro.
I think I'm used to it now. So yeah,
I wanted to go out, but I didn't want to
get a haircut. I don't want to sit on
the chair for now. It's boring, bro.
Well, obviously I'd have to the next
time I go out. So,
so how people on Reddit make it seem
easy, I shall never know.
I hate America. I hate Americans,
but they seem to think it's so easy
there, which I can't. But this guy said,
"If you come to Chicago, they might like
your accent." I said I'm not [ __ ]
going to Chicago, bro. [ __ ] that.
Absolutely. [ __ ] that, bro.
Trying to get me killed.
They'd only like your accent if you was
in somewhere like [ __ ] Georgia or
[ __ ] Tennessee or Yeah, maybe even
Chicago, but you know, not somewhere
like [ __ ] New York or [ __ ] Boston
where they [ __ ] hear it a million times.
Your accent's not going to.
It's just too It's just too hard in this country, bro.
That's what it is.
Taking a baby away from its mumar. chasing rainbows. So yeah,
I'm waving that white flag.
I'm waving that white flag, matey.
Well, I got this one in Canada, but
Canada's not abroad, is it?
Is it, Mike? Canada. Canada's not
abroad, is it?
Canada's not abroad, is it, lad? No.
Is Canada abroad or no? No.
Yeah. I I don't know why I said it so
hard yesterday, bro. I'm never normally
that confident. I'm normally just fed up
with it all.
But I just thought, why not in it?
Not doing anything else. Yeah.
Yeah. Stay in the club, bro. I was
holding her hand. She [ __ ] almost
beat me in a [ __ ] arm wrestle, bro.
I'm [ __ ] I'm getting weak, bro.
I can't. She literally we had an arm
wrestle and she almost beat me.
>> Damn, bro.
>> I still feel I could have someone in a
fight. I feel like I generally feel like
I could have a bouncer in in a fight though.
I generally feel like I could cuz I feel
like once you hit him in the right
place, bro, they're done.
I genuinely feel like I could, bro.
You know what I'm saying? And I
generally feel like I could
really So what what did Barry think
about it all?
What did Barry think about it all? Huh?
Yeah, it's my mom's birthday tomorrow,
so I need to go and give her a card.
Yeah, obviously I went with the escort
with £100 and I got £30 from it cuz she
only charged 70. So I just put £30 in a card,
send it to Laney in it.
Oh, he's got cinema Friday. [ __ ] the
conjuring. E, the conjuring is on. Yeah.
I do I used to tell the Australians
about Mick Jonathan Robinson.
Do you remember Nicolola? I used to warn
the Australians about him.
dirty [ __ ] pedo.
He was put into care at a very young age
because of it.
Was put into care. He was put into care
until he was 18
and then when he come out of care. Um,
obviously the council gave him a house
or [ __ ] bed, but you know, you know
what I mean? Yeah. Yep.
So, what what was she doing when she was
on the plane back home? What was USA
Izzy doing when she was on the plane
back home? Nicola.
The boy is getting jealous again that
I've met a new woman.
He gets so jealous when I meet new
women, doesn't he?
Look at this. Right. I don't think I've
ever seen a more cringy moment with the
m trying to torch the opposite set.
Massively disabled with no life
experience. Now, you know that account,
you know, um you know this account is
just some fat, ugly 40y old virgin that
that can't leave his house. That's all
they are on here, bro.
That's literally all they are on here
are just fat, ugly people that ain't got
a life. That's why nothing they do or
say bothers anyone because we know the real them.
We know the real them, bro.
We know the real them. Fat, ugly nerds
that come on YouTube cuz they ain't got
a life. We know about these people now.
It's not like we don't know about these people.
Yeah, that's the one. Yeah, he's a sad
How the [ __ ] can they sit there obsessed
every day over someone they don't even know, bro?
Sat on YouTube every [ __ ] day typing
away about somebody that they don't even
know. They never even met and they they
don't even know. They're fat, ugly
virgins, bro. I swear to God, that's why
they never come on camera. They're fat,
ugly people and they don't realize that
their opinion doesn't mean anything to anybody.
You know what I'm saying, bro? Like none
of these people's
uh none of these people opinions mean
anything to anyone. They're just fat,
ugly life losers that ain't got a life
sat on YouTube every day. You know, at
the end of the day, you can't meet you
can't meet these people, bro.
You can't meet these people. They'll
never meet you, mate. Look at that
[ __ ] David. You [ __ ] UFC trying to
say, "Oh, I didn't know you was in
Newcastle." What? Three times, bro.
They're all the same on here.
You try to meet them, they pretend they
didn't see it. You show them money, they
pretend you didn't show them money. Bro,
it's the same on here, bro.
That's why we don't waste our time on
these [ __ ] idiots anymore.
How long have they been sat on YouTube
calling me skin?
What did I go and do yesterday? I spent
over £200. These people don't know what
people have. These people don't know
what's in your bank account. They
self-reflect of their own lives. You
know what I'm saying?
And you knew by that whole Mark Samson thing,
that whole Mark Samson thing says it
all, bro. You're wasting your time with
these fat, ugly, jealous people. If
you're fat and ugly and disabled like
them, then they they don't mind you.
They like you. You understand?
Because they're all wrong and all wrong
got on with each other. But the moment
you're younger than them and you're
better looking than them and you got a
better life than them, they hate on you.
They literally hate on you. Cuz
these people don't know you, you know?
They don't [ __ ] know you in real
life. They're [ __ ] writing about
someone all day on YouTube that they
don't even know. Imagine that, bro.
Imagine that. Stalking every day. All
day, every day. Someone that they don't
even [ __ ] know in real life.
Sat on [ __ ] YouTube like the low
lives that they are. [ __ ] pathetic, bro.
They need to act their age, not their
[ __ ] size, bro. That's what they need to do.
And yeah, they just they're just clearly
jealous of something in life, bro. For
them to do this all day every day,
they're clearly jealous of something.
like how they spend all their life,
right, trying to make you insecure
when deep down they're the fat, ugly
ones that know that you're better
looking than them. That's the that's the
funny thing. And they're the ones that
are getting annoyed. They're the ones
that are getting frustrated because they
have to come online every day triggered.
They have to come online every day, all
day, every day triggered.
All day, every day triggered.
Right. Think about it, Nicolola. How
long has that red star been triggered
for? Four years.
How long has he been triggered for?
About four years. 5 years.
Sat on YouTube triggered. [ __ ] madness.
It's cuz they're hopeless losers. They
got nothing in their life.
They got [ __ ] all in their life, bro. I
could only keep up for like [ __ ] two days. Imagine
me or you. Imagine me and you coming on
the internet stalking someone every day
that we've never met for 4 years. Just
just imagine it. I know like a lot of
your brains don't work properly, so you don't actually
acknowledge how disabled it is, but just
think about it. D. Yeah,
let's get some piggies. Nah, bro. Too greasy.
Too greasy, bro.
Nah, I'm going to go. I'm just going to
wait for the Chinese to open
or just have like a nice curry and uh
I'm going to do a video on dating.
Well, that will never happen because
they never meet anyone.
So, that will never happen because they
will never meet anyone.
You know what I respect about that
Kenji? Yeah. When I actually went and I
showed him up, he never bothered me ever again.
That's mad. Like, he never ever bothered
me ever again. When I put him in his
place, he never bothered me ever again.
I'm saying, which is good, you know.
Yeah. He never bothered me again.
which is what people do. They should take L's.
Nope. I don't put any approaching videos
up on this channel. They're on my other
channel, but uh
they uh they were my other channels, but
um my other channel, but no,
I'm not interested.
I'm not, bro. And a lot of it would bore
you anyways cuz it's it's the same it's
the same ending and the same beginning.
And it's just different characters.
So why do you want to see a protein
videos? They're all the same. Most of them.
I still got the USA Izzy one, but cuz I
feel like I'm never going to delete that
because that was a one in a lifetime thing.
You know, that was a one in a lifetime thing. So
um yeah, he was a weirdo, man. But you
won't want to see approaching videos
because they're all the same, just different characters. So yeah. Yeah.
And so it should,
you know, so it should. But obviously
you might go out one day and you might
find someone. I didn't do it. I couldn't
do it. So
they're all just too stuck up. That's
that's all it is, bro. It's nothing more. Nothing.
Nah, bro. There's no point. They're all
the same. I just put them on my other
channel to show Reddit
like my experiences and stuff. I just I
just do it to show Reddit. Yeah,
they said, "No, they said to me, yeah, I
don't know what it is. You look normal
and you talk normal. There must be too
many stuckup [ __ ] in your country or something."
That's what they said. They said, "Um,
there just must be too many stuck up
[ __ ] in whatever weird country you're
in." And they're right. Like if you go
to any Simmons in London, they're just
all stuck up. They're all NPCs. Like
they're just they're just such, bro.
They're just too stuck up. So
too many stuck up [ __ ] in your
country. I think they were right, bro. I
think we didn't give them enough rating.
But I re do you reckon if I lived in
Newcastle I would have
found someone by now? Maybe. It's hard
to say. It's hard to say. Like you know
even though I've been all over the country, right?
You know the thing is is that like you
might have got unlucky once or twice on
the places that you've been.
But I feel like if you lived anywhere
else, I feel like eventually you would
have found someone
in like a month or something. I don't
know. But you won't ever know cuz
you haven't been there long enough. But
leads was [ __ ] bro. I thought leads was
going to be a lot better. So
I went to I went to Newcastle and this
woman said, "You're too handsome for Newcastle."
And we started hitting it off.
But that Simmons is the worst. Yeah.
I chucked it back at him as well, bro. I
chucked it back at him as well. Don't
get it twisted. I I I chucked it back at
him as well.
But I wish I said something better now.
I wish I said I'm only a pedo when it
comes to your kids.
I've only got my eyes on your kids.
That's what I should have said to him
now. Coming to think of it, he tried to. Yeah.
I said only when it comes to your juicy
kids. That's what I should have said. I
should have said a lot of different
things to people, but you just don't
think in the moment. Like that woman
when I was riding the bike,
like not even like nasty things. I wish
I just said obviously when I said I'll
do what I want
and then I said come back and say to my
face. Yeah, I know. I stuck it on then,
but I wish I said something more like
why don't you mind your own [ __ ] business.
That's and then just said that, you
know, but obviously you don't have time
to think at the time and it's so far
and that's all you'd have to say. How
about you mind your own [ __ ] business?
That would have just completely owned
them, bro. Like there's nothing else
that they can say
because these people don't understand.
And I don't care if you've had a bad day.
I don't give a [ __ ] if you've had a bad
day or No, no, no, no. Like, you're not
taking your [ __ ] out of me. Simple.
Like, I don't care who the [ __ ] you are.
You understand? Like,
you're not you're not doing that, bro.
I'm not these little s [ __ ] You
know what I'm saying?
So it's like you even have to deal with
[ __ ] even if you go to work.
You know these entitled people, bro.
>> Yeah. these these [ __ ] um
entitled [ __ ] uh puns basically.
What's the football lineup for uh next Saturday?
Let's have a little whirl.
I won. Do you remember when I won the
football bet when I was with that
Australian Nikolai? I put 20 pound on I
won 60 quid.
Do you want my Do you want my opinions
be ah Ah,
they're all [ __ ]
She don't want to know you. She don't
want to know you. She don't want to know
I think you need to chill out. Is that
right? Yeah. Everybody knows that you're
a crazy [ __ ]
I think you need to chill out.
>> Is that right?
>> Yeah. Everybody knows that you're a crazy [ __ ]
You're not like we used to. >> Yeah.
YouTube would be boring you without out
me in it.
>> She don't want to know. She don't want
to know. She don't want to know you. >> Yeah. Um,
but the only way this is going to change
in this country is probably when you're
like [ __ ] 40 or some [ __ ]
That's the only way the dating game will
ever change here is when you're like [ __ ] 40.
I feel like if you're like 40 then it would. Yeah.
I wonder what Virgin Boy would do
without me. Do you reckon he'd finally
like go out and get laid or do you
reckon he'd finally lose it?
Lose that vod.
You remember that old man that used to
hit on Monty
when he was on PlayStation? That old man
TJ Hooker? He said he it gives him
nightmares. Hey Jamie, I'm a gay guy
from Canada. It's a choice. It's not a
choice to be gay.
That's what you say. I'm from Canada,
guys. I'm trying to find that old man to
show Monty to like so it haunts him even
more. Yeah. Hey guys, I'm I'm I'm from
I'm a gay guy. Yes. I'm from Canada. [Laughter]
He died. Yeah, he died, man. Yeah.
Do you know you know I hate grieving?
You know when you masturbate a lot and
then you get a [ __ ] It hurts. So you
have to not like masturbate for like 2
days cuz sometimes it will hurt.
If you masturbate, it would actually
hurt you and when you get a [ __ ]
again. If you do it if you get one too quickly. Yeah. Yep.
Well, I need to do a video about this
dating [ __ ] in a bit. I'm [ __ ]
getting really hungry now, man.
But I'd rather let the hunger build up
than eat and then just go sleep. Cuz
after I drink rum, I can eat like three
times a day. Three or four times a day,
bro. I can easily just eat and eat and
eat and eat and eat. Don't bother me,
bro. Like that's what happens.
Get a slim chickens. I love slim
Yeah, that's where that re That's where
I had that Carolina Reaper burger.
Yeah, that's where I had a Carolina Reaper burger.
Yeah, bro. That's been a thing in London
for ages, man. It's [ __ ] expensive,
though. And And they're only in central
London. There's not any like near me.
They're all in central London.
Have you ever had lobster greavves? I've
got a lot I've got a lot more life
experience than Griezy, but Griezy is
older than me.
I need to have a shower, man. [ __ ]
Yeah, I had lobster once and
I can't say I was keen keen on it.
My beard's getting really long, bro. [ __ ]
Surprised I got any [ __ ] numbers yesterday?
Grezy, what? Who Who do you think's
better looking? Me or Virgin Boy? honest opinion
because obviously you're a you're a um
you give a uh an unbiased opinion.
So, who do you think who do you think
looks better, me or Virgin Boy?
No homo, obviously.
Oh, the lady seems to think [ __ ]
Peter Belly, man. You know what I'm saying?
I think Grezy would pick me.
Oh, is that right, Greasy? You pick me,
huh? Bless you then.
Bless you in life.
I'm [ __ ] way better looking than that [ __ ] virgin.
Yep. The truth though, is it?
Well, I don't have as much money as I
used to have, but I've still got more
money than them.
And better looking as well,
which is true though because why why
else would they do what they do every
day if that wasn't the truth? If that
wasn't the truth. If you actually think
about it, it actually is true.
Because then if if that wasn't true,
they would just leave. They would just
live their perfect life.
You understand? They they don't know
you. They've never met you.
So, I mean, at the end of the day, if
that wasn't true, then they would just
live their life and leave you alone, but
they can't. And he was right that
they'll never leave you alone either,
which is true. They will never leave you alone
because obviously since he's been on
here a year, they've still been doing it
for years. So, it's true. They they will
never leave you alone.
That is uh the truth. So, yeah,
they will never leave you alone. No
[ __ ] true word ever spoken, bro. To
be honest, I'm actually thinking of
really taking these advice I'm not even joking, bro. So, yeah,
I could win the lottery. I actually had
some money lying around actually in
cash, but not showing any of these
people anything. I don't show projectors
money. I don't show skin people money. Nicolo
Yeah, I don't show skid people, money. Nah. Oh, [ __ ]
About my little short. Gosh darn it. I
like them little shoes.
Oh, gosh darn it.
I want to wear this. Oh, go crazy.
>> I'm having stitch boxing. It's locked. Virgin B. Virgin boy.
That's my like normal reaction now. Bro,
you watch my little videos. Greavvesy.
I bet you sit there waiting patiently
for a little Peter Belly upload
bad, bro. I do feel bad for these
people. It it do it does get to a point
where you just feel sorry for them, you know. God bless.
Yep. I didn't even plan to go out
yesterday. They just My little legs just
took me out and about, you know. I
Nicola. I bet sometimes when you're out
yet in the pub, you think of things I've
said and you start laughing, is in it. I do sometimes.
You know, I think of like Sig was never
your mama. Sig's not Peter Belly's mama.
Grezy, I've got Stitch on my underpants.
I've got Stitch boxes. I'm wearing them right now.
Yeah. I feel like what about when I feel
like like when I lost like when I when I
lose gambling I feel like I've been raped.
Yeah, you do feel like you've been
raped, bro. What the [ __ ] It's disgusting.
You actually feel like it sounds funny
to you. Like it actually does make you
feel like that.
That's why I had to stop the machines
and the roulette and stuff. It's horrible.
It's horrible experience. Yeah.
No. Yeah. Cuz it's funny, isn't it?
Taking a baby away from its mama.
But I'm the one that come out with all
of these sayings, isn't it?
Taking a baby away from it mama. Yeah.
God can only You need God, little man.
And only God can save you.
Yeah. I messaged I messaged Damon
yesterday at uh today 4 in the morning.
I said, "Daddy," he said, "Hope you find
God. He's the only one who can save
you." Yeah. I messaged him saying, "Daddy."
Yeah. I call I called him daddy.
You're better looking than them. You
have more money than them. You have a
better life than them. And it kills
them. Get off of YouTube and live your
life. That's what he said.
I think he was right, bro.
I think he was right.
Especially the never leaving you alone
part. They will never leave you alone.
It's the truth though, isn't it? You know,
they will never leave you alone.
They will never leave you alone. I might
go live on a Saturday and go to the pub
and do some approaches on on a Saturday.
Yeah, but that's different. She's my
actual she's my actual mama,
you know. That's a bit different,
you know. I come from her, you know. So,
taking a baby away from its mama.
Did you piss yourself when I come out
with all of these sayings?
You're part of the family now. [ __ ] off.
Am I part of the family? No, I'm not.
You're part of the family now.
I'm part of the I'm part of the family. Remember?
Well, what about the other one that
stand I had on my birthday? She could be my mama. Nicolola,
she could be my
Yeah, she could have been my mama. Who
knows? You don't know, bro? Do you really?
Maybe I did. And maybe I didn't.
How do you know that?
Sig's not Peter Bell's mama.
Yeah, but how did how did you know that?
Yeah, but you don't know that.
Maybe I can get attached now. And I
know maybe I can get attached now to my mama.
What is that dirty westernized look that
they give you?
What is that look that they give you?
That what where do they get that from?
Like that westernized look.
You can see it in their eyes. Like I
don't know, bro. It's weird.
Is it from like watching too much Tik Tok or
would never change, would it?
What is that look though, bro? I'm
looking on it now.
It's them eyes, bro. What? Where did
they get them eyes from?
They've all got that same look in their eyes.
I mean, it's weird. Yeah.
Yeah, you can see the westernity in
their eyes. It's so weird.
You can see the westernity in their eyes.
It's mad. Anyways, I'm going to be back