Awesome. Thank you. Heat. Heat. Heat.
There is something
You hear me now?
I hope I haven't been speaking the whole
[ __ ] time and you haven't heard me. I
was basically Yeah, I was connected to
my earpods. Yeah, I was saying I was
speaking to Finnish Izzdy yesterday. So,
two numbers replied back out of four.
So, it's not the worst really, but yeah.
Oh, no. I was saying you didn't get Oh,
I have to repeat myself. I was saying
you didn't get a number.
I was saying you didn't get a number yesterday.
Stop talking [ __ ] bro. You don't
even leave your house. You never got a
number. I was going to do a football bet
today on the National League North, but
can't really afford to be betting
losing, bro. So,
I'd rather put the money towards something else.
And I'd rather um I want to go um
even if I won a football bet, won loads
and loads and loads of money, I still
wouldn't go out this week. I prefer the
whole detox being greasy, not going out
for two weeks and then going out.
I just It's just more better, you know,
doing it every two weeks.
I don't know. It just is. It feels better.
You enjoy it more. I don't know.
Really? I've never had someone be rude
like that to me. Well, I had somebody
try to give me that attitude the other
day, but that's cuz I said about you're
going to end up 30 and alone,
but I've never had it like straight off
the bat. Someone just be rude like that.
I would, bro.
I don't think so. Not someone that I've approached.
They must look at you like a [ __ ]
bro. Cuz that ain't never happened to me.
>> Never happened to me, bro. No one could
ever [ __ ] talk to me like that, bro.
They've been like stuck up and [ __ ] and
walked away or like
that's very rude. You know,
Yeah, I'll give you the box in a minute,
bro. But yeah, I just think it's better that way.
There is a National League North playing today, but
that would probably be a good for um
that would probably be good for like a
both score no draw them northern
leagues, them south leagues and them
northern leagues. I think there will be
the ones for the the both score no draw,
but I'm not betting [ __ ] I'm not
betting money, bro. [ __ ] that.
So, at least she replied to finish one.
She did reply and she seems all right to be honest. So yeah,
same age as me as well. I'm 2 months older.
I don't know. I like it when you meet
people that's the same age.
I don't know. I like it. You know when
you meet somebody that's exactly the
same age as you? Like there's no age
gap. Like it's just good. I I don't know, man.
It's kind of weird cuz
USA Izzy is [ __ ] older than my sister.
When you put it that way, it's kind of
weird. Like, she's actually older than
my sister. She's down to me. Yeah, but
I'll have to go Finland.
Isn't that right, Grezy?
Yeah, but I'd have to go [ __ ] Finland
cuz they're not in London anymore. there
in Scotland and [ __ ] So yeah,
which is still an option. You know,
Finland's not Finland's not Finland's
not that far. It's only a couple of
hours on a plane. It's not that far.
Somewhere like Finland isn't far.
No, she's not going back the next day.
She's in Scotland now.
But either way, like Finland's not far
at all. Finland's not unrealistic.
[ __ ] America's unfucking realistic.
[ __ ] Australia is unrealistic. But
Finland, what's it like 2 and a half
hours? It's easy done. Easily done.
Think of it, Gre. If it means going to
another If it means going to another
country, right, and this [ __ ] all
ending, and it doesn't even need to be
as far as Thailand, isn't that a good
option? I feel like that's a good
option. Say you had someone in Finland,
right, and they proved that they weren't
all like the other women and they were,
you know, you actually had a chance,
then you wouldn't care about two two and
a half hours on a plane or they wouldn't
care about two and a half hours on a plane.
You know, it's it's
things people got to do. You know what
I'm saying? It's nothing, man.
Well, at least you done an approach.
I feel pissed off. I don't [ __ ] Well, I
don't feel pissed off at all, actually.
I don't know why I said I feel pissed
off. I'm used to it now. So, it doesn't
piss me off because I'm used to the [ __ ]
So, actually, no, I'm not pissed off.
I'm used to it. But to have got two
repliers out of four numbers is pretty
good, to be honest. It's 50%, you know.
So, that's good in London.
See, if you never approach, you wouldn't
even get a conversation. That's how
that's how do you know the thing I was
thinking is this is how [ __ ] up it is,
right? Is you wouldn't even get a
conversation with somebody on Facebook
or Instagram if you message them. You
know how you know how mad that is. Like
if you message these women on on social
media, right? If you message these women
on social media, Grezy, they would never
reply back. And if they reply back, you
could never guarantee they were actually
real. So, you can't even speak to
you can't even get a conversation out of
someone unless you [ __ ] approach. And
by a conversation, I mean via text. I
mean via like text like WhatsApp. That's
that's [ __ ] insane, bro. If you think
about it that way.
I'm thinking of doing a bet on the
National League, you know, the National
Northern League, but
I don't think it's a good idea, bro.
I really don't.
So, you know, at least you can actually
get a conversation with [ __ ] someone.
She was a personal trainer as well,
which ain't bad because she doesn't
drink much, which is good cuz I don't,
you know, that's I don't really drink
much. I just had to go out on Sunday cuz
I would have just went insane if I'd ever.
And I was saying to Ant-Man as well,
like I don't know how you used to go out every week
cuz I'm not going out every week, bro.
Even if I had loads and loads of money,
that's [ __ ] madness. You just don't
enjoy it as much. It's unhealthy.
Um there's just so many pros to like
doing it every two weeks.
And when you go out, you send it
anyways. So, you know, it isn't affordability.
It might be affordability in the sense
of I could use that money for other
things. But still, like even when I was
getting loads of money, I still didn't
go out every week.
I stopped for like sometimes I'd stop
for like a month. It's not good, man. It
ain't good. But I didn't get a hangover.
It must have been that pizza grievy. I'm
telling you, it was that pizza I had.
It was that [ __ ] pizza I had, bro.
I had no hangover. And I was drinking
like white rum and everything. I was
I've not had a hangover. It's got to be
that [ __ ] pizza.
Nope. There is literally no other way.
It's got to be that pizza, bro. It
soaked it all up. I didn't get any hangover.
And the ones that I approached on
Sunday, I generally believe two of them
actually did have a boyfriend because of
the way they worded it like, "Oh, my
partner." And no, I generally believe
that some do, but just most of them are
full of [ __ ] Like the first one I
approached was full of [ __ ] Oh, I have
a boyfriend. I said, "Oh, really?" Where
where you from? She said, "I had a
boyfriend again." People don't [ __ ]
talk like that, bro. People just walk
away. Like, you can tell when someone's
just lying, bro. But two of them, I
think they were actually legit just the
way they were actually wording it.
You just know, bro. Like, it's when
someone's actually genuine and someone's
actually full of [ __ ]
Like, it's it's obvious.
And obviously the one that was sitting
down who I got the number from, right,
she couldn't just stand and walk off.
She might have thought it was rude to do
that. But no, I generally believe they
were seeing someone the way they worded
it. But some of them, they're just full
of [ __ ] You can just tell. But most of
them are full of [ __ ] with like the
expressions on their face and it's just
it's just [ __ ]
So, but some of them
I feel like the ones that actually do,
if they're walking, they'll just walk
away. If you approach someone and
they're actually with someone, they will
just walk away. They won't even say
they've got a boyfriend. They'll just
walk away. Um, that's a sign to say when
they're telling the truth. Um,
and also the ones that um
say they have a [ __ ]
say they have a boyfriend after like a long conversation.
Um, definitely a [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying? So you you can
Yeah, there there's a big You just know, bro. It
Yeah, I will in a minute.
Cuz why is that Finnish one not got a
boyfriend? She's a personal trainer. She
seems like she's pretty much got her
[ __ ] together. So, you know, a lot more
people are single than you actually think.
So, just always remember that, you know,
if they're saying they're seeing someone
and they weren't like that, they're probably
telling the truth, but not the way these
other people talk. They're [ __ ] full of [ __ ]
Yeah. One second.
I'll put a link up now.
So, what do you think of football bet
today on the uh Northern League?
I don't know, man.
I don't know. I don't really want to
lose. I don't like losing.
What do you think, Greavves? I was going
to do like Darlington and [ __ ] I think
they're good to
>> Yeah. Get get Smelly Philly up.
>> Smelly belly. Wait one second. I can let
me redraw. Hold on. God.
Smelly [ __ ] fell. It's a [ __ ] Why
did you run off, fell?
Yo, can you hear me?
>> Yeah, I can hear you.
>> Yeah, I can hear you better now. Yeah, I
was just saying no, I'm I'm not talking
to you. You told me to [ __ ] off
yesterday. You was being a meanie.
>> He was being a meanie. >> Yeah.
>> No, you [ __ ] keep sending me [ __ ] on
[ __ ] these clowns on YouTube that I
don't want to [ __ ] know about.
>> I sent you one person.
>> Yeah, Lord J.
>> It wasn't Lord Jay.
>> It was it. See, I don't even look at him
cuz I was looking at him. Tim Timmy Eldridge.
>> Well, Timmy Eldridge.
>> Yeah, but yeah, because he he was
gambling and he was saying beautifully
done and stuff. He was making a fool of himself.
>> You're only on a five.
>> Yeah. He was like, "Oh, beautifully done."
>> Yeah. He's something Hemy's just
something to laugh at, ain't it? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I'm going to call you mean I'm
going to call you mean I'm going to call
you meanie Monty now.
>> Meanie Monty. That fairy up then.
>> He's not trying to come up. Oh, so why
you spilling box?
>> Anyone that tries to come up, I let them in.
You know what I'm saying, bro? So, yeah,
that's what I'm going to call you now.
I'm going to call you meanie. Meanie Monty.
>> Meanie multi.
>> Yeah. What do you think about that?
>> Standing is it?
>> You like that little name?
>> Good name, is it? Mean big.
You're a [ __ ]
I am dick. I've got I got a dick and three balls.
>> You're a proper [ __ ] man.
>> Why are you such a [ __ ] man?
>> I haven't got a [ __ ] I've got a not
>> No, you got a [ __ ]
>> I've got a not. So, I was called
approaching last night. Did you do any
cold approaching last night?
>> No, I didn't. I done it on Sunday, man.
Yeah. You were just saying that two
girl, two women contacted you.
>> Yeah. Yes. Yesterday. Yeah. Because from
Sunday, is it? >> Nice.
>> But still talking to him about >> Yeah.
>> Obviously, I expected to get I expect to
be blown up at some because you just
expect it in it. But is what it is.
>> They're probably talking to you to be nice.
Yeah, just doesn't it just doesn't
bother me anyways, you know.
>> I'm used to it now, Monty, bro. I'm
[ __ ] I've met you. We've gone on the
piss together, you know. [ __ ] you
know what I mean? Like
>> Yeah. Yeah. Of course. Of course.
>> That was It was good that time, is it? I
liked it, man. I like drinking the rum.
>> You know, yeah, it was all right now. It went
>> I still can't I still can't believe we
done it on a [ __ ] empty stomach. I
still can't believe we done that, bro.
That's crazy, man. Yeah, we did it though.
>> Yeah, probably why we got drunk quicker as well.
>> Yeah. Yeah, probably.
>> So, I always knew me and you was going
to be like friends to the end, isn't it?
>> We're not friends till the end.
>> We are friends to the end.
>> If you get off YouTube, we'll be friends
through the end.
>> Okay, I'll get off YouTube if you get a
tattoo of my name on your finger and
I'll do the same. How
>> about that? [ __ ] off.
I've already got Natalie's name tattooed on me.
>> Yeah. Well, you should you should have mine.
>> No. No. I've got Nat, >> huh?
>> Look, I've named David.
>> Yeah. Look, look. I've only got N's name. Now see
bastard. I know.
>> What? Do you want me to get a P and you
get the chair? Yeah.
No. In fact, you get the P. I get the
chair. That's more like it.
All the P is you when you talk about
when you have picture of my children up
on you all your little nons you're the
biggest N in this community fell no one else you
the one who's being kicked out your
house for being a nunch you prick and um
on your report we're being told you're
being molestering your own children you sick [ __ ]
We're being told you being molestering
your own kids too, fell the molester.
The child of molester
fell the child of molester.
You remind me of Uncle Bessie. You the
child of molester.
This is where your head goes sick fell.
It's called helping two girls out with
the police there and the ambulance crew
and the hotel management there. So do
you people with the sick brain now
who think about [ __ ] like that? Why
don't you come up and talk about it?
So, are you with the nonsing brain
go helping two people out who needed
help from the actual [ __ ] predator
from that hotel?
I'm not being funny, Philly, but you had
my kids up on the wall with your [ __ ]
head on it. Head on it. And then you go
around talking about raping other
people's children and [ __ ] like that.
You're a sick [ __ ]
You know, you don't leave that number
five no more, do you? You're being
kicked out for being a n. You ning bastard.
You can talk about me or all what you
want, but I'm no nons.
You can call me whatever the [ __ ] you
want. You can sit there and call me a
none. Not a n you are.
Anyway, f. Why don't you see your kids
anyway, fell? Why don't you see your
your children, fell?
Where's your children gone? Where's your
children gone? Far far away. Your kids
have got stepparents now. Ellie's not a
parent anymore, peeps. Ellie's not even
a get down. All these five kids have got
step daddies and stepmomies. All of them.
There you go, Fell. I'm ripping into you, lad.
Your kids have gone getting brought up.
My kids are at my mom's house. I get to
see my kids early unlike you. My dog
don't really care about my dog. Well,
obviously I do. But you talking about
diesel don't really affect me. But
where's your house gone, fell? Where's
your [ __ ] Where's all your flies gone?
Where your flies gone? Where's your
flies gone? Where's your flies fell?
You've lost your flies, you [ __ ]
Really, this is the thing. Rice ain't
not allowed near my kids. Rice ain't
allowed nowhere near my children. So,
rice ain't even a stepdad. So, that's
not even going to piss me off. Rice
would I said my videos to my mom about
rice cing cancer on all that lot. Rice
not allowed nowhere near my kids. So
that's going to be impossible for rise
to be even a step to my kids and they
will never be able to see my kids.
But Natalie's a stepmom to mine. Natalie
is going to be a stepmom to mine.
Philly, you know, I'm going to get a one
day I'm going to say, "Nat, will you
marry me?" And I'm going to say, "Yeah."
And me and Natalie are going to get
married. Then we're going to have five.
We're going to have five kids ourself.
Yeah. We're going to have five children
ourselves, me and Natalie. And I'm going
to keep all of them five. I'm gonna keep
the other two I've got already.
Yeah, Ellie's lost it. He's all five. Ellie's gone.
>> Sorry about that, man. I was talking to someone.
>> No, no, no. You're good. You're good.
>> Yeah. So, what we talking about?
>> No, just Ellie. Every time he has kids,
he loses him. >> Oh.
>> Any news of Rice?
>> No. Rice is Yeah, Rice is like house is
it? Yeah, but like anything else? No.
>> No. Just like that. He's crying his eyes
out cuz he's lost his flat like belly.
And there's me peach in a gorgeous
[ __ ] house. There's me in a gorgeous
house. I'm not showing much. Not showing
This This is how you keep nice clean
flat house. This how you keep a nice clean house.
>> Oh, bless you then. Bless you.
Nice clean out.
>> I remember Hey, hey, hey, listen. Um,
Nicolo, remember smashing the bookies up
because they weren't paying out? That
had me dying on the [ __ ] train. Yeah,
I was getting the train somewhere and I
was thinking of it and I was dead cuz
they weren't paying out.
>> Timmy Timmy just embarrasses himself, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Yeah. So does Felly. They both do.
Fell embarrass himself and so does
[ __ ] Right. I'm not being funny on F,
but Fell's got to
um to attach to the PayPal coming
through and all that. That's why he
thinks he can come back and people are
going to start paying him again. That's
why Fell ether because Belly thinks
people are going to jump on this paying
for his view again.
>> I don't think that could happen anymore.
>> So Bell is not going to be getting no
more PayPal links off anyone else pretty
soon in this community either way. So he's PayPal.
>> Why? Why can't I grievy? Why can't I?
>> One second. Monty. Yeah. Why can't I?
I can't. Can't I? Why is that?
One sec. I don't know. You're at
No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No, no, no.
>> So, why is Nelly not coming up on the channel?
>> Greasy, are you sure about that? Why
these people said that I can't get
attached anymore, Grezy? Um, money, cuz
I've already found my mama.
>> Yeah, I know. I I knew some guy before.
Basically, he's a family um
family uh one second. Like, he's a he's
like one of like my cousin's dad, like
in the family, and like I've known the
guy for like years and [ __ ] years,
years and years. Like he took me to WWE
and that and um he went to the bookies
and he was like trying to scam the
machines like years ago with like one of
the workers. They had like a thing going
on in there and they they refused to pay
him out and he just smashed the whole shop up
kicked out of Rotter. Sorry.
>> Yeah. Like that's the funny thing is is
that he smashed it because they refused
to pay out, not because like he lost
money. It's the whole like they refused
to pay him like the money because he was
obviously like cheating with a worker
and he just smashed the whole shop up.
Police was called police was called. >> Yeah.
>> He's here. >> Yeah.
>> Have I ever been kicked out of Roscale? >> Yeah.
>> Why you saying that for P? Why you
saying your fault?
>> Yeah. You question what you want.
>> How about [ __ ] being kicked out of
Rodale or PJ? You [ __ ] clown. >> That's
you as you ask why. So why ask me a
question when I when I [ __ ] this
community, you [ __ ] prick and you know that.
>> Yeah, but you Yeah, but you know why?
>> I again, have I been kicked out of Roxdale?
>> Well, you know you haven't. So why why ask then?
>> Well, yeah, because I wanted you to tell
felon that I haven't. Yeah, but you know
you haven't and they know you haven't.
So why why ask me then?
>> No, no, you're good. You're good. Go on.
Carry on. Sorry. Go on.
>> Yeah. So, yeah. It just made me laugh, Nicolola. Yeah.
>> No, I'm not doing any I'm I'm good, man.
You can do it, though.
>> Idiot, man.
>> How's your morning, >> huh?
>> How's your morning been?
>> Nice, man. Just having a nice cup of
[ __ ] a nice cup of tea.
>> And another thing, you can't even use
that PlayStation [ __ ] against me when I
used to take sides because on here you
kind of done the same thing for a while. >> Yeah,
>> cuz look at that [ __ ] Tradal thing,
bro. You snaked me and then they went
against you. So you you know, we're
we're kind of even now anyways. So
>> yeah, we are even. We are even.
>> So you used to like when you thought the
heat was off you, you used to like lick
ass and [ __ ] man.
>> No, I knew the heat weren't off me. I
knew what they would deal with. I just
wanted to see what this discord [ __ ]
was about and only what they do is put
piss up pictures of kids play talk about
people on Discord.
>> Oh, do you remember what Barquest used to do?
>> Dildos off his ass.
>> Yeah, but he used to lick ass when like
bomb and Pat used to come in the
hangouts and me and you was arguing. Remember
>> is a repeating prick. Is that bar
fantasy story? It is, isn't it? >> No.
>> So fantasy story. Why do they sound the
same? Why does it sound like they both got [ __ ]
>> Cuz they're both Irish.
>> No, no, no. When they say they sound the
same, Irish, all Irish sound different
in the different tone, but them two
sound exactly dead on the same.
>> Do they?
>> Yeah, cuz everyone I get confused with
him on [ __ ] Vquest. >> Oh,
bless you then. Bless you.
What are you doing today?
>> I don't know. I don't know. I was going
to go to Phelly's house today and kick
[ __ ] out of Philly today, but he don't
live there no more, so that's impossible.
>> If they don't pay out, Michael, I'm
going to smash the shop up and they
don't pay out. What would you do if if
some if if the betting shop owed you
money and they weren't paying out, Monty?
>> You've got to pay out. You win. You win
and they've got a payout. They were
saying they didn't. You'd smash the shop
up in it. Yeah.
>> No, you just tell them you wrap it all
and record anyway. So you record it all.
>> They refuse to pay out. >> Yeah.
>> It's all recorded. If it's all recorded,
they can't refuse the money cuz it's
there on evidence. You've won
>> your skin for two weeks.
>> I'm not skin for two weeks, you [ __ ]
Why do you all think I'm skint?
>> Yeah. Why do these people Why do these
Why do these people call us skint every day?
>> Cuz they [ __ ] skint the PJ the
repeaters. That's only what they do.
Just you every day with them. >> Yeah.
>> [ __ ] hell. It's getting raing that
[ __ ] now to be honest with you.
>> Not even [ __ ]
>> It is. It's [ __ ] boring to [ __ ]
send the pedo [ __ ] All
>> he was entertaining me was [ __ ] fell
a little n
In fact, he's not even [ __ ]
entertaining. He's just a little sick on
new sit thinking he's well [ __ ] big on YouTube
today or not.
>> I want to do like a northern league like
Darlington Spennymore. I don't know. I used to
>> go on a night out in Rodale. >> What?
>> You want to go on a night out in Rodale, do you? No.
>> Why? I'd come rot. Me, you, and my mate
and that. We'll go [ __ ] Well, my mate
I've never been to Manchester. I'm
scared of Manchester. I've never been.
>> Oh, no. No. Saying that, my mate is
still after you. So, no. [ __ ] that.
>> No, he might have forgot me.
>> No, no, he hasn't forgot you. He He's
still after you. So, no. You out of that.
>> Oh, did you see videos of me in Manchester before?
Yeah, I've seen your videos in Manchester.
>> Did you think they were Do you like them?
>> No, they gay. >> Huh?
>> Yeah, a bit gay. >> Why?
>> Just the gay.
>> How they care? You silly. You silly goose.
You look like the Undertaker.
>> Do I?
>> Yo, fell. The funny thing is is that I'm
going back to Rodale. Um,
>> who who was who was your favorite
wrestler, Nicolo, back in the day?
>> I got two.
>> I would say mine was Yeah, I liked so
many of them. I'm talking back in the
day though. I'd say it has to be
Undertaker, man. It's got to be I think
back when I was a kid and like now like
the old ones. I was looking at it the
other day. All they're all [ __ ] new
wrestlers. The only ones that I know of
is that [ __ ] Seth [ __ ] Rogan or
whatever cuz or whatever he's cuz he's uh
cuz you hear about him. That's how I
know of him. But all they're all [ __ ]
different now. [ __ ] know any of them,
bro. Yeah, I liked him as well.
But that's like WWF. That's even that's
that's before our day, bro. But yeah,
him and I'd say Undertaker. It's got to
be in it.
Monty reminds me of the Undertaker a little bit.
>> Undert Oh, I remember little I remember
Little Ray Ray. Um
Greavves. Yeah, I remember little Ray
Ray. He was very springy, wasn't he? >> Yeah.
>> Who's being kicked out of Swathan? Yeah.
>> I don't know.
John John Cena was good, but his
finisher was [ __ ] Like his finisher was
just bad, bro. That's the only thing.
Like what what is that finisher? Yeah.
Lifting somebody up and just throwing
them on their back. That's a That's a
That's a [ __ ] finisher. The best
finisher. Yeah. I like the [ __ ] um
uh I like the pedigree
and the [ __ ] Stone Cold Park, the the Tombstone.
I think they were good. They were good.
Do you know what? Do you know what mine is? >> What?
>> It's called the Sleeper PJ.
That's the best one. The move I like to
do, the sleeper move.
>> Yeah, true.
>> He grabs one by the throat.
>> It will never be the way it was like it
was in 2009. Nicolo 2009, 2010 was its peak.
The only one that's still there now is
that Sheamus, but she's quite popular as
well. But yeah, but then it was at its peak then.
Now probably kids are not into it like
when we were kids, you understand? Yeah,
but the rock still goes back and forth there still.
>> No, he Yeah, but he doesn't wrestle.
He's too old.
>> He's not too old.
>> He is, bro. He don't [ __ ] wrestle.
>> He has wrestled.
>> Yeah, years ago.
>> What about he still wrestles, don't he?
>> Yeah, and he's grave. He's dead.
>> Yeah, I know he's dead.
>> He wrestles in his grave. Um, but yeah.
>> Who's being kicked out of Swatham?
Number five for Swatham. Who's being
kicked out of Swatham?
>> Nice, isn't it?
>> No. Belly.
Belly's being kicked out of Swatham.
Belly's not allowed.
>> That was so cute when That was so cute
when I went to Birmingham and saw you,
Monty. And it I won my little football
bet and I thought, "Oh, let me go and see Monty."
>> Yeah. Yeah. We're good. Now, we should have gone.
>> I thought you I thought you I thought
you was going to give me I thought you
was going to give me a hide in.
>> You did? Yeah.
>> Yeah. I thought No. Do you know what I
thought you was going to do? Yeah. Like
you know when we was walking back to the
train station like when I was going to
go back when I was going back home. I
thought you was going to hit me.
>> Ellie, I'm not you who's scared of rice.
I'm scared of myself. You're the one who
got paid to come to me house and ran off. Yeah.
>> Yeah. But Yeah. But then Monty, that
would be silly if you done that, in it,
because then you'd lose a good friend
that come and helped you, in it. So,
it'd be silly in it to do that.
>> What? Me and you?
>> Yeah, we're friends.
>> Anyways, cuz you apologize for what you
said about my children and what you done.
>> Yeah, but bro, that would Yeah, but that
wouldn't be good enough for most people.
Are you mad?
>> No, obviously not. But you apologize.
>> You know that. Do you remember when that
Fraser tried to set me up and and I I
never went back and forth with him?
Nowhere near as I did you, bro.
>> No, I'm not a setup. I tell you if I'm
going to bash you or not.
>> The thing the thing is, M, you need to
be like, you know, before you meet
someone, obviously I know you're not
scared. But I'm saying what if you have
history with someone, it doesn't matter
what you've like if you said sorry or
whatever, the history is still there. Do
you understand? So like,
>> you know, they a lot of people will try
[ __ ] you know what I mean?
>> Of course, course. Of course. And look
at Philly tried to co [ __ ] But have you
seen the state of you fell? You're a
crap lad. You're a dirty stinking [ __ ]
You're a woman abuser. You rape cla you
sick [ __ ] Yeah. You got no message for
Petering. Yeah. Saying you were going to
rape someone's kids and that you sick
[ __ ] Yeah. You're a [ __ ] nons lad.
You sit there and say that I've been
kicked out of Roxdale. Prove that I've
been kicked out of Roxdale. Google my
name, Rosdale. Google me, fella. You
[ __ ] clown. You're the pranc on
YouTube with [ __ ] flies flying out
your fridge, you [ __ ] You're the
one with stings all over your toilet
with a broken seat. You [ __ ] crampy
>> That's yucky.
>> It is. He's a [ __ ] lad. He's a [ __ ]
He's a stinking dirty ramp. And he's
supposed to be a Ker for collect no carer.
He can't even care for his [ __ ] self.
>> Oh [ __ ]
>> He's stinking. He's [ __ ] stinking.
You smell wor and cosmic kit is flat, you [ __ ]
>> No. No. He does. He does. You walk into
that house. Yeah.
It won't smell of cat [ __ ] Yeah. That's
the excuse for cosmic care. belly stakes
of human [ __ ]
>> That's the difference.
>> I remember that. Nicolo, you're not my
mama. Yuck. Yuck.
You're not my mama.
>> It's not a fake fell. It's a real fell
>> because he's already found his mama. M
>> who's who's my mama? Um Monty.
>> Yo mom.
>> It's called what?
>> Oh Dorine.
>> God bless.
>> Bless you then. Monty
>> and another thing fell. But why doesn't
Lord J come to me when he offer room
fives and all that? Why don't Lord J
come to me? Why don't [ __ ] rice come
to me? Why haven't you even come to me, Fell?
That's the thing. I've offered Lord J
out times to meet me. Bird times. The
same as you, Fell. Bird times. Same as
right. Bird times.
>> Do you want my opinion, Monty?
>> AJ, do you reckon I'm soft?
>> No, but do you want my opinion on it all?
>> Well, go on. They're all [ __ ]
I used to say that to Conrad all the
time, you know. He said, "Oh, he he knew
what was coming." I said, "Do you want
my opinion, Conrad?" He said, "Oh, not
here. Here here we go again. Here we go
again." He used to say, "Well, good old Conrad."
>> So, where you living now, Fell? Anyways,
what what's your address now then? So, I
can come to you now, Phy. We always
>> know I don't really like No, no. Do you
know the thing is Greasy with One
second, Monty. Yeah. You know, the thing
is with with like Burger King and stuff,
it the the the beef doesn't taste it
doesn't taste real. If I'm going to have
a burger, I'm going to get homemade
mints and make a homemade burger, bro.
Because [ __ ] it's it just doesn't
taste like proper beef. Do you
understand what I mean, Monty? So, what
you're going to do is get some [ __ ]
minced meat and make your own.
>> You get some You get minced meat. You
You get some minced meat,
onions. You can get peppers.
>> Yeah. You get You get You You You You
basically get the mints, right? You
marinade it in like onions and [ __ ] You
marinade it, then you get the burger press
>> and then you press it into a burger
shape and then you make you just make a perfect
>> You don't need to do that. You can just
use your rind, push it down, and mix it
all up either way. So, that don't really
matter anyway. But I've got I've got an
actual burger press like a special
one makes actual >> Yeah.
So that's what I'm saying, bro. Like
because I Yeah.
>> Yeah. I know. Benny doesn't know how to
make all my burgers. You can't even
afford a [ __ ] mince, mate. Can't even
afford afford a packet of eggs.
I got a call, man. [ __ ] Yeah. Can you
hear me? Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I can hear you.
>> You can hear me?
>> Yes, I can hear you.
>> You're on flight again. I need to up my thing.
>> You don't need to do nothing. Just turn one sec.
>> I just turn my mic up.
EJ, there you go, lad. You can hear me
probably better now.
>> Yes, I can hear you.
>> Why have you gone? Why are you quiet,
man? It's my phone's [ __ ] But yeah, I
was basically saying, well, to be
honest, Grezy, Burger King's not the
worst, but you can go you can go to some
burger places like in chicken shops and
the burger just tastes like it's been
frozen. It's horrible, man.
>> Have you been to Have you been to Popeye's? Huh?
>> Never. I know what it is, but I've never been there.
>> Yeah, it's pretty nice, you know.
>> Is it?
>> Yeah, it's pretty nice. Pretty nice.
>> When When are we going to meet up again
and have an omelette like we did last time, Monty?
>> I don't know. PJ,
>> it was quite cute, wasn't it?
>> It were It were like a date, wasn't it? >> Yeah.
It were like my first ever [ __ ] boyfriend date.
>> Yeah. Let's
>> never again.
>> Yeah, we are going to do it again.
>> Yeah, but I'm not called approaching. No
one for your peas. Yeah, you did actually.
>> That's the thing with But Burger King is
not the worst. Burger King. Burger King.
Yeah, but there's even worse places than
Burger King. Like I went to um a chicken
shop up the road last week and had like
a burger with two rings cuz it was a
meal and it just tasted plastic.
It's horrible, bro. Like even frozen
burgers are horrible. It's just
disgusting. Horrible, mate.
>> Like Scottish beef, you know, you need to
>> be honest with you. Yeah. If you're
going to order Yeah. Off if you're going
to order it. Yeah. Like just say off a
takeaway order and that Yeah. It's not
going to be 100% fresh.
If you order it, if you go into the shop
and then away, it's going to be
>> Five Guys Burger is No, the best burger.
No, the best burgers, right, is Gourmet
Burger Kitchen. You're saying Five Guys
is good because you've never had Gourmet
Burger Kitchen, but Gourmet Burger
Kitchen is actually the best. B Gourmet
Burger Kitchen is is [ __ ] out of this world, man.
>> Dunky Chicken's nice, Pete. Yeah, chunky chicken.
>> GBK. I don't know if you have one near
you, but Oh, it's banging, mate.
And Job does the best. Job does the best
fried chicken. Job is like KFC, right?
It's like a big brand. Bit like Slim
Chickens, but um it's like KFC, but no
grease. Job is nice. It's always packed
as well. Yeah. Sorry, Monty.
Dunky Dunky Chicken's nice. Have you
ever been to Chunky Chicken? >> No.
>> Yeah, Dunky Chicken's blood.
>> I've been to Chucky Chicken.
>> What do you think of that? Stinky Chicken.
>> Yeah, I went to Chuck I've been to Chucky Chicken.
>> Never been.
>> Yeah, it's quite nice.
>> Chuck for a [ __ ] parcel. Me, >> huh?
>> I'm waiting for a [ __ ] parcel to come.
>> Oh, bless you then. If if you're waiting
for a little parcel,
>> I've got a dildo coming. >> Really?
>> Yeah. Scrap on.
So when I was approaching women when I
was with you, what was what were they
saying? Do you remember what they were
saying to me? Some of them,
>> some of them were talking to you. >> Yeah.
>> Walked away. >> Huh?
>> And the others just he blanked you and walked away.
>> Yeah. But did anyone say they had a boyfriend?
>> No, not really. Only only two.
>> Yeah. I done the one with her [ __ ] um
her her mom and dad. I was a crazy [ __ ] isn't it?
>> That was the second one, was it?
>> Yeah, I was a crazy bastard. No.
>> Yeah. I don't have even done that. Then
you done it again with someone with a
mom, but you got her number.
>> No, I never with a mom. Who?
>> When we [ __ ] was in that pub and she was outside.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Next to the girl when you Yeah. She was
next to the dad and the and the mom. >> Yeah.
>> You're going to laugh at this. Yeah. I
You did You know this just this just
this just this just finish one that I
approached the other day. Yeah. I said,
"Oh, like I know you're with your mom
and that and you know, whatever." And it
turned out to be your sister. It was so
awkward. I wanted to ground I wanted to
the ground to swallow me up, bro. I
swear to God. I was like, "Oh no, what
have I said?" But they were fine about
it and I got the number and we're having
chats and stuff. It's quite it's quite interesting,
you know. Yeah, it's pretty funny like that, >> huh?
>> It's pretty funny that calling
>> [ __ ] a It's [ __ ] embarrassing.
>> Is it [ __ ] It was a sister. >> [ __ ]
>> You would have died of embarrassment, isn't it?
>> Embarrassment of what?
>> I done one when I was [ __ ] sober as
well when I first met you. I done one
outside sober before we even started drinking. Amen.
>> My [ __ ] my I was just thinking of
that all night. Me.
>> Yeah, but Nicolo, you never you never
know until you try. So, it doesn't
matter if they're with their parents or
not. You you know you you only live
once, don't you, Monty?
>> You live once. Of course you do. Of
course you do. You might as well live
your life when you can if you don't. And
then you're sitting on YouTube. You're
wasting your lives away. [ __ ] off.
>> Yeah, these people waste their lives
away in it.
>> Not most of them. Yeah, most of them do.
But some of them are not on.
>> Well, on they got a life.
>> Yeah. Well, true. Yeah.
You've got a life in it.
>> Obviously, I don't go live no more. You
only go live on people's panels now.
>> Well, bless you then.
>> That's cute, isn't it?
>> What does what's Nick said? >> Um,
no. That's too awkward for me. Nothing's
awkward for me. I've done it on a train.
I've done him I've done him everywhere. These approaches.
I don't give a [ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ] monkeys.
>> I've had a bl I've had a I've had a blow
job on a bus. Back of the bus.
>> No, you haven't.
>> Of course I have. I've had a bl on the
back of a bus. Public bus.
>> Who gave you a [ __ ]
one of me ex back in Manchester.
>> Well, bless you then.
Bless you then if you got a little [ __ ]
>> Oh, that's cute. Yes.
>> We had a wanking McDonald's toilet.
>> Oh, bless.
>> That's so cute. Monty. >> Yeah.
>> Really cute, Monty. We had sex at the
cinema, but we didn't have no condom, so
I just used a Chris packet. >> Bless you.
>> Yes, you
>> g you. >> Why?
>> Yeah. I like the way you say it.
>> But it is cute though, is it?
>> No, not really. No. >> Why?
>> You've got more body than them. You're
better looking than them. And you've got
a better life than them and it kills
them. Ronald McDonald,
>> who's that?
>> It's you.
>> No, me aar.
>> Yeah, it's you.
>> Is it? [ __ ] It's Timmy El's uncle Lester.
>> I think you and Timmy just need to make
up and just go for a beer.
>> No be with a [ __ ] weird one like him.
Are you mad, man? He burn my reputation right down.
>> You nonslegs and Timmy.
>> [ __ ] you. Why don't you go away with
nonsense and I go out with Timmy?
>> I end up [ __ ] smashing the cut in.
>> Yeah, right. You don't kissing him.
>> No, that's you.
>> I don't know. You know,
>> I think you, him, and Timmy will have a freeze them. >> No,
>> I think I think you'll be the one to
take their virginity.
>> What? The ass virginity. Yeah. Their
dicks are too I think you they would
lose their virginity. Yeah. Yeah.
They're still virgins, aren't they?
>> That's what I'm saying. Yeah. So, you'll
be the one that like would be the one to
have them lose their virginity, in it.
>> Well, Jimmy's already been born by a gay
man. So, Timmy's not a virgin, is he?
>> Yeah, but nons are still a virgin.
>> Yeah. Nons will always be a virgin. He's
into kids. He is. >> M.
Yeah. Uh, you would be friends. You'd be
friends if you I would literally smash
his [ __ ] face in if I ever see that
[ __ ] And that is a promise, bro. That
is an actual promise.
>> You did kill him.
>> No, I don't forget I met him through you.
>> You didn't meet him through me. It was
the community you met him through.
>> Yeah, through your community.
>> Yeah, maybe through my community on PlayStation.
>> And I met Jack the Ripper from you as well.
Jack, he's just a sick [ __ ] Either way, he is.
>> Yeah, I met him through you.
>> He's a [ __ ] mental [ __ ] [ __ ] That bastard. How do
>> you even come across all of these people?
>> You play games, don't you? You just add
people and you come across party chats
with them and then they start.
>> I used to play the wrestling games, but
obviously most of the people are
American, isn't it? So,
>> yeah, there was a lot there's a lot
American on PlayStation. You know,
>> I don't play PlayStation anymore. PD,
I've quit quit PlayStation now.
>> I just play Franklin.
>> You like Franklin, is it?
>> Franklin? No, not really. I don't I
don't play GTA anymore. PJ, I don't play
games anymore. What's the point? I get
stalked on them, so there's no point.
If I do go on, I just make a new on them. How? >> What?
>> Stalked on them. How? How do you get
stalked on them?
>> Oh, you think about it.
>> Yeah, that was Jack the Ripper. The one
that I met in [ __ ] um the one that I
met in Birmingham. Yeah, that was the
one I met him through Monty.
>> No, you didn't meet him through me.
[ __ ] I've known Chat the Ripper for
years off YouTube,
but I've I've never even I won't even
have the bollocks to meet him.
>> Yeah, he was really weird, man. He was
he he was putting an American accent on
the whole time, and he always wanted to
be on the phone with me constantly. And
if I wanted to and if I didn't want to
be on the phone, he would literally like
he would literally um start swearing at
me and [ __ ] He was obsessed with me, Monty.
>> Yeah, he's gay.
[ __ ] weird, bro.
>> What is F saying PG?
>> What the [ __ ] Hold on. He said that
you're a victim.
Or did the victim are all the kids you
touch? Any victims?
That said, multi.
Yeah, I reckon
>> that's why no draw. What do you think?
>> Why do you always bring up kids, Phyll?
I'm only doing it because you always
talk about him. So, kitty kitty kid.
It's only YouTube, is it fair? I don't
bring up the kids like you bring them
up. What you want to do and that you know
what was you saying you wanted to do to
your next door neighbor's kids? Fair >> not saying that. >> Yeah. >> What?
>> He fell out with Virgin Boy, so he met
up with you. Yeah. You remember the
story then, don't you, Nicolo? Nicolo
knows too much, you know. Just this account Nicolo.
>> What? Okay. So,
so he fell out with you then and he was
m with Shy Long Legs. No, he met [ __ ]
Virgin boy first and if [ __ ] >> um
um then Yeah, basically.
>> Wow. You mean [ __ ] way? Do you do man?
>> Who you like then?
>> I [ __ ] like him. I've never liked John.
Never remember back in the day when he
used to [ __ ] switch his camera on on
PlayStation and he have pictures on his
wall of Elf Presley and all that lot. >> Yeah.
>> [ __ ] weird man. It's a weird one. Why
the [ __ ] would you have pictures?
Obviously. Yeah. He's a fan of Elvis.
Yeah. But why would you go all that way
to have about 50 odd pictures or
>> Elvis? Elvis also liked kids as well.
>> Yeah, I know. I know. He sung a song
saying, "Hey, something about this girl
dancing, saying that she dances good and
all that. Come here to her and all that."
>> Virgin boy got owned so bad by me he had
to go to the police. What a loser, ain't it?
>> These people get on daily. Delegates.
>> Imagine being so much of a loser you
have to go to the police over getting
owned on YouTube. That's madness, bro.
That's crazy, Monty. It is crazy
>> cuz you got owned so badly. [ __ ] virgin.
Would you live in F's house if the
council offered you Fell's house now PJ
to live in cuz he don't live no more.
>> Number five swap him. Would you live in it? >> No.
>> No. Fell is lifting it.
>> No. I wouldn't even step foot in that
house to be honest with you.
>> I really like you Monty.
But I don't I really want you, but I
don't think you want me.
>> I'm not gay. Peace. Yeah,
>> that's what a woman said to me before. I
really want you, but I don't think you want me.
>> Yeah. So, why didn't you say, "Yeah, I
do want you."
>> I did. I got a [ __ ] in the alleyway.
>> Okay. So, why you not still with her?
There's Bellish toilet there.
>> Why Why am I not still with her? Uh,
maybe because she lived in America and
she went back cuz she was only visiting here.
Look, look, look at Fell's toilet there.
That's Felly's toilet.
>> It looks like you.
>> Fell's toilet cleaning.
>> It looks like
[ __ ] all this. I He can't even afford soap.
>> I really want you, but I don't think you want me.
>> Gave me a lovely [ __ ] in the
alleyway. I like [ __ ] but you
>> would you finger blast CL EJ?
>> No, but I'd think of last year.
>> I wouldn't, man. You have stinky finger.
>> Well, I'd think of last year.
>> No. Would you go out with Claire? He
needs a better man than what Fed is.
>> No, I'd go out with you though.
>> Am I all right?
>> I'd go out with you. You're better.
>> Mr. B, is it the real fell?
>> Yeah, I'm going to be that Northern
League bet today, Nicolo. You reckon
it's going to come in?
Stick 80 on it in it.
>> See, how do you think I was able to
spend 250 and then spend 80 and No, no,
no, no, no. Because the thing is,
Nicolo, I'm not skinn like these people.
These people self-reflect constantly.
That's why I just laugh at them. I just
leave them to it when they say, "Show
money. Show money." I don't need to show
any of these mongos. Nothing. You know
what I mean, Monty?
>> No, you don't. All what you need to
realize is that you're not the skinniest
person in in this community.
They're the ones they're the ones that are skin.
>> Yeah. Belly. Philly is I say Phy is the
first skin taste in this community.
Yeah, but non legs is skin as well. >> Yeah,
>> leg is non legs is skin.
Imagine that showing a 800 holiday and
saying that I can't afford it, bro. I
was doing that [ __ ] when I was 23.
>> £800. You know them virgin cheap cheap
deal holidays that he's going on. I'd
done all that when I was 23.
>> Yeah, £800 ain't even a lot of money.
>> I can afford that.
>> I was doing that when I was 23. I went
Amsterdam. I went Belgium. I don't know.
When I was 23, bro. When I when I was
traveling [ __ ] the Virgin's 31 and
he's doing it now.
>> Yeah. I can pay for I can do like twice
offer for me and Natalie if I
>> He'd be [ __ ] He'd be [ __ ] Nicolo,
he'd absolutely be [ __ ]
>> He'd starve for a week. Literally, bro.
>> It's a boy.
Why don't you go out with him, PJ?
>> Nah, he's your boyfriend.
>> Why you Nicholas seem you're getting on
like house on fire in here.
>> Nah, he's your boyfriend, bro.
>> I don't know. You know,
>> he's your boyfriend, mate.
>> I don't know. You know, PG, I think you
and Nicola will get on fire. >> No.
>> Are you sure?
>> Sure. Well, tell me then you're turning him down.
>> Tell him, man. Tell him.
>> You tell him.
>> I'm turning you down, bro. I'm sorry.
I'm not interested.
>> Cold approaching is in my DNA, isn't it,
Nicolo? It's in my DNA.
>> Cold approach is in your DNA.
>> What do you think of that?
>> I don't need a cold approach, mate. I
get cold approached on PD. That's the difference.
>> I get called a croch.
>> How have I not How have I not done it?
Yeah, Nicolo. For [ __ ] 3 weeks and
then when I do it again, I can do it
like perfectly like not nervous or
anything. It's because it's in my DNA.
You remember that [ __ ] woman in the
pub at the at the finger stroking that
man's bald head?
>> Yeah. You liked it, isn't it?
>> This is that is stroking my head. >> Yep.
>> Why did he just stroke my head? That's [ __ ] up.
>> I don't know. But you liked it, isn't it?
>> I didn't like it. He said, "Are you
going to stroke my head?" And he said no.
>> It was funny, isn't it? Did no to PJ
just walk in his head.
>> Yeah, but you liked it in it.
>> No, I didn't like it.
>> Yeah, you did.
>> I had to take my cap off and some woman
[ __ ] come over and start stroking
some man's bald head.
>> Virgin Yeah, virgin boy would be [ __ ]
for a week. stuck in my head.
>> If he lost, Virgin Boy would be [ __ ]
for a week.
>> Barely want
needs to come up on the panel, don't he?
He's getting owned by everyone in this chat.
>> Yeah, but you like it.
>> How do you like it a lot? >> Yeah.
>> Depend on when it's not you.
>> So So how much money do you have right
now, Monty? About a grand, >> huh?
>> A grand? >> Really?
>> That's in the bank.
>> Oh, bless you.
>> Yeah, you always keep my money in my bank.
>> Bless you then. If you got a grand
out a we good do, huh?
>> I'm taking Natalie out for a good do. God bless.
Do you know what a we good do is PJ?
>> No. What is it?
>> Something to read or we're going up some
we good do.
>> God bless.
>> No, I can't be bothered doing the bet
today, Nicolo. Man, I don't really want
to lose [ __ ] 80 to 100 pound. [ __ ] that.
>> I'm sure like you and Nicola are dating
behind the scenes. PG. All right,
>> that's our little secret.
>> Is it? I'd rather spend £100 on a night
out, bro. You know what I mean?
I'm going to jump off anyway, PJ. Yeah.
>> Yeah, man.
>> I'm going to go and [ __ ] have a good old tug.
>> See you in your dreams.
>> You sick [ __ ] I've been [ __ ] killing
you in my dreams. >> Why?
>> [ __ ] that, man.
You're not welcome in my dreams. Why?
Cuz it's just me and Natalie in my dreams. on that. >> Sure.
>> See you later. Yeah.
>> See you later, K.
See you later. It's me.
But then if I win the football better be quite good.
I'm not sure.
I don't really want to be losing that
kind of money.
You see what I mean?
Yeah. Virgin boy skin. That's why virgin
boy skint skin flint.
He is actually skint. That's the thing.
What's the day today? Tuesday. Yeah. Um,
might just stick a £100 on it.
I can't lie, bro.
Which will leave me with about
I'll just stick 90 quid on it. [ __ ] it.
Could do with a walk as well to be fair.
Look, one of the teams is slow. Should I
bet on slow
grind a month, boy? Yeah.
Yeah, that's southern leagues. Yeah, I might do. [Music]
I might do slow and horns. Slow and ship
again and horns versus ding.
Bro, what part have I'm done for two
weeks? Do you not understand?
Do you not understand English?
I literally said I'm done for two weeks.
I don't care. I went out yesterday on
Sunday cuz I was bored.
I am done for two weeks and know I'm not
going to see them where I live now.
though. And even if I did, I still
wouldn't do it. Oh my [ __ ] god, man.
You don't I don't think you understand
English, do you?
English must not be your first language.
No, I can't be bothered to I'm not going
lio. [ __ ] that. I can't be asked. I'd
rather spend it on a night out. 80
pound. I think that's I think that's the
right idea, would it, Grezy?
Yeah, I think that's the right idea, man. Yeah.
[ __ ] pointless, isn't it?
What do you think, Grezy?
Why don't you tell us what you think?
Could do it. Could try. But um
what do you think, Nicolola? Really? Um,
I'm thinking whether to or not.
I was I was going to do like the northern leagues.
What do you think, Grezy?
Do you think just not do it? Do it.
Don't do it. What do you think?
What do you think? Should I walk to the
shop and do a football bet?
Nah, can't be lost. [ __ ] it. I'll go for
a walk, but I'm not betting.
What? And what? What should I stick? 90 on it.
And what should I stick 90 quid on it?
I was thinking of sticking 90 pound on it.
I'm just going to have a pizza in the
freezer. I've got I've got a pizza in
the freezer. I'm probably just going to have
I got a freezer. I got pizza in the
freezer. I'm probably going to have
might as well just stick 100 pound on
the football in it.
At least I would have save even if it
loses at least I would have saved £300
this month which is pretty good
considering how I used to [ __ ] be in it.
I'm going to walk to the shop and do
this bet anyway, J. All right.