Yeah, man.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. Yeah, man. One second.
Yeah, money. I just saw that from on somebody's channel.
It was the first time of me seeing it,
so I thought,
yeah, was [ __ ]
Yeah, man. Why not send it to you in it?
I'm more addicted than you. No way. You
can't even take a day off of YouTube.
I'm more addicted than you. [ __ ] no. You
can't even take one day off of YouTube.
I've spent weeks and weeks and weeks off
of YouTube before. I'm like, I'm more
addicted than you. Why am I [ __ ] more
addicted than you?
>> I'm getting rather pissed off with you, PJ. >> Why?
>> You know why? Sending me [ __ ] like that
with Natalie and all that. Look, I'm
pissed off at you now. PJ, man.
Sending me [ __ ] out.
>> I told you.
>> Grezy, you're on my live again.
>> You can't talk about anyone.
>> You can't talk about anyone cuz you're
on my live again. Who me?
>> No, the people texting.
>> I'm just saying one second. One second.
One second as well, M. Why are you
saying I'm I'm Why are you saying I'm more
>> Why are you saying I'm more addicted
than you when you can't even take a day
off of YouTube? You didn't answer my
question. The person in the comments, I
just asked you a question. You didn't answer me.
I want to know why why you sent me that
why you sent me that picture.
>> Oh boy. Why?
>> It wasn't a picture. It was a video.
>> Yeah, the video of someone's channel
with with Natish [ __ ] muff on there.
>> It wasn't a moth.
>> It was a moth. A picture of a muff on his avatar.
Does not know what a muff look like. Obviously not. No,
>> sent me a link to his channel.
>> Yeah, I sent you the the person on
YouTube's link and on his appetite. He's
got this funny. Yeah, on his channel.
>> I could go see that. I know.
>> Why did you send me [ __ ] like that?
>> I just wanted you to see the shadow in
it. What the [ __ ] Why is it a big deal?
I don't get it. What the [ __ ]
>> It's a big deal. It is a big deal
because I did not know Natalie done
that. Yeah. And not knew about that
[ __ ] I know about Natalie flashing
herself and all that love shaking the
tits around, but Natalie showing them a
muff line. I didn't know that and that
just pissed me off. PJ,
>> I didn't even know that in him
>> and it's not like they just turn around
and just say she didn't even know she's
done that. So Le had to get her pissed
for her to do that.
>> Get [ __ ] hell. That's just
>> You know what I'm saying? >> Yeah.
>> He's basically pulling what they
shouldn't even have on the phone. He got
a woman pissed just for a woman to show
him off online.
>> Madness porn.
>> This is This funny. Nothing's funny.
This is how weird all you are in this
community. I'm not I'm not I'm angry at
PJ cuz PJ send it to me, but I'm not
falling out with PJ offer it. What's the point?
In a way, PJ probably sent me a lot of
my back in a way, but it has pissed me
the [ __ ] off.
Why are you more angry at PJ Why are you
Why are you more mad at PJ for sing a
picture rather than mad at Nat for being a disgusting
>> I am mad at I am mad at that but not
apologized not told me why she done it
but N was already pissed didn't know
she' done that does not shown the
picture he didn't know she's shown her p online
>> I can't remember doing that for a star [ __ ] hell
You know what I mean? So they got porn
on their phone what they had to get a
woman pissed. So that's basically rape
porn in some kind of way.
>> What? How rape?
>> How it some form of that?
>> What rape?
>> To get a woman pissed out of her face
just to show [ __ ] and take pictures of
it and put it up over YouTube.
>> Okay. What the [ __ ]
I never seen a [ __ ] funny.
>> Yeah, it's madness, isn't it?
>> It's madness. All these are [ __ ]
weirdos in this community. They [ __ ]
weirdos put picture of women's fatties
all over YouTube and [ __ ] like that.
That tells me completely that leaves
people. He had a nice Tommy Tank. Uh, no
I didn't. Why are you using weirdo words
like that? Why is that what you call a
wank? A Tommy tank? You people are
[ __ ] weirdos. That what you call
>> what I mean. You only can wank over it.
I'm getting a real thing.
>> I never wanked over it.
>> Most of these probably have wanks over.
>> I [ __ ] never
Is that what you call Is that what you
call a wank? A Tommy Tank. What a
weirdo. That sounds so pedoish. That does.
>> They are pedos. PJ. This is why they
call people pedos. I don't give a [ __ ]
if you had a teen on my phone. Yeah. Be
called this peeps. Yeah. I don't give a
[ __ ] about what I had on my phone. Never
went on it. Yeah. Mostly kids. [ __ ] out
most of these kids. I don't give a [ __ ]
Not meaning that.
>> No, I never actually No, I never
>> Jaden. Jaden [ __ ] day told me to do
that. What the [ __ ] are you on about?
Jaden didn't tell her to do that to you. >> Myself,
well then you not got me pissed.
>> And you know what I do when I'm pissed?
I can't remember what I do.
>> [ __ ] hell.
>> Wow. Todd, that's so weird. You are
pedo. No, you're a pedo. You people are
pedos. You sit there and call people
pedos for what they say and what they
do. Yeah, PJ. But when these are up on
fairly chat room, yeah, doing what they
do, talking about other people's kids,
put in pictures up there of other
people's kids for people to react. These
people are [ __ ] popping down and out
pedophiles. Natalie's Natalie knows me
from the start of YouTube. She knows
everything what's going on on YouTube.
It's only you people who sat there and
calling people pedophiles
>> when you [ __ ] use the actual
pedophiles who sit there and get
pictures of [ __ ] obviously that woman
but it's all not the point
you're not doing [ __ ] like that as well.
That is madness.
>> The tube then talking to [ __ ] other
women and [ __ ] recording it on YouTube.
>> Yeah, I was only pissing you off. I
didn't expect you to do that.
>> I can't remember doing that.
>> That's why we're talking to just to piss
you off. Not to piss you off like that.
Just to make you jealous. But obviously
it backfired on my ass. It
>> belly is pedo and rice is a pedo too.
But that doesn't mean everyone is you
spazzy [ __ ] You better not be
>> Hang on a minute. So what did you all
do? What did you all do when I first
come to this community? Who do you all
target in this community?
>> People's children.
>> Yeah. They target kids
>> and that's what they do. They try to get
what what they used to do. Peeps, you
sit there and call me something what I'm
not. Listen. Listen. Time to get this
out in the open. Yeah, you are the ones
who picture of my kids and other
people's children's on your devices.
Yeah, you are the ones who go up on
fell's chat room and talk about other
people's kids and argue with other
people about the children. Yeah. Me
about Pat Mus when I call Pat M's kids.
He's the man who went around putting
pictures up of FL and I said what I said
back then because of that. That don't
make me a nut. What makes you a nut
should be going on people's Facebook
grabbing picture of children putting
them up. Hey, look at this. I've got a
kid on me happy child what's not even
mine and then you got a feather who puts
pics up on his wall.
>> [ __ ] happening?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Then you go around and call
other people pedos. I make mistake. I
didn't even mean to put that app on my
phone. That don't make me a [ __ ]
pedo. But putting that app on my phone
if I went on that app and talk to kids
on that app. Yeah. But this pedest
So why the [ __ ] am I going to go on here
and have people where to talk to kids
when you're not even talking to kids?
You're talking to grown adults
and explain. So why are pedophile
hunters on these app as well? Why are
pedophile hunters on these teen dating
app? That don't make no sense at all. I
could have been me I could have been
catching pedophile on pedophile myself.
You you don't know that. But you call people pedos.
But I didn't. I downloaded that by
accident. I had that. Why the [ __ ] would
I put that app on YouTube
if I if I knew it was on my phone? Why
the [ __ ] would I put it up on YouTube? I
wouldn't. If I knew it was on my phone, I wouldn't.
You know what I mean? Literally, I
[ __ ] wouldn't. And they used to even
call people nons the same as you
with your sister's [ __ ] with your
sister's kids when they went around and
put your sister's kids all over for
YouTube. Your sister's not even on
>> I know. I know.
And you go around putting pictures up of
your sister's kids uploading and they
call you the [ __ ] knots for it all.
These are the [ __ ] pedos.
You know what? If I put every single
video what I've got of all these all
over my Facebook, man, they'd be [ __ ]
I might do that. You know, this
community once and for all for what they
all have by putting all their pictures
and all their sayings what all these say
all over Facebook. I might do that and
this community might go up on the page
as well. So you might get more people
than this community calling the [ __ ] out
of you weirdos.
>> People remember Do you remember Do you
remember when they tried to call people
skin? It's weird, isn't it?
>> They still their skin. The skin.
>> Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
>> Yeah. If you all think that I've been
kicked out of Manchester. Yeah. I go
back to Manchester just to prove it. Me
and N. Yeah. And if you think I've been
kicked out in Manchester, Google me in Manchester. Rodale
cares about this community.
>> It's obviously you all care about the
community because you won't in this
community. Oh, yeah. You do all care
about this community or you won't be s
on this community.
>> Not yet.
>> So, so it's obviously you do care about
this community. But I might I might
actually do that. take all these videos
and put this YouTube community all about
me anyway just to completely [ __ ] it up. >> Yeah,
>> I might I might just do that all over my
Tik Tok YouTube everywhere. everywhere.
At the end of the day, these putting
some people up there actually put the
ped up the facts
on this community.
>> Oh, one sec. Someone just sent me a
message. Hold on. One second. Two seconds. Yeah.
There peeps. Yeah. You are the four
grown adults. All of me and N. Yeah. And
you all sit on here doing what you're
doing. You're all [ __ ] in this
community. I tell you know for sure you
all pathetic. One, you don't get on my
chicks. Two, you don't
annoy me. You don't do call to me. You
annoy yourself by being, you know, [ __ ]
At the end of the day, people said none
of you are the ones who know me. Yeah,
you had mates. You had all this. Yeah,
you had that. You all go. But why you
not why you not out?
Why you all Why you all s on YouTube day
in and day out
taking pictures of women's fies
paying for women's beers just to get
them pissed so you all can see a bit of
tits on fanny
why you all doing that then you go pedos
and use a [ __ ] little per in this
community and [ __ ] pedo sitting there
explain that then pigs yeah
explain that I don't have to go out and
get a woman pitch to show me a chair
If I wanted to see none of this [ __ ]
now, I can see it right now. How'd you
go on paper like [ __ ] or get a woman
pissed do that [ __ ]
You know what I mean? End of the day,
that's only what you people can do. Get
pictures of women on YouTube and I can
get the real thing. Roll the [ __ ] up,
you little weasels.
I'm talking to someone.
Can you hear me?
>> Yeah, I can hear you.
>> Yeah, sorry, man. Yeah.
>> Yeah. This communities I'm thinking of
coming off this um community.
>> Well, you might as well
[ __ ] weirdos in here, lad. I'm
telling you now. They [ __ ] all
pension all [ __ ] old farts and
>> Yeah. Depressed with the lives. This is
why they on YouTube.
>> They're so depressed with their lives.
They sit on YouTube and try and make
other people's lives depressed because
they haven't got a miss and they alone
alone just like
>> and every [ __ ] around else. Yeah. They
sat here getting pictures of women
because they don't have nothing to [ __ ] >> Yeah.
You call people. What was the proof on
me? What me calling Pat must kick in
that moment? putting pictures of of my
kids around the dating that I never even went on.
Have you ever denied these? No, I
haven't. You s
on YouTube and beyond pissed madness.
>> You are the [ __ ] freak little [ __ ]
in this community. If I ever bump into you any
but you're getting a crack, clucking
point. Don't tell me you talk to you.
Why you getting a crack? Yeah,
>> I'm going to smash these
lucky lucky bump into me. >> Oh,
these are no bies in this community.
They're no bodies, PJ. These are actual no bodies. >> Yeah.
>> And that's what they had. That's why I
need on YouTube to tell look at you
being kicked out of all these towns and
that prove that I'm being kicked out of
all these towns. Prove it.
>> You did nothing.
>> Yeah, you did.
>> Yeah, [ __ ]
I think I left. Have I left?
>> No. No. Yeah. Yeah, you
>> Yeah, I met Trixie.
Ricky had to get [ __ ] back up outside
the pub with him. Did not all see that
when Trixie when me and K was recording
across the road and we was watching him.
We were stalking Trixie. >> Yeah.
I'm not one in the middle of tower. This
camera's like said to us
is just a little weasel. There's like
the rest of us in this community.
>> Yeah, I laugh at Timmy. Jimmy won't meet
me. Evil way.
It's funny, is it?
>> It's not fun, PJ. No, it's not funny.
It's [ __ ] weird. We weird as [ __ ]
arguing with people who you don't even
know on YouTube.
>> That's what they do.
>> Yeah. Yeah. It's weird. It's just
[ __ ] weird as [ __ ] Like these people
haven't got content.
>> It's like there's no content here.
>> They come on and they repeat themselves
every day calling people pedophiles and
calling people and calling people to get
a job. If that's only what they've got,
then they're not scaring me. Either way,
they can sit there and call me a key to
power. I don't give two shits to be
honest. It doesn't matter me one little
bit if it don't if they think it does.
It doesn't even L owned Monty man. Who
the [ __ ] is Lorna?
>> Lorna. Lorna is the one who was Lorna
got owned off me last night. You prick.
Some ugly fat ugly woman with glasses on.
>> Oh yeah. a weapon
>> here people. You people own yourself on
this community. You own yourself on the
[ __ ] you do. You don't think about that
>> You all coming on YouTube calling the
[ __ ] out of people. You people are
[ __ ] wh in this community.
>> You people are embarrassing to [ __ ] you
older and me and PJ most in this
community. That's no [ __ ] And then
you come on YouTube and do what you all
do. Where's your content, Pete?
What content have you got? >> Yeah.
>> What content have you people got except
sitting there calling people who you
don't know and getting women pissed just
to take pictures of them? Getting
illegal porn on your phone basically.
>> Okay. Yeah, I see what you mean now. Yeah.
>> You see what I mean? Illegal porn. >> Yeah.
>> Getting women pissed. taking pictures of
women when they pissed out of the faces
naked or trying to get them to do no
money. That's what they do.
>> It's basically illegal porn
meaning that they have to get a woman to
do [ __ ] and it's not funny PJ. It's
basically class as some form of rape in
some form of way. Obviously, it's not
cuz you never done nothing to that.
They just said
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> This is mad. Yeah. Cuz you little
[ __ ] little that lead just said
your little [ __ ] person.
>> No, that's why they all bing over your
Hey, look at Natalie sping all over YouTube. Hey,
>> that's why they b over it. That's why
they got pictures of other women's spies
and titties in this community because
they can't get it. They got to get a
woman pissed before they can even
[ __ ] No woman will get anything out
to these people. Oh yeah. Actually for
Bible bash you only the one who actually
will get get everything out. So
>> she doesn't know what she's doing. I
didn't know what I was doing. I don't
come on here just to do that [ __ ]
>> That's illegal. Natalie didn't know what
she was doing. Like she said, well,
these have got basically illegal porn on the phones.
>> Porn beal
legal porn. Think about it, PJ. Getting
a woman pissed out of her red, not
knowing what she's doing just so she can
show her fanny and all that online and
then take pieces off it and all that.
Look, that's basically some form of
illegal. Oh, no. It
>> It's the same. It's the same to say you
you go to a pub, you do sober, you get a
woman pissed out of her head. Yeah. You
take that woman over. Yeah. Cuz she's
pissed. You You take a page over cuz
she's pissed. That's classed as um rape.
That's basically classed as some form of rape.
>> Well, I got I got a [ __ ] I I got a
[ __ ] in the anyway from a drunk
person, but I was also drunk.
>> Yeah, but you're still classed as some
form of rape when you pitch out your
PBO. Google it.
>> No, I don't. Obviously, like obviously I
wasn't going to say no, was I?
>> It doesn't matter if a woman's pissed.
Yeah. And the You don't take a woman
down the back alley
cuz she's pissed out of her face. You
take her own, sleep with her.
>> She She kept She kept coming on to me. So like,
>> well, that's different. Well, that's
different then. If she's coming on to
you, that's different.
>> She said,
>> she said she said she said, "I really
want you, but I don't think you want
me." That's what she said. That
was different compared to these to these people.
>> You know what I mean? Money.
>> I can't believe that actually happened.
But that's actually funny as
>> Lord J got it. Two people. No.
>> Yeah. Two people bought my drink. I got
20 off Lord J and then 20 pound off someone else.
>> So you got the three bottles of poker.
No, just one
for about30 all together with a pot that
>> Oh, 30.
That made that made you laugh. That made
you laugh in it, Monty.
>> What made me laugh?
>> That that person come on to me saying I
really want you. Do you think that's funny?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> But do you think it's funny though?
>> No. Natalie's laughing at that.
>> Cuz it's funny as [ __ ] is it? No, not
really. Because some women might find
you attractive, some women might not.
It's just miss me. Something
>> Yeah. Some women women
>> when women I've had a drink PJ. Yeah.
They get more rowdy. More rowdy than
what a man does. Yeah. Obviously men I
can't with you. I can't get when I'm pissed. I
find it hard.
>> You have to take You have to take it.
>> No, I just can't get when I'm pissed.
sent. I don't do I need fiagra at that. >> No,
>> I don't need fiagra, mate.
>> I don't need hold on, hold on. L sent
her 20 quid. Natalie got herself pissed.
L is a s.
>> Yeah, J got a pissed. Sorry, it's L is a
[ __ ] weird one on his community. got
and then Jaden and another person paid
for the deal with BJ and then um Jaden
paid for Natalie's current ticket to
come come and join me in my life. >> Yeah.
>> Well, try and get me kicked out of that
play with him.
That's what happened. So, because
Natalie didn't [ __ ] do any of that.
>> Yeah. You know, they're just they're
just weirdos, man. He's
getting a woman pissed just to get
pictures of him naked.
I mean, it's not his fault in a way.
>> Come on, show off my fing. >> Yeah.
>> When you don't remember what you do and
you do things you don't do normally. >> Yeah.
>> For that. So, so do you think that drunk
person remembered to give me a [ __ ] on you?
>> What? What? PG? Yeah.
>> I said, "Do you think that drunk person
remembered giving me a blowjob?"
>> No, I don't think she would. No. No. I
don't think she would have remembered
>> until she woke up the next day with the
taste in her mouth.
>> Still don't remember. Huh?
>> He probably still doesn't remember.
I will never ever sleep with a pissed
woman unless I'm dating them and going
out with them and we both know what we doing.
>> I had a few night sands. I had a few
pissed one night stands.
>> Say that can advertise Coca-Cola.
>> Yeah, fake. Fake.
All the [ __ ] weirdos in this community.
>> Why that boy? Do you know what I don't understand?
Can you hear me?
>> Don't worry. Don't worry. Because that's
only what you're going to be seeing of
Natalie ever. You're not understand what
I understand is why all these women go
out drinking just to tell everyone
they've got boyfriends. It's a waste of
money if you ask me. Is it?
>> No, because some women like to go out on
a night. But women like to go out on a
night out just like
>> if you think about it. Yeah. Like why
would you even waste why would you even
waste your time and money if you're just
going to tell everyone you've got boyfriends?
>> Like I said, PJ, some women will say
they got boyfriends. It depends if they
find you attractive or not. Right. Just
let me put this in in mind for you. Yeah. >> M
>> a woman like you say in a pub with that
B bald man and that woman was touching
that bald man's head and then I come
over with my bald head next to you at
the bar and then she started strogging
my bald head. >> Yeah.
>> She didn't like she didn't like me cuz I
wasn't bored and [ __ ] in it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So because you you know what
I mean? It's what people see and what
what you know what I mean?
>> You know what I mean? Yeah. That was so
weird money is it?
What? The woman didn't talk to you already.
>> I bet I bet it gave you a hard on it
when she was stroking your head.
>> Definitely not. PJ,
>> I bet you felt something in your tongue, didn't it?
>> He He knows how to get people in
trouble, don't he?
>> You're the one. You're the You're the
>> Yeah. Yeah. [Laughter]
You're the one that blew it up though,
not me. Yeah, I do remember. It was
weird, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Do you know what?
>> Some people will see you differently.
>> It's the funny ruthless. I mean, I think
you seen one. They all the same except
for some big got big lips. Some people
got small lips. Different group.
>> I'm not being funny, but Natalie is
[ __ ] funny. He's tight, peeps. It's
tight. It's [ __ ] tight.
Too much too much information, man.
[ __ ] hell, buddy.
>> Sorry. Sorry. [ __ ] hell.
>> They're [ __ ] You know what I mean?
They're probably wanking to this. You know that.
>> Yeah. Do you know what peeps? You know
what? When I'm up on someone else's
channel, watch me just pull my [ __ ] out
now. Yeah. Watch me pull my dick out
someone's channel. No, boo. I'm not
lying. Watch. You want to see an actual
real man? I pull my dick out for you.
Did she did she did she end up getting
off with that uh bold guy Monty? >> No,
>> I don't know. We weren't there.
>> We was having a drink. You was cool
approaching. So, we don't know. >> Yeah.
>> I'm not asked about any woman. All woman
I'm asked about is Natalie.
>> It was fun. It was freaked.
>> What? What? It was fun, but it was expensive.
>> Screenshot in the chat. It screams piss you kick Natalie.
Kick it. Kick that Natalie account. And
that's what I talk about on these peeps. Kick it.
>> Where is it? I didn't even see it.
>> Yeah, it was on Natalie's [ __ ] Moo.
>> I'm not ask about it. It's not going to
piss me off now. Anyways, cuz I've seen
it. So, it's not going to piss me off.
>> He was on the one who got a woman piece
and got that picture and that's
freakified on their behalf.
>> Ruth as well. I mean, anyone else in a
fan seriously acting like [ __ ] Christmas
and [ __ ] the thing is I don't think
>> these are old fat [ __ ] in this
community. some scary [ __ ] in this
community, but they all fat probably
some of them are still [ __ ] virgins.
>> I'm too scared.
>> Another thing, another thing. Another
thing, yeah, Monty, next time you if we
ever go out for a drink again, remember
your [ __ ] ID, man.
>> Well, when we're going out for the next drink, >> huh? >> No.
And he's not letting me go out on your pe yet. >> Why?
>> Well, does she wear the trousers in the relationship, Monty?
Monty, you don't know what that means, is it?
>> [ __ ] cold.
>> Yeah, but Yeah, but Monty never done anything.
>> And nobody tried to.
>> I didn't try to. I didn't. I didn't try
to. He he was live streaming when he
went up to that other woman. No, please.
>> No, that he was No, he was Yeah, he was
keeping her friend company because there
was two of them. So, yeah, he wasn't
trying to get
>> Yeah, but no.
>> What the girl? You about the women the
girls who were walking with. >> No.
At the bar when you went up to him and
whispered to PJ, he went, "Yeah, go on."
And then you went
>> Yeah. Yeah. It's on about the woman who
I went over to who you told me to. >> Exactly.
>> And I told you I told you. Okay. Then I
went over to the woman and said, "You
pretend I'm cold approaching your mate
wants me to cold approach her." So I
started talking to her for a little bit
and I just told her to walk off and she walked off.
>> Ruthless. A wet patch. You never know
what a wet patch is on a girl then, do you?
>> Done a wet patch last night actually.
>> Did you?
>> Yeah, it was a good It was a good night out that
>> you do [ __ ] dried up all you.
>> He doesn't know what that is anyways.
>> Called [ __ ] fanny booth. That's what it's called. >> Yeah.
>> It's not nice. I let PJ kick that
account again, please.
>> Why are they putting it up? That's weird.
>> Because they will be talking about it.
They weirdos. That's one what they
freaks. These are the actual pedophiles
now. People who are putting these
pictures up. These are the ones who go
around and call other people penos.
These are the real penos. Yeah.
>> Why does Mike still try to All right,
Natalie. Does Mike still try to contact you?
>> No, we just lose messages
>> every now and then.
>> Oh, okay.
>> [ __ ] off, J. you slag.
>> At the end of the day, most well, all
men in this community do not have a
respect for women at all. At all,
>> it's a fake account of Jane.
>> I'm just saying. I'm just saying. I
don't I'm just saying
>> he [ __ ] emails me. Think about it,
Monty. Think about it. Yeah. She's 40
years of age. Yeah. And she [ __ ]
emails me. I just ignore it every time.
Like I mean, you've got nothing better
to do at [ __ ] 40 years of age and
[ __ ] messing someone half your age.
You know what I mean, Monty?
>> Yeah. But she might like it. Even if
she's in her 40s or not, DJ, she's she's
not in 60s or 70s. Slight rise.
You know what I mean? You're a full
grown man. You're in your 20s. It's not
It's not bad or nothing like that if you
went out with a 40year-old,
>> is it? [ __ ]
>> No, I'm not saying that. But it's just
weird, you know.
>> It's not even weird.
>> No, Jane's an actual ped. You don't understand.
>> Is she
not even [ __ ] [ __ ] dried off?
Definitely dried off.
Oh my god, man. [ __ ] weirdos.
>> Yeah, just keep kicking them. That's
only what they can do is kick.
>> They're [ __ ] weirdos. I agree. They're weirdos.
>> They all laugh at what they do. Try.
There's another one. PG above above.
>> Oh yeah, I didn't see that one. My bad. Oh,
>> find it funny. They don't know what
fatty juice is. I mean, seriously,
>> I suck. I suck none of this fanny juice up, mate.
>> That must [ __ ] be
>> That's disgusting. That's nasty.
>> Why is it? I'm [ __ ] proper. When I
see it coming out, I lick it all up.
I've only I've only licked a fanny once.
>> I'd never do it again. It's gross.
>> I like it. B. I lick it for hours on end.
>> You're gross. You're [ __ ] gross.
[ __ ] [ __ ] sucks Asian juice.
>> No, he does not. No. Shut the [ __ ] up. What's the
>> That's what a I'm just reading a comment.
He has to read that one out.
>> He has to read the cocky out.
>> It's good to see It's good to see Monty
and happy. Yeah, it is good.
>> [ __ ] hell, man.
>> No, I don't like [ __ ]
>> Where does that Where does that Where's
that Jaden from? from Sheffield, isn't it?
>> Yeah, Sheffield near there. Yeah. Man,
uh Manchester or Sheffield, one of the other. >> Yeah.
Do you remember that Lee Greener? Do you
remember that Ronnie? You might not
remember him, might he?
>> You remember him? >> No.
>> He's from Rubber.
He used to troll all the streamers.
>> Did you see get kicked out of his house?
No, but I saw I saw Rice. I saw rice get
kicked out of his house.
>> Yeah, they own rice both at the same
time. Basically the same week they got kicked out.
>> I'm going to make some burgers soon. I
got the nice burgers for today.
>> They will never get kicked out cuz I never do
>> so they never find out where I am.
>> These people are weirdos, man. [ __ ] hell.
>> Yeah, just keep kicking it. Yeah, keep
doing that. This is weird.
>> We don't. So, we just start our own community.
>> Yeah, we should do.
>> They keep kicking all wankers in it. [Laughter]
>> You like this community though?
>> No, I just keep kicking them all and
then keep all the good people in.
>> I did like that time we met in
Birmingham. It was a nice piss up.
>> It was a good piss up, wasn't it?
>> I've only drunk two times. I've only
I've only drunk I've only drunk two
times since. I've only I've only drunk
two times since.
>> Yeah, we go out again, but Natalie's
coming with us this time.
>> Yeah, we can all pull. We can all pull together.
>> No, no, you can pull yourself. I've
already pulled. I don't need a ping. What?
>> No, we can all pull together.
>> No, no, we're not having enough for anywhere, PJ.
>> No, I said we can go out and p together in it.
>> Up the up.
>> Where would Where do you want to Where
would you Where would you want to go out drinking? >> McDonald's.
>> No, I mean I What? Like where? Like city
center again? Yeah.
>> Yeah, city center again. Yeah, if you want.
>> That' be nice.
Natalie's coming out though this time.
>> That's all right.
I've never met Natalie before. Ever. So,
it'll be the first first time for
everything, isn't it?
>> Oh, no. I'm going to slap you though. PJ. >> Yeah.
>> If you went out with
>> No. Too far.
>> I can guarantee you I won't, Jane.
Guarantee you I won't.
Why don't you take Jim for a little meat spin? >> Nah. >> Yeah.
>> You knew what was about spin. Yeah.
>> Yeah. But nah.
>> That's what
loves Turkish men. So you're in luck. Peter belly.
Never been with Turkish man.
What a weird thing to write, eh?
That's so weird, Monty. Huh?
>> DJ belongs on a [ __ ] Cherokee farm. >> Yeah.
>> Why are they writing these weird things?
>> You see [ __ ] weirdos and [Music] >> woman?
>> No, I don't. If Natalie was PJ's ring
woman, he get nowhere.
>> No, mate. If if we all Monty if you if
you [ __ ] you know that if you ever
cheated on Natalie you'd be toast and it
>> I'll never cheat on Natalie. I will
never ever ever cheat on Natalie. That's
one thing I will never do. I [ __ ] I
love Natalie too much.
>> No, I'm saying if you did you'd be
toast. You know that, right?
>> Yeah, of course I'd be toast.
>> Do you even know what that means?
>> Yeah. Or I'd be a dead man.
>> You'd be toast.
Well, you know that [ __ ] L. He's
rough as toast, man. He's [ __ ] ugly.
He's rough as toast.
>> EJ, there's a lot of ugly bastards in
this community. A lot of them.
>> Well, I The only the only thing I say to
Monte is I hate the fact I met Nons. I
say it all the time.
>> [ __ ] you now. You met him through the
>> You didn't meet him through me.
>> I [ __ ] met him through [ __ ] you.
That weirdo. You met him through the community.
>> I met through you.
>> Me through the rest of the community. [Music]
>> Yeah. You met him in RI lights channel lights?
>> No, I didn't. It was someone else's actually. >> Yeah.
>> Oh, well then you didn't meet him through me.
>> No, but I got into it because of you. I
bet that's because of you. So it's all
it's all linked to you.
>> [ __ ] off, man. Did that [ __ ] Did that TJ
>> or weirdo?
>> You [ __ ] I met him through you.
>> I I think if TJ was still alive, you
you'd hook up with him.
>> No, no, you can [ __ ] off, mate. He
scares me to
>> I think I think you'd hook up with him. Definitely.
>> No. No. He scares me, PJ. He does [ __ ]
me up. I'm only scared of him. I'm not
scared of anybody in my life but him.
I'm scared of. I'm completely scared of him. >> Yeah.
>> Even though Even though he is dead, I'm
still scared of him. >> Really?
>> I have nightmares of him sometimes that
he's going to come and bumate me
sometimes and all that lot. But you don't understand.
>> Yeah, you probably don't even remember
what he looks like.
>> Yeah, I do. Skinny, grayish.
Don't remember what he looked like.
gray as your [ __ ] couple of wrinkles
on his face. I even remember when he
used to chill in his bed, he always be
in his bedroom with the stairs going up
to his door. Come on,
>> come on.
>> Like I said, that man scares me to [ __ ]
So yeah, I do remember everything.
>> Do you remember? Do you remember that Mr. FTP? No.
>> And that one from Birmingham. Do you
remember that one [ __ ]
Yeah, she is down syndrome. Um do you
remember um Monty? That one we used to
argue with from Birmingham. Nons's
girlfriend. Down syndrome. Yeah, she is.
But um yeah. Do you know that one we
used to argue with in Birmingham? Monty,
the one from Birmingham.
>> I argued with a lot of people. Yeah,
>> we're not from Birmingham.
But who was it?
>> What weirdo, bro?
>> There's loads of weirdos back on PlayStation.
>> I think he said his name was Jack or something.
>> No, I don't remember. He's the one who I
said if I'm talking to you, you know about it.
>> You remember that fat one with the glasses?
>> No, he was the fat one with glasses.
>> Oh, never mind. There's too many.
>> Yeah. Y like Iron [ __ ] the main main
people I say. >> Yeah.
>> Weren't even in the community who you talk to.
>> Yeah. True.
>> Yeah. He's a stalker, man. He's obsessed
with me. That [ __ ] nonsleg. Yeah, we
know Jane. Well, fake Jane, you know.
Yeah, you're a widow.
[ __ ] skint bastard.
>> Proper weirdo. Proper proper weirdo.
>> Blanket outside with it.
>> I heard Timmy done his bollocks and
gambling. Is that true?
>> In it.
>> Is that true?
>> No. No. Because he gave John West a
tenner last night.
Yeah. What? Jimmy?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Timmy. Yeah.
>> So, I think he g Yeah. Yeah. Give John
West a tenner last night.
>> I think he was just showing off, Lord,
to be honest with you cuz I was up on a panel. So, >> yeah,
>> I think he's kind of showing off. Hey,
look, I've got money. >> Yeah.
These people in here are obsessed with money.
>> You're getting punished tonight. You >> punish. >> No.
>> What? Unless you want to get punished, please. Yeah.
>> You donated£10 to rest after you spent
320 on yearly mobile.
Yi is rich.
>> Yi is rich.
>> Is he? I'm [ __ ]
>> me and money are
>> No. What? Why? Why? Why do you think
you're getting punished tonight? PJ,
>> you might come and b me or something.
>> I don't take it that way.
>> I take a [ __ ] if you like. That's
different. You're not gay.
>> No, you give me one.
>> No, you got to give me one. PJ, it's not gay.
No, you have to give me one.
>> No, you got to give me one, Pete. Yeah,
>> you got to bite it as well. Yeah, you
got to give it a little nibble.
>> I've had I've had six [ __ ] That's
not including escorts. You've only had
two in it. Well, six different people.
>> I I haven't even slept with no escorts.
>> No, that's not including the escort.
That's what I'm saying. I've I've had
six without escort. How many women have
you set with all together? PJ,
>> what including escorts?
>> No, they rarely don't count. Normal the regular.
>> Um, six. Five or six.
>> Is that it? >> Yeah. >> Wow.
>> Yeah. Five or six.
>> That's not even a lot.
>> Oh, no.
>> I must have slept with about what?
We don't even know
>> if we're count if we're counting in
escorts then [ __ ] 300.
>> No escorts. So I don't really count
really cuz you
>> Yeah, but it still counts. You still
[ __ ] them and [ __ ] You still like it counts.
>> Not you still [ __ ] them for money. So
not really counting basically.
>> I don't really count
>> either way. Even I think I think I've like
>> Bro, I think I've [ __ ] I think I've
[ __ ] more escorts than any anyone in
the world as well. >> It
was even joking. Yeah, I
>> I never s with the escort.
>> Never never ever would I sit with a Escort.
>> I've done it. I've done it. I've done it
more than anyone in the world, I think.
I'm not even joking, bro. Like, I'm not even playing.
>> You sent a Escort to my house? No, never.
>> Yeah, you did. She sent a [ __ ]
escort to my house ages ago.
>> You liked it.
>> Did a [ __ ] like it? He walked away.
>> You liked it a little bit?
>> No. No. No. Did a [ __ ] We was at the
door having next minute this taxi pulled
up. This woman got out of a [ __ ] car
with high heels on