Yo yo, sorry man. I had to do something.
Them burgers were yummy.
You can't be homemade burgers.
I like Grizz. Yeah.
Yeah, sorry about that.
What's You know what I mean? [Music]
Yeah. Waiting for Bonnie to come back on.
Hold on, bro. Uh box.
Yeah. Shall we talk about LJ like he
does? Like we're bullsh
>> Yeah. Shall we? Like all the selfing
[ __ ] he does. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. It Yeah. He's a self projector, isn't it?
>> Yeah. On his YouTube channel there
basically calling everyone to [ __ ] his way.
>> Well, I don't know why he I don't know
why he tries to call people skint every day.
>> The man is skinn. He just admitted he's alone.
>> He just aditted he has no one and he's alone.
>> He hasn't he has nothing.
>> Well, the man will never have nothing.
Sadly, we were saying, "Hey, peeps, have
you seen the video? Have you seen a
video of Natalie Cheese M?" Hey, go over
to everyone seen it already. Lord, yeah.
>> You know how you know these people are
weirdos, Monty? Yeah. Because you know
people from his channel. Yeah. Will be
watching us even though they're blocked
and they can't type. They'll sat there.
They'll be sat there watching us. Is
that not weird to you?
>> They freak. They freak on you.
>> Yeah, [ __ ] weirdos. Is it?
>> Yeah, weirdos.
Is that on L paddle and all that [ __ ]
L Jake kept on kicking me every time I
told him it's his fault why Natalie did
that for getting a piss. Basically
getting a woman pissed.
>> He's a [ __ ] weirdo.
He has to get a woman pissed us to get a B out.
>> Madness, Monty. Madness.
>> No more. Oh, you know
I don't know what just weird.
>> Hello Monty. Do you want some RC cola with that?
>> Yeah, you can sort of give [ __ ] to
me. It don't work like it works with everyone else.
>> You're uh you got some very lovely legs,
Monte. You ever thought about just doing
some squats or something or getting a
job or exercising? What about yourself?
What about yourself instead of living at
store with mommy or something?
>> I still got some nice ham legs. Yeah,
there you go. You like
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You're fat [ __ ]
Yeah, that American [ __ ] has been eating
his [ __ ] pies.
>> Come on. Let me have another donut. Come
on. Give me another donut.
>> Yeah, you fat [ __ ]
>> Who the [ __ ] is that?
>> It's an American Yankee bastard. Incest
bastard. Someone who sags his sister now
and again on a weekend.
>> Oh, you're very You're very fixated on
incest, Monty. Should we talk? It's just
what you Americans do in it. It's just
what you incest [ __ ] do. You incest.
You You're into that [ __ ]
>> Why are you so fixated on incest? Why?
>> Well, why why do you all immigrant like
all you Americans? Shagg your cousins
and your moms and your dads and your
[ __ ] what? What? Why do you do that?
>> Why do you [ __ ] your own realities?
>> You got some kingy
bastards. All of you.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
You wouldn't even survive, Monty.
>> Man, do you go down on your sister like
that? Yeah. Would you go down on your
sister with that kind of talk?
>> You do realize. Yeah. Do you do realize
that if you ever were in Hillbelly Town,
you wouldn't be able to be breathing?
You'd be waking up.
>> Of course I will. Of course I simply the
people I'm like people dumb and fake
body. You need to live, man.
>> I got a better body than you. Why don't
you show yourself?
>> I doubt that. I doubt that.
So, show yourself l
>> and show yourself. If you're better,
>> it better show yourself. >> Uhhuh.
>> Go on. If you're better, better looking,
better body, better [ __ ] what? Bigger
dick of me. Show me.
>> Better body. Better body.
>> Show me your dick.
>> I've seen Look at Monty. I've seen you
shirtless. That one time you were
throwing away Takis or whatever you
types of chip crisp you.
>> Yeah, I can go shitless now if you want.
>> Imagine wasting food. No wonder you have
a skinny buddy. So skint and skinny.
>> I don't waste food actually.
>> Uh-huh. Yeah, you are. You're skint.
>> I'm a skinn, am I?
>> Uh, I am.
>> Oh, no way. No way. Oh, wow. That that
that proper at my feelings like that's
the best world.
>> Yeah, my wallet proper last time we talked.
>> Your wallet's got flies flying out of your cloud.
>> Why do you Why do you people Why are you
so obsessed with skin people
in that a m
Why do you feel like PJ Why do you feel
like women owe you a favor?
>> Why do you feel they do?
>> No, they don't. No, they don't. Hang on.
Hang on a minute.
>> One second. Let me finish. Let me let me
let me let me let me let me speak to
this guy by myself. Right. Hold on a
minute. Let me kick you, Monty. Cuz
>> bro, you know sing is never going to get you laid.
>> In what way was I sing?
>> Because Oh, women don't owe you
anything. Bro, it's never going to get
you laid. It's just ridiculous.
It's sing. That's exactly what simps
say. Well, it's never going to get you laid ever.
>> Have you gotten laid? >> Huh?
>> Have you gotten laid? Yeah, more times
than you will ever and I never ever had
to s once.
>> I pressed the X button for doubt. That
is a horrible doubt right there.
>> One second, Money. I let you back in. I
was trying to speak to him and you you
was talking over me, so I had to kick
you. So, anyways, why do you defend women anyways?
>> Why do you feel like women owe you a favor?
>> Why Why do you defend women?
>> I don't. I just don't lick their asses.
There's a difference.
by harassing them.
>> I mean, I don't lick ass. Because I
don't lick women's asses. I'm what?
>> So, why do you defend women? Do you
think it's going to get you laid or something?
>> Do you use this as a shield to cover?
Like, see, it's a different year, PJ. It's progressive.
>> Yeah. Don't kick me, PJ. He's better
than when he's 21.
>> Yeah, it's a different It's a different
year. So, what?
>> Look at that. Two lovers in quarrel. Oh
>> yeah. At least at least two loveries are
not repeaters. At least we're not >> Yeah.
>> And at least we don't have to go around.
>> Wait. Why do you Why do you defend women?
>> Why do you think women owe you a favor?
Like they should hand you [ __ ] on a plate.
>> I already I already answered you.
>> Wait. Wait. One minute. One minute. Why
do you pay women to get on? What?
>> Why do you pay women to get a check out?
Why do I pay women to jig us out? What
the [ __ ] I
>> Why do you get women pay you money on
YouTube like Natalie [ __ ] Bible bash
you to get a [ __ ] funny out and all that? Look
>> her money. No.
>> Yeah, right. Of course you are. Of
>> So why house? Monty, are you going to go
to her house and punch?
>> I am going to go to her house. I am
>> Wow. Really? You're threatening to to
hit a mother.
>> No, no, no, no. I'm not going to be
whacking anyone who's threatening. I'm
going to tell her she does show her and
showing everything she does. That's what
I'm going to be doing.
>> You said that you were going to go to
Bible Bap's house because you wanted to
deal with her. You said you wanted to
>> No, I am dealing with her. I am dealing
with her by showing her partner all the
videos she does on YouTube.
>> Really? I'm pretty sure all of that all
of that's already been out there.
That'll matter. I know you're going to
go over there. going to fight her. Imagine
>> imagine. Imagine him.
>> I'm going to be telling the wrong spirit
everything she's been doing.
>> You and PJ deserve each other.
>> So you never answer my question. Why do
you think Simpson's going to get you laid?
>> Uh-huh. So do you really wear glasses
anyway to specify
question? He asked questions, right? And
then you're going to throw a tantrum
because Okay, I'm I'm kicking. Sorry.
>> He is a fat gun. You know, no, don't kick him.
No, I kicked him because I asked him
questions. He doesn't answer my
questions. [ __ ] him.
>> Yeah, they won't. He's a fat [ __ ]
That's what they do. These fat people,
they self-reflect a fat American [ __ ]
man. Eating a bit too much [ __ ] cheesecakes.
>> Do you know Do you know what state he lives in? >> California.
>> How do you know?
>> [ __ ] I'm just guessing.
>> Do you know where Chicago is?
>> Yes, Chicago, but it's America.
>> How do you know? Because the basketball team got balls.
>> Team, mate.
>> Cuz I like I like basketball. That basketball?
>> Yeah. Same. Basketball's my favorite sport, too.
>> I like Chicago Bulls. Michael Jordan.
>> I don't like I don't like football. I prefer basketball.
>> Michael Michael Jordan used to play for Chicago Bulls.
>> Yeah, that's that's Air Jordan. That's
where Air Jordan. He made Air Jordan. Huh?
>> Air Jordan. [Music]
>> Air Jordan. The brand, the night brand
with the man with the basketball. Air Jordan.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. That that's from Michael Jordan made that.
>> Yeah. Michael Jordan then turned into a
baseball player. Did baseball.
>> Well, I like I like Simpsons cuz you
know Simpsons is a good cartoon and it's
English as well. So
>> yeah, but I want to know why they all
yellow. It's like they got like like the
Americans are color blind. It's like
they see yellow.
>> Yeah. But do you think English do you
think Simpsons is good for an English um cartoon?
>> Well, it is good, but it's a little bit
lame is because all the characters are
all the [ __ ] same color except for
the [ __ ] people. >> Yeah.
>> No, but I I like Simpsons. I like
Simpsons cuz it's British.
>> But he's not British. It's American.
>> No, it's not. It's British.
>> Oh, it's English. What did English makes the Simpsons?
>> Yeah. Why did you Why would you think it's American?
>> I just thought it would have been
American because the [ __ ]
the place, the town, and everything. I
thought it would have been American.
>> Nah, it's English.
The guy who made it is from Manchester.
>> The guy who made it is a woman who made
it, you [ __ ]
>> No, it was made No, it was made by a
man, but a woman voices B. It was made
by a man.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But the woman voices
more than just B. Milhouse as well. >> Yeah.
>> And she does um um the bully.
>> God bless you.
He does the body.
>> Bless you, Monty.
I really like you.
>> You should call it.
>> Monty, I really like you.
>> Why do these people self-reflect like Lord? Yeah.
>> Cuz that's their life.
>> Lord, yeah. Answer this. I mean, PG,
answer this question. Yeah.
>> Has Lord Yeah. ever put his kid on the
phone to you? his son on the phone or
his daughter on the phone to you. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. He's done that with me as well.
And he and he loads of times.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> And I tell And I tell his kid to shut
the [ __ ] up.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Lord J put his kid on the
phone to FY as well. And then he and he
denied it. He denied it. Yeah. And he
denied putting his kid on the phone to people.
And that's like loads of people saying this.
>> Even myself, he's put his kid on the
phone to me. Yeah,
>> Pat must have did the same as well. Like
when he was saying, "Oh, he's sick."
What [ __ ] was saying about Pat must
kids, but what was Pat Muster saying
about man and your well my kids and your sister's kids? >> Yeah.
>> And doing that and then all these are
going out me and you for what Pat
mustard what we say about Pat Mustard.
[ __ ] them all.
>> They're all little pedos in this
community and that's only what they had.
You stick up with all the pedophiles and
when you react to these people or do
whatever you class as a nons for what
these put you up but you know what I
mean they only go for people who they
only stick up for people who they like >> 100%
around and completely everybody just
pick all the PD keep you pick all the
selfs and keep all the good people in.
That's it. That's all we do. [ __ ] all
these. If they got a problem, tell them
to meet me. Tell them to come to me
where I am. Yeah.
>> You wish you wish you wish you never
went on this community now, isn't it?
>> No. I wish I grew in somewhere because
of Natalie. I met Natalie and
I put my life up to. But I put my own
life up by staying on YouTube. But I
want to be with Natalie. You know what I mean?
>> So in a way my life is not [ __ ] up.
Their life's more [ __ ] up and mine cuz
you got to make little lies and [ __ ] up
on people. Natalie's been watching me
from day one of being in this community
cuz you got me onto here. But Natalie
knows everything what's been going on on
YouTube from the start to the end.
>> You know what I mean?
So that's why Natalie's with me.
Yeah, he's seen everything. She knows
what's going on in this community. He
knows everything what's going on in this
community. She knows what's happened
with my children on here. He knows why I
said the [ __ ] I said about my two kids.
But don't matter either way. How many
times do children get rung up in this
community? A lot of a lot.
I'm not bringing it up either way. I'm
just putting it out there evil ways that
these people go on about other people's
children, but when we do it back to Le,
they cry about it. Yeah.
You know what I mean? Cry about it. Then
look at Lord J self reflection. He's
already admitted as a lord. He's trying.
He turned around and me and Natalie were
walking. He said if me and Natalie split
up in the send money to Natalie for a
laugh. So now Natalie knows. So now
Natalie knows that they're using her
basically just for what she does. So
basically what he's saying, yeah, I will
pay her to get a pedic
again basically. Meaning that these
people you've got to get a woman pissed
or Lord Jed
to even do that online.
They refused to pay out, Monty.
>> No, no, they paid out. Lo got got got
got got got got got got got got got got
got got got got got got got got her a be
um Jaden paid Natalie's train ticket
train ticket to get to me. >> Yeah.
>> So Natalie got to me and it it fought
them over because they can't get
refunded for the [ __ ] they got for Natalie
>> because you remember when do you
remember when suicide Mark was in the
bookies? Monty, you've seen videos like
that, is it?
>> No, you haven't seen him in bookies, actually.
>> Yeah, they refused to pay him out. He
started smashing it. He was another one.
>> What? Smashing the machines up.
>> Why does Timmy Why does Timmy gamble all the time?
>> Cuz he's a weasel. Cuz he's a freak and
he wastes his money every time. Do you
remember when he said beautifully done?
That was beautifully done. He's a
weirdo, isn't it?
>> Yeah. And it won't even be beautifully
done. He only want to for [ __ ] sake. >> Yeah,
that's beautifully grown.
>> All of these people on your skin.
>> No. No. PJ, they asking they
selfrelectors. They [ __ ] idiots.
They like to [ __ ]
they like to
put people up for what they are for what they are.
>> You know what I mean? They don't they
don't put themselves up cuz they know if
they put themselves up there then it's
just showing up there nons. Here's
another Yankee American little it's your
favorite Yankee con. Listen. Okay. You
know what? All right PJ I'll answer your
question. I'll answer your question. Okay.
>> No. No more questions.
>> No. No. No, no, no. I'll answer your question. What?
>> No. I'm not I'm not I'm not answering
any of the questions, Monty.
>> No, don't answer them. Don't answer
them. Don't answer our questions.
>> They do it to us. Don't answer. >> Yeah.
>> What's the point? What's the point of
answering your questions when you people
don't answer our questions? >> Yeah.
>> Did you know your questions? We're right
on your questions. That's why you can't
answer your questions.
Because you know if you answer questions
you [ __ ] up on yourselves and that's why
you people don't answer your own questions. >> Yeah.
You left or you kicked in?
>> He left.
>> Oh get him. Oh, wanted to see what to say.
>> I can imagine what you would be like if
if you didn't get paid out. You going
mad, wouldn't you?
>> I don't I don't do gambling. This is the thing.
>> No, but say you done a job and they
refused to pay out. He's going mad in it.
>> If I did a job, Yes. and didn't pay me
for the job. Yeah. I got mad for the job
I done and he didn't pay me for it. Yeah. >> What?
>> You might go gambling cuz you need money
to eat and [ __ ] in it. So obviously
money is important in it. Y bastard.
>> Dirty [ __ ]
Ollie sneezed and that we sex it.
>> No, you're a dirty [ __ ]
>> ain't it?
>> Do you remember we met in Birmingham in
a train station? It was funny, isn't it? >> Why?
>> Oh, that [ __ ] uh Storm added me on
Xbox. Yeah, she actually did add me. Did you? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, man.
What do you talk to? >> No,
>> there you go.
>> I said there you go. So, he's not even
in that place no more. He's popped off as well.
No, he end up [ __ ] up because of him bullying her.
>> I thought she
I thought she liked me.
AJ, she might have a lot going on at the
moment. She was homeless. Don't forget
>> she's skinn.
>> No, she was just obless
[ __ ] English people.
>> You were skint last month, isn't it? Obviously
skin. I'm always skimped. Yeah, I'm
proud to be skin.
>> I I am proud to be skinned. Completely
proud of it. I'm glad I'm glad I ain't got money.
>> I'm glad because when you got money,
forces you to do [ __ ] Go out drinking.
Make a [ __ ] off yourself. But going out
drinking is good, isn't it? It
>> depends, doesn't it? Really? That's m
>> Yeah. I want a football bet. So I went
out with you cuz I won a football bet in it.
>> It's not you.
>> Is what you used? >> Yeah.
>> Nice profit.
>> See the smart shots a t-shirt wear.
>> Money. What's the funniest video you've
seen of me with a woman? You've seen
quite a few, haven't you?
I don't care what women get with Pios [Music]
what you need to think only what you
need to think about is yourself really
>> not women.
What do you mean?
>> What do you What do I mean? It is stop
cold approaching and let a woman code
approach on you. I do. >> Yeah.
>> Cuz I won't go up to a woman with me. I
let women come to me. Not meaning
to me. You know what I'm saying?
>> You nasty plant. >> Yeah.
I'm getting a bath in a minute. I need
to wash my bollocks.
I'm writing your mom tonight, PG.
>> I'm joking, man.
>> What's your pictures, PG? Okay. Picture
of your dog.
>> He's so cute, isn't it?
>> No, it's a fat bastard.
>> Yeah, he got really fat, but he's cute.
The face is cute, is it?
I don't like them dogs.
>> You Everyone loves King.
>> No, I don't like them dogs in natural. >> Why?
>> [ __ ] ugly dogs and too small.
>> Oh, you dirty [ __ ] Not really.
>> Soon as I get myself sorted in my own
place and I know I can't get booted out.
I'm getting my old I'm getting a new dog
from a puppy. Not on middle day. I'm
getting one from Po. I know I'm not
getting rid of it, peeps. I have no
choice to get rid of diesel. I didn't
want to get rid of him in the first
place, but I had no choice to
do. I miss diesel, people. Yeah, I do
miss my dog. I do miss you.
>> I [ __ ] bring
>> Yeah, I'm not bothered about what they
do. Like, they can bring him up, but he
don't hurt me or affect me. That
[ __ ] that [ __ ] I'm not a girl who
will sit there and cry all of something.
I got rid of him. That's my fault.
>> Now I got
>> Well, that guilt doesn't bother me when
these people say, "I've got to live with
my guilt." But it doesn't bother me when
these people say, "Look at you. You got,
you know, good on myself. I needed to. I
need to give him a new arm cuz he didn't
have a [ __ ] arm."
Are you still alive?
>> Why did you have a [ __ ] video? >> Huh?
>> Yeah. Wow. Why bring up the broad video?
>> You liked it. Was it?
>> You've only got two people watching.
>> 24 people.
have come from shelf reflected Lord J's channel.
>> I want to know why Lord J won't meet me.
>> That's what I want to know. Yeah, meet
everybody else but not me.
It comes to you. You like You like the
[ __ ] video, ain't it?
>> No, I didn't like the [ __ ] video. >> Look,
>> we're going to get into mad.
>> One second. One second. One sec. One