[Music]
Just on some football bets, bro. [ __ ] [Music]
diab. Hopefully we get a
Double both both teams score no draw this time.
Eh probably not
though. Probably not that. No, no, no.
Yeah. If any of them win, I'll go out on
Saturday. If not, I won't. Obviously. [ __ ]
that. Don't know why, but I think this
has got a good
chance. Even though it kind of looks
like it doesn't, but I think that what does.
Yeah. Another 70 worth of
bets. Also attempted to play the
machine, but I never so
I just got some fish and [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. So if we win a football game,
we'll go out Saturday. If not, then no.
a week after realistically.
Yeah. Yeah, bro. I just done some
football bets, bro. I was [ __ ] bored.
I went to get some fish and chip [ __ ] I
just reduced 70 quid and just on some
football bets, bro. I'm [ __ ] bored as [ __ ] lad.
I didn't go on the machines, but I mean
at least it makes me not think about the
dating game for like over an
hour. I just done these two football
bets, bro. 70 worth. So,
uh, just reduced 70
quid. I'd say I was saving that, but
like yeah, I'm just sticking to football
bets, bro. I'm [ __ ] I'm bored as
[ __ ] Like, I'm bet, man. I just had
some fish and chips.
So hopefully any of these football bets
win then we'll go out Saturday. If not
then I'm not going
out crazy. My parents, my my parents
flew away. My parents flew away and left
pee and belly in the
nesticles. I love fish, mate. I love
everything. Now I've got double both
teams to score 50 returns 180 and a
double both to score no draw 20 returns
151. That' be nice if you got both of them in
it. But they're basically a 50/50 chance
of one of them winning.
Yeah, but obviously I start money that
like you're realistically probably going
to do football bets every week.
Realistically, you're probably going to
do them every week, bro. You die aboard
them. Yeah, I couldn't find him either.
You You get Bro, there's no there's
nothing in the cinema. Like, I swear to
God, bro. Like, I didn't play the
machines or nothing. I just only bet
because there's nothing in the cinema.
I'm [ __ ] bored, lad.
It's hard to save though,
Grezy. I think I've got about
1,700. It's not that bad, is
it? So, at least you're able to save something, is
it? It's better than nothing, is it?
It's still quite a
bit. Well, yeah, man.
But if we win one of these bets, we can
do stuff with the money and then, you
know, it rolls over and goes quickly.
You know what I'm
saying? You understand,
bro? Yeah. I can't save to save my life,
bro. I'm finding it hard. I was supposed
to save 1,500. Now I've got
1430. Oh, now I got 1430. But it's all
right, bro. We'll still have save. You
need the thing is you need to I got my
rid of my passport. All of my bills are
paid. So if you carry over some for the
next month, that's when it starts going
up. You need to get everything out the
way first and carry some over, you know,
and trust me, you'll you'll start seeing the difference,
bro. Then we just got to get through a
month. But obviously if one of these
football bets win
then So how long would it take you to
save to go to America? Greasy getting 750 a
month. How long will that take you?
music. Yeah, I'm in a wheelchair,
bro. Yeah. How' you know that?
It would take you grievy about what 8
months. Why did my mommy and daddy leave
me? Steven Howard, you got banned. Yeah. Under
Yeah. You'll never find that [ __ ] lad.
Never. Never, lad. [Music]
Them machines are a [ __ ] waste, lad.
You're not going to [ __ ] win anything
on them, are you?
Let's be real. You're not going to
[ __ ] win anything with them,
[ __ ] Did you actually lose that
pound? [ __ ] that, bro. Yeah, I last
Thursday. Yeah, I'm done with the machines. Me,
lad. Yeah, I got Swinden and South both
teams to score. on purch both teams to
Yeah. Does the dating
game? Yeah, he's got a mate with a cap
and a beard. There you go. You
remembered, huh? Does the dating game
get you? Does a date does a dating game
down? [ __ ] gets me [ __ ] down,
mate. Does it get you down, Steven
Howard? It [ __ ] gets me down,
mate. How something is rigged against
you no matter what you do or what you
try. That's a [ __ ] madness.
And there's nothing you can do about it.
I messaged that bartender today. She's gone quiet. Same
old same old mate. Same
[ __ ] It's actually rigged against men.
How mad is that? Like a woman can just
go out and get anyone she
wants. That's [ __ ]
bro. Yeah. Hopefully this football bet
wins. One of them.
Hopefully both of them. Yeah,
bro. Back to the old school Peter By days, isn't
it? We should bring it back to the old
school Peter belly days. E Steven Howard [Music]
gym football bets traveling. E, would
you like to see it back to the Peter By
days? That KFC earlier was [ __ ] nasty, lad.
It's actually going really disgusting,
bro. I know gambling's bad and that and
you shouldn't do it, but bro, I'm
[ __ ] balling out my [ __ ] head,
bro. Really boring out my [ __ ] head.
Like, I'm not even just using that as an
excuse, bro. Like, if I was trying to
[ __ ] waste money, I would have went
on them shims. I'm [ __ ] bored, bro.
You know that in the cinema is the only
cheapest thing you you bro. The reason
it wound me up [ __ ] the other day is
because I was so close to [ __ ] winning. But
like that's like the cheapest thing you
can do nowadays, bro. It's the [ __ ]
cinema and a [ __ ] football bet.
Nothing else is [ __ ] next to [ __ ] nothing, is it? You
know, cooking football bets traveling.
There you go.
D. That's old school peer belly.
E, would you like to see some Glasgow videos, Steven
Howard? Would you like to see some, eh?
Oh, I bet you would.
H, probably them Celtic [ __ ] banned
you. E, they [ __ ] banned you, did
they, the [ __ ]
bastards. Yeah, it's going to cost a lot
of money though. If I go for if I do it,
it's going to cost
like you're talking a good probably
about600. You're talking a good 600
[ __ ] quid, bro.
If I lose two
days. Yeah, you're talking you're
talking600. I'm not even
joking. That's a lot of it. That's enough.
Let's do this,
bro. A remember when Pig Betty goes out
and get kisses by himself. Steven
Howard, what a lovely
sight. All by myself, eh? You
crazy. I think I'm dying from all the
[ __ ] [ __ ] food I eat. I'm not even joking,
man. All the shitty [ __ ] food I eat,
guys. I help for ages, bro. That's why I
think I'm ill, you know.
Some London what? London, Turkey state.
Anyways, I'm going I need to [ __ ]
make myself a tea and [ __ ] So, I'll be
back later on. 100.