Get up there, Sunny.
Guess who won the football bet?
Wait, did I? Oh, yes, I did. Yeah, I
told you about them [ __ ] lower
leagues. That's how I used to win the [ __ ] Yeah.
Oh, I'm so happy, bro. I would have been
so [ __ ] A joke. I would have been so
[ __ ] if I didn't win that football bet, bro. Oh man.
Yeah, that's a lovely run. Lovely 380, isn't it? Yes.
That must have been the ones that I was
[ __ ] betting on before, isn't it?
Just make sure that's right. It is. Get
the [ __ ] up there.
I thought I'd never get over 300 pay out
on the [ __ ] football, but
[ __ ] finally I won a football bet, bro.
Yeah. 1380 from 120.
Just put 120 on it. 1380. So, not bad, is it?
Yes. Get the [ __ ] in there.
That's good, bro. I would have been
[ __ ] Otherwise, I would have actually been
not [ __ ] [ __ ] but I would have
almost been there, bro.
>> I would have almost been there, mate.
Trust me, I would have almost been there, bro.
Yeah, that football bet needed to come
in, bro. I would have been [ __ ]
would have been actually [ __ ] Yeah,
them them lower leagues, bro.
Them [ __ ] lower leagues, bro, is
where is where they're [ __ ] at, man.
I'm telling you.
Them lower leagues. Yeah. Is where it's
at. I swear to God, it's where it's at.
Literally, it is.
You get so many goals in like the first [ __ ] ping.
That's not a bad payout. [ __ ] 387, bro.
So, we must be up a lot from the football.
I should have just put the whole 160 on
the [ __ ] now, bro. Not 120. I should
have put the whole [ __ ] thing on it. Is it?
Yeah. Just hope that [ __ ] bet comes
in cuz we would have been [ __ ]
We would have had like £300 to our
[ __ ] name until next [ __ ] week. I
would have been [ __ ] bro.
I could actually touch. Yeah, I put 120
on the both teams to score, bro. It returned 387,
so just shy of £400. It's quite a good
win, is it really? But I lost 40
earlier, but I wish I just put the 160
on the [ __ ] thing.
So, yeah, it's good, bro. It brings us back up.
Happy [ __ ] days. I'm telling you that
that lower league, you know, the lower
league, that's where all the goals are.
Them northern leagues, they they cuz
they will just start scoring like all of
a sudden they'll just start scoring, bro.
Trust me, I would have been [ __ ] if I
didn't win, bro.
Like seriously, I would have been
[ __ ] Not [ __ ] like most people, but
you know what I mean?
I need to start doing some [ __ ] work
for next week, bro, or something.
Yeah, I'm still talking to that Finnish
one, but she's being a bit of a [ __ ]
Yeah, but she's being a tiny bit of a [ __ ] So, yeah,
I need to So, yeah, I must be up like
what, 5,600 from the football.
Must be in it.
Yeah, it must be.
Must be, bro. Must be in it. Yeah.
If you ever want to do both teams to
score, choose the [ __ ] national
leagues. They score like [ __ ] because
all the teams are [ __ ]
Yeah. All the teams are [ __ ] [ __ ]
aren't they? So
yeah, all the teams are proper [ __ ] So
it it was just like 2 minutes of the of
the of the other round. They all just started scoring. So yeah,
that's good. Is it?
I would have been [ __ ] Honestly, I
actually would have been completely [ __ ] bro.
I would have been completely [ __ ] mate.
It'd be like It'd be like the Virgin Boy
days all over again. E, Zippy. Nah.
No. I would have actually been [ __ ]
It's not even a joke. Yeah.
So, 100. What do we need? 100. So, we
lost 180 of that. So we must be up
like£600 with the football.
And man was like, "You best hope that
[ __ ] bet wins then, isn't it?" I said, "Yeah."
He said, "You best hope that bet wins."
It's true, though, isn't it? You best
hope that [ __ ] bet wins.
That's what he said, isn't it?
You best hope that [ __ ] He said, "You
best hope it wins then, or you'll be [ __ ]
Yeah, cuz we spent a lot of money on
[ __ ] Sunday, ain't it?
>> Sunday. We spent a lot of money, bro.
A lot of [ __ ] money, bro.
Now, obviously, we got the escort as well. So,
yeah, we spent a lot of money, matey.
Not even a joke. Yeah, man.
Do you reckon Virgin Boy will ever get laid, Nicolola? Like,
do you do you reckon Virgin Boy will
ever lose it?
Do you reckon Virgin Boy will ever lose it? Oh, nah.
What do you think?
Do you reckon Virgin by will ever lose it? Nah, mate.
Well, I won't be out this um this week.
Next week I will be week after maybe. I
need to start this work thing soon, bro.
I need to work. I need to uh start this
work thing soon, bro. Otherwise,
could be like LJ and Virgin Boy at some
point. Hopefully not, though.
Well, I don't think so.
My mom's birthday today as well.
How much did I have? Yeah. So, I'm
basically back to square one.
You know what would be such a good
feeling if you had £500 on both teams to
score? Say you had £500 on both teams to
score. Yeah. And you just [ __ ] And
you just won.
And you just won it whilst you were
pissed. Imagine you was getting pissed
up. Yeah. And you won it as you got pissed up.
That would be sick. As you got pissed.
So you had like six 700 pound on the
both teams to score. [ __ ] that.
Let's just hope they [ __ ] pay out
tomorrow, is it?
Yeah. Let's just hope the [ __ ] [ __ ] pay out.
Let's hope they [ __ ] pay out, mate. It
I [ __ ] smashed the P. They they they
[ __ ] They [ __ ]
They don't [ __ ] Do you remember that?
They ain't [ __ ] paying out.
They ain't [ __ ] paying out. Remember that?
They're at 150.
I'll say to the tenants of like you're
even more [ __ ] than I am. I'm [ __ ]
in the sense where I'm [ __ ] cuz I'm
[ __ ] to me but you're actually [ __ ]
No, you are actually [ __ ] Like you
work every week. You work every month
and you get paid and then you [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying? You get paid and [ __ ] um
you get paid and then you [ __ ] um
you get paid and then all your [ __ ]
money's [ __ ] spoken for. So you're
just [ __ ] again.
You know what I'm saying? You're
actually [ __ ] That's why I say to
him, you're actually [ __ ] You're
actually [ __ ] I'm [ __ ] but not
[ __ ] like you. Poor virgin boy in a
bedit with no money. But still, I am pretty [ __ ]
I'm still pretty fat.
You know what I'm saying?
I got [ __ ] Franklin coming out soon.
Yeah, [ __ ] Franklin coming out.
Yep, it came in. Lovely mate. Five. It
all come in on the five uh in the within
the five minutes of the second round.
It was nil nil one and one was what?
4-0. Then it was the second it was 5
minutes of the second half and then
[ __ ] all of a sudden they started scoring.
No returns 380.
380 from 120 which is more than triple
obviously what the bet is. So
yeah which is obviously triple what the
bet isn't it? So
which is good man.
So we're back to where we started.
That's good it man. [Music]
Bro if I didn't win it I would have been [ __ ] up.
Yeah, them them them [ __ ] uh lower
them lower leagues, bro, they score like
mad cuz they're all [ __ ] with [ __ ] but
they're all [ __ ] with [ __ ] defense.
But yeah, if it lost, I would have been um [ __ ]
Actually would have been [ __ ] bro. It
might It wouldn't even be funny.
>> Yeah, it's not even I would have been [ __ ]
Not bro, but I would have been just
[ __ ] So, yeah.
And like I said, it's not about money,
bro. I'm not going out this week regardless.
Yeah, I just won a football bet, but I'm
not going out.
[ __ ] that. I ain't going out, bro.
You know, one's 11 one and one's 41.
There you go. I give you some [ __ ] clues. So, yeah.
There you go. That's what the [ __ ] clues are.
I don't think I done too bad, you know,
the past two months, you know,
month or so,
considering how much [ __ ] I actually lost,
which was a lot of [ __ ] So
that's why I don't have anxiety. You see?
You see, that's why I don't have anxiety
cuz of um
I gave my mom some birthday money as well.
If you actually realize that, bro, it's
actually quite mad.
And then you also feel the financial
sting as well. You get financially stung
as well, which ain't good. And that
might take one or two or three months.
And one day you're just going to you
just get financially stung.
And it ain't [ __ ] good, man. You know,
I need to start this work thing soon as well.
It's one thing you don't want to be
worrying about is money. Whereas most
Well, most people do worry about money
though. Is it?
Most people do worry about money. It's
quite normal. It's the norm. But I don't
want to [ __ ] ever be worrying about money. So
now, why didn't the tenant reply back?
Because he knows I'm right.
cuz he knows.
Cuz he knows I'm [ __ ] right, bro.
Cuz he knows I'm [ __ ] right. What I'm saying? [Applause]
My [ __ ] is not your [ __ ]
That's like I said something they need to understand.
That's something they need to
understand. You know,
my [ __ ] is not their [ __ ]
So, how much have I lost on the
football? All in all, I think I've lost
180 on it.
I think we won like 300 on it. So,
so we won 380
on it, I think.
Yeah, we lost We lost three. Yeah. three50,
but we lost 180.
So yeah, up a lot.
But it's not a stable um
it's not a [ __ ] stable income though, is it?
Cuz what if you lose one time? You know
what I mean? Yeah.
Don't want to be worrying about money,
mate. That's one thing you don't want to
be worrying about.
Women and [ __ ] money. Could you
imagine that? No. Um,
I need to see if that pays and then if
they [ __ ] actually
Hey, cuz I saw some reviews saying how
they don't pay people their [ __ ] money
on that [ __ ] delivery thing. So,
let's hope they actually pay people money. Otherwise,
it's not good, is it?
What's the day tomorrow? Wednesday.
Nope. I tried, but I wouldn't play
online anymore either way.
So, I was still able to do my mom's
birthday. I was still able to go out,
still able to have my own money. So, I
think I done pretty good to be honest,
considering I've lost so much. You know
what I'm saying? So, yeah.
But I should have just put the 160 on
the bet, but I wanted to put 40 on the FBI.
So, still got all the stonies.
Still got all the stonies. Yep. They
need dry cleaning.
I think I need to go cinema on Thursday as well. Yeah.
I got all the stonies, bro. They [ __ ]
dry cleaning now, man. [ __ ] minutes for ages. So,
need to try and think of sort of other things
for money. Now,
like I said, I need to buy a thingy and
then try this job thing out. See if they actually pay.
At least I can chill now. Don't have to
worry about money. Don't have to worry
about that bet. No, I've got that money
coming. So, it's all good, man.
Out in two weeks.
Jobs are good. Yeah.
But I don't know why I say that's one
thing you don't want to be worried about
is money because most people worry about money.
So most people most people worry about money. [Music]
Well, I was You know what? This would be
Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ] This this league will be
good for a uh
this league will be good for a [ __ ]
both score no draw, bro. The amount of
goals you get on this league. This is
how I I must have always used to win
from this from the whole [ __ ] league thing.
It must have been from when I used to um
that's what it used to be. It's got to
be from that.
It must look how many [ __ ] both
teams. Bro, I'm telling you, you can get
you can get a treble both score no draw
on this league.
I'm telling you, you can. I'm [ __ ]
telling you you can, bro. If I don't
both score, no draw on this. You know
what? I'm going to do that next time.
Both score no draw.
I'm going to do a both score no draw on
this, bro. I swear to God.
I swear to God. I'm telling you, bro.
But this league has got so many goals on
it. It's the Northern National League.
If I put that 120 on a both score, no
draw, it would have been even more.
Yeah. I just want a football bet, Rich. Uh, Cory,
I put 120 on it and it returned 380.
So, kind of happy about that, bro. Yeah, them
right there. You can get a you can get a
both score, no draw on these kind of
matches, bro. Once you study these enough,
once you study these enough, I think you can.
And most of the time you get both got no
draw in the first half. Morin Darlington.
Yeah, they they definitely done it. hopefully. Yeah,
the one I was going to pick was 33.
Yeah, I'm going to go out.
I'm going to go out next week.
No, not Yeah, not this week. Next week.
Yeah, next week I'm going out, bro.
Yeah, next week I'm going out, bro. I'm
not going out this week. So yeah,
there's no point going out every [ __ ]
week, bro. What the [ __ ] You don't,
like I said, you don't enjoy it as much
if you go out every week. It's not about
the money. It was never about the money, bro.
Yeah, I won some extra money, Greasy.
So, Franklin will be well paid for.
Bless his little heart.
I'll put some of that towards the
[ __ ] Thailand as well.
Yeah, like I just woke up today and I
just it was my mom my mom's birthday. I
gave her some money or gave her some
and I just felt like doing something really daft
like you never you never get them type
where you just wake up and let me just
like put 120 on a football bet
or we drew 160 and then put [ __ ]
thingy on the [ __ ] football.
want to do this delivery thing soon,
man. I'm gonna do it maybe. [Music]
>> Yeah. One, bro. 380 from 120.
Quite decent. It's 20 off 400, man. It's
still [ __ ] stuff to [ __ ] go out
drinking, isn't it? Still decent, bro.
Yeah, just about [ __ ] one, bro.
It was all looking [ __ ] and then uh all
of a sudden they just started scoring.
That's what happens. They're mad. These
these leagues are mad, bro.
Yeah. Before I come in, I was just
thinking about how depressed depressing
it is now. It's hard to make money and
[ __ ] And yeah, you don't want to be
worrying about money. That's one thing.
You don't want to be worrying about [ __ ] money.
But everyone, most people worry about
money because most people here don't
even have money. Most people in the
country don't have money, but it's not
something you ever want to really be worrying about.
But I mean,
most people do. So most people don't.
It's like these the tenants were saying,
"Oh, you're [ __ ] You're fucked." I'm
[ __ ] but I'm not [ __ ] compared to you're [ __ ]
You're actually [ __ ] And the reason
you're actually [ __ ] is because the
reason you're actually [ __ ] is because
you work every month and
[ __ ] by the time you paid everything,
you got nothing left.
I'm just like
[ __ ] in a different way,
but still [ __ ] So, you know, like
um kind of think things, bro. Cuz
imagine that you live in a house. Yeah.
Imagine that you live in a house. So
you're used to the house.
You're used to the [ __ ] tenants.
You're used to the [ __ ] money. And
then you you move and you don't even get
that income anymore. That's madness,
bro. That's [ __ ] madness. That's
another thing I would have I think
people would have ended up killing themselves,
but they would have ended up killing
themselves over that as well, I reckon.
Probably the stress of that, but
yeah, not me, matey.
Not Peter Belly, matey.
Yeah, I told Antman like the struggles
and that and he was like, "Oh yeah, you
best hope that bet comes in then."
That's what he said. Um, Greasy, he
said, "Yeah, you best hope that bet
comes in then."
And I gave Laney £30 for her birthday. I
sent the car to her cuz I got 30 off the
escort. Obviously, I gave them 100.
So all this [ __ ] ain't [ __ ] um
I was just saying Grezy we done quite
good for the past few times we gone out
Birmingham won a football bet [ __ ]
went out again won a football bet so
it's not like we haven't tried you know
with the [ __ ] money that we [ __ ] won
what I'm saying we Yeah,
we [ __ ] have, mate. So, yeah.
So, yeah, I got my bag. Now I just need
a phone. Got the bag. Now I just need a
and then um see how much money you could
actually make on this delivery thing, isn't it? Um
you should be able to get a good enough
phone for 150 to work in it.
150 should get you a workable phone like
brand new just to do some [ __ ]
deliveries. What do you think,
Greavvesy? 150 200? It should be enough, isn't it?
This should be enough in it. The uh
200 maybe. So you got 200.
Obviously, you probably have to work the
week to get it back.
But I don't know if you work six hours a day.
I don't know. I don't really want to
work easy. I'm [ __ ] lazy, man. [ __ ] working, bro.
Imagine working. [ __ ] that, bro.
Yeah, this this country is trying to
kill us off. Greedy.
I like some burgers, bro. I went in the
supermarket. Most of the [ __ ] was off.
Them sup them supermarkets are going to
go bust soon, bro. They're trying to
kill us. I'm telling you. They're trying
to kill us off. They are
trying to kill us off.
Like, it's not even a [ __ ] joke.
They're trying to [ __ ] kill us off.
It's a madness. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Everybody knows that you're a
crazy [ __ ] Well,
>> I wish I stuck that extra 40 on the
football. That would have been like 450.
It would have been a lot better in it.
It would have been a lot better, mate.
But I'm happy anyways. Any money is
money in it. So
Franklin's coming out. Well, Franklin
doesn't come out until the 26th.
Yeah, Franklin doesn't come out till the 26th.
Is that cute?
I could have done with that extra 40 on it though.
[ __ ] 40 on it, bro. [ __ ] But yeah.
How much an extra 40? Probably. Yeah,
probably like 500 maybe.
What do you think of my um my my one of
my best friends? Well, one of my old
best friends dad. They didn't pay him
out in the bookies and he smashed the
shop up because they refused to pay out.
What do you think of that?
They refused to pay out. Griezy. [ __ ]
madness, isn't it?
They refused to pay out. Yeah, he
smashed the stuff up.
That's [ __ ] funny, is it?
Yeah, that's funny, bro.
they they refuse to pay out.
They refuse to pay out, Greezy. Oh [ __ ]
I don't know. I don't know the exacts,
Stewie, but I just know they refused to pay out
cuz him and the one of the workers, they
had a thing going on.
Yeah, they had a thing going on, didn't they? So yeah,
what the [ __ ] is finish is he doing, bro?
Yeah. Why is the tenant not replying back?
Is it cuz he knows he's [ __ ] Cuz he
knows what I'm saying is the [ __ ] truth, bro.
Cuz he knows what I'm saying is the [ __ ] truth.
still stalking me on Reddit, by the way. Yep.
They're still stalking me on [ __ ] Reddit.
These [ __ ] losers, man. Stalking me.
[ __ ] weirdo, isn't it? Anyways,
I'll be back