of [ __ ] sugar.
[ __ ] almost close to ending up like
the [ __ ] skin virgin [ __ ] bedit
[ __ ] yesterday, mate. [ __ ] We got
them [ __ ] girls.
You know what I'm saying? Oh [ __ ] I
forgot to uh open your message, Monty.
One second. My messenger.
Oh, you didn't even answer me.
[ __ ] hell, Monty. Man, why the [ __ ]
did you introduce me to that [ __ ]
skint virgin in a [ __ ] bedit? [ __ ] sake.
I could actually throttle you, you know.
I actually could. Can't believe you
introduced me. That [ __ ] skin virgin
with his skin shitty [ __ ] used
guitars. [ __ ] hell, man.
Honestly, what the [ __ ]
Nah, mate. I'm not the one that's got a
channel on him.
Yeah, lucky I won that football bet
yesterday, Nicolola. Couple more
outings, mate. I'd be like the [ __ ]
skint virgin if I done a couple more
than 400 pound outings, mate. I'd be
like that [ __ ] You have a day off of
YouTube. It's your life. I've had weeks
off of YouTube.
I'd have been if I went out a couple of
more times spending 400 pound. I'd be
like that skin virgin lad.
[ __ ] Why does this controller vibrate
like that? I'd actually be like that
[ __ ] skin [ __ ]
I'm saying that skin bastard. I mean,
I'd be like that skin bastard. [ __ ] hell.
But yeah, you have a day off of YouTube.
It's your life.
It's your [ __ ] life. YouTube's your
You sit on YouTube all day every day.
Don't [ __ ] turn me each other day off, lad.
Oh, you missed a football bet yesterday,
Steven. How would I done one? I put 120
on two teams. It would turn 387.
Yeah, one, man. The national uh North
League. I need to start doing them
leagues more often. Yeah,
mate. You're on YouTube right now.
You're on YouTube. Type it to me right
now. If you get a notification, ignore it.
Yeah, you missed out on this. Uh,
you missed out on this football bet,
mate. You're on my live right now. Get
off of YouTube. One second.
Bro, you're on YouTube right now. [ __ ]
going live. One second. I'm going to I'm
going to give Monty the link.
I spent about £400 [ __ ] Sunday,
you know? [ __ ] hell.
I don't want to be skinned like that
[ __ ] tent virgin. Skin virgin boy
with no money. You know what I'm saying?
All right, Nicolo, do you remember them days?
Do you remember them days?
Do you remember them days? Nicolo, show
me your the color your money virgin boy
and it used to kill him. Should we start
play that game again? Nah.
So, should we start owing them again
with the money game? Nah, I don't I I
don't show skin projecting people money.
If I went out about 10 more times
spending £400, I would be [ __ ] I
would have been [ __ ] skimp, mate.
It's [ __ ] obvious. If you don't all s
mate, you're on YouTube right now.
You're on YouTube typing. Get off of
YouTube. Live your life.
How can you say that? I'm like, you're
on YouTube now typing.
You are typing to me on YouTube.
You are on YouTube typing. Get off of YouTube.
Stop. Stop typing telling people they're
on YouTube. No, but you're typing to me,
so [ __ ] off. I know, but you're typing
to me, so [ __ ] off. That's even worse
that you're typing to me, you [ __ ] idiot.
Yeah, you're typing to me. That's even [ __ ] worse.
Get off of YouTube. Live your life.
This [ __ ] tea tastes [ __ ] awful.
You can't have [ __ ] tea without sugar.
Yeah. So, what's your opinion with that
uh Canadian Monty? I sent you a voice
note and I showed you it.
I think it's [ __ ] dodge, mate.
I think it's [ __ ] dodge.
I said to this guy on Instagram, "Yeah,
I'm going to go out in 3 weeks."
I'm going to go out in 3 weeks. He said,
"Why 3 weeks?" I said, "Why not 3 weeks?
Why would I go out to Why would I go out
this week? It's the same [ __ ]
Why would I go out this week? It's the same [ __ ]
bro. Stop saying welcome back. You
people can't even take a day off of
YouTube. I've gone on off I've gone off
of YouTube before for weeks.
You people can't even [ __ ]
take a [ __ ] day off of YouTube. Stop
talking about other people to finish Izzy.
I didn't [ __ ] it. I didn't [ __ ] it at all.
I think some people have actually got
brain damage. Grievy,
I say literally, I'm not going out for
two, three weeks. It's not about the
money. I just can't be bothered doing
it. And then they still [ __ ] tell you
to [ __ ] do it.
when I've literally said the reasons why
I'm not going out.
You know, I was I was going to do a
video about the cost of it. No, I didn't
[ __ ] it up with her. I'm talking to her. So
that's another thing you just
interrupted me is that uh I was thinking
of doing a video about the cost of this
all the cost of dating.
You know what I'm saying? Like it's even
it's actually the cost of it know like I
said I went out on Sunday I spent [ __ ]
yeah £400 I think I spent food and stuff
and whatever. So that's another thing
people don't take into consideration the
cost of it all you know
that's another Yeah that's another thing
people don't take into consideration the
cost of it all and the fact that most
people work in their [ __ ] skint as
well. So, how are they going to date
when they're [ __ ] when they got no
[ __ ] time and no [ __ ] money? But
hey, hell, that's another thing, is it?
The tenant never replied back to me. He
was like, "Oh, you're [ __ ] You're
fucked." I said, "You're more [ __ ] than anyone."
I said to him, "You're more [ __ ] than
anyone. You work every month and you
don't have 1020 your name. You're you're
more [ __ ] than I would ever be. And
then and then he didn't reply back.
Oh, I just put 120 on the bet and it
would turn 380.
So I said, "Actually, you're [ __ ] I'm
not [ __ ] [ __ ]
I've actually been doing all right the
past two months with money and [ __ ]
actually." So no, actually I'm not
[ __ ] Actually, you're [ __ ]
Let's get into it. You're the one that
doesn't have 20 [ __ ] pound at the end
of [ __ ] every [ __ ] month to even eat.
You know what I'm saying? Yeah. I had
160, but I put 40 on the roulette and I
just put 120 on the [ __ ]
um then I put 120 on No, I put 40 on the
roulette and I just put 120 on the
football. So, yeah, it's just over three
times the amount.
Yeah. You know what I was so mad J is
there was no goals and then as soon as
the second as soon as the second round
was they all started scoring.
One of the games was 3-0 and one of the
games was nil nil and as soon as it was
the second half within 5 minutes 1-1 4-1 [ __ ] madness
that's crazy. I'm going to bet on that
league from you know that that national
the national league. [ __ ] so many
goals. I should have done a both score
no draw. Oh, could you imagine I've done
a both score no draw cuz they were both
score no draws.
Yeah, it would have been good, isn't it?
So, anyways, you're coming up Monty.
What's What's your opinion on this uh
Canadian? Oh, I had a McDonald's at 3:00
in the morning, Grezy. I had a night I
had some nuggets.
Yeah, they're all [ __ ] They're all [ __ ]
with [ __ ] defense.
They're all [ __ ] with [ __ ] defense.
You had a McDonald at 3 in the morning. Yeah. So yeah,
we need to go cinema on Friday.
Yeah. I don't know what this guy means
by, oh, why 3 weeks? Why not three
weeks? What do you expect me to go out
every week or something? Why am I going
out every week? For what reason?
Going out every week for what [ __ ] reason?
I'm going Thailand
in November. You need to get off of
YouTube. You need to get off of YouTube.
No, I shouldn't be going out every two
days. Waste of time. Waste of money.
Have you got brain damage? I've
literally said I'm done in this country.
I went out on Sunday cuz I was bored.
There's no hope in this country.
I I I went out cuz I was bored, bro. I
hadn't been out for like two, three
weeks. I I'm not interested.
You are on YouTube. Get off of YouTube.
You know what? I'm going to help you get
off of YouTube.
There you go.
You're No, I'm good. Thanks. I'm going Thailand.
No, I'm good. I I'm going Thailand.
I'm all right, mate. I'm going Thailand,
I I I I found the solution,
you know. I found the [ __ ] solution. >> You
what you watching?
>> Just chilling, man.
>> Yeah, I'm just out at the moment. I
didn't join the chat straight away.
>> Yeah. So, what's going on with that
Canadian that I showed you?
>> I don't know.
No, but I told you. Is it?
>> I think he's playing games, mate.
>> What kind of games?
>> Been teasing you.
>> Yeah, but is it her in the pictures?
>> No, I don't think it is, you know.
>> But it is actually a woman though cuz I
was speaking to her like on the phone
and [ __ ] isn't it?
>> Oh, it might be. It might be.
You never know, is it?
>> Asking to send you some [ __ ] tip pics
and that [ __ ]
tip pictures. You're such
>> You're such a You're You're such a
beast. You are.
>> He's asking for a couple of [ __ ]
funny pics and that and then you find
out he's just real.
>> You're a beast, Monty.
>> A beast. >> Yeah,
>> I don't do beastiality.
I swear I could throttle you sometimes, you know. >> What?
>> I could throttle you sometimes.
>> You can't even throttle your knob.
>> No. [ __ ] introducing me to that
[ __ ] virgin. [ __ ] you, man.
>> I never introduced you to nobody,
>> you know.
>> So, stop blaming me for shy long legs. [Laughter]
>> I told you about him. I warned you about
him back on PlayStation. >> Yeah,
>> you you just stayed there and kept on
talking to him and saying, "No, he's
not. No, he's not."
>> You know?
>> Yeah. Cuz I Cuz I felt sorry for him. He
kept getting bullied.
>> Yeah. Cuz he's a [ __ ] N. A real N. Why?
>> You know,
must be hard being [ __ ] Bless him.
It's not hard being me. It's actually
lovely being me. It's [ __ ] amazing
This bastard gets ly.
>> What? What?
>> These people. >> Yeah.
>> Why are they saying that? Oh, you're on
YouTube. You're on YouTube when they're on YouTube. What?
They say to me, "Oh, you're on YouTube.
You're on YouTube." But they're on
>> Yeah, they watch you. They must have
your own [ __ ]
popups or they know when you're live straight away.
>> [ __ ] can't Monty can't get a job
because he can't read.
>> Well, it doesn't matter if we can read.
All right. I don't want to jog your disabled cult.
Why the [ __ ] I want to go work for you
disabled cult? Why you not work? >> Yeah,
actually. How do you know? I might be at work, peeps.
>> I can't believe these people are still
on YouTube. Monty,
>> I might be out working all day, peeps.
You don't know that. You don't know that, peeps.
Molly, these people can't get off it.
>> Yeah. No, please. Come work me. Look, not PJ.
Come out with me, PJ. I'm at work.
I'm at work here, lad.
I can't work.
I thought I don't work.
You reckon these people never get off
YouTube? DJ, they got live. You know
>> what you doing, PJ?
>> I'm just chilling, man.
>> Are you chilling? Yeah.
>> Yeah, man.
>> Yeah, I'm just at work. Me, PJ, just
doing some gardening in it.
Well, bless you then. You're doing some
like ruby dingy rapids in it.
>> Bless you then. PG.
What's this number?
>> I know. Nicolo. Uh, four years in
counting. I know.
>> Why don't you go?
>> Why do these people keep telling me to
go out and approach women when I've told
them I give up?
thinks they're pissing you. >> Monty, >> what?
>> Why do these people keep telling me to
go out and approach women when I said
I've given up?
>> Because these people can't approach with
women and they want you to embarrass
yourself by doing that. >> Really? [Laughter]
>> Yeah. I see you got a cold approaching. Yeah, true.
>> I sent them to get some videos up there.
I said to do some content.
>> I to prove that they work.
>> They can't cuz they don't work in it.
>> Yeah, that's clearly that. So there you go. Self reflectors all around.
>> I'll never know. Nicolo, do you remember
that? Now I'll never know.
>> Works. Did you know that? Yeah. >> Huh?
>> Nicola works.
>> Does he?
>> It's a girl. You [ __ ] Nicholas is a
girl's name. You prick.
>> Well, I don't know that.
>> If you don't know that, Nicola, right?
If you think about it. Yeah. Nick is a
boy's name. Yeah. Nick is a boy's name.
>> Nicola is a girl's name. Nicola. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. That's a girl's name. >> Mhm.
He's using a girl's name. So it's a boy.
>> It's weird, isn't it?
>> You like to get on the piss, isn't it?
>> I don't like drinking piss. No, like sour.
>> You like to get on the piss, don't it?
>> No, I like pissing in the toilet. PJ,
>> bless you then.
>> I like pissing in that toilet.
>> God bless.
Someone said that you've got the IQ of a sewer rat.
No, no, the IQ of a sewer rat. At least
I've got the IQ of a [ __ ] worm.
At least a series has got more brains on
the [ __ ] worm.
>> Oh no, they're still talking about that
[ __ ] teen dating app. What the [ __ ]
>> Yeah, that's teen dating app. Yo, peeps,
if you're obsessed with this tea dating
app, download it yourselves. Yeah.
Download it yourselves if you're so
obsessed with it. Yeah,
[ __ ] idiots in it. Tell them to
download it yourselves, PJ.
>> Yeah, download it yourselves
in it. You talk about it daily. You
might as well just download that [ __ ]
yourselves. Go on that [ __ ] yourselves,
please. Make sure
it tell you talk about it. Go on it,
peeps. Go on it. Not wrong with it,
peeps. Not wrong with it.
Why you always bring it up? So damn
[ __ ] is he? >> Yeah.
>> A [ __ ]
>> being a pedo. You know people, it's all
right to be a pedo in this community.
It's okay. Come out your shells, peeps.
Go and download it.
I think Virgin Boy needs to get laid.
>> What do you think, Steven Howard? I
think Virgin Boy needs to get laid.
>> I don't think he's ever going to lose it like that.
>> What do you think? I don't think he's
ever going to [ __ ] lose it. Me, Steven Howard.
>> Yeah. Congratulations. Diesel's dead. Ps
is [ __ ] dead. I give it to you.
>> Tell him I don't care about Diesel.
>> You know
>> why do they think I'm going to cry off my dog?
>> You idiots in it.
>> Yeah. They think I'm going to cry off my
dog when they bring him up.
>> Monty is disabled like that. Jesse
Well, you must be the disabled ones for
watching the the disabled through.
>> These are about This is a pretty great
disabled guys, isn't it? >> Yeah.
I say what's it like being a spaz, please? Yeah.
>> What's it like being a spaz?
Free pip, mate. Free pip. [ __ ] awesome.
>> You like these people?
>> I don't like these people. They just repeat.
>> [ __ ] is a nunch boys.
>> Man, you just need to stop talking about yourselves daily.
>> It's what you are. You talk you talk
about yourselves daily in this community daily.
Yeah. And I love how you people repeat yourselves
>> ain't it? >> What
>> I said and I love how these people repeat theirelves.
>> They always repeat themselves.
>> Yeah, of course they do. They bring
diesel up. They bring my kids up. I come
ask if I lost my kids my dog. I'm not
ask peeps. I'm a man who doesn't give a [ __ ]
I'm a man who has nothing.
>> Do you think Virgin Boy will ever lose it?
>> Lose what? Virginity.
>> Yeah. I don't think so, mate.
>> PG. Have you seen this community?
It's full of [ __ ] It's full of them.
>> It's full of them. >> Yeah.
>> Are you all right, mate?
I don't think Virgin Boy will ever lose
at me. What about you, G?
>> PJ, have off me, man.
>> Are we going up?
>> Yeah. PJ, why do they let yourself
reflect on theelves all the time?
I'm going as well. I need to talk to
someone on the phone. One sec.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Go on there.