[ __ ] hell. Skint virgin boy didn't [ __ ] reply.
That [ __ ] virgin boy could [ __ ]
strangle him sometimes, mate.
That skin virgin in a bed sit [ __ ]
strangle him sometimes.
Okay. So, there's quite a few. This must
be a popular movie then. Um,
there's quite a few of these on. [ __ ] hell.
I was actually expecting Virgin Boy to answer.
Do you know what I think you need to do,
Virgin Boy? Do you know what you need to
do, virgin boy? You need to literally
look in the mirror because no matter how
many times someone else does it to you
that you're not going to understand that
like you really really are the skin one,
you how many times did these people get
beaten at the money game?
Like you literally are skint absolute
skin flint. That is literally yourself.
your skin to the bedset. You have
nothing. For [ __ ] sake, it took you to
[ __ ] 30 to [ __ ] go, bro. That's
how skint you are. You got owned at the
money game god knows how many [ __ ]
times. You know what I'm saying, bro? Like one sec.
Yo, can you hear me now?
Yeah. So, that virgin, he really needs
to understand that he actually is the
skin one. I'm not the one in a [ __ ]
bed with [ __ ] £800 in my [ __ ]
name. You understand me? I'm not the
[ __ ] skint [ __ ] in a shitty bedit
going on cheap [ __ ] holidays.
You understand, bro? I'm I'm not I'm not
that [ __ ] You understand me?
I'm not some [ __ ] skin [ __ ] in a
bedit. You know what I'm saying, bro? He
is. He's definitely [ __ ] delusional.
He literally is sk than a skint flint.
Literally a skint bastard. Okay. If you
weren't skin Okay. Okay. Okay. Listen.
You know what? Let me One sec. I don't
know why it's bad. It might be connected
to my earphones or something. One second.
How about now?
Right. How about now?
Is it better now?
Right. If I If you're not skin, okay,
just answer me this question. Don't
answer it with a answer. Right. Yeah.
You're talking about yourself. You
asking. Yeah. Stop talking about
yourself. Okay. Okay. Just watch.
Right. If you are not skin, why did you
all run away when you kept being show
money over and over and over and over
and over and over again? Right. Let's
just say that I got that money with a
lighter. I got a lighter on that money.
Let's just say I got a lighter on that
money. Right. And I burnt all that
money. I literally burnt it. I didn't
even lose it. I burnt it. Why did you
all run away? Why did you all run away
not being able to show anything?
I'm going to give you I'm going to give
you a uh you know, a minute to answer
that. You know, really think about it.
Think about it, man.
Why did you all run away? If you have
all of this money and you're not all
skin, right? How comes every single time
you have been shown a couple of thousand
pounds you will run away? Even [ __ ]
£1,000 you run away. Answer that
question. That's a good question. I
think you know I think that's a
question. Why did you all run away?
It's because you people are skinned.
[ __ ] sake, bro. It's it's obvious.
It's cuz you people are the skinn ones.
It's because you people are the skinned
ones. It's [ __ ] obvious.
You know what I'm saying?
Why is that Joe not coming on my chat anymore? Anyways,
[ __ ] stupid little [ __ ] No, you
didn't show money. You didn't show
nowhere near as much money as I did.
Yep. Talking about yourself, Virgin boy.
You're the M that's with a disabled girl
on a bedit. That's exactly you. You are
the ski m stalking my sloppy seconds.
Yeah, you are the mint m on a 600lb
holiday. Yeah, that's you. Woo. Skint
[ __ ] in a bedsit with an ugly face with
a disabled girlfriend. Yeah, that's you.
Yeah, the ugly boy with an ugly fat
girlfriend who I made running to the police. Anyways,
answering your question. Um, no, you
didn't show more money.
No, that's yourself. Um, ugly boy. Um,
listen. No, you didn't show more money.
You had 18 months. Listen to me right
now. Yeah, you got shown money back when
I wasted my time. Just like when I
wasted my time meeting you people.
Nobody showed more money.
Nobody showed more money at all. No, you
[ __ ] did not. Yeah. And another thing
is, right, let's just say that Smokey B
showed more money. Okay. And let's just
say that Smokey B wasn't around then.
Let's give Smokey B the benefit of the
doubt. Okay. That still leaves Joe. That
still leaves Virgin Boy. That still
leaves LJ. Why did you all run away?
Don't answer it with a question cuz I
just I could have got the money and burnt it.
It's irrelevant. You know what I'm
saying? You got showed money and you
couldn't show nothing
multiple times as well. It was multiple times.
>> You know what I'm saying? So, it's like
this is why we don't waste our time when
you skip projectors anymore.
>> This this is exactly why we don't waste our time.
It's like that [ __ ] mic. I'm not
going to go to [ __ ] B. I'm not going
to go back to Birmingham. He can come to
London today if he's got a [ __ ]
problem. I was going to do a video on
him. You know, that that stupid little
[ __ ] [ __ ] But I thought, [ __ ] it.
You know, let him come on there. I'll
tell him he can come to London. I wish
he started doing all of this [ __ ] before
I went to Birmingham, you know. So,
and no, you didn't show money.
None of you showed money. The only one
that did was smoking me. So it just goes
to show that you are skin.
So that just goes to show that you
actually are the good ones then isn't it you know
think of it right it's even I was going
to do a video on that Joe right um
yesterday but then I just couldn't be
bothered cuz it's just a waste of my
time you know and it's like bro you
saying you got all of this money and
people are poor okay so why did you get
owned at the money game answer the
question don't sit there and say oh
where is it now no no no no no it was
there you got show money you all ran
away and it did happen more than one
times time for a long time. So, I mean,
just just pack it up and leave it now, you know?
Same thing as like when you start
arguments with people and it's not even
about money, you know? It's like, [ __ ] me, man.
It's It's weird. It's just weird. Yeah.
He's showing a pension. Yeah. Which is
he he doesn't even have access to that
pension. He doesn't even have access to that pension, right?
He doesn't even have access to it.
That's the funny thing about it. He
doesn't even have access to to a p to that pension, you know.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. Yeah. So,
it just goes to show that these people are skint
boy [ __ ] law J. If they really could
had money, they would have beat me at
the money game and they they did it then
and they still can't. You know, people
put the money in the back because they
were sick of keep showing you money and
you didn't show anything back. So
eventually it had to go in the bank and
then I also got backdated money which
had even more money that got put into my
bank account. I was like I'm not doing
it anymore cuz we know what you little
skin self reflectors do every time. You
call people skin, you get them to show
you money, they show you money, you run
away. It's a waste of everyone's time.
So it's it's it's the truth. You know
what I'm saying? Like that that that
virgin boy in a bedit is is the
definition of skin. Everything is skin
about you. Bedshit £700 to your [ __ ]
name. You know, you got absolutely
[ __ ] all. You ran away. You couldn't
beat the You could have beat me at the
money game. How the [ __ ] can that little
virgin try to call anyone's skin? He has
literally been living the Okay, listen.
Right. What the [ __ ] was this virgin boy
doing in 4 years? You know,
they don't have money. They're all
skins. Like, I'm on here, bro, cuz I'm
saving. I don't really go out and do
like the the [ __ ] approaching anymore
cuz I can't be bothered with it. But I'm
going out later.
I'm going to cinema and [ __ ] But bro,
like I'm on here cuz like I'm not really
doing much nowadays, you know?
Not cuz of lack of funds, you know? I
I've been living the life for [ __ ] 4
years. It's not lack of funds at all,
you know? It's just be [ __ ] bro. You know,
that's the whole point is that they
don't have money. None of these people
They ain't got money, mate. And a
pension is not money either. You can't
even I was saying exactly the same thing.
And I was just saying to if that Joe has
got all of this money, why did he run
away when I when I showed him money?
You know, and I'm going to keep bringing
it up because I know you like to forget
it happened, but it did happen.
It happened quite a few times,
you know. Even like Virgin Boy, he
couldn't show anything.
This skin [ __ ] in a bed sit with a few
shitty guitars couldn't show anything.
What the [ __ ] bro? I used to say,
"Virgin boy, get your money out." And he
had nothing. He had [ __ ] all. So now
when he tries to show me a shitty
£1,000, I laugh at him. I was like,
"Okay, buddy. It's funny, you know, like
you just laugh at it, bro.
You just laugh at it. These people truly
have nothing in their life. They truly
have [ __ ] all, you know? It goes to show
like they have to come on [ __ ]
YouTube every day, [ __ ]
people that they don't know, that they
will never know, that they've not met,
that they'll never meet, you know? They
got [ __ ] all. They got nobody sat on
YouTube with [ __ ] low life every day.
Come on, man.
It's [ __ ] weird, isn't it, bro? It is [ __ ] weird.
I'm going picture soon.
I'm going to good old pictures soon.
You can't beat going to the pictures,
can you, boss?
Maybe I could have on my bed and turn over.
Yeah, these people, bro. These [ __ ]
people on here, man. [ __ ] weirdos.
If they had a lot of money, they
wouldn't be there all day, every day.
Unless they're saving for something. I
mean, they they could be saving for
something, but I doubt it.
They ain't got no money, mate. If they
had money, they would have beat me ago.
And let's just say Smokey B has beat me.
Okay. And he didn't see my [ __ ] Okay.
So, that's one person. What about all of
these other people?
You know what I'm saying? What about the
skinned virgin in the bed [ __ ] that
couldn't show the early 50s? You know,
we wasted our time with you numerous times,
you know, [ __ ] trying to say you've
got 14 grand. You've never had 40 grand
in your skitt little bedset. In that
skit shitty little bedset, you're trying
to say that you've had 40 grand in your
shitty little bedset. [ __ ] out of here,
mate. That's a [ __ ] comedy sketch.
What in that exit? [ __ ] [Applause]
But yeah, they're [ __ ] Um, self-reflectors.
That's all they are.
You know me with horror films, mate. As
soon as horror film comes out, have to
be in the cinema. Can't wait. Oh man.
Yeah, I'm going to watch this horror
film in a minute.
I need to leave soon.
Yeah, I kind of have to leave at 10:2. What's that?
Yeah, it must be quite popular cuz
there's a lot of there's a lot of
showing just like when Stitch was on.
Just like when Stitch was on Yeah.
I should spray my after shave on me.
some sage after shave, but I want to try
to save it, you know.
Just going to get like pick a mix and some popcorn.
Virgin boy would never have a million.
He'll need a million to get that shitty
[ __ ] Kent bed suit.
That [ __ ] [ __ ] in Kent with [ __ ]
700 quid to his name. [ __ ] virgin.
>> You know what? I don't understand this
whole money thing, bro. Why do these
people come on here like they've got
money when they literally have nothing?
I don't understand to be honest.
You I could go out today and spend 150
on a drink and have a good night, you
know, grieves. I could actually go out
today and have a good night if I wanted to.
You understand what I'm saying, mate?
These people are obsessed for people
that don't even
leave the house. They don't even do
anything. And all they do do is talk about money.
You not think that's [ __ ] madness.
I'm going to leave at 10 to you.
I'd like to get this out the way.
Yeah. I'm going to cook myself some
chicken today. Greasy.
I can't keep these uh
I can't keep it up with these takeaways,
bro. cuz uh
they're expensive and I want to become fat. So yeah,
see if I was thinking, oh, should I
spend £23 on a takeaway or should I just
spend it on a few beers? And I thought
I'm not going to go out for a while now,
so just spend it on what we have to do
now. Greavves, you know.
Yeah, you save money as well. But
obviously I'm not going out for a little
bit like that. So I could actually go
out today if I wanted to. I'm home
alone, you know, got nothing to do. So
but no, I can't be asked.
I'd rather go pictures
and tomorrow probably to go for a walk. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
It's expensive, is it, bro?
This guy was like, "Oh, bless you. up, bro.
Bless you. If you're going to start
cooking in Bengal Bless you.
To be honest, I'll probably go in 5
minutes. Yeah. So yeah,