You know what, bro? Yeah, I'm so tempted
to get my [ __ ] self involved with
this whole [ __ ] Timmy and Monty thing,
you know, cuz of that [ __ ] [ __ ] mic. But
I don't know, bro. Like, we all know
what these people do on here, is it?
Waste of time, waste of money. We all
know what they do on here. Lose and act
like they've won. You know what I'm
saying? Like, that's that's the only
thing that puts me off, you know?
You know what I'm saying, bro?
And another thing, I don't know why he's
still doing call out videos when when we
was there, he wasn't anywhere to be seen.
You know what I'm saying?
Straight in hell, bro.
[ __ ] madness, bro. It's just annoying
me, bro. Watching it. Just watching that
annoys me. I swear to God it does.
You know what I mean? Why don't you come
to London, Timmy? Timmy and Michael,
come to London. I'll meet you anywhere.
Anywhere in London. Might as well. [ __ ] it.
You might as well. [ __ ] it. Bring
whoever you want. You might as well, man.
Yeah, Timmy, man. Come to London
tomorrow. What day is tomorrow?
Saturday. Come to London tomorrow with
your [ __ ] [ __ ] friend Mike and
I'll meet you anywhere. Anywhere you
are. Just [ __ ] annoying watching that [ __ ] bro. You know,
I swear it's annoying, bro. It is actually annoying.
You know, come to London.
Come to London. Please come to London,
man. Come on. I already went to
Birmingham. You was nowhere to be seen
when you being called the [ __ ] out God
knows how many [ __ ] times. You know
what I'm saying? Bring your [ __ ]
[ __ ] friend Mike as well and see what
I do to both of you, bro. [ __ ]
winding me up just watching it, bro. I
swear down. Yeah.
Swear to God, it's annoying, bro. I
swear to God it is.
Come to London. Please, man. Please come
to London. I'm not [ __ ] wasting my
time going to Birmingham. You know, I
already done that. You was nowhere to be
seen as usual like all of you little mongos.
Just stop doing videos, man.
[ __ ] hell. It's annoying, bro.
Come to London TV with Michael. Yeah,
I don't like snakes.
You know, any opportunity I've got to
[ __ ] get them, bro, I will do it. Yeah,
come to London. You can even call LT if
you want cuz I know he's going to try
and get involved. I'm not asked. Simple. Yeah.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] That prick [ __ ]
annoys me, bro. That's why I blocked
him. Yeah, I was civil cuz, you know, he
didn't say anything. But then when I
caught him [ __ ] being a little snaky
little [ __ ] just come to London
tomorrow. I will meet you anywhere. More
street [ __ ] you know what I mean?
Know what I'm saying?
Simple, bro. I want you and Mike to come
here tomorrow. I'll meet you anywhere.
Mar Street. Sorry, not um Yeah, what's
the one called again? My bone. Sorry. Miley Bone.
You know what I'm saying? Molly Bone.
You know what I'm saying? You're outside my mom's.
Really? Well, I don't live in my mom, so
tough chart to that one. Yeah. Okay. So listen,
come to London tomorrow, you and
Michael, to me. Yeah,
please. And stop this whole YouTube [ __ ]
Oh, will you? Okay, you go do that then,
you keyboard warrior. Yeah. Bye-bye now. [ __ ] right?
Put it We'll go Uh, bye-bye. Boring.
People that have actually got to do
stuff just does it. They don't [ __ ] write stuff. Boring.
Get blocked again, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
Right, I'm going to do a I'm going to do
a video to Timmy, bro,
cuz this is actually annoying me now.
You know, cuz I don't like that [ __ ]
Michael, bro. Come to London. I'll meet
you anywhere, bro. Anywhere you want.
You know, you ain't got no excuse. You
know, last time you come, I met you. I
mean, you can't even use you can't even
use an excuse anymore, you know.
I'm not even sticking up for Monty, you
know, to be honest. I'm not sticking up,
but it's just annoying, you know, just watching it.
Yeah, it's just annoying watching it.
Just come to Just come tomorrow, bro.
[ __ ] this. I'm doing a video now, bro.
They [ __ ] pissing me off, bro. [ __ ] this.
Yeah, bro. I'm just doing I'm doing a
video to Timmy, bro. One sec.
Cuz I don't like that [ __ ] money mic,
bro. And I don't like him. So, I just
done a video. I told I'm I'm telling
him, "Come to London tomorrow. I'll meet
you anywhere, bro. I'll meet them
anywhere they want.
Yeah, let me do it. I just got done a
video, but let me upload it, bro.
Yeah, it's not even funny, bro. It's
annoying. You know, I was so close today
to going to Birmingham. You know that? I
was so close to going back up there,
bro. I swear to God and calling that
[ __ ] [ __ ] mic out, bro. You don't
even know, bro. It annoys me, bro. That
snaky [ __ ] And you know the only reason
I didn't do it, bro, is because like we
know what they're like, is it? You know,
you waste your time, you waste your
money. You go up there, they don't meet
you, and then they pretend they've won.
You know, they've done it three, four
times now. You know what I'm saying? So,
so I'm just doing a video. I'm uploading
it now. Bro, I want them to come to
London tomorrow. Bro, stop this back and
forth [ __ ] with Monty, mate. You was
nowhere to be seen when we called you
out when we was last in Birmingham.
Yeah, I was in Birmingham. I didn't call
my cat when I was in Birmingham cuz I
didn't know he was doing this [ __ ] until
[ __ ] recently. Otherwise, I would
have called him out as well.
What's his channel again? That money mike.
[ __ ] think you're going to snake me
behind my back, you silly little [ __ ]
[ __ ] I'll pay for your [ __ ] train
tickets if you want. And what are they
going to say? Oh, you're going to hide.
They can't even say that, bro. Because
when they come here, I met them. So, how
can I hide? You know what I mean?
No, it's not funny, bro. It's annoying.
It's not even funny, bro. It's annoying,
bro. Just watching it is annoying. You know, [ __ ] madness.
That's one thing I don't like is these
snakes. Hate it, bro. Can't stand it.
I can't stand it, mate.
I hate it, bro. You don't understand. I
hate it, man. You know, if someone's got
something to say and they say it, okay,
they say it, bro. I hate it, bro. When
you go on someone else's chat, bro.
Yeah. And you see these stupid little
[ __ ] [ __ ] that lick your ass, try
and [ __ ] talk [ __ ] about you, bro.
You don't understand. It's annoying,
bro. And it's the way they do it as well.
You know what I mean? There you go. I
just done a video to him. It's uploaded
now. It's annoying as [ __ ] bro. You
know, I've caught a few of them doing
it. Why do you think that Joe F don't
come on my channel anymore? The [ __ ]
[ __ ] The [ __ ] old man, you know,
and at the end of the day, bro, if this
was two if this was two years ago, I
would have went today. I swear to God, I
was so close, bro. But like I said, the
only thing that stopped me going is cuz
I know what happens when you go. A wise
man learns from his mistakes. With Mark
Samson, with Bomb, with Virgin Boy, you
all do the same [ __ ] So, at the end of
the day, bro, if you if you want to come
tomorrow, I'll pay for your train fair.
It's not a problem.
And [ __ ] Monty. I don't even give a [ __ ]
about Monty anymore. I don't give a [ __ ]
about him, you know? It's not because I
even like Monty. It's just because they
they're annoying me. You know what I'm saying?
It's annoying, bro.
I hate them, bro. I swear to God, I hate them.
Like, you come here with Tiger, I'll
come here with Money, Mike. Come here
with Money Mike, bro. I could beat them
both. That's how bad it is. But if
they're not coming, then I ain't going
to them. No way, bro. My traveling days
are done with these people on here.
Been there, done it, worn the t-shirt.
[ __ ] annoying. It is.
It is annoying, bro. It is annoying, lad.
And then they don't come back on it. So
they slate. They talk [ __ ] Yeah. And
then when you call them out for it,
they're nowhere to be seen.
Yeah, let him talk about me, bro. You
can do a [ __ ] video. Listen, bro. One sec.
Yeah. Defeat me, bro. That
you know what I'm saying? [ __ ] [ __ ]
Tell him to put the link up.
Tell him Tell him to put the link up,
bro. Tell him to put the link up. [Laughter]
Listen. Tell him Tell him to put the link up. Yeah.
Tell him to put the link up, bro. [Laughter] [Music] Hold on.
Tell them to put the link up.
Oh, big no. Same repeating. Fat ugly people.
Oh, here we go. The repeating. [Laughter] [Music] Yep.
Is he putting the link up or no? Nah.
Tell him to put the link up.
There you go.
See what I mean? He has to talk over
people. You see what I mean, bro? He's
talking all hard and that. Yeah, but
when I was in Birmingham, he didn't meet
me or Monty. So why is he
Mark Samson? This Mark, Listen, this
Timmy, right? He's another Mark Samson.
Yeah. He's all the mouth over a
keyboard, bro. I was in Birmingham with
Monty. Yeah. And he was online and he
didn't do anything. He ain't about
nothing. He's a waffler. He's another
Mark Samson. That's all he is. He's
another Mark Samson.
Yeah. Now that [ __ ] Money Minim to
come to London tomorrow
about kill me. How could he kill me,
bro? He He didn't even lay a finger on me.
He didn't even lay a finger on me. The
[ __ ] idiot. He didn't even [ __ ]
lay one finger on me, bro. What the
[ __ ] All he does is talk over people.
He's a [ __ ] Mong. He's another Mark
Samson. That's what he is. [Music]
You know what I mean?
See what I mean?
Oh, it's Timmy Eldridge.
Um, this fruit mad world.
There he is.
He's little self-reflectors again. PJ
know women know nothing. That's story of
their lives. That's why they're sat on
YouTube every day. These old men
because they are skint
with nothing talking about themselves again.
Bro, these people need to really stop
putting themselves down.
These people really need to stop putting
themselves down, bro.
I'm starting to actually feel bad for them
talking about themselves like that.
And all he does is talk over people
because he knows I'm right. Shouting
over people, bro, at [ __ ] 9:30 at night.
Ted, come to London tomorrow. I'll pay
for your [ __ ] train fair. What the
See what I mean? They're [ __ ] mongos, bro.
talking. Why is he shouting like that, man? Yeah. Here we go Another Mark Samson.
He's another Mark Samson. He's ended it
again. He's another Mark Samson. But
He's another M Samson.
See what I mean, bro? He keeps kicking
me. He keeps kicking me. This is what I mean, bro.
I'm saying, bro, this is exactly what
I'm talking about.
I am talking about bro.
Waste of my time. He's another Mark Samson.
He's another Mark Samson. Little chicken
[ __ ] That's what he is.
Another one that got called out and then
ran away. But again, apparently that
never happened. exactly why we don't
waste our time on you people anymore.
This is exactly why we don't waste our
time traveling to you people anymore.
Cuz you're all the [ __ ] same. Every
single person that tries to [ __ ] call
people out, you're all the [ __ ] same.
[ __ ] off, man.
You're all the same.
Yeah, you would beat PJ and you and Mike
together. He has no chance. Okay. Well,
then come to London then. If that's the
case, then come to London. I'll meet you
anywhere in London. I'll even pay your
train fair if you want.
You know what I'm saying, bro? He's
another He's another little weasel.
He's another little [ __ ] weasel
just like Mark Samson. Yeah. [ __ ]
See what I'm in? H.
Why did you get build this shitty community, bro?
Well, let me go on that money channel. One sec.
Where's his channel again?
Pull on that Jo.
get disabled as [ __ ] bro. I swear to
God, these people are disabled.
Yeah, it just says ended every time you
try to join it.
Yeah, I can't be [ __ ] I'm going to
bed, bro. It's [ __ ] ridiculous,