Yeah, this is my um last [ __ ]
live stream on this [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] community.
Yeah, like it needs to it comes to a
point where you need to um
leave the mongos to it. Yeah.
Leave the mongos to it.
Comes a point where that happens. You know,
it's a [ __ ] place full of self-reflectors. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, I done a football bet today. I
only put 30 pound on it though. Both
teams got no draw, returned to 190,
which I thought, no, let me just do a
little one cuz I don't need money, but
it's just for fun, you know, cuz I'm not
going out today. If I needed money, I
would have put like one [ __ ] 601 170
on it. But yeah, I don't need
loads of money. So yeah, just a bit of
fun, you know? 30 versus
[ __ ] how much? Know what I'm saying? Versus
[ __ ] 200 going out on the piss.
I think it'd say go out, send it.
If it wins, nah. Nah, Grezy. No, at all,
mate. My Black Ops 2 game, the thing
come out for it, by the way. I paid it.
So, yeah. Nah. Nah, mate.
Nah, bro. Maybe
next week. No, I literally do it every
like 3 weeks. Time [ __ ] flies, don't it, Grezy?
Yeah. I just
I was speaking to Antman about this.
Yeah. And he was saying that, oh, like
if he was here, he'd still go out
because he'd have hope and
t and I said I said to I don't see it
that way. I don't see it as there's hope
in this country. I know there is no
hope. I go out cuz I'm bored. When I
don't go when I go out every 3 weeks,
it's cuz I'm so bored. It's better than
doing nothing. I generally don't have no
hope. Like look, I won that football bet. Um,
you know, the other day, you know, I've
got money. I could easily go out. You
know, the I could easily go out, get on
the piss, watch the football, wait for
the football bet to hopefully win. But I
have no hope in this country. So, yeah,
I I think me and him see it a bit
different. There is no hope in this country.
When you've done it as many times as I
have, you know there's no hope.
There's not even anything telling you
anymore there is. That's how you know
you're you have you've completely lost hope. Um
and to be honest with you, I feel like
even if I wasn't going on holiday and I
needed to save, I still feel like I
still wouldn't go out.
Nah, cuz there is just
But like I said, that's what happens
when you've tried more than anyone in
the world. I guess that's why people can't relate.
All right, Grevy, you know that [ __ ] is
such a narcissist. You know you want to
talk about narcissists, right? Right. Do
you want to know who the biggest
narcissist on here is?
I'll tell you.
I I'll tell you a perfect example of narcissism.
It's common with people with um autism.
Since you like the word um narcissism,
since you like that word,
I I can tell you who the biggest
narcissist is. If you want Yeah.
My [ __ ] was AI that [ __ ] whole time,
bro. I didn't even know
to be fair.
Yeah. No one cares what these self projectors say.
No one cares what these fat ugly
projectors say. No one cares. They're
nobodyies. No one cares what they say.
These fat ugly self projectors.
Yeah. No, no one cares what they say,
you know? They're just little
self-reflecting 40 odd year old losers.
They ain't got a life. No one cares
about them. This is exactly why I'm
coming off this [ __ ] Waste of time. and
waste a [ __ ] life.
No one cares what these fat, ugly life
losers that don't fit in society say. No
one cares about them. You know,
you know, like I've said a million times
before, you've been shown money, you've
been shown women, you've took many L's,
and you just lie to yourself. Part of
reason why I'm coming off this [ __ ] you
know, like it's it's pathetic. Like, do
you know how much I had to hold myself
yesterday not going to Birmingham and
calling that fat [ __ ] out without money
mic? But then I realized, you know,
exactly how the how the uh chocolate
chip cookie crumbles every single time
you do this stuff. You know, you got a
history showing these people money, them
running away, um going to Mark Samson's
area. You know, we've got a history with
this now with these little mongos on
here. and then you get to a point and
you feel like there's just no point
wasting your time, your energy, um you
know, even your money if you're thinking
about going there, you know. So, yeah,
just leave these fat, ugly, 40-year-old
self-reflectors to throw at people that
they don't know every day cuz that's all
they've got. That's all they've got in
their sad rejecting [ __ ] lives. You know,
cuz you got to understand it comes to a
point where these people on there, they
don't like you cuz you're not fat like
them. You're not ugly like them. You're
better looking than them. You have a
life unlike them. So, they just like
you. Have you not Have you not
understood? Like the people on here,
right, they're all the people that get
on and speak to each other, they're all
alike. Fat, ugly, no life, anxiety
ridden, spasticated, you know, and any
anyone that comes along younger than
them, better looking than them, better
life than them, they just dislike pe
people like that. So they never ever
leave they will never ever leave you alone.
Um, and that's it. Yeah,
that's the way it is. So,
hope this football bet wins, boss.
Be nice. I don't need it to win, but
it's fun if it does.
I was thinking of putting 160 on both
teams to score, but I like nah. No point.
Don't lead it.
I've literally said about a million
times I'm not going out for like 3
weeks. Have you got Have you got memory problems?
I literally said that I've lost hope in
this country and I don't go out unless
I'm very bored. You seem to have forgot
about that. So,
I don't know, man. Each their own.
Even if the bet wins or it doesn't win,
I'm not going out. I don't need a bet to
win. I have money, but I just don't want
to go out and waste money here.
The thought of it makes me tired.
The thought of it makes me so tired.
Going out, drinking, approaching. It's so exhausting.
It's such [ __ ] as well. Uh,
I've dealt with enough [ __ ] with these
[ __ ] for so many years, you know?
Got a nice McDonald's coke.
That would [ __ ] enough
over the [ __ ] years. So yeah. So yeah,
but there is no hope.
There is no hope here. No.
Oh, my bones are [ __ ] man. King after
they're not even worth wasting your time
on anymore. You know, Virgin Boy, you
know, [ __ ] M. They're just not worth
it. They're not worth the time a day.
Let them be obsessed low life skin goes
on YouTube every day of their life.
Please jealous of something.
Won't get into that. Yeah.
What I find funny is how these people in
here think they've got room
to talk about anyone else
when they're sat at home every day in
their [ __ ] 40s. Old wrinkly men, old
farts don't leave the house. Never seen
a woman naked and they think they can
try and [ __ ] talk about you. That's
what makes me laugh, you know?
That's what makes me laugh, mate.
Though they can sit there and try to
talk about [ __ ] you and they don't
even know you. They don't [ __ ] know
you. They've never met you. You're
[ __ ] probably half somebody's agent,
their ages. You know what I'm saying?
And like I said, two years ago, maybe
two and a half years ago, if I didn't
know what this was about, you know, I'd
call that Joe F out. I'd call I'd go to
Birmingham and call that Money Mic out.
But we all know how the chocolate chip
cookie from Subway crumbles. We all know
what you people do now. You know, you
take L's, but you never admit the L's
that you take because, like I said, if
you're not fat and ugly like these
people, they get jealous of you. This is
this is what happens. And then when they
don't when they're jealous, what they
do? They don't like you. So,
yeah, I know. I don't even bother going
out anymore, bro. I'm not going out
today. I don't a football bet. Um,
a little one, but I I'm not going out,
bro. I can't be bothered. I'd rather
just chill. There's no point going out.
I just go I I only go out when I'm like completely bored.
Like when I'm out of this world board,
like if I'm not been out for like three
weeks or otherwise I don't even I don't
go out, bro.
It's not even about the money. I have money,
you know? I can go out. I can go out in
the piss today, tomorrow, next day if I
wanted to. Just Yeah. Like I said, when
you lose hope, you lose hope.
And it doesn't come back after you lose hope. So,
um, so yeah,
I got I put 30 on a both score, no draw. So So
yeah, there's just no point cuz I could
tell you exactly what would happen. You
go out, you hear, "I've got a
boyfriend." And you you have people give
you attitude. You get numbers that [ __ ]
you around. I know how the cookie the
chocolate chip cookie from Subway
crumbles. So when you know, why would
you even try?
Like that's just real. That's not even
being negative. That is actually real, bro.
I don't bet on international football,
but you get my [ __ ] point, you know?
Yeah, I put 120 I I put £120 on the
football bet on Tuesday and I got back
380. So, I was happy with that.
And yeah, I'm up on the football the
past two months,
but I only really bet when I need like
the extra money, so on it.
I can go out whenever I want, bro. You know,
you know what I mean? Um,
but yeah, there's there'd be no point in
going out today
cuz it's always the same old, you know. So,
Because Colin, put it this way, right?
If it's not changed then, why will it change now?
How will it change now? You know what
I'm saying? If it hasn't changed then,
how is it going to change? How will it change now?
That's the way I see it.
That's not you. Go away. I mean,
I think I'm uh
I think I'm right with that, Colin. What
do you think?
I will go out again cuz it's fun as [ __ ] but
I go out when I'm bored,
you know? I go out cuz I'm bored as
[ __ ] not cuz I think I'm going to pull
or I'm going to meet someone.
Cuz the thing the problem is, yeah, is
that like, yeah, you know, people can
sit there and say what the, you know,
how the future, you don't know what the
future holds and no no, but the problem
is is like even when I lost that house,
right, I'm still okay with money. Won a
couple of bets. Something else is
probably going to come up very soon or
who the [ __ ] knows what's going to
happen. No one knows. But I feel like if
anything was going to change with the
women, it would have already changed
because God knows how how many times
you've gone out. God knows how much
money you've spent. God knows how many
like it would have changed. Like what
would make today so different than all
the other times.
And not to mention the fact that I've
not been on a date for like maybe 3 4
months. So it's not even like there's
been any leadups. There's been nothing.
There's been literally [ __ ] all. Like
it's not even been like you've been on a
date and then you [ __ ] it up or you
know you get a date every month you get
nothing. So like why would today be any different?
Like it wouldn't be any different. You
know I've got so many numbers on my
phone you know since I got my phone
stolen and I bought a new one and all it
is is time wastings kiss takers. It's
just the same old [ __ ] You know, I'm
I'm I'm now like I'm just speaking to
people online and if anyone's like
interested, I'll just go to them, you
know, wherever they live. Canada,
[ __ ] America, I don't give a [ __ ]
you know? I feel like, okay, well, we've
not tried that before. Let's try that.
It's just not It's just not going to change.
You go out cuz you're [ __ ] bored out your head.
Whereas it used to be I used to go out
because I actually thought I was going
to meet someone.
I just don't know how anyone can have
hope after all them experiences. But yeah,
I'm surprised I had hope for so long.
And like I said, that's what I was
saying to Antman. I said, but here's the
thing. Yeah. Is that I have no hope.
Like I know what you're saying about
like okay well you go out every week
because if you don't have hope but if
you don't have hope then you don't have
hope. Like I don't have hope. Well I
don't waste my time.
I don't waste my time. I don't waste my [ __ ]
waste my time. Waste my um Yeah.
That's why I won a 30 football bet today cuz
what else is there to do, you know?
No, no, no, no. Shoot. zil, bro.
I didn't go to bed yesterday until 6:00
in the [ __ ] morning. I about to put
my bed in in the wash. Just [ __ ] granari, bro. [ __ ] granari. So, yeah,
I ain't done both teams to score for a while. Yeah.
So yeah, that's how I see it, bro. Really?
Hey, do you want to know who's a
narcissist? Squeezy, I tell you who's a
narcissist since you like that word narcissist.
Yeah. Yeah. I had loads of wanks in it
yesterday. I was speaking to someone on Instagram. Um
yeah, I was uh do you want to know who's a narcissist?
I could tell you who's a narcissist if you want.
I'll say this to you, but you left. So,
this little virgin, right, Timmy
responded saying about how um you're
obsessed uh you're obsessed with PJ and
he's like, "Oh, he's the obsessed one.
He's going to court over what he's the
behavior towards me and my um my
partner. He's such a narcissist. You You
want to use the word narcissist? What a
narcissistic little virgin, you know? He
started literally everything. What a
That's exactly what you call a
narcissist. That is exactly what you
call a narcissist. You know,
you know what I'm saying, bro? Like you
you like that is a narcissist. He
started it even even before with his
vile disgusting mouth. He didn't stop
meeting me greasy because of my quote
behavior. He stopped meeting me because
I wanted to [ __ ] him up and he couldn't
walk all over a grown man. So what did
he do? He played the victim just like
all of these women do. That is what you
call a narcissist.
Just like what these women do, you know,
you know, most of these women are
narcissists. You know, you know, like he
the way he tries to be the victim. He is
such a narcissist.
He is such a narcissistic little virgin.
You You're one to talk about
narcissists, right? Yeah. You You're one
to talk about narcissists. He started
[ __ ] Okay, I'll tell you how this all
started. Yeah, before this whole YouTube
[ __ ] he started [ __ ] talking about
people's dead [ __ ] relatives, right?
And I had to listen to that disgusting
ugly malfaries, that virgin malf every
[ __ ] day, right? And then I said to
him, "Meet me. Meet me. I'm going to
smash your face in." And he didn't want
to meet me. Right? So when I turned
about 18, 19. Huh. Funny, isn't it? How
they never want to [ __ ] with a grown
man. Right? So then then he then he kept
ignoring me. Then okay, I'm going to do
some videos on you, you little [ __ ]
Right? And I'm going to show all your
friends what you're about. Right? And
then he comes on here doing it back then
trying to play the victim. You
narcissistic little virgin. I've never
met such a narcissist in my life. He's
got to be worse than [ __ ] USA. Is he?
So you act the big [ __ ] like you're some
kind of big man, right? In your shitty
little skint bedset with your disgusting
mouth. And then when you can't walk over
people, you then play the victim. Sort
it out, mate. [ __ ] hell.
You know what the [ __ ] If I was a If I
was a 15, 16y old kid, you think he'd be
going to the [ __ ] police?
Do you think this [ __ ] virgin would
be going to the [ __ ] police? If I was
a 15, 16y old kid that he could walk all
over? No. Exactly. You know, [ __ ]
narcissist. You when I read that? Yeah.
That little narcissistic little virgin
[ __ ] Yeah. Do you know the thing is
right you you want to try and say right
in the past like oh all of the things
I've said is nasty nowhere near what he
said nowhere near what that little
virgin said mate if I was a 15 16
probably even a 17 year old kid you know
he'd be more than happy to keep doing
these little things but as soon as
you're an adult as soon as you [ __ ]
grow a pair of balls you know oh please
picking on me
[ __ ] virgin you Huh? I swear if I
ever see that [ __ ] I'm smashing his
face in, you know? I don't give a [ __ ]
about the police, bro. I swear to God if
I ever see that little virgin [ __ ] out
with his disabled girlfriend, I'm
smashing his face. I don't give a [ __ ]
you know? Like, I honestly don't give a
[ __ ] about the police, bro. You know,
just reading that annoys me. Don't come
online acting like you're some kind of
big [ __ ] lanky boy. If you're just going
to play the narcissist at the end of it,
you know, play the victim and be a
narcissist at the end of it.
Same as these women in in in a verbal
way, not in a physical way, but in a verbal way.
There's no point if you're just going to
play victim in the end. You know,
there's no point if you're just going to
play victim in the end. You [ __ ] I I
don't think I've ever met a worse
narcissist than that. You know,
Izzy was a narcissist. USA Izzy was a
narcissist, but not like that.
That [ __ ] is an actual
narcissist. And and it's very well, he's
not even a man. He's not he's not the
[ __ ] same gender as me. Um, let's
just call it a thing. But it's very rare
that a fe someone that's not a female is a narcissist. You know,
I don't think I've ever met one that's,
you know, maybe the odd one, but it's
normally women that are the ones that
are narcissists, not that [ __ ] thing.
You know what I mean?
And then you ran to the This is why I
don't waste my time with these people,
Grezy. This is why I don't waste my time
going back and forth every day cuz
they're clearly jealous of something.
They clearly ain't got a life to do what
they [ __ ] do.
Like I keep saying a million times, I'll
say it again. If I didn't know what
these people do, I would I would have
been in Birmingham yesterday. It
wouldn't have even been today. It
wouldn't have even been today. It would
have been yesterday.
It would have been yesterday, mate. It
would have been yesterday. But then I
was like, "Oh, well, you've done this a
million times. You've been here. You've
been there. You know, they play the
victim, you know. Um, these people play
the [ __ ] victim.
um or you know they don't give you
credit for your W's and then you just
realize it's just a big waste of time.
You've been wasting your time with these
jealous people that ain't got a life. So you know
I'm not going today. Nope. I'm not going
today. I wouldn't even waste my time. I
wouldn't even waste my money. We all
know how the chocolate chip cookie
crumbles. We know exactly what's going
to happen. It's happened a million times
before when I've gone somewhere. You
pretend it never happened. Mark Samson,
Trevor Dawson, Bomb, [ __ ] Virgin Boy,
and you all sit and pretend like it
never happened. No [ __ ] way am I
wasting my time or money. You You can
[ __ ] You can [ __ ] go and have a
wank somewhere, you know? Just like when
you get shown thousands and thousands
and pretend it never happened. Get that
absolute [ __ ] out of here. Eat a dick [ __ ] Simple.
No way. No way, mate. You people want to
start giving me credit for Mark Samson
yet? You people want to start giving me
credit for Trevor Dawson yet? What about
Bob? What about Virgin Boy?
You know, [ __ ] that. You think I'm
wasting my time with you generous people
again? Wasting my time, effort, money,
energy. You can absolutely have a wank
in a bush if you think I'm doing that.
We all know how the chocolate chip cookie crumbles.
Isn't that right, Grezy?
Just like you lose the money game and
you pretend you never lost it and then
you show smaller amounts acting like
you've won. We all know what you people
do on here, man.
You're not even you're not even worth
it. You know, I actually asked Monty
like, "Are you still in Birm Are you in
Birmingham? Are you still in Birmingham?"
I asked him if he's still in Birmingham. So,
but you know what I'm angry with you?
These people are biased. You know, I've
beat them at the money game, they deny
it. I've gone to Mark Samson's area
twice, they deny it. I've gone to try to
meet Bomb two times, they deny it. I've
gone to Virgin Boy's area, they deny it.
So, why would anyone waste any more time?
Why would anybody waste any more time?
And you know exactly what would happen.
I can tell you exactly what would
happen, right? You'd go to Birmingham
today, right? and you'd call that
[ __ ] monkey Mike out and that [ __ ]
Timmy, right? And they will not show up.
And this is exactly what's going to
happen. Yeah. So, you're going to waste
money probably going to have a drink
there. You're going to waste £300 and
then what's going to happen is you come
back and then people are just going to
act like it never happened and then
they'll just go on as normal with their
stupid little videos. I'm not wasting my
time. I am not wasting my [ __ ] time.
I said to that money Mike, if you want
to come to London, I'll meet you
anywhere, anywhere you want. Bring Timmy
with you as well. But that's how the cookie crumbles.
How about just not do that and just go
out in London and have a drink if you
wanted to do something? If you wanted to
waste your time and waste your money,
wouldn't you rather just go out in
London and just get pissed?
But I think I think that's would be a
better way of wasting your money than
going to Birmingham on trying to meet
people in a biased community on a
clearly biased community. Think about
it, Grievy. How many times did that Mark
Samson keep coming back and coming back
and coming back and no one said
anything? Nobody said anything. Do you remember?
And nobody said anything at all.
And then it's only when people started
to realize what well they already knew
what he was like. It's not that they
started to realize they knew what he was
like and then they started going at him.
But then when they're going at him,
they're not actually bringing up the
times I've tried to meet him two times.
Oh, it's the past. It doesn't matter.
Okay. Well, then it doesn't matter what
Prime did then. That's the past. That's
the past. It doesn't matter what Tiger
did then. That's the past. you know, so
I mean, you're you're wasting your time
on a biased community trying to meet anyone, you know,
but if they want to come London, I'm
more than happy to meet them anywhere, you know?
Like even when I went to Birmingham to
meet Monty, I feel like that even was a
waste of time because it's like he's
just going to snake you in the end, you
know, and you know what I'm saying? And
like, you know, we did call people out
and the whole point weren't to call
people out and they're starting again.
You know what I'm saying? They're
starting again. So, it's just a waste of time.
And they're starting a [ __ ] game, bro.
You know what I mean? So, all of that
was a waste of time, a waste of £200. You know,
I'm good at the football bets. Oh no, Grezy.
This one's going to be interesting. They
both score no draw. This is going to be
harder to win. But it's all just a bit
of fun, eh?
It's all just a bit of fun, eh?
Yeah, for Ant-Man to have still had some hope.
Obviously, he never tried nowhere near
as much as I did clearly, even though I
knew he tried and stuff cuz Yeah,
even thinking about going out just makes
me so tired. Like my actual I went for a
walk today. I walked three miles to the
bookies, but just it just makes me feel
so tired. the thought of it. Like my
actual bones are actually I feel like
I'm I'm I'm [ __ ] 70 years old.
All that approaching has caught up on me
over the years.
Oh my [ __ ] bones. So yeah,
have you heard of that AI thing, Grezy?
There's a lot of women pretending to be
like models on Instagram and like
messaging people and [ __ ]
What I find with people on the internet,
you know, like Reddit and stuff, they uh Yeah.
Yeah. Exactly. Exactly. Exactly. And
even that, so why am I going to waste my
time going to Birmingham? We used to all
be biased again.
because we know what you people do on
it. Like I said, if you're not fat and
ugly like these people, they're jealous
and they don't like you. And then if
they don't like you, they're biased. So
no matter what you do, you're just
wasting your time on it in in that
regard. So yeah,
now I've got [ __ ] I've got [ __ ]
accounts, right, that don't even never
met me, don't know me, that are I'm half
the age and they're sat on YouTube
stalking every day.
That's what you call jealousy. That's
generally what you you call jealousy.
Just like this little virgin. This
little narcissistic virgin. You know
what? I'm I'm going to start calling him
that now. The narcissistic virgin. You
know, I've never really called anyone a
narcissist before. I don't think it's a
word I use, but that that that he's a
narcissistic little virgin. That's what he is.
Cuz think about it. Yeah. So Ramlot
since you seem seem to come in here and
talk sense. If you had all of this money
and somebody was ugly in their skin
apparently, you would just you would you
would waste your time on them,
you know. But the fact that these sit
here all day every day wasting their
time on me, it's obvious it's jealous.
Jealousy. Younger than them, better
looking than them, better life than
them, can do what you want like them.
Um unlike them, you know, they're it is
it is jealousy. It definitely definitely
is jealousy if you if you see it from a
normal point of view. Yeah, a normal
person. You wouldn't waste your time on
someone that's not worth it. You know,
you know what I'm saying? So that's
that's what it is. They're sad, fat,
ugly people that ain't got a life.
They ain't got a life but YouTube and
hating on people they don't know.
You know, they probably don't like it
that you've actually got hope in life.
Not with women. There's no hope there.
There's definitely no hope there. Um but
in terms of like um
doing things and
moving forward and quitting things and
[ __ ] you know,
cuz it's mad because they don't really
go for anyone else but me, you know.
They only do it to me.
That's how you know it's it is jealousy
with these people ain't got a life s on
YouTube every day.
Imagine I imagine I come on every day
stalking USA Izzy from the time I woke
up to the time I went to bed.
Could you imagine that?
Or I mean they could be gay. I mean they
could love you. They could be gay. It's
either jealousy or they're they're in
love with you or both.
I mean, what what else could it actually actually be?
But I do think sometimes I think, "Oh
[ __ ] I'm not going to waste my time on
this little narcissistic scorny little
virgin anymore because I know I'm better
than him. I got more money than him. I'm
better looking than him. No need to
waste my time on some little rat.
You know, that's and that's how they
would feel, you know.
They're very strange people on here. You
have to you have to admit, you know,
very very strange people on here.
But yeah, the snaking they really know
how to annoy me. They do know how to
annoy me because it's the staking thing
that annoys me, Greasy. It's the snaking
thing that annoys me because I know that
if that money m was in my face, I'd
smack him right in it and he wouldn't
even get up, you know? It's it's the
snaking [ __ ] that annoys me. It's not
people with like different opinions or
people that agree or disagree or people
that just stop coming. It's not it's not
that, bro. It's the actual snaking that
that's what annoys me, you know.
about so he doesn't gamble anymore
laughing emoji bro you are you mad that
was winding me up yesterday you know
like when I was out and about I was
thinking of that bro it was annoying me
like you don't understand bro it was
actually annoying me and I said if only
this was two and a half years ago when I
didn't know what you people were about
if [ __ ] only
if [ __ ] only. Yeah.
Then you might have got my time and money. Yeah. What?
Right, the football's starting soonly,
lad. Another one's coming in. Uh, really? Yeah.
And I went out Sunday and spent [ __ ]
knows how much just to get [ __ ] all in
the end. So you know,
same old story it Uh,
who the [ __ ] is that whistling, mate?
Who the [ __ ] is that whisting? Yeah.
I've noticed Joe's not been back on here.
Often the case, is it mate? When these
snakes get caught out, they never come
back, do they?
H. Isn't that mad?
Isn't that mad with these fat 40y olds?
When they're caught out to be what they
are, they never come back.
Nah, mate. I was going to go to [ __ ]
uh Birmingham. You know, Charlie, I've
got no problem with you, bro. You know,
I've met you and stuff. You know, you're
like the only one on here that I say is
like cool and [ __ ] You know, I've never
had a problem with you. But that money
mic, bro, I was going to go Birmingham
yesterday and smash his [ __ ] face. Cuz
the thing is, Charlie, yo, I don't like
people, right, that lick your ass,
right, on um and I know you got no
problem with him, bro, but I do that
lick that licks [ __ ]
people's [ __ ] I know you, you know,
you you try to stop the drama and [ __ ]
I get that, bro. But I don't like it
when people lick your ass on, you know,
on your chat and then [ __ ] talk [ __ ]
behind your back to people that you hate
the most, bro. Like, I hate it, bro.
Like, you don't understand. And Charlie,
the only reason I didn't bother is
because, bro, the thing is with these
people, yeah, is whenever you go and you
try to meet them and they don't show up,
they just act like they won and everyone
forgets about it because that's what
happens when you're not liked on here.
So, it's it's it's it's [ __ ] up, bro. Like,
this is what I mean, bro.
It's [ __ ] It honestly is [ __ ] But,
how are you, man? I've got a football
bet on anyways. [ __ ] all the drama.
I got a double. Both teams score no draw.
Both score no draw. I stuck 30 on it. I
thought I'd take more of a risk this time, bro.
More of a risk this time. Yes.
Yeah. I put 120 on two teams on Tuesday,
bro. It returned 380. It was good.
I had bookies with 160. Yeah, I put 40
on the roulette, lost it. I thought,
[ __ ] it, let me just put 120 on the
football bet. Got it to 380. I just wish
I put the one all the 160 on it now.
But, you know, it's still good, isn't it? Yeah,
there's loads of goals in that National
League, isn't there? National Northern League.
Yeah, I'm coming off in a bit, bro. I'm
going to go watch it and Yeah, man.
[ __ ] I'm tired as [ __ ] Charlie, man.
Know what it is. I'm exhausted, bro. I'm exhausted.
[ __ ] exhausted, man. Oh, dude. Anyways,
I'm going back. See you.