Yeah, sorry about that.
Was a uh was a late one last night. Oh [ __ ]
Yeah, you actually feel like the
atmosphere so weird. Like you can
actually feel it in the air. It's like,
you know, like the [ __ ] London
Underground, you can actually feel the weirdness.
I don't know if it's just me or everyone
else, but I can um certainly feel it, you know.
[ __ ] it now. Certainly can. Weirdness.
Oh, by the way, Jo, you need to stop
with these uploads.
You're going to give yourself a [ __ ] heart attack.
Oh man, is it There we go. Yeah, you're
going to give yourself a heart attack.
You need to stop with these uploads.
You know, you can keep acting like
you've won at the money game, but I know
the truth and deep down you know the
truth as well. Even though you'll never
admit it, just like the whole Mark Thson
thing, you never admit it, but it never
means it never happened. Again, a kind
reminder of why we don't waste our time
on you people.
You know, to be honest with you, I
shouldn't even be [ __ ] entertaining
you fat, ugly, jealous people that ain't
got a life. But, you know, you just get
sucked into this sometimes.
You know, you sit there and pretend like
you've got to tell. It's madness. It's
actually crazy, man. Honestly is.
And you didn't answer the question
yesterday. Oh, well, I didn't show you
the money because I didn't have the
money in cash. Okay. Well, why don't you
go to the bank? You know, I mean, it's
Isn't it pretty obvious now why people
don't waste their time when you you self-reflects?
It's literally so obvious.
Oh, I showed Monty that yesterday. You know,
you know, it's mad.
It is actually madness, man. It is
actually madness. What's the day today?
Sunday, isn't it?
That it is that it is. Um, yeah. So yeah,
[ __ ] virgin boy. Oh my god. The [ __ ]
was that [ __ ] yapping on about yesterday?
The truth makes someone a narcissist.
Never ever heard of that.
Never ever ever heard of that. So, when
you're forced to when you're forced to a
conclusion, you're a narcissist. Oh, really?
That's news to me. I didn't know that. I
didn't know that was a trait. H you
learn something new every day, don't you?
I come to the conclusion
that I was better looking than these
people and I've got a better life than
them because they will not leave you
alone. You've got a bunch of wrinkly old
men that don't know you, that will not
leave you alone, that literally never stop.
So, I mean, like, what else could it
actually [ __ ] be?
Of course, it's [ __ ] jealousy. It's
common sense that it's jealousy what
these people do on here.
It's like, what the [ __ ] The truth
become make someone a narcissist. I
mean, I know the truth hurts, you know.
Ronald P was writing them. Never stop,
will they? These people will never stop
their jealousy towards me. They will
never ever stop. He was so right. You
know that that account wherever the [ __ ]
he's gone probably on some other account
now to be fair. He was actually right
that they literally would never stop
their jealousy towards me. It's actually
the truth. They don't they literally
don't stop, you know. And for people to
like put all of that effort into
somebody that they don't know, it is jealousy.
Think of it. These people are [ __ ]
fat, ugly, old gamblers that ain't got
nothing. They're sat on here every day
calling people that they [ __ ] don't
know. That's what they are.
Old, fat, ugly gamblers. [ __ ] Most of
them are probably [ __ ] virgins. So, I
mean, for [ __ ] sake, you know what I'm saying?
Madness. Absolute madness.
If they if they left you alone, right,
and they didn't do this [ __ ] every day,
then I'd think, "Oh, well, just a normal
person just like everyone else. Nothing
special about me." But these people make
you feel special. You know, they
actually do. But when they're stalking
you and harassing you every single day,
it's clear as day is jealousy. It's
clear as it's clear as the uh it's clear
as a sunny day outside that it is,
you know, cuz and don't say they do it
for reaction cuz they don't do it for
reaction. And even if people done it for
a reaction, they would eventually just
stop. People eventually would just stop.
So, and they'll never ever stop. They'll
never ever stop. So,
>> how come you have different How come you
not overseas or I've already been I've
already been abroad.
Um, again, something that you choose to
forget which ties in with the whole
biasness again. Uh, you know, you I've
seen me abroad uh multiple times, but
again, you probably forgot that just
like you forgot I went to Mark Samson's
area and forgot I tried to beat the
bomb. Forgot I You forget a lot of
things, don't you? When it's someone
else doing things. I mean, bro, I'm
coming to the conclusion that
if you've got all of these fat, ugly old
men obsessed with you every day that
don't know you, that's never met you,
that will not leave you alone.
Yeah, it kind of is jealousy cuz there's
literally nothing else it can actually
be. You know, they don't know you.
They've never met you and stuff. Yeah,
he can do videos all he wants. No one
cares what he what he's doing. He done
nothing when he when I was in
Birmingham. Something else that you
people choose to forget. You forget a
lot of stuff, don't you? When it's
somebody that you don't like. Isn't that mad?
Yeah, he was doing videos. Well, he
wasn't doing videos when I was in the
city last month, was he? And he didn't
come out just like that. Prime, you're
all the same on here. This is why
there's no point with any of you anymore.
Any of you clowns,
you know? There's there's literally no
point in any of it, you know.
Similar to what I was saying with the
money bike thing, if I went there on
Friday, we would know exactly what would
happen. You know,
you people are clearly [ __ ]
and I have been to different countries overseas
and you don't need to go to a different country overseas
to have a better life than someone. You
could just have a better life than
somebody being better looking, having
more money, going out, getting pissed.
You know, you don't need to go overseas.
That's not what a better life means
necessarily. But I mean, bro, you you're
the one that's got me to this
conclusion. You know,
you got fat, ugly, 40-year-old stalking
you all day, every day. It's got to be
jealousy. There's nothing else it can be.
Facts. Give the nine all you want. Sorry.
Yeah. Here you go. Virgin PJ. Yeah. Self
rejected again. Timmy, I'm not even
watching it. I'm not even watching it.
I'm not going round and round and round
and round in circles. Just like I'm not
going round and round and round in
circles with that joke thinking that
he's beat me at the money game. And we
all know the truth of when you get shown
money, you will run away. I'm sick of
repeating myself, you know. You're not
I'm not going round and round and round
and round in circles. If Timmy had
anything to say, he could have come out
in Birmingham when I called him out last
month, you know. End the story. And I
know he's watching this, so I'm not
going to do videos back and forth, back
and forth, back and forth.
You know, I was in Birmingham. I called
you to come out. You was on the chat, so
it's like you didn't see it. You didn't
want to come out and now you're starting
your [ __ ] again. You know, typical
person on this YouTube. They've done it
in Liverpool. You know,
you know what? I'm actually coming off
this [ __ ] you know. I've decided I
actually am going to come off this
[ __ ] and just go on my main channel.
You know, I've actually decided I really
really have decided, bro, like on on a
on a on a natural real now. You
see, look at this same self-p projecting
thing again. He's approaching 30. Never
had a girlfriend. Had a girlfriend. Got
friends. Had a girlfriend. Have more
money than you. And I don't live with my
mom and I've got more money than all of
you. Again, it's just self-p projection.
This is what I mean with this community.
You know, you're saying that someone's
approaching 30, bro. You're in your 40s
and you ain't got to put the piss in.
You know, you keep saying that I'm
approaching 30. It's just you trying to
make yourself feel better. The fact that
you are in your 40s, you are the skinned
virgins. You know, you're talking about
people that's not had a girlfriend,
mate. You people probably ain't even
seen a woman naked.
You people probably ain't even seen a
woman naked and you're in your 40s and
you want to talk about a 27 year old
that still has hope.
You know what I'm saying? Like this is
exactly why I'm coming off of this [ __ ]
You know, this is exactly why, bro. I've
actually decided, you know,
I've literally had a girlfriend. I've
got more friends than anybody. Um, I've
got more money than these people. And I
don't even live with my mom, you know?
It's just self-p projection. This is why
people don't waste. This is why I'm
coming off of this [ __ ] You know,
this is what I'm This is what I'm saying.
You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
And it's the same with that [ __ ]
Ricky account as well.
You know what I'm saying?
If you've got anything to say, come and
say it to my [ __ ] face. Stop it.
Right. [ __ ] this, bro. One second. Let
me go back on this. Hold on. Yeah.