[Music] slow.
So yeah, another one. Started something
you can't finish. Oh, what is it with
you people on here, man? Come on. Come
on, Timmy. The only people that are skin
and a virgin is you and your [ __ ]
ugly followers, fat, wrinkly old farts
on YouTube. Come on, give it up. You know,
don't know why you even do these panels
like when you just get owned every
single time. I've spoke about you. I've
spoke about Money Mike. I spoke about
his sister. I spoke about her kids, you
know. And you're not coming to London.
I've even offered to pay for your trade
fair. You're not coming to London, mate.
And then the excuse is, oh, I live in
the outskirts of Birmingham. Yeah, of
course you do. To me, it's always
excuses. It's always excuses. You know,
I'm sure if that was the case, you would
have said that when you was actually
watching the live stream,
the only virgin is you and your little
gay little [ __ ] old wrinkly
followers. Ain't got no life. Sat on
YouTube every day calling people what
they are themselves. Skint. Well, what a
life that you've got, is it?
So, you going to come today or not? You
know, I'll wait for you all day. I'll
meet you at Marley Bone if you want.
I'll make it a little bit easier for you.
As long as you bring that spaz mic with
you, you know, I want I want it to be
both of you as well. It can't just be
one. It's got to be both of you little
[ __ ] Come on. Come on. Come on. You
get a free day out on a Sunday. You
know, why not? What What's there to lose, you know?
get the money out now for you if you want.
If you want, it's not a problem, you know. Oh [ __ ]
Typical, is it?
Typical. Typical. Typical.
You know, when are you, Timmy, seriously
going to stop self-reflecting? When are
you and your followers going to grow up?
You're [ __ ] basically double my age.
When are you going to stop all of this [ __ ]
You know, calling people what you are
yourselves every day. When are you going
to stop this, man, and actually grow up?
You know, sat online [ __ ] jobless
talking about other people that you
don't know every day, calling people
that you don't know every day what you
are. When are you going to actually grow
up? Come on.
Mhm. You're time to grow up, you know.
It really is. [ __ ]
This is what I mean with these people in here.
You [ __ ] double my [ __ ] age. God.
You know what I'm saying? Like if you've
got anything to say, right?
What's he say? People
are sad 40 year old virgins that hate
anyone with a better life than them.
That's why they're on here every day,
bro. Cuz they're [ __ ] their skin. You
know, do you know the thing is, right?
It's it's not even the fact that they're
on here every day. It's what they
actually do on here every day. It just
goes to show that they're unhappy skin
lowife people. That's what they are.
That's literally what they are. And bro,
do you know why I don't even waste my
time like saying, "Oh, show me where you
are or let me come to Hull or you don't
you didn't need to own them for me, bro.
I already own them." Because we all know
how the cookie crumbles cuz deep down we
know what you do. You do this [ __ ] every
day cuz you're jealous. That's that's
the main part of this, right? You're
jealous. You're biased. So then no one
would actually waste their time. You
know what I'm saying? Just like that
Ricky Millington account, bro. He talks
about me, yet he's he's a 40year-old
who's probably never even seen a [ __ ]
woman naked, sat on YouTube in his 40s,
which is basically double my age, ain't
got no life, but trying to call other
people that he doesn't even know. Like,
think about that, bro. Like, actually
think about that [ __ ]
You know, sat on YouTube talking about
people that you don't even know every [ __ ] day.
Well, jealous ugly people that ain't got
a life. Why people can't be bothered
with it anymore? You know what I mean?
This is why people can't be bothered
with it anymore, Cory. You know what I mean?
You just post your own content or you
just [ __ ] leave. Simple, bro. You
know what I'm saying?
They're proper proper disabled fat,
ugly, jealous people. You know what
makes me laugh here, Cory? And you get
these 40, 50 year olds trying to say
that you've got no job. You've never had
a girlfriend and your skin. They
literally try to project their [ __ ]
existence onto you every single day on
YouTube. That's literally their life.
That is honestly their life. I have
shown more money than these people. I
have shown more women than these people.
I have proved that I'm better looking
than these people, which there's no lie
there. I mean, that's why they go for me
every single [ __ ] day. And then they
try to tell you. I've shown I've got
more friends than these people as well,
which I've got friends. Some that they
don't have, you know. All they are is
lonely, fat, ugly people that ain't got
a pot to piss in. So they take out on
random people on YouTube,
you know. And that's that's literally
what they do. Greavves. You know I'm
right. You know what I'm saying is You know,
they live right.
Think about it. They live to hate every day.
Think about it, bro. Living to hate
every day. Who has the energy for that? You know, no one,
mate, if I was on YouTube for another 10
years, here's the thing, Greaves. You
know, I'd be posting content. I'm not
going to be sat there [ __ ] I'm not
going to be sat there calling people
that I don't know. I'm not going to be
sat there calling people that I don't [ __ ] know.
You know, like these people, they're sat
there calling someone half their age all
the things that they are. I've done more
in two years than these people done in
their whole [ __ ] life. Been seen with
more women than them. Women that I've
met multiple times. I've shown more
money than these people. I've shown I'm
better looking than these people. I've
shown I've got a better life than these
people. This is why they go at me. This
is generally generally why these people
go at me because they're jealous. That
is why they do it.
Would you not? Okay, let's let's let's
ask Grezy. Of course, there's an element
of jealousy. Think about it, bro. How
many people are there on this community?
And how many people go for me?
And all of these people just seem to be
uglier than you. Isn't it funny? It's
jealousy. Of course, it's jealousy.
Everything about it is jealousy, bro.
You know, of course, it's jealousy. It's
like what Ronald Pump said, you know,
even when I was watching that Virgin's
video yesterday, bro, I was like, you
know, every single time he's trying to
say that I've got a big nose, he's in
denial. Like, at this point, he's you
can tell he's saying it to make himself
feel better. Like, he knows that I'm a
million times better looking than him. A
million trillion billion gillion zillion
times better looking than he will ever
be. And all he does is come across as
insecure. Whenever he does this, he just
he's just coming across as insecure, you know.
It's weird. You know, these people need
to grow up, man.
And you, Timmy, you need to grow up.
Should should I put the link out and
let's start showing what he Let's Do I
need to put the link out again and ask
you people to show money and show what
you look like and I and I will really
really show you people up for the
jobless skin ugly people that you really
are. How many times are you going to keep losing?
losing? Like I can do it again if you
want. You know, we're all this, we're
all that. Come and show us a bit about
you. Let's get to know you people. Let's
see all your money, all your friends
that you don't have. Exactly. Cuz you
don't have nothing.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] trying to make
videos on me. I said, "Come today with
money, Mike. I I'll give you the money
for the train.
How much do you need?" £500. I'll give
you £500 if you want. That should cover
the two or three of you. You know, I'll
send you the £500 if you want. Can't say
that's not enough. Book the [ __ ] show
you on the train and I'll show and I'll
show you and I'll send you £500. Simple.
It's not a big deal, is it?
Disabled [ __ ] virgins talking about
[ __ ] people that they don't even know.
All cuz their lives are [ __ ] [ __ ]
It's at the [ __ ] pits. And if it
ain't, come on, come and defend
yourself. Come on and [ __ ] defend
You know, come on.
You know what I'm saying?
This is why I don't waste my time with
these people no more, bro. Like I keep
saying, you don't know how badly I
wanted to go to Birmingham on Friday.
But there comes a point where you you
need to learn from your mistakes with
the bomb, with Mark Samson, even going
to Birmingham last month and none of
these people [ __ ] show up. You know,
you there comes a time where you
literally need to need to actually take
a look at, you know, what these people actually are.
sad little jealous little narcissistic
and vindictive fat ugly people that
can't get off of YouTube. I know you I
know you like that when I [ __ ] say
that [ __ ] Greasy. They go at anyone
with a better life than them that they
don't even know.
I've had more sex in in in in the past
two years than they will ever have in
their life. Not that they've had in
their life that they will ever have in
their life because, you know, they're
virgin. Because because because that
they've had in their life doesn't mean
anything because they're [ __ ]
virgins, you know. Because they're
[ __ ] virgins. They are. Just like
that Mickey Millions account. All of
these little fat, ugly, angry gamblers
have got nothing. They got nothing in their life.
You know, the people that I would
believe that actually have stuff in life
is is people that just come on here and
don't do much but chill, you know, like
Charlie or, you know, even uh what's his
f what was his name again? What was his
name? Oh, the one that come my door, right? [ __ ]
Oh, what was his name now?
Come on my door with a football bet and a coke. Uh,
what was his name again?
Oh, what was his name? You know what I'm
talking about, ain't it? Uh,
it's not how hard can it be, is it? Who
is it? Who is it? Who is that guy that
come my door with a coke and a football bet
when he was at O2? Oh, [ __ ] What was
his name now?
that him I would believe you know he's
got a life you know even though he comes
on here and whatever because you know
that's how people that age should be
acting you know it's what these people
do on air every day calling people that
they don't even [ __ ] know you know
they should know better at their [ __ ]
age I don't know what his name was I
forgot I'm sure it was how hard can it
be is but he's I forgot what the [ __ ]
was his name
oh that's going to annoy me now his name
was it wasn't Charlie wasn't Oh,
the fact that these people do what they
do on here every day, calling people
they don't know, it just goes to show
like you I'm 30, almost 30, and I've
never had a girlfriend. I'm all of these
things. Bro, what are you like? What the
[ __ ] are you people fat, ugly, skinned
people on YouTube every day? You know,
that's not even a skit, bro. Telling
someone that I'm not even anywhere near
30 anyways. Even if I've never had a
girlfriend, which I actually technically
have, that doesn't mean anything.
You are in your [ __ ] 40s and you
can't even get laid.
At least I've actually been with [ __ ]
[ __ ] You know what I mean?
Uh, how hard can it be? His name was
What was his name now? Uh,
yeah, he bought me a Coke and a football bat.
I wonder why I stopped talking to him.
He was actually all right.
I remember my [ __ ] mom come upstairs
and said, "Oh yeah, someone's on the
door for you." I said, "What the fuck?"
Bear in mind I was like in my dressing
gown and I was like, "What the fuck?"
Yeah, man. But I forgot his name. You
know, that's how people should be acting
at their age. These [ __ ] little
clowns just seem to come on here and
self-reflect every day.
Self-reflect their fat, ugly skin lives
every day. You know what I'm saying?
Cuz look, look at Gregy. How how much
how do these people know how much money
you have? All I know is I don't know
what anyone has. So, I'm not going to
sit there and pretend. But I know that I
have shown money and I've had you all
running away. I know that for a fact. So
if you don't have facts about [ __ ]
there's no point of [ __ ] saying
anything. You know, you have been shown
money and you will run away. I mean,
read into that what you will. You know,
you don't see me [ __ ] coming on
YouTube every [ __ ] day. Start [ __ ]
calling [ __ ] people I don't [ __ ] know. You know,
do you know what I'm saying?
And then and then I'm a narcissist
because I say that I've I've had more
money than these people and I'm better
looking than them. Well, where have I
got that from? The fact that you keep
stalking me every day and you won't
leave me alone. So, I mean,
is it wrong to come to that conclusion?
And then you've got Joe Greavesy. He
didn't even answer the question properly
yesterday. Oh, he claims that he's got
all of this money.
Uh, okay. Why didn't you show me money
when I showed you money? What was his
response again, Grezy? Do you remember
what his response again was? Oh, I don't
have I didn't have it in cash. I said,
okay, well, couldn't you gone to the
bank? And what and what's what's the
excuse for that then? You see, this is
why I don't play these silly little games.
This is exactly why I don't play these
silly little games with these people
anymore. these silly little
self-reflecting games, you know, self-p projecting.
If they had a better life than you, they
wouldn't be sat on YouTube doing what
they do to you every day. Simple.
It's jealousy. Absolute jealousy. And it
stinks like fish, you know,
cuz think about it, bro. Should these
people be happy in life,
you know, at their age? Should they be
sat on YouTube not calling people that
they don't know
arguing with people that they don't know
that they're never going to [ __ ]
meet, you know? Because I've been all
over the country. None of these people come out,
you know? The more these people do this,
it makes me feel so much better about myself.
You know, it makes you feel like you're
actually doing something right. It's
like Eminem, you know, haters give you
the motivation. It's actually true. You
know, they actually where they're so
obsessed and jealous, it makes you feel
like you you're all the things that you
never thought you were before.
You know, better looking than them,
younger than them.
I mean, generally, do you really think
any of these fat mongos on here have got
a better life than me? And my life's not
perfect. Do you really really think
you could go out right now? I could go
out right now, get pissed, go out
approaching, go and have a laugh. These
people can't even do that. These angry
That's how you know it's they are the
ones that are skint.
They are the ones that ain't got a life.
They are the ones that are the virgins
at their age. They all it's all about
themselves that they're talking about. You know,
it's self projection. That's what it is
with these clowns.
They said I've done my balls and I don't
even [ __ ] gamble in anything but the football anymore.
All right, that Triple H thing was
yesterday though. Is it Gre That was
funny in it. Yesterday, Grezy, the
Triple H thing, you know.
I mean, yeah, I let Triple H in because,
you know, at the end of the day, let
bygones be bygones and he's not really
slagged me off. He's just [ __ ] stirred.
Um, so I thought, okay, you know, he's
better than a lot of the other people,
even though I have slagged him off in the past.
Him and his little Jordy accent. Yeah,
but you know, that's just that's completely different.
You know what I'm saying?
He just [ __ ] stirs. Maybe he finds it
funny, you know. You can't blame
somebody for finding [ __ ] stirring
funny, you know, but
that's all he's really done, which is,
you know, I don't know, just let him on
the panel, is it? You know, so
but what this Ricky Million account does
and these other people I mean,
all of these people on here self-reflect.
You old men sure have a degree.
Yeah. Do you know what the [ __ ]
I've tried to [ __ ] respond to this
comment and it didn't let me. See?
Yeah. He's talking about people being
skint again. Oh, it's because he's he's
uh he's deleted a video.
These people asking, that's why they go
on about people being skinn every day
cuz they asking, "How the [ __ ] do they
know how much money you have?" How the
[ __ ] do they know how much [ __ ] money you have?
Yeah, that's that's that's a good
question, you know.
They don't know about They don't know anything about anyone. [ __ ] sake.
When are you people going to grow up?
When are you people going to [ __ ] grow up?
You know, no job, no money, no this.
You're just talking about your [ __ ]
selves. That's all you do is talk about
your 40year-old virgin selves. Cuz if
this wasn't you, you wouldn't be sat
there calling people that you don't know
every day on [ __ ] YouTube.
You know what I'm saying? every single
day that you don't know on YouTube.
You know, we got somebody with a rat
face with no teeth trying to tell
someone they've got a big nose.
Everything screams insecure about these
people. You know what I mean?
They call people skin. It's because
these people are angry gamblers that
have got no money.
So, they seem to think everyone's the
same as them, you know.
Skill about me, kid. Yeah. So yeah,
I just can't be bothered with this [ __ ] anymore, Grezy, you know.
See, my chat's cool. You know, you got
Grezy, you got Steven Howard. We don't
have people on here. Call people that
they that that that we don't know, you know.
Put your camera on. Let's see all the
money that you've got. Come on. Come on.
These people are fat, ugly, old gamblers,
you know, like proper proper proper,
dude. They're balls and gamblers, bro.
They actually are.
It's trying to say, "Oh, well, yeah, you
ain't this, you that." I was like, I I I
reply I tried to reply to the comment,
um, Nicolo, but it never let me. I said,
"Typical 40 odd year old projector. I've
shown more money than you. I've shown
more women than you. I've shown more
friends than you. And I've shown a
better life than you numerous times.
Stop self-reflecting your your life onto
others just cuz you've done your balls
in. You know what I mean? They
self-reflect because they're unhappy,
old, ugly people.
You know, I can go out now and meet a
friend if I want. These people are the
ones that have to call people and talk
to people that they don't know all day
every day cuz they're skimp loners. You know
what I mean, bro? No. What I find mad is
the self projectors.
These little 40-year-old ugly people
that ain't got a life trying to say that
you've got no none of the things that
they don't have and never had. It's
madness, isn't it? You know,
they're just talking about their own
miserable, spasticated lives. And if
they had friends and they had money,
they wouldn't be on here all day every
sat on YouTube calling people they don't
know for a living. Sad, spasticated bastards.
It's like, do you know Virgin Boy's
video yesterday, Nicolo?
I don't know if you watched it, but you
can tell like he's not even believing
the stuff what he's saying when he's
saying that I'm uh that I've got a big
nose. I was like, "Bro, did you see his
face throughout that whole video?" He is
an ugly ugly bastard.
An ugly ugly bastard.
It's which is part of the jealousy, you
know. You need to put two and two together.
So it is jealousy. It generally
generally is jealousy. This is why I
should be like the better person and
just leave the [ __ ]
[ __ ] obsessed with my [ __ ] nose.
There's nothing wrong with my nose.
[ __ ] hell. Why are you so obsessed
with my nose? You should be obsessed
with your ugly face and that mouth with
no teeth in it. But it is it is
jealousy. It is It is jealousy.
It is jealousy, bro. This is why I
should I shouldn't be scooping to these
people's levels. You know what I'm saying?
You know what I'm saying? That's what it
is. It is. They They are jealous.
Definitely jealous of something. You know,
and they can sit there and say, "Oh,
you're this and you're that and you're
this and you're that." But at the end of
the day, if you was all of these things,
bro, then they wouldn't be wasting their
time on you.
You know, they they wouldn't be sat
there at their age trying to call
someone they don't [ __ ] know if you
was all of these things.
Think of it, bro. Okay, let's go by the
facts with Virgin Boy, right? I'm better
looking than him. I've got more money
than him, right? Better clothes than
him. Been with more women than him. I've
got more life experiences than him and
he would ever have. I've got teeth in my
mouth unlike him. I mean,
it doesn't look good, does it?
And this is why they go This is why they
go at you. Yeah, I've seen it. This is
why they go at you.
They go at you because they're jealous
of you. That's what it is. It's It's
clear as day now. It's clear as a
summer's It's as clear as a right
summer's day, you know.
So, you started [ __ ] and you've run away again.
Yep. And you know the stories he was
making up like my um my dad's um
slapped my um mom and sisters around. I
just laughed at it because it's so made
up that I was actually creasing.
I was like, "What the [ __ ] That's just
so made up. And no one's ever pinned me
down anywhere. That was what your
stepdad done to you when you was making
up them stories that you went running to the police.
But yeah, you are the narcissist virgin boy.
And you know all of these people that
say, "Oh, he will hurt a woman badly one
day." Can see it coming. What they hate
is the fact that you're better looking
than them and you've got a better life
than them. They don't like it. These
little 40-year-old sorry ass losers. Cuz
that's what they are. They're sorry ass
[ __ ] little mongrel weasels sat on
YouTube [ __ ] hating on people that
they don't even [ __ ] know, you know?
And and and when and at the end of the
day, man, when when you put yourself on
the internet, Yeah. people can have an
opinion. You know what I feel like
doing, bro? You know what I actually
feel like doing with these little sorry
ass little virgins? I feel like going
going out to a club and just like
showing them what they can't do. You
know, like that Ricky Millon, you know,
that fat ugly little weasel, little s
living in a hole. You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
Yeah. I might just show what these
weasels can ever do cuz they ain't got
the money. They ain't got the looks.
Like I You know what? When they do this,
bro, they they are actually giving me
this ego. You don't understand. They actually are,
you know what I mean? Ricky Millin, the
little Ma could never do this in these
shitty little beds sitting hole talking
about somebody that he doesn't even know
because they're better looking than you
and they got more money than you.
[ __ ] hell. So, because I'm better
looking and I don't have to s like you
little virgins that's never seen a woman
naked, I'm going to hurt a woman. Why?
Because I say women are [ __ ] sometimes
and I'm not a s like you. What the [ __ ] bro?
Oh, [ __ ] hell.
You know what I mean?
And he says it's hilarious calling
someone a girlfriend. He's had a
girlfriend for years. He literally is a
virgin. He's the biggest virgin going,
you know. And yeah. And Ricky Millon is
so ugly. He couldn't even pay for sex.
He's so ugly. He's got no money sat in
hole being skint every day, you know,
talking about people that he don't know.
Mate, sun-kissed. I don't know what it
is with these [ __ ] self-reflectors.
They tell me I've never had a
girlfriend. I have. They tell me that
I'm skint when I got more money than
them. And they've all ran off. Um, you
know, they say that I've got no friends.
Got plenty of friends who I can meet
anytime I want. These people are never
going to move forward. Keep
self-reflecting every day. They're never
ever ever going to move forward. You
know, them keep self-reflecting their
sorry ass 40-year-old loser lives onto
me. It's not going to make them move forward.
Do you understand?
It's a sunny day. Yeah. It's never going
to make them move forward. Do you
understand? They're they're never going
to move forward.
You know what I'm saying?
They're just self They're just self
projecting. That's all they're doing. You know,
sat on YouTube calling people they don't
know in their 40s and 50s. is what a
[ __ ] life these little Mongols have
then like listen bro I'm not going on
like my life is perfect yeah but I'm
younger than these people I'm better
looking than these people and I and I've
got the money to do what I want you know
I'm not [ __ ] rich and they're talking
about me someone half their age they
literally are life losers they are life
[ __ ] losers and why do I say that I'm
better looking than these people and all
of these things because they won't [ __ ]
off and leave me alone so what what is
Is it then if you've got all of these
middle-aged men, right? Listen, if
you've got all of these middle-aged men
that will not leave you alone all day,
every day, and they don't stop, wouldn't
it come to a point where you think,
"Okay, maybe these people are jealous of
something, you know? They don't even
[ __ ] know you, bro." You know, and
and also, as it stands now, they're
never going to stop. Then these people
are never ever going to stop, you know?
These people are never ever ever ever
going to stop ever. Even when they're
dead and then we're a narcissist because
we come to conclusions that it's
inevitable that it is. What the [ __ ]
If they left you alone, right, then I'd
think, oh, well, I'm just a normal
person and t but you clearly are not a
normal per. So, in a way, these people
actually help me in a way cuz when you
have so many people obsessed and jealous
of you every day, it's it's quite
refreshing. And then you got [ __ ]
Timmy that tries to [ __ ] pretend to
call people out when we all know when I
was in his area, he was nowhere to be seen.
I was in Birmingham and then the excuse
was, "Oh, I live in the outskirts of
Birmingham." See, it's always excuses
with these people.
Bomb used to do it.
You remember Triple H and his little
Jordy accent? The reason I let Triple H
back on again is because yeah, I didn't
like the fact that he would [ __ ] stir,
but you know, at the end of the day,
it's like, okay, let bygones be bygones.
All he's done is [ __ ] stir. He's not
really snaked anyone. He's just [ __ ]
stirred, which I can understand. You
know, it's it's entertainment
entertainment for um for people.
You know what I'm saying?
You know what I'm saying, bro?
But so I just Oh, [ __ ] it. Okay, so he's
just [ __ ] stirred a few times. Just let
him on the panel, you know?
But it's like this Ricky Milling did
account. Do you think this [ __ ] fat
nerd would ever say anything to my face?
this little fat skint little virgin
who's never seen his who's never seen a
[ __ ] woman naked and the only [ __ ]
he's ever touched is his mom when he
come out of it. Do you think a nerd like
that would ever say anything to my
[ __ ] face? Do you think a [ __ ]
nerd like that could ever even look my
way? Yet on the internet it gives It's
like the quote that Mike Tyson said, you know,
but somehow they act big on the internet
because they know they're untouchable.
Do you think a little nerd like that?
Same thing with that [ __ ] money mic.
Do you think a [ __ ] little geeky
little albino looking [ __ ] like that
could ever snake me to my face? No, he
couldn't. You know, and we proved that
in [ __ ] Birmingham. You know,
you know what I'm saying? Some little
[ __ ] hull, little [ __ ] [ __ ] A
You want to talk about poverty, right? I
tell you exact I'll tell you about
poverty. Hull is is voted the worst
[ __ ] place to live in the whole of UK
there in Middlesbrough. So, do you think
some little hull boy sat in his mummy's
little [ __ ] bed at his age can ever
try and chuck it to someone like me
who's never even seen a woman naked?
These people ain't been seen with women.
I have. These people ain't been seen
with money. I have. The list goes on and
on and it goes on and on and on. You
know what I'm saying?
Do you know what I'm saying? [ __ ]
hell. Get off of YouTube. Get a [ __ ]
life. Stop talking about people that you
don't [ __ ] know every [ __ ] day.
[ __ ] me, bro.
Yeah. Like, [ __ ] I'm not claiming
that I'm rich. I'm rich and I've got
loads and loads and loads. I've got
enough money to do what I need to do
when I need to [ __ ] do it.
And yeah, it is probably over gambling.
Look at my clothes.
You know, look at me. I'm [ __ ] 20
[ __ ] seven. I've got clothes worth
more than these people's life. You know
what I'm saying?
You know, I've done a lot of [ __ ]
traveling. I've done a lot of like I've
got probably the best life than anybody on here.
You know, like probably
And then you got some little geeky
little [ __ ] You know,
you know, I still gambled the odd time
on football, but [ __ ] not like [ __ ] Timmy.
Why? Cuz it's expensive in London. You
go out, you spend two300 [ __ ] pound, it's expensive.
So, you know what I'm saying? I can go
out whenever I want,
do whatever I want.
Yeah. Well, I've been doing it for
[ __ ] years. I've been cold
approaching for [ __ ] years, mate. So,
you know, it's normal to me now, you know.
And then you got [ __ ] Joe F, right,
who's doing videos showing his [ __ ] pension, right?
Um, showing his [ __ ] pension off, right?
Yet when he got shown six grand, he ran
away. You know, like it's it's it's like
what the [ __ ] bro? These people really
have got a mind of a child, don't they?
And think about it, bro. If I'm so ugly,
why is Virgin Boy tried to get with all
of my ex- flings? I'm I'm like, at this
point, right, he's literally just
lying to himself. Like, it's actually
it's actually something to be pied. I'm
ugly, right? Apparently. Yeah, I've got
all of these women that he wish he could
have got, but I'm ugly. You're just
lying to yourself now. You are literally
literally lying to yourself. Every time
you're saying that,
you can see the disappointment in his
face. You know what I mean?
You know what I'm saying? You can see
the disappointment in his face.
He even tried it on with USA is he
[ __ ] and she rejected him. She
I think that Ronald was right, you know,
sun-kissed. He said they're jealous of
you cuz you're better looking than them.
You got more money than them and you got
a better life than them and it kills
them. I think my man was right, you
know. I'm I'm not even joking because if
you've looked at the time frame, you can
see these people have not stopped.
And it's not that that they just go for
[ __ ] everyone. It's they go for you.
If they went for everyone, then I'd be
like, "Oh yeah, okay." They're trying to
they're trying to just get a reaction
out of someone or something. But the
fact that they only go for me and then
you need to actually look at yourself
and you think, "Oh, yeah. Okay, now it
does actually make sense now." It is jealousy.
If you think about it,
you know, even if you've got a normal
life and you've got normal looks, you
know, compared to these [ __ ] people,
bro, you're [ __ ] probably Brad Pit.
I've kissed women. I've shown I've
[ __ ] I've shown more money than these
people. And you still get the
self-reflectors. You still get the disabled self-reflectors.
When are you going to actually get a
life and stop hating?
You know what I'm saying? Or people that
you don't know. Ricky Milling the Virgin
Living in Hull. Think somebody could
ever tell me anything, bro. From there,
they're [ __ ] No. Ghost. Do you know
why? Cuz I find it weird. And I'm not
giving them what they want. Listen.
Okay. Let me let me let me explain this
to you again. Yeah. Cuz every single
time I explain this to you, right, um
you you you sort of leave. They don't do
it for a reaction because even when you
don't react to them, they will still do
it. Even if you never react to them ever
again, they will still do it. They will
never leave you alone. They don't do it
for a reaction because that's defeating
the whole object. Look at their channel.
Look at what they're doing every day to
get this I quote reaction. It's not a
reaction. They do it because they are
jealous. That's why they do it,
you know, because if I Okay. Okay. Let
me Let me give you Okay. They do. Okay.
Then answer me this then. Okay. They do
it for a reaction. Okay. Let's just say
they do it for a reaction. And I promise
you that I'm not going to react to these
people in for 6 months, right? So then
they will do this all day every day for
6 months, right? And then when you
finally react to them, okay? And what?
So they've wasted all day, every day
stalking you for one reaction in 6
months. Um, okay. And then what? Well,
you're going to do it again for another
6 months. Doesn't make any sense. You
understand? So, no, they don't do it for
reaction. They do it because they hate
the fact that you're better looking than
them. They hate the fact that you got a
better life than them. You're younger
than them as well. Age is age is a good
thing. Um, you know, they don't do it
for a reaction. They don't do it for
And also how long that they've been
doing it for as well, you know, how long
that they've been sat there doing this
for, you know, and the fact that they'll
never stop. So long as you're on here,
they will never stop.
So they don't they don't do somebody
doing something for reaction, right? Is
someone going on Timmy's and saying
you're an IVA mong and it takes two
three seconds. You're an IVA mong. And
then he'll react. I mean, yeah, that's
for a reaction, but this the ext the the
the the levels that these people go to
to try to get a reaction, it just goes
to show that they're jealous of low
lives. Low lives is like the biggest
thing of it, you know? Sat there in
their 40s hating on people that they
don't [ __ ] know. [ __ ] spastics,
bro. Aren't they really? Yeah.
Do you know what? I should blame my
[ __ ] sister's boyfriend for getting
me on this [ __ ] community. You know
that with these little mongos.
You know, if I didn't play that [ __ ]
roulette machine in that bookies, I
wouldn't have found Timmy and I wouldn't
have found this disabled community.
You know what? I should actually go and
smack him in his [ __ ] face for that
because I can actually confront a grown
man. Um, unlike you, Virgin boy. Um, you
know what I'm saying?
Oh, that's another thing he tried saying
is that I got beat by my sister. Bro, if
a woman ever ever ever
done that to me, I I would just kick
them straight in the [ __ ] I'd kick them
so far up their [ __ ] my [ __ ] foot
would be coming out their mouth. Um,
that's another little simpy thing he
used to do. Um, he used to make up
stories that I got beat up by women
because he's a s. And he used to do all
of these things to defend women because
he's a s. Yeah, bro. I got beat up by a
[ __ ] woman. Yeah, my name's not Money
Mike. My name's not Michael Basset. You
know that is uh I would All you'd have
to do is kick him straight up there.
Fanny, and that would that would be the
end of that, Grimzy.
I like uh Triple H's little accent. No,
that's too far. Peter. Peter, that's too
I don't know if he still got but he did. Yeah.
But yeah, he's actually to blame for it
to be honest because then I wouldn't
have found this community. So actually
that is one of my biggest regrets in
life is actually gambling
in a way where I found this community
not in the not in the sense that like
anything else cuz it never really ruined
my life you know I've still done all the
things I wanted to do. still had money.
So, it didn't affect me like it did
Timmy, you know, but
it it it affected me. Obviously, I've
got on this community with these little mongos,
self-reflecting skin people, you know.
Yeah, but I might have not done it. But
I might have not done it though. That's the thing. [Music]
That burger boy
that M. I found a site I could gamble on
yesterday and I didn't. I was so
tempted, but the way I see it is, yeah,
I can gamble 100 150, but I'd rather
spend that on a night out.
Um, you know what I'm saying? I'd rather
spend that on like a night out.
It's good way of thinking, ain't it, Grezy? Yeah.
Yeah. Do you remember when I used to see
that 150 150 150? Jesus [ __ ] Christ. Damn. Yeah.
They all life losers.
They're little self projectors as well. Yeah.
But I need to be careful with money now,
bro. I don't have money to keep losing.
That's the thing.
It's not good, bro.
I'll probably do a double. Both teams
will score like put 200 pound on it at
some point this month.
I don't know if the National Northern
League is playing anymore or not.
Oh no, man.
It's bad, is it?
It's not bad, but Yeah.
And then [ __ ] Ricky Millindon wants
to say about how, oh, imagine paying for
sex. Imagine paying for sex. Imagine
paying for sex. Well, let me let me let
me tell you this, right? If you had the
amount of money that I did, right, you
of course you would pay for sex. You're
not going to [ __ ] you're not going to
[ __ ] regret on your deathbed paying
for sex cuz it got to the point where
it's like it's not even you actually paying anymore,
you know? Like you're [ __ ] like if
you had all of that money, bro, of
course you'd be [ __ ] with escorts.
I was speaking to this Brazilian escort.
Yeah. And she said that she would have a
kid with me in 4 years. You know, I
actually think that is the way forward.
You know, go meet a Brazilian escort,
right? They will marry you to get a visa
and have a kid with them. And Brazilian
women are not ugly either. And they're
actually nice. Like I generally think
that would actually work. If you want to
think about things that would actually
work, you saying, "Oh, yeah, in four years
like that would actually work,
you know, you know, catching, you know,
then you could actually get somebody
that would marry you. You know, you can
have kids or if you want kids or you
know, you can have sex and stuff.
Brazilian women are nice, bro. They're
not rude like these westernized [ __ ]
And they don't say they got boyfriends
either. Cuz if they actually did have a
boyfriend, they wouldn't say it.
Yeah, it's not possible. There's nothing
possible about it.
And the amount of energy and I never
even done it because I couldn't pull a
different woman. I would have done it
anyways, mate. If you're single or even
if you're in a relation and even if
you're getting laid and you've got all
of this money and you're constantly
getting money, everyone uses escorts.
Why do you think so many famous people
do it? It's so easily accessible.
Why the [ __ ] would you not think of it,
bro? Yeah. You're going out approach and
you've got all of this money. You're
dressed up good. You got a couple of
numbers. Why wouldn't you get an escort?
Why the [ __ ] wouldn't you? It's so easy
accessible, you know? Like, why why the
[ __ ] wouldn't you?
That Ricky Milling is still a [ __ ]
virgin in his [ __ ] 40s and he's
talking about people using escorts.
What the [ __ ]
They're such self-reflectors. It's
[ __ ] madness. And the escorts are
better looking than [ __ ] normal women. Yeah, exactly.
Yeah. Chinese Izzy was said, "Oh, you
should come and see me cuz she's in
[ __ ] Manchester for [ __ ] sake.
She's in [ __ ] Manchester.
Yeah, she's in Manchester, man.
Nah, I'm never leaving [ __ ] London
again, bro. There's no reason to
a good oldfashioned piss up.
Go out for a good oldfashioned piss up.
I'm due one of them, you know. So I do
it next week. Uh
what's next week? Two weeks, which Oh,
it's actually this Well, it's actually
this week. Maybe. Maybe
I might do, you know, because it would
have been two weeks in it.
A good oldfashioned piss up. I love a
Yeah, Finny uh Finnish Izzy said, "Oh
yeah, she'll meet me if I go there."
But yeah, I've retired from this [ __ ]
now, bro. This whole traveling and
whatnot. I've actually retired.
I feel like I've actually retired, bro.
You take the piss out of it, but I'm being serious.
Yeah, there was this woman, the one on
Tinder said that um she would have sex,
but she wouldn't give a [ __ ] I said, "Fuck you."
But you're not going to give me a
[ __ ] [ __ ] off. If some if a woman's
not going to give you a [ __ ] I
wouldn't get with one.
And it's not about if it's your thing or
not. If you're with somebody, it's the
whole point of them making them feel
making you feel good.
Like a woman that doesn't give [ __ ] [ __ ] that.
No thank you. Bye-bye now.
Like I'm going to go out my way to meet
somebody that doesn't give a [ __ ] [ __ ] that.
Even the ugly ones are [ __ ] in this country.
Yeah, they hurt when you [ __ ] wank.
Have you ever had it where you've wanked
a lot and then you've got one and then it hurts?
Maybe I'll go back this week. I'm not sure.
It's just so expensive. That's the thing.
Who do you think's better? Who Why do
you think Nle stalks me every day? Sun-kissed. Huh?
Yeah. Yeah, I might go out Thursday and
Friday. I might actually do Friday, you know,
mix the days up a little bit.
I'll just do Thursday and uh Friday,
maybe this week on next week.
This going out is so expensive, bro.
He calls me ugly. Son kiss. Do you think
I'm ugly? I don't think I'm ugly. I
think I look like a pretty good [ __ ]
I think I look like a pretty good [ __ ] Jeez.
I need to go to the barbers, bro. What the [ __ ]
Go back to Birmingham and slap up Tim. I
would do that ghosting, but I can't do that.
I can't do that because I know how the
Subway uh I know how the Subway um I
know how the Subway cookie crumble crumb
I know how the Subway chocolate chip cookie crumbles.
So, I I I I can't do that anymore, bro.
Oh, she's she's replied back.
Yeah, I might go to Finland on my
birthday, you know. I might I might do
go to Finland.
Yeah, she said she'll meet, but then I
have to go to [ __ ] Finland.
Yeah, but she lives in Finland.
So, I might ask um
lady and stuff to give me some money for
my birthday. I'll [ __ ] off. Yeah.
I'll be able to afford it, mate.
Oh, quite a while. Quite a while.
So, maybe I found a new mama.
Yeah, she was actually nice. She's my
age as well. I'm 2 months older than her
and she's a personal trainer.
Oh, he's in Thailand. He lives in Thailand now.
Do you know what? Looking at her, she
just looked like really stuck up.
But she's actually all right.
Yeah, but he's not hilarious, bro. Cuz
he's the wrong.
You don't even want to know what he done.
See, he [ __ ] himself up with all of that [ __ ]
you know, all of that weirdo [ __ ] that he done.
It would be a little penguin, is it? Me
and the baby can live with the penguins. Nikolai,
you can give baby Peter some milk.
But yeah, he lives in Thailand now anyways. So,
which do you know what? Yeah. even
though he isn't wronging and [ __ ] that
he's done, you know, like he is still
someone to look up to in regards to like
he come off YouTube, he lived his life,
he made the most of his life and he actually changed,
you know, as even though he's a wrong,
you know, it's hard to believe that, but
you know what I mean.
You even showed somebody like that
showed who showed you how it's done. You
even you even had a weirdo like that
show you how it's done.
Yeah, he's personal. He's funny as [ __ ]
though, isn't it? Even if I have to [ __ ]
their kids to [ __ ] them. Yeah. They were
mocking you. They were laughing at you.
He said that when I was traveling up and
down the country, they were mocking you.
They were laughing at you.
Yeah, I've been there. It's a [ __ ]
Yeah, that's East London. I've been there.
Where do you live?
Yeah, it's that's a [ __ ] Yeah, barking.
I'm going to go out again at some point.
Ghosting, but it's so expensive, bro. If
I didn't win this football bet on
[ __ ] Tuesday, I could have been in some bother.
Like, not that I would I would have
starved or something or something. I
would have had money, but um
I'm just like a normal person that works.
I would have been in some bother, bro.
If I tried going out again a few times,
I would have been in some actual bother.
I would have actually been in some
serious bother, bro.
If I tried to do them
400,£300 a couple more times, I would
have been [ __ ] you know, which is
obvious. Like, you live in London, bro.
At the end of the day, like most people
are even struggling.
I'm used to having like loads and loads
of money coming in all the [ __ ] time. So,
yeah. Yeah, if I didn't win that
football bet, bro, then um yeah, we
could have been
like maybe 15% toast, mate. Basically,
Chester. What? That's near Southampton, isn't it?
I met a woman from Southampton the other
day. She's a stuck up [ __ ]
Uh yeah, I done a 30 pound both score no
draw for a laugh,
but on Tuesday I done a 120 um double
and it come in for 380
which I should have put the 160 on it. I
was going to put 160 on it. Um but I put
a 40 on the roulette. I wish I put the
160 on it now.
But I'll probably have to do that again
during the month. During the month, lad.
probably in a two weeks I'll probably
have to do some sort of other football bet
cuz in about in London it doesn't matter
how much money you have it just goes
but I mean there's a place that has
happy hour on drinks and stuff.
So yeah, I I put 120 on [ __ ] This is
why I don't want to lose money anymore,
bro. Cuz it's so hard to like come by
nowadays, you know, money and [ __ ] that
you don't really want to lose it.
But I I I signed up to an online casino
right yesterday and I was going to
gamble like 150 and I was like, I don't
really want to be risking it,
you know? I don't really I don't really
want to risk it,
you know. I don't really want to risk
losing that kind of money because I can
spend that on a night out. So, I'm just
like a normal person,
you know? So, I'm just like a normal
person that basically just works.
I'm probably better off than probably a
lot of people as well. And even in
London, it's just a struggle.
If you want to go out and keep drinking,
it's expensive as [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, she's blonde, man. I might just go
to Finland in it.
How you doing, Kim with the gambling,
man? You're right.
You're a braver man than me, bro. Like
cuz we're on like the same amount of
money now. But I I I can't even.
We probably will have to get to that
point when I'm low on money again. If
I'm low on money, I probably will have
to play roulette. But I signed up to a
casino yesterday, bro, and I didn't want
to lose £200.
I'd rather spend it on a night out.
I don't It's not that I don't have it to lose.
It's not really worth the risk,
you know, especially now, you know, it's
like I I'd rather just
if I'm lucky, I could probably get two
nights out with like 200 pound.
So, it's like if you lose 150 200 Yeah, man.
It's bad. It's hard trying to bet. I
done a 120 football bet on Tuesday and
it returned um 380. Yeah, I withdrew
160. It was my mom's birthday and I was
just bored and I was like, "Yeah, I want
to try and win like some extra money cuz
I went out Sunday and spent [ __ ] knows
how much." A lot. Um and she uh yeah, I
just put 120 on it. So, I was like, "Oh,
it covered for basically what I spent."
It's expensive, bro. London's expensive,
man. You know, even when I was on that
three grand a month, it seemed to like,
oh [ __ ] where's the money go? Where's
the money going?
[ __ ] madness, bro.
Yeah, I've won three. I've won three out of six. Yeah.
I wish I had more in it, though.
I wish I had more on the football, bro.
I wish I had more in it.
But that's always the way you wish you
had more on it, isn't it?
Yeah, there was an online site like I
might gamble next month like 150 or
whatever, you know, and see, you know, but pointless.
How when you going to lose it, how you
going to lose it?
How you going to lose it?
You know, he's a narcissistic, horrible little [ __ ]
bro. All you all I do is both teams to score.
But yeah, 120 to 380. That's quite a
good return really. Um,
and obviously I don't want to be losing money because
then I'm basically [ __ ] So yeah,
I don't want to be losing money, bro,
cuz it's just going to make problems a
million times worse. So at the end of
the day, if I can have like some money, then
just go out with the money in it, but
I'm probably going to go out drinking
Thursday and Friday. Maybe not this
week. Maybe this week, maybe not. Maybe
next week. But
I don't really go out drinking much anymore, Kieran.
I don't really go out doing it much,
bro. I've done it so many I've done it so much.
You don't know how happy I was to win
that football back, bro.
You really don't.
You really don't know.
[ __ ] [ __ ] But yeah. Anyways, at least
I can say I could I might have found I
found a new mama.
I found a new mommy in Finland.
No, I don't play them.
Just the football, bro. I don't play them.
Wonder how much it will be to go to
Finland for 3 days. [ __ ] sake.
It's like 3 hours on a plane.
taking a baby away from its mama.
That's not socially acceptable.
That's not socially That is not the socotally acable
because it's my mother cuz I can do some
cold approach in Finland as well.
I can go and live with the penguins, you know.
I swear, Kier, when I'm getting old, you
know, mate, with all of this traveling
up and down the country, [ __ ]
approaching and [ __ ] Oh, I feel 100
years old. I'm retired from this [ __ ] now, mate.
I'm [ __ ] retired. [Laughter] I'm retired.
taking a bumpion away from its mama.
Taking a bumpion away from its mama.
Taking ashion away from it mama. No,
it's not near Russia. It's near Sweden.
So, how much money do you have now, Kieran? H
I want to go down to the brewery again
and get pissed.
I like going to the brewery and getting pissed.
It cost a [ __ ] bomb, mate. A roast
dinner and a cup of [ __ ] pine is like
50 [ __ ] quid.
It costs a [ __ ] bomb, bro.
Is this how people have been living for [ __ ] years? years, man?
Working. And I've got more disposable
money than probably most people.
And is this how people been living for years?
What did you win it on?
So what? Now you're skin. Yeah.
So what are you skimp now or [ __ ]
So what your skin now?
What? You actually owe money? I only owe
the barber money because um I didn't pay
him because I was walking the other way
and I didn't want to go back. So I don't
owe any money. I've got no bills. So yeah.
So I take it your skin now.
So how how much would you say you have now?
To be honest, I'm just lucky I had a
house for 3 years.
I should have saved more from it. But
see, this is normal. Like how I'm living
now. Like I'm not skinned. I'm fine. But
when you're used to having so much money,
it probably take like 6 months to adjust, you know,
cuz of um I always had money coming
here, there, and everywhere. Now I
don't. So when I have money, I just have
I just have that money, you know, like
even though you're not skin, you're not
like struggling. You're still better off
than most people, believe you me. But
it's still like
it nice to have like £300 coming in
every week or something. It's difficult now, bro.
But now I know something will come up,
you know. Sorry. Yeah.
Like I said, if I didn't win that
football bet, well, I would have been in some bother.
So, how much money would you say that
you've got now?
I must have been in the mind. minority
with all that money I used to have, bro.
In London, I must have been
living the dream, bro. Living the [ __ ] dream, you know.
But it doesn't really matter, bro. I
just even if you have like 2.7K in your
account, you're laughing.
Even something like that, like you can
just build yourself up. But it's hard
nowadays, you know.
bad. It's hard, bro. It's hard.
[ __ ] sake. [ __ ] getting your
haircut is like 40 quid.
So, I'll probably have to like free
drink now, which is what most people do.
Cuz I used to look at my friend, right,
is like you you're drinking at Tesco's.
Why are you drinking at Tesco's?
Why are you drinking at [ __ ] Tesco's? Um,
you know what I'm saying? And then I was
like, "Oh, that's why."
Because obviously I got stung by it
eventually as well, the cost of it all,
you know. So yeah, see £400 that
wouldn't be enough for me, bro. Cuz when
I'm which is enough for most people cuz
when I go out, I'm going to spend a
bomb. I'm going to spend an absolute
bomb. I think I've got like 1,300
money that I can actually touch, you
know, like. But once you go out once,
you're basically screwed.
But there is two days I'm going to go
out. But I'm going to have to be I'm
going to do a Thursday and Friday. So
some people do Saturday, Sunday. I'm
going to do Thursday, Friday. I think
them two days are good. Um
yeah, probably looking at about £300,
but I think we could probably lower it
down if we wanted to.
See, we're not [ __ ] We're good. But
you know how it is, bro. It see if you
wanted to go out drinking, you'd be done for.
Which is why people don't go out
drinking in this country. It's only
tourists that go out.
Cuz people don't have money here. You
know what I'm saying? That's why people Nah. Nah.
What do you mean it wouldn't cover a
night out? Like you wouldn't spend 400
on a night out in it. To be honest with
you, Kieran, bro, I'm bored of the whole
going out now. I do it like once every
two weeks minimum. I'm bored of it. Like
I'd rather just sit and chill, you know?
And like I I'm not like I was. And it's
not just cuz the money. It's cuz of um I
just got bored of it. I've done it so
many times. You know, like he
you know what I'm saying?
Um it's not that it's the fact that like
I I where I've done it so many times
which is probably why I don't even
gamble much anymore. I've done it so many times.
Yeah. I I always go central because
yeah, a night out will probably be like
100 120, you know, but
I do it every like couple of weeks
because it's not because of the money,
bro. Like, it isn't. But when I when I
won that football bet, I could have easy
went out that midweek if I wanted to. It's not
it it's not just about that.
It's about the whole like I've done it a
million times and I'd rather do it when
I'm really bored.
So like I appreciate it more. Like I
might even go fabrics. I haven't been
fabrics for ages.
So obviously if I'm going Finland then
I'm going to have to obviously be
careful. So you know like just a normal
person now to be honest.
Yeah, without money I should have
started like some sort of my own
business, but you don't think when
you're living in the moment, you know?
Yeah. Virgin boy. Virgin boy can't go out.
No, it's not. Listen, listen. It's never
going to happen again. Kieran. Kieran.
Kieran. Kieran. It's never going to
happen again. I know how the Subway
chocolate chip cookie crumbles, you
know. I I'm never going to do that
again, bro. Just what, Kieran? Why do
you think I don't show these people
money ever anymore? Why do you think I
don't call these people out? Because I
know what they do. Just like the Mark
Samson thing when I went to his area two
times and then whenever he'd come back
on YouTube back to like the big man, no
one ever mentions it. You got to
understand, I don't know how you look,
right? But if you're not fat and ugly
like these people, right, they do not
like you. And if they do not like you,
they will always be biased. So, bro,
it's never happening ever again. Cuz I
know like like I was saying, which you
didn't hear. Yeah. I was so tempted on
Friday, bro, to go to Birmingham and
smash that cunt's face in. But we all
know how the cookie crumbles. We all
know the story on here now. We all know
the five city stories, you know. You know,
you know. Yeah. Exactly. They do it.
Yeah. Because they're skin. And you know
another thing is right when I bank that
money, let me tell you another thing.
When I bank that money,
when I bank that money, bro, right? When
um, I also got a back payment from the benefits.
So, you know, I I I you know, I got I
got money from the benefits that they
owed me. Bro, do you know how much money
I had? And I was like, I'm never showing
these people money ever again. Just like
when I was in the bookies. I'm never
ever showing them money ever again. They
can cry. They can winge. They can say
that I'm skinn. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
I'm not showing them anything ever again.
Look at this book. Look at this skinned
virgin in the bed sit Kieran thinking
that he's got money, thinking that he's
got 14 grand, you know? Um, was there
any 14 grand when you were showing money
for [ __ ] god knows how many months?
You know, bro, these people asking, I'm
never showing them money again. I'm
never meeting any of them again. If he
comes to London, I'll meet him. I said
to I said to uh Michael and [ __ ]
Timmy, if you come to London,
I will literally meet you anywhere. And
it's like this Joe F guy, you know,
showing his pension and showing 1,500
pounds, trying to give people a lecture
about working, but okay, you've got all
of this money. Why did you all run away?
When whenever you get show money, why do
you all run away?
That's that. You know what I'm saying?
So, it's like it's pointless. It's
pointless with these people, bro. It's
pointless getting into it with these people. Yeah.
And don't forget that that that that
um money that Virgin Boy showed. Yeah.
Is bro, he has no life experience.
He's never even been to Scotland. He
hasn't even been anywhere, you know? So,
at the end of the day, it's like this Jo,
they they forget when you show money.
They forget when you show dates. They
forget when you've gone to mark
something's area two times.
If you're going to be on there, you
might as well just post your own content
and just ignore these clowns, these
jealous people that ain't got a life.
You know, they got shown so much money
for so long. And I was like, "Fuck it.
I'm just spending some of it now and
banking some of it cuz I had so much of
it." So I was like, "Fuck this."
they skip themselves, bro. All of them
are skin. They're all little low lives.
I have to hate on people every day that
they don't know.
14 [ __ ] grand. You've never had 14
grand in your life, you [ __ ] virgin.
Every single time Yeah. I was showing
that money. All he could show was £800.
That's what I'm saying, bro. This This
is pointless on here.
Yeah. And apparently I'm the one that's
got [ __ ] anxiety.
Never had anxiety in my I don't even get
anxiety when I drink now.
Anxiety about what?
Do you know what I'm saying?
I don't get anxiety because of like I'm
I've been through so much [ __ ] you
know? Like there's nothing that could
give me anxiety.
You know what I'm saying, bro?
So he got £400 to last you the month.
Oh, bless you then, Karen. Bless you.
But um yeah,
let's [ __ ] in life.
Let's [ __ ] in life.
If you want a grand le
Yeah, I used to play that fishing
frenzy, but it would just [ __ ] rinse me, man.
It would absolutely just [ __ ] rinse me. Oh, [ __ ] I can.
I [ __ ] can. Virgin boy.
skin. Virgin boy. I love that me. You
love that as well. Karen. Virgin boy.
I love that. Love that.
I went to the pictures on Friday. Nah.
Yeah. Till he own. He made up a story,
right, that my sister beat me up.
He's such a simp. That's singing to a new level.
You know that my sister beat me up. I
didn't know my sister beat me up. That's
news to me. Wow, that's interesting.
He's such a narcissistic little virgin, isn't it?
He needs to get laid. He need He's in
desperate need to [ __ ] get laid.
I think when he finally loses his B
card, bro, I think he'll actually be a
nicer person, you know?
Yeah. Yeah. I said they're looking at
you like they think that they're the
[ __ ] Yeah. With that westernized look
that they give you. Yeah, I said that.
But no, my [ __ ] sister never beat me
up. And my [ __ ] dad's never hit my by
my sisters. That's made up. That's self
projecting from his [ __ ] up childhood
cuz he got starved by his mother and he
was put into care.
No, my my dad's never hit my mom or my
sisters. No. No. That's completely made
up. That's your childhood.
That's your childhood, mate.
No, that's your childhood.
And then you started saying about how my
um I asked my sisters about anal. No,
that never happened. Never mentioned I
never mentioned anal in my life.
Never mentioned anal in my [ __ ] life.
What the [ __ ] Made up. Made up
Yeah, literally made up.
You can't even keep a a straight face
when you're making up these stories.
Yeah. Why would I tell someone that my
dad's beating up my sisters and my
[ __ ] mom? What the [ __ ]
Who the [ __ ] would tell some random
person that if that actually happened?
Yeah, that's just made up.
Yeah, that's made up. You know, all of
this is projecting from his [ __ ] up childhood.
How are you going to lose it? How are
you going to lose it? And I was only a
baby elephant back then. I didn't know
that he was projecting his virginity
onto me all along. Nicolo, I was a baby
elephant back then.
I was a baby elephant back then.
But yeah, rest be assured, Kieran. I'm
not going to Birmingham, bro. I'm not
wasting my time or money on these people
ever again, lad. Rest be [ __ ] assured.
Rest be a shard.
You know, I know what they do, bro, with
Bob. They're all the same on here.
They're all the [ __ ] You know what
you should do on here? You should just
go out to a nightclub and just start
approaching women and just annoy them.
That's what you should do. Just annoy
them and show them what they can never
do and what they can never afford to do.
That's what you should do. you know,
just by saying that they'll probably
just pretend they never saw it like they
always do. But, you know, deep down like
a good old live stream once in a while
will annoy them. Yeah.
I'm not going to get kicked out cuz they
don't know the places that I go.
They don't know the places that I go to.
This community is so narcissistic.
Have you noticed that, Kieran? It's so narcissistic.
No. Go live and just annoy them by
showing you speak to women and stuff.
Do what kills him. Do what kills them. Yeah.
And then you got these little snakes
Kieran, right? Like Ricky Millindon. You
think some little [ __ ] spaz from hole
could even look at me in real life like
let alone try and slag me off on the
internet? Like I said that Mike Tyson
quote all of them years was true. Mike
Tyson quoted this before. You know
something about how a keyboard gives
people power. Yeah.
Yeah. They got me banned. I mean they've
helped me. They've saved me a lot of money.
It's a very narcissistic community. This
is Kieran. It's basically fat, ugly
people, sorry ass losers, cuz they're
all sorry asses that ain't got no life,
got [ __ ] all to live for. So that's why
they come online calling people that
they don't know every day cuz they're
sad skinned, miserable. You know, the
more they do this, the more happy I feel
I am to be myself. They could actually
make people feel good about themsel.
You know what I'm saying? So yeah,
do a little video in Finland in it, Nicolola.
Do a little uh video in Finland.
How did you know baby elephants was my
favorite animals, Nicolola?
Yeah, they're obsessed with Timmy, but
they're more obsessed with me, bro.
They're more obsessed with me. Like, you
know, Red Star, Virgin Boy, you know,
I've got more people obsessed with me
than that's how you know you got a
better life than them. You know, if
you've got that many haters, bro, you
know that like you're doing something
right. That's why they've actually make
they've made me feel good about being me.
You feel good about being me, you know.
I had three pieces of chicken yesterday,
Nicolo. Two fives and one middle breast. Yeah,
you can't beat two fives. And so what
are you going to do for the rest of the
month, Kieran, with 400 left? Bless you.
Bless you in life. Then what are you
going to do?
How you going to lose it?
He's an agrophobic fat ugly bastard that
ain't got a life. He's a fat ugly
triggered little bunter that ain't got a life.
My face, bro. I'm not scared. Look,
he'll be he'll be clipping this now.
Look at my little face. My little eyes.
My beard. I'm better looking than these
people will ever be, bro. Ever be. Even
looking homeless as I am now. Don't
remind me. I need to go to the barbers. But yeah,
I know. I need to go to the barbers. Don't judge.
Yeah, but how are you going to go out and drink?
Yeah, but Yeah, but how you going to go
out and drink?
See, he'll be clipping this right now
cuz he ain't got a life. Look, I've
actually got teeth. A certain virgin
don't have teeth.
See, look. All of this stuff like you've
got a big nose. There's nothing wrong
with my nose. I look like a normal human being,
you know? I look like a normal human
being. There's nothing wrong with my
nose. There's nothing wrong with me.
You know, you're just an insecure little virgin.
That's why you talk about people's nose
because you're an insecure little
virgin. You know, all of this, let me
let me put it this way, right? All of
this time that you've wasted, right? All
of this time that you've wasted talking
about my [ __ ] nose. All you've done
is embarrass yourself because you don't
make anyone feel ugly with your ugly
melted face. You little virgin face on
YouTube. with your little [ __ ] virgin
face with a fat ugly girlfriend in the
beds. That's my little nickname for you, mate.
Oh, bless you then if you're just friends.
No, I need to go out and get some
[ __ ] women, matey.
That's why sometimes I need to win these bets.
I I remember when I [ __ ] spent £700
on a night out. That's never happened again, mate.
That's [ __ ] never happening again.
[ __ ] £700 on a night out.
Yeah, that's when we were [ __ ] made
of money, Kieran.
That's when we was [ __ ] made of money, lad.
That's when we were [ __ ] made of money, mate.
We were literally made of money, mate.
From the from the [ __ ] toes to the [ __ ] head. Literally, mate.
No, he said two grand on a night out.
Yes, he said two grand. He's full of
[ __ ] The only reason Well, I said I
spent £700, but I gambled, but I won the
money back from the gambling. I put I
was with the 19year-old, right? I put £300 in
and then I got uh 900 out. [ __ ] got pissed.
Got absolutely wrecked. Booked the hotel.
[ __ ] madness, bro. It was a madness.
But I obviously won on the gambling
stuff, but obviously still turned out to
be £700. But obviously, yeah, I couldn't
do that now.
Oh, bless you then. If it's doing your
head in bless.
Yeah. Bless you then. You should meet up
with me. Go for a pipe. Karen. We can go
to the brewery.
You know, we'll show these women who's boss.
You know, we'll show them who's boss.
We'll show them who's boss.
Is that okay with you, boss?
Make it so.
Okay with you, boss.
Okay with you, boss. I love that.
Is that okay with you, [ __ ]
Is that okay with you, pun?
Make it so.
See, I'm not like you anymore, Kieran. I
used to be like you. Bless you. Oh, mate.
Yeah, that was what me and Antman was
saying. 100. Yeah. Oh, bless you.
Friends to the end.
So, yeah, I found a new mama now. Nicolo,
you like that USA, Izzy, didn't you, Kieran?
You like that USA?
You wanted a little binge.
I can't believe I was speaking to her
friend on the phone for 5 hours. She's
like, "She actually did that?"
Yep, she did. She came on kissing me and
it was very inappropriate, actually.
Yes, I can.
She did that. I said, "Yep."
How did I even get involved with these Yanks? You know,
save. You need to find God, little man.
Only he can save you.
Peter Belly can't get attached anymore
because he's already found his mama.
So, you know, this Finnish one, yeah,
she's 27, but she's 28 in December, and
I'm obviously 28 in October. So, it's
nice to find somebody that's the same
age as you.
That [ __ ] Ukrainian one was supposed
to meet me, but she turned out to be a [ __ ]
[ __ ] ghost and [ __ ] in it.
Yeah, she turned out to be a ghosting [ __ ] man.
No, she said, "Oh, sometimes I forgot to
reply." She said, "Yeah, Scotland's been
good." And um yeah, you can come
anytime. And I said to her, "Oh, yeah.
It gives me time to think about where
I'm going to take you on our first
date." She said, "Haha, sounds good.
That's my mama."
How cute is that? Finding a new mama, you know?
Yeah, but USA Izzy wasn't my mommy, was
she, Nicolo? Cuz she didn't look like me.
She didn't even look like me. So, how
could that be my mama, you know?
How could that be my mama? Yeah,
virgin boy can't do that.
Yeah, I approached her. She was with her
sister was in the brewery. Peter Betty's
got some balls, don't he?
Peter Belly's got some bollocks, don't he? Hey,
don't want you
don't want to know.
She don't want to know.
Don't want to know you.
Don't want to know you, mate. Don't want
to know you.
She don't want to know you. She don't
want to know you. She don't want to know
you. She don't want to know. I want to
know. I want to know.
>> Yeah, I know, bro. I wanted the ground
to swallow me up. I said, "Oh, I didn't
want to like be rude cuz obviously I
know you're with your mom."
And she's like, "Oh, uh, yeah, it's my
sister." I said, "Oh, man." But they
didn't make it they didn't make it
awkward cuz that's why I was It was a
few things. It was like, "She's not
exactly my type and she's with her mother."
So like the thing is right it's like
sometimes you know when someone's good
enough but they're not good enough for
you to actually waste your energy
approaching especially when you know the
outcome you feel like ah I can't be bothered
you know but I was like you might as
well [ __ ] it in it you know.
Yeah I thought it was her mom but it was
awkward as [ __ ]
cuz she looked quite a lot older than
her as well.
Her mom must have had her young and her
sister her later. It did not look like
her [ __ ] sister at all, bro.
Like at all at all.
That's what I'm saying.
Taking a bubin away from its mama.
Taking a bubin away from it mama. Bless.
don't want to know you.
So, I've I've spoke to Britney
from Canada and Okay. And and what what
has she said? Don't want you, mate.
What What do you mean don't want you?
Don't want you. Literally don't want
you, mate. What? What? What do you mean?
She just just don't want to know you.
Just don't want to know you. They simply
don't want to know your ugly ass. And
that's the end of that. That's all she
was saying for for the whole four hours
of me speaking to her. Don't want to
know yet. Just don't just don't want to
know. Just don't want to know.
Just just just don't want you don't want you.
Theism is strong when you're obsessed
with somebody in Canada that that don't
want you that you've never met. How can
you be obsessed with somebody
3 years who you've never even met that
that literally was not interested in
you? You know, at least with my mommy,
you know, I kissed her and I got to
taste her boobs and I got intimate with
her and [ __ ] [ __ ] hell. But [ __ ]
three years for somebody that rejected
you. [ __ ] hell.
Three years. Somebody that you didn't
even know. You don't even want to know you.
You didn't get to let take her lady
parts. All of the things I done with USA
Izzy, you've never done with Britney.
That's where the jealousy comes into it.
And you know that I own this [ __ ] on
YouTube so badly that when the loser's
got no fight left in him, he's got he's
on the ground literally fighting for his
life for being owned so badly. He's got
his ass a good oldfashioned Mike Tyson
weapon. He has to run to the boys in
blue. Boo. What a loser. They always go
to the police in the end of losers.
But they literally struggling like ah
they've got nothing left in them. And
then they find a number of the boys in
blue and then they call the boys in
blue. What a [ __ ] loser.
Imagine being that much of a loser. You
have to run to the police over YouTube
again. People forget they didn't see
that. Just like they forget Peter Belly
didn't own them at the money game a
million times. It doesn't suit them.
To the boys in blue.
Yeah. You just wear a cup of tea. That's
what Natalie G said about um about him.
She's just not just not uh just not her cuper.
He don't tickle my fancy with her exact
words. And that's absolutely fine. You
know, there's there's nothing wrong with
somebody not finding you physically
attractive. You know, it's like I'll
give you an example. I have three sugars
in my cup of tea and my muma has no
sugars in her cup of tea. Everyone's got
a different taste. You know, you just
you're just not for them. And that's
absolutely fine. That's absolutely fine
to be rejected. You know, there's
nothing wrong with that, you know.
There's nothing wrong with that, mate.
There's nothing wrong with that, you [ __ ] virgin.
Oh no, Franklin, don't stick your middle
up. Don't stick your middle finger up, Franklin.
That's food. Franklin,
don't stick your middle finger up. Franklin Franklin.
Sorry, man. I just Franklin's been
really bad today. You know,
it's okay to not tickle someone's fancy.
You You just didn't get their vagina
wet, you know. and you just didn't get
them weakened the needs.
You know, it's like when I approached
USA, she knew she wanted that Podger
straight away when she offered me her
number. She wanted a she wanted a D
there and then she wanted a Peter
Belly's special, you know, I made her
weak in the knees, you know, the little
tart, you know, whereas you
you you're not her cup of tea, mate, you
know. You're not her cup of tea in life.
Just didn't want to know, you know. No,
that's absolutely fine.
Nothing wrong with that.
Yep. Do you want my number?
Yeah, I want your number.
You remember that? That's Do you know
that day is when I bought the Stone
Island and a new pair of trainers? It
was my first time going out in the GS,
you know? Uh yeah,
it was the first time
me going out in the stony and that's why
I became a believer in it for so long.
That's why I became a believer in it. A
believer in the Sony
cuz of um
uh I don't think so. No, I have got a
body warmer but I didn't have it on. No.
I just thought, oh, let me try my luck
with this young lady
and see what the score is. I've still
got the video, you know, where I approached
cuz I want to keep it forever because
it's just a one in a lifetime thing, you know.
Yeah, that was the same day.
Uh, maybe I did have it on. I don't
think I did. Maybe I did. Maybe I didn't.
All I know is I was wearing a Sony. So
I can't do that. Imagine my car that I car
the [ __ ] virgin me
[ __ ] virgin virgin nasty nasty
[ __ ] virgin cut me nasty [ __ ] virgin coming.
Yeah, I've still got all the little stonies.
because I've already found my mama.
Cuz I already found my mama.
How cute is that when you've already
found your mama?
Because he's already found his mama.
All right. Do you remember that time,
bro, with the Indonesian guy when um it
was me and the army lads
and the Indonesian guy, right? And uh
I was like, "Oh, let me approach this uh
woman. Let's approach these two women."
So, I approached one who I like the look
of more cuz she had bigger boobies. And
then he approached another one
and then she didn't like him. And then
she ended up kissing the army guy's
friend who was already in a
relationship. I was like, "Fuck that.
That is brutal."
Damn, that is crazy. They were mocking
you, laughing at you. Cuz she didn't
like him. But obviously her friend me
and her friend was kissing and then me
and the ar me and the ar me and the army
me and the me and the army guy was
kissing the two women and he was just
sat there like a lost little puppy.
Yeah, of course he did. He said it's torture.
He said it was torture. [Laughter]
Do you remember?
That was funny as [ __ ] bro. It
And it's happened before. They done it
in front of him. Horrible. [ __ ]
horrible that is. Yeah, [Laughter]
[ __ ] Yeah. Yeah.
That is crazy, isn't it? And he went out
with me on my birthday and on my
birthday I had a one night stand and he
had to go all the way home by himself
from the swan,
you know, in a way. Yeah. He is actually
an all right guy, you know, like he he
went out with me for my birthday and stuff,
but he is actually really scared to
speak to anyone,
which is strange cuz I I'm not scared.
Me, I don't give a [ __ ] bro. I don't
give a lion. [ __ ]
I talk to any [ __ ]
Maybe two and a half years. Yeah.
But I don't know why he's scared cuz me
and the tenant used to go out approaching.
Um he would only do it in the club,
which is strange cuz he doesn't drink
cuz he's Muslim, right? But he would do
it in the club. So he would he would
never do it on the street, but he would
do it in a club even though he never
drunk. But he was Muslim. He never
drunk. That was the one that was
actually all right.
So, it's kind of like, well,
it's crazy cuz he would do it sober in a
club, but he would never do it on the street. Yeah. Strange.
Mad. It's not hard for me, mate.
It's not hard for me. I do it anywhere.
Train station, street.
I don't I do it everywhere, mate. I
don't give a [ __ ]
Yeah, everybody knows that you're a crazy [ __ ]
I'm trying to think the weirdest place
I've done it. I've done them everywhere, bro.
Trying to think of where is a hard a
hard situation to do it. I think the
weather spoons can be hard sometimes cuz
it seems very awkward. There's no vibe.
But I'll just go and approach anyone. I
don't give a [ __ ]
Maybe the weather spoons. I think
they can be quite difficult. What's the day today?
They can be quite difficult sometimes.
Yeah. What makes me laugh is you'll
approach somebody and then everyone just
looks like mind your own [ __ ]
business. Do you remember the guy
clapping on the balcony? Oh my god.
I attracted a [ __ ] crowd. So my
friend was like, "Oh yeah, you should go
and approach this person that's walking.
And at the time I was like kind of fed
up with the whole I've got a boyfriend [ __ ]
I was just fed up with it. I was like,
"Okay, [ __ ] it. I might as well." Then I
done it. I've still got their number, by
the way. They never ever reply back.
And um all of a sudden, you hear this
clap come from [ __ ] nowhere. And I've
looked up and the guy was at the [ __ ] balcony,
you know? It's like clapping. I was
like, "What the [ __ ]
They must have been watching me off. Yeah.
Yeah, that's funny. Yeah. And then the
shopkeeper asked me how it went. I said,
"Yeah, I got the number." Yeah.
You take my [ __ ] money, I'll [ __ ] take yours.
That's a funny saying as well, is it?
You take my [ __ ] money. You want to
take my money, I'll take yours.
I don't even think I've ever said that
to be honest.
That's got to be quote of the [ __ ]
year. You know,
we all know how the five city stories go
with these people in this community.
I said to Trip H, I'll come to Newcastle
next Saturday and we'll go for a good oldfashioned pissup.
Good oldfashioned piss up. What do you
think? Me and Trip 8's going for a good
oldfashioned piss up. But what if I
actually go there? Do you reckon he'll meet me?
I'll go to Newcastle.
I'll go to Newcastle, bro. Yeah,
I'll go Newcastle, mate. will go for a
good oldfashioned piss up. But will he
come out though, Nicolo?
Good oldfashioned piss up.
Now we can go, you know, good old
Newcastle fashioned piss up.
How do you How do you know, Nikolola?
The first time I went there, he said he
couldn't meet me because he's in
hospital. Then the second time he said
he was in Wakefield.
And then the third time,
I can't actually remember what happened then either.
He used another excuse. So I've actually
been to Newcastle three times,
but he never comes out.
He never comes out.
You know that little [ __ ] Jordy tow rag.
What the [ __ ]
I've already seen what he looks like on
WhatsApp. I've seen what he looks like. Tall [ __ ]
[ __ ] tall [ __ ] No, I've seen what
he looks like. I used to have him on [ __ ] WhatsApp.
That all night Spaz gives it the big
but. But when I was in Scotland two
times, he was nowhere to be seen.
And he's still You would have thought,
bro, in them years these people would
have grew up by now.
They've been doing this for [ __ ]
years. Like, I shouldn't even be
laughing at these little mongos, right?
But they've actually been doing this for
for actual years, bro.
They've actually been doing this for
years. Like, it's not even a joke, you know?
And they're still doing it even when
they don't show up.
He was nowhere to be seen the Scottish Spaz.
You know why would you think you are the
[ __ ] when you know you ain't the [ __ ] You know
do you know what Oreo man said? He said
what? He hates working. Like you don't
want to work all your life, you know,
getting up from your comfy bed in the
morning, going to work, you know,
getting up from your comfy bed.
Getting up from your comfy bed.
From your comfy bed in the morning.
I missed a 19year-old giving me um
giving me a [ __ ]
She swallowed my babies, Nicola.
She swallowed my She swallowed my bubins.
My little bubshins.
How cute is that?
I don't see the the the the the the
problem with escorts.
I don't see the problem with escorts to be honest.
I mean, it's not a right or wrong
answer, but I've never I've always seen it as
there's nothing wrong with escorts.
I don't know about you, but
I don't see the problem with it.
Do you remember Nicolola? Go to bars. You know, you know,
do you remember go to bars on Reddit?
They say go to bars, you know.
I might say to that little finish Izzy,
I'm going to take you to get your little nails done.
She's mine now. She's all mine.
Nobody else is
Nicolo. See, once they meet Peter Belly,
they can't get rid of the [ __ ]
You can't get rid of the [ __ ] on it.
You're my mama now. Nobody else's.
You're my mama. No one else is. [Laughter]
Taking a baby away from its mama.
Now I want more. Yeah.
It's like USA. Is it? She gave me a
taste of what Boston's like, what
Americans like. Now I want more.
You know, now I want more. You know,
you can't have the goodies
only once. You know what fun is that?
You know, you can't have the goodies only once.
you know what Oreo man was saying?
That's who they That's who these women
give the goods to. That's who That's who
these women give up the goods for.
That's who they give up the goods to.
That's who these people give up the goods. Yeah.
Yeah. I said I'll make his kid give me a massage.
Yeah. He was Yeah. I lost 150. That's
the time when I went out with that
19year-old. I just I ditched her and I
had money. I had loads of money, but I
just lost with 150 and I thought, "Fuck
it. I'll ditch her own it."
Yeah, just ditched her
when I said I hope the [ __ ] casinos
manager kids rubbed my back in a bath.
Yeah, I wanted to do the [ __ ] in. I was
close to doing the [ __ ] in.
You want to take my [ __ ] money, I'll
[ __ ] take yours. You want to take my
money, I'll take yours. Yep.
[ __ ] blaming that poor house edge.
Poor [ __ ] Only 2 months and 7 days
old and he gets the blame for it. That
poor [ __ ] house edge. Bless it. It's
done no one no harm in life and he gets
to blame for everything, you know.
[ __ ] house edge. Yeah.
Imagine I didn't come on here and I
didn't give you all these fun
experiences and I didn't take you around with me. You know,
>> I really want you, but I don't think
you'll want me.
You don't want me? I do.
But we're in public. We're in the public
eye, you know. We need to go somewhere a
bit more quiet, a bit more professional.
You know, I really want you, but I don't
think you want me.
You know, but I don't think you want me. I do.
She gave me a lush [ __ ]
and then she blocked me the next day.
And even her sometimes I still try to
message her. Cuz
once you meet Peter Belly and you give
him some sort of sex, I'm with you forever.
Can't get rid of the [ __ ] I know what
it's like. I can't get rid of this
little tent virgin
with a fat ugly girlfriend skin in a
fing bedset. You know, I know what it's
like when you can't get rid of a [ __ ]
[ __ ] I can't get rid of the [ __ ]
The only way this [ __ ] will stop is if
they're dead or in prison.
I can't get rid of the [ __ ] you know.
I don't know. I I searched his name up
the other day and I can't I can't find
him. Luke Lambbeath.
And you didn't say about Cheryl Cole's
not uglier. You said that if you don't
find her attractive, you're gay. Yes,
you are copying. That is being a
copycat. Cuz if you look on the
internet, everyone will say the same
thing. You don't find Shevel Co
attractive, you're gay. You're [ __ ]
gay. Yeah, they all copy each other.
No one said ugly. Someone said, you said
if you don't find her attractive, you're
gay. Yes, you're copying. That is
copying the crowd.
Yeah, you're copying. You just want to
fit in. Bless him. He just wanted to fit
in. He just He just wanted to fit in.
Bless him, Ben. If he wanted to fit in,
he wanted to fit in with the crowd. Bless him. Hello.
That's it then.
Bless him then. He wanted to fit in.
What should I eat today? I'm not sure.
I shouldn't let him he wanted to fit in.
Yeah. They refused to pay out.
Yeah. I've got um a friend that's got a
dad and um he was up to some dodgginess
in like the bookies with one of the
workers and um they refused to pay him
out. Like they were fiddling with like
the credits and then one day they just
refused to pay out. He smashed the shop
up. They refused to pay out.
They refused to pay out. Yeah,
they refused to pay out.
Yeah, they refused to pay out. He
smashed the shop up. Crazy bastard.
Yeah, they were like fiddling around
with the credits
like making it seem like he had more and
they were in it together and then Yeah.
They caught none and they refused to pay out. Yeah.
[ __ ] that. Imagine they refused to pay.
Yeah. Police were called, I think, and everything. Yeah.
Yeah. Police were called.
Police were called, mate. Yeah.
Do you remember when I used to cook pork chops, Nicolo?
I used to cook some lovely pork chops.
How cute is that?
Do you remember that date I went on? You
know the one from when I come back from
Belgium? We was holding hands. >> Yeah. Antman
says, "Yeah, I I don't know why these
women go out if they're just going to
tell everyone they've got boyfriends."
It's true though. Why go out to look
good and waste your money just to tell
everyone you got boyfriends?
It's like, say I went out, right,
and there was no way I could speak to
somebody. I don't think I'd go out. If I
couldn't even speak to any new people,
like men or women, I don't think I'd go
out. Why would you go out just to tell
everyone that you got boyfriends?
some madness. It's It's an actual m I
don't know why these women go out.
I don't know why these women go out,
you know, just to tell everyone they've got boyfriends.
It's true, isn't it? [ __ ] waste of
money, but it
don't even know why they even bother
going out. It's not cheap, you know.
And then Virgin Boy was like, "Oh, um,
yeah, how do you know that they have
See, I feel like if they went to like a
concert or something,
you know, then yeah, it's possible they
can have boyfriends because people go to
concerts with their friends and, you
know, it's like I believe that, but like
slagging it about until early hours in
the morning and you claim you got a
boyfriend, no chance.
No [ __ ] chance.
No way in a million years.
Concerts are a bit different. You know,
my my sister went to a concert um the
other day and I feel like Yeah. I mean,
but slagging around early hours in the morning,
you know, they don't exist. There's no
way that many of the boyfriends would
let their women go around slagging it
off and about.
And if they actually had boyfriends,
they would just walk away.
you know, they would walk away if they
actually had boyfriends.
You know, people that actually have
boyfriends, I'll give you the signs,
right? So, if you're if you approach
someone and then they just walk away,
then they might have a boyfriend or, you
know, it's I don't even know why we're
still having this conversation. We know
that they feel the [ __ ] most of them. Um or like
that one that I approached in the park,
she said, "Oh, I've been seeing someone
for three months and I believe them."
You know, there is ways to tell people
are genuine, but the people that sit and
speak to you and then turn turn around
and say they've got a boyfriend, there's
just no way because if they had a
boyfriend, they wouldn't even entertain
you. They just walk past.
Like, they would literally just walk
past. They wouldn't even entertain you.
And it's the way they word it as well.
Like, you can tell, bro, they don't have
friends. They're full of [ __ ] So, yeah.
Yeah, but people on Reddit say go go on
go to bars, Nicolo.
Go to bars and clubs. You know
what about that?
What about that? Go to bars and clubs.
You can go to bars and clubs, can't you?
Yeah. What about the bars and clubs?
You need to go to where women expect it, they say.
So they say, "Yeah, you need to go to
where women expect it, like bars and
clubs and stuff."
You know, you need to go to bars.
You need to go to bars. Bars and clubs
where women expect it, you know. Yeah.
So, did that sound like a plan, Nicolo?
We'll do Thursday and Friday.
Thursday, Friday. Yeah,
we'll do a Thursday and Friday. Okay.
With you, boss.
Obviously, I have to run it by Well, I
have to run it by Greavvesy first, but um
but I'd actually be doing it just to try
and get women. So, I'm kind of [ __ ]
it up again, you know, cuz if I was
doing it just to go out, I would just do
it like once a week.
I can't cuz I can't be [ __ ] bothered.
I can't be bothered to do it every two
days. I can't be [ __ ] mate. I've got
enough numbers on my [ __ ] phone to
retire forever. I can't be [ __ ]
I can't be asked, mate.
You know, I do it.
Even if I don't do it for three weeks,
I'll still be confident to do it. I
don't need to do it every two days. I'm
not [ __ ] Nah,
I'm going to go out Thursday and Friday.
But then that's not really enjoying it.
Enjoying it. So, um
yeah, they won't leave me alone. They
I might go out. Um,
I don't know when I'm going out, bro. [ __ ] those.
Why? Why? Why do they stalk me every day, Wadley?
They're so obsessed. Why don't they
leave me alone?
Why don't these people leave me alone?
Why don't they leave me alone,
Nicolo? Why do do these people not leave me alone?
I think they're jealous of me. That boy.
I think they're jealous of me, bro. Yeah,
they're jealous of me.
They won't leave me alone, you know.
Let me see how much this Finland thing
is going to cost.
This is going to be a barrel of laughs.
This is going to be a barrel of absolute loves, mate.
Right. What's it called? Hennessy. Yeah.
You actually think I'll go, Nicolo?
Yeah, I'll go, mate.
How do you spell that again?
No. What's that called? A cup of No. One second.
No. What's that place called again?
Right. Hold on.
It's called Hiniski in it.
So, it's going to be
You don't know what PE what Peter
Belly's would do for love? One second.
Oh, it's called Helenski. That's the
one. I knew it was something, right?
Let's have a little look. Right,
let's have a little look, matey. Yeah,
right. Three nights.
You nasty virgin. Scrap.
Right. This is going to be
it's about £500 400 437. Yeah,
I'm going to book this. You know,
>> I'm going to I'm going to book it. Yeah,
that will leave me with it again. Yeah,
it will be a pretty lovely site.
It will be a pretty lovely site, matey.
There's some decent ones here.
That's a decent hotel.
Let me have a little look. Five.
This one's pretty good. Obviously,
that's where all the magic's going to be happening.
Yeah, I think I'm going to book this, bro. Yeah,
get some more money in a couple of days.
So, I think I'm going to book it
and just get the [ __ ] out of here. It
okay with you, boss.
Virgin can't do that. Virgin boy ain't
got the funds to do that.
Virgin boy ain't got ain't got the funds
to do that, mate.
Can't do that. Do that. Yeah. [Laughter]
You're better looking than him. You've
got more money than them and it and a
better life than them and it kills them.
Quoted by Ronald McDonald's.
Ronald Mcfucking Donald sin.
Yeah. What was her problem? Why didn't
she meet me?
That was quite that was quite rude. You
know what I'm saying? Why didn't you meet me?
They're all [ __ ]
Do you want my
One sec. I'm just making myself a cup.
Sorry, mate. Made myself a tough cut.
So, yeah, I'm I'm going to do this um
Finland thing. Me thinks Oh, yeah.
Me thinks, bro, 100%. Da 437
flights and hotel for three nights.
Oh, lovely. Can't say the dates though
cuz uh you know these people are like mate.
You [ __ ] know what these people are
like, don't you, mate? It ain't [ __ ]
good, man. You know what I mean? Yeah.
Hey, did you bring that thing at me? >> No. couple. I said,
"Were you what are you [ __ ] speaking
about, you silly goose?" Um,
that doesn't even make any sense.
Did you get alert? Nah.
Yeah, I'm going to do this um Finland
thing, I think.
What's that? [ __ ] spending 437 to
find your mama because he's already
found his mama.
Oh yeah. Oh yeah. With a pawn thing and
stuff. No, but I know what it's like
with a porn thing. Yeah.
Going to go to Finland to find my mama. A
travel. That's what I'm going to title
the video. The airport. Traveling to
Finland to find my mama.
To find my mama. How cute is that, Nikolai?
Traveling thousands of miles to find your mama.
Who would have known, you know? Who
would have [ __ ] known?
When you put it that way, ain't it? It's
mad when you [ __ ] put it that way. Ah,
no. He'd be a lovely Ba. Oh,
he would be a lovely bubin.
An absolute lovely bump shin.
Do you want me to go out on Saturday and
get on the piss?
Show the little virgin who's boss.
No, I'm not doing it every day, but I'll
go out on Saturday, man. If
you know, I'll go out on Saturday. Maybe
Friday. Saturday. Maybe Friday or
Saturday I'll be out. Yeah.
scaring the [ __ ] away. I always used
to say, right, hide your daughters.
Peter Benny's in town, you know, I'm
here to create chaos,
you know. Hide your daughters,
you know. Hide your daughter.
Hide your daughters. Yeah.
Hide your daughters. I've I'm coming out to play, you know.
I'm coming out to play.
Oh my god. What are you doing, Frankie? >> Uh oh gosh.
>> And you won't even need much spending
money a day in Finland. What? 150
150 a day? you know
I am considering going bro I am
considering actually going but
where I what about when I have to go back you know
that wouldn't be a lovely site would it go
less caring if he's got £400 left for the month.
He's got £400 left for the month.
Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ] I forgot my earphones.
Send in 20. Yeah, I've done it a few times.
Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ]
So, do you think Finnish Izzy likes Peter Belly?
[ __ ] hell, man. [Laughter]
You think she likes Peter Belly?
Oh, that's disgusting, bro.
Do you think?
>> Yeah, she must like Peter Bell.
So, how comes Virgin boy's never been on a plane?
That is disgusting, bro. Look at all
that crust on my ears. Disgusting, bro.
Why do you think
Yeah. Do you think she likes Peter Belly?
with USA is I actually thought I found
the one Nicolo but it was all a load of lies.
It was all a load of bllocks.
It was all a load of [ __ ]
It was all a load of [ __ ] mate.
Literally is it?
It was special then, but it's over now.
That rattled virgin boy, didn't it? You
remember the video? Do you want my
number? He was like, "You don't know how
to speak to women. It's so cringe."
Oh, he wanted me to be a virgin like him.
He wanted me to be He wanted me to be a
virgin like him. Nicolai,
he's a [ __ ] He's a big virgin, you
know. He's He's a big virgin. He's a
He's a He's a big virgin.
He's a big virgin, you know.
He's a big virgin. Big big big virgin.
This guy is a big virgin. You know,
he's a big big big virgin. He's a big
He's Oh, you keep saying that I'm a
virgin is not going to convince people.
No, I'm not trying to convince anyone,
mate. I'm telling you that you're a
[ __ ] virgin. I don't give a [ __ ] who's
who's listening, who's not listening.
I'm [ __ ] telling you that you are the
biggest virgin going. I don't give a
[ __ ] if people believe me. If they don't
believe me, I'm I'm telling you that you
literally are a virgin.
It's because he's a virgin. He wants ins
and outs because he's never had sex.
because he's a virgin
and he needs reassurance that you're a
virgin like him. And if you don't get
the re reassurance right, then he goes
mad. It's like the escort stories when I
used to say, "Oh, yeah, I [ __ ] an
escort." No, no, no, no, no. He used to
always find ways to not believe it.
Um, which I never knew why. And I was
like, "Oh, it's cuz he's a virgin." A
couple of years like later, I was like,
"Oh, it's because he is one. Damn, he's
the virgin. He's the big virgin." That's
why he made all of these excuses that,
"Oh, yeah, they asked for ID. You didn't
have sex with an escort." He didn't want
to believe it because it would mean that
you're not a virgin like him. Yeah.
And you can show you with a disabled
girl for another million years, you're
still a virgin. It doesn't prove
anything. You know, I'm telling you that
you literally are a virgin. And I don't
care what what you show you with a
disabled girl who you don't spend time
with cuz you're on YouTube all day
talking um about me. You literally are a
virgin. You never had it and never will.
You're going to die one.
That's what you're going to do. You're
going to You're going to die one. You're
going to die one. Time's running out.
You're going to die one. You're going to
die that Kent virgin. The skinny little
skint [ __ ] in the bedsit. The skint
bastard in the bedit. Oh, you skint
bastard who can't show me any£50 notes.
Talking to [ __ ] you. [ __ ] everyone
else. I'm talking to you. You skin ugly
bastard in a bedset
trying to [ __ ] tell me who I live
with, mate. trying to tell me who I live
with in your [ __ ] shitty council
beds. Trying to dictate to me who I
should or who I shouldn't live with
while she sat in a council bed sit with
no bed in it, mate. Skin, get a [ __ ]
grip, mate. Get a grip, mate. Go get
laid. Don't lose that vcard before it's
too late, mate. Ricky Millington.
He licks ass and then when he's done
balls when he's done his balls in he
self projects his skess and his ugliness
and then when you call him out on it he
has the [ __ ] about it. What the [ __ ] Ricky Millington.
What a [ __ ] waste man.
Look at Timmy still doing videos.
[ __ ] skinnier than a [ __ ] skin flint.
You're skinn a [ __ ] skin flint.
That's what you You're skint flint, mate.
Do you reckon these people will ever
leave me alone? Nicolo
Ronald Pump said, "Get off of YouTube
and live your life. These people will
never leave you alone."
I should have took his advice, man.
How comes there's no national How comes
there's no national northern league
playing on Saturday? Huh?
There's no National Northern League
playing on Saturday. What the [ __ ] Why?
Why is the National Northern League not playing on Saturday?
Oh, what the [ __ ]
Like slowing that. Where's the National
League? It's not They're not playing.
How comes they're not playing?
So, what are they will they be playing
again next week?
Will they be playing again next week or
>> Oh, fine. Well, next Saturday or
Yeah, I'll have to do a bet then.
Probably put 180 on two teams. Yeah,
I'll put 180 on two teams. USA is
she loves me deep down, don't she? USA is he?
She said to her friend, "Oh yeah, this
cute guy approached me
and I done something bad. I gave him my number." Oh,
how cute is that?
I love my and my mama loves me. Little quacker.
Why are you doing it all by yourself, mama?
What are you doing sat there all by yourself, mama? You know
what? Are you doing all by yourself, mama?
Poor little cracker.
That's cute, isn't it? Oh, and I still
love you, mama. Oh, bless cracker. Remember,
yeah, that's cute.
What do you think of this [ __ ] JF character?
He says he's got all of this money, so
why didn't he show me 12 grand?
account. There's another 40-year-old
virgin that ain't got a life.
PJ thinks because he has nothing in life
than everyone on YouTube also has
nothing. PJ assets concept of a stone
island jumper and a mobile phone. He's
deluded. My clothes are worth more than
these people's whole life. These are the
ones that are sat on YouTube in their
40s calling people that they don't know every day.
That's how we know that you people have
got nothing because of what you do every
single day. You know, sat on YouTube
arguing with people that you don't know,
calling people that you don't know. It's
fairly obvious to to paint a picture of
what your sad pathetic lives are. You
know, like these people ain't got if you
if you people really had something
right, then you wouldn't have ran away
when I showed £6,000. It's it's it's
it's that simple. It's not like you
didn't get, you know, multiple chances.
Um, you know what I mean?
It's, do you know what I'm saying? It's
not People don't think people know. You
know, I don't think I know when you've
got a bunch of 40 year olds upset with
you every single day. Something ain't looking right.
You know, it's not like these people
that are, you know, how hard can it be
when he come and gave me a coke and gave
me a football bet. He's in his 40s. I
think he was Yeah. 42 then.
And uh we used to like he was, you know,
he was on YouTube, but he was just like
a normal person.
What's his name? How hard can it be? His
name is I'm still trying to figure out
his name. We was trying to figure out this earlier.
Oh, where's his [ __ ] name now? You
know, but the fact of what you people do
all day every day, it shows that you
have nothing. It's not about thinking
anymore. It's not something to think of.
It's what we know. Because if you had
money, you wouldn't have let me keep
beating you at the money game the
multiple times that I did. But again,
you pretend it never happened. So, no,
you literally don't have anything. You
know, my life consists of a stone island
jumping a mobile phone. Really? Let's
see what you've got in your lives then.
Let's see your lives. You know, come and
hang out and show everybody what you've got.
At the end of the day, no one cares
about an updated [ __ ] pay slip. We
want to see cash, which is how you
started the game. This is what I mean
with these people. You just fry yourself
arguing with them, bro. This is what I
mean. They're so disabled that you can't
even get through to them. It's a bit
like that Joe. He's he's slow in the
head. You know,
you know what I'm saying? It's like they
all come here and I don't understand
what is the point. Are you trying to say
that you're rich or I don't understand
the whole point. Maybe I'll have to do a
video um asking
um him to do this.
And if you've got all of this [ __ ]
start showing what you got. Let's see
your car. Let's see all your money. Not
a [ __ ] pension. Come on. You know,
I've got nothing in life. I've got more
in life than these people will ever
have. They're the ones that are sat on
YouTube calling people half their age.
You know, that they don't even [ __ ]
know. Do you think people mature adults
with a family would do that? Do you
think normal people would do that?
What the [ __ ] do you have in your lives?
Let's start. Let's start showing things
now. Let's start showing things now.
Let's see all your money. Let's see all
your cars. Let's see all the things that
you have that I don't have.
Exactly. So, I mean, what's the point of
all of this, you know,
then [ __ ] a pension that you can't
even touch? You'll probably be dead
before you can even touch the pension.
You know what I mean?
Yes. I've asked for cash and that cash
that you've shown is nowhere near the
amount that I've shown. We're just
having the same argument over and over
again. Which is why I seem to think that
these people are generally disabled cuz
you're having the same argument over and
over and over and over and over again.
Like we're actually having the same
argument over and over and over and over
and over again
over and over and over and over and over
again. Has anyone else noticed that?
Arguing with [ __ ] people that you
don't know on [ __ ] YouTube. What the
[ __ ] People in life that have things
don't do this. You show yourselves to be
what you are every day.
You know I'm [ __ ] right. You know, simple.
You know, you're sat on YouTube, right,
telling somebody that's half your age
they've got nothing when they've got
more than you will ever have. You know,
and that's already been proven. You know
what? What? What the [ __ ] bro?
You would never think these people are
older than me, would you?
You said, "Oh, I've asked for
everything. You've gave me everything
I've asked for." No, you haven't.
Because when you've got shown money in
the past, right, you ran away. Let me
explain it to you again like a simple
thing a million times, right? That cash
that you are showing just as nons
is less than what I have shown. Stop
being disabled. Come on. You're better
than that. You know, you got asked for
cash for 18 months and you all ran away.
I know you like to forget that never
happened, but it did happen. What the
whole I don't understand what the
content on your channel is trying to
prove. What that you've shown less than
half of what I've shown. Okay,
you lost the money game. What? I don't
understand the point of it. Then someone
help me understand it because I'm kind
of like this has gone all this has gone
over my head, bro. I'm not even joking.
You know, these haters have got nothing.
That's why they do what they do every
day because they have nothing. That is
the whole point. You know what I'm
saying? You see all of these comments of
these people that are in their 40s, 50s
telling you that you don't have the
things they've never had, that they've
never shown. What the [ __ ] You know
what I'm saying?
Sat there obsessing over someone that's
half the age that they don't even
[ __ ] know. You know what I mean?
Arguing with people that they don't even
know what the actual [ __ ]
And actually, I've asked you to show six
grand cash, which you haven't done. So,
yeah. So, that in my mind, going by the
evidence must mean that you ask him.
Isn't that right, Nicolo? Let's let's go
by the evidence here, right? You show
these people 5.7 grand. Whether you want
to call it six, we'll say 5.7.
and they've not shown anything. So then
I just put the money in the bank because
I couldn't be bothered anymore. Then I
got a back payment, had even more money.
So then they showed no money all that time
and then as soon as they've won money or
whatever, they've shown half of what
you've shown. Does that not tell you
that you are skinned? Because from where
I'm crossing my legs rather than not
fitting, it sort of tells me that you
actually are the skinned ones.
You know what do people have in their account?
I could be a millionaire. You don't
know. I could be a thousand there. I
could have one pound tomorrow. You don't
know. You only know your own lives that
you try to project onto other people
every day on YouTube.
You know, you get a lot of these people
on Timmy's channel as well. They don't
come on my channel. We don't let these
self-reflectives on my channel, you know.
It's not about being the one that's
right. If you had money, you would have
shut me up within the second day of me
showing money. Money. It's not you
saying that you don't have cash is not
an excuse. You have started like you
people usually do. You start and you
won't leave people alone. Okay, [ __ ] it.
I'll show you money cuz I had the money
and cash there. You got shown money. You
ran away. Lord Jay ran away. and Virgin
Boy ran away. Yes, I am [ __ ] right
because none of you have shown anything.
You think by in your delusional head,
you seem to think showing half the
amount of money is you winning.
You seem to think that's you winning in
your head, but it's not you winning. You
know what I'm saying?
Like, I don't understand what the whole
point of your channel is
cuz some of some of them you can
actually see what the fact that you've
shown less money than what I've shown. Congratulations.
Do you do you want a silver medal or do
you want a gold medal?
I don't understand.
You don't understand how life works. You
don't even understand how the game works
that you invented. You know what? I'm
going to do another video to this [ __ ]
because, you know, at the same time,
bro, it is actually entertaining to see
how stupid these people actually are.
You've not shown everything at all. And
you know what? I'm going to ask you to
reply in the video since you're the one
that tells me that I've got anxiety,
which is another thing I'm going to add. Um,
just stop it because you're not going to
win. You know, you're really, really,
really, really not going to win. And you
try to say where the money is now. It's
not cutting it because that money could
be anywhere now.
You didn't show nothing whether I burnt
the money. So stop saying that you've
shown people what they've wanted to see.
You've shown £1,500
which the which the amount the amount
was five times over that.
Do you know what? It's it's kind of
entertaining to me how stupid these
people are. It actually becomes an
actual addiction. Yeah. I mean, it fries
your brain because they're so [ __ ]
[ __ ] but at the same time, it
actually becomes an addiction
because they actually make you feel
good. You know what I'm saying? These
these people actually make you feel
good. It's actually an addiction, you know,
like you're not more intelligent than
me, you know, so there's no point you
even trying. You're just going to lose,
you know? Like it's it's ridiculous.
Yeah, we all know, bro. He's self
projecting. We all know I'm better
looking at him. Yeah,
of course, bro. He's He's insecure.
Yeah, it's jealousy. It's something
called jealousy, my man. We've already
been over him.
So, you know what I'm saying? Like, this
Joe needs to really, really, really stop
because he's not going to win.
And the reason I say that you people
have nothing in life is because what
have you really really [ __ ] shown
over the years? Every single time that
you've been shown money, you're [ __ ]
middle-aged people telling people half
your age that they don't have the things
that you've never had. What the actual
[ __ ] Because you've done your balls in
[ __ ] gambling or whatever. You know
what I'm saying? [ __ ] me.
So, it's just Yeah, it's just just a
disabled community, you know. I don't
know what else
what else one can say about it. Talks
about my looks when I'm a million times
better looking than him. I know. It's a madness.
It is crazy. At this point, he's just
lying to himself.
He's just lying to himself.
He has to convince himself these things
to make himself feel less ugly about himself.
If I had one Stone Island jump on a
mobile phone, I'd have more than you
would ever have. What about all of these
life experiences that I have that you've
never had because you've been sat on
YouTube calling people that you don't
[ __ ] know? You're supposed to set a
[ __ ] good example, you know? You're
supposed to be a [ __ ] role model at
your [ __ ] age. Could you imagine,
right, I was on here Yeah. arguing with
a bunch of kids.
Do you know how stupid that would look?
Imagine I was on here arguing with a
bunch of 17, six, [ __ ] 18year-old
kids. You know, you would think that you
would actually be the [ __ ]
you'd actually be a [ __ ] role model.
What the [ __ ]
And I have got more in life than these
people will ever have. More life
experiences, show more women than them,
show more money than them, better
looking than them. That's facts that has
already been shown to you biased people
when you were still on YouTube [ __ ]
telling people they don't have the
things that you don't have. You're
self-reflecting old miserable farts.
That's what you are
under these stupid little accounts in your [ __ ]
Right. I'm going to reply to this in a
bit anyways, but I need to go shop and
that. So, I'm just going to chill. I'll
be back later anyways. Hopefully Triple
H comes back.