Oh, [ __ ]
Sorry, bro. I had to go and eat and fill
up my Peter belly. I'm back.
Yeah, sorry about that. I could have
been properly I was too hungry.
Oh, now I'm sleepy.
All that food. Oh,
yeah. I'm back.
I don't think I'll be on um YouTube tomorrow 100%.
I know I I know I say that, bro, but like
the stupidity it's addicting, bro. It's
addicting. It's addicting because where
these people are so stupid like Joe and that
you know um
that's why you come back on it because
they're so stupid it's addicting
if that makes sense.
But they really are just, you know,
bastards on there.
was busted for this community
on this community, mate. You got no
life. You on YouTube.
No life but YouTube.
Red Star's been stalking me again. No,
leave me alone.
Whoa, he actually did as well.
Let me see. Wait, did he actually
Yeah, you just know that this guy is
just some fat virgin loser ain't got a
life. You know, I did say that, but I
actually didn't expect you to do it.
Wow. You actually are a sad little virgin.
Like it actually is actually confirmed
now. Yeah. You You literally sit on
YouTube recording everything every day
just like what Pat Mustard used to do.
Yeah. That's how you know these people
really are skint virgin noife people.
It's so obvious these these people now.
Yeah, like Red Star. Oh [ __ ]
Oh, you actually did do it as well.
Yeah, they're sad little bastards. I
expect that they they record everything
like trying to get you to incriminate
yourself so they can get the police
involved or something.
Wow, what a loser. S on YouTube all they
stalking. What a loser. If I ever end up
like that at my age, at that age, bro,
I'd be having some serious words with myself.
What a loser. I could never imagine
being that much of a loser.
You You sure have the traits of a uh
triggered skinned person for somebody
that tries to call somebody else it. You
sure have all the traits.
And you just make me feel so good about
myself. You know, these people, do you
know what it is? I'll tell you the
truth. Yeah. Why this community is
addicted because they make you feel good
about yourself. You know, they they give
you an ego. It's like a woman's, you
know, ego being inflated. They inflate
my ego. The fact that you've got these
middle-aged ugly people obsessed with
you every day. It makes you feel good
about yourself, bro. I can't lie.
It actually makes you feel so good about
yourself. And they're sat on YouTube
stalking men half the age that they
don't know every day. normal to them
because they're weirdos, but not normal
in the public eye, you know.
Wow, what a loser. Sat on YouTube,
screen recorded all day. I told you all
along, bro. He's a fat virgin living
with his mom. That Red Star, I'm telling
you, it's a 40-year-old fat ugly virgin
living with his mom.
Whoever's behind that account, it's a coward.
That's all we know, bro.
Whether it's [ __ ] this person or that
person sat on YouTube every day,
jealousy seriously is a drug.
It seriously seriously is a drug.
Jealousy, it's one of the worst things,
you know. Somebody could be someone is
jealous. Jealousy is horrible thing. I
can't relate cuz obviously I've never
been jealous of anyone in my life, you
know, but obviously why have so many
people jealous of me and believe you me
it is jealousy which is why they do it
every day. It's it's it's seriously a
drug. Jealousy is a horrible thing,
you know. It's killed it's killed loads
and loads and loads of people,
you know, in the past and stuff.
Horrible disease. Jealousy.
I'm so glad I've never been jealous of anyone.
Sat on YouTube stalking all day, every
day. What a loser. But it doesn't matter
how many times you say this because
where these people are disabled, [ __ ]
they don't they don't understand it
because it's normal to them. Whereas if
you was to Sorry about that, man.
You know, it's not like you're going to
it's not like you're describing it to
like a normal person. You're describing
it to retards. So that's why they
actually think what they do is normal.
Sat on YouTube stalking all day every
day. Someone you've never met. That is a madness.
These people really been hurt in their life, you know.
And Joe, he's he he he's not that
stupid. He's not that much of a
simpleton. He's just addicted to men
half his age attention because he
doesn't get attention in real life. Um,
he's addicted to me giving him
attention. That's why I'm not giving
them no attention anymore. So, every
time he brings up the money, I'm
ignoring him. Every time he shows money,
I'm ignoring him because that's what
they want. They want attention. It's the
same thing with this Joe. He wants
attention. and he wants me to keep
explaining myself and doing videos on
him. It's not happening. You know, you
know, you lost the money game. That's
it. Whatever you say, I I'm not asked.
I'll just keep changing the subject now
cuz that's what they want. They want attention.
That's what they want is attention
cuz they're sad, fat, ugly people that
ain't got a life. [ __ ] look at that
left turn almost, mate. [ __ ]
sat on YouTube all day continuously
stalking someone. What a virgin. What a triggered virgin.
Everything you say about everything you
say is about yourself. Triggered skin.
That's all yourself and bored. That's
yourself. That's why you're on YouTube
every day doing what you do because you
are all of them things that you try to
project onto other people, you know?
[ __ ] absolute weirdos on this community.
>> Sat there recording every day. What a
loser. Look what that [ __ ] Pat Muster
then ended up looking like.
Yeah, I'm coming off this community,
bro. Tomorrow, hold my word. Uh, hold me down. Um,
hold my word down from that, bro. 100%.
These people are creepy.
They give me the EBGBs, lad.
They actually give me the EBGBs.
Why have I got so many middle-aged men
obsessed with me? Oh my god.
I'm only a [ __ ] 27 year old. It's not
my fault. I'm better looking than them
and I've got more money than them.
Ronald, where are you? Help me. Ronald McDonald. [ __ ] hell.
Ronald McDonald, help me.
Help me. Ronald McDonald help Hey,
help me Ronald.
I wish I never got involved in that
PlayStation community either cuz I
[ __ ] want. Then I wouldn't have met
this little [ __ ] virgin, this weak
little virgin stalking me every day. You
know, I've got [ __ ] every right to be
pissed off with this [ __ ] [ __ ] You know,
I really fancy an ice cream.
You know what I'm saying?
I've never so known so many old men
desperate for attention.
It is so sad.
Sat on YouTube every day recording.
What a [ __ ] loser.
Jealousy is a [ __ ] insulin drug, bro.
It's like, you know, insulin, you know,
like a drug. Yeah. When it's injected in
your body, bro. What a [ __ ] loser.
Living to do this every day. You know
what? These people give me motivation to
do better. You know, these people in
this community, they actually motivate
me to actually want to do better. You
know, you don't want to be like these
people, you know, in your [ __ ] 30s, 40s,
[ __ ] on your job. You got no life
about your job.
You're no life. your YouTube.
You're no life for YouTube.
You watch YouTube. Yeah.
When are you going to give it up? When
Sat on YouTube being a [ __ ] stalking
virgin all your life. When are you going
to give it up, mate?
And and it makes me laugh when people
say they do it for reaction because they
don't do it for reaction because even if
they don't get a reaction, they still do
it. I mean, yeah, we re we're reacting
to them now because we're telling them
how weird they are and some home truths
about themselves, you know, which is
what someone has to do now and then, you
know, as like a um renewal thing. Yeah.
Cuz we're telling them about themselves.
That's why we're reacting to them. We're
telling them that they're weirdos. Just
like if you was to see a [ __ ]
pedophile on the [ __ ] street
or some [ __ ] madness, you would say
it. You know,
I think Joe does it for reaction because
he likes younger men's reaction
because he's a fat, lonely old man
that's got nothing in his life but
gambling. Just like Red Star, just like
the rest of these losers.
I mean, think of these think of these
mongos on here. They can't get off of
YouTube. They [ __ ] They can't even go
on another community because they get
bullied. So, they have to find a [ __ ]
community full of the same fat, ugly
people that ain't got a life. Um, you
know, that they get on with. These
people truly are the down and out losers
of of society, bro. They they generally generally are.
They really really are.
really really are absolute losers. How
How long can they keep this [ __ ] up for, bro?
How long can they keep this [ __ ] up for?
Yep. Same self-reflecting people to seen them comments.
Same self-reflecting people.
Yeah, I'm done with this community after
today, bro. 100%. Yeah, I'm going to use
these little mongos on this community.
People like Joe, people like Red Star,
people like the others to motivate me.
I'm going to use them as my motivation.
These little mongos.
Yeah, I'm leaving, bro. 100%.
They've actually motivated me now. They
really, really, really, really have.
Don't want to end up like these [ __ ] losers
sat on [ __ ] YouTube every day and got
a pot to piss in trying to [ __ ] talk
about people half their age that they
don't [ __ ] know. Who knows? I might
be I might end up like that when I'm
[ __ ] 40 if I stay on here. You know,
if you stay on here with these little
mongos, these little low lives
that don't even leave the house. You
don't [ __ ] know that if you stay on
this [ __ ] It could happen.
could happen with these little mongos.
One second. I need to call some
Yeah. Sorry about that.
Yeah. Yeah. I'm off I'm off today.
Yeah, I'm off after today with these mongos.
These little weirdos on here
sat on YouTube in their [ __ ] 40s
trying to talk about other people. These
all old farts don't even leave the
house. [ __ ] hell. It really is a It
is really a place full of [ __ ] That is
why there's only like 20 people on this [ __ ] community, you know.
And then we have the same argument, the
same conversation. They lose. They don't
admit they lose.
boring. But that's what happens when you
Well, to be honest, it's a [ __ ]
community. So, I mean, what do you really expect?
I mean, the people in here were [ __ ]
disabled. Fat, ugly, jealous, disabled
people. You wouldn't really expect
anything more from a from a community
like this, would you?
I just can't believe these people
stalking all day, every day, bro. Like,
Red Star, they're literally sat there
stalking every day.
Uh, I got an Indian, bro. I just to me
like I know it seems normal to you. Yeah.
And um stuff, but I just can't believe
how they can be so jealous of someone
that they don't even know. It's wild, bro.
Having to wake up every day and stalk
someone all day, every day. It's They
must They must really hate themselves, isn't it?
I feel bad for them. I actually feel bad
for them, bro. But like in in in a way
they actually motivate me.
Sat on YouTube all day stalking. It's
mad. They really are life's losers,
aren't they? I'm coming off here. I'm
coming off here um tomorrow, bro.
I'm off here tomorrow for a bit, I think.
>> Cuz do you know like I don't know about
you. I don't know who you are, bro. But
I feel like with these people,
the more you argue with them and stuff,
like the more you actually lose brain
cells. I actually feel like I've lost
brain cells arguing with that joke.
Uh they're so re they're so [ __ ]
bro, that like the stupidity is almost addicting.
You know what I'm saying?
I'm coming off this [ __ ] tomorrow, bro.
100%. I hope um Triple H comes back today, bro. One sec. Yeah. Yeah.
These people, bro, I'm coming off
YouTube after today, bro.
They fry my brain, lad. They're so disabled.
All of these. Think about these people's lives, lad.
These people don't bully me.
They try to join up to bully me, but
they don't bully me. None of these
40-year-old ugly people have ever
bullied me and in their life, lad.
They've never bullied me. Never. They're
jealous of me. That's why they do all of
this stuff because they're jealous.
That's why they do this every single
day, bro. Think of these people, bro.
They're sat there in their [ __ ] 40s.
They're all ugly. They've all never seen
a woman naked. Half of them are [ __ ]
probably 80% of these people are
virgins. They hate being them. That's
why they come and they're doing what
they do every day. It's the same thing
as that Joe. He likes attention from
younger men. He's an insecure gay.
That's what he is, bro. He's a He's a
homosexual. He likes attention for men
because I refuse to believe, right, that
these that somebody can be that stupid.
So, I'm actually like giving them the
benefit of the doubt now. They're all
losers. They're all fat, ugly, skin
lifebum losers, just like that Ricky
Milling. They're all angry fat, wrinkly
gamblers, old farts. That's what they
are. All fat, all ugly, all got no life,
all never made it. But they're they're
also good in a way because they they're
they're to be used as motivation, you know,
because it's weird, bro. I can't stop
talking about them because to me it's so
weird like sat on YouTube stalking
someone every day. It's It's weird to
me. I can't get over how weird it is.
It's [ __ ] so weird how jealous they
could be of someone that they don't even
know. Like this is what I mean because
it's weird what that red star does is
weird. Sat on YouTube screen recording
all day. He's a 40year-old virgin.
There's there's nothing else, you know.
And yeah, I mean, I will block them. I
have blocked them, but bro, they're
still going to do what they do because
the whole point of it is they don't do
it for a reaction, which is what I've
explained about a million times. They
don't do it for a reaction.
They do it because they're jealous.
That's the whole that's the cold truth
of it. They don't do stuff because they
don't do it for a reaction. They do it
because they are jealous and they hate being them.
You know, they they they they wake up
every single day, I hate being me. They
don't do it for reaction because even if
you don't react to them, I'll say it a
million times, they will still do it.
That's what I'm trying to say to you.
It's mad. It's a weirdo weirdo community.
Yeah, I'm coming off this [ __ ] tomorrow
anyways. So, good luck to you all
I fancy some ice cream. Yeah,
but yeah, these people have never bullied me.
Yeah, these people have never ever ever
bullied me. If they bullied me, I
wouldn't still be on here.
You know, at the end of the day, if they
bullied me, I wouldn't still be on it.
They don't bully no one. They bully
themselves. That's what they do. They
bully themselves cuz they ain't got a
life. They're low lives. Low life 40year-olds.
Oh, I found some ice cream, but I can't
be bothered going to the [ __ ] shop.
Sad little low lives.
I just find it mad how you can be on
here for like 20 years and they would
still be doing it. I just find it so mad how you know
these people have never bullied me ever.
They don't bully no one. I've spoke
about them. I've spoke about their kids.
No, they don't bully anybody. They bully
themselves. They're living their worst
life. Them coming on YouTube talking
about their own existence and self-p
projecting their [ __ ] life onto you is
not bullying me. They don't bully me.
They bully themselves. They're the ones
every day that have to come on here
obsessed with somebody that they don't
know being triggered. But they're never
going to meet you. They're never going
to say anything to your face. They
literally have never ever bullied me.
I've already ate my curry. The curry
already came. You think a bunch of fat ugly losers
because they self project, right? They
bully people. Anyone can do that. My
niece and nephew can do that. If they
were bullying me, mate, they wouldn't be
[ __ ] begging the black man to do
their dirty [ __ ] work.
Do you know what I'm saying? They don't
bully no one. These people in their 40s,
their life's losers. They're fat, ugly,
nothing in life. They've been bullied.
They know all about being bullied.
They're bullied every day. Every day
they wake up. Every day they wake up,
they see their ugly face and they hate
being them. Yes, I know the word bully.
They are bully victims.
Yes. Yes, I know what bully is. But
they're bully victims. They've been
bullied their whole life. Look at them
on YouTube. 40. No life, no girlfriend,
no sex life, never had a woman. These
people have been bullied. They got the
right. They got the word right.
They're keyboard warrior bully victims
that have failed in life and they're no
hopers. So, not only are they bully
victims, they've got no hope because
they're all old. So when they sit there
and try and say you you ain't got this,
you ain't got that. It's because these
people are sat at home skint bully
victims, no girlfriend, no friends,
everything is themselves. Literally
everything that they do is about their
own lives. You know what I'm saying?
It's a self-reflection of their bully
victim lives. Anybody can sit on here in
their 40s and say, "Oh, you ain't got
this. You ain't got that. You ain't got
this. You ain't got that." It's them
that ain't got any of these things.
These people are life's losers. They
want benefits. Why do you think they sit
here all day saying, "Oh, you need to
get a job. You need to get a job."
Because these fat, ugly people have
never had a job. That's why they're sat
on YouTube every day. Think about it.
Two weeks I was off of here. No, no,
[ __ ] 3 weeks I was off of here.
You come back, these mongos are still on
here. These skin ugly people are still
on here. Is that lying? No, it ain't.
You know what I'm saying?
So, if I had to come on YouTube all day
obsessed and jealous of someone every
day, I would be the one being bullied.
That's you being bullied. That is you
being bullied. You can't bully someone
behind the keyboard. You can only bully
someone in real life. And you people
will never bully no one. You bully
yourselves fat, ugly, and jealous. Take
that L and hold it forever, bro.
Take that L and hold it for the rest of your life.
You're sat on YouTube every [ __ ] day.
You ain't got a [ __ ] life life to
[ __ ] stand on in one leg trying to
talk about [ __ ] other people. You
bully yourselves. You generally
generally bully yourselves. You've never
made me insecure about my looks. How
many times have you come on here
projecting your ugliness, your skintess,
and your singleness onto me every single
day? I'm not bothered. I'll show my face
every day of the week. But Red Star
won't show his face. All of these other
people won't show their face. But I'm
the one that's being bullied apparently.
Bullied by you fat ugly mongos. You fat
disabled little munters. You can never
bully a man like me, mate. [ __ ] off.
You think you 40-year-old no hope and
sorry ass losers could ever bully
someone like me? Get the [ __ ] out of here, man.
Have a [ __ ] word with your [ __ ] self.
You people have been bullied since you
come out your [ __ ] mom's [ __ ]
You ugly narcissistic little virgins
have been bullied since you come out
your mom's [ __ ]
I need to delete that video now as well.
Sat on YouTube every day. No life.
Just like a Red Star. Just like Virgin
Boy. I'm coming off here tomorrow. I'm
going to kill you people by coming off here tomorrow.
Watch. I'm going to make sure I don't
come back on air for a very very very I
love it. Yeah. You watch. Yeah.
Sad little mongos that can't get off of YouTube. Yeah.
I'm going to prove it tomorrow.
I'm going to so prove it tomorrow.
How you people can't get off of YouTube.
I'm going to prove it tomorrow. Yeah,
you little little red star. The little
40y old virgin in mommy's bedsit. I'm
going to prove it all tomorrow, bro.
Yeah, you people don't bully no one.
I've I've [ __ ] asked LJ to come here
millions of times and he won't come
here. You people don't bully no one. You
have been bullied. Any bullying that you
seem to think that you do on YouTube,
right? Yeah. You have been bullied your
whole life. You are the 40year-old ugly
people that ain't got a life. You
probably can't even step out your front
door without being slapped for being so
ugly. Anything that you do on the
internet, it doesn't come anywhere near
the amount, right, of bullying that you
people get bullied every day. You, bro,
these people probably wake up every
morning, you know, like Red Star, right?
They they probably wake up, look in the
mirror and see their ugliness and hate
being them. I've been bullied my whole
life. Ugly bastard. Sat on YouTube every
day. Can't get off it. And then [ __ ]
all they do is project their life on
here every day. This is what these
people do. They don't bully anyone. They
bully themselves. They put themselves
down every time they come in here trying
to talk about you. Yeah. At the end of
the day, all you [ __ ] do is is is is
project your life.
That's not what bullying is. Well, you
bully yourselves. Yeah. But you don't
bully me. You [ __ ] will never bully
me. You think any of you fat ugly mongos
can ever bully me?
sat on [ __ ] I wouldn't be on here if
I was being bullied. I wouldn't [ __ ]
be on it if I was being bullied, mate.
I'd be off here. I'd be [ __ ] telling
the [ __ ] school teacher.
You know what I mean? Yeah.
And I just realized I'm just wasting my
life on these losers. They're clearly
doing what they do every day cuz they're
jealous of me, you know? I don't care
what you say. I don't care what you
[ __ ] do, right? At the end of the
day, actions speak louder than words,
you know? And that's a main thing. And
you can sit there and say how you're not
jealous and no no, but you're the one
obsessed all day every day on YouTube.
That takes dedication,
you know? That takes time and that takes dedication. So yeah,
it's like that Joe. He just wants
attention. That's why I didn't reply to
the next thing. He just wants attention.
That's all it is. You just want
attention. You're not getting attention.
Go to your [ __ ] makebelieve wife. You
don't need attention from someone half
your age. Cuz I I thought he was being
serious at first, bro. But I was like,
"Oh, nah, he just wants attention. He
just wants me to keep reacting to him."
Yeah. Oh, that's what it is. Yeah. Yeah.
But at the same I wasn't any better
either because the stupidity got
addicted, you know. Yeah,
these people are clearly jealous of
something in life.
You know what I mean? So yeah,
I fancy an ice cream, but I don't know
if I can be [ __ ] to go to the shop and get it.
But I do fancy one.
Yeah, I think I'm going to have to go
and get an ice cream, man. [ __ ]
No, I can't be asked.
I was claiming some ice cream, but I
can't be bothered to go and get it.
I don't know. Should I get ice cream or
should I not?
The shop's about [ __ ] 5 minutes away.
I don't really crave ice cream much, but
I am today.
What do you think? Easy.
Right. I'm going to get some ice cream.
I'll be right back. Yeah, I'm going to
mute my mic. I'm going to keep the live
on, but I'll mute my mic. Be right back.
I can't believe that a [ __ ] account said [ __ ]
>> these people bully me. These people
never bully me. They bully themselves.
Their motivation to be not like you
don't want to be like these losers when
you're in your [ __ ] 40s
sat on YouTube. These fat ugly people,
these fat ugly people like Redsaw.
You know, I'm actually going to start
the gym tomorrow. No,
I'm actually going to start the [ __ ] gym tomorrow.
I'm actually going to start Oh, one
second. I'm going to start the gym
tomorrow. Actually, these people are
like actual motivation,
you know. Yo.
>> Yes, bro.
Can you hear me? Oh [ __ ]
I don't want to be like that red star
virgin 40year-old no life no money no
girlfriend sat on YouTube stalking
someone I don't want to be like that
some little skint [ __ ] in a bed sit
ain't got nothing in my life but YouTube
wouldn't you want something better for
me I don't want to be like these
40-year-old skint people that can't get
off of YouTube these little bully victims
I don't want to be like these fat little
bunters that can't get off of YouTube.
These fat, ugly, low lives that's never
been seen with money or a woman. Do you
think I want to be like these [ __ ] people, Greasy?
[ __ ] you, mate. I thought you would have
want the be the best for me, lad.
I don't want to be like these fat, ugly
losers that can't get laid.
I thought you would want the best for me, lad.
But no, you don't, do you? Yo,
>> did you hear me? Yeah, bro.
>> Did you eat?
>> No, I'm waiting on it now. [ __ ] I go in
the bathroom now.
>> One second. Stay on here. One sec. Bye. Yo,
sorry. I had to reset my thing. >> Yo.
>> Yeah, I can hear you better now. Sorry,
my thing went a bit quiet.
What's happening? Did you have scram?
>> Yeah, some curry. No, I fancy a Ben &
Jerry's. I'm going to get one in a minute.
>> I like a pudge brownie, man. That
>> Oh, I like the cookie though one.
>> I've never had that. My lad. >> Never. >> No.
>> I like your little accent.
>> Know what? I like a milkshake and that, mate. >> Yeah.
>> You don't like a proper [ __ ] dessert?
>> I like I like an Oreo milkshake.
I don't like Oreos, mate. >> Really?
>> I don't like Biscoff either.
>> Oh my god.
>> I like um What ones do I I get milky or
I get um I know Milas.
>> Yeah, I like my man.
>> It's nice, isn't it?
>> Are you smoking? Veron [Laughter]
Steven Howard P Mrs. B.
>> We should go to We should go to the
pictures, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Have you seen that new um
Conjuring watch has come out?
>> Yep. I saw it the other day. It wasn't that good.
>> Oh, have you watched it?
>> Yeah. Whenever there's a horror film, I
go watch it straight away.
>> Yeah, I like horrors. Like was it as bad
as the B make out or
>> which one?
>> Was it as bad as everyone makes out?
>> It was just [ __ ] Yeah, the oligor is
[ __ ] now. Like years ago.
>> No, you should have watched. You should
have watched the one called Bring Her
Back. That was a good one. It's an
Australian one. I don't know if you saw it.
>> Did you see that on Tik Tok where before
the people had to go and they have to
get them holy watered and off? >> No.
>> Did you see that?
>> Me and So me and you can go to the
pictures together and watch a horror.
>> Say that again. So me and you can go to
the pictures together and watch a horror. >> Huh? >> Hi.
>> We could be munching on the popcorn and stuff.
>> Did you have a tezy there?
>> No, but I want to take you.
>> Wait, who is that? Who is that red star account?
>> I thought it was Pat. I don't
>> whoever it is, it's a [ __ ] coward, is it?
>> Yeah. He's on your army. He is such a
coward, isn't it? I think these people
need to get laid after these people. Do you?
>> That seaside match been drinking again. Eh,
>> it's going to kill him one day, is it?
>> Yeah, it's um
it's uh he's got a problem, hasn't he?
It's an addiction.
It's not nice, fell.
>> It's funny, is it?
>> It's not funny. It's just sad to see it really. Really? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. But the break, what was I saying?
So when you go out when you go out
drinking again, where are you going to
go? Newcastle. Yeah.
>> Darren probably.
>> Yeah. But Newcastle's better, isn't it?
>> So why don't you ever go Newcastle?
>> I don't know. I like D.
>> Yeah. Like Greavves just said it.
Addiction it not nice. It not, mate.
>> No, it's funny. in it.
>> Bags all over the cinema floor.
>> So when you when So if we you know you
know when you go out drinking you start
in the weather spoons in it
>> sometimes lad.
>> Have you ever done an approach in the weather spoons?
>> No I don't do approaches me.
>> Yeah you do.
>> Do you have them dating sights? >> Nah.
>> N then bro years and years ago like
>> So what? You've never approached? No.
>> So, how do you how do you pull when you
go to a club then?
>> I don't pull the guy from
>> No, but but no, but when I No, cuz when
I spoke to you like a few years ago on
WhatsApp, you were single.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But
he's having a crack, don't you? Do you
want a few tips? Like, fella,
don't want a few tips like
>> Yeah. No, you just need to be [ __ ]
confident in that, don't you? around
them and just obviously
>> Yeah, but you don't you don't approach it.
>> No, I'm like I don't know what you mean
by approach like yours are weird. Yours
are like in the in through daytime and
that I'm about like on a night out
>> yours wild through the day.
>> I thought it would like the training
that is it.
>> Yeah, like middle of the day and that's mad.
>> Well, when you do that.
>> No, no. Not well.
>> It's funny though. Is it?
>> Yeah. It's wild color.
So, like when you when you go out
drinking, what time do you come back?
Like 4 in the morning, is it?
>> Yeah. Normally 4. Yeah.
>> You crazy [ __ ]
>> I just can't get out of there. P.
>> I just can't get out of there. P bills
on. I'm in. >> Yes.
>> Hello, PJ. You dick.
>> Hello. Hello, dude.
Why did you meet me? Why did Why didn't
you meet me in Birmingham?
>> Because you're a dick, mate. And you can
get your mom to [ __ ] phone the police.
>> Excuses again. Excuses.
>> Excuses. Your mom phones the police.
>> Tell your mom. Stop getting involved.
>> It's too addicted.
Excuse. It's too addict.
>> DJ, why did your mom get involved? Seriously,
>> it's too addicted, isn't it?
>> No. No. It's not about being addicted.
Why did your mom get involved?
>> Timmy, why why did you meet me in
Birmingham? Were you scared? Was you
scared of me?
>> I was scared of some money.
>> You were scared. You were scared. PJ
can have a serious conversation. Anyway,
how you doing, Edge? Legendar.
Anyway, PJ, why can't you afford a haircut?
>> Why can't I afford a haircut? I
>> Red Stars uploaded the video where you
said you owe the barber's money.
>> Red Star is a 40-y old virgin like you.
>> Do you know what a virgin means, PJ?
>> Yes, I know it's you. You're the biggest
one. PJ. A virgin is someone who
constantly talks about women.
>> You're the virgin. You are the virgin.
Yeah, I know what he's
>> PJ. You won't beat an argument.
>> If we were all virgins, people exactly
talking about women 20.
>> You know, do you know the thing is to
me? Yeah. Even if somebody beat you, you
would just [ __ ] on the chess world and
pretend like you won. You know, that's
what Tom Wood.
>> Yeah. Exactly. Do you know what Tom Wood
said once? Do you know what? Do you know
what Tom Wood said before?
>> You know what he said? Do you know what?
Do you know what Tom Wood said before?
You want me to tell you?
>> No, but I don't give a [ __ ] But go on.
>> He was like, there's there's no there's
no point arguing with Timmy because even
if you beat him in an argument, it's
like playing chess with a pigeon. He
will just [ __ ] all over and pretend like it's
>> Tom is actually correct. You'll never
beat me, PJ. I always win. >> No. [Laughter]
PJ, it's the internet. It doesn't bother
me, mate. It's got [ __ ] B going on
all day. Just leave him to it now.
PJ, ask you a serious question.
>> Why do you block people, mate? It's
YouTube. I don't know why you let it get
>> because I don't like self projecting repeating people.
>> PJ, you self.
>> I don't like selfj.
>> Where's Monty? Where's Monty?
>> I don't know. But why why do you like
that dick PJ? Why why why why do you
want to be friends with someone who's
got a teenage dating app on his phone?
>> What do you mean?
>> Well, he's a he's a he's a nons. Who has
a teenage ding app on their phone?
>> Yeah, but didn't you offer alcohol to a
kid on the bus?
>> No, I said where's your ID? There's a different.
>> Yes, I do. PJ, I can replay the video.
>> Okay, go then. Okay, I will when I find
it somewhere because I said to him, PJ,
I'm not going to give a kid alcohol. Obviously,
I wouldn't have given them anyway. I
mean, PJ, you've been listening to
Groomer Chan. You have He's a [ __ ] Nazi [ __ ]
>> What's his name? [ __ ] Welsh [ __ ]
G. I don't know his name. I know his
name. I'm not.
>> It's Ga Chan. It's not Groomer Chan.
>> He's a [ __ ] Nazi who needs to be shot.
>> So, why are you a nonsense?
I'm not well one PJ I don't talk about
children constantly like you wanting
them dead and stuff like that
>> PJ you [ __ ] n you said a nons
you said get back in your mother's womb
you [ __ ] dirty wrong
>> you know what I'm saying take it to
heart PJ it's YouTube but
>> no you love YouTube
>> no I don't I just like coming on here
taking the piss out of people like you want to
>> link the piss out yourself
>> PJ I don't come on here for days PJ
>> yes you
I'm having a line of sniff PJ cuz I
deserve my buzz cuz I'm 100 pound up
today. So let me have my
>> Hey, I'm the buzz.
>> Yeah, I'm having my little
>> Timmy basically. So basically your skin
>> PJ I've got [ __ ] 260 quid in my I've
won £100 today which is paid for my
kettle. My k's for free. My buzz is for
free. My ease are for free and my 30
wings is for free.
>> You and you and you and um you and Money
M should come to London. PJ, don't start
this because you'll get your ass kicked.
>> Go then. Go then. PJ will whack you in
one of these. Not in a good mood with
you, by the way. So,
>> tell him to come. Tell him to come.
>> PJ, he won't come cuz he'll whack you.
>> Yeah, of course he will. Lots of bacon, lad.
>> I'm coming from you. Speaks to PJ.
You give alcohol to show your face cuz
you'll be scared, bro. Knock your bacon
ass to the floor, mate.
>> You're the bus, lad. This is a bus mate.
Come on. You like this?
>> What's a bus? Come on, you [ __ ] You
think you know?
>> No. No. No. Sing a video. You [ __ ]
Do you remember Jane? Do you remember Jane Greacon?
>> Yeah. What's What's a bacon? You wool.
You haven't explained it yet. You call >> people 1984.
>> Nothing. So you've come you've been
completely owned. No such thing as a bus
nons or an internet nons. A nons is a
nons. And you're the one who's friendly
with the bacons. Not me. You love PJ
that much you want to shag him at the
bum, don't you, lads?
>> Lad, you call me a bacon as much as you
want, but I don't communicate with the
bacons. You do.
>> You support them, lad.
>> No, no, no, no, no, no, no. You support.
You support. You support PJ and you
support a guy with a teenage dating app
which I never will make. All right,
Timmy, why did you why did you give kissate with l
>> bro? You can't [ __ ] be a bus n or a [ __ ] internet.
Anyway, wool. Anyway, wool. Anyway,
wool. Anyway, wool. How many nons have
you communicated today?
Are you obsessed with nons?
>> No, no, no. You're the nons.
You're the one who looks so much nons.
You only calling me a nons cuz you're
self projecting that nons.
>> Who are you, mate? What you going to do
about it? [ __ ] all you does. I moan on
your internet all [ __ ] day like a big
girl's blouse. You owe no [ __ ] soccer
ball. You owe no one your softball. Come
and come to my baby and I'll kick your
ass. But you won't cuz you press
you only got Lord Jay as a friend cuz
you're a loner a [ __ ] loner in
Liverpool paying for your [ __ ] friends.
Mate, you don't want to leave your front
door cuz you'll get knocked out like a
[ __ ] bacon. That's why lad.
You're a [ __ ] ho. You're scared to lose
all your money,
mate. You're the clown. You have to get
internet friends cuz you haven't got any
friends, lad. And bacon. You can call me
a nons if you want. I'm communicate with
nonsies. You love bacon so much.
>> You remember when?
>> You remember when Monty said, "Why did
you get me on this community?"
>> [ __ ] hell. I get over excited over
>> Timmy, why did you get me on this bastard community?
>> I didn't get you on the community. You
helped yourself, wasn't it? You dick and
I got it.
slapping his head.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I'm flapping my hand from someone like
who has to pay Lord Jay to 12. You're
[ __ ] scared to meet me. Slapping your dad, lad.
>> You wouldn't slap anyone, mate. You're a
[ __ ] 30-year-old virgin.
>> You know nothing, bro.
>> You don't own nothing, mate. You got no friends. You
>> know, like museum [ __ ] pieces cuz
you're scared to worn them down.
>> You know nothing about me, bro.
>> You really [ __ ] own me, don't you,
mate? At least I wear my [ __ ]
designer clothes. Don't leave them in
the wardrobe for 5 years. Grab your
skin. You got no clothes.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I'm skin. Okay. If I call
myself skin, when you get a hard on, mate.
>> We've seen your clothes.
>> If I call you skin, my dick will get
hard, too. Yeah.
>> You're a little [ __ ] bro.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I'm a [ __ ] mate. Yeah.
Yeah. Coming from you. Put your picture.
Do you want me to put your picture up
right now for everyone to see on PJ?
We'll make a decision. Who's the [ __ ] lad?
>> Do as you're told, lad.
>> I won't do as a little [ __ ] [ __ ] by
you. [ __ ] all who likes nons.
You nons bacon. Go and [ __ ] off you
bacon. The only reason why you're
calling people nons because you've got
something to hide. Ain't you bacon boy?
>> We know you're the No. Come and tell
tell us the truth. Bacon boy. Come on.
Tell us the truth. You're only trolling
on here cuz you're scared to leave your
front door cuz you're going to get
knocked out like a bacon. Get into
someone's face. You [ __ ] plonker.
>> Anyway, you've been owned in a bit.
>> Anyway, yeah. Yeah. I've been owned by a
little [ __ ] [ __ ] who lives in his
mom's bedroom at Wallland. Okay. See you
later. You bacon boy.
>> See you later. You bow me. You bow me
little boy. See you later. You play GTA.
>> See you later bacon.
>> Go [ __ ] go bip.
Have you ever played GTA 5 boozy you [ __ ]
>> Yeah. [ __ ] Yeah. Yeah. You can do what
you want, mate. You wouldn't say that.
>> You don't play anymore.
>> Okay. See you like See, boy. See you
like there's no N boy. It's a nons or
nothing. Can it? See like
>> own you.
>> I can't even hear you.
>> You owe me.
>> I can't hear you with these two.
>> The people that owe me the people are
too scared to go live in my area. So
what we what we mate
two [ __ ] can't help John Eldidge
[ __ ] clowns are [ __ ]
>> Timothy John Eldridge.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Timothy John Eldidge
68 1984. You're really hard a younger.
Yeah. You're really hard. You owe me.
You [ __ ] [ __ ] a well-known bacon.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'm not wound up
in straight, mate. You are a [ __ ]
mate. This internet is not owning
anyone, but you are a thick [ __ ]
>> So, if you got a PlayStation now, triple
>> m you carry on living in childland.
Yeah. See you later, ns. See you later, child.
>> Iva beacon.
>> Yeah, you
1984 blah blah blah. And you [ __ ] got
your dick hard now, lad. Is your dick
massive cuz you think this is bullying?
>> I agree. I was saying,
"Do you have a PlayStation?"
>> By clowning,
>> by Timmy, do you have a PlayStation?
>> Nah, I can't be asked with that cuz I
might end up tracing Dazby and beating
him up and you'll go I'll go to prison.
>> You know, I met
>> Hi, Timmy. Do you know how Timmy, do you
know how I met Nods? >> Who?
>> Do you know who I met? How I met [ __ ] Nods Legs?
>> Yes. Through PlayStation.
>> Yeah. Through Jamie H. Well, Matt,
doesn't that tell you something? That
[ __ ] Jamie Haves has ruined your life
by introducing Shawn and he keeps owning you.
>> He doesn't own anyone, man.
>> He does, bro. You do get
>> He doesn't He went He went crying to the
police on YouTube.
>> He went crying to the police. Crying.
>> Of course he cries to the police. He
ain't a fighter.
>> Yeah. Well, then stop coming on YouTube
like you're a fighter then when you're
crying like a little [ __ ] when you get
home, didn't you?
>> No, DJ. I'll tell you about Sean. The
reason why he winds you up because you
>> He doesn't wind me up. I wind him up.
I'm not holding you.
>> I wind him up in his bed. You don't
>> He went to the He went to the police
over YouTube cuz he's a little [ __ ] He
got owned so badly he had to cry to the
police. Do you think anyone can make me
cry to the police over YouTube?
>> That he gives you a loan of stick and he
wants to the police. Okay, I will give
you that. He's a [ __ ] for that. I will
give you that. But the problem is PJ,
what he's still owning you. I'll explain why.
PJ, this happened with me and Mass
Miller. I went on with Mass Miller for
10 years. And I look back and it's
pathetic, right? And because I was
giving him a response, he was only me. I
don't give them responses anymore. He
did a video on me about going in the
freezer. I just laughed and thought,
"Yeah, whatever, mates." You know, if
you respond to them, PJ, I don't know
how many [ __ ] times I got to tell you
this, they're going to keep trolling you.
>> Yeah, but even if you don't, they're
still going to do it.
>> Well, PJ, I left YouTube for 13 months,
as you They went on about me for four
months and they gave up PJ. They do
eventually give up.
But the thing is PJ, they know you're
going to keep reacting and they'll keep
doing it. And to be honest you PJ, don't
take this personally, but I find it
quite funny when you react because I'm
thinking [ __ ] hell, PJ. How many
times has Triple H told you? How many
times has Toasty told you? And how many
[ __ ] times have I told you?
>> So Timmy,
>> yeah. So, you've got £260 to last you a month?
>> No, I've got actually to last me in the
month, PJ, £960.
And I've got two weeks till I'm paid.
>> So, are you going to go drinking?
>> Can't be asked, PJ. You know what I'm
doing now, PJ? I'm having a big fat Bob
Marley and I'm going to switch off
YouTube in 10 minutes and I'm going to
[ __ ] have my time.
>> All right. How you doing, Edge?
>> What do you mean, >> Tim?
All right. You having a smoke tonight,
Trip, or you just staying off it tonight, lad?
>> I'm off it, mate. I'm waiting for got
big on the pizza. I'm waiting on me. No way.
>> You're You're addicted to roulette,
aren't you, Timmy?
>> Of course I'm addicted to roulette,
mate. I [ __ ] love the game, but it
also gets me in the [ __ ] You know, I
lost 500 pound in 10 minutes on it on
Friday PJ in the casino. I did
fucking£500 Well, five 100 pound spins
and not one of the [ __ ] came in.
Yeah, it's brutal. That's gambling. It's
>> the thing is the thing is right PJ and
triple agree with me this now because MI
technology you know what MI means don't
you? I can't MI technologies they can
program something before it lands in the
wheel. So basically like I was watching
what they were doing but I was 400 in
right they were putting the numbers what
numbers to go in before the wheel [ __ ] span.
>> Mhm. And that all the little people are
doing little tiny bets were winning and
people are doing like big bets like me
and Mike [ __ ] did our bollocks in.
>> Did Mike blow a lot him?
>> He blew the same as me. 500.
>> [ __ ] hell.
>> But the thing is I won 350 back when I
went to North Wales Shbury Wednesday,
didn't I? So I was quite lucky. I was
only 150 down. I won 150 quid today. So
I'm only I'm probably down the month
about a couple of hundred. I'd say
>> that that Timmy Timmy. Yeah, but Timmy,
you get £800 a month.
>> No, I don't. PJ, I don't know who keeps
telling you this.
>> You said it.
>> PJ, I used to get £800 a month, but I
work now, so I'm on a lot more. And the
thing is, PJ, if you was if you didn't
be a [ __ ] on YouTube and you didn't
dox people and you was a good lad, I
would teach you how to work for
yourself, you know, to get out.
>> You work, mate.
>> It's whe it's a piece of piss working
for yourself. know what you're [ __ ] doing.
>> Do you work?
>> Yeah, I go around charity shops. I buy
items and I sell it for more on eBay. [Music]
>> Because I've been taught by the best
what to get and how to sell it.
>> You could do the same, PJ. You
>> So you're like a reseller, Tim.
>> Yep. You live in London, PJ. You could
go around charity shops 9:00 in the
morning, get rare comics for about 20
quid and sell them for 80 quid on eBay.
But you got to know which ones to buy, PJ.
I think you're a troll to me.
>> I'm not trolling you, PJ. That's what I
do. I do a bit more than that, PJ. I'm
not discussing fully what I do on here
because you know what the [ __ ] trolls are like,
>> you know. Yeah, but
you said Yeah, but Timmy Timmy stalking me.
>> Timmy, you know that online You know
that online roulette's fixed.
>> No, I didn't play online roulette. I
played a live table. I was at the casino, PJ.
>> Yeah, but it's fixed, isn't it? Of
course it's we just explain to you why
it's we because it's MI technology and
they can put I saw them cheat the wheel
PJ I will never go in a casino again
>> mad man.
>> Yeah but online is rigged as well it
>> yeah but the fault is at least you can
get an edge percentage back you that
roulette mate you can put two I mean
look at what you said today what you had
£6,000 and it went for I've done five
grand in one day and I've won PJ you've
got to look at this the more you
>> I've never lost six grand. Yes, you did, PJ.
Most I've ever lost was two grand on roulette.
>> Yeah, in a day. Yeah,
>> in an hour.
>> Wait, I'm going for me lad. I'll be back
in a bit.
>> I'll catch you in a bit.
>> In a in a in an hour.
>> In an hour. [ __ ] you.
>> Yeah, but you think Yeah, but you think
you think Yeah, but you think gambling's
funny. That's why I never talk about you anymore.
>> PJ PJ, can I explain? Right. And you
know what I choose is if you lose the
money and you've done your bollocking,
what can you do about it? Seriously.
Nothing in it. You're [ __ ]
>> Exactly. So why moan and complain about
it, PJ? You've took a risk. You've lost
the money. You've got to deal with it
like a man.
>> Yeah, but you cry over it. You used to
like not cry. You used to find it funny. The roulette.
>> But PJ, I'm I'm I've done it for 23
years now, mate. I'm sick of feeling
depressed over it. I know that I love
gambling too much, mate. I I do try to
quit, don't get me wrong, but I I'm not
going to lie. I I love it as well. But the
>> What I'm saying is What I'm saying is
you find the gambling industry funny.
No, I don't find it funny. I [ __ ]
hate them. But PJ PJ, I pay my bills and
I get my food and what I've got left
over, I do. And if I've done what I've
done left over, there's no I don't have
any weed for the week. I don't have any
of that. I don't have any beer. I just
sit there and take it like a man because
there's no point complaining if the
money's done because you ain't going to
get it [ __ ] back. I mean, you went to
rehab over gardening, is it?
>> Yes. If it doesn't matter, PJ, there's
some people been to rehab three or four
times and they've had to quit like after
the fourth time. PJ, addictions are the
hardest [ __ ] things to stop and as a
person, you should [ __ ] know that. I
>> I just I I just found the football now.
>> Yeah, but PJ, you bet on [ __ ] teams like
[ __ ] shoes bringing that lot.
>> I mean, [ __ ] hell. They lost two
weeks on the trot, 4-0, and you're still [ __ ] back.
>> No, I I put I put 120 on two teams on
Tuesday and I won 380. Not bad, is it?
>> Yeah, but that's not going to happen all
the time, PJ. to risk
>> cuz I know I know it's going to I know
what's going to happen, PJ. You're going
to come on next week and you're going to
go the football's rigged. I've done 250
quid and you're going to stop your
[ __ ] eyes out.
>> No, listen listen. I I signed up to an
online casino last night and I was going
to gamble like 150, but I never, >> right?
>> Because you just know it's [ __ ]
>> Well, PJ, gambling is there for
entertainment, right? It's not fun
anymore cuz it's not fun when you do 200
pound an hour. It's not fun when you're
[ __ ] losing quick on pub machines.
But it's the new generation of gambling
within PJ. You've got to it's it's all
computer wise now. There's [ __ ] all you
can do about it. The thing is the thing
is PJ it was different in my day. You
could cheat machines. You could do
things to machines. You could skill the
jackpots. And you can't do that anymore.
It's all MI technology now.
>> Yeah. Do you remember to me when they
refused to pay you out?
>> They've done it to me more than once,
PJ. And I've had to go down the gambling
commission and get it back.
>> The book you not watch because they
refused to pay you out.
>> I've had [ __ ] lab books refused to
pay me out. I got the money back, but it
took three months.
>> Well, they refused to pay out.
>> Yes, they refused to pay me out. Yes.
>> Why not?
>> I was I put about 90 and I got it to
180. I collected it and she goes, "Well,
you're you're banned. I'm not paying you out."
I went to the [ __ ] gambling
commission everything to get it. I got
it back, but it took a bit of a while.
>> Well, you're the thing is thing is PJ,
right? You are in it to win it or not.
And at the end of the day, PJ, if you
lose, you've got to take it like a
[ __ ] man and accept it.
>> Yeah, but I don't like
>> Well, don't gamble then. You know what I
mean? Yeah, but yeah, but it's easy to
get quick money nowadays, you know? But
PJ, it's also easy to lose quick money
at the same time.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> And PJ, no, don't take it personally,
but when you do your bollocksing, you're
like a you're like a bull in a
Chinatown. You [ __ ] go off on one
like a tion like no [ __ ] Tomoa.
>> Yeah, but you don't it
>> PJ when I've done my bollocking, I don't
come on the internet because I don't
want to give anyone the satisfaction.
>> Yeah, like Red Star them loses it.
>> I don't mind Red Star. I think he's all
right. He's always been good to me. So,
I'm not going to start on someone.
>> He's a loser.
>> Well, you might call him a loser, but
you know, I I know where starving will
life. I'm not saying who he is. I know
>> So, I'm You mean bullying a China um shop?
>> Yeah, bullying the China. But the reason
why he goes for you,
>> can I can I tell you why Red Star goes
for you? One, because you're an easy
target. Two, because the [ __ ] you said about women.
>> No, that's an excuse. That's an excuse. There's people.
>> Stop. PJ. PJ, you're lucky to still be alive.
>> Okay. Do you do you want me to tell you
why Do you want me to tell you why Red
was for me?
>> Go on then.
>> I'm younger. I'm better looking. I got
more money than him. And he hates it.
>> Did a Red Star show three and a half
grand the other day?
>> I showed him I showed six grand.
>> Yeah, but PJ, you skint now. You haven't
got it, have you?
>> Oh, same argument again. Oh my god, my
brain. Help me, Grezy. It's the same argument, right?
>> You got Can you show me six grand now? There's nothing.
>> I showed you six grand and you all went
running for 18 months. That proved my
point. I don't need to waste my time anymore.
>> So, you haven't got six grand then?
>> I have shown you six grand for 18 months.
>> I've shown people on WhatsApp. Six grandy help me.
>> Grey All you got to do is show me the
balance. It's not rocket science.
>> I showed Did I Okay. Why didn't you show
We're having the same argument.
>> I've already shown three grand the building.
>> We're having the same argument over and
over again. You're just like that Joe.
>> Okay. I'm like Joe S. Mhm.
>> Okay, then why? Okay. Okay. When I
showed that six grand, why did you all
run away for 18 months? Can you answer that?
>> I didn't run away. What the [ __ ] She
>> Bro, who showed me money when I showed six grand?
>> I've shown you [ __ ] PJ, I'm not going
to go to the bank and take five grand
out to show YouTube.
>> Oh. Oh, but you want me to do it though?
>> Well, PJ, I don't brag about money. You
want me to do it,
>> PJ? PJ, I don't need to tell the reason
on people on YouTube I've got money. Why
do you got to feel the reason that you
need to tell people you got money?
I don't. They're the ones that
>> do because you call everyone skin
pathetic virgins and then and then and
and then people actually do show you
money and then you [ __ ] won off.
>> No, I showed six grand that made you all run.
>> Yeah, but that was about a year ago.
>> It doesn't matter how long ago it was.
It was the fact you all ran off. It
could have been 10 years ago.
>> So, how did we run off then, PJ?
>> It's because no one show Okay. Okay.
Because you never showed money. Nonsle's
never showed money and Joe never showed money.
>> Well, non-sleg show about 10 grand the other day.
>> He has never shown 10 grand in his life.
PJ, he's shown 15
grand in his own notes.
>> He has never shown 10 grand. He's shown £800.
>> He needs to put that in the bank because
soon he won't be able to spend them 20s.
>> You don't have mate. He's shown £800 maximum.
>> PJ, I've seen him when he showed money
the other day and there was bundles 20.
There was at least 12 grand there.
>> There was not 12 12 grand. Nowhere near.
Show me this.
>> Okay. So, Sean does a video now and goes on.
>> Do a video. Do a video right now. Yeah,
do it. If Sean does a live stream and
shows 12 grand. What are you going to say then?
>> It's not going to happen.
>> I know it's going to happen. I know he's
got about in that place.
>> Well, you weren't showing any of this
money when you were showing six grand.
>> PJ, I can use a bank account cuz I work.
>> Okay, let me ask you this question. When
I showed six grand, why did you all go running then?
>> Nobody went running, PJ. It's in your head.
>> You what?
>> Nobody went running, PJ.
>> Okay, so how many of you show
>> was trolling you more than ever? [ __ ]
was trolling you. I was doing a bit of
trolling because it was funny cuz your reaction. >> No. >> Yes.
>> I've already I've already proved
millions of times you people are skinn.
I don't need you to
>> Well, PJ,
what's been skinned to you, lads? Come
on. Let's see it.
>> These people here, they've got absolutely nothing.
>> Okay, PJ, but they live at homes.
They've got mortgages. They pay bills.
They take their families out. Do they?
>> So, I would
How do you know that,
>> PJ? I know Pat Mustard's got a good [ __ ] job.
>> No, he [ __ ] Yes, he has.
>> No, he does [ __ ] go to university for
that, you dick.
>> Okay. Okay. Okay.
>> PJ, it's a good job. You get paid over
£25 an hour.
>> Okay. Yeah. Yeah.
>> I'd do it. I'd fix bridges for a living
and [ __ ] go to university and get £25
an hour plus.
>> Yeah. Really?
>> PJ, he's [ __ ] shown his life on here
by accident. That's how he got doxed.
>> PJ is more minted than you'll ever [ __ ] be.
>> Even though he's not. If you had ordered
this money, you wouldn't have let me
show him six. Pat Pat's more minted than me.
>> So why you got an issue with trolls having money?
>> Because none of you have money. That's
the whole point.
>> But PJ Pat showed about [ __ ] 10 grand
on air. I've shown >> Yeah.
>> So PJ, when people have got
>> I realize I'm never going to win. So I'm
not arguing with you. I'm not arguing
with you. It's pointless.
>> PJ But PJ people have got some people
have got their houses paid off and
they've got their future sorted. So you
can't call them skink cuz I do a bit of rolling.
>> I know, man. I showed six grand and no
one run off. Yeah. Yeah, you're right,
bro. Yeah, it must have been
>> I show n grand, but that's gone now.
That's history. Like your
>> It doesn't matter if it was gone. You
all ran away. But yeah, it never
happened. No, no, it never happened. It
must have been in my head. Yeah,
>> DJ, I showed in 2018 £9,000. Toasty
shown £15,000 on camera. Yeah,
>> you can't call anyone's skin on it. No,
Toasty did show 15 grand. He did.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
>> No, no, I think it was 30 grand he
showed actually. Didn't you remember the
video when Toasty did all them [ __ ]
notes and he was running it around? It's
a lot more than
>> No, I wasn't around them times.
>> So, you can't say no people toasty shown
four figures more than you.
>> So, why didn't anyone show me when I was
showing six grand then?
>> Cuz you weren't around then, was you?
>> You know,
show PJ, should we go by order?
>> So, how did he get all that? How did he
get all that money?
>> King's shown 10 grand. I've shown nine.
>> You've never shown Arch Deacon shown 20 grand. So
>> you've never shown you you and you and Nonex 2000.
>> You and Nex has never shown.
>> Yes, I did. PJ,
>> you did.
>> Yes, I did. I'm not going to argue with you,
>> PJ. I've had the videos. I put them up
to piss you off.
>> Okay. What's the most money you've ever
had in your life?
>> 12 a half thousand in a savings account.
Sorry, 23 grand. I apologize. 23 grand
I've had in a savings account.
>> And then you lost it.
>> No, I paid to [ __ ] get the house done
up cuz I owned the house then before I lost it.
I used to get 40,000 a month.
>> What the [ __ ] are you on about?
>> I used to get 40 grand a month on YouTube.
>> PJ, you got 40 grand a month, you'd have
no [ __ ] universal credit, you dick.
>> Yeah, it's not that much a month, is it?
>> 40 grand? PJ, if I had 40 grand a month,
I'd be coming [ __ ] left, right, and center.
>> You know what I'm saying? Yeah,
>> PJ. 40 grand a month. That's what
[ __ ] Stoke stars get a month. If I
had 40 grand a month, even have to pay
[ __ ] 10 grand a month tax and I got
30 grand, I would be [ __ ] over the moon.
>> You would waste it all on gambling though.
>> No, I wouldn't. I put it up my nose, go
to Las Vegas, [ __ ] love life, and
just [ __ ] you know.
>> Yeah, I'm I'm going broad street next week.
>> Let me know cuz M wants to punch your
head off when you go.
>> Yeah, he Yeah, he will see about that, won't we?
>> I know he will, mate. I love you, mate.
I love you all.
>> Okay, PJ, do you want to do a natural
betting thing? So, I'll bring a few people.
>> I love you all. You know,
>> PJ Mikey beats you, you have to put 500
quid down. You're
>> I'm going to slap him up for being a
little snake on YouTube. I've caught
him. I've caught him out. Uh, Timmy.
>> All right, then. So, if I put down 500
quid for Money Mike,
>> right? And you put 500 quid in Money
Mike wins. That 500 quid goes to Money
Mike. I get my money back and you end up
losing 500 pound.
>> Well, he won't throw hands. He got beat
up by a [ __ ] woman. Lisa. Lisa beat him up.
>> Yeah, but PJ, you can't hit a woman
back. Don't be
>> mate. He got beat up by a [ __ ] woman.
>> So, you got beaten up by a 12y old. So,
what's the difference?
>> I got beat up, bro. You got beat up by a
[ __ ] woman. Imagine that.
>> I'd rather I'd rather get beaten up by a
woman than a 12-year-old. That is ins
and never beat me up. But yeah,
>> he will, mate. I'm telling you that now,
>> You know what I'm saying? Yeah,
>> I can own it. Mike can [ __ ] beat me
up, mate. It's a good fight.
>> He can't be any, bro. He's [ __ ] like
5 foot tall. He's 5 foot tall.
>> It's not about height, PJ. It's about
[ __ ] tech. He's been fighting since
he was [ __ ] four years old.
>> Yeah. And he shouldn't be. Yeah, I told.
Yeah. Don't snake me then and you won't
have these problems. Simple.
>> Well, PJ, it's I wouldn't worry about
him snaking you over a fiber cab. I'd
worry about him putting you in hospital.
He he would never be able to pull me
off, mate. Are you Do you know how
little he is? I've met him. He's tiny,
bro. He's probably more tiny now.
>> Recognize B Street next week. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> I'm a big I'm a big [ __ ] You
>> It's your funeral, PJ. That's all I'm saying.
>> I'm I'm a I'm a big [ __ ] I'm a big [ __ ] Me?
>> Yeah, PJ. But you will get beaten, mate.
>> I'm a big bastard compared to him.
>> I'm that confident Money Mike will get
his £500 back from the casino and I'll
put it on and he'll flash you
>> and Money M
I've got a problem with I've got a
problem with money mic cuz I caught him
snaking me. So I thought I'll just start
in a minute cuz you caught him snaking
me, bro. That's the story.
>> PJ, you do realize Money Mike's not
bothered about a fiberactic cable. He was
>> Well, I'm bothered. I'm bothered about it.
>> You are I don't like that [ __ ] It's
annoying. It's annoying.
>> Pisses you off, lad. The internet pisses you off.
>> Yeah. No, I just don't like snaky
people, that's all.
>> PJ, it's [ __ ] YouTube. Why does it
bother you? Why don't you unblock Tram?
Unblock [ __ ] Lord J. No, I don't like
I don't like self projectors on my channel.
>> So, you are scared of names on a screen then?
>> No, I just don't like self projectors. I
don't give self projectors.
>> No, you are scared of names on a screen.
[ __ ] tells me all the time.
>> Timmy, when did you Timmy, when did
Timmy, when did you last have sex? >> Yesterday,
>> with who?
>> Uh, that would be
Timmy, you're just so stupid. Do you know that?
>> Yeah, I'm stupid, PJ. But I honestly did
have sex yesterday with somebody in Tinder.
>> What? Somebody on Tinder?
>> PJ, I can [ __ ] get you birds online
like butter wouldn't melt if you was a good lass.
>> Are you sure? >> Positive.
>> Well, you could get you can get me like
sex and stuff.
>> I can get you a bird on the internet if
you get on your knees and say, "I'm
sorry what I've said on the internet."
All the nasty stuff. And you got to say
sorry to Prime for calling him a [ __ ]
because you know Prime would beat you in
the real world.
>> I called Prime out last month.
>> I will help you get a bird. Trust me.
>> Where was your Prime last month when I
called you both out in Birmingham?
>> PJ, we [ __ ] double the size as you.
[ __ ] get people going.
>> Jimmy, are you are you forgetting that
you've already come here and you lost against me?
>> PJ, I've never lost against you. I think
>> Yes, you have. You couldn't even kick
me. You were trying to kick me and you
couldn't even kick me. PJ, I did it on
purpose for you to [ __ ] back off cuz
you to PJ, I'm not going to fight
someone who's [ __ ] half of my size,
half my vantage. And no offense, PJ. If
I [ __ ] put one punch into you, you'd
be out till next week as
>> you wish. You [ __ ] wish.
>> Well, you got your party money, Mike,
next week. Any I want to get money,
Mike. 500 quid. So,
>> I would knock that [ __ ] flying.
>> We'll see next week, won't we?
>> Yeah, we will. We will. And you're and
and why are you I know where you live as well.
>> Where do I live?
>> You live in Kitty Minister.
>> No, I don't. PJ
I'm not far from there. You are right.
I'm not far from Kitty, but I don't live in Kitty.
>> You've actually been uh you've actually been traced.
>> What? Back to Kitty, have I?
>> Yeah. Do you know what made me laugh
about you, Timmy? Do you remember that
time when you said, "Yeah, you done your
balls and then you had to live off like
moldy bread." That was that was lies.
>> That was 10 years ago, PJ. Yeah, but
that was lies though, is it?
>> No, that was true.
>> You You was living off bread.
>> I was making my own bread, PJ. I had
flour and [ __ ] had to buy east. I had
about10 for the month.
>> Well, how much did you lose?
>> Probably about 1,200 back then. [Laughter]
>> That's mad to me. That is [ __ ] mad.
>> Well, PJ, haven't you had to live off
the food bank?
>> Not the food bank, but I've had no money
before from gambling. Yeah. But do you
know how long ago was that? [ __ ] like
four years, five years.
>> Exactly. Mom was years ago as well,
>> you know. I haven't been like that for
years cuz I just don't get myself like
that, you know. >> Yeah.
Somebody says Jaden. So that's not the
wheel. Jaden, there's somebody in your
bat chat saying, "Timmy, get ready. Your
windows are getting smashed in, lad. You
won't see it coming. Letters are get
sent out this week, Timmy. In your
bigger bigger trouble, my old lad. It's
only been you've the only virgin on
YouTube is you Timmy and skits three
weeks, months. Haha. The Yeah, that
that's a fake J.
>> Oh, you you know you know um Sheffield's
near Birmingham, isn't it?
>> Sheffield's nowhere near Birmingham, bro.
>> Yeah, it is because [ __ ] um Natalie
had to get to change up at Sheffield to go Nottingham.
So, they're near each other, isn't it?
It's near each other, isn't it, to me? Huh?
Hey, baby. What are you doing to me? Timmy. Aldridge. Aldridge Macdonald.
Yeah. Ghost, have you ever done your
balls in from gambling? Huh?
You ever done your balls from gambling, lad?
I haven't for like 4 years.
What do you say? You lost £500. [ __ ] hell. [ __ ] that.
Why don't I go to Braum tomorrow?
Because I'm not wasting my time with
these people anymore.
Because we all know how the Vice City store go.
Really? It's hard to make money now,
ain't it, Goston? It's hard to make
money nowadays, lad.
It's hard, bro. I want to go out on a
drink this week. You know, when I went
out Sunday drinking Ghost,
tied in with the food and [ __ ] I
probably spent about
£200, bro. It's expensive.
It's so expensive, bro.
What do you think? It is, isn't it?
It's expensive, man. Going out drinking in it.
I'm speaking to some woman in Finland
ghosting. She said that she'll meet me
if I go Finland. I met her on Sunday and
she doesn't ignore that. She's like
really nice. So, I'm thinking of like
going Finland next month. It's my
birthday next month, so I might go to
Finland. You know,
if he wants to meet me, he can come to
he can come to London.
I'm not going to have dessert. I wanted
dessert earlier, but yeah. Yeah. Hey. Hey.
Now, if he wants to meet me, he can jump to London.
I'm not wasting my time with these people anymore.
We all know how the cookie crumbles.
We all know how the how the chocolate
chip cookie crumbles with you people
here. Think about it. Ghosting
like I'm going to waste my time, waste
my money, right, to meet these people.
And then you come back home
and then um and then they pretend it
never happened. How many times have we
done this, bro? I mean, you're an old
school viewer. You know how many times
I've gone to meet these people, you know?
So, it's just a waste of my time.
Waste of my time, lad.
We all know how the cookie crumbles.
I probably won't be on YouTube tomorrow
to be honest. I might have a busy week.
I'm going to go out this week
doing some approaches and drinking.
I said I'd go out like every two weeks and stuff. Yeah.
You know how it is. [ __ ]
Yeah. So, no matter what you do, these
people will always pretend it never happened.
So, it's pointless.
Pointless trying to meet these people.
Just leave them to it.
I don't know how they have the energy to
do this every day, bro. It's crazy.
like this Red Star ghosting. Who do you
think it is that Red Star account?
Are they not going to regret this? Like
when they're near like dead like 70, 80
that you know they're on YouTube, they
could have had a better life, but
instead they were stalking someone half
their age. I reckon it will catch up
with them when they're older. You know,
I think you'll I think you'll catch up
with them last.
They were stuck on YouTube. They
couldn't get off it.
He's a [ __ ] loser. I'm leaving these
people to it after today anyways, bro.
So there'll be no live streams.
They might actually get a life.
They might actually get a life, man. You know,
they might actually get a life finally.
These people will never have a life, mate.
You still there ghosting?
You still there ghosting, lad?
I don't know if you went still there.
All that Joe does is gamble all day, doesn't he?
He gamble all day. Yeah.
But yeah, I will be on there um
from tomorrow, bro. So don't say I
didn't tell you, [ __ ]
You reckon Virgin B will lose it? So
what do you reckon these people will do
if I don't come on YouTube? Yeah.
Yeah, these people are just mad, bro.
I just don't know how, man. These these
people can do this.
It's madness. Anyone can get a bird for
the night or pay them, but try
substaining the relationship and career
has no idea.
Um, I've already shown you me with a
woman. This is what I'm saying, bro.
This is why I'm coming off of this
community because of stuff like this,
you know, or like even coming off of it
for a long time is because this exact
thing, you know, arguing with these
disabled people that ain't got a life.
This is exactly what I'm talking about,
bro, with these people on here.
It's just the same disabled [ __ ] What's
the point of being on a biased community?
You know what I'm saying? A biased
community full of retards.
You know what? Sometimes I'd love to get
my hands on one of these people, bro.
You don't even know.
I It would have been Money M the other
day if I didn't know what all of these
people are about.
It never stops in here until you leave,
is it? I noticed that. Unless you're on
here, this [ __ ] never stops. The same
atmosphere with these people. Have you
noticed that with these [ __ ] lowife [ __ ] people?
I think I just need to leave and live my
life, you know. Bro, honestly, like on a
on a real now with the these people are
never ever going to stop. Well, you was
told that they were never they're never
going to stop. So,
I might just come off this [ __ ] bro,
and live my life forever. I'm not even joking.
Why did who turn?
I don't see the point in all of this.
I honestly don't see the point in all of
this, bro. You know, I really don't see
the point in it all.
like they it makes you appreciate how
much life you actually have.
How did he how did he turn? Um well, he
was on here licking my ass and I caught
him on non legs when I've been reacting
to gambling cuz I got p you know when I
get pissed off when I lose and he
commented saying um oh
but remember he doesn't gamble anymore.
Laughing emoji. I was like you think
you're going to snake me like that
brother? Are you [ __ ] mad? But then
we all the reason I didn't go there is
because we all know what these people do.
We all know what these people do on
here. You know,
it's jealousy at the end of the day. You
need to just get off of YouTube and
leave these little mongos to it. That's
what I'm doing, bro. I've got a busy
week next week anyways. So,
and because they're so disabled, these people,
when you're uh the more you stay on it,
the more you lose brain cells because
you're talking to these people all day
every day, these retards like Jo, Virgin
Boy, you know, these people, the more
you like stay on there, the the more of
a [ __ ] you become as well because
they're so [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying? I've noticed
that as well. And you notice that when
you come off of it, even for like a day
or three days
and then like you come back on it and
then it's oh, and then the second day
and then the third day it's like back to
square one again.
Nah, he's not cool. He's I've explained
it. I've literally
right explained about a million times
about the money game and he's still
trying to say, "Oh, but it doesn't count
cuz it's past." Like, it's clear that
the guy just wants a reaction from
somebody half his age. Like, he must
have a fetish with somebody half his
age. Like, if you keep if you want to
keep believing that you won the money
game, crack on. I'm not asked I'm not
arguing with you little mongos anymore,
you know? I'm not doing it anymore.
Crack on. I'm off from tomorrow anyways.
You know what I'm saying?
Like you actually I actually lose brain
cells arguing with these jealous people.
Like you don't actually understand. You
actually lose so much energy and brain
cells arguing with these [ __ ] little mongos.
No m what what whatever you say to them
is not going to go in their brain.
The guy is showing a thousand. It's just
the same conversation. It's just the
same [ __ ] This is why I don't come on
here for like two weeks. And then you
wonder like, "Oh, where have you gone?"
Because it's just the same [ __ ] with
these people every time. Every single
[ __ ] time with these mongos.
That's why I can't be bothered. You know
what more do you want? I've shown more
money than you people. I've proved I'm
[ __ ] better looking than you people.
I prove I've had more women than you
people. What the [ __ ] is the point of
all of this [ __ ] I don't get it, you know?
And he says, "Oh, well, the past is the
past. The past is not the past because I
beat you at the money game.
So, it doesn't matter if it's the past
or not. It's just the same old argument.
Same old [ __ ] argument every time."
No. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Listen, listen, listen. I'm going to
explain this one more time to you again.
I asked you to show me cash. Yes, 12
grand cash when I showed you £6,000,
which you never showed me. It doesn't
matter if it was the [ __ ] past. You
lost the game and you've still lost. You
showing this stupid £1,500 2,000.
Listen, you're about 18 months too late
and you still haven't won.
I think you're gay. I I I honestly think
you're a gay lord. I think you like
attention from younger men. It's clear
that you just want attention now.
It is obvious. It is clear now that you
just want attention. Oh, it is. It's
clear as day now. Yeah.
Well, there's such thing called a bank
account. Okay. Okay. Well, you didn't
have it in cash. Okay. Get it from the
bank. Okay. Couldn't you couldn't have
you got it from the bank?
The more I sit on here and actually
spend time with you losers, I'm actually
just glad to go out and have a drink.
You know, you really ain't got a life.
It makes you actually like
happy that you can do things that these
people can't. Okay, you didn't have 12
grand in cash. Well, you could have got
it out the bank, but why didn't you get
out the bank?
Why didn't you have Why didn't you get
it out of the bank?
What what's the excuse for that then?
I can show you money, but I'm not going
to show you money because of why I've
already explained. Just like I'm not
going to go to Birmingham because of why
I've already explained, you know.
No, I don't hang on to the fact I've had
something. I hang on to the fact that
when you've been shown something, you
will run away. So, it's not worth our
time. Again, why didn't you get the 12
grand from the bank?
Why didn't you get the 12 grand out of the bank?
Because you don't have it. So, at the at
the end of the day, we can go round and
round in circles all day, which I'm
surprised you actually have the time to
do since you claim you got a MS. You
claim that you got a wife, but you're
you'd rather sit on here arguing with
somebody half your [ __ ] age that you
don't even know.
You non-legs large eight. You got beat
at the money game several times for a
very long long time.
Exactly. Cuz you don't have it. So don't
come on here and [ __ ] try and say
about how, oh yeah, well, oh, you asked
me to show you curse. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. You know,
it's not all. Okay. So, you didn't have
the 12. So, you didn't have access to
the 12 grand. Okay. So, you never had it
then. So, you lost. Simple. There you
go. There you go. There you go. Okay.
Well, you didn't have it then. Okay. So,
you lost the money game then. Thank you.
We're getting somewhere.
You didn't You You didn't have 12 grand
to show. So, you lost. Simple. And it
actually wasn't 12 grand. It was
actually 10 grand. It was actually 10
grand actually. So you never had 10
grand to show, buddy. That's you losing
the money game. You can show two grand,
you can show [ __ ] £3,000. You can
show £4,000. Not interested. Simple.
You've already shown what you're all
about. When you get show money, a wise
man learns from his mistakes.
You're making up all of these excuses
why you couldn't get 10 grand out.
You're a [ __ ] joke, kid, you know.
So basically, you never had the money to
show, so you actually lost, you know.
Yeah. Okay. So there you go. Then come
back to me when you got 12 grand then.
Simple. Yeah. Exactly. So you lost the
money game. Yeah. So what what what
what's what's the point?
What's the point?
Okay. So, you couldn't show the money
cuz you never had it. Okay. So,
therefore, you've lost. But why do you
keep going on about it?
Yeah. So, then that's there we go. You
answer your own question. Then you've
lost you've lost the money game. I'm
going Finland next month by the way.
Yeah. I'm going Finland next month.
Might do a little video as well.
Sorry, mate. That's just the uh You know
what? So, you couldn't show 12 grand.
You couldn't show 12 grand. So, that
means you lost the money game then.
You didn't You just answered your own [ __ ] question. [ __ ] hell.
I'm not doing this with you anymore,
bro. I'm not going to Birmingham to
waste my And it's not even about the
money game, bro. Do you know how much I
want to smack up that money mic? But I
already know what you people do. And
that guy couldn't beat me, bro. I'm a
big [ __ ] compared to him.
Trust me, compared to him, I'm a big [ __ ]
You know, this is a couple of years. You
know what I'm saying? But it's like,
bro, it hurts my brain as well. It gives
me a headache. This is why you have to
take two weeks off this [ __ ] because you
actually lose brain cells.
But I know this Joe guy is not really
that stupid. He just wants attention off
a young man.
He just wants attention off of a young
man. He might have a fetish for young
man. Maybe he's bisexual
cuz it's clear he just wants attention
now. You know, it's clear as day now. He
just wants attention cuz no one can be
that stupid. Come on. You know, it's
ridiculous. Now, you you clearly want
attention, ain't it?
I love to smash that money, Mike. And
you know, some of these people sometimes
I'd love to grab them and just squeeze
them. I'd love to just grab you and just
squeeze you. Squeeze until your [ __ ]
eyes pop out. You know that? Some of you
little narcissistic [ __ ]
No, I'm not trying to give it a big one.
I don't like I don't like snaky people.
I don't like snaky people. I don't like
it. I've never liked it. And that money
mic's a snake. And compared to him, yes,
I am a big [ __ ]
Yeah. I don't I don't want it. But it's
clear, Joe, that you just want you just
want attention now. It's obvious. It's clear.
It's clear you just want attention.
Yeah. You just want attention now. Okay,
I get it now. It's okay. Yeah, you want
attention. That's okay. I'll give you some attention.
Bro, even if I don't react, you Well, I
don't know about you, but these people
will still do it. I'm reacting because
of how weird what you people do is.
Yeah, I'm reacting now, but actually,
even when you don't react to these
people, they still do it. So, why does
it matter whether I react or I don't
react? Because you're still going to do it anyways.
Like I said, I could post traveling
videos again and I could come back in a
year and you'd still be doing it every
day even though I didn't react. So like
you don't you don't do it for reaction.
You do it for attention. You might do it
for reaction because you're obviously
attention seeker now. You're obviously attention seeking.
Um but you know these other people like
nonslegs and they are actually jealous.
Like they're not doing stuff for a
reaction. They are actually jealous.
You didn't prove me wrong. Okay. Okay.
How did I How did you prove me wrong?
You got shown £6,000 and you couldn't
show me anything. How did you prove me wrong?
You got shown six grand and you've just
admitted that you didn't have 12 grand
to show me. That is you being proven
wrong. Not me. That is you being proven
wrong and then you've come on here with
what? £2,000 acting like you've won. Uh uh
uh. Okay. If you're not all skinned,
then why is it you allowed me to show £6,000 for
18 months and you done absolutely
nothing? You done absolutely nothing
about it. Okay. Okay. You're not skin.
No legs is not skin. Lj is not skin.
You're all not skin. Okay. So, why did
none of you show me money before I put
that money in the bank?
Answer the question.
Answer the question then.
Listen, all you have shown is a pension
that you can't even touch yet until you're retired.
Yeah, he is a little You're a little
weasel, bro. You're a little [ __ ] And
oh, and another thing. He said, "I can't
get women, even though I've had more
women than anyone on the community."
Yeah, you're clearly just attention
seeker now. It's clear you're just
attention seeking. You know, I gave you
the benefit of the doubt, right, a few
times, but yeah, it's clear that you
just want attention. Oh, it's okay if
you want attention. Peter Belly will
give you attention.
Yeah, it's clear that you just want attention now.
Yeah, I've never had I can't get women
yet. I've had more women than all of
these people on here. I I don't have no
money yet. I've shown more money than
all of the people on here. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
You're just attention seeking, but you
just want people to keep explaining themselves.
You You don't He was very clever with
it. You were very clever with it. You know,
you're a sad bastard. Really sad
bastard. You are. If I'm sure if you
nons weren't skinn, you would have beat
me at the money game ages ago. But you
never because you're skin. So end love.
You already prove whatever you're shown.
You just deny it,
don't you? You you whatever you're
shown, you just point blank deny it.
Why? It's cuz you're just attention
seeking. That's what it is. You just
want attention. It's okay. I'll give you
attention. It's fine.
Ah, here we go again. Bro,
you're boring now, kid. I'm going to
stop entertaining you now. You're
actually hurting my brain.
Oh, you're actually hurting my brain.
You just admit you just admitted that
you never had 12 grand to show me, so
you lost the money game.
That's the end of that. There's There's
no more to it. That's the end.
I tried explaining this to LT the other
day as well. I swear to these people
actually disabled. I actually I swear
these people are actual mongos.
I'm going to have to clear my head for
like two weeks. You people are [ __ ]
You're scrambling my brain. Oh my god.
Well, why? Well, you could have easily
got the 12 grand out, you know.
Well, you could have easily got the 12
grand out. There's no excuse. Well,
there's no excuse.
Well, there's no well, there's no
excuse. And another thing is, right, you
saying things of the past doesn't wash
because you people love to live in the
past. You talk about Prime, you talk
about L, you talk about Izzy, you you
use the same repeating words. Like, you
people are living in the past every day.
All you do is live in the past. You
never live in the future. But whenever
you get owned, it doesn't count because,
oh, it's the past, bro. Stop attention seeking.
Stop [ __ ] attention seeking.
Let's see the past so you show present
future. I have no I am not showing you
anything ever again. Just like I am not
going to Birmingham to meet Michael or
meet Timmy because I've learned from my
mistakes. I'm not showing you nothing.
you. Every time you get shown something,
you just deny it anyways.
So, at the end of the day, I'm not
showing you [ __ ] all. And if you want to
think I'm skin, go on. You can think I'm
skin. That's on you, man. I don't give a
[ __ ] I'm not showing you nothing. I'm
not playing these games. I'm not playing
these games with you anymore.
You've been shown women.
You say that people can't get women.
You've been shown money. You pretend it
never happened. Bro, you're a waste of
my time. If you're going to say
something, stop wasting my time, you know. So, yeah. Um,
no, not in this community. No, I'm not.
And I'm going Finland next month as
well, and I'm not showing that either. So yeah,
you people really really make my brain
fight. Ah, [ __ ]
You people really really are disabled.
It's not even a [ __ ] I'm not even
just saying that, bro. Like it's a madness.
You actually fry my brain. I'm going
Finland next month. Finland. [ __ ]
Yeah, I've got somebody to see in
Finland. Got some business over there. Uh,
but you launch Legs Red Star, you're all the same.
You need to get psychological help.
I think you actually need help.
But you motivate me to do better to be fair, you know.
Yeah. Really? How much money do I have right now?
Uhhuh. So, how much money do I have
right now? You don't even know how much
money I have right now.
Uh-huh. Ever heard of people had
savings? People might have won money.
You don't know about anything. Joe,
listen. You're a waste of my time.
You don't know what I have.
You don't know what I have. So, and I'm
not showing you anything ever again. So,
there's no point guessing. And re rare.
All of this show money, show money is
just a self projection on your part
because you are the ones that are skin.
Cuz if you really weren't skin, all the
times I've shown you money, you wouldn't
have all ran away. And yes, the past
does count because you love living in
it. So, at the end of the day, stop
wasting my time.
People have [ __ ] more women than you.
You say they can't get a woman. People
have shown more women uh money than you.
You say that they don't have no money.
You're all the same. You need to sort
out your online jealousy to people that
you don't know. And I hope you really
get help for it as well when I'm gone.
You really, really, really um I hope you
get help for your [ __ ] when when I'm
gone, by the way. You know,
it can't be healthy being jealous of
people that you don't know there. So, uh,
have a word. Honestly,
yeah, you can go self-reflect on another
channel. Another self-reflector. Um, you
also can't have more than three color benefits. Really?
says who ever heard of another account?
Never. Have you ever heard of another account?
How can you and Red Star do what you do
every day? You really live sad lives.
You give me the motivation to be better.
You actually give me the motivation to
be better. Like I said, I might even
join the gym again tomorrow.
Yes, it is quite expensive and I would
have the money for it because I have
money. Oh, I forgot I don't have money.
I'm skin calling to you people. with you
little self projectors. Um,
I don't know how you But anyways, like I
was saying, you actually give me the
motivation to actually want to do better
cuz you're all fat, old, ugly on YouTube
every day trying to argue with people
you don't know. You actually make people
actually appreciate life a bit more. You know,
you know, I don't know how you can sit
there all day and be jealous of people.
It's madness. It's actually people that
you don't even know. It's mad. I feel
bad for you.
Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Whatever you say.
I'm skinn. I've never had a woman. I
can't get women. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. You
keep telling yourself that.
You keep telling yourself that.
Yeah. You keep telling yourself that, matey.
I don't know what you're jealous of,
mate. Only you can answer that. Only you
and Red Star can answer that.
I don't know what you're jealous of. I
have no idea. Only you know that cuz you
are the ones that sit on YouTube every
day at your age arguing with people that
you don't know.
You know what I'm saying? Arguing with
people that you don't know. I don't know
what you're jealous of, but it's
something. It's not for me to say, mate.
I don't have a say in the matter, but I know, right?
If I was doing what you was doing on
YouTube all day, every day, especially
at your age, mate, something came right there.
You know what I'm saying?
YouTube. Yeah, exactly. I put my life I
put my life on YouTube for the past 5 years.
You're you're jealous because I'm
younger than you. I'm better looking
than you. I can go out and do more
things than you. I'm able. I mean, when
was the last time you and Red Star
actually [ __ ] left your house?
Yeah, I'm all over the show. Okay. I'm
all over the show. You're the one sat on
YouTube arguing with somebody half your
[ __ ] age every day.
You are jealous. You're jealous of something.
Probably jealous of the fact I could
just go out and speak to people. I can
go out and approach. It is It is
jealousy with you people. It generally
generally is jealousy with you people.
It is. That's why I'm coming off this
[ __ ] for like two weeks.
might come back in like two weeks just
to see if it's the same people every day
like it will always be. Yeah,
you virgin boy and [ __ ] Red Star. It's mad.
Shut up [ __ ] [ __ ] you [ __ ]
Listen, you idiot, Monty. Yeah, stop
saying you've pulled more than me.
You're the one that cried over a slag.
Yeah, if you really could get women.
Yeah, you are the M. Stop talking about
yourself. Stop self projecting. It's not
good for your mental health, you
repeating bastard. This is why I'm
coming off this [ __ ] shitty community.
But anyways, Monty, right? Um, stop
saying that you've pulled more than me,
mate. You're with a [ __ ] slag with a
body count of about 100, mate. You had
to cry over a slag. Yeah, that's why
that that just goes to show how many
[ __ ] you can actually get at your
age. 30 [ __ ] four. Crying over some
slag. But oh, I can pull all of these
women. No, no, no, no, no. You can't
pull nothing, mate. You can't pull [ __ ]
all. If you could pull someone, you
would be crying over some [ __ ] slag.
That's everyone and everyone's.
Yeah. I can't I don't know, man. Just I
I feel like you people on here are
[ __ ] disabled, bro. LT, I actually
think you and Joe, you're actually
disabled. You're actually frying my
brain, bro. You people are actually
frying my brain, lad.
Yeah. What do you think the them brass
uh body counts are? Um I don't know. I
mean, I never cried over an escort. I
never cried over one. And I didn't bang
most of them either. I just got a [ __ ]
This little [ __ ] [ __ ] wants to
[ __ ] talk about [ __ ] One second.
I'll give you the box now. Crying over a [ __ ] slag.
Yeah, bro. You people are disabled.
People explain things to you several
times and you don't understand it. Like,
you truly are disabled.
These people motivate me to want to do
better. You know, they've actually
motivated me. I'm actually going to the
gym tomorrow, bro. I swear to God. I'm
I'm actually going to the gym tomorrow.
These people have actually motivated me, lads.
You actually motivated me, bro. Like,
I'm not even joking. You people really
are mongers on this community. Yeah. Anyways,
they're disb yeah yeah sit flag when you
can pull these flags and that's your
river slag. You're with a slag. You're >> Es
with a slag. But you're with a slag. Your name.
You was crying over a slag. Shut the
[ __ ] up. Christmas. Yeah. Slags.
>> Over slag.
>> Standards. What standards have you got?
>> You was crying over a slag. Man, you got
to get over. You was with a slag.
>> At least I can get a woman. At least I
He kicks himself.
At least I can get a woman peed. Yeah.
Now that she's definitely 100% not a slug. Yeah.
>> Yeah. I'm back now. Listen, you was
crying over a [ __ ] slag that's [ __ ]
everyone on YouTube. Shut the [ __ ] up.
>> Shag slag spirit.
>> [ __ ] crying over a Yeah, but you was
crying over one. You're with a danger.
her body. She actually shown that when
she were pissed
that women for money, not having
>> Well, I know drunk people that don't
show their money. I know people that get
drunk that don't show money.
>> Yeah. What about the one who you
actually give co money to to Shagger?
>> No. No. I didn't do that to Shagger.
>> Listen, listen. Why is she showing her
fanny all off of YouTube?
Why do we use women for sex? Yeah.
>> Listen, Molly, why did you call her slack?
>> No. No, you call you call slag. But why
do you use women? Why do you use women
for sex pee? Yeah.
>> Because it's funny.
>> So, yeah. Why are you crying over a
slag? Yeah, but you're with a slag.
You're with one. There's a difference
between [ __ ] one. Anyone can [ __ ] a
slag. Anyone can [ __ ] a slag, but
doesn't mean we date one and cry over
one. You [ __ ] idiot. You know,
there's a big difference. There's a big
[ __ ] difference. Slags are for one
thing only, not to date and cry about
and go to the next man straight up. And that's
>> You know what I'm saying?
>> That's a slag.
>> Yes, she is a slag.
>> No, you slag slides and that's it.
>> Show her off on YouTube.
>> Yeah. So what she know
she banged LP? That means I got a family me.
>> Yes, she has.
>> He told me. Yeah, he told me.
Well, saying she hasn't.
>> Yes, you did. Tell me that. She's saying she hasn't.
>> Yes, she did.
>> Yo. Yo,
>> come on.
>> You all right, boss?
>> AJ called again. >> Yeah.
LG watch your email, Natalie. He wants
to get in your knickers by the sounds of it.
>> Natalie's email
is got he's old woman AC in America.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Exactly. You got USA is he?
I'm going Finland next month, by the
way, LT. I'm going to show you some
videos. I'm going Finland next month to
link up with someone. I'm going to show
you. Yeah, I'm going to send you all the
videos and you can try and [ __ ] tell me something.
>> Don't come and see no one. You need to
go and see PDF first.
>> You need to be a man first. A man, why
don't you come and see me?
I'll wait till he sees you first.
>> He wants to want to see man to come and
see you. Then he's man to come and see
me then is it until later been to see you.
>> He wants to come and see you.
>> He's not seeing nobody. Pier, he's seen
himself and that's it.
>> Triple H.
>> Yo, so what um so what date are you free
this month? The end of the month. Yeah, I
>> I'm going to come up there. Yeah, I
>> But you better meet though. We're going
to get drunk and stuff.
>> Will I? Yeah.
>> Okay. Good, good, good.
>> I want to know why Taylor wants [ __ ]
not email like what's going on there?
probably because he want you
>> let Taylor on that. Let Taylor come up and talk.
>> He's not trying to come on >> funny. >> No. >> Mi
>> just go with your girlfriend. You say
Izzy. Um LT since you want her so bad.
>> No, it's more bothered about everyone else's girl.
A bit like P. Yeah.
>> Go on. Go and get USA. Izzy. You two are
made for each other.
>> What do you think, Triple H? They were
>> I don't know. I think he wants everyone
sloppy seconds. He
>> wants to see you. What you said the other day.
>> It's true. Why is he
>> He wants to see weird.
>> True. It's true. Why is he sitting there
selfrecting a woman?
>> Did you like American Izzy? Did you
think she was good looking? >> Woman
is a woman.
>> Can't remember what he looks like.
>> The one with the brown hair. One
>> black color.
>> Listen. And Monty, when I come on the
22nd, make sure you're not with the excuses.
Oh, is Taylor.
>> Make sure you're not >> listen
what she looks like. Triple.
>> No. No.
>> I think you like her. Me?
>> I don't even know what she looks like, Matt.
>> You do, man.
>> So, is is that London Taylor going to Monty's door?
He don't he don't even know where I
live. Oh man, I'm not even scared of
London. Anyways, your Monty Timmy was on
Ellie. You know
>> what? Timmy
>> was on Timmy. Yeah. >> Yeah.
Many ways. He only come in the big man
with PJ and then I turn around and I
told him well you have sex with American
woman but you're never going to see
as a question
he's black and then what what did he
said oh no wonder he's obsessed
I said that they're made for each other
>> she likes black guys anyway so what's
what's the problem
it tim Meldridge was eating moldy bread,
>> boy. Triple H, do you ever reckon you
and Fraser will make up?
>> Why though? He didn't even do anything to you.
We usually like argues.
>> Yeah, but he didn't do anything to you,
did he? Triple.
>> No, just
>> No, he didn't ask me.
>> So, you could have went on like a
session like you both like slags anywhere. PGA.
Well, I haven't said your >> misses.
PG had the chance he he'd get one at me.
>> I think there's a difference. Anyway,
both of them.
>> So, are you like paying for sex and PJ?
Yeah. only paying your mom.
>> My mom's too expensive for you. Yeah.
>> Yeah. You taste money might come when
you eat her out. That's true.
>> I don't actually. >> That's
come out all the time. PJ something what
you don't taste.
>> No. Really? Yeah. Cuz I don't eat [ __ ] That's disgusting.
>> Male females come.
>> Yeah. Because I don't eat [ __ ] That's
disgusting. And Triple H don't eat [ __ ] either.
>> Why not? That's the best thing for women.
>> Huh? Don't you eat [ __ ]
>> Like it.
>> N it's frowned upon where I'm from in
London. It's frowned upon.
>> It's called You're not a woman. Now
that's the thing.
>> It's called It's called It's called It's
called a Bocat. It's frowned upon. You
can't do it in London. Some people
sexy qualified in that way yet. You
know, it's [ __ ] disgusting. It's
[ __ ] vile, mate.
AJ what did you did you eat what Triple
H like have you had like a lot of one
night stands then
>> nah not really like lad no [Laughter]
>> more like about about five is it
>> and it's not even that half of the girls
who you been with have been actual
[ __ ] monsters on you off of you
>> who who
was ringing around in a club man she
looked Like Sha's ex-girlfriend.
>> Yeah. Like a gay woman.
>> Look like she had a shower for 16 years.
>> She look at your crackhead.
>> She's better than Natalie.
do Is Natalie your time? No m. >> Why?
>> I like blondes, me, mate.
>> Blondes? Yeah. Oh, I like brunette.
>> Oh, yeah. Brunette like brunette.
>> Yeah. If you like if you like blondes, bro.
>> No. Natalie too fat. Sorry
is loving this, isn't it?
>> Yeah, it's not nice to hear that about Natalie, lad.
>> Yeah, but you No, but it's true.
>> Do you know what I think?
>> Do you know what I think? I think PJ is
jealous that Monty man got Natalie when PJ
>> Yeah, I'm so bro. If I was jealous,
>> if I was jealous, Listen to your brace.
If I was jealous yet, don't you think
I'd be trying to get her to meet us when
we was in Birmingham?
>> Yeah, truly.
>> I was I was getting,
>> you know, I'm one of the first people
she tried tried it with for before was
even on here. >> Yeah.
>> I didn't even know.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Did you
>> found out how small your dick was? She
She took second chance and thought, "No,
give him a fake."
>> You've got a small dick.
>> All right. Remember when I said I sent
Monty a video of me getting a [ __ ]
>> Yeah. It's weird that it's cute, isn't it?
>> It's weird. >> Really? >> Yeah.
>> So, I would say so I'd say I'd say
you've had sex with like four people. Is it?
>> Yeah. You see me get your mom. double
figures, mate. But like, so you have had
one night stand then?
>> Yeah, I had a few
think once they had a blow job outside.
>> Yeah, but you know, Triple H, you know
that you know the one night stand you've
had. Yeah. They didn't all give you
[ __ ] though, is it? Nah. >> Yeah.
>> Not all.
>> Yeah. Some of what? Like some of them
don't, is it?
>> Yeah. Some glosses don't like doing it. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Yeah. But that's just that's just a turn
off, isn't it? PJ, where do you get your
ugly nurse from? Cuz it's definitely not
from your mom.
>> You look like you've got cancer. You
look like [ __ ] Dobby.
>> Look like
>> He looks like Dobby in it. >> [ __ ] um
the ring. What What is it called now
with my precious? Um what's it called?
>> You look like
>> one of the rings. One of the rings.
[ __ ] no, man.
>> Why don't you be a bouncer? >> Hey,
>> why don't Why don't you be a bouncer?
>> I have been a bouncer before, lad.
>> Really? Yeah.
>> No, you haven't. Yeah. Really? [ __ ]
hell. I didn't know that you kept that a secret.
>> Yeah, I keep a lot of things in my life
secret fella. Who's Taylor? He's teller.
>> Your boyfriend's not PJ. >> What?
>> Your boyfriend's over there?
>> No, that's Natalie's ex.
>> No, definitely not PJs.
>> Yeah, it is. Hey, London Taylor doesn't
say his mics me up there.
>> So, do you like that then P?
>> Do I like that? >> Yeah.
>> So, you say sorry then to N then PJ
>> because she she snaked me before like Mike.
>> Excuse she hasn't snaked. You sn when
when she went even on to her pendel. >> No. me.
>> You say to me.
>> No, he said something about
you said that he was going to book a
fake hotel and stuff. What the [ __ ]
>> Who was
setting up a fake hotel for him? [Laughter]
>> [ __ ] hell. That's That's after you
sent the picture of your dick, PJ.
>> Have you sent that dick?
>> No, I've She's never seen my dick.
>> Yes, she has.
>> I bet you I bet you when I sent you When
I sent you a video of me getting When I
sent you When I sent you When I sent you
a video of me getting a [ __ ] you
probably wanked over it.
Only thing I told me, "Yeah, use my
mom's chicks. That's it. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah, that's it.
And that's your mom's tit popped into my
head as well.
>> Oh, your mom got some nice tits.
>> Not as nice as yours.
>> No, no, no. I'm asking you now. Yeah.
>> No, not as nice as your your mom's.
>> What about your mom's ass and now? Do
you ever look at your mom's ass when
she's walking downstairs or anything? >> Yeah.
>> You You like You like You like
Whiteheads his daughter.
>> A bit too young for me, PJ.
>> No, you like him young. The younger the better.
>> No, why do you always talk and [ __ ] You
showing long legs a little bit.
>> No, you've always
used to go there.
Oh yeah. You used to go to Whiteheads
all the time.
>> You used You used to go to Whiteheads to
see the kids sit down, didn't it?
>> You were kids.
>> Wants to meet you.
>> You had a crush on P. Yeah.
>> Yeah, but I was her age. You was [ __ ] older. He
>> No. No. No. No, he was more or less her
age. He was a little bit younger than you.
>> No, she [ __ ] wasn't. We were the same
age, you idiot.
>> What was she [ __ ] She was what? 13.
>> No, she wasn't [ __ ] 13.
>> Yes, she [ __ ] were. I don't even know
how old she was. She was about 12.
About 13. They're my mates in
Manchester. You deal with them all the time.
>> YouTube. Your girlfriend's a YouTube suck.
So, you staying on this community forever,
>> ain't it? I agree with that comment.
Absolute [ __ ] comment. We are
[ __ ] So, we're proud of it. Spast
nation, isn't it?
>> Yeah. You made this bass noises, PJ. You
make it even better. So, um, Monty, um,
you staying on this community forever,
>> PJ, when your mom comes to me house, I'm
getting off YouTube. >> Huh?
>> When your mom comes to my house, I'm
getting off YouTube.
>> Weird, isn't it?
>> It's [ __ ] mad.
>> Yeah. Hey, Monty, why did you burn the
Stitch Teddy? Someone wants to know.
>> Stitch for calling me names. H
>> Stitch recording me names. >> Really? >> Yeah.
>> You know who Stitch is? Triple R.
>> Yeah. Leo and Stitch.
>> You watched it in the cinema. It
>> watched it when I was a kid. >> Yash.
>> Would you meet that nonsex triple H?
>> Do you fancy Sean? Do you actually No,
we're not talking. We're not talking to you nons.
>> No, no, no, no, no, no, no. You call
everyone to [ __ ] yeah, PJ, but you
actually kicking your ass.
>> I've only asked him a question. >> [ __ ]
>> Triple H. Do you fancy Shan?
>> Help me. No.
>> Do you fancy Shan? Triple H. >> No.
PJ now. Can Can you stop bringing him
up? Maybe you fancy him.
>> All I fancy is your dad.
>> Well, that's a bit hard cuz he's dead.
>> It makes it a lot harder.
>> Do you know what I used to do when I was
in a relationship, right? I used to
always go for nice food and that and [ __ ]
>> nice food
>> like going nice like Italian and Indians
and that way. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Do you miss it?
PJ, you never put yourself on big, do you? >> What?
>> You never put yourself on big, do you?
>> What do you mean?
>> Don't worry.
>> Yes. Yeah, I know what you mean with a
restaurant trip. Bless you.
>> Yeah, good times eh. decent lad.
>> So why is this person not talking?
>> His mis he's got his mate muted.
>> Yeah, Taylor's
here. He looks can see my friend.
>> Why not?
>> Give him some attention. He wants to
talk to you.
>> So, what do you think of that Sean's girlfriend then?
>> I think she's a
>> I think it's BJ's type to be honest.
>> I think she's a pig.
>> Don't worry, Trip H. When I come new,
you know, when I went new, I went to a nice Italian.
>> It was nice. Trip H.
>> Did you?
>> Yeah. I went on a date with this lassie.
>> Yeah. I like it.
>> Cute, isn't it? What's your favorite
type of cuisine?
>> Indian I think. Man,
>> you're an Indian. Big Indian lover. I'm
Italian me. Like
>> I've not really had that much Italian.
I've had Italian food. Not like a
cuisine to be fair. Oh no. To be fair.
No, but I like a steakhouse. I like a
nice like steakhouse to be fair.
>> Yeah, I like steak.
>> Nice bit of steak, you know. Oh, can't
beat it. Don't worry. When I come to
Newcastle at the end of the month, mate,
we'll go with loads of dates and stuff.
Yeah, we got
>> I wouldn't end up stroking your leg, you
know. It' be me. >> What? >> You
going to the place with me in the pub? >> Huh?
>> You like going in for the case in the pub?
>> Jamie has never been to a restaurant. He
thinks going to McDonald's is going out
for dinner. his skin.
>> Actually, actually wants to move his Gregs.
>> Jeremy, why do they keep doing this and
saying things about you?
>> Because they're disabled. [Laughter]
>> They always on Jammy's case, are they? >> Yeah.
>> I'm not asked about it. It just shows
I'm a big fan of [Laughter]
They love you deep down, don't they?
>> Why do I do remember rates? Why do these
people call people skin? Because they
are skin isn't it? >> Yeah.
>> What is it with this skin? I bet
everybody in here is racing you.
>> Yeah. Not you though.
>> I think I'm poor me. >> You
only had 20 to last him two weeks. Yeah.
Got me want some cheeseburgers. >> Cheeseburgers.
>> We're from McDonald's. Jeremy.
>> No, I love me.
>> Can 20 last you two weeks?
>> No. I'll tell you. You want to go to bed? >> Really?
Do you have a tick on your bum? >> No.
>> I think that's all the [ __ ]
fascination you get.
>> 20 lost 20 last two weeks is funny. Is it
>> look on Natalie's channel? She does a
lot of coke and updates, doesn't she?
>> Yeah. She rather keep herself to herself
now and she rather not go live the same
as me. That's why you use PJ platform.
>> Why don't you just go live yourself? He
should buy him entertain spastics. [Laughter]
>> Money, can we be friends? Money, can we
be friends again?
>> Apologize to that.
>> Yeah, but she has to apologize to me as well.
>> Apologize to N.
We're friends again. Yeah. >> A
sake. Hold up. Uh, I need to put
Can you hear me? >> Yeah.
>> Your boyfriend's here, please. Yeah.
>> Can you hear me? Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> No, we can't hear you.
>> For [ __ ] sake, man.
>> We can
>> We can't hear you.
>> PJ, your boyfriend's you, man. >> Yeah.
Why is your mic? >> What?
>> Why is your mic [ __ ] like that?
>> Your face is [ __ ]
>> Yeah. You remember back in the day when
that govern that used to go Matt Brown's
house and the lot used to be in
>> Yeah. Money used to like it.
>> No, you got me involved in this [ __ ]
>> It's your fault. All this [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Can you hear me now?
>> Yeah, we can hear you anyways.
>> Yes, we can.
>> You can hear me? Yeah. Yes. >> Yeah.
>> All right. So, what I'm saying is, yeah,
Monty, you've been running your mouth
for a while about me. Yeah. And I'm I'm
just thinking to myself about random ass women.
>> It's not Listen, I'm not here to listen
to me. I'm not here to listen. I'm not
here to argue or any of that silly [ __ ]
Yeah. I just want to make you know, I I
would just like to know where is a
convenient place for you. Can you give
me a field? Or furthermore,
>> get Natalie to confirm a field or something.
I'll come up there. I'll come up there
and I'll slam your head into the ground.
>> I'll see PJ first. Yeah.
>> What do you mean see PJ first? PJ's run
for me. I broke into that guy's I broke
in two times.
>> Exactly. He broke into his house. You were faithful.
>> Yeah, I broke in. Did Does he tell you
that he ran out the back? Does he tell
you that? Does he tell you?
So, what about the park as well, PJ?
There's another time. There's a park.
What about the park when you was
whistling and doing all that silly [ __ ]
and you run as well that time?
>> I'm not going to keep playing these.
Listen, I've heard you. I've heard you.
You keep calling everybody out. Yeah.
And then you make excuses when it comes
to me. So stop stop this [ __ ] like
I've not come to your Stop this [ __ ]
like I've not come to your house about 100 times.
>> Stop this silliness. Like this is
actually silliness. I've come to your
house 100 times. All okay. Fine. Fine.
>> A lot of time you've come with people
and a lot of the time I've come I've
come once. I've come once with people. I
came once and when I came with people
that one time
>> when I came when I came once with one
person with with a couple people that
time it was going to do it was going to
be something major that's why I don't
need to explain myself to you're
obviously weaker than me like what the
[ __ ] you're like half my size says
>> okay bro okay whatever >> be
let me tell you something any normal
person if you go and try to meet someone
after all the [ __ ] that you saying yeah
you're supposed to come outside like a
man yeah so obviously I don't need what
what more do I need to prove I've I've
gone your door. Every single time
someone does something to you, PJ, is an
excuse. When Lord Jay came to your
house, you say that he was hiding behind
a gate. There's always an excuse. When
Terry's come for you, when Terry's come
for you, when Terry's come for you, what
did you say?
>> I've gone to Terry's area.
>> Okay. I'm not going to lie. Yeah, that's
true. Okay. Yeah, that's true. You went
to his area the second time, but the
first time, See, I'm not a liar. I'm not
going to sit on here just lie. The The
first time that he came to you, he ran
off. He was running. We've seen a video ourselves.
>> Okay. And
>> when Lord Jay's come to your house, when
Lord Jay's come to your house, you said
that he was hiding behind a gate, right?
>> No, he stood behind the gate and done
nothing. Let me rephrase what I said.
Let me rephrase it.
>> Yeah, but you didn't step outside. No,
no, but listen to what I'm saying.
Listen to what I'm saying. The deal was
already done. You told him to come. He
came to you and you didn't step outside.
What more does man need to do? Well,
you're you're basically telling us that
we need to risk our liability. Yeah. Um
break in and then drag you out and then
do all this extra stuff. We shouldn't
have to do all that. If you've got all
this mouth online and someone comes to
your house, you should be able to be a
man. Yeah. And come outside and deal
with it. That's what normal people do. But not
>> when I told him to come back and I'll
pay for him to come back and he hasn't. Like
>> Well, he came the first time. Okay. But
>> He went to Timmy three times. He went
for Timmy. It's just like me. It's just
It's just back to me again. Yeah. I've
come I've came so many times. I don't
know why you're telling Monty trying to
make out like I can't I've never tried
to move. What are you talking about?
I've came to you several times. I've
live streamed outside your house while
you're inside your house. What are you
talking about? You've definitely not
come outside when other people on here
has told you LT's outside your house.
You said, "Oh, that's good for him."
What are you talking about? How many
times that happened? I came with £1,000.
I left outside your mother's house and
you was inside there as well. You didn't
come outside. What are you talking about?
>> You like to forget things. You like to
forget things as well. You talk about
other people forgetting things. You like
to forget things. Now, back to I would
like to speak to Natalie because I want
to know what area she's in. Yeah. I want
to come up there to see Monty. Let's
see. Let's see if I bottle it and do all
this silly [ __ ]
>> You're not coming
yourself out there.
What you're doing, hey, this is
deflection tactics. Oh yeah, I won't do
this. I won't do that. I promise you I
will. I promise you I'll come up there.
Go ask if she believes that I'll come up
there. Ask her. I'll tell you the date
that I'm coming up with PJ's girls and
[ __ ] like that on YouTube.
>> No, he says nothing to do with PJ's
girls. See, PJ doesn't tell the whole
story. Let me tell you something. PJ
does not tell you the whole story. What
happened was PJ was sending me multiple
voice notes. Yeah. Do you know what he
was saying in those voice notes? Do you
know what he was saying in those left? >> Yeah.
>> PJ was sending me cuz you know with PJ
he's been in this narrative that I'm
trying to chat to a girl in America. I'm
really not. What happened was he sent me
multiple voice notes one morning. Yeah.
Stating that he's going to do this to
this girl. He's going to do that. He's
going to punch her up. He's going to
grape her. He's going to do all this
madness. Yeah. And I said to PJ,
"Listen, mate, I'm at work here. You're
pissing me off. If you carry on with
this nonsense, giving me your rants."
Cuz what he does is when he's upset, he
starts giving me all these [ __ ] voice
notes. Yeah. Madness. And then I said to
him, I think it was on Instagram. I
can't remember, but he gave it to me on
something. And then what I I what I then
said to him, which I have put out on on
my old channel, by the way, I did put
these things up. I said to him, I said
to him, I said to PJ, "If you carry on,
I wait, listen to me." I said, "If you
carry on, PJ sending me all these
threats of abuse, and you're gonna do
this and do that to this girl." and he's
calling her all these names under the
sun. He's getting racist and all this
bollocks. I said, "What I'm going to do
is I'm going to contact her myself
because he already gave me her details."
So, I said, "I'm going to contact her
myself on Instagram." Yeah. And I'm
going to let her know so then we can So,
you know what I mean? I can try and line
something up here for for months. I
actually believed him. I would never
have done it normally, but I actually
started believing him cuz he was going
on about her for years. He was going on
about her for two [ __ ] years. If
anyone else can confirm this, he was
going on about her for 2 years. And I
actually did believe him because he did
show me a a holiday that was booked and
I said, "Okay, he's being serious this
time." Like honestly, and there is
people like this on the internet that
we've heard of in the past where no one
takes them seriously. Nobody takes them
seriously. Yeah. Until when they go and
do something. So obviously I went and
told her that's what it was. It's got
nothing to do with flirting. Don't Don't
listen to PJ. Yeah. He's talking
nonsense. I've never tried to try to
speak to that girl ever. Not like that. Anyways,
you once again like always, you know.
How did I bring you in for anything? PJ, what?
>> No, no. That's what I'm on about PJ.
Like basically getting you in for well,
not in char
getting involved with magic with my women online.
>> You see the PJ? Yeah. He sits on here
and he takes advantage. The fact that he
knows that I don't want to come on these
live streams and and and explain myself.
So, he takes advantage of it and then he
sits there and he he makes up lies and
he says, "Oh yeah, I'm trying to chat to
this girl in America." That's absolute
[ __ ] And most of the time I just
sit there quiet and I don't even bother.
I don't even care to even like respond
to it like when he's saying these
things. But he knows in his head what
what it is. If he was real like that. He
just told the truth into your into your
own [ __ ] PJ in a way.
>> No, I was me. I was
>> No, this is your own doing in a way. PJ
dragging him to dragging him into
[ __ ] by leaving him text me and [ __ ]
like that. Like
when I mean he was listen I tell you the
time frame he was doing it. He was doing
it from 6:00 a.m. in the morning. Yeah.
which I was getting ready to go to work
and he never stopped until about 5 after
5 in the evening and I said, "Right,
PJ," I even let him know before I did
it. I said, "Right, PJ, I've had enough
of your [ __ ] today." Yeah. You put me in
a like, you already [ __ ] off my mood.
Like, he already put me in a [ __ ] off
mood. Yeah. So, I said, "All right, what
I'm going to do now is I'm going to
contact her. I'm letting you know that
I'm contacting her." I didn't do it
slightly and tried to do any funny stuff
behind his back. I went and contacted
her. I said, "Listen." Yeah. Like, I
don't know. Obviously, you're aware of
this [ __ ] PJ guy, right? All right.
And she said, "Yes." I told her
everything, explained everything. She
said, "Thank you." And then the whole
time that I actually took him seriously
cuz I cuz he did show me the ticket that
he was going, he did book it. Regardless
of anything, he did book it. I saw it.
Yeah. So, what I then did is I told the
girl, "Right, I was giving her plans to
how how she should approach him and who
she should get and blah blah blah."
That's all it was. It was nothing to do with
>> That's why you didn't go That's why you
didn't go to America MP. Yeah. That's
why you didn't turn up.
>> You know,
and he knows I'm telling the truth. If
he knows I'm telling the truth, that's
why he's being quiet. He knows. But if
PJ was real, just tell the truth right
now. Like there's no point telling
people, "Oh yeah, I'm trying to take
your sloppy seconds." You know, it's not that.
>> So this guy, you're obsessed with that.
Oh, that USA.
>> No, but
I don't think he's obsessed with
But you was writing stuff saying that
you were facetiming and flirting.
>> No, no. Yeah, I did say I FaceTimed her.
Yeah, I did. But you No, no, no. There
was nothing to do with flirting. I've
never once told you I was flirting with
her. Stop it. Stop it. Stop it. Stop it.
You're lying. Stop it.
>> You said though. You did say
>> I never once said I was flirting with
her. Stop that behavior right now.
That's a absolute [ __ ] lie. I told
you straight up. Yeah. That yes, we
FaceTime because obviously she wanted us
to have a conversation about you and we
did a couple times.
>> And and and and let's just Hey, let's
just clear this up as well. Let's clear
this up. Let's clear this up. She was
honestly scared about PJ at first. Yes,
she was. I'm not going to lie, she was.
And I told her it was me. I told her,
said there's nothing to be worried about
because then I started showing her all
the L's that he's taken. Yeah. You know
when Lord J's gone to his house. I just
scanned the internet. I said, "Look, if
you if you Google his name yourself,
you'll see a bunch of [ __ ] that's just
happened to him over the years." And
then she saw the one with the bus
driver. She saw the one with Venom and
the 12-year-old and all that. And she
said, "Oh, oh, let him come over here."
Like then she started getting brave.
Like she started piping up again. I was
like, "All right,
>> that Venom video was wild." Like [ __ ] hell.
>> But why didn't you just Why did you
waste all your money, PJ? Yeah.
>> You know, I got some of it back in the
end from the bank, by the way.
>> Your post link for Tim.
>> Not all of it though.
>> Yeah, but you went over there to go for it.
>> I do. I do remember I do remember people
was making saying that PJ didn't pay for
the ticket or anything. But I I I'm the
only person that he did actually confirm
and he did show me the ticket. I saw it
myself. I even knew when he was going
and I remember I even spoke to him on
the day when you were supposed to be
gone. Yeah. And he said, "Ah, he's not G
anymore. He can't be bothered." And I
said, "If I had known, you should just
gave me that ticket that but you
couldn't transfer it and all that." So, yeah.
>> Hang on, PJ. So, basically,
you want you knew that London was
already talking to this girl in America,
but still you sending
um London information about tickets and
stuff like this. like when you were
going where you were going now cuz in
Chance and you knew that I didn't I
didn't show the what hotel I say that at but yeah
>> no he didn't yeah he didn't he I don't
think you even booked a hotel if I remember rightly
>> no I did it was all it was everything
>> but what what I'm not getting at is why
would you show London chair the stove yeah
>> he didn't believe me
>> yeah I didn't believe him that's why he
showed me but the thing was right but
the thing the thing was he was getting
on my nerves and I said listen mate yeah
like go and tell her all of this
nonsense and he said yeah And that's the
only reason why. Listen, normally I know
that PJ's just venting and he's just
talking. Yeah. But because I actually
saw the ticket. That's when I took him
seriously and that's when I contacted
her. I never saw like I never even
contacted her before I saw the ticket.
It's only when I saw the ticket. And if
you remember, there's all these things
that go on in America with some of these
like messed up individuals where no one
takes them seriously because they look
like idiots and then they end up doing
something drastic. Yeah.
This could be another PJ. You never
know. Anyone's capable of anything when
they're angry or whatever. Huh?
>> It will be I've got a feeling PJ will go
around London one day and just do a
massacre one of these days. But if he
did Yeah. And if he did Yeah. It'll be
It'll be on like It will be on innocent
like very innocent little kids or
something like that. It wouldn't be It
wouldn't be someone.
I think it'd be more women. I don't
think he will go for K. I think it'd be
women cuz it's it's a women who's got
what he's really obsessed with.
>> I don't think
he's an idiot, bro. I swear he's an idiot.
>> You don't.
>> So he's got all these lot on there. He's
got all of you honesty on here. Yeah.
Believing that. Oh yeah. I'm trying to
get on to his sloppy seconds. That's
absolute nonsense. And because he knows
I don't want to come.
>> You won't know. But you did use because he knows.
>> No, but you know, you did try.
>> I did not try it with Sig either, you
idiot. What are you talking about? I
told you from the jump that she was ugly
when you first showed me the picture.
>> You wanted a number. You wanted a
>> I thought you got stand PG.
>> Yeah, but you wanted a number. Yeah,
that was a one night stand, Monty.
That's not a [ __ ] relationship. Big difference.
>> I think you know it is. I think I was
retaining information cuz I knew I was
going to eventually just give it out and
I knew that I knew that you had problems
with Sha and I know if Shauny gets hold
of that, then he'll just You know what I
mean? That's Yeah, that's that's why I
think I asked you for the number, but I
didn't do nothing person. I didn't come
>> I don't know.
>> Yeah. So, you're on So, because you know
that I don't want to come on live stream
and explain myself. Yeah. So you take
advantage of it, PJ, and you start lying
and telling people, "Oh, I tried to
tried it on with USA Izzy and all that."
No, it's only because you was going on
about it for 2 years. Listen, I know
when you're venting sometimes, and I
don't take it seriously, but it's only
until when you prove to me the ticket, I
said, "Oh, yeah, I've got to contact her
now." Like, you know what I mean? And
because you started contacting the the
ex-boyfriends, the dad, all of this
[ __ ] Yeah. I said, "Oh, yeah. Now I can
affection. I can probably get you killed
over there." Like, I honestly was
thinking that. like, you know, they I
know that they've got I know that
they've got stand your ground rules um
laws over there. So, I was thinking,
yeah, maybe maybe you can actually get
clapped and not come back.
>> Probably will do cuz if he's calling his
that girl to [ __ ]
to do [ __ ] then they [ __ ] funny.
>> They got they got gun licenses.
All they want to do is in a 4x4, you [ __ ]
>> And and after this happened, Yeah. I
even told PJ, yeah, I wasn't flirting
with her or anything. I told her I told
him, it's not even like I've like tried
to hide anything. I told him exactly
what was the plan. And then he was
telling me, "Oh, she doesn't know
anybody and everything." I said,
"Listen, it's always wrong to assume
that people don't know anything." I
said, "At the end of the day, she's a
girl." Yeah. Do you honestly think that
someone's just going to let even if it's
a man in her family? This guy doesn't
have to be a gangster or anything like
that. But it's like I've got a sister,
right? Or forget me, any normal man,
you've got a mother, right? If you know
that some man's going to come and do
something or try and do something to
your mother, you're going to stand
you'll probably die for your mother, right?
>> Yeah. Of course you would.
>> Exactly. So that's that's what I'm
explaining to PJ. Like I don't care. You
don't have to be a gangster or anything
like that. Yeah. It's just if you think
you're going to come and harm someone's
daughter, someone's sister, someone's uh
cousin or whatever, and you think that
you're just going to get away scot-free
and you're from another country going
into her territory doing this [ __ ]
Yeah. I said, "You got to come on.
That's just that's that's stupid. You
can't even think like that.
And and they and they've got the history
of PJ threatening and saying stuff. He
he's not just gave me all these threats.
He's gave it to the dad. He's gave it to
all of them as well. So they know about
him. They all know about him.
>> Yeah. So you be
you have been a bully through your head
PJ. You to be honest with you.
But I was actually disappointed that he
never went because if I know that he
like I honestly thought he was going to
go but because he never went I just
thought oh man I can't be getting
involved in this stupid [ __ ] anymore
because that's just what it was.
>> I think if you didn't tell PJ about
Norway then I think PJ so would have
gone. I think it's cuz PJ knew what was
going to happen.
>> PJ PJ PJ's not getting on that play man.
like when it come before.
>> Yeah. But what did you tell me when you
got in that plane to to Scotland? What
did you tell me?
>> Yeah. I said I didn't like it. It was a
bit felt a bit scary. Yeah. So,
>> right. And you didn't get a return
flight, did you?
>> I never got a return flight.
>> Yeah, that's what I'm saying. You didn't
get a return flight, isn't it?
>> Yeah, I didn't. Yeah, but I didn't Yeah,
but I didn't book one.
>> That was your first time on a plane, right?
>> Yeah, but I didn't book a return. That's
what I'm saying.
>> So, how did you get back home? I got a
train back on you in a long ass train.
>> Just in case I didn't like it. Just in
case I didn't like it. So what, bro? >> Yeah. >> What?
>> Yeah. [ __ ] bag. You're not getting a
>> You're a [ __ ] bag. You're a [ __ ] bag.
>> And let me ask London Taylor this. Why
aren't you going to James after James
saying that you and me met and you rape
me? London Taylor. That was your mom
that said that stupid [ __ ] Oh, yeah.
That's another thing as well. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Thanks for reminding me.
Yeah. Yeah. Did What? Did Jake J never
said that? I'm sure she never. That's [ __ ]
>> No, she said it yesterday on Is that
>> I was told that it was your mother that
said that dumb [ __ ] but Okay. So So
it's that [ __ ]
>> So I was I was sent a picture I was sent
a picture about that Jane the other day.
Yeah. Apparently she's got her dentures
out or something and she's got brown
teeth. Listen, man. Uh, listen. I don't
know why she's coming online and saying
all this nonsense. She also went and
said, "What did she say? What did you
tell me, PJ?" She said, "Everything
about me is fake." How would she know?
What does she know about me? She don't
know nothing about me. Do you think I'm stupid enough?
>> She sent you nudes and you showed
everyone as well.
>> I never showed her [ __ ] What are you talking about?
>> He sent you nudes of herself and you
showed people her nudes.
>> Who else did he say?
>> I never I never I promise you right now.
See, this is what I'm saying about these
people and lying. You know, if I if I
showed her something Listen, she you
know what she did?
>> She took something off of my YouTube channel.
>> You said she said you also raped someone else.
>> Yeah. You know what? All right. All
right. Okay. Okay. No. No. Do you know
what? I don't even care about addressing
stuff like this. Yeah. Because it's
preposterous. How the hell would she
addressing that someone's going around
what I'm saying is what I'm saying? No.
No. What I'm saying is the woman has
already threatened to call police on me
multiple times. Yeah. What am I supposed
to do with this dumb [ __ ] I can get a
girl to come and come come with me and
drive up there and thing and then what's
she going to do? She's not going to come
out. She's not going to like face up
into anything. I don't know why she's telling people.
>> Let me let me break something down.
Should I do you want me to tell you
about this woman?
>> I swear to God. Yeah. I swear my nan on
everything I love. Yeah. You know this
woman threatened to kill herself if I
didn't talk to her. I've got that. I
swear to God. I've got that in my email.
She said, "If I don't speak to her or
whatever and and phone her or whatever,
she she she's going to do something um
crazy." It was along them lines. That's
exactly what she said to me. Yeah. Don't
listen don't listen to this mental
health [ __ ] bimbo, man. I'm telling
you, this whole time she just plays
little stupid games, this stupid woman.
And let me tell you something now. She c
she tried to message me uh about nearly
2 weeks ago. Even still, she's still
trying to message me. I ignored it.
She's tried to send me emails still.
I've ignored it. She tries to send PJ
emails. Has she not PJ?
>> Yep. As always.
>> Exactly. People ignore her. I'm telling
you right now, this woman's sick in her head, man.
>> Like, that doesn't I don't even want to
explain myself to be honest. If you
don't honestly believe that, then you
believe her. I don't give a [ __ ] man.
Like, if you honestly want to believe
that I raped [ __ ] come on, man.
>> But I swear I got told it was your
mother that said that, though. I don't
even get told it was her
>> apparently. So, but she got it in her
head. And even though I told her
yesterday it's not true, she's still
saying it was true.
>> Oh, is she online? Wait, wait. Is she I
told people I told you PJ comes online
saying this nonsense. Yeah. To call like
to to get hold of me. I Oh, come on.
>> Well, this was last night.
>> Are you laughing?
>> Who's Whose panel was she? Whose panel
Whose panel was she on? She's still
talking about me. Hey, listen. Let me
tell you something, Natalie. Yeah. You
know what she did? She got on her fat
injections. Yeah. And she took like her
her fat injections. Yeah. And then like
now she's got like disgusting senulite
skin. Trust me. So now she thinks that
she's a bit popping. This woman has
filters galore and makeup. She's never
confident without any of that stuff.
She's got a head full of gray hairs.
Yeah. And she like she always dyes her
hair and stuff, isn't it? Like she goes
and gets Botox, all of this nonsense.
Yeah. But she can't cover up the fact
that really she was a fat [ __ ] Like
that's that's the honest truth. That's
why she never used to show her body
before. Because when your mom outed her
for being a fat [ __ ] really. Yeah. um
she went and uh she had some like mental
breakdown and she went and got some fat
fat injections to lose all that weight.
She never done it naturally. She never
went to the gym and what normal people
do. No, she got on the fat injections.
That's what the and now she thinks she's
brand new. Now she thinks she's brand
new with all that makeup and stuff. Take
all that makeup off and you'll see a
plain dead [ __ ] that's on on on live
like just trying to she what she's
trying to do she tries to flirt with
everybody to get like to boost her own
ego. She's not going to meet no one. And
the same people that she slags off to
me, apparently she's running back to
them. Like, do you know how much time
she used to slag off Lord J to me? >> Yeah.
>> Trust me, this Listen, it's it's cool. I
don't even expect anyone to believe me,
but she knows what she does. No [ __ ] mad [ __ ]
>> She's meeting Lord. Yeah.
>> Oh, yeah. Sure. All right.
>> She's meeting. She's She's meeting
everyone, man. Yeah, she's meeting
everyone. She's meeting PJ as well.
She's meeting me as well.
Yeah, she's meeting everyone, man.
>> Yeah. Look, let me tell you something
about this woman as well. She knew that
me and Mark had tension, right? And she
would still go behind Mark's back when
his mother was dying and still try to
speak to me. That's how I'm sick in the
head she is. I I even used to say to
her, here's here's the thing. Why would
I trust a woman that will go behind her
own man's back whilst his mother is
dying and he's in he's in emotional
state and she's still trying to chat to
me? Why would I trust someone like that
to show anything? What she did is she
took a picture or she took um she
screenshotted something on my own
channel that I put out myself. I never
sent her jack [ __ ] I promise you. Ask
her to show you what exactly I've I've
sent her. I never sent her nothing. If
you see the text messages, I've never
sent her jack [ __ ] Nothing.
Don't listen to these people. These
people chat absolute and you know what?
It's because I'm quiet and I don't even
like explaining myself so people take
advantage and think she can just go
around spurting [ __ ] It's absolute nonsense, man.
But whose panel Whose panel did she say
this on anyways?
>> Last night.
>> Oh, she was on
>> last night. Yeah, yesterday.
>> What time was it? Okay. What I've
noticed about this woman, what you don't
understand yet is on the weekend she
gets drunk. And she gets drunk by
herself cuz she's got a disabled
daughter. Yeah. And her daughter's not
young, by the way. Her daughter's not
young. Her daughter's like 26. Like
she's just a couple years younger than
PJ. So like she what she does is she
gets drunk and then she comes on and
when she feels that she's a bit horny
and that she comes and tries to get
attention from people and she knows she
can't call my phone or anything like
that. Yeah. So she's now resorting to
YouTube now. That's what she does. So
she's come online. So she's come online
and she's talking madness and I would I
blatantly was See, that's what I'm
saying. No one told me. Normally someone
would tell me PJ would tell me or
something. Yeah. Nobody told me nothing.
So I didn't know. Mad
madness. She's still doing this. You
know what it is? She wants my attention.
Oh, yeah. Jane, I know you're listening,
[ __ ] Why the hell are you going online
still talking madness about me when you
know in your head you're still trying to
text message me? You're trying to send
me text messages. I ignore you. That
doesn't make sense. That blatantly is
because you want my attention. You want
me to say, "Oh, Jane, why are you saying
this? Why? I'm not messaging you.
Nothing. You can piss off. Yeah, I
already done what I had to do. I just
wanted to show Mark I just wanted to
show Mark here that you're a cheap
little [ __ ] that I can just like just
mess around with and just show him.
That's what it was. I I don't care about you.
>> Oh, and by the way, yeah, she was
telling me everything about Mark as
well. Everything. How he suffers from
anxiety attacks and uh Yeah. Yeah. And
how she has to like mother mother him
basically. She told me she told me
everything. She's the one that told me
about this guy don't own [ __ ] as well.
And she told me that he owes her money
for going on a holiday or something. He
owes her 500. That's what I'm trying to
say. Listen, man. I could there's so
much [ __ ] I could just think of the top
of my head what this woman does. And she
knows that me and him don't like each
other, but she will still tell me these
things. Why would I trust a female like
that? Does that even make sense? I'm not
stupid, you know?
>> Monty owes me money.
Yeah, but that's not that's not that's
not that's not that's not um it's
different from when uh if you if you're
going out of a woman. Yeah. It's
different. Like if you're if you owe a
mate money, that's different from when
you're going out of a woman. You're
supposed to be taking care of that woman
or or something. Do you know what I mean?
>> Yeah, I know what you mean. PG. I don't
know what to do with that though.
>> Money owes me money. I don't owe you nothing. PJ,
>> you owe me £500. 500?
>> I can't believe it. This woman said I
raped people and I raped someone else.
Is this [ __ ] woman all right? Like
this one. Oh, I swear to God. Like
that's that's madness.
You know what? I really I shouldn't even
address it. I should just stay quiet and
just let you run with whatever you want
to run with. But like, man, what the
[ __ ] Like that's why
>> I would I would just throw at her door.
>> Why Why even Do you know the funniest
thing? If I do that, all these Listen, I
could easily do that. Yeah, but why? If
I do that, I'll get nothing but
[ __ ] come out the out of the
woodworks. Oh, he's bullying all female,
but he can't do anything to PJ. [ __ ]
off, man. I'm not like to slam me. I can
I can I can bring a girl. I can
definitely get a girl to I can
definitely get a girl. But the thing is,
is she going to already call the police
before I even get there? That's that's
the question. Like, come on, man. Cuz I
already I already had someone that was
on my channel that's seen her [ __ ]
anyways. Yeah. And that said that they
would easily just wash her. What? >> Yeah.
>> And all I'm saying is Yeah. Here's
another thing, but is any person can
speak to her. Just be better looking
than mock. Anyone. Just give her a
little bit of attention. Listen to her a
little bit and she will tell you
everything that everything about her stupid life.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You go. You're in there,
Monty. You're in there.
>> Yeah. Trust me, man. It's right here. I
don't need no other woman. I know. That was
I can't believe it. Like, what? So So,
so wait, hold on. She went and said all
this, PJ, and you didn't even like just
tell her like, "Come on, that's that's
[ __ ] Come on. That's Come on."
>> I sat I sat I sat there and watched.
>> Yeah. You know what? The lie is more
entertaining than the truth, is it? No,
I get it. Don't worry. I get it. Yeah.
>> Entertaining, is it?
>> Yeah. Yeah. I get it, man. Trust me, I
understand. No, but but that's but
that's mad though. You you sit on you
sit on here and you pick your moment, ain't it?
>> Yeah, but that's mad to accuse someone
of something so he heinous like that
though. That's Oh, bro. I can't even
That's That's mad. I can even say that about someone.
>> What woman have you met up here? Someone else.
>> I ain't met none of the I ain't met none
of these women off of here. I've spoken
to them like I've spoken to I've spoken
to various like you know what I mean? Listen,
a couple of them even
>> brother. I never even told you that.
That's another thing as well. Yeah. I
never even told you that. PJ PJ, why
would I tell you knowing full well that
you open your mouth?
>> PJ PJ PJ PJ PJ. Why would I tell you
anything knowing full well that you open
your mouth? I if Natalie Natalie can
confirm this when I was speaking to her.
Yeah. I told her, "Do not ever tell none
of these dudes nothing." Like I told her
from the start. I said, "Listen, I would
never chat about her and just vice
versa. Keep that same contract. Don't
talk about me to none of them. And then
I also let Natalie know the only reason
why I was speaking to her. Yes. To piss
all these guys off because these dudes
were all racist at the time and they had
a big problem with it because I remember
how they used to go on. I I've never met
this seaside dark guy or heard of him or
anything like that yet. Well, I only
heard what Natalie's told me. But she
told me how these people were so mad
that that he piped her. Do you know what
I mean? So obviously I said, "Yeah, like
I would like to get these guys mad as
well." That's all it was. >> Wow.
That's it. And I did tell her lie. I
told her just keep st keep quiet. But
these people, what people don't know on
on these things, they don't know how to
be quiet. Just like this stupid [ __ ]
She's going around telling people I rap.
Who did I Who else did I flipping rape then?
>> Who's supposed to pick someone up or
something in a car?
>> No, that was me. Picked me up in the car
and fired me.
>> Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I know. Yeah, I
know what she's talking about cuz she
said Yeah, she's Yeah, she said that
before actually. Yeah. to be fair, but
she never said rape though, but she did
say that one before as well. Apparently,
um I I picked Natalie up and I got ahead
of her in my car or some [ __ ] And then
I heard another thing that I gave her I
gave Natalie 20 for a [ __ ] or some
it's mad. Like, yeah, I've heard I've
heard bad [ __ ] No, but listen to me.
These people are the same people that's
going around telling people that I'm
wet. Like, do you know what I mean?
>> These are the same people like Yeah, but
Natalie is like like what that guy said,
Natalie is a bit of a scar, though.
Natalie's not a scared yet.
>> Oh god.
>> Natalie about you with
>> Natalie. Do you remember Do you remember
that? Do you remember that song um for my birthday?
>> Oh yes. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Okay.
>> No, you can tell you two have definitely
got history, mate.
>> Oh, shut up, man.
>> 100% mate. Is it? Yeah, you can tell. Is
it? Oh, but hey, you're trying to stir
[ __ ] man. Stop it.
>> 100%. Nah, you can tell. Stop.
>> Don't worry. I'm not going to I'm not
going to say nothing. I know.
>> You're trying You're trying You're
trying to stir [ __ ] man. Stop it.
>> No, no, no. I'm not saying nothing now.
It's between you two and it
>> listen man. I don't have no Listen,
Natalie, you see how Natalie, you seen
how I've gone on with Jia? Have I ever
gone on like that to you? >> No.
>> Exactly. Because this because you don't
like as long as you just leave me alone,
I don't bother nobody. as of anyone. If
you just leave me alone, I won't bother
you. But it's this woman, she gets a kick.
>> But this Jane, this Jane woman, she gets
a kick. Yeah. Out of trying to wire me
up. You You don't understand. She plays
[ __ ] up little trolling games. You
know what I think to myself? I think to
myself, she's a troll. Yeah. But then at
the same time, I think, no, she might
not be a troll. She's just mentally
disturbed. Yeah. And it comes across
like she's trolling. Do you know what I mean? >> Mhm. >> Yeah.
That's your girl though. >> Who? >> Jane.
>> Yeah. All right.
>> I got to Hey, I got to shoot now.
Anyways, man. I'm just outside the house anyways.
>> Okie dokie.
>> All right. Cool. A bit.
>> Yep. You're now
two have definitely got history. Okay, definitely.
But I won't um I won't say anything.
That's our little secret.
I want your opinion, Grezy. Yes. Uh-huh.
She sucked out his Willie. Yeah.
Yeah. What's your opinion?
>> Do you in my opinion mean
Mr. Mcoo and his ugly little mates?
I'm not a virgin, Liam. I'm not a virgin. Oh, wow.
Do you want my number?
LT was just on the panel. Nicolo,
what? You don't want sex from a woman, Greavvesy?
You don't know what you're missing out on?
on then, do you?
Do you want my opinion to be? Ah,
yeah. Well, [ __ ]
But that America thing, I got some money
back for that. Anyways,
and the reason I didn't go is because
that 19year-old was begging me not to
go. I said, "Oh, yeah, I need to go."
I've got some history in America and
[ __ ] She said, "Oh, don't go. Don't go.
that time. I won that four grand and
etc., etc., etc." So, yeah. Anyways,
Yeah. I kept telling her about it in it.
Yeah. She said, "You can't go. You can't
go. You can't go." I said, "I want to [ __ ] go.
I'm gonna have these bastard corn
flakes." You remember when Sippy said that
I'm going to have these bastard corn flakes?
She don't want to know you. She don't
want to know you. She don't want to know Um
don't want to know you. She don't want
to know you. Don't want to know you. Natalie.
Natalie loves Peter Belly. If I went to
Birmingham, she would be throwing
herself at Peter Belly. She loves Peter
She'll be like, "I really want you, but
I don't think you want me."
But I don't think you want me. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm a virgin, bro. Yeah.
[ __ ] rape victims. A lot of them. You
remember that one?
Rape victims. A lot of them.
Great big sims. A lot of them victims.
That's funny. That
Yeah, lucky for you I've got both.
You remember that, Nicolo? Lucky for
you, I've got both.
Funny enough, Nicolo Ant-Man sent me
some Chucky thing today where Chucky was
going around with a knife.
He sent me some Chucky thing.
Oh, I just made up stuff.
You already know it's made up. So why
you asking what was he on about when you
know all of the [ __ ] he says is made up?
You already know what that virgin says
is made up.
Who has curly hair?
But yeah, I'm coming off of this [ __ ]
after today anyways, bro. So don't I
didn't tell you. So
these little weirdos, we can't be sat on
YouTube all day every day. I've got a
busy week. Um, next week
we can't all be on YouTube like Ricky
Millan and all these little low lives. So yeah. Yeah. Ricky Millington.
Yeah, bro. That would be me.
Can't sit here talking to these skin bastards. Henry Nicolo.
Why do these people come here and call
me Skid Nicolo?
Cuz they're skin.
It's cuz they're scared, is it? They
call people skin cuz they're skin
just like that Jo. He just wants attention.
I'm not giving him any more attention.
Sad old man. One second.
Why is LJ sat there recording?
Uh Ricky Milling. He's a 40-y old virgin
just like a lot of people on here.
The only thing that makes me laugh about
this huge drinking is Timmy.
Tibby makes me laugh on this community.
I don't know about you, but
Yeah, he makes me laugh, man.
Does he make you laugh?
Yeah, he makes me laugh out loud, bro. It's funny.
Yeah, they're all the same on here.
They're all the same on here. These little mongos.
These little mongos