I thought I'd go back live for this
little [ __ ] terrible trainers cuz his
comment has just come up. One second. 11 minutes ago.
Terry, why are you giving it the big?
Yeah, when you Listen, I'm going to come
to your area tomorrow. Yeah, this time
don't run away. Yeah, you skin little
[ __ ] bastard. Don't run away this
time, terrible trainers. Yeah. I'm going
to come to your area tomorrow. Sure. You
got a McDonald's there or something.
This time don't run away, big man. Yeah.
And you can cry to your little boyfriend
all you want. Yeah. You little keyboard
warrior. You little [ __ ] mate. You're
on £300 a [ __ ] month. You're on £300
a month, mate. You can't even afford a
new pair of [ __ ] trainers. You're
[ __ ] all skin, bro. You are skin. You
You don't even have £1,000. You skid
bastard. Have you seen your trainers?
You silly little [ __ ] [ __ ] coming on
here pretending that you got kids and
[ __ ] [ __ ] emailing people. Don't
[ __ ] pretend that you're not on here now. You know, you know,
[ __ ] stupid little [ __ ] [ __ ]
Come back on here. Yeah, you commented
13 minutes ago.
I'm going to go to this cunt's area tomorrow.
100 [ __ ] million%. Yeah.
I thought, you know what? [ __ ] it. It's
not going to cost us It's not going to
cost more money.
Yeah. Come on in.
Come on, you little [ __ ] What are you
waiting for? You're online. I don't know
what you're waiting for. You silly little [ __ ]
You silly little terrible trainer.
Little [ __ ] [ __ ] You ran away when I
come to his area. You little [ __ ]
[ __ ] We know you're on here. Come on.
Oh, [ __ ] it. I'll go about life for you.
You know, you little skint bastard. Have
you seen your [ __ ] trainers? You
silly little kitty fiddling [ __ ] You
silly little bastard. I'm coming to your
area tomorrow, big man. I'm coming to
your area tomorrow and I'm going to go
live and I'm going to show everybody.
Well, saying that, you will bias on it.
But, you know, I'm just going to laugh
at you because I know what's going to be
the truth when you don't come out again.
You silly little [ __ ] Mate, you're on
£300 a month universal credit. How the
[ __ ] can you talk about somebody that's
got a grand more than you? What the
[ __ ] You silly little [ __ ] You silly
little skint [ __ ] Coming on here
pretending that you got kids. Coming on
here pretending that you're [ __ ] you
know, pretending that you know uh what
was it? You silly little [ __ ] What was
it again? Lying that uh you're [ __ ]
what was it?
What was it? Old man on £300 a month.
lying that you got [ __ ] kids and
lying that you uh you're on um
a suspended sentence, bro. Yeah.
You know what I mean? Yeah.
Come back on here then you little [ __ ]
Come on here you little middleage skint
bits with the shitty trainers. Come on.
Come on. We all know you're online. Come
on. You was on here 11 minutes ago.
Love it, mate. You're a [ __ ] [ __ ]
with no money, mate. You're on £300 a
month. I'm going to this concert area
tomorrow. I'm going to his area
tomorrow. [ __ ] it. I'm going to his area
tomorrow. [ __ ] it. Make sure you don't
run away this time, big man. I'm coming
to his area tomorrow. [ __ ] this. Let's
see what the little skint [ __ ] has got
to say to my face with these shitty
little trainers. This silly little [ __ ]
Let's see what he's got to say tomorrow.
Let's see what this little [ __ ] has got
to say tomorrow. And I go to his area.
I'm sick of this bastard commenting on
my [ __ ] channel all the [ __ ] time. Yeah,
100%. Let's see. Let's [ __ ] see. Oh,
I'm not I'm not the one, bro. I'm not
the one telling people how you're not
the one. You're a little [ __ ]
spasticated [ __ ] on £300 a month. What
the [ __ ] is not the one about you, you
silly little [ __ ] You silly little
bully victim. I'm going to this country
area tomorrow as soon as I wake up. Make
sure this guy does not run away again.
Yeah, you can ring LT all you [ __ ]
want. You can ring whoever you want. I
don't give a [ __ ] Let's see this little
skint [ __ ] with his shitty little
trainers and I'm going to bang him so
hard in his face and I'm going to show
everyone this little [ __ ] on YouTube.
This horrible jealous little skint [ __ ]
who touches up his daughter. Yeah. I'm
going to his area tomorrow. 100% I'm
going tomorrow as soon as I wake up.
Yeah. Tell me if I don't [ __ ] do it.
I'm going to show everyone the skint
[ __ ] [ __ ] and his ugly face and I'm
gonna smack him up. You know, all of
this [ __ ] Yeah. That these big people
have been [ __ ] doing for years and
years and years people. Let this little
ugly [ __ ] with his ugly kids that he
touch up touching up come out and see me
tomorrow. Simple, bro. Yeah. Come on
then. Come on. Let's see this little
[ __ ] that touches up these kids. Let's
see what Let's see if this how this guy
is not really really the one. Yeah.
Let's see if this little [ __ ] man
ain't really the one tomorrow. Yeah. All
right. [ __ ] this, bro. Yeah. Hold me by
it, bro. I'm going to this Terry guys
area tomorrow. Show everybody how you're
not the one tomorrow when I'm in your
[ __ ] area. And you can run to LT all
you want. Crying all you want. Because
you know what? I would love to embarrass
you one more [ __ ] time. You silly
little skint. Little ugly ugly kid
bastard. I'm going to [ __ ] I swear to
God if this guy comes out tomorrow I'm
going to smash the face liber. I'm going
to smash these ugly skinned face in
these ugly kids. I'm going to this
cunt's area tomorrow. Yeah. Simple. And
you know what? Funny enough. Yeah. This
guy got brought up. This guy got brought
up yesterday as well. Yeah. Are you
going to come out tomorrow? You silly
little touches up his kids, you know.
Are you going to come out tomorrow or
[ __ ] or you going to make some more
excuses up? Well, we'll see you
tomorrow, won't we, big man? You're not
to run away like all of you other little
[ __ ] people on here. I'm going to get
you trainers, smack you around your [ __ ]
in face with it. And I will teach you to
keep coming on here bothering people.
Yeah. Every single [ __ ] day. I'm
going to piss all over your area. Talk
about kids and you're going to do
nothing about it. You silly little
[ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah. Since [ __ ] LT
would like to [ __ ] he seem to have
brought you up yesterday.
Yeah. I mean, why not? What? Now's the
time for a [ __ ] renewal. And I'm
going to show you exactly what these
people do when you go to these people's
area every single time. I'm going to
start with this little skint [ __ ]
This [ __ ] skink ugly [ __ ] when I go
to his ugly area. Yeah. Now, I don't
want to hear no excuses.
I don't want to hear no excuses from
this little [ __ ] [ __ ] when I'm talking
about kids in his area tomorrow. I don't
want to hear no excuses. Do you understand?
I'm going to go and smack the [ __ ] in
his face and smack it again. Yeah. And I
think, you know what? Let's say no one
won the two times. Let this [ __ ] come
out tomorrow. Yeah. Let this little [ __ ]
come out tomorrow
and see what happens to him. Yeah. [ __ ]
this, bro. [ __ ] this. The guy got
brought up early as well, so [ __ ] it. Why not? Yeah.
[ __ ] don't come on my channel unless
you're going to back up your [ __ ]
talk, old man. You understand, old man
with shitty white trainers. Don't come
on my channel saying about how I'm not the one.
I'm not the [ __ ] one. Well, go and
suck up your kids that don't exist. I'm
coming to your area tomorrow, but bring
whoever you want. And all of this family
Yeah. that you came. Oh, you know, all my family.
Well, you can bring them out tomorrow.
You know, he made a good point. It's a
draw. Let's see who comes out tomorrow
then. I can't believe I'm wasting my
time with these [ __ ] mongos yet again
on this skint. I'm going to [ __ ] him up.
Show everyone his ugly face just like
all of these people in here. And that's
what I'm going to do, bro. 100%.
This skint little ugly [ __ ] This
turnpike lane [ __ ] Yeah. I don't even
know why the [ __ ] he got [ __ ] mentioned, you know.
Don't I don't want to hear no excuses.
You turn fighting kitty fiddling [ __ ]
you know, trying to say how you're not
the one to people. Start emailing people
how you're not the one.
>> Yeah, this will be an easy bet to win as
well. This is going to be an easy
[ __ ] bet to win. I'm going to smack
this cunt's face in. I swear to God, I'm
going to smack his [ __ ] face.
All right, listen. I'm coming to your
area tomorrow, [ __ ] Yeah. So, make
sure you don't make any excuses, you
little turn pike lane skint bastard with
your ugly kids. Make sure you don't make
no excuses tomorrow cuz I am coming. I
don't want to hear no excuses, [ __ ]
boy. Yeah, you're emailing people about
you're not the one. You're not the one
when you're touching up your [ __ ]
ugly kids and you're not meeting anyone.
Listen, come out tomorrow and don't make
no excuses, [ __ ] boy. You little skin
ugly drained ugly [ __ ] [ __ ] Ugly kid
man. And I'm going to say all of this
[ __ ] to your face tomorrow. Yeah. Make
sure you show up. Listen. Make sure you
show up tomorrow. Yeah. So I can smash
your face in, ugly man. Let's see who's
not the one tomorrow when you don't show
up. Listen. Cuz we all know your area
and we all know where you live. So make
sure tomorrow you show everybody how
you're not the one [ __ ] boy. Yeah. I'm
coming to your area tomorrow. I'm coming
to your area tomorrow. Let's see how
much you're not the one big man. And how
you're not a keyboard warrior, big man.
You know what I'm going to do? I'm going
to smash your face in. Show everyone
your ugly m face and spit in your mouth.
Yeah. And it will teach you. Yeah. I
will teach you that you're not going to
keep coming back on YouTube. I am going
to spit in your mouth and I'm going to
humiliate you and I'm going to send the
video to [ __ ] LT um and basically say
this can't ain't the one, bro. This
4-foot [ __ ] with the ugly traders and
the ugly face. This skid little bastard
on benefits is not the one. This skid
little bastard ain't the one. So I will
come tomorrow at 6. Okay. I'll come
tomorrow at 6:00 p.m. Yeah.
All right. Listen, [ __ ] boy. I'm going
to come to your area at 6 p.m. tomorrow.
Yeah. Don't run away this time with your
ugly trainers and bring your ugly kids as well.
Bring your ugly kids as well. Bring your
And you remember the [ __ ] email that
you [ __ ] wrote as well. Yeah.
Remember the email that you wrote. Don't
run away this time. Don't pretend you're
on probation this time because I'm
coming at 6 p.m. Oh, so using work as an
excuse. I'll be there at 6 p.m.
tomorrow. I don't want to hear no
excuses. I don't want to hear I'm not
the one. I'm on probation. I don't want
to hear these excuses. I'm going to show
everybody the real life ma. The real
life skint benefit m cheap online, bro.
I'll be at your area tomorrow at 6 p.m.
Let's see this little coward bun. Let's
see the bun. I'm going to show everyone
the ugly face. The ugly bun. You're not
going to run away, are you? You're not
going to run away, are you, skid boy,
skid trader boy? You're not going to run
away, are you? I'll be there at 6 p.m.
So, don't make any excuses this time,
you little [ __ ] Don't try and make
excuses that you're that you're uh that
you're on probation, cuz you're not on
probation. You're literally not on
probation. You've never been on
probation in your life. You've never
been nicked in your life. I'll see you
tomorrow at 6 p.m. I will see you
tomorrow at 6 p.m., you little skid bastard.
You little skint ugly [ __ ] You ugly
kid bastard. I'll see you tomorrow at 6
p.m. Yeah. Do not make excuses this time
cuz I'm going to screenshot this as well
where you said you're going to be there.
Please come out, bro. I want to show
everyone the manta. The ugly old man.
And you know what? You're going to
you're going to hide your face. You're
going to hide your face, but I'm going
to show everyone the real life manta.
I'm going to put my light I'm going to
put my face next to your face. Yeah. And
I'm going to show everyone the Terry
Manta. the 300 pound in a month manta
that let me come to his area manta.
We're going to see the real manta
tomorrow. We're gonna see the [ __ ]
manta. The 4 foot [ __ ] manta, the ugly
old man m. Make sure you show up
tomorrow, bro. This is going to be a
proper proper proper ownage. Please show
up tomorrow, you know, and bring as much
as you can as well cuz I'm going to
[ __ ] rob you as well. I'm going to be
a dirty thief in your area. I'm going to
be a dirty [ __ ] in your area. Just don't
make excuses. Just don't make excuses.
6:30. Yep. That is your life. You ain't
got no money. You ain't got nothing.
That is you. And I'll see you tomorrow
at 6 p.m. 6:30 p.m. You can say all of
this stuff to my face. You ugly skint
[ __ ] with shitty trainers. Shitty old
man with shitty trainers. You can say
this [ __ ] to my face tomorrow. You
jobless skin ugly bastard. Yes. You can
say all of this stuff tomorrow. You
skint ugly [ __ ] with no life and no money. Yes.
Yes. We'll see you tomorrow, ugly man.
Don't run away this time. I don't want
to hear about probation. Don't run away
this time. Do not run away this time.
And then start emailing people how
you're not the one. You skint [ __ ]
with no money with shitty trainers. With
shitty secondhand trainers. And I'm
going to show everybody your trainers
again as well. You're skint trainers.
You little skid bastard. You little
skint [ __ ] Make sure you don't run away tomorrow.
Yeah. because I don't think this time
people are going to not say anything.
You know, I'm coming tomorrow at 6:30.
I'll do 6:45 in case you use any more
excuses. So, yeah. I can't wait.
Tomorrow, I'm going to show everybody
the manta, the real life ugly manta.
I'll put my when I knock you out. Yeah.
When I smash your face in, I'm going to
I'm going to put my face next to your
ugly face and we can decide who the
manta is. Even Listen, I will see you
tomorrow. You're not making excuses. I
don't want to hear no excuses like the
skint virgin in the bedsit. I don't want
to don't make the same excuses as the
skint boy in the bedsit. The skint
virgin with no money like you. I don't
want to hear no excuses. You are skinn.
I've got more money than you will ever
have. £1,000 more than you will ever
have. You've got nothing. You can't even
afford a new pair of trainers. You're
that skint on benefits having to pretend
that you work. Is there any truth that
comes out of your mouth?
You [ __ ] stupid. You are skin. Look
at your trainers. Everything screams
skin about you, you [ __ ] Are you don't
Are you forgetting that everyone's seen
what you look like? Trampy boy. [ __ ]
boy. Are you Are you forgetting that
everybody has seen what you look like?
[ __ ] boy. [ __ ] You little [ __ ]
[ __ ] boy. Are you Are you forgetting
everybody has seen what you look like?
You [ __ ] dirty skin [ __ ] Have you
seen your trampy self?
Have you seen your trampy, poverty
ridden self? I mean, [ __ ] hell. Jesus
Christ. Have you seen your [ __ ] self?
You absolute skin [ __ ] Have you seen
them trainers? You trampy bastard. You
can just tell. Yeah. This little [ __ ]
this little £300 a month [ __ ] He just
gets boyed off in his area like I'm
going to buy him off tomorrow.
You stupid little [ __ ] Yeah, I'm skinn
like I like I've just repeated to you.
Have you seen your trainers? Them
traders can't call anybody skinned,
mate. You are skinned. You're on £300 a
month. Yeah, you show your bank account.
Yeah, you show your bank account, skin
boy. You are the definition of skint. I
have more money than you will ever have,
Skid boy. Look at your traders. Do you
know what? I'm going to wear that Stone
Island jumper tomorrow. No, I'm going to
wear that Stone Island jumper tomorrow
as well. Yeah. When I show you that
you're just the same as nods legs, all
keyboard warriors, all skin keyboard
warriors. I'm going to boy you up in
your area so badly tomorrow, bro. You're
going to have to come out. I'm going to
talk about the most vile [ __ ] I'm and
and I'm going to make you come out.
Let's see if the [ __ ] [ __ ] Let's see
if [ __ ] boy comes out. Terry the [ __ ]
boy. Terry the [ __ ] boy.
Please don't use probation as an excuse.
is this time bring your trampy self out
with your trampy trainers and your
[ __ ] ugly face and I'll and I'll knock
you out. Simple. And I will knock you
out. Simple. That's it. Just make sure.
So yeah, you're the one you have money.
So let's see how Listen, I'll see you
tomorrow and you can bring your
so-called money there. Don't make excuses. Please
don't make no excuses. We've all seen
your [ __ ] emails. Don't make excuses
tomorrow at 6:45. There you go. You've
got an extra You've got an extra 15 minutes.
Yeah. If I'm the one running when I'm in
your area, you'll come out tomorrow. If
I'm the one that's running, run away
from you. Are you actually forgetting what happened?
Yeah. Brandon, what happened? Listen, I
will see you tomorrow, big man. Yeah,
when I'm in your area. I shouldn't even
be doing this again, but [ __ ] it. I'm
going to boil this. I'm going to show
everybody the m because at the end of
the day, right, you're no better than non-slegar.
So, [ __ ] it. If someone's close to me
and I can give them another L, I'm free
tomorrow. [ __ ] it, I'll do it. [ __ ] it,
I'll do it. Simple. No problem.
Don't let Don't let this little [ __ ]
Terry little [ __ ] [ __ ] try [ __ ]
email you ever again after [ __ ]
tomorrow. He ain't about that life. And
listen, I give you permission to bring
anybody. I give you permission to
absolutely bring everybody. Everybody
and anybody that you want. Yeah.
Everybody and anybody that you want, you can bring.
Yeah. So, you can bring your stupid [ __ ]
your family. [ __ ] all your family. I've
already told you [ __ ] your family. So,
you know, you can get them involved
tomorrow if you want. I'm not asked,
mate. I'm generally generally generally
not asked. So, I'm coming tomorrow
anyway. 6:45. So, put your money where
your mouth is, [ __ ] boy. No one's ever
run away from you, mate. You got memory
loss. When I went to your area last
time, you didn't come out cuz you knew
you was going to get [ __ ] up. Yeah.
That's why you had to pretend that
probation. You was on probation. You
stupid little [ __ ] [ __ ] And I'm
going to show everyone your face as
well. Watch. When you're unconscious,
when you're unconscious on the floor,
everyone's going to see your [ __ ] face.
Everyone's going to see that ugly face.
That ugly face that thinks he can come
on [ __ ] YouTube and start talking
about [ __ ] other people. You know,
you're an absolute clown. An absolute
[ __ ] clown. I'm seeing you tomorrow,
bro. Don't watch that. Yeah, I'll run
away. Anyways, I'll see you tomorrow. Yeah.
You're going to get [ __ ] up.
I'm going to [ __ ] you up tomorrow.
Watch. I'm coming to your area tomorrow.
I'm coming to your area tomorrow and
you're not going to do nothing.
You're not going to do nothing. You all
We all know you lost. You're not going
to do nothing, [ __ ] Terrible,
terrible, tererry, terrible trainers. I
will see you tomorrow. I can't wait.
Don't run away this time.
Don't run away this time. Don't be a
non-sl. Don't be a red star. Don't be a coward.
And I'm going to And like I said, bro,
I'm just going to show everybody who the
m is when you when you come out
tomorrow. I'm going to show everybody
who the m is.
I'm going to show everybody who the m is.
You're going to take my phone.
Okay. I'll see you tomorrow. 6:45 p.m.
Yeah. Oh, [ __ ]
6:45 p.m. Yeah. Give you an extra 15
minutes in case you want to you want to
make more excuses. You absolute [ __ ]
You are an absolute [ __ ] mate. You're
on £300 a month. Look at your [ __ ]
trainers. Look at your [ __ ] trainers,
man. You're an absolute [ __ ] [ __ ]
You're an absolute [ __ ] skint [ __ ]
You're talking about other people, bro.
But what the [ __ ] trying to say that?
What? Someone's got 11,200 pound. Bro,
you ain't even got 20 pound to your
[ __ ] name. You [ __ ] skin bastard.
Are you forgetting? We've all seen your
trainers, Terry. Terrible trainers.
[ __ ] hell. You're worse than [ __ ]
Timmy. You [ __ ] [ __ ] You absolute
You're an absolute trant.
You know, you know that you're an
absolute [ __ ] mate. And you're and
you're talking about other people when
you're on £300 a month pretending that
you work. Look at the state of you. You
know, we're going to see even more
tomorrow as well. [ __ ] hell. You're a
[ __ ] An absolute [ __ ] Tramping a [ __ ] half.
You're a [ __ ] mate. You ain't even got
100 quid quid to your [ __ ] name. You
ain't even got 100 pounds to your
[ __ ] name. You [ __ ] [ __ ] You little bastard.
Mate, you don't need to laugh. Just look
in the mirror. You'll laugh at yourself.
Just look in the mirror. You'll laugh at
your [ __ ] [ __ ] fat ugly self. If you
look in the mirror, you'll laugh at your
fat ugly self.
You'll get the you'll get the biggest
laugh. You won't even need to rely on me
to say anything. Just look in the
mirror. Same with you, Terry. Look in
the mirror, bro. Look in the mirror
before you try to call other people skimp. You're delusional.
You're delusional. I I even remember
when you tried to say [ __ ] um three
grand a month is nothing, Terry. Terry,
you're on£300 a month. You're a [ __ ]
You literally are a [ __ ] a trampy
bastard. You live off benefits your
[ __ ] self. I remember when you trying
to say three grand a month was nothing.
You're a [ __ ] [ __ ] You're on £300 a
month. You're living in poverty. Are you
forgetting we've all seen you, lad?
If I could.
Nah, you ain't got no money. Nothing
stacked about any of you people, mate.
You're on £300 a month,
bro. Crying because I'm skin. Listen.
Listen to me. You are skint. You on
three400 a month. You are skint. You
come on here pretending that you work.
Bro, what what's what's your what's your
job? Did you ever tell anybody what your job is?
Yeah. What is your job, actually? Yeah.
What's your job?
You never ever said what your job was, did you?
No, you never said what your job was, did you? Ah.
Uh. Show bank account. You want people
to show you things again?
Uh, no. I don't live with my mom. You
don't know who I live with. Try again.
Uh, you want people to show you things
again. Uh, isn't that funny, Terry?
Terry, you're on benefits. Shut up.
Terry, you're on benefits. Shut up. You
don't work. Look at the state of you.
Stop it. You're embarrassing yourself
now. Trying to tell people that they've
run away when when I went to your area.
You literally did not come out and you
come up with an excuse. That was you.
How did I run from you? No kids, no
money. Yeah, that's you. That's That's
Well, that's not you. Well, you got the
age wrong. It's actually 47. No job, no
misses, no kids, no family. That's you,
but you got the age wrong. Uh, add a add
a add another two on that, Terry. It's actually 47,
Terry. It's 47. You're not 27. You're
You're You're 47, bro. You're not 27.
So, yes, it's 47. No job, no misses, no
kids, no family. Yeah, that's you. How
did you get your [ __ ] age wrong? You
[ __ ] silly bastard.
You listen, bro. You are Look at what
you wear. You asking and then you're
asking people to show your bank account,
bro. Why don't you show your bank
account? Why don't you show your bank
Why don't you show us your money?
Because all we've seen is your shitty
little [ __ ] trainers, bro. I'll see
you tomorrow. Yeah. Don't run away this time.
Don't run away this time. Oh, I'm on
probation. I'm on probation. I'm on
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. I ran away from
you. Right. That's that that's what you
want to go by. If I ran away from you,
you wouldn't have been keep calling me
out, bro. I ran away from you yet you
kept calling me out. Then when I went to
your area, you made up an excuse, bro.
If you made me run away, you wouldn't
have had to call me out a second time. I
came to your area and you come up with
an excuse. You ran away. You didn't even
show up. That's even worse. You know
what's even worse? You didn't even show
up. That's worse than running away. You
told me to come to your gay area. I came
to your area and you didn't even come
out because you was using excuses.
That's even worse than showing up and
and and [ __ ] running away. Yeah, you
asking. Yeah, you asking, Terry. Like I
said, look at your trainers. Look at
your dress sense. Everything is skint
about you. Yeah, you are skin. Just like
nons legs and just like Red Star. Yeah,
you are skinn.
Yeah, you are skin. Look at your
trainers. Look at your dress sense.
You are skin. 47 in skin.
47 in skin. That's you. You are skints.
Terry trampy trainers.
Terry [ __ ] trampy trainers. You are [ __ ] skint.
I came to your area and you didn't even
show up. It's [ __ ] worse than running.
That's [ __ ] worse than [ __ ]
running. That's even worse than running.
Oh, I'm on probation. I'm on probation.
You're all the same. I'll see you
tomorrow at at4 to 7. Yeah. I'll see you
tomorrow at quarter to 7.
I'll see you tomorrow at quarter to 7.
Yeah. And we'll see who's running away.
You are the pit m. Have you seen your
face, you ugly old man? You are the pit
ma. Look at your traders. You are the
pit ma. That's you. Skint boy. Skint
[ __ ] with trappy traders and trappy
clothes. That's you.
Yeah. That's you. You are the pit bunter
at 47. That's yourself you're talking about.
Don't make me laugh. That is you. You
are the bun. The ugly [ __ ] with shitty trainers.
I would rather be you any [ __ ] day
the week, mate. I'd rather be me any day
of the week than [ __ ] you.
You got all this money. Have you seen
your trampy self? Have you actually seen
what you wear? Terry, why don't you come
Why don't you come on camera right now
and show us your [ __ ] ugly face?
Nah, because you're too much of a
bunter. You're too much of a bunter.
You're too much of a mon. We've all seen
you, mate. We've all seen you. Why do
you think people dig at you for your [ __ ] trainers?
Why do you think people dig at you give
you a dig at you for your [ __ ]
trainers? Old man.
Old man. It's so obvious, bro. You're on
benefits. You don't work.
You [ __ ] dirty bastard. You don't
work. You [ __ ] [ __ ] Shut the [ __ ]
up, you ugly [ __ ] Oh, my nose. Oh,
[ __ ] hell. You know what's so funny,
Terry, though? Yeah. Isn't it mad how
I'm better looking than you and I'm
better looking than Nex? Isn't that mad?
Isn't it Isn't it funny? I'm better
looking than both of you little mters.
I'm better looking than you [ __ ] ugly mas.
Yeah. Look at me, bro. Someone that's
better looking than you. Yeah. Okay,
Terry. Again, we've all seen you. We've
all seen what you look like. Terry Trampy Trainers.
Yo, we should call you. We should call
you Triple T. That should be your new
name. Terry Terry Trampy Trainers.
Yeah. Look at my hair, bro. I'm better
looking than you and N legs combined.
What the [ __ ] are you on about, bro?
Yeah, secondhand phone. Anyways, I can't
wait to see you tomorrow anyways. I
can't wait to see you tomorrow anyways, mate.
You know, I can't wait to see you
tomorrow anyways. It'll be a laugh.
It'll be fun. I can't wait to see you
tomorrow anyways, man. It'll be good
fun. It'll be good fun. It'll be good
Yeah, it will be good fun to see you tomorrow. Yeah.
Better looking at a relationship. That's
not going to work, Terry. You're not
going to get me explaining myself again.
Like I said, I'll see you tomorrow.
And I'm going to let LT know to um watch
um this whole thing as well that this
little Terry guy is not about anything.
He's a he's a typical keyboard warrior.
Just like Nons, just like [ __ ] Red
Star. They're all the same spastics old
men on pip. Yeah. So, at the end of the
day, I'm going to let LT know, you know,
that this is the guy, remember, that
says how he's not the one and how he
knows all of these people. And no, no,
no, no, no. I'm just going to let um LT
know that before I go to sleep. I'm
going to text him before I go to sleep.
Yeah. So, everyone can see what you're
really really really really about.
Really, really, really about.
I can't believe I'm having to do this
again. For [ __ ] sake. But I'm going to
do it again cuz I'm going to I'm going
to laugh at you and I want everyone to
laugh at you when you think you're going
to come back on this [ __ ] thing
and LT is going to laugh at you as well
because you've tried that to like you're
some kind of big man multiple times. So
yeah, I'll see you tomorrow anyways.
Yeah, make sure you um make sure you're there
and I'm going to screenshot where you
said you're going to come as well. Yeah.
So, you can't say, "Oh, well, I didn't
say I was going to go and no."
Listen, Terry, I'm going to go and see
you tomorrow. Yeah, you little [ __ ]
You little skin bastard.
Bro, listen. Listen. You're not going to
do that, Terry, because you're scared of
LT. I'm not scared of LT. I'm not scared
of no one. Yeah, you can you can bring
whoever you want tomorrow. You can say
what you want tomorrow, you skin little
bastard. You can say it to my face.
Don't be a nonsg. Don't be a red star.
Don't be a keyboard warrior.
Don't be a keyboard warrior. And dude,
you're not going to meet me tomorrow,
Terry. Do you know exactly why? Because
it will be the last thing you do. You're
not going to ever come back on here if
you meet me tomorrow, bro. I'm going to
literally uppercut you in your [ __ ]
jaw. Right by your eye. Yeah. I'm going
to spit in your face. I'm not even
joking, bro. I swear to God, I'm coming
tomorrow, bro. Everyone can tell me that
I didn't come if I don't come tomorrow.
And then I'm going to show everybody
your ugly face and I'm going to be like,
"Do you know what? Right, since nonslegs
doesn't want to meet anyone and since
Red Star doesn't want to meet anyone,
this is what your average troll looks
like. This is what your average troll
looks like and then I'm going to show
everybody your trainers and everyone's
going to laugh at you. That's what's
going to happen."
So yeah, I'll see you tomorrow. Anyways,
yeah, it is the real one. His name is
TTT. Ter Terry Trump trampy trainers. Yeah.
Yep. Deflecting is not going to work.
Terry, deflecting is not going to work.
I will see you tomorrow. Yeah,
mate. I'm going to show everybody the
real manta. See, Terry, I don't think
you're going to meet me, bro. I
generally don't think you're going to
come out. You'd be very, very stupid if
you come out.
You know, Triple T, you're going to be
very silly if you come out tomorrow
cuz I'm going to show everybody how ugly
you really are. I'm going to put my face
next to your face and put it on YouTube.
That's what I'm going to do. Yeah, 100%. Yep.
He has a job, mate. He ain't got no job.
He's on £300 a month. He's on benefits.
Look at what he wears. Look at what he
Yeah. Anyways, everyone's going to laugh
at me. Well, you can laugh at me
tomorrow when I'm in your area, can't
you? Triple T, how can you laugh at me?
You're an absolute povertyridden [ __ ]
You've got no new trainers. You dress
like a [ __ ] You're a [ __ ] and you're
ugly. How come someone like you laugh at
me? How come somebody like you laugh at
You're some [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah, you
you're a scruffy little [ __ ] skint
bastard, bro. You laugh at yourself,
you know, just like I'm going to be
laughing at you tomorrow when you don't
show up. That's the only one who's going
to be laughing is you when you don't show up.
I'm going to be laughing at you when you
don't show up.
That's who's going to be laughing? How
can some [ __ ] little [ __ ] [ __ ]
like you laugh at someone like me?
[ __ ] hell, bro. Taking a piss out of
£100. £100 almost half of your monthly money, Terry.
That's almost half of your monthly money. Yeah,
that's that's half of your monthly money.
Yay. I will do. I will do.
I will do. I'm going to show everyone
your ugly face. Yeah.
So, um Yeah. I'll see you tomorrow
6:30. Yeah. Good.
Yeah. You little [ __ ]
You the wolf ugly [ __ ] [ __ ] You
know, skin [ __ ] [ __ ]
You non-slar, you're all [ __ ]
skinned, bro. You ain't even got £1,000,
let alone £1,000 a month. You ain't even
got £1,000. Look at you. You're [ __ ]
skin to the [ __ ] eyeballs.
You know what I'm saying? Your skin to
the [ __ ] eyeballs, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah. Laughing. Yeah. So, what was it?
What was the excuse you didn't come out last time?
You told me to come to your area and you
didn't come out. What was the excuse that time?
I think people forgot what the excuse
was. What was the excuse One second.
I'm gone in a minute. So, I'll see you
tomorrow. Yeah. 6:30. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah. Anyways, I'm I'm going to see you tomorrow. Yeah.
Make sure you don't run away this time. [ __ ] bastard. You bastard.
>> To say that you worked. You've never
worked a day in your life. You [ __ ]
You're a [ __ ] wolf. You're a little Awesome.
Anyway, stop deflecting. I'm going to
see you tomorrow,
bro. Stop deflecting and talking and
talking about LT. I'll see you tomorrow.
Yeah, stop deflecting. I'll see you tomorrow.
Stop trying to get Stop trying to change
the subject and try to get another
argument. Yeah, you are the M man. Look
at your face, you ugly [ __ ] foroot
[ __ ] You trampy skint [ __ ]
hipridden bastard. You are the mto man.
And I'm going to show everyone your ugly
face tomorrow. You are the Mto Man, the
alltime Mman on benefits. I'm going to
get your ugly face on camera as well.
I'm going to get your ugly face on
camera and show everybody what you look like. Yep. One sec.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay, bro. That's
fine. You can say all of this stuff tomorrow.
Yeah, that's fine, man. You can say all
of this stuff tomorrow
when you don't show up. Yeah, that's
fine. You can say all of this stuff tomorrow, [ __ ]
You can show all of this stuff tomorrow,
you [ __ ] You can say all of this stuff tomorrow. [ __ ] sake. Anyways,
I'll see you tomorrow. Yeah, you ma