[ __ ] hell. Why are these people
trying to ruin all the [ __ ] fun? It's madness, bro.
We got people showing [ __ ] three
grand, pretending it's 13 and then you
got people trying to ban the live
stream, bro. What the [ __ ]
These people are trying to get it
banned, man. That's [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] thing.
You know what I'm saying?
>> Sorry, lad mate. I'm not showing you
nothing. Nope. I've said a million times
I'm not showing you no money. I haven't
show money for the past 15 months. And
yet I'm not showing you nothing. I
refuse to show you money. You're not
going to bait me. You think I'm going to
show you money again. So you will run
away like you did last time. You're not
going to bait me, lad. I'm showing nothing.
I I refuse to show anything. You can
keep calling me skinny because you're
not skinny. It's not going to It's not
going to work, mate. I am showing you
zil no money. You can Yep. You keep
saying that, mate. Just like when you
got shown six grand and you didn't have
it. Just like it took you years to show
[ __ ] the money you're showing out
because you didn't have it. Keep
self-reflecting. You're not going to
bait me. You ain't got it. That's why
you let me beat you at the money game
for years cuz you're skinned. The
evidence is there. So, mate, again, you
can keep talking all you want. Being
skinned triggered people. I'm not
showing you no money, not even £10. You
could all be completely skin. I'm not
showing you nothing. Listen, bomb.
Listen. You have been shown money. And
stop showing six grand like it's
anything, mate. You ain't got nothing.
Remember when you were showing 600,
bomb, you've been shown more money than
what you're showing. But then I realized
not to waste my time on you little skin
bastards because you always run away.
Every single time you get shown money.
Nope. I do have money. And I'm not
showing you it. I swear to God on my
mom's life, I have I have got money and
I'm not showing it because I know what
you people do. Bro, you people don't
humiliate no one. You people are single.
You're ugly. You got no money. You
people are ugly bully victims. You can't
even get a bird. You're too ugly. You're
too ugly to even go out and get a bird.
You don't own anybody.
You're single ugly people sat on YouTube
with no [ __ ] money every day. And I
proved that every single time when I saw
the six grand and made you run. You
people have been bullied for your ugly
looks. That's why you're sat on YouTube.
You got no bird. You got no nothing. At
least when I [ __ ] go out. At least
when I go out, I can pull birds. You
people are too ugly and skinned to go
out. You got no money. You got no nothing.
Mom, if I was you, I would have already
killed myself, mate. Bat ugly 40y old.
No money. And mate, like I told you
before, show that money again in three
months. You're sat in a bedsit, not
traveled, ugly, no kids. I don't want to
be like you, mate. [ __ ] ugly man in a
bed sit, bro. Listen to this, bro. My
even my TV is better than yours. That's
how bad it is, bro. And I don't even
like [ __ ] TVs, man.
Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. You can keep
calling me what you are, skin. Yeah, you
can keep talking about yourselves. You
are skinned. You people are the skinned
ones. You can keep talking about
yourself. It's so bad that, bro, my TV
is better than yours. That TV in your
bed sit. That's how skint you are.
Anyways, I'm banning these people now. oh [ __ ]
I'm banning these little mongos now. Anyways,
I've got more money than you will ever
have. I've got more money than you will
ever have. Skid boy in a bedsit. Skint
boy in a bedit with a shitty TV with
nothing in your life. showing money
because you won a football bet. Mate,
I've got more money than you'll ever
have. Fatty, you ain't been abroad. Lie
that you got kids. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You
can Yeah. You can keep saying that
before skin. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
You can keep talking about your 40y old
lives. You can keep talking about your
40year-old selves. I'm not even going to
ban them. I'm just going to leave them
to it. I'm literally going to let these
little mongos, these ugly people, keep
talking about their lives and keep
wasting more of their life on me. But
I'm not even going to ban them.
I'm not even going to ban these ugly
skinned people with no life. These ugly
bastards, skin [ __ ] I'm going to leave
them to it, bro. Let them. Let them keep
self-reflecting their 40-year-old ugly
skin life. Leave them. Let them
embarrass themselves. They don't need to
get banned, bro.
They don't need to get banned.
They don't need to get banned. Leave
them, bro. Chill. It's cool. It's fine.
Leave them here. Let them show
themselves up, lad.
You know what I'm saying?
We've all seen what Bob looks like.
We've all seen his little bed sit. Just
let him crack on.
Just let him Just let him crack on, bro.
Chill. It's not a problem. It's all
good, man. It's all good in the hood.
It's all good in the hood, bro. Just leave it.
Trying to look. Look. You know what I'm
saying? The lid.
Yeah. Anyways, I'm just going to let
these people carry on, bro. I'm not even
going to ban them.
Think about it, Stephen. Howard. Yeah.
Let me Let me Let me just ask you this
question. You want me to Let me ask you
this question, bro. You want me to
really answer you this question, bro?
Manto man, and we forget all of these
people. Look at it, bro. That is not £13,000.
And guess what, bro? Even if it is £13,000,
which it isn't. Do you know the funniest
thing about it? What none of these
people will tell you? Do you really want
to know what the funniest thing is about
it? It took 2 years to show 13 grand.
That's how skint they actually are. If
if by the 1% chance that is 13 grand,
bro, it took you 2 years to save up that
money, which is less than 1 grand a
month. That is skint literally. Like
bear in mind, bro, like yeah, that's how
it is, bro. Like it's two years to to to
show get more money than me. You don't
know how much money I have and you don't
know how much money I get. So you keep
saying that. So at the end of the day,
bro, it took you two years to show that
money. That's how skinn you are. Yeah, I
do have 30, bro. I've told you I'm not
showing you no money. Yep. I don't have
it. Yep. I'm skinn like you people. Yep.
Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Yep. Yeah. And Gareth, life owns you.
You ugly bastard. You ugly 40. You old
[ __ ] coming on here like you. You old
man trying to tell me about my life. You
old skinned little bastard. Let's start
talking about you people sat on YouTube.
No money, no life, no future, no job,
all [ __ ] ugly. Let's talk about you
little skid people on YouTube every
[ __ ] day. You know, listen,
let's start talking about you little
[ __ ] skin bums. Ain't got a life too
ugly to go out and get a woman. Let's
talk about you ugly people on YouTube.
But listen, Joe, bro, even if it is 13,
which it isn't, think about it, bro.
That took two years to save that money.
That's the definition of skin, bro. Do
you know I can save roughly, bro?
Maybe 3 months, four months. Yeah. He
lives richer than me. You don't know how
much money I have. Again, you don't know
how you don't know anyone's lives. You
You don't know anyone's life. You don't
know what people have.
He got you in a cell, bro. And guess
what? I've got him stalking my women
that he will never get. I've got him
obsessed with my women that he will
never get because he can only get
disabled girls. I've got teeth in my
mouth. I've got better clothes than him.
I've had women that he will never be
able to get due to his ugly looks. So,
Peter Bell is doing the owning, mate.
Why doesn't it make any sense, Joe?
Why doesn't it make Bro, listen. You
don't know what I have. You don't know
how much money I have.
Saving 13K in 2 years is the definition
of skint. Yes, that is very skint. For
somebody that doesn't even go out and
anybody that doesn't drink, yes, that is
skint. Because at the end of the day,
I'll do a video on this later if you
want me to.
Yeah, I need to call my mom for money.
You don't know how much money I have.
What the [ __ ] is prop money? What the
[ __ ] prop? What the [ __ ] does that even
mean? What is prop money b money? I
don't even know what the [ __ ] that means.
Um, okay. Okay. Okay. Let me ask you a
question. Okay. Now, I'm going to ask
you this question again and don't answer
it with a question. Okay. So, when I
showed you £6,000,
right? Why did you all run away? Don't
make excuses. Don't say you never had
it. Don't say that you couldn't get the
12 grand, lad. Why did you all run away?
I am skin. I've got nothing. I'm
literally I've got one pound to my name.
I'm going to starve. Okay. We've been
through this. Okay. I am skin. I'm this.
I've never had a woman. Yes. Okay. Fair
enough. Okay. You have all been shown
£6,000. Listen to me. Listen to me. And
what did all of you do? What did you do
when you got shown 3 to6,000?
Tell me what you all did. Don't don't
start changing the subject and start
doing this and start doing that. What
did you do? Don't say you didn't get the
you can't get the 12 grand from the bank
cuz you can. What did you people do
without typing over each other?
What did you do in them 18 months? Tell
me what you did. Just answer the
question. What did you do?
I'm waiting, bro. I can wait here all night.
What did you people do? Answer the
question. You ran away because you never
had it. Which is why I don't waste my
time on you anymore. You know what I'm
saying? I don't waste my time on you
anymore because that was the evidence I
needed that you people don't have
anything. I showed you money then I put
the money in the bank cuz you won't show me nothing.
You know what I mean? Yeah, I'm skinn.
Okay. You keep telling yourself that I'm
skinned. You don't know how much I have.
You don't know how much money I have.
You don't know what I have. You
literally don't know what I have.
But again, that was the evidence I
needed to know that you have nothing.
Which is why I do not waste my time on
you people. No matter how many times it
is explained to you, I know I didn't
spunk six grand and I also got backdated
money as well. No matter how many times
somebody explains this to you, you don't
get it. So there's no point because
you're just going to keep talking [ __ ]
every single time. You've been shown
money and you all ran away cuz you ain't
got no money. That's why I don't show
you money anymore. You can come back 2
years later with money that you've won,
which is less than what I've shown. No
one's asked, bro. No one's asked. We
have seen We have seen the real you. We
have seen the real you. When you are
showing money, I don't forget the past.
So, bro, just say what you want. It's
fine. It's cool. No one's get banned.
It's cool. You know what I'm saying?
Yeah. You will run away. That's why I
don't show you any money. But again,
you're not going to you're not going to
remember that because you're biased. So,
yeah, you asking. Yeah, you people
asking. Yeah, you people asking. Uh-huh.
Yeah, you people asking radio. Right on.
You people asking, you know yourselves,
skinned people with no life and no
money. Yeah. So, Joe, you can't really
answer the question.
You can't really answer the question.
I've still got a picture of it if you
want to see it. And also Joe, the money
got banked and I also got backdated
money. And I still had loads and loads of money.
No, I've got more money than that. I'
I've got more money than that virgin
boy. Listen, listen, listen, bomb. I've
got more money than you. I've got more
money than you, but I'm not showing you
money. I'm not showing you nothing,
mate. You can keep thinking that you got
money that ain't even going to last 3
months. You know that shitty money
you're showing, mate, wouldn't even last
me a month. No, we're not forgetting
about the past. We're No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. We're not forgetting
about the past. We're living in the
past. We are living in the past. And
bro, that [ __ ] money that you've shown
wouldn't even last a month. That [ __ ]
money that you're showing. So, I don't
know why you're you cuz you won a
football bet in two years, mate. That's
[ __ ] all. That wouldn't even Do you know
how much I used to spend when I used to
go out, mate? That money is nothing.
Literally nothing. Do you know what?
Come back when you've actually got a
million. You know what, bro? Come back
when you've actually got stacks. Yeah.
No, no, no, no, no. We're not forgetting
the past. You don't forget the past. So,
I'm not forgetting the past. You people
have been shown six grand and you've run
away. Listen, listen, Gareth. You're a
40-year-old virgin. You're an ugly [ __ ]
that's never been with a woman. You
can't get a woman because you're too
ugly, not even for a one night stand.
You're an ugly bastard. You don't live
in reality. You are the ugly people sat
on YouTube with no money every day. You
know what I'm saying? You people are so
ugly. No life, no money. That's your
reality. Ugly. No woman, no life. I've
done more than you. Listen, bro. You're
not understanding, bomb. That money
you're showing is nothing. That money
you're showing is nothing. You're going
on like you're a millionaire, bro.
You're sat in a bedsit showing a couple
of thousand pound on your lonesome. That
is nothing. Actually show some actual
money. Come out when you got a million,
bro. Yeah. How about you actually come
back when you got a million? Not your
shitty couple of,000 pound that ain't
going to last 3 months. Come on, bro.
It's ridiculous now.
That's up to you if you want to show
proof or not. I will never show these
people money ever again.
Keep under your bed. Yeah. Is that Is
that why? Is that why 3 4 months after
that, bomb, you could only show £600?
Bro, you're on benefits. Bomb. You're on
benefits. You are on benefits. You are
disabled. Gareth. Look at you people
online every day in your 40s. No woman,
no money, no life, disabled. You people
are disabled. Your job is calling people
what you are every day. Your job is
calling people what you are every day.
Ugly, middle-aged, skint, no money. And
we've proven it millions of times,
right? We've proven it a million times.
That's how disabled you are. You're sat
middle-aged by yourself, no money. You
need to look at your reality. sat on
YouTube calling people you don't know
when you're middle-aged bums wrinkly old
men wrinkly old men with no money. That
should be the same thing. And you're
trying to talk about other people. Look
at your reality. You've got nothing. You
ain't even got hope. This is the main
thing with you people. Yeah. You don't
even have hope. Yeah. I get £80 a week.
Yeah, bro. I get £350 a month. Yeah.
Okay, bro. Yeah. Yeah. Listen, you need
to look at your own disabled realities
on YouTube in your [ __ ] 40s. You
ain't got no money. You got no bird.
I've had more women than you will ever
have because you're too ugly. Faulty.
Scoop. This is what I'm saying. Scoop.
Listen. Listen. Listen. Okay. I've not
seen you for a long time here. Yeah.
Listen. Yeah. I'm going to explain to
you why I do not get I do not show money
to these people. Now, I don't know how
many times you've been watching this. I
don't know how many times you've not
been watching this. These people have
been shown money multiple times. Yeah, I
have shown them thousands and thousands
and hundreds and thousands and every
single time they've run off. I don't
waste my time on them anymore, bro. This
is what I'm saying. You know what I'm
saying? I don't waste my time on these
little self-reflecting middle-aged
people, these skint bums that ain't got
nothing but typing to people that they
don't know. I don't care, bro. It's just
the same old [ __ ] It's the same old
argument. It's the same old argument
with these people, bro. I've seen you on
L JS and that.
Yeah, it's been the same old [ __ ]
Yeah, listen. Anyways, we're going to
time out these [ __ ] idiots for a
while. And that's what I'm saying, bro.
Show show some actual money. Yeah, it's
just the same old [ __ ] scoop, honestly,
bro. Yeah, I went on L J's yesterday. I
swear I come out of there disabled, bro.
I swear to God, this community makes you
disabled. It makes you lose brain cells.
I swear to God, bro. You know when you
said that? You know when you said
before, you know when you said before,
you know when you said before how you
don't come on here no more. I swear to
God, bro, I lost brain cells. I'm I'm
not even joking. It It does, bro. When
you're arguing with a bunch of stupid
biased people and you know the thing is,
bro, and LT will tell you the same [ __ ]
These people are biased. They are
Whatever you do, they don't give you
credit for. You understand? Look, I'll
give you an example, bro. Bomb's coming
on here trying to give it the big man.
No one's mentioning when I went to
Manchester two times. Do you understand,
bro? Do you know? Do Do you understand
what I'm saying, bro? There's no point
with these disabled people. I can see
why you don't come on here no more.
Think about it, bro. It's not even just
about that. I'm better looking than
them. I've got more money than them. Do
you know what? It's not even about
money, right? Okay, let's It's not even
about [ __ ] money, lads. Yeah, I'm
young. scoop. I'm better looking than
these people. It's I I have money. Yeah.
What What is What are these people
trying to prove, bro? I don't
understand. They've got no life
experience. It's the same thing with
that nonslegs. How many years has he
been doing this?
You know what I'm saying? Saying, bro,
no one. And listen, bro, even if it is
13 grand, which it ain't 13 grand, bro.
It took you two years to show it.
You know what I'm saying? No, but
Ghosted, I'm saying to you, this is why
these people do this.
You know what I'm saying? Yeah, you are
skint and disabled. Yeah, you are skinn
and disabled. Stop talking about
yourself, you 40-year-old middle-aged
[ __ ] I've noticed every single time,
bro. Listen, you people are skint on
YouTube. You've never had a woman in
your life. You've never been laid.
You're on benefits. Look at your own
ugly lives. You're in your 40s alone
every day, middle-aged. You ain't got no
misses cuz you're too ugly. And you
think you're going to come on here and
talk about a 27 year old that's got more
than you. I'm going out on Saturday and
I'm going to get a [ __ ] You ugly
people are going to be sat on YouTube
disabled talking about people that you don't know.
You're going to be sat on [ __ ]
YouTube all alone with no money. [ __ ]
disabled like the keyboard warriors you
are. This is why Scoop don't watch you.
It's boring, bros. It is boring.
Do you know another thing, Scoop? Yeah.
You come on here for two days, lad. Yeah,
bro. Listen, it doesn't matter whose it
is. It's not 30. And yes, I have had a
girlfriend. Scoot. Listen, bro. I've
shown more money than these people,
right? I have shown more women than
these people. I have shown that I'm
better looking at these people. The
thing is with these people, right? Let
me tell you something, bro. I think
you're like 39. You got to understand
what it is with these people. Yeah. If
you are better looking than these people
and you are not old like these people,
these people will not like you. Do you
not understand? This is why most of
these people get along with each other
because they're all the same. Fat, old,
ugly, no money, no life. You understand
what I'm saying to you, bro? Anyone
that's younger than them, better looking
than them, they go for this is their
life every day. As long as you stay on
here, bro, the more they're going to
keep doing this. It is jealousy. Do you
understand, bro? You know what I'm
saying? They don't do it for a reaction.
They do it because they're jealous.
Think of all of the people, bro, that
that Think of all of the
over the years, like come come on here.
Over the years, bro. Yeah. And how many
people they do it to, lad? They They
target me. Scoop. Listen, ask yourself
this question. Yeah. You can tell me I'm
right. You can tell me I'm wrong. Yeah.
The thing is with these people Yeah.
Um, if you ask them, because a lot of
them are narcissist, why would they go
for me? What do you think they're going
to say, bro? They're going to say,
"Because you've said this, because
you've said that." But the problem with
that is is they like this reaction. When
you react to these people, they love it.
They would love you to talk about kids.
They would love They love it, bro. Deep
down, they love it, bro. They want They
want people to have mental breakdowns.
They want people to have mental
breakdowns. And mate, you can keep
saying, "I'm on benefits living with my
mom." You're middle-aged on benefits and
you ain't even got any money. Look at
your own life. You must be jealous of
something. For people to do this every
day scoop, it has got to be jealousy.
And they say jealous of what? But
they're the ones that will waste their
life on you. They're the ones that have
got all of this money, all of this. Not
jealous, but yet they'll waste every
second of every day on you, bro. I've
only started reacting to these people,
right? I've only reacted to these people
recently cuz I I feel like I I shouldn't
even scoop to their level. They're b
It's like nonslegs. He's ugly. He's got
an ugly disabled girlfriend. He's got no
money. No matter what his dad know this
is why he does this every day because
jealousy is a drug. They will never
leave you alone. They will literally
never ever ever ever leave you alone
ever. Trust me. They will never because
it is jealousy. People that have got
money people they wouldn't do this every
day. Don't let them [ __ ] try and tell
you that this that and the other because
bro it's not this that and the [ __ ] other.
Funny enough I thought heyke I thought
you was going to ask me about the USA is
he thing bro. Don't argue with these
bunch of jealous ugly people. I had to
react today because these will show
money. Yeah, you people don't bully
anyone. You people bully yourselves.
You're in your 40s and you're hopeless.
You people have always been bullied.
Ugly. Can't leave your house. You people
are bully victims. You people get
bullied every day. I come back for more
because you obviously don't bully
people. You people don't bully people.
That's why we come back for more because
you literally embarrass yourselves.
bies, no life on benefits, talking about
other people that have actually got hope.
That is madness. But yeah, it is
jealousy. 100% jealousy. Bro, do you not
remember how many times this ugly
toothless little virgin tried literally
um Yeah, no woman will want me. You're
talking about yourselves again. You're
talking about yourselves again, lad.
You're talking about yourselves again,
lad. Yeah, stop talking about yourself,
you little 40year-old. 40year-old loser.
Call you old loser on YouTube. No hope, no life.
[ __ ] madness, bro.
So what I'm saying? Yeah. So what?
At least you know the channel, bro.
£340. You If only you knew, mate. If
only you knew. You don't know what
people get. You don't know what people have.
Talking about yourselves again. Keep
talking about your 40-year-old selves.
Lonely people on YouTube with no money.
And if they had money, they wouldn't be
doing this every day on YouTube. You
know what? I might add this in a
response video. To be honest, these
people have got all this money, but
they're on YouTube angry every day.
Something's not adding up, which is why
I need to be a [ __ ] uh you know what I mean?
This is another thing, bro.
This is another thing.
And it's not even just about money, bro.
It's not even just about money. You know
what I'm saying? [ __ ] weirdos.
I think Scoop's gone now anyway. So, yeah.
But yeah, you can keep saying that
people are skint and whatever. You're
not I'm never showing you money ever
again. I'm literally showing you [ __ ]
all. Yeah, I'm at rock. Bro, you're
already at rock bot rock bottom. You're
in your 40s,
bro. I'm not showing you. Don't you
worry about what I get. Worry about your
own lives. Why are you so asked about
other people's lives? This is what I
don't understand with you little bongos.
It's you're so you're so insecure about
your own income. This is why you do all
of this [ __ ] And Maddy, I'll never be
rock bottom like you people. You people
in your 40s, you're hopeless. You got
nothing. You ain't even got hope. No
money, no life on YouTube every day in
your 40s. Your life is [ __ ] in your
40s. You got nothing. Nothing. I wish I
could actually shout that. You got
nothing but YouTube and being
middle-aged and your and your life is o
[ __ ] over, mate. Your life is [ __ ]
over in your 40s. You can't even you
can't even talk properly, bro. Let let
me put the link up and you can come in.
You ugly bastard. You 40-year-old
virgin. I'm calling you what I want.
Yeah, bro. Listen, Gareth, you're an
ugly 40-year-old disabled bastard.
You've never worked. You're on £300 a
month. That's what you people do on here
every day. You gamble your little
benefits cuz you got [ __ ] all. You're
losers. You're absolute [ __ ] losers
in your 40s. You're all ugly. and you
see somebody half your age better
looking than you and you want to get me
down to your ugly skin level. You trying
to bring me down to your disabled, ugly
40y old level. [ __ ] off, you [ __ ]
virgin. I'm going to put the link up
now. Show us how you talk, big man. Come
on. Get off your little fake disabled
account and show us how you [ __ ] Come
on. One second. Let me put this link up.
Let me put the link up. Come on. Come
on. Come on.
Exactly, bro. He ain't going to do
nothing. That's what I'm saying. It is
the same argument.
It's the same argument. It's the same
[ __ ] These people are bored. They're
sat at home. They're skint. That's why
they [ __ ] do this every day, bro.
They're bored cuz they've got no money.
They got no life. They got no life.
They've got no [ __ ] money. They got
[ __ ] all. That's why they're on here every day
being idiots. What the [ __ ] else do you
call them, bro?
Obsessed every single day. You're not
coming in LJ, you skin bastard. [ __ ]
off. Go self-reflect on another channel. Go self-reflect.
Yeah, I made that mistake [ __ ] yesterday, bro.
Um, I made that [ __ ] mistake yesterday,
you know. Yeah, I got no money. Yep.
Yep. £700 a month. Yep. You keep talking
about yourself. You know what? Every
time these people are doing this, Yeah.
they're talking about themselves. No.
No. No. No. No. No. Ghosting because
it's just the same projection. It's the
same projection with them. There's
There's no point, lad.
Oh, yeah. I don't do the house thing
anymore. Scoop. So, I basically lost the
[ __ ] house and it's [ __ ] expensive
now. So, finding other ways to make
money. So, I thought I'd let you know
that. But um yeah,
Ant-Man moved to Thailand scoop. Ant-Man
moved to Thailand.
Now you can't have a decent
conversation. It's all projection
ghosting. It's all It's an argument that
doesn't lead anywhere, lad. It's
literally an argument that don't lead no
more. It's anywhere. It's the same [ __ ] every day.
Do you remember that USA is scoop?
Uh, I don't think I've spoke to you
since I've met anyone new, did I? Um,
nah, it's been a while, bro. It's been a
[ __ ] while, lads.
It's been a while, man. Um, yeah.
Yeah, LJ owns me. Yeah. Yeah. You keep
telling yourself that.
You know what? You people need to
seriously grow up.
No, no, no. But the thing is though, the
thing is when I'm on Lar's, they talk
over you and they play the same videos.
So, do you know do you know do you
remember when there was they was playing
the same videos ghosting?
Do you know when they were saying the
same videos, lad?
Yeah, it's going to seem that way, bro.
Cuz it's too expensive living here.
Scoop, I don't have the house anymore in
it. So, um, they don't make money on the
house anymore. They took the [ __ ]
house in the end scoop. But anyways, um,
the thing is, Ghost, whenever I join,
they just put the same thing up over and
over and over and over and over again.
So, they're living in the past. But then
as soon as you say, "Oh, you've shown
six grand. Oh, you're living in the
past. Oh, you're living in the past. Oh,
you're living in the past." They're
biased. They're literally biased. Like,
you might as well just do your own thing
on here, lad, and just ignore them. Oh,
you're living in the past. Stop living
in the past. These people literally live
All they go on about is the past. Every
day we hear the same thing about Prime,
about [ __ ] L.
Yeah, it all comes to an all good. I
should have prepared myself a bit more
though, Scoop. But
yeah, I mean this is this is what I was
thinking, Scoop, bro. Yeah, bear with
me. Yeah. So,
um, you know, like I'm 28 next month.
So, I was going out like from 21 to
about like 27 and about 6 months ago.
I've only like lost it like 2 months. I
stopped the going out, bro. Like, it
wasn't even financially. I just stopped
really going out. I go out drinking like
every two weeks now. I just feel so old
and [ __ ] I just can't be bothered
anymore, bro. I've done it so many
times. So, I mean, like I said, it's
kind of good that I lost it. Well, it's
not good. It's not good I I lost it, but
I mean, it's better that I lost it now
that I don't get tempted to really go
out as much anymore. Um,
you know what I'm saying, bro? Cuz yeah,
I had four years of it, bro. Going out,
[ __ ] gambling, [ __ ] escorts. It's
uh it's one of them, bro. Is it? Like,
it is good, you know? But
I don't know how I would have been able
to afford it in um I don't know how I
would have been able to afford that [ __ ]
without the house, bro. I don't think I
would have. But I'm sure I would have
worked or something something. I would
have I would have had to done something.
So that's the thing, Scoop. It's uh
it's what it is, bro. I was doing the
Uber delivery thing for a little bit.
Yeah. Yeah, I can't go out now. I'm
going out on Saturday, you [ __ ]
idiot. I can't go out now, mate. I'm
going out on Saturday.
Oh man, it's horrible, is it, bro? It's
horrible. And and and and and I bet you
never stung you straight away as well.
It might take like a couple of months um
to sting you as well. It might take like
a couple I'm out on Saturday getting
women, bro. What the [ __ ] are you on
about you little self-reflectors?
I'm going out on Saturday. Um, but while
I was saying scoop yet, um, the thing
is, bro, how long did you have it for?
And it probably and and the thing is
when you get stung by it, it doesn't you
don't get stung straight away like with
me. Yeah. Because I was going out and
stuff, I was like, "Oh [ __ ] Okay, if I
do this a couple more times, I'm kind of
in trouble now." But then I won some football bets.
Um, but obviously I'd done some football
bets and [ __ ] so I kind of got lucky
with the football bets.
I I wouldn't have been skinned. Scoop. I
weren't going to be skinned, but I like
to have a certain amount of money in my
account. I weren't going to be skinned.
Like, nowhere near skin. Trust me, I
weren't going to be skinned, bro. Like,
not at all. But like, I'm sure you're
you're the same. Like, but I would have been uh
I would have been in some problems, bro.
I'm talking to a woman in Finland. I met
her in London. She lives in Finland. She
seems all right. She seems all right.
Um, but yeah, that's crazy. 10 15 grand
a month. [ __ ]
That's crazy, bro. [ __ ] Damn.
Yeah, man. [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. Cheers.
It's bad, is it, lad?
Yeah, that USA is I was speaking to a
friend the other day, Scoop.
I kind of got over that in the end, but
every time like you you come in now,
it's just going to make me like it just
makes me think of you like it makes me
think of you. The whole USA easy thing.
Like it's been a long time, bro. Long
time. But uh yeah, man.
But to be fair, Scoop, I have done all
right. Like cuz I don't know about a
house now and obviously I don't work.
I've still done pretty good.
Like you know what I'm saying? Like you
if you got [ __ ] three grand you're good.
You know what I'm saying? Yeah. It was
bad bro. It was bad bro. I still think
of it when I go cinema. You know you
know when I go cinema I still think of
it. I don't know why but every time I go
cinema Yeah. Cuz I love horror films in
it. And like, bro, I swear to God, every
time I go to cinema cuz it [ __ ] mad.
You know what I'm saying? It was crazy, lad.
Yeah, it was crazy, bro. It weren't even
funny. It was [ __ ]
It was [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, it weren't even funny, bro. It was mad. Um, nah, bro. Nah,
no I haven't.
No, bro. Not for I messaged her friend
two weeks ago just because her friend
come up. Like I don't stalk her or look
for but it just sort of come up. So I
was like, "Oh, let me just" and I was on
the phone to her friend for like 5 hours and
yeah, she's told me like obviously the
thing is bro like you you and LT is
always going to have your like opinion,
right? But I I still don't think I was
in the wrong, bro. Yeah. Okay. I might
have went OTT, but I still don't think
that I done wrong
because Yeah. But not She was We was on
the phone for like 5 hours, bro. But I
don't look the [ __ ] up, though.
Honestly, I don't. But um I still think that like
they they still were in the wrong kind
of thing. They still were. It was the
ghosting and the entitlement, bro. You
know what I'm saying? And the narcissism.
Did you know I went on a date? Yeah.
Like four months ago. And even though
they wasted my time. Yeah. They
explained it at the end of it.
Oh, I tell you a date. I went on scoop. Yeah. [ __ ]
I tell you what happened, bro. I've been
on like I think I've been on three
dates. Nah, she's got a man now. I went
I went on this date, bro, back in I
think it was March. I think it was March
or April, bro. And I had this uh foot
thing called uh paranal tentoninitis.
And bro, I couldn't even barely walk. I
was limping for like 6 weeks. I couldn't
walk. I think I banged my foot. And I
was in this um bar thing. I'm not going
to say the name. Had this [ __ ] woman
meet me. Say, "Oh, yeah. You're
good-looking." She approached me. I
said, "Oh, let me get your number." Went
on a date with her. Literally was as
normal as I could be. 20 20 minutes
they're like, "Oh, yeah. I don't feel
the vibe." 30 minutes. So like, what am
I supposed to do, bro? You know what I'm
saying? I give up. And then the other
one was we was holding hands and [ __ ]
Um, but when I tried to kiss them, they
just like kind of used that as
as an excuse. But the the the thing is,
no, no, I wasn't speaking to her. I was
speaking to her friend. No, she will
never talk to me again. She will never
ever ever talk to me again, bro.
Oh, did you know about that 19year-old I
was getting with Scoop?
Um, we was meeting and stuff. She used
to come around and like give me [ __ ] Um,
and uh, she was giving me [ __ ] and
[ __ ] and then I kind of stopped talking
to her because I couldn't deal with her
anymore. You might have not se Well, I'm
sure you have seen her, but apart from
all that, bro, nothing's really really changed. Um,
and yeah, uh, it just seems to have
gotten harder now, bro. Cuz I know
people that I have actually [ __ ] up
with. I actually know people I've [ __ ]
up with, and I know people that have
just wasted my time as well. So, I know
where I've been wrong, and I know where
I've been right, if that makes sense.
Oh, she was just being entitled, bro.
Like just [ __ ] the attitude. Like as she
got older, she just started being a
[ __ ] Um, and I just respected myself
too much to like it was only like she'd
come around the old house, she'd see the
tenants, I'd get a [ __ ] we'd get a
Chinese, and that's it. Yeah. I was into
[ __ ] for a very long time. Like not
even sex, just [ __ ] But yeah,
nothing wrong with her. It was just like
I couldn't deal with the attitude, bro.
I'm saying I just couldn't deal with it.
But um but yeah, there was an Italian
one and it's like we was holding hands
and [ __ ] We was with together like two,
but then when I tried to kiss, she said
she doesn't kiss. So, it's kind of like Yeah. But
and obviously I had loads of money back
then as well. Like loads of money I
could just spend like so I just I don't
anymore like I used to. Obviously I've
still got money, bro. I'm not going to
starve. I can't It's not like I can't go
out. But um
but yeah, obviously I know what you mean
with the USA thing, but I still think
she was a [ __ ] I still think she was a
nasty little [ __ ]
cuz I don't think I've met someone else
like that before. She was an actual
[ __ ] bro. And believe you me, I'm only
talking about it now cuz you're here. If
you weren't here, bro, I don't care
about it. Like, I literally don't care. But um
I'm trying to think of this. Oh, I went
to Birmingham last month to see Monty
cuz he was crying over Natalie G. I'm
sure you might have seen it. Then he
snaked me and No, no, no, no, no.
[ __ ] not. First time I left London in
a while, bro. Yeah. So, yeah.
So, I'll be out on Saturday, lad. I go
out every two weeks now.
No, it's not that she used me, bro. It's
the fact that all you had to do was say
that you've gone back home. No, no, no,
no, no, no. If you ever come around,
I'll show you around as a friend and you
probably would have never spoke to them
anymore and that would have been the end
of that because most women I've met have
done that. I don't think someone is just
blocked. No, they never have, I don't think.
So, I mean, it's not about being used,
it's about like how you went about it
wasn't very nice. But like my friend,
well, my friend, her friend said that
she's basically been abused. Um,
she's basically been abused and stuff.
So, I said, "Oh, okay." So, she was
telling me things I didn't know, but
just that in itself
is just it wasn't good, bro. You know
what I mean?
Um, so yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I went to Monty. I went to
Birmingham last month, bro.
Where you I know you don't come on here
anymore cuz of the same [ __ ] but um Yeah.
But yeah, she's not a nice person, bro.
I can't believe I messaged her family and [ __ ]
Like, I get your point, bro. Like, I get
it. I understand, bro. But the thing is,
yeah, is the thing is is that like when
when you deal with a narcissist, it's
hard to explain to someone what they
what they do
unless you've dealt with a narcissist
before. So, you won't really understand
it until you've dealt with it yourself.
You you know what I'm saying? Because
you moved there now. Yeah.
Nice, man. Yeah. I done £120 on three on
two teams, bro. On Tuesday, it was my
mom's birthday. I [ __ ] um won um 380,
bro. I wish I had more money on it. It's
the thing with them football bets.
always wish you had more money on it
every time with a football in it.
You always wish you had [ __ ] more in
it. But that's just the way it goes on
them football bets, bro.
I played roulette uh two days ago. First
time in three months.
First time in three months, bro. Yeah,
I just do the football now kind of thing.
But you always wish you had more.
You always wish you had more of it in it. >> Yeah.
Yeah, I've won. So I won I won first
game of the season, second game in the
season. So I've won three out of six bets.
But scoop. Yeah, I remember when I was
19, bro. I swear to God, I put one pound
on six teams. Bear in mind, I don't know
anything about football. And I thought
it was like never ever going to come in.
I thought it was never going to come in.
£1.75 return. I wish I had more on it. I
wish I had more on it, bro. Even if I
had 20 on that. Yeah, that's 1450. And
obviously when you're 19,
you know, it's a lot of money, is it?
Obviously 1450 when you're 19, bro.
[ __ ] It's all a lot of money. It's a
lot of money now, but you get what I
mean, bro. Like, um
I was thinking of putting like500 on two
teams, but it's a lot of money to lose,
bro. But if it doesn't come in, is it?
It's a lot of money to um lose
if it doesn't come in.
But yeah, that you you win a lot on
them, bro. You win a lot on them. I do a
double both teams to score.
You know, cuz you know the National
League, you know the National Lag,
there's loads of goals.
Yeah, there's loads of goals.
Loads of goals, bro. [ __ ] There was
eight teams in a row. Both score. They
both scored, bro. You know, like the on
the on the table. Yeah. [ __ ] eight
[ __ ] teams in a [ __ ] row. Could
you imagine you had money on that? Yeah.
>> Yeah. Cuz you could you imagine you had
[ __ ] money on that, bro. >> [ __ ]
[ __ ] imagine you had £500 on eight
teams. both teams to score.
>> Living the dream, lad. [ __ ] living
the dream, bro.
But the thing is, uh, yeah, I don't know
what happened, Scoop. I don't really
feel like going out drinking much anymore.
I feel like I've outgrown it, lad.
I'm 28 next month, and I feel like,
yeah, I just don't have the energy for it anymore.
And it's not financially. It's not
because of the financial thing. Cuz like
I said, even when I had the house, the
last few months having the house, I
didn't really I was like, "Oh, kind of."
I would have a shower and just chill. And um
you know, I lived in that house for 8 months.
Yeah. When I left my mom's, I I lived in
that house for 8 months. I was living in
a room with a guy. I was sleeping on the mattress.
And the thing is, Scoop, you know, I
lost a lot from that house, bro. I lost
obviously the money which I feel like
the money you can get the money back you
know you can do you can do something
that you get £200 a week and then you're
basically if you get £200 a week from
something you're basically getting the
same amount of money but you know you
lose the house cuz I I moved back there
for 8 months so you lose the house you
lose the money from the house you lose
the tenants you [ __ ] their life up and
then you obviously lost the food from
they used to cook me food and stuff and
obviously I've lost the
So I mean you lo you lost you lost a lot
of [ __ ] bro you know from that house.
Um and obviously I was getting used to
the area all the Chinese the escorts
like everything was sorted there sort of
thing. It was just um I don't know man.
I I seem to feel like um I I I felt like
my mental health was a lot better in that house.
Does that make sense? Like I felt like
my mental health was a lot better in
that house. I was always if ever you
felt like a bit pissed off, you know,
you just have a laugh with one of the
tenants and I actually became friends
with them. So they kind of put everyone
in the [ __ ] Really? Same room as
another guy. Did you ever get the No, I
never got the window fixed. I just told
them that like Yeah, some drunk guy come
and smash the window. Yeah, I was
sleeping in the room because I was
getting more money.
No, it was different. No, we changed tenants.
and one of the tenants stole my [ __ ]
um after shave and basically a lot of
them show their true colors but like two
of them are okay like I still talk to
like two of them but the rest of them weren't really
you know they were obviously I get
you're pissed off you got to move but
look at me I'm also [ __ ] now as well
you know but that guy with a bike no
they're different there was they're
different tenants bro I've had about
three four new three four They've been
set to [ __ ] tenants, lad.
Know what I mean? So,
um, but some of them weren't nice in the
end, bro. But
obviously, I still talk to two of them
and stuff, you know what I mean? Um,
but yeah, it wasn't good, lad. It wasn't
good. So, I slept in a guy's room
because on the mattress on the floor
because I wanted to get more money for
the other room.
No, there was this woman, bro, and she
only liked black guys.
And basically, one of the tenants told
her about the house, which I worked cuz
she she went abroad. Yeah. And I don't
think she was going to come back for
like another 6 months. So, what I was
going to do is obviously take all of her
stuff, keep getting the money from her,
and then when she comes back, I'll be
like, "Oh [ __ ] Yeah, I didn't know what
happened." give her the money back and
give her her stuff. So, I was I was
trying to rinse it for as much as I
because obviously 350 a month is still
350 a month. Um, but she only like like
we went out I went out drinking with
her. She was a good friend and that but
she turned weird as well which was a bit
odd like all after all that house thing
happened they all well not all of them
like some of them just started being all
weird and that brom.
But yeah, she turned a bit like weird
like she turned a bit dodgy and that
you're not going to get Bro, do you know
why I asked her? Do you know why I asked
her, bro? You're not going to believe
why I asked her. Yeah, cuz we used to go
out clubbing and that.
And I I actually thought she was going
to say yeah. I swear to God I asked
this, bro. I was myself. I said to her,
so you know how like you give
um I must have had like money at the
time. I said I said, "You know how like
you give rent every month, right?" I
said, "Oh, do you want to I said, "Do
you want to instead of um
instead of giving a rent, do you want to
like just give me like a blowjob?" I
swear to God, bro, it was the most
awkward voice note I had to [ __ ]
send. I said instead of like the 350
now, I thought I thought you know there
there was two things I was thinking. I
thought, okay, they're going to say
yeah, cuz obviously they're struggling.
They're struggling for money, right? And
obviously they don't want to piss the
landlord off that they kind of know. She
said no. And I told all the other
tenants, they said, "What?" I said,
"Yeah." I was like, "Fucking that's
almost £400 a month, right?"
£400 a [ __ ] month. Yeah. Which is a
[ __ ] lot, bro, to pay if you're just
going to give someone a [ __ ] [ __ ]
And Yeah. She weren't having she weren't
having it at all. Nah, not at all. At
all. Which I don't know. I don't even
like her. The thing is she was never my
type. But I just asked her cuz I
thought, "Fuck it. Why not? I don't need
the extra £400."
Like kind of like I think I weren't like
getting anywhere going out. So I
thought, "Fuck it." In it. Blowjob's a [ __ ]
But uh yeah, she weren't having it at
all at all.
And the tenants were shot because
there's like what £400.
One of the tenants, one of them I think
was was gay, bro. And he gave someone 150
150 to one of the guys gave he gave one
of the guys 150 to hug him and touch him
and he and and literally they got the
150. They got the 150, bro. And I think
one of them were being like gay. So
yeah, that in itself that that goes to
show that she's a [ __ ] bro. That's what
I mean. like you're you you get took the
piss out of in this country because like
you're not even ugly or anything and you
know when you go out and you're dealing
with this women [ __ ] it's just a pissake
and even that's a pissake like [ __ ]
£400. I could understand if they had
money or they were in a relationship,
but that is that is insane, bro.
You know, I actually went out offering
people money scoop like for [ __ ]
Yeah. That's another thing I forgot to
say. I literally withdrew money. Yeah.
Like touch his ass and touch his dick
and he gave him 150. Yeah. So, bro, if
he can give 150 and he's not even gay
for a gay person to touch him, why
wouldn't you give 400 to to give a
[ __ ] That's crazy, bro.
You can't even take someone's virginity
with that. So, I actually went out
offering people money like
6 months ago. Yeah. Like sober. Yeah.
Yeah. I actually did. Never worked. I I
actually thought it would have worked.
Definitely scoop. I actually I actually
thought that would have worked
like offering money like I I thought it
was going to work, bro. No, seriously, I
did cuz I feel like obviously like you
know it's money, you know, a lot of
money, bro. Yeah. It's That's mad, lad.
I thought it would have worked. I
genuinely thought that was going to work.
Go away, Virgin. Yeah,
I I generally thought it was going to
work. Me, Scoop, bro, I'm like, [ __ ]
So, I just kind of stuck to the escorts
for a while, bro.
But, you know, you It's good with the
escort scoop, you know? You know, you
know, with these Brazilian escorts, if
you keep talking to them and you keep
seeing them, bro, you can probably have
a kid with them.
You could probably have a kid with them.
To be honest, you probably could cuz
obviously they need a visa and they if
they marry you, they can get a visa.
So, I just stuck to the escort thing and
get [ __ ] to be fair. And I like
women from South America. They're nice.
I've been with a few South American
unlike these horrible Americans. I hate
Americans group. I hate American women.
Got a [ __ ] in the alleyway. Oh, bro,
there's so much madness that that's been
on here, bro.
Yeah. Like the thing is scoop. Yeah.
Like it's just like and and the thing is
Yeah. The way I see escorts is you just
pay for what you want,
you know? Like it's it's cheap. Like
it's I don't know, bro. It's just I just
got addicted to [ __ ] though. Like
that's what happened. Like
But yeah, Brazilian women are nice. I
don't know if you've ever been with Brazilian women.
I'm trying to think who else I've met.
But you know what, Scoop? You know how
we were saying before? Yeah. About the
dating game and that. I think it's got
harder, bro. You know when I you know
when I used to complain Yeah, bro. When
I used to complain. Yeah. But when I
used to complain and whatever, bro. But
you know, it wasn't even that bad. You
know, I'd still go on dates and I [ __ ]
it up with a lot of people, bro. Like, I
[ __ ] it up with so many people, bro.
Come to think of it. But now, I swear to
God, now it is it just seems hard now. I
don't know how people do it.
You compare it to two years ago, bro.
Okay, let me give you an example. You
know that 2013, 2023 when I met USA,
bro, I fingered [ __ ] in clubs. I
kissed people. I went on dates. I had
one night stands, you know, if you
actually compare it to now to now, bro.
Now it just seems I don't know how
people do it, bro. I don't know how
people do it. But two years ago, yeah,
it was actually like you didn't really
have anything to really complain about,
to be honest,
cuz it wasn't easy, but it's not
supposed to be easy.
You understand? But now it just seems
very, very hard, bro. Like I don't know
why. I don't know if people have started
going more to Tik Tok. It just seems
hard, bro. It just seems a lot harder
than it than it was.
Cuz that 2023 I had one night stands. I
had women. You know, even though I had
to deal with a lot of their [ __ ] you
know, you know, you could still say, "Oh, well,
you know, when I come back from Belgium,
I feel like, bro, it has definitely
gotten worse, hasn't it?" It has. It was
easier then. Or is it just me? I swear
it was easier then.
You know these dating apps? Yeah. When I
always used to say they don't work. I
actually met three people on these
dating apps years ago. Like when I come
back from Belgium. So it's not like you didn't really
I don't know. It just seems so harder
now, bro. It don't seem It's just not easy anymore.
It's not easy, bro. It used to be
easier. It It did definitely used to be
easier, bro. I don't even know what I
was complaining about back then because
it just seemed a lot easier.
Um, but now it's just I don't know why
it's so hard, bro. I don't know how
people do it. It's it's weirdo scoop cuz
cuz you go to Newcastle and then the
women approach you.
Did I have I spoke to you since I last
went to Newcastle? I don't. Yeah, I did.
Wait. Yeah, cuz you I last spoke to you
like a year ago with the whole USA easy
thing in it.
Yeah, I think the whole Yeah, like if
you go to Newcastle, bro, the [ __ ]
[ __ ] talk to you.
That's my experience when I went there,
bro. I had a better time there than I
did in London. They're all stuck up in London, bro.
There's these bars you go to, bro. In uh
Yeah, I think when I'm in my 40s it'll be easier
cuz Antman was saying that it's even
gotten worse in um Thailand.
He said it's even gotten worse in Thailand.
He said even Thailand, yeah, it's it's
gotten it's bad in Thailand as well.
Thailand's bad for it. He said it's
still a lot easier, but he said in 10
years it's not going to be worth coming
out coming out here.
Yeah. He said even in he said in 10
years it's not going to be worth coming
out out there.
I don't know if you've ever been to Thailand.
Bomb's never been to Thailand. Virgin boy.
No far west.
More like the west country. I've not
been to Wales in a while. Um,
you know, the thing is, scoop. Yeah. If
somebody was to ask me what was my
favorite second city, Yeah. I'd say
Edinburgh. Edinburgh doesn't get enough
credit, bro. Like, I like Edinburgh.
It's got that thing about it, bro. Where
it's like it looks really nice. Yeah.
But it's really cheap. Um,
it's sort of like you get out the train
station, bro. They call it Weather
Spoons Weatherly, bro. Like, I don't
know. I really like Edinburgh cuz it's
got that it's got that where it's like
it looks really good. It's smaller and
it's a lot cheaper.
I like Edinburgh, bro.
But also that's not the place if you
want to avoid stuck up people. But
obviously it's a lot nicer than [ __ ]
probably a lot nicer than London, bro.
But I ain't never I've never been
Scotland like since, bro. It's too far,
man. What the [ __ ]
I've been Newcastle three times.
Yeah, I've been three times to Newcastle. Um,
yeah, three times. But I've been
Scotland twice, but I just never went
back, bro. Like, had no reason to go back.
But Edinburgh is definitely the second.
Definitely the second city. But I feel
like yeah, when I'm in my 30s, I feel
it would it will get easier. Hopefully. Fingers crossed.
Yeah, Scoop. There was this one time,
bro. There was this American in the bar.
She's like, "I really want you, but I
don't think you want me."
This [ __ ] was coming on to me, bro.
And I took her around the alleyway and
she gave me a [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. that sweat out.
It was a madness.
Yeah, I flew to Scot Scotland for like 75 quid.
Yeah, 75 quid. I flew to Scotland for £75.
Yeah. Oh, I've still got the videos,
man. Do you know all of this [ __ ] Yeah,
nonslegs is doing scoop. I done this
when I was 23.
You You don't understand why he does all
of this stuff on the He does all of this
[ __ ] cuz he's jealous, bro. He sat He
does all of this [ __ ] cuz he's [ __ ]
jealous, bro. He's older than me. I'm
better looking than him. I've got a
better life than him. He stalked every
single woman that I've been with. He's a
[ __ ] loser, bro. You know, people
like that just literally need to be ignored. Any minute. Yeah.
You know, it actually got to the point
where I had to I I hated watching the
videos. He's obsessed. I think he it is
jealousy, bro. It is jealousy. They do
all of this stuff cuz there is they are
jealous, bro. Think about it, bro. Even
if this [ __ ] had more money than me,
which he doesn't.
Yeah, think about it, bro. I'm better
looking. I have more life experience. I
have a mom that doesn't starve me. I
have been with women that he will never
get. You know what I'm saying? Even if
he had more money than me, which he
doesn't have more money than me. Yep.
He's still with He's still with her.
Yeah. This is why he does all of this stuff.
This is why he does, bro. You've seen it
yourself. He has stalked every single
woman that I've been with.
And you know this yourself, bro. If if
you if somebody really believed, yeah,
if somebody was generally ugly, Yeah.
you wouldn't waste your time on them. We
all know how psychological things work,
right? The the the what he does on his
YouTube channel every day. It's like he
hates that he's not you. That's You
wouldn't waste your time all day every
day doing this. If you had money, if you
had a life, you wouldn't do this. You
would not do this, lad. There's no way
you would do this. You know, at the end
of the day, scoop. Yeah. You know,
remember when people, you know, when
Timmy used to um You know when Timmy,
right, you know, when he's you know when
Timmy, right, used to come live and
people used to type [ __ ] for reaction?
Bro, anybody could do that. I can get I
can I can write something, but it's the
extremes that these people go to. Scoop.
Have you seen that [ __ ] Red Star?
He's even worse. He stalks me, bro. From
the time I wake up to the time I go to bed.
To the time I wake up to the time I go
to bed. Bro, it's not even a joke.
That's why people think That's why
people think Yeah.
That's why people think [ __ ] um
That's why people [ __ ] think that um
what's it? That's why people think it's
[ __ ] Pat Mustard.
They they they will never stop, bro.
These people on here will never stop.
They will never ever stop, lad. They're
jealous. People that aren't jealous
don't do this every day.
They don't do this literally every day,
bro. It gets to a point like you you
could ignore these people and they would
still do it.
But remember, we're the skinn one, we're
the ugly one, we're this, we're that.
Make it make sense. You know what I'm saying?
Look at all of the women I've been with.
scoop. Yeah. And look at who he's been
with. Think about it, bro.
Then he tries to say that people live
with their mom. Most people in London
live with their parents. And you know
that as well, Scoop. First, I don't even
live with my [ __ ] mom. Secondly, most
people in London live with their parents.
Like, or they live with their parents,
bro. Not even a parent. Or they live in
a box room. people in London, they live
in box rooms. Um, or they live with
their parents. Obviously, not everyone,
but a large major, a large percentage of people do.
Like, a lot of people [ __ ] do, unless
they have kids and obviously the council
will give them a house, but if you find
like a single normal person that works
like a normal job, they live with their
parents. Trust me, in London, they do,
bro. So, I mean, there's an excuse for
it, you know? It's not like Liverpool.
You can buy a house for £1, bro. Like,
there's every reason. There's every
excuse to live with your mom. There's
every reason. There's every excuse to
live with your dad. It's not unheard of.
It's literally not even a skit, bro.
Don't forget, Scoop. I've lived by
myself. I've lived with tenants. I've
lived with my mom. And yeah, there's
some like in there's some cons, but it's
nowhere near as bad as he's making it
out to be. There's nowhere It's nowhere
near as bad as he's making it out to be,
bro. Nowhere [ __ ] near.
When I had that foot injury, lad, when I
had that foot injury, I had to come to
my mom's like a few times, bro, cuz I
couldn't sleep cuz of the tenants. They
were so loud, lad. My [ __ ] foot was hurting.
Um, no, she's not.
On and off. Yeah. Venom. On and off.
Yeah. On and off, lad.
Oh, [ __ ] But yeah, lots of people live
with their parents, bro. In London.
>> What did I just put that there, lad?
Lots of people live with their parents, mate.
Hey, look. I'll show you something if you want.
Look what I got, bro.
I got a Chucky cap. Look at my face,
bro. Look how better looking I am than
that virgin. Look, I need to go to the
barbers. Look at my face, bro. Does my
nose look big? No, it doesn't.
Oh my god. I need to go to the barbers,
bro. [ __ ] I'm going to start looking homeless, bro.
My nose is supposed to be big. Is that
supposed to stop me showing my face or
something? What the [ __ ] Pathetic, man.
Oh, and apparently I'm balding.
Yeah, that's news to me. Put your hair
back down up here, belly. See, the thing
they don't understand, Scoop, is they
can go on about this all day long that
you're this, you're that, you're this,
you're that, but they're never going to
make me insecure. I'm going to go out on
fat Saturday and I'm going to put my
camera on as well. Show my face the whole time.
The whole time, bro. These people, they
need to understand that they're never
going to make me insecure.
The more they do what they do.
[ __ ] The more they do what they do on
here, the more they show themselves up,
the more they show what they really are
about. The more they do this, the more
they waste their life on on this [ __ ] thing, bro. The more
the more [ __ ] Bro, I was going out in
a [ __ ] tracksuit, lad. Oh, Scoop. I I
I'd done this thing, bro, where I was
going out in a in a [ __ ] tracksuit. I
was going out in a tracksuit, bro. And I
was getting more success in a tracksuit.
Yeah. Country's [ __ ] The country's Yeah, man. Yep.
There we go. You like my hair? I'm
thinking of putting it into a knot.
What do you think, lad? Put into a knot.
But yeah, like the more they do it, the
more they show how jealous they are.
The more they do this, the more they
show that they're jealous. That's the
only thing they do when they come on
here doing this. But
but I feel like a lot of people don't
like me because of my race.
Cuz obviously I don't look fully right,
do I? I don't look fully white, do I? Scoop.
So I don't know. I kind of doesn't really Yeah.
>> Oh, [ __ ] Oh, mate.
I need to make my bed in a bit, bro.
I don't know, bro.
Cuz I'm good looking matey or I'm decent
looking matey. I should be getting some
more success matey.
It's hard bro. It's hard. It's hard.
I'm trying to think, bro. Yeah, I think
I've been on three dates this year.
But some women are weird. Like they'll
just kiss you and then they [ __ ] just
ghost. They'll actually kiss you. You
actually be snogging someone and then
they just ghost you as [ __ ] Well, you
don't like the little man bun scoop. Come on.
I'm not joining his panel. He's a snake, bro.
Yeah, he thinks I'm jealous of Nataly G.
God, you need to get a life nump's legs.
Why do you want Why do you want my
attention so bad?
Why do you want
Why do you want my attention so bad?
You're [ __ ] You're I'm skinn I'm a m
apparently. Why do you want to skin
Mont's attention so bad? Oh mate,
how many times have I got laid with escorts?
Lots without escorts. Lots. Well, I
didn't get laid. I got [ __ ] cuz I
only got [ __ ] from the 19year-old.
I just I just don't have the energy anymore, Scoop,
to do the approaching and I just I just
can't be bothered with it anymore, bro.
Leave me alone, you little virgin,
bro. Imagine this scoop. Yeah, just
picture this, right?
Picture this, bro. Yeah,
you've gone to the police about someone
by the way, I showed the police all the
[ __ ] he's been doing. You've gone to the
police because someone's owned you on
YouTube. So, you've gone and run into
the police and you're still on YouTube
doing this. That is beyond obsessed.
Oh, I stopped meeting you because you've
done this because you've done that. If
you stop if you cut someone off, bro,
you wouldn't be doing this every day.
That's another thing.
These people never ever stop. You can't
get rid of the [ __ ]
Think of it, Scoop. They're like, bro,
it's like they're like Chucky. You can't
get rid of the [ __ ]
You know, look at USA is I gave up in
the end and I [ __ ] [ __ ] the [ __ ]
and I get and this it wasn't every day
and I gave up with the [ __ ] That's
madness, bro. How they do this every day.
I stick to what I say, bro. I think
they're they're just 40year-old ugly
people that are angry at the world
because their lives are a [ __ ]
See the thing is bro like scoop. Yeah.
Anyone can be any any age and come on
YouTube. Yeah. Like you because they
just come on YouTube you know people can
just come on YouTube but it's what they
actually do on this every day
cuz we can sit there and say you're just
38 39 and you're just chilling bro you.
But these people can't be because it's
what they actually do on here every day.
Like it's [ __ ] weird bro.
There's not many normal people around
anymore. Like you, unworthy clock. Um,
and Joe is okay, but he's still kind of
trolling because it's clear he just
wants attention, but there's not really
many normal people, bro.
Greavvesy, but like I don't It's just
They fry your brain, bro. They're [ __ ]
They're weirdos, man. They're weirdos.
They sit on here every day hating
on you because they don't have the
things that they're saying that you
don't have. It's weird. You don't
understand how it's weird. Like you
explain it to to people, but if they're
disabled, they don't understand it.
Do you not understand how it's just
weird, lad? It's just weird.
One second, my man. Baby, [ __ ]
They're in. That's why I say that.
They're this, they're that, they're
this, they're that.
And you know how you know it's his dad's
money as well? Because is because
is because right
is because um think about it bro it
doesn't even sound realistic someone
goes to Holland right someone goes to
Holland and what they're going to what exchange €13,000.
Does that sound Does that sound believable?
Does that sound believable, bro? That's ridiculous.
Yeah, people go to Holland and
what's prop money? What is this prop
money you speak of?
You know, there's ways to get money. You
can go to university and get a loan out
and [ __ ] like that. No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I mean, he's even admit he's even
admitted that he that's is his dad's
money. Think about it, Scoop. Yeah,
think about it like this, lad. Yeah. I
don't know if he was around when I
showed this £6,000. This is why I don't
get into these same cycle arguments,
right? I showed £6,000. No one showed me
nothing. and he kept trying to show me
8900 pound. If somebody truly wasn't
skin, right, it would not have took
somebody that long to show money.
And I I don't know what prop money is.
What the [ __ ] is prop money?
I don't know. I actually don't even know
what that is. Um, but the thing is,
Scoot, when you're not liked on here,
they they're biased. They they they
believe what they remember what they
want to remember. That's what they're
like on here.
You understand, lad? So they they they
forget that. But they've been shown
loads of money, bro. Multiple times. And really,
who knows? But it ain't his money. He's
skinned, bro. Like that's like I said,
that's why I don't like scoop you. You
know that money mic right? He was
snaking me, right?
Um he was snaking me, right? Yeah.
Um and that's one thing I don't like on
it. I don't like snakes.
I don't like people that like lick your
ass in the chat and then they they talk
like I've caught a lot of them doing
this. And bro, why do you think you know
last Friday when I went cinema you
wasn't on here? I wanted to go
Birmingham so badly and punch him in
bro. Like, but the thing is, bro, you
know, when you do these things,
all that happens is you come back
and then they pretend it never happened
and then it just starts again. So, in
it's just a waste of time. It's just
like they're showing money. It's just
like it's just the same thing. It just
goes round and round and round and round in circles.
Even when you're like meeting people,
like even if you try meeting people or
even if you show them like women, like
it could be any different. It's
anything, bro. They like to remember
what they want to remember.
That's a big part of this community.
Like you could be Brad Pit, bro. You
could be you could be you could be, bro,
Brad Pit, a millionaire, a billionaire,
bro, and they'd still talk [ __ ] about
you. That's That's what I'm saying, bro.
And I don't think it's necessarily that
they I Well, I personally think that
they are jealous. And even if they're
not jealous, it's because you're the
youngest on here. You're better looking than them. So,
you got a life. They don't have a life.
So, that's why they do this [ __ ] So,
yeah, you get the point. Anyways,
it's madness, bro.
You can't win because they're all
biased. That's what I'm saying there.
But it's even like L J's, bro. Like,
that is the most disabled thing.
Yeah, there's no point with them, bro.
There's no point. Like, I've got another
channel where I've got all my
approaching videos on there and [ __ ]
I've got I've got a I've got another channel, lad.
that these don't know about.
But I've got my own like secret channel
that these people don't know about.
Like even Ant-Man come off here and live
his life. You know what I mean? madness. Yeah.
But like I said, that that L that LJ's
that LJ's channel was the worst, lad.
For self [ __ ] fleeding. Oh my god. I
don't know how you go on there
sometimes. I saw your comment saying
that it's embarrassing that he's
clubbing at 38. [Music] Oh,
have you got any tattoos?
You'd give um
you'd give USA easy one in it, Scoop.
You'd give USA one, in it. Yeah, man. Oh,
you would, wouldn't you, lad? Bless you.
Yeah. Why not? What? You don't like her?
You don't like her, mate? Why?
You wouldn't give a You wouldn't [ __ ]
the [ __ ] Why?
Yeah, but she's got big tits, isn't it,
Scoop? It's all about them boobies, is it?
All about boobies and [ __ ]
I would I wouldn't get with a woman that
wouldn't give me a [ __ ] you know?
It's just like, nah. I was speaking to
one on the dating app, bro. She's
Australian. She said that she would
[ __ ] but she doesn't give [ __ ]
But she doesn't give [ __ ]
She doesn't Yeah. It might not be your
thing, is it?
I mean, I know. They'd have to have some
really like nice tits for me to get with
them if they didn't give a [ __ ] You know,
they'd have to like be really
The best [ __ ] I ever had was a
[ __ ] from an American, bro. The alleyway.
It was a good [ __ ]
What's a deal breaker?
You might not like [ __ ] in it.
Yeah, you might not like [ __ ] lad.
What do you mean, bro?
So, what? You'd get with a woman that
don't give [ __ ]
I couldn't get with a woman that don't
give [ __ ] bro.
They would have to give [ __ ]
Yeah. It's a deal breaker. So yeah, you
wouldn't get with somebody that don't
get blowjobed. Yeah,
that's that's what I'm saying, bro. Yeah,
it's a Yeah, it is a deal breaker.
But at the same time, I don't lick women out. So
I don't lick women out, bro. Cuz [ __ ]
it's frowned upon basically where uh
where I'm from, you know.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. Yeah, it
is a deal breaker
cuz you always start with [ __ ] Like
I I had this problem um scoop right where where um
I had this problem where a lot of these
escorts where I'd be into [ __ ]
right? They would they would not let me
come in their mouth.
Um so they give you a [ __ ] but you
can't come in their mouth. And I had
this problem a lot. Um and it was hard
trying to find one. And there was Bro,
you're going to laugh at this, right? I
remember I finished this Uber Eats job
thing. Yeah. I just going to go to an escort.
I'm just going to go to an escort, bro. And uh
[ __ ] get a [ __ ] in it. And they
weren't having it. They give you a
[ __ ] but you can't come in our
mouth. No, no, no, no, no. Bro, I had to
go all the way to Harrow, which is near
Wembley, cuz I was like, bro, I want a
[ __ ] [ __ ] today. Um, I had to go
all the way to [ __ ] Harrow. Bear in
mind I was in Stratford to go and see an
escort that I had already known that I already knew.
So, but if you if I got with somebody
and they said just don't come in my
mouth, I think I think you could work
with that, you know, not coming in their
mouth. I think you Yeah, you can just
they can give you a [ __ ] and you can
just [ __ ] them. But that was a good
thing in a way because it was like,
okay, well, they'll give you a [ __ ]
you can't come in their mouth. That's
fine because then you can just [ __ ]
them. And then it got me more into sex
again, which is what I should be into. I
should have been into sex more and not
just [ __ ] So yeah, I should have
been into sex more and not just [ __ ] Um,
yeah, but I I would get with somebody.
Yeah, as long as they give you the [ __ ]
But I used to be I used to like it when
they used to swallow it scoop.
Like I used to like when I used to have
the house and I I'd pay like £200 for
them to give me a [ __ ] and swallow it.
I paid £250 to this Somalian girl. Yeah.
She stuck my dick in the toilet. In the
Weber Spoon's toilet.
Yeah. Because money weren't a thing
then, bro. We don't care about money. We
can just [ __ ]
throw money away. You know what I mean? [ __ ]
what I'm saying, lads. So, it wasn't it
wasn't a thing. I was a crazy bastard,
bro. I was a crazy bastard.
Trust me. Yeah, I was crazy, bro. I
didn't give a [ __ ] obviously. Yeah,
cuz I used to gamble a lot and used to
win that in it. just don't really care.
But like I said, at least this house
thing happened now. Scooping it where I
feel all old and I can't be bothered to
go out anymore.
Very, very good. Very good, bro.
Going to I'm going to put bro 150 on two teams.
next week, lad.
No, I wasn't keen, but I thought I might
as well. Was it? [ __ ] it. Yeah,
she turned out [ __ ] mad, bro. Yeah. N
Yeah. Yeah. These people love cocaine.
I've got friends in the army that do
cocaine scoop, but I don't do it.
Do you remember Fraser Scoop? Oh, good
times, man. Good times.
Good [ __ ] times, eh?
Do you remember when LT was like
messaging USA like warning her about me?
What did I cause, bro? Scoop the scoop.
Do you remember all the [ __ ] I used to cause?
Like all the sayings that I used to come
up with, bro. That's why going live
Yeah. just got so addicted because it's
like you'll be saying these sayings,
right? And you get these people on here
that cop. I don't even know where I come
out with these sayings, lad.
I don't even know. Like, do you remember
when I used to say like taking a baby
away from its mama? Bro, I don't even
know where I come from. I got these
sayings from, bro. Yeah. Rape victim.
There's a lot of him. I Bro, I used to
say some I don't even know where I got
these sayings. Um, he comes on here occasionally. Yeah,
he's a pretty good [ __ ]
You know, he's a he's a pretty good [ __ ]
You still you still watching the sideman scoop?
You still watching the sideman?
You're still watching the sideman,
aren't you? Bless you. Taking a baby
away from its mama.
taking a baby. Bro, I don't even know
where I got this [ __ ] from. I think it's
cuz where she had like big tits and [ __ ]
and then like she just disappeared and
abandoned me. I don't know, bro. Taking
the baby away from it, mama.
Mad [ __ ] [ __ ] I am, bro. And then
the couch should copy everything I say.
Uh, it's funny how you know who they
are, is it?
[ __ ] go, bro. I wish I could rob
them, you know? They're [ __ ] rich.
I wish I could [ __ ] rob them, bro.
I used to watch their hide and seek [ __ ] videos, but
they will uh die down in a in a few
years, but they're minted for life in it. So,
I don't YouTubers watch them anymore, bro.
I watched that mash tag scoop, but I
only I only discovered him like a couple
of months ago.
You know that mash tag?
Yeah, bro. If he sold that whole thing,
he'd be a billionaire, you know?
He He would be a [ __ ] billionaire if
he sold that Prime thing, bro. He would
be a billionaire, bro.
He's [ __ ] really rich.
Hey man, you good?
>> Yeah, we got [ __ ] nonsleg showing his
dad's money off again. Kieran.
Yeah, I watch Mashtag
and I only discovered him like 3 months ago.
How mad is that, bro? You know what we
should do, Kier? Me and you need to meet
up for a drink on Saturday and do a
video to that nons legs.
Do you know what's so mad, Scoop? is if
I if I contacted this [ __ ] I'd get nicked.
Even though he started all of this [ __ ]
you know how [ __ ] up the system is.
They've actually got their favorites in
this country, bro. You don't know the
[ __ ] I went through with the police,
with this [ __ ]
Yeah. Do you know how [ __ ] if I, you
know, I've got this cunt's number? If I
messaged him right now, you know, I
would get nipped. You know that? Because
of the court thing.
Yeah. The police have got their
favorites and [ __ ] I was advised
I was advised by the court, right,
and the police and the solicitors to
report it to the police. And every single time
I reported it to the police, they'd say,
"Oh, we can't do anything." Or, "No, no,
no, no, no, no." Well, like they'd make
all of these [ __ ] excuses. So, I had
like a big problem. I had a big problem
with the police for a long time. I don't
think he was on here. And it's like and
I'd have the argument saying, "Oh, so
you're fast enough to come on my door
when somebody reports me, but then when
I do it, you're not interested." Um,
and um, yeah, they've just got their
favorites in this country, bro. The the the police.
I hate the police, bro. Yeah. In a
minute, bro. In a minute.
They've got their favorites, lad.
I've got everything, bro. I've got I've
got a whole folder scoop of what this
cunt's done. It's called the harassment
folder. I'll send you it if you want.
I've got everything on there. I sent it
to my solicitor. I sent it to the police
and they just didn't care. And then the
irony scoop, right? They were telling
me, "Oh, to report it to this, report it
to that, report it to YouTube." I said,
"Was you telling them to report it to
YouTube when you was on my [ __ ] door?
You can't play two sides of a [ __ ]
coin." And then and then, funny enough,
when I went to that police station, this
was about 3 months ago. Yeah. when I
still had the house, they were like,
"Oh, um, you know what they said? They
were like, "Oh, well, yeah, we need to
give you an involuntary interview
because you said something to some woman
on Instagram." And they never bothered
ever contacting me again cuz I think
they know that I would just tell them to
[ __ ] off, bro. They play two sides of a
coin. These these police, they play two
sides of a coin. Like,
I've been nicked about 20 times over
YouTube. I'm not even joking, bro. I
used to get nicked all the time on here.
That's mad to think like how I've
actually been nicked so many times on
this on this website, bro.
100%. I will
100% and I'll smash his [ __ ] face in.
And then when it goes to court, I will
bring up all the [ __ ] that they've been
doing to me. All the [ __ ] that they've
been doing to me.
But yeah, I I've been nicked so many
times on here, bro.
So many times I've been nicked.
So many [ __ ] times. Like it's not
even a joke. I remember one time, bro, I
was just about to go to bed. It was like 12:00.
It was 12:00, bro. And the police come
on the door, nicked me. I was in the
police cell for 7 hours.
Yeah, bro. I got [ __ ] Do you know the
last time the police come on my door? I
put the phone in the garden. Yeah. The
tenants were there in it and there was
police on the door. I weren't expecting
them to come. I was like, "Oh, let me
put my phone in the garden in case they
tried to take my phone in it cuz I just
got a new phone and that in it." And
then I was in the police cell. Then I
had to go court and they let me go from
the court, right? And then um I went
back to the house. Oh mate, it was a mad [ __ ] piss. Yeah.
Yeah. And I hid my phone and that and
then I come back and then I found my
phone. So yeah.
So yeah, that's why I hate the police,
bro. They're all [ __ ] bent. They're
bent pedo lovers. Yeah. Cuz he went
crying to the police and I showed the
police his channel and everything. They
didn't care. Yeah.
I went to um I was in a police cell for
two days. I went to court and then they
they let me let me go from the court.
Yeah, bro. And then I went back to the
house. The tenants were like, "What the
[ __ ] happened?" I said, "Yeah, just some
shit." They were all worried and that in
And that's why I had to really be more
careful when I had that house cuz I
didn't want to like I I didn't want to
lose the house cuz I was making money
from the house. So, I had something to
lose. You know, like you're making three
grand a month. You don't want to lose
three grand a month. So, that's why I
was really careful with what I was
doing. I was more careful then than I am
careful now. Cuz now I don't give a [ __ ] bro.
Cuz I had a responsibility, you see. So
I couldn't do anything that landed me
getting getting in trouble, bro. You
understand? I couldn't
I couldn't um, you know, risk losing the
house and the people and the
responsibility and the money. You know
what I'm saying? So that's why I had to
really really be careful.
But obviously now it's like it doesn't
really I mean you still have stuff to
lose but you understand what I mean that
like you still have your your freedom
and that but I had the responsibility
you know what I'm saying
and I was thinking I was like if they
don't let me go what's going to happen
in the house they're in the house who's
going to look up who's who's going to
look after the house and that
similar to if like someone's got kids
you know what I'm saying if you've got a
responsibility then you don't really
want to do anything that put you in
prison. You know what I mean? So
yeah, I know that, bro. Yeah, they're
biased. Yeah, that's what I'm saying.
Scoop. Yeah. Yeah, of course. Of course.
Of course. If I was to come up here for
two weeks, bro,
they they'd all go for him. Yeah. Yeah.
They'd all go for him, bro. Yeah. Uh-huh.
And I think that's why it never really
used to piss me off the dating [ __ ] as
much because obviously it's like you
don't know how lucky you are, you know,
getting that kind of money a month and
you're not, you know, you're not working.
So it kind of was like
but somehow it did still really piss me
off. I mean it was around. Yep.
Yep. I wonder who that Joe account is.
Yeah, he is an unlikable person. Why do
you think Izzy doesn't meet him anymore?
Why do you think Kenji don't meet him anymore?
Yeah, I've not seen uh I've not seen
Isabelle in years scoop. I think me and
Isabelle should meet up again. What do
you think like
seven years later?
Oh, I off No, I I offered money for a
[ __ ] I didn't offer Monty a [ __ ]
Obviously, I [ __ ] didn't offer him a
[ __ ] He's talking [ __ ] bro. What the [ __ ]
I think me and Izzy should meet now.
Like, it's six, seven years later.
We're older now, ain't it? A little Isabelle.
See, that one was my fault. I know when
I've been wrong, bro. I've never said
I'm not wrong. I know when I [ __ ] up.
you know, basically me and that
19year-old would have been me and Izzy
if it wasn't for YouTube.
So, I mean,
that was me. That was definitely me. It
was her as well, but it was more me.
It was more me, lad. But obvious
though, you know what I'm saying, Scoop?
It was still a little bit her,
but it was obviously more me because
obviously if you didn't put them on
YouTube, this wouldn't have happened.
Whereas the whole USA,
whereas the USA Izzy, that wasn't
YouTube. That was just her. She's a [ __ ]
And the thing is with with Izzy, the
problem with it is Scoop is like she was
young. You brought her onto this
community, you know?
It was still like 20% of her fault, but
obviously it was it was more my fault.
But at the end of the day, you brought
somebody on this community, right? And
they're quite young and you didn't need
to bring them on this community and all
of it is cuz of YouTube.
Whereas obviously [ __ ] with USA Izzy,
what's the excuse? You're a grown ass
woman. YouTube weren't involved. So I
mean there's two different things. But
obviously she weren't perfect. Izzy
wasn't perfect. But
you know obviously it was obviously me
as well you know so and obviously the
one with the Nottingham one the big one
so I know like but then there's also
been people that's wasting my time so
I'm I'm aware of the difference you know so
19 old it's nearly 10 years station a
19year-old she's actually 20 now
nearly a 10 year age gap. It's nowhere
near a 10 year age gap. She's actually
Yeah, she's When was her birthday? September.
So Izzy's got to be like 23, 24 now.
Why do you think she had a soft spot for
me, Scoop? No, she's not. She's 20.
She's not 19 and she's actually 20 now.
Yes. Your birthday is on September.
Yeah. It was my mom's birthday. My mom's
birthday is a day after Nons legs. His dad's birthday.
I remember that.
Mick Jonathan Robinson.
Horrible little nons.
Yeah, because I'm getting older now, bro.
I'm getting older now. You know, you you
get you get hit by reality, bro. You
know, you know, that whole house thing
was like a reality. You know what I
mean? You look back on it and see, you
know, you could have had it a lot worse, lad.
I'm just old. I just feel old, bro. I
feel 100 years old, lad.
I go, you know what I'm saying? I just
feel 100 years old. I just I don't have
the energy for it anymore. Like, I mean,
I've chilled out, bro.
You know, sometimes you look back on
things and [ __ ] is it? Yeah, I was
[ __ ] Well, I was [ __ ]
And the only reason I didn't go to
America the first time, you know, that
first time is because the 19-year-old
was begging me not to go. She said, "Oh,
don't go. Don't go. Don't go." I said,
"No, I'm going to show this little
country who's boss." I got some money
back from the bank at the end.
She's not teen. She's 20. But yeah, but
it would have been funny, bro. The first
time cuz it would have it would have
been me or them. Simple, bro. It would
have been me or them. You know how long
that [ __ ] took to get over Scoop? It's
me or them, bro. You know what I'm
saying? It's simple, bro. If you go there. Yeah.
If you go there, bro, it's me or them.
Cuz I I messaged her, but I swear I
messaged her exad. And again, I'm
talking about this, bro, cuz you are
here, is it? So that's like the first
thing we remember that it's literally
like it's me or them. Is it
simple, bro? No one's going back. Yeah, I'm [ __ ]
looking back on that now. It's actually
bad, is it?
Yeah, but [ __ ] mad. [Laughter]
That's actually mad. [ __ ]
yeah. Me Izzy Izzy just needs to meet Peter Belly.
Yeah, she likes She likes Peter Belly in it.
You know how I actually met Izzy? I met
Izzy on a student call. Yeah, I used to just uh
I used to just like
um I used to just [ __ ]
Oh, this bed's lush. I had to put in the
dryer. Um I was on a student room form
and um I was moaning about women and
[ __ ] and she like, "Oh, how about we
meet up? How about we meet up and I'll
show you like um we'll see what the
problem is in this shit."
Yeah, yeah, it is. It is.
Yeah, we can see your comments, bro.
Yeah, we can see you. And she Oh, we'll
meet up. We'll meet up.
So, we want to meet up, bro.
So, okay, let's meet up.
Yeah, she [ __ ] Do you remember? I
remember exactly that day, Sk. Remember
when I won on the roulette?
I think I won like£300 on the roulette
and uh she saw it and she said, "Oh, do
you want to meet up? Do you want to meet
up?" She got I thought, "Oh, I thought
you uh had a boyfriend. I thought you
Yeah, his dad's money. Yeah.
Yeah, I remember exactly that, bro.
I kind of made this community, bro. If
there was no If there was no me or there
was no Timmy, there'd be no YouTube.
There'd be no [ __ ] YouTube. You know
what I mean?
[ __ ] me. There'd be no YouTube.
Oh, [ __ ] You still there, Scoop?
Yeah, cuz I can't go in a dirty bed with
with a good body, a fresh body, you
know. Even though it's took the smell off,
I can't do that, bro.
Should be dry now.
Oh, should be lovely and dry.
I I'll never forget. Yeah. Um Ant-Man's
video, lad. When he when he lost in the
bookies, he said, "You want to take my
[ __ ] money? I'll take yours."
Nah, bro. I've lived I've lived a life
that you will never have, and I've got savings,
so I'm all good, lad. Nah, not at all,
bro. I'll find another way to make
money. And I've got savings.
It's all good, matey.
Um, I think he's that Red Star account.
I don't know if you've seen it. I think
he's Oh, [ __ ]
I think he's that Red Star account, man.
Yeah, I think he's that I think he's
that [ __ ] Red Star account.
Nah, matey, I don't need to work. I've
got a brain, matey.
Yeah, I think he's that red Oh, [ __ ] I
think it's that [ __ ] Red Star account.
I can't believe you've never been up
north. I can't because he does the same
[ __ ] as him. Bro,
that Red Star is definitely him, mate.
Stat on [ __ ] That Red Star, bro, is
is prolific, man. Like, I can't even put
into words. He He He will never stop,
bro. He just sits online recording
everything every day.
Wait, what the [ __ ]
Hold on, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, been owning me. That virgin will
never own me, mate.
But I need to stop saying I'm I'm going
to stop coming on here and that. I just
need to stop entertaining these little
mongos. These weirdos,
that's all, lad.
Yeah, he records everything.
He records everything, bro. I swear.
Hopefully the bed don't [ __ ] up. One almost. Yeah. Antman,
you [ __ ] nasty virgin.
You nasty virgin.
Oh my god, these sheets are This is
[ __ ] bro. The sheet is on wrong.
You know what, Scoop? I used to come
back and make the bed better when I was pissed.
How How am I going to make money now? Scoop,
how am I going to make money now, lad?
I've got this delivery app on my phone.
I need to do this work soon, but
I don't know when.
I'm so lazy, bro. I don't want to work.
I'm [ __ ] lazy, lad.
Oh, I'm [ __ ] lazy as [ __ ] man.
I won a football bet last month and this
month, so I got like 1,400 instead of in Yeah.
Nah. Anyways, bye-bye now.
I do talk to you, bro. You haven't asked anything.
You should come on the um the the hangouts, bro. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah. So, I won the football bet. So, it
was like 1,400 in two months instead of
like 1,100, 1200.
It's hard to make none. The only thing I
can think of, Scoop, is if you if you
lump on two teams. But the thing is,
bro, if you lump on two I was thinking
of putting 500 pound on two teams. Yeah.
The thing when I done when I done scoop,
bro, uh when I done the Uber thing, I
earned 90 in a day. It took about 9
hours. But to be fair, I did start very
early. So, I think if I stay started a
bit later. I think 1:20 I could have got maybe.
Oh, it's long though, man.
It depends what day you go, bro. Like,
Sundays are to be avoided, but it
doesn't matter if you can make 200 pound
a week, bro.
200 It's 200 a week,
which is like It's like five hours every
couple days if you wanted to, bro. It's nothing. Yeah.
It's not supposed to be
It's not supposed to be a normal job.
That's what I'm saying. But that's the
risk you take. But that's the only way I
see you could actually get money, bro. More money.
Yeah. It's less than minimum wage. It's
not supposed to be a job. Yeah. But
Yeah. But you don't obviously.
Yeah, but it's not a it's not a a main job.
It's a side hustle. It's not supposed to
be a main job. But it doesn't matter,
bro. If you made Think about it like
this, Scoop. Yeah. If you made £200 a
week, that's basically the same as the house money.
Maybe maybe about maybe 8 900 off.
as an example. Yeah.
If you obviously if you like
if you if you got £200 a week, right,
and you want and you want a football bet
every month, that's basically the house money back
pretty much. So when you put it that
way, I mean, yeah, you could work more
hours, but you don't want to get sick of
it. You know what I mean?
But some days are bad, bro. I worked
eight hours once to get 50 pound.
on a Sunday. Sundays are not the days to
work, bro. And you know the thing is
with that with that delivery thing scoop. Yeah.
The thing with the delivery thing um
um the thing the thing No, it doesn't
because they don't know anything cuz you
just don't declare it.
You just don't declare it and you're and
you're allowed to make a certain amount.
Obviously, you just don't declare it.
But the thing is, bro, is that Saturdays
were the best days to work. And when
you'd go in central London and you would
try to work Yeah. they would um
they would block the road off. They done
it about three day three times, bro.
They block the road that goes to
Westminster and then that's 90% of the deliveries,
you know? That's like 90% of the [ __ ] deliveries, bro.
That's literally 90% of the deliveries.
So if if it stays like that, you
couldn't work. You'd have to go back
home cuz any delivery that's going
there, they block the whole road off.
So you're [ __ ] basically.
That's why you could never do it on
Saturdays really. Well, some Saturdays
you obviously could, but there'd be
protests, gay pride, and nah, you can't
work like that, bro. Because most of the
deliveries are going that way, you know.
That goes to Elephant and Castle, it
goes to Batisy,
it goes to,
you know, it goes to most places,
you know. No, I never said I'm on UC.
I'm just saying that you wouldn't
declare it to you see.
They can phone them up all I want, bro.
I didn't earn I didn't earn anything
bad. They can They can call them up.
They can call them up. You're allowed to
earn a certain amount of money a week.
You're allowed to earn about £144 a
week. They can they can call them up all they want.
Mhm. You haven't done anything wrong.
You're allowed to earn 40 £144 a week.
And these people have already tried to
get my money stopped multiple times. I
don't even think they believe them
anymore. So when they try to ring me up,
when they try to ring up the benefits
and [ __ ] they don't even listen anymore.
Yeah, they don't even listen anymore, lad.
So I never earned over the amount. So
and if I started working, I would never
tell anyone on here anyways.
I would not I would never tell anyone
that I've started working. Even when I
have worked, I would never tell them.
So, I only tell them about the Uber
because the [ __ ] account and [ __ ] I
would never tell people I'm working.
Yeah, they tried to get my benefits uh
stopped a few times with the sublet
money, but I was too smart for them.
I'm not going to tell you how, but they
like, "Oh, can we see bank statements?"
I said, "Yep, you can see bank
statements. I don't know what you're
talking about." Subleting.
Yeah, bro. I had to send like
[ __ ] Oh, bro. They were asking for
bank statements and [ __ ] madness, lad.
Yeah. And I've got You didn't get my
sublet money stopped at all. You can
keep saying that. You never got my
sublet money stopped.
You never got my subleting money
stopped. The landlord took me to court
after 4 years.
Um, after 4 years. You never got my
sublet money stopped.
Not even in the slightest. People on
YouTube can't do that. You never you
never got my um subleting money stop.
That's all. Listen, let let me tell you
something, Scoop. Right. Listen, bro. We
have been on here for a while now. If I
If I Yeah. If I
If anybody right got my sublet money
stopped, I would have killed them. I
would have found one of these people and
I would have killed them. And it doesn't
matter who they are. And how do you know
I'm not lying, bro?
How did why do you think I'd done the
posters with Virgin Boy? Because I had
these benefit people on my case and you
know how much money they were trying to stop £180
which is about 10% of my income, right?
And then even though yeah, it was £180.
It's like bro like you're not going to
[ __ ] with my money. You're not going to
[ __ ] with my income. You that is not
going to happen. And um you know the
fact that they done that and you know
they were talking about doing it bro I I literally
um I literally went with the posters
because of that thing and that was £180.
It doesn't matter. It's not the point.
£180 is your money. Who are these people
to try to stop your money? And I went
around putting posters up with the
little [ __ ] which people seem to [ __ ]
forget. So bro, trust me if anybody I'm
going to stop coming on here soon. I am
bro. Don't worry about that. I am um
they I would have killed someone, bro.
And they can literally send that to the
police. I don't give a [ __ ] And it
would be anyone that I could get my
hands on. Trust me. It's very very
serious [ __ ] You know, and it's to do
with kids and people's money and stuff.
You know what I'm saying?
It's very It's serious [ __ ] bro. Trust
me, nobody would have got my income
stopped and still be on there laughing
cuz that [ __ ] weren't laughing when he
was running to the police,
you know. Um,
that's [ __ ] that you don't [ __ ] around
with, bro. Like, I don't mind like the
banter and [ __ ] and you know, even the
arguing is entertainment, but when it
when it's to do with people trying to
get people's money stopped. Nah, bro. No
one's getting my money stopped. Simple.
Simple as that, bro. And it could be
anyone, you know, money mic. It could as
long as I got one of them, bro. Then
someone that snaked me, you know,
obviously, then I'm happy. We call it We
call it evens, isn't it?
Um, so yeah, they are low lives. They
are low lives. And they didn't get my
sublet money stopped. None of them did.
It's not even possible, bro. The
landlord scoop took it to court after 4 years.
They were trying for 4 years to get a
house took. They were going to take the
house back anyways cuz they took it to
court. It had nothing to do with these
people on YouTube.
People on YouTube can't speed up a court process.
They never got anyone's money stopped.
And even without that money, that's I've
still got more money than them. They're
narcissistic low lives on here. This is
what I'm saying, bro. They're
narcissistic low lives.
This is what happens when you get
bullied your whole life. You end up like
fatty bomb and nonslegs. But yeah, that
was £180, but it's not the point. So, I
would have still been getting my main
money and I would still be getting my
sublet money. It's not the point, bro.
No one's going to try and stop my money.
That's not going to happen. That is not
going to happen, bro. And I'm sure they
probably tried again, but they um they
obviously just don't listen to them now.
So, no, it is.
You know what I mean?
That's a madness, bro. A [ __ ] madness.
I I remember I just come out the shower,
kid, and I got these people calling me.
That's how you know you've got more
money than them and you're better than them, bro.
Cuz they're they're
they were saying you don't know what
they told the benefits as well, bro.
Kieran, they were telling them mad [ __ ]
They were telling them that I've got six
grand. No, no, no, no, no, no. They're
proper grasses, bro. They're they're low
lives. They got nothing.
You know what? Actually bringing it up.
I actually remember what the woman was
actually saying to me. They've got
nothing. They're low lives. These are
the people that you need to look at.
It's what my sister calls them as well.
These ski low lives, bro. And just use
them to motivate you.
Cuz that's what they done in the end,
they motivated me that I don't want to
be like them.
They don't like you cuz you're better
looking than them and you're younger
than them. Even if by the 1% chance you
never had as much money as them, as long
as you're not struggling, bro, as long
as you can afford to do [ __ ] you're
still better than them. Even if they had
more money than you, when they don't
even have more money than you anyways,
but if you wanted to speak
hypothetically, you know?
So, yeah, they've been trying to [ __ ]
with me for years.
It just goes to show about their lives.
Like I said, I'd say leave them to me,
bro. [ __ ] yeah. You know,
but yeah, they are low lives. That's
what my sister calls them as well. Low lives.
They can't stop the madness, bro.
That's what they can't stop the madness.
Yeah. Come on tomorrow, bro. Come on
tomorrow. I'm going to do a video um
later on about these people anyways and
I won't be reacting to them anymore.
Uh I might not do one this week, bro,
because there's no football playing that
I want to bet on. I want to bet on um
the National League, the Northern National League.
So, they're not playing this week, so
I'll have to do it next week. So, yeah.
Will you be on here again or
I'm going to go live Saturday in the
clubs and [ __ ] So, uh yeah. Yeah, man. The patience
now this channel is just my channel to
go live on, bro. There's not going to be
no going entertaining self-reflectors.
We're not We're not doing that, bro.
We're not We're not doing that anymore.
They've never stopped no one's money, bro.
They will never stop. This is what they're [ __ ]
It's just weird eyes, bro. They're just weird eyes.
You still there, Karen? Mhm.
Oh my god.
Do you want to do you want to join that?
You want me to put a link up?
Yeah. You want me to put the link up? Right.
Let me put up you want to join. Yeah.
Someone else might want to join.
But I won't be entertaining these people
again. bro from from tomorrow lad
go live and that bro more than happy to
talk to people bro I do football and
that bro I'm not [ __ ] entertaining
these little low lives anymore lad you man [ __ ]
You coming, bro?
What the [ __ ]
Yeah. See, this is what I'm saying.
They're fat, ugly, old people. They
ain't got a life, bro. This is glorious.
About to do some work whilst listening
They ain't got a life, bro. Yo.
>> Yo, what's up?
>> [ __ ] all, man. You?
>> Yeah. Nothing, man. I'm just [ __ ]
bored. I was just watching you.
>> They're [ __ ] weirdos on air now, is it?
>> Yeah, especially with the [ __ ] skin
talk. I don't know if you're trolling
me, mate, when you keep talking to me
about how much I get and all this [ __ ]
>> No, why would I be trolling you?
Because, bro, do you know that's all
they talk about, bro? That's what I'm saying.
>> Yeah, man. It's just a [ __ ] saying,
"Oh, I only just [ __ ] join just to say
[ __ ] leave in it." Like leave full time.
What do you mean?
>> I don't know. Delete your channel.
[ __ ] walk, man.
>> Yeah, because they're [ __ ] They're
weirdos in it.
>> Your ass is on [ __ ] standby for some of them. >> Really?
>> It [ __ ] is, bro. You know what I
mean? I mean,
you know what it is? I've come off here
like for [ __ ]
like weeks and then I come back on here
>> and it's the [ __ ] same [ __ ] and I just wish
>> you probably bro come on it will always
be the same [ __ ]
>> and then I just think to myself, oh I
wonder what PJ's up to and then I just
search you and then I'll just cuz I
unfollow you. I unsub whatever it's
[ __ ] called on here
>> and or whatever and then I just think,
"Oh, I wonder what he's up to." And when
I search you, you're live and it's the
same [ __ ] arguments.
>> It's the same, bro. Did you see me? I
was on L's the [ __ ] other day. It's the same.
>> I saw it. I saw it cuz I'm suck to him.
>> That's what I'm saying. It's the same [ __ ]
>> It's the same [ __ ] every day, is it?
>> He can sometimes be normal. Do you know
what I mean? He can sometimes post
>> normal. Bro, the thing is it's like you
join that you join their [ __ ] Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> They don't you join their [ __ ] They
argue with you. Yeah. And then they
[ __ ] put up [ __ ] where they're just
talking over you. So it's just pointless. No.
>> I saw it anyway. He was putting up um
old posts or whatever it is.
>> And and they tell us that we shouldn't
live in the past. This is what I mean.
You're never going to win with these
people, bro. You know.
>> Yeah, I know. But sometimes I think like
I only came on here just because every
time I join it's just like you always
want to talk about money and [ __ ] I
just think to myself, "Oh my god, does
he think I'm flat broke or whatever?"
You know what I mean?
>> They think I'm [ __ ] broke.
>> Yeah. No one's [ __ ] flat broke.
>> They are. Yeah. Except these people.
You know what I'm saying?
>> So, what are you like? You going out on
a drink this week?
>> To be honest with you, I only I only
have a drink at home. Not. That's why
whenever I join
>> I might couple but you know like it's
just one of them things where you know
me PJ I don't join for [ __ ] weeks or sometimes months. >> Yeah.
>> I saw you and [ __ ] was it earlier or
yesterday Monty and you going out here
man that was funny.
>> Yeah. He's a snake is it?
>> He's a [ __ ] rat mate. I know so much
[ __ ] about that guy.
>> You know what I mean?
Oh, do you know about you know PlayStation days?
>> You know about the Discord and that
>> I've heard of it, but I'm not [ __ ] joining it.
>> That's the three great pedos. The P
that's that's where the pedos go. Look at that.
>> Yeah, I'm not [ __ ] joining that [ __ ] man.
>> Yeah, they're pedos. The free pedos.
>> I joined it. I only joined Discord.
my official username like the the
username I don't use on here but
>> my username so and then I hid the
account I don't use this call for
anything else other than that it's just
I don't want to [ __ ] know about it
it's just weird is it lad
>> why did you join Discord man
>> huh I didn't
>> Oh you just said that you joined about
>> No it's just for the pedos Cuz
I mean, man, if you join Discord, you're
going to get [ __ ] ruined, man.
>> Yeah, they're going to get your like
they get people's addresses and [ __ ] in it.
>> Yeah, but they know your address. O,
mate, are you it is it October your
birthday? I I [ __ ] forgot. I know I said 27th.
>> Oh, okay. Cuz I didn't [ __ ] know when
it was. I knew it was October. I know I
sent you the card last year.
>> Yeah. Thanks for the call with it. You
put 20 pound in it in it.
>> Yeah. In it.
>> Yeah. Thank you.
>> You didn't [ __ ] say anything about
it. And you know what? I had a nasty
thought. I thought to myself, did Elaine
need the [ __ ] money or [ __ ] I was
just think cuz you never said anything about it.
>> I'm sure I did. I'm sure I did. >> No,
>> not to me. You didn't. But
>> no, you I definitely did say something.
You just must have not heard it. I definitely did.
>> Okay. Maybe I
>> Bquest had done something like that
before. I I mentioned it, but Barquest
is a snake, ain't it? Do you remember
that bar first?
>> Do you know what? I used to like it when
I first You know what? He he was one of
the first ones.
I joined Lord Jay's and then when I look
join Lord Jays and I followed um I did
follow Shauny Lawn Legs. I admit that
for the first thing and then I followed
Bar Crest because they were into gaming
and all that [ __ ] but then Barress
[ __ ] disappeared. Surely he's a
[ __ ] nons, but seemed all right, but
then he just [ __ ] [ __ ] off. >> Yeah,
>> I don't know whether he's back or not or what.
>> No, he he is he Barquest went he come on
like uh two weeks ago and he and I was
speaking to him on WhatsApp. Yeah. But I
just stopped talking to him, bro, cuz I
remember what he used to do with like
Pat Mustard and [ __ ] in it.
>> Is he still with that um world? No,
>> me. Nah.
He's probably going to want to try to
get with you then. But you're not gay.
You know, he might try to get with you.
>> He going to get with me, mate, cuz he
doesn't [ __ ] know who I am.
>> Bless you, man. Bless you.
>> So, what's going on with you anyway? You good?
>> You good?
>> Are you good or what? What's going on with you?
>> Yeah, I'm good, bro. Just the same old
[ __ ] is it?
>> Honestly, mate. [ __ ] come off this
[ __ ] It's just
>> you know you know the loss of the income
from the house is kind of [ __ ] was kind
of [ __ ] in it.
>> Yeah. Like did did you save money or did
you just [ __ ] spend it?
>> No, I had Yeah, I have a little bit but
I should have a lot more, you know?
>> Give it a couple of months like just
[ __ ] use the bare necessities or
whatever it's [ __ ] called and then just [ __ ]
uh rent out privately or whatever it is.
What do you mean?
>> See, I don't [ __ ] know because where
I live, I own half of the house. I might
be on [ __ ] benefits and all that
[ __ ] but I mean I'm I own half of the
house where I live in. >> M. >> So,
I don't get housing benefit, all that
[ __ ] [ __ ] all of that. But I mean, obviously you
>> Yeah, I'm on I'm on the same amount of
money that you're on now anyways. Yeah,
but you but you um uh I'm not saying
this [ __ ] like a troll, but you're
obviously back with your mom and that's
the council flat or whatever it is, housing association.
So why can't you just [ __ ] save up
and then just go into private rented or whatever?
>> Yeah, but why am I going to do that? How
am I going to be able to save how am I
going to be able to afford it?
>> I don't know. [ __ ] save up for three
or four months or whatever.
>> What? £1,100 a month.
>> You can do it, mate. I've done it. But
then but then I'm [ __ ] used to being
like this. So it doesn't maybe I'm
>> going to be I'm going to be used to it
now as well. It just takes time to get
used to it. You know what I mean?
>> I don't know. Just do other stuff. I
don't know. What were you doing?
>> What? So what do you do like save like
500 a month?
See, with me it's different because I
don't have [ __ ] housing benefit. I
don't have the where I live is
>> I've only got, bro, I've only got um my
phone bill which is cheap and my and my
Xbox which is cheap. But obviously I won
like some football bets like last month
and this month. So it kind of helped a
little bit. come in.
>> Oh, cuz where I live, I mean, my dad
paid out the house. So, I own 50% and my
mom owns 50%. So, if she [ __ ] dies,
whenever she obviously I don't wish up
on her cuz that's my mom. But when she
dies, I'll own 100% of this place and
then so I don't have housing like
>> So, you don't you know, you know when
you said, "Yeah, you got £400." That's
the last you the month though, is it?
>> Yeah, but PJs, you know what it is? Is
when when I get paid, I [ __ ] buy
everything at once,
>> so I'm never short. My my fridge is always full. >> Yeah,
>> you know, like I got everything to go. I
got my Pepsi Maxes, I got my drinks, my
water, and all that [ __ ] So, I've got
my food. I've got my
>> um all my toiletries, whatever you call
it. So, I'm all right. You know what I mean? >> Yeah.
>> And then I have about 300 400 left over.
>> Yeah. I don't have to I don't have to
like pay much. So, I'm I'm all right, you know.
>> Yeah. You're on the same boat as me. So,
surely you've only got about the same
amount left over as me.
>> I would, but obviously I won some
football back since you're here. So,
yeah, I would be. Yeah. face pretty much. Yeah.
>> Unless you don't pay the electric or gas
like I have to.
>> No, I don't pay nothing. If you don't
have it, you
was my mom's birthday, bro. I won a
football bat. I gave her 30 quid. If you
don't have it, you don't have it. But
then you do.
>> Yeah. But the [ __ ]
the D man, electric man don't care about
if you ain't got it. Someone has to
[ __ ] get it. You know what I mean? Yeah.
>> I'm not [ __ ] started. I'm just saying.
>> You know what I'm saying? It's [ __ ] in
it. It's this But you you gamble every
You normally gamble your money though,
don't you? Yeah.
>> Yeah. Who the [ __ ] is this in the
background? It just keeps coming up.
>> How did you win a grand in the booking?
You lucky bastard.
>> Hang on a minute. Why are you skin? Who
the [ __ ] is that?
>> I don't know, bro. So, you want a grand?
You won a grand, didn't you?
>> Hi, Wickham.
Meet me in Ho Wim. I'm not even from
Hickim. What the [ __ ] Wage on your
lonesome. That's either [ __ ] Sean or
one of them lot
>> probably. Yeah,
>> I'm not even reading it. [ __ ] off, man.
>> How did you win a grand?
because I was in the [ __ ] Norfol
because obviously I'm back from all the
places around my area. So I went to Northol and
you would love this. There was a Turkish
bar there, you know.
>> So um I went there and then I went to a
lab at Northol and I got to
>> there's a new game called Huff and Puff.
Have you seen it?
>> No. It sounds familiar though. No, it's
an American slot, but they've only just
released it here. You would have seen
it. It's always on on the [ __ ]
American slot channels.
>> Mm. Yeah.
>> Yeah. So, I got um
I got a jackpot on that. I had to
[ __ ] spend about 80 quid to get the
jackpot. And then I went on to another
game called I don't know if you've heard
of it, Magic [ __ ] Magpie.
>> Yeah, I have.
>> Yeah. And I got about I got a hit on
that and then I went on to the [ __ ]
100 to one roulette
>> key key bet 100 whatever they [ __ ] call it. >> Mhm.
>> And I got a couple of hits on that. So I
was over I was over a grand but then I
kept going until I got to a grand and I
just [ __ ] cashed out a grand you know.
>> Better than nothing. It
>> Yeah. But I didn't really see most of it
cuz I had to [ __ ] owe loads of people
money, you know. So I only saw about [ __ ]
>> 200 or so of it. >> Yeah.
>> You need to pack you need to pack that
[ __ ] gambling in it. >> Yeah.
You know, like that's what anyway. But
it is what it is, my dear.
>> Are you drunk?
No, I'm just looking at this [ __ ]
comment. Why are you
>> Have you been drinking though? Is it
>> earlier on? I was, but I'm not now.
>> You're a bit drunk, isn't it?
>> I'd kick you and your cousin all over.
Is he all about you or me?
>> He's all about you. Yeah.
>> Who's my cousin? I don't have a cousin.
But listen, bro. Um, are you going to
are you going to gamble again this month?
>> Probably not. Why?
>> Just wondering, bro. It's addicting, isn't it?
>> Are you going to go this month?
>> Yeah, you are.
>> You know what I mean?
>> Oh, the football. Yeah.
>> Yeah, the football. Yeah. Do you do like
the non league games like cuz they do
[ __ ] like high goals and all that
>> Yeah, I do. I do. Yeah, I do the
National Northern League. >> Yeah.
>> On Tuesday. On Tuesday, I put 120 on two
teams and it returned 380. So, I won 380,
>> but I was going to put 160 on it, but I
put 40 on the roulette, so I just put
120 on the football.
This guy's a [ __ ] mong. Whoever this
I'm not even going to look at. I'll just
talk to you anyway. Yeah. So, yeah. It's
a hard life, isn't it?
It's not really hard. It's just [ __ ]
life, isn't it?
>> M Why can't we be millionaires in it? We're good.
Millionaires on [ __ ] peasant wages.
>> What do you mean?
>> I don't [ __ ] know. You know what I
mean? I just mean for all benefits all
that [ __ ] It's just it's never going to
[ __ ] be what you want it to be. You
know what I mean?
>> Yeah. Obviously. >> Mhm.
>> I'm going to get off here. But listen,
mate. I want to I wanted to say to you,
just leave this [ __ ] man. Just or just
come back irregularly. You know what I mean? just >> [ __ ]
>> coming back to the [ __ ] same [ __ ] cuz it's boring.
>> Yeah, it's so boring, isn't it? Yeah.
>> I keep, by the way, I keep [ __ ]
unsubscribing from you cuz you keep
saying you're going to leave and then
you come up on the YouTube when I'm
scrolling. So, I don't know
>> what's going on.
>> I will leave, bro. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Anyway, what's going on with you
and Monty? You're now falling out for good.
>> Yeah, man. He's a snake.
>> He always [ __ ] was, mate. I know. I I
can remember him back in PlayStation
when he had B Macan as his profile picture. >> Yeah.
>> Do you remember that? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. There you go.
>> Yeah, I remember cuz Yeah. Yeah. Of
course I do, bro. He's [ __ ]
He's a roller, is it?
>> He tried to [ __ ] say, "Oh, no. I
never had her as a profile picture.
Denny turned around and said, "Yeah, I
did have Meline Mat as a profile
picture, but only just to raise
awareness." Like, "Listen, mate, you're
a nons. [ __ ] off." >> Yeah.
It's just weird, isn't it?
>> Yeah, man. I don't know. Do you get this
all the time when you're live? Like
people in the back chat just [ __ ]
talking to themselves. >> No.
>> Oh, just me then.
>> So like, yeah, you need to stop gambling
though, is it? We need to stop.
>> Yeah, I'm trying, bro, man. I mean, it's
a [ __ ] It's not like I want this.
>> It's hard though, is it?
>> What the [ __ ] You keep inviting me to
your Streamyard on [ __ ] Facebook
>> because you kept inviting me so I
thought I'd invite you to mine.
>> You did that. Did I? [ __ ] I'm live. I'm
live on my own. I've not even fired you once.
>> No. How many days have I got a PJ joining this?
>> I sent you some videos.
>> I said join me.
Oh, Monty, just do what I do. Just
[ __ ] leave this community, man. Cuz
it's never going to change.
>> No, it's all repeating bastards. And Pet
is one of them.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I'm being one of them. I'm
one of them. How am I one of them,
>> man? You repeat every day the same as these. like
yeah but Monty why do I come and
PJ you sit there and join in with the
[ __ ] with them
>> you know why have they been repeating on your chat
>> yeah but they're getting blocked they're
getting blocked you get blocked you
bring up people get blocked
>> blocking but they're always here
whenever I come back maybe they're on
new accounts I don't know
>> my new accounts
>> yeah you just keep blocking That's it.
Don't react to the comments. Don't bring
>> Yeah. Hey, did you see earlier K? I
didn't even block them. I weren't even blocking them.
>> That's the best thing.
>> Just let them embarrass themselves.
>> Just block them. Just block them.
You don't give them a platform or a
panel and if they end up on your plan
panel, you just block them off your
panel and keep them off your panel and
talk about something totally different.
>> Keep typing. Let them keep typing in it.
>> Yeah, but you don't do that PJ. You like
this content. Every time I block them,
how many times they come back?
>> Yeah, but it don't really matter. You
like this content. There's people on
here who actually do want to act like nickname
trying to join. [ __ ] off.
>> Well, let him join. Let him join. What's
he going to say? You know, there's
nothing much for him to say and I'll
come back at him. You know what I mean?
>> It's just the same [ __ ] every [ __ ] day, bro.
>> If it is, okay, put it out this way.
Okay. So, why don't you ensure it don't
like just have it out now in your panel?
You have on your panel. Come on, get the
off and done with and then never bring
them up again.
>> Say, you know what I mean?
>> Me and him will keep out of it. It's
between you and Sean, not me. It's not
between it doesn't mean anything. Do you
know what I mean? You know. Yeah.
>> So, so it's just between you and Sean. I
keep my mouth shut. I'm not getting
involved. It's used to
>> I'm not entertainer. This little weirdo.
>> No. Let him up and have you have it out with him.
>> You know, for a minute he will shut up
and then I can go in on him, you know.
Just let him have his [ __ ] minute.
Then then you won't then you won't have
to bring him up anymore.
>> You know Kieran what he's doing he's
trying to do. Don't you get it?
>> Yeah. Yeah. But this is when you know
what he's doing. Just [ __ ] let him
up. Just let him up. He's he's going to
he's going to be doing this in four
years time. You know what I mean? Just
let him do it.
>> No, bro.
>> Why not?
>> Because the police said I shouldn't do that.
>> Yeah, but he's still doing it. And
you're not taking the screenshots.
I am taking the screenshots. I am taking
the screenshots. I've got about 300
screenshots on my phone, bro.
>> It's only your actions. What will get
you into trouble or get
>> There you go then. So, stop telling me
to let him on cuz you know what you're trying to
>> meaning your actions.
>> Meaning your actions is what you say to
him will get you into trouble.
>> Put the screen up. Put the screen up and
just put him on. He's got nothing to [ __ ] say.
>> No, I don't let my channel.
>> Let let him start the conversation with PJ,
>> you know. No, cuz it's just the same
repeating [ __ ] We've heard it about a million times.
>> Yeah, but I'm sick of I'm sick of
hearing [ __ ] Shy long legs this, Shy
Longlegs that. Can't he go to the police
of you talking about him all the time on
your panel? Of course he can. >> Yeah,
>> you're basically talking about the guy
24/7. Can he go police reply? Yeah, he
can because you're basically talking
about him and bringing him up. Or you
might as well get your little tiffy out
the way with him. >> Nah,
>> I don't think it is, Sean. To be fair,
>> I know what you're trying to do. He's
trying to get the police involved. I'm
smart, Monty. So,
>> it's not about the police, is it?
>> Yeah, it is about the police, Monty.
>> Soon as it fon you've got the proof on
your channel, a you what he's doing.
>> Yeah. They don't care though. That's
what I'm saying.
>> Yeah. And only what you have to do is
just talk normal to Sean and let Sean be
the one that
talk to him. Just stay silent.
>> I've got a court order that says I can't
talk to him. Do you understand?
>> So why aren't you recording all of this
and then going to do
>> I am I've done that a million times. I
have done that.
>> Well then he's breaking a [ __ ] court
order then and then you
>> you know what I'm saying? I have broke
Kieran. I've got a fold of everything he
has done. Kieran, Kieran, I've got a
folder of everything he has done and I
have sent it to the police.
>> BJ's already broke his co owner by
talking about Sean bringing him up in compensation.
>> No, it's not not necessarily I haven't
mentioned his name and I've not contacted
>> you. You've been mentioning his name.
I've not mentioned his name.
>> RKP you've been talking about Sean 24/7.
>> When when did I say his name? and he
been bringing up.
>> When was the last time I said his name
and contacted him? There you go.
>> But you've always whenever I come in
your chat, you always hint at him or
>> hints. That's different. Yeah, that's a hint.
>> Yeah, but it's still the same [ __ ]
No, it's not the same. No, it's not the
same because it is because it is not the same.
>> No, it's not the same thing.
>> Because it is because he knows what what
you on about. He knows you about. He has
to prove that to the police and he can't.
>> If the police will even prove he is you
all about him.
>> Stop trying to be a snake. You What is
wrong with you? I don't get why you do this.
>> I'm not I'm not being a snake. I'm just
>> You know what he's doing. You know what
he's going to do. So why are you like I
don't get it.
>> He's almost
grass in it. But he's already [ __ ] three times.
>> But if you let him up and then he's
greased it that means the car will get dropped.
You don't get it. He's the one who's
briefing the court order. Not me you.
He's the one who's preaching it. So I
let him look.
>> Yeah. Listen PJ, let him on and I will
screen record. I've got the screen
recorder button going now. Just let him go on.
>> He's basically he's basically the reason
he's reaching it. Not you. He is. I'm
talking to you.
I've got the screen recording going.
Just let him on. Let's say and I'll send
it to you and then he's [ __ ]
>> Just kidding. >> Okay.
>> No, I'm not I'm not trusting it, bro.
>> Trust it. He's He's breaching. He's He's
breaching it either way. Either way,
he's breaching it.
>> You know what I mean?
So I would let him up and let him brea
[ __ ] either way.
>> Money's a snake, bro. Money's a snake.
>> I'm a chatting [ __ ]
>> Go on your let him up on your panel then.
>> I'm not letting him up on my panel. He
don't really talk about me like you.
>> I don't talk very. I know he's too
faced. I know it.
>> I'm too [ __ ] I'm all too faced. I'm
being too faced. I'm telling you the
facts what you want to hear and you're
not taking it.
>> If he comes up on the channel, he can
get in [ __ ] for that and that's your cer.
>> You think that's me being too faced? >> Uh,
>> okay. PJ Natalie,
do you know do you know if Sean and PJ
are going to court yet? Right.
And Sean's not allowed to speak to PJ,
but if PJ lets him up on the panel,
think Shan piece on that.
And don't that mean that PJ won't could
get off with it or that see
you don't understand
>> I'm not chatting no [ __ ]
>> mate she's a she's asleep mate why you
why are you talking to her whoever
you were just [ __ ] chatting to
Natalie or Kaye Emma Mitchell or whoever
it is You
>> what you want about it's not you I'm
talking about you come on who I'm with
you right there who I'm with
>> I don't know whichever fat [ __ ] you're
with this week. I don't [ __ ] know mate.
>> What bird are you with?
>> I'm not with the [ __ ] fat [ __ ] with the black.
>> Obviously you ain't got a bird. Have you
not self rightly?
>> Why don't you go with your comp?
>> I don't like you. I never did.
>> Yeah, I don't like you. I've never liked
you. Who is it, man?
>> Who is it? [ __ ] off.
>> It's all man. You sound like joking dick.
>> You're a [ __ ] [ __ ] mate. Just [ __ ] off.
>> You You You need a [ __ ] ball before I
can get laid like PJ does.
>> You're a [ __ ] prick. Kaye, Emma, Kirsty.
>> I've never been out with Emma. Yeah, do
things with Kirsty, but not Emma.
>> Dirty little [ __ ]
now. [ __ ] off and get
>> Listen, listen. The weirdo is you. The
>> You and Fat Dan, Nippity City. I know
all about you, mate. I know he's got I
know he's got and right there
>> in the PlayStation chat room.
>> Well, they used to call the [ __ ] out of
fat down on PlayStation. You sad
>> you were in there.
>> Yes, I did. Yes, I did. Oh, taking a
piss out of fat down cuz she had a
vagina on the wall when I used to say
[ __ ] Yeah, we're taking a piss out of fat dad.
Yes, I was. Yes, I was. Someone's bullying bad.
>> Why don't you clown city?
>> I know you
dirty bastard. You will go down fat dance vagina.
>> You [ __ ] you bully man. I b you man like
you playation. So you want to talk about
fat dance vagina? Yeah. What would you
do to fat?
Would you go down?
You little prick. Now [ __ ] off. Would
you go down? Would you like something in
your face? Yeah.
>> You met PJ when he was 14? You met Shy
when he was 14.
>> I've never met Sean. I've never met
Sean. I've met PJ but not when I was 14.
>> PJ, when did I meet you? How old was you
when I met you?
>> Yeah, he was 14.
>> Not in person.
>> You're 14. Just ask
>> in person. PJ in person. Not
PlayStation. In person. >> 23.
>> Well, there you go, lad. He was like
sweaters when I met him. >> [ __ ]
>> No. This guy thinking he knows me. So, go on.
>> How old are you when you started
chatting to him? When you were trying to say,
>> "The man's a man. The man's a lad. He's
a lad. I'm not here, lad. What are you
trying to say?
>> I'm going to say the [ __ ] out. When I
see you, you little prick. more
dig [ __ ] head in as well.
>> What? What are your women Peter? Are you
about women do you?
>> Yeah, I will. Natalie, I'll make an
exception of and then I'll do it in
front of you and you'll do [ __ ] all you
jealousy. A lot of jealousy kicking in.
>> Jealousy of what? Of
>> jealous of what you jealous of of your ugliness
>> of an unwashed [ __ ] Now [ __ ] off.
>> Unwashed [ __ ] That [ __ ] is nice and
tasty and it's washed every night
actually every day.
>> Oh god. Talk about ripe, mate. Talk about ripe. >> Too.
>> Oh my them piss flops right out. Even
when it tastes like piss. It's nice. Tastes nice. >> Yeah.
>> Oat. You fat [ __ ] [ __ ] What's your
>> It's not the best you got. That's repeating.
>> Who's repeating?
>> You've got a woman. [ __ ]
>> Cuz that's only what they can bring is repeat.
>> Yeah. Your dick was glowing green, mate.
And you boasted about it. What the [ __ ]
>> Yeah, I know. Do I see it? It's still green.
>> Yeah. Look at you. You're You're a
[ __ ] match made in hell, mate.
[ __ ] get on with it.
>> We are. Oh boy, we do know what you got
that in one. We are matching now.
>> Yeah, I'll get with Kaye and make your
[ __ ] kids my [ __ ] daughters, mate.
Yeah. What are you going to do about that?
>> I'm kids. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Don't call me daddy. And what are
you going to do about that?
>> Who would want to call you daddy? You're ugly.
>> Lo call me daddy. Yeah,
>> never call you daddy. You're too ugly.
You're a dirty [ __ ] boulder.
>> You were naunt. You were nons. You just
sat there and just basically told me
that could have called you daddy and l
is only six. You're announce mate. Yeah, you're nons.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Me and Christie. Yeah,
you got that right. Emma, you want me to
go to Libby City files? Do you want me
to get it out?
>> Liberty City. Oh my god. At Liberty
Oh my god. You go and get all the files out.
>> Yeah. Liberty City. When you were
I was sending Pu
ago women pictures.
Women. Women. PJ will even tell you that. >> Google
sent you on Google search. [ __ ] kids.
DJ will even tell you that. >> Huh?
>> No. When they used to get pictures of
off all the women on PlayStation back in the day.
>> Oh my god. He's just admitted it. You're
a dirty man at me. That were [ __ ]
years and years ago that that's what I
mean. You're building something what was
[ __ ] years and years and years and years ago.
>> You were [ __ ] single. But I was
always ready to mingle.
View was always there. Some jealousy is
through people in it. Did you see
Timmy's videos earlier?
>> No. Oh, PJ, I'll talk to you in a
minute. Let me just deal with this kind
of Oh, wait. Liberty City with whatever
you want. Yeah. Go to Liberty City.
>> He made you search for [ __ ] kid porn
and you went and
>> did he [ __ ] No. Did he [ __ ] make me go
search from America? [ __ ] yeah from
America is it?
>> Did he [ __ ] used to you are you used to
sending pictures of [ __ ] women off
[ __ ] PlayStations or what the [ __ ]
are you on about?
>> Is isn't that that guy from America though?
>> Yeah. Yeah. You used to [ __ ] give me
trophies for go and get women naked on PlayStation.
But I don't know what this guy's on
about. Kitty porn.
>> Yes, you [ __ ] did.
>> I don't know what you're on about kitty
porn. He was [ __ ] station
but would never [ __ ] that [ __ ]
what you're saying. Yes, it is.
>> Liar, mate. You're a liar.
>> My kids [ __ ] life. She prick. I don't
need to lie on my kids. Stole of her
piggy bank. It means nothing.
>> Piggy bank means Oh my god. Is it a clown?
>> You stole her pocket.
>> I [ __ ] diesel. Oh no. I got rid of
him, didn't I?
>> Yeah, you did. So that doesn't mean
anything either. You
>> my mean everything to me. You [ __ ]
clown. So you can sit there and make up
any excuse you want. You look
>> even like my mom likes me.
>> So if I'm all the If I'm all these and
all that, why am I allowed to see my
kids? Don't make sense now, does it?
>> She has two.
>> One more thing. One more thing. DBS
check. So that's another one.
>> You're a [ __ ]
>> So we can keep playing these little
games if you want.
>> Yeah. And I will win all cuz you don't
know anything about me. I know about
him. You don't know nothing about me.
You just just got bare [ __ ] What
you just seen on the internet? What
people have just bought? Oh, random [ __ ]
>> 13. And listen, mate, I don't even like
Shauny Longlegs, but he's got everything
about you down long legs. Shy Long Legs
go [ __ ] all on me. Shauny Longlegs. He M
Taylor as he's the one who would doing
[ __ ] with him and make sure put that
[ __ ] on me. You
>> just want to groom him into doing your
[ __ ] You know what I mean? Oh, I've
never tried making Sean do anything for
me. Are you sad? Why would they get that
little weasel to do anything for me on PlayStation?
>> You're a liar.
>> Are you [ __ ] real liar? I swear I've
never been m Sean on PlayStation. He's
the biggest nons.
>> You're a liar.
>> He's the biggest nons on PlayStation.
PJ will even b me up on this one. DJ did
I did I show him when he was
>> he was going to say 15 but you were he
was 14 when you met
>> oh my god I met Sean through [ __ ] Dean Dean by
jumped in and tried to save him PJ
Listen PJ I'm not your fault
>> you know pedophile back on PlayStation.
I'm going out with a girl called
11y old girl called Tiff. I mean Beth Beth.
>> Come on, man. Sort yourself out. You
know absolutely nothing. You b me.
>> You don't even know me, Monty. But I know you
>> and I know you. And I know you. You're abuser.
>> No, you don't know me. That's the thing.
>> EJ, who is this?
This guy, what's his YouTube name? >> Ken.
>> No, he doesn't know. Listen, PJ, I like
you, but I'm on some throwaway account
here that's going to get deleted after
bits. He Listen, PJ knows me, but he
doesn't know me at the same [ __ ]
time. Listen, Monty, I know you.
>> Well, you don't know me. So, what's my
full name then? Yeah, if you know me,
what was my YouTube? What was my PlayStation?
Obviously, not YouTube. So, what was my
PlayStation name back in the day? Like,
>> was it Sir Ramlot or whatever? It's [ __ ] war.
>> What was my one? So, what was my other
one then? What? I used to talk to Sha on then.
>> I didn't talk to [ __ ]
>> No, no, no. Go on. Go on. So, what was
my other one before went on a lot?
>> Go on.
>> You say you normally Well, so what was
my two accounts? I had another two. Go
on. Which one was it? Oh, throw away
a lot now. Who was that? Because more
account. So, which one was it?
>> Listen, I don't even like Sha, but he
was 14 years.
>> I'm asking you which account was it? I'm
asking you a question. Which account was
you talking to?
>> You were talking to Shauny when he was
14 years old and you were 21 years old.
>> One Sean's alive anyway. So what was I
talking to Sean? I was never Sean's
mate. Do you get that for your [ __ ] head?
>> You were [ __ ] then he turned on.
>> Oh my god. I've never been Sean's mate.
You [ __ ] clown.
>> [ __ ] why? He just didn't like I'm not
denying because I've never been his mate.
>> No, but you know sat on his [ __ ] sat
on his bed all day with his lly
all over his wall. Do you think I've
been mates with someone like that? Are
you sure about that?
>> Elvis Presley. Yeah. Come on, man. I've
been with someone like that. Someone who
got bullied off his whole mom and staff
to death. Yeah.
>> Yeah, he did. He did.
>> But he knew what you were like.
>> Sean's a little weirdo on you on
PlayStation. Freak on PlayStation.
>> He's a [ __ ] freak on PlayStation, you
sad man. I've had nothing to do with
Sean on PlayStation at all. Nothing at
>> I thought you're a liar. You I'm not
lying. I am not lying.
>> I am not lying. I ain't got nothing to
lie about. I'm not sitting with you
saying that I was mates with a lot of
nons like Sean.
>> Oh my god. PJ, if that Sean is waiting
in the background, let him come on. Just let him.
>> I don't know if he is in the background or not.
>> I can't let him on. Sorry, man.
>> Oh, let him up, man. Let's let you PlayStation
talking to him. You're talking to me,
you little freak.
>> Listen, you little prick. I want to
[ __ ] stab you in the face. You're
>> talking to me. You can't even stab
yourself. You [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> If it's not him, just boot him.
>> You're not allowed to say my name. Big news.
That's not him.
>> I see a letter anywhere. Yeah. Yeah. You
enter his little freak. Yeah. You making
all these little excuses up with you.
Yeah. Because I would never be
>> When Jamie When Jamie introduced me to
Britney, I was 15 and I met him from the brand.
>> Don't get [ __ ] Shauny in here, man.
>> You see what I mean? This is why I'm
for [ __ ] sakes. It's
>> [ __ ] weird as [ __ ]
is not allowed to say my name.
>> Oh, Sean, sort yourself out, you little ner.
And we both know that, don't we?
>> We both know that, man. M. We both know
you went out with MMO, don't we, Sean?
in a chat room with Emma when she was 13.
>> Definitely not. Definitely not.
>> Yes, she did. You
>> can make these excuses. She knows a lot of excuses. Listen,
she's the same age as me.
>> That's another one. Yeah, he's right.
Whoever that I think that's Tram, but
whoever that is.
>> No, it's not. It's not. It's not. never
even two months older than me. Her
birthday is in December.
Most [ __ ] is
>> skin virgin with the disabled.
>> She was 15 years of age and he was
dating her online dating.
None of this even happened and you know
why. You know why listen
>> 2010? You pedophile bastard.
>> It's pretty funny. You know the dates
perfectly on time and all that lot in it.
>> Ain't it? I'm going to [ __ ]
>> It's funny that I'm not [ __ ] not
allowed to say my name.
>> I'm actually laughing at all this [ __ ]
>> Imagine being in a bed at 31 with no bed
s masturbating over
>> right now with my woman. We're both naked.
>> What? What?
Man, you went out with actual [ __ ]
kid on PlayStation. Britney. Yeah. True.
True. You introduced
[ __ ] No one introduce you to
>> No, no, no. I didn't introduce you to
get laid, son.
>> You're going to die of virgin if you
keep on like
say my name big nose and I will be
seeing you in court in 3 years.
>> Go get your virginity,
>> mate. You just mate, you just added the
[ __ ] wrong Shauny. That was Tramodo. I think
>> it's not trading [Applause]
idiot. I'm not Todd.
>> It's not Tramodol.
>> I'm Sean.
>> No, I don't think you are. But I don't
>> It is.
He's not allowed to say my name ever. If
he says my name, the police will come
knocking on his door and they will slap his bum.
>> Go get laid, you little virgin. Go get
some money, skin bastard. Go get
yourself some money.
>> You skinned bastard with fat ugly
girlfriend. Can't get laid. No. I just
can't even come back.
>> I just showed £13,000. You [ __ ]
won a casino with your mom. Try to tell
people that they live with their mom and
you're in a shitty little bedsit with no
bed in it. You skin bastard. I'd rather
live with my mom or my dad than live like you.
>> Get it right.
>> I'd rather live with mom than live in a
bed like you [ __ ] able to afford to live in
>> a shitty bed suit with no bed on a
virgin [ __ ] flat. [ __ ] no money.
>> No 20 no money to your [ __ ] name.
>> You punk bastard with no money. I don't
think that's Shy, mate.
>> You have a big news.
>> I think that's Tramodol.
>> It's not Tramodol. It's the [ __ ]
virgin with no money.
>> You have a big [ __ ] nose
>> and you've got an ugly rat face and you
got no teeth and you have to date a
disabled girl who's fat and ugly.
>> Isn't it funny how big nose about you
make big nose? Isn't it funny how
[ __ ] big no they've had to resort to
a disabled fat girl like you?
>> Isn't that funny?
Disabled fat with no money.
>> Oh my god. Look at that rat face. >> What?
>> Just just cutting Mark. That isn't Shauny. I a Kieran.
>> Oh my god. Go on.
>> It is Kieran, lad.
>> Is he gone?
>> Mate, that was Todd Doll.
>> It wasn't Tramodol.
>> Oh my god. You're another kitty, man.
This is what This is what I used to go
through with Kitty all the time. Like
people will come on with fake accents.
You believe it was. It doesn't matter.
Anyway, where's Monty? Is he gone?
>> I'm I'm going tell him to come back.
Is it going to come back? Cuz obviously
with what I just said.
>> It's not funny, is it?
>> It can be funny at times. >> Really? >> Yeah. Well,
it's give and take, can it? We all get
it and we all have to receive it. You
know what I mean?
>> Yeah. You like this community, though.
Look. Oh [ __ ] Oh [ __ ]
If you want me to my face if you want to
listen. Yeah. If you don't see me Yeah.
for a couple of days and stuff. Don't
>> want to keep going on because
>> listen listen. When you don't see me on
here for a little bit. Yeah. Don't try
to get me back on it. I'm just sick of
>> Listen. You're the one who keeps on
texting me to come up on your panel.
It's just the repeating [ __ ] Monty. I
can't do it anymore.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'm going to stop the
repeating. Yeah. If you think about
being out with Emma, make sure Yeah.
Give her a text. Yeah.
>> No, I never repeating.
>> Ask her. Text her if you want.
>> Ask her. Have you been out with her?
>> Done with my life.
>> No, no, no, no, no. You put these
allegations up, so go and prove it. I
have no go and text now. Go face the
camera on and give her give her a text.
>> Go on, mate.
>> If I ask her about Taylor when you're
right as well. Yeah.
>> Yeah. I know what Mark Taylor did. I
know what he did to Kirsty Mitch.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So, so, so you know then.
Yeah. So, so, so you know that I was
going out with Em Well, not going out
with but doing things with. Yeah. Not
Emmy. Yeah. You need to get your story
right because that was my turn. They
were doing [ __ ] with um MMA. I doing
school. I [ __ ]
>> So get yourself get get your stories right. Yeah.
>> I'm going to get a horse whip and
[ __ ] whip you.
>> Listen, I love that kinky [ __ ] Yeah.
Listen, I can show you a video of that
whipping me right now. I can get her to
rip whip me now if you want me to.
>> I know she does. She
>> listen whipping [ __ ] Excuse me, man.
>> You all the time, mate.
>> Listen. Listen. You're a little cop on
YouTube. Yeah. You got no proof or
nothing. Text her. Yeah.
Yeah, do me a favor.
>> Yeah, you text her.
>> I can say you little freak.
>> Why did I text that [ __ ] No, no, no.
Why? Why? Cuz you're putting the
allegation there. Get your assigation
there that me and them doing stuff and
not being out. So, I never said
I never said I never said that. Monty, I
never said that. You're repeating. I
said that they're repeating. They always
repeat. They always bring up make sure
like I've done stuff with her. They go
and ask you where they think do
something. I don't know why you put on
the same me when you said that I run off
because of all this [ __ ] you bring up.
All this [ __ ] you bring up is [ __ ]
So give her a text.
>> You go on the why this allegation on me.
Yeah. Is because I put the allegation on
Sean going out with the actual kid on PlayStation.
No, you did that. But he had
do any of that [ __ ] They should get
you sorry straight because you know you
just you just hear this and that's it.
And you watch little videos and you just
said, "Oh, that's it. That's it." And
that's it. That's what you're doing.
You know, [ __ ] all. You just put story
to story. That's it. [ __ ] all.
Why don't you be a man and find out the
story and text them and then you find
out a little bit more with them, won't you?
>> Listen, I'm going to [ __ ] horse whip
you, mate. If I ever [ __ ] see you
your face around here, mate. But you won't. So,
tell me where you where you live. Impulse,
>> come to [ __ ] Listen, come to Hephro
airport and I I'll guide you at the
airport. You're not [ __ ] strand [ __ ]
out of you now. [ __ ] off. Listen, I'll
put you in a suitcase and send you to
Africa, you dick.
>> No, you [ __ ] won't, mate. I'll traffic you.
>> I'll send you to Africa to all the poor
country, you bastard.
>> I'll feed you to lion suitcase. >> Yeah.
>> Where do you find this clown?
>> Yeah, let me talk [ __ ] cuz he keeps
over talking me and I'm trying to
[ __ ] talk. Yeah, cuz you're not
you're nothing. You're just not on
YouTube. That's it.
>> No, you did this to Shaie and I don't
even like [ __ ] Shy, but you do this
to I don't do this to Sha on YouTube.
>> Shorty. Oh my god.
You Sean, what you shag him? Because
you're going on about him. >> Shy
PJ goes on about Sean.
That's how to get into Listen PJ in
future if he ever goes silent. Just say shorty.
He just [ __ ] talk.
>> Hey Monty, that's Hey Monty, that's
another thing. Yeah, you say that you're
not too faced, but Bomb's back and you
don't defend me against Bomb. >> Yeah.
>> Oh, PJ. Was that Bomb?
>> Yeah, it's Bomb. Bomb's back.
>> Yeah, I think that was him. But
>> yeah, well, good for you with Bomb's
back. I'm happy Bob's back is no one
ever leaves YouTube to be honest with
you. You got Bob's back. Bob doesn't
even like you, Monty. What?
>> No. Look, listen. Listen. Please tell me
something I don't know.
>> You just got another [ __ ] troll. And you
>> I know. I know. But good because it's
another troll for PJ. What's back in it?
So, I'm not bothered. It's another Why
does bomb Why does Bomb troll every day?
I'm not bringing B or PJ. So you could
talk about B.
>> Yeah. By the way, PJ, that [ __ ] money
was gambling money. I don't give a [ __ ]
That that money will be lost in a few days.
>> Obviously, bro, that's what they do.
They gamble their benefit money and show they >> win.
>> Oh, listen. Shut up. Money. You don't
gamble. [ __ ] off.
>> I don't like gambling. It's for [ __ ]
>> No, you're [ __ ] That's all. That's
all. Gamblers are [ __ ] Gamblers.
>> Yeah, gamblers is virgin. So
is your friend?
>> PJ, is this guy a virgin? He sounds like one.
>> Your friend.
>> No, this guy's broken angry with life.
You know, he is a virgin. You know
broken into yet.
>> Was people calling you skin on your panel?
>> No, not really. Cuz that [ __ ] don't
affect me PJ like it affects you.
>> No, it doesn't affect me. They're just
self- actors. It doesn't affect me.
>> Yeah, I'm sick of fairing skin to be
honest with you.
>> That's all. Yeah, but that's all they bring up.
>> O Monty, put Natly on. Put Lately on. We
talk to her.
>> Why does not they want to speak to you?
>> Cuz I've got a few [ __ ] home truths
to tell her.
>> What's the home truth?
about her [ __ ] black [ __ ] that she
needs to [ __ ] wash out. Here then >> concerned.
>> Are you looking it?
>> Why you so concerned?
>> Why don't you [ __ ] wash your [ __ ]
black [ __ ] man? >> Please.
>> You're a dirty [ __ ] [ __ ] mate. You
know, wash your [ __ ] [ __ ] out.
>> You was watching it happily. No. Shut
the [ __ ] up.
>> I'll kick your [ __ ] head in, mate.
Yeah, you're not a [ __ ] woman. You're
a beast. Shut up.
>> Yeah, they say kicking in there. You
ain't got me just another woman hater
because he's probably been rejected.
>> No, PG.
>> No one's been rejected more than you. No
>> I don't even like LT, but you rejected
by loads of women.
>> No one's been rejected more than you, Monty. >> Well, You [Music]
lied about raping you. You lied about on YouTube
>> and I'm off to sleep in a minute.
>> Yeah, we are.
>> Let them be lonely.
Go to sleep or I'll put you to [ __ ]
sleep. You [ __ ] You dirty [ __ ]
[ __ ] The [ __ ] you come out with about me.
>> Is that all you can say? >> Charming
your [ __ ] face and put you to sleep. You dirty
>> [ __ ] charming.
>> You told everyone that someone raped you
and they didn't rape you. You're a [ __ ] liar.
>> See on about now.
>> LT told your mom that LT raped you and
LT hasn't even [ __ ] met you. I don't
even like LT, but you [ __ ] You're a
sicko. You're a [ __ ]
>> How the Lord Molly is
>> them words come out my mouth. Did you
hear me say them words?
>> Yes, I did. Through your mother. Your
mother is your representation.
>> Okay. Okay. You never heard them from me. Okay.
>> Exactly. It's a weird one. It just goes
off other people's heads and stories and
[ __ ] like that. They go call out.
>> I know. When you start telling it's like
you don't know [ __ ] out with your mother.
>> Yes, he is.
>> [ __ ] [ __ ] Have you had it out with her yet?
>> You're a weird one. Had you?
>> I know. He's got Kate, hasn't he?
>> It's not. It's just weird words. Really?
Just [ __ ] put yourself down there.
>> Oh my god. I'm talking and these [ __ ]
are saying they don't hear me. Are they?
>> We do hear you.
>> Yeah, you're fine. You're just talking weirdies.
>> No, because you're over me, you little
prick. I'm saying, have you spoke to
your [ __ ] mother about the allegation she's made?
>> Never you mind
[ __ ] have. And she was clearly
telling the truth. Now, [ __ ] talking.
>> What did you say? Sorry. We're talking over here.
>> Yeah, of course you were. I said go to
sleep or I'll put you to [ __ ] sleep
now. [ __ ] off.
>> You can't even put yourself to sleep. I
think you're putting yourself to sleep
with your own sayings, you clown.
>> Oh yeah. Where's Kay these days? Where's
the mother of your [ __ ] kids?
>> Oh, she's shaking rice these days, ain't she?
>> Yeah. What do you tell your daughter?
What do you tell your daughters?
>> Well, he's on the [ __ ] coat.
>> No, it's a lot of [ __ ] hair in it.
That's what it is.
>> I bet you bring the daughters. I bet you
bring that Lola and Primark around and
you [ __ ] show Natalie and they're
like, "Nanny, nanny, nanny, I want to go
home. You're a [ __ ] punk, mate.
You're a dead beat. You're a [ __ ]
dead beat. Go away.
>> You're a dead beat.
>> You don't know me. [ __ ]
>> pissed off.
>> If I'm a dead beat, why am I s with a woman?
>> Oh my god. He doesn't even know what the
meaning of dead beat means.
>> PJ, you know what I mean? I mean, it's
like to a fit dog like go fetch and they
don't [ __ ] fetch. You know what I mean?
>> Is a bit like Timmy in a way.
>> He's a horrible piece of [ __ ] Well,
he's nothing. He's just a weasel. He's
not making no sense to me. It's [ __ ]
coming out of his mouth.
>> That's it.
>> Yeah. He's a bit like Timmy.
>> Allowing I'm getting laid. I see you later. Yeah.
>> I'd rather not get laid and get laid
with that. But yeah, >> anyone.
>> That's all you That's all you can get.
>> Go by. Go. [ __ ] off. Delete him, man.
>> That's all you can get. you [ __ ] months.
>> I'm going to go in a minute, PJ, but I
want to talk to you before I just want
him to go and then I'll talk to you.
>> He's not to say just delete him.
>> Yeah, he's gone. He's gone. He's gone.
>> Yeah. Oh, mate. Just delete this [ __ ] I
can't even believe I got [ __ ] dragged
back into this.
>> I can't believe I did, bro. It's his
little [ __ ] weasels, isn't it?
And also, by the way, I do think that
was Shaunie in the background. It was It
>> No, no, no. The one called I'm not I'm
going to only say it once. Don't [ __ ]
shoot the messenger. The one called skin
big nose. Just ignore it. He's got a big
nose anyway. He's a Jew. So,
>> he's ugly, but he's got an ugly rat face
and he is skint as well.
>> Yeah, they're just self-reflectors. Just
leave them to it, bro.
Everything. Oh, by the way, PJ,
everything I said about Monty, you know
deep down what I said was [ __ ] true.
>> But you knew him on PlayStation. Yeah,
>> I didn't know you. That's the weird
[ __ ] thing. I didn't know [ __ ]
Shauny, but I knew Shauny had said that
he got [ __ ]
I'm not trolling.
>> Cases do. These people here are really weird, bro.
>> I I remember Shaunie said that his
mother wouldn't pay the [ __ ] internet
bill. So I don't maybe I did see him but
I don't remember him.
>> It is him, bro. It is him.
>> I remember [ __ ]
Monty. I remember [ __ ] Fat Dan. I
remember all of them.
>> And that's how
I found Lord Jay's community by
accident. And then when I saw [ __ ]
Monty, I thought, "Oh my god, I know
him." And that's how I [ __ ] got
dragged into all of this [ __ ] And then
everyone was going on you. So, I went on
to your channel and well, we got on and
then the [ __ ]
>> and that was that. You know, I don't
care if people call me an incel cuz I
know I'm not an incel cuz I shag [ __ ]
brasses. So, I don't care what people say.
>> Well, you bang their schools.
>> Yeah. Well, it's either that or my
[ __ ] sock, mate.
>> Yeah, pretty much. Yeah, I do it as well.
You know what I'm [ __ ] saying? So
that's how I found all this. But I know [ __ ]
>> That's what I'm doing. I need to come
off this shitty community, is it? It's a
[ __ ] It's a weird community, bro. It's a weird community.
>> I told you [ __ ] ago, don't bring me
into this [ __ ] And then I ended up
getting into this [ __ ] again.
And then I knew by when you added Monty,
I was trying to be nice, but I can't
[ __ ] do it.
>> At some point, I'm going to [ __ ] say
what I think. You know what I mean?
>> Yeah. This is a shitty community though, is it?
>> Yeah, it's Oh, by the way, it's nearly
1:00 and this is my [ __ ] bedtime. So,
I'm going to go in a minute, but
>> All right, bro.
>> Listen, sorry to bring [ __ ] to your
[ __ ] stream. And
>> why do these people call me skin seaside
dark? I think it's because they're skin,
isn't it, Kieran? >> Yeah.
>> No, seriously.
>> Hang on a minute. Kieran any uh I'm just
going to go on the first comment. Kieran any
>> he was in the [ __ ] play the the chat
rooms on PlayStation. Listen PJ, you
must remember [ __ ] Fat Dan and Monty
on the play in the play room.
>> Yeah, of course I do.
>> Yeah. And they were in there for and it
wasn't for a [ __ ] week and it wasn't
for [ __ ] two weeks. I'm talking about
[ __ ] M when you're joining [ __ ]
play and leaving and I remember him because
I can't even hear it [ __ ] go going
into it but I remember that [ __ ] Monty
[ __ ] perving on American [ __ ]
teenagers and [ __ ] like that.
>> Shaunie was the same as well with that
Britney but that came later when once
Jamie had [ __ ] initiated initiated
him or whatever they call it. M
>> you know this [ __ ] You know what I'm
saying is true.
>> True, PJ. I know you don't want to get
involved in it, but you know what?
>> You know if I was to [ __ ] put Why are
you up to a lying machine now? You know
I'm telling the truth.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Obviously
>> I sometimes feel like [ __ ] making a
[ __ ] channel up and just a fake
throwaway channel. just [ __ ] saying
everything and then just changing the
password and deleting the [ __ ]
channel. Then everyone can see it
forever cuz I've got so much [ __ ]
[ __ ] to say about Monty and and I've let
it go. I've let it go cuz everyone's
like thinking, "Oh yeah, he's harmless.
He's harmless." He's not [ __ ]
>> He's a [ __ ] beast, mate. He's a [ __ ] beast.
>> And that Mark Taylor is as well, but he
doesn't he stopped [ __ ] replying to
me. He doesn't acknowledes
as well. I I'd say he's probably the the
least the worst of him. Even though he
is a [ __ ] N himself, especially with
that [ __ ] Downey. He's [ __ ] pumpkin.
>> Do you remember when he was messaging
USA? Is he Kieran trying to get her knickers?
>> Yeah, she blocked him though, didn't she?
>> Yeah. You thought it was funny, isn't it?
>> Was it USA or was it that New Zealand [ __ ]
>> No. No. It was both. He done both. He
done it to both of them. Yeah, he did.
You remember the New Zealand once said
he said he came off as strange, so I blocked him.
>> And then he blocked Denny kept [ __ ]
messaging the American woman, but she
doesn't apparently she didn't answer her
messages all the time. So when she
checked it was about 30 messages and she
went, "That's a weirdo." And she blocked him.
>> You remember that?
>> I remember that. Yeah. I remember in
America once and said he he kept [ __ ]
replying to it. He kept [ __ ]
messaging and [ __ ]
>> You you had a crush on her.
>> I liked her picture until you [ __ ]
till I went and deep searched her and
then I just thought, "Okay, that's
another [ __ ] filtered catfish." >> Yeah.
>> Who was that [ __ ] American dude that
kept [ __ ] replying to you?
>> That's her ex. her ex.
>> Yeah. And then you had Charles who said
he was going to ragd doll you. But who
was that [ __ ] guy who kept saying he was trying
>> on her ex? That damn her ex.
>> Oh yeah. He was trying to mock the English.
>> Yeah. I was telling him about himself.
>> Yeah. Didn't he reply recently or something?
>> Yeah. He said you need He said to me
that I need God. He said you need God, little man.
>> Yeah. I don't [ __ ] know. But anyway,
I'm going to get off here cuz when I go
to [ __ ] Ben, I didn't expect it to go
on as long as it did.
>> All right, guy. See you in a bit.
>> Uh, probably see you in another about
[ __ ] 3 months or so. Anyway, anyway.
>> Yeah. See if anything's changed on here in it.
>> It won't change. It won't [ __ ] Every
time you I come back on here and you
bring it, it just starts again.
>> I start out all day and then about two
days later, what the [ __ ] have I come
back on to? >> Yeah.
Yeah, just listen mate. Just take a
[ __ ] week's break off it, you know.
>> Yeah, it's the same [ __ ] is it?
>> It will never change, in it, right? I
need to have a quick shower, mate,
before my Byes.
Oh, I'm back. Sorry about that, mate.
Had a shower. Yeah. Oh, lovely.
Lovely matey. A shower.
I have to have a shower before bed, you know.
Oh, you're a big virgin. You know, he's
He's a big virgin. Yes.
My eyes are a big
No, he's a he's a big virgin.
He's a big He's a big virgin, you know.
a big virgin. He's a big virgin, you know.
Big Be a big virgin.
Yeah, I'm coming off the [ __ ] after
today. It's [ __ ] weird.
Yeah, this community is very weird. Yeah.
What's day tomorrow? Wednesday. It feels
like Wednesday today. [ __ ] hell.
Oh, what? You're a big virgin. You know
you're a big virgin.
What the [ __ ]
What is that?
You're a big big big virgin.
>> You're not allowed to say my name and
you're most certainly not going to put
any pictures up of me.
>> Big big big virgin you are.
>> I'm in bed with my girlfriend. We're both naked.
>> You're never going to have one of them.
>> Big I don't have a disabled girl. No, I don't. Go.
>> You're never going to have a girlfriend.
You never had a girlfriend in your life.
You're nearing 30 and you're still I've
had women that you wish you could get
with, though. I've had women you wish
you could get with, but you can only get disabled girls.
>> Not one.
>> Being in your little beds with no money
showing off your dad's body.
>> Your your sister in your imagination
does not count. Pig news.
>> You stalked all the women that I got
that you can't get cuz you're ugly.
>> You have a very big nose.
>> You're ugly and you got no teeth. You
have to go for disabled girls.
>> Very large. You must admit. You can't
deny that. You can't deny that. Okay.
Your nose is very large.
>> Noises that you make. You make them
noises, don't you? Them autism stming noises.
>> Are you diagnosed with autism?
>> Aren't you diagnosed with
>> Yes, I am. But I don't make them noises
like you do. You're diagnosed with
autism. You can't talk about anyone, can
you? Skid boy.
>> Skid virgin.
>> When are you going to get a house and
start living in a city with no bed in
it? [ __ ] some people
>> I'm in a flat and I'm in bed with my
girlfriend right now.
>> You are in bed with a disabled girl.
>> Yes, a disabled fat girl.
>> A disabled fat the wolf. Cuz that's all
you can get cuz you're an ugly bastard.
>> That's all ugly people can get.
>> What are you going to chew in return? Wobbly hooter.
>> You are an ugly bastard. Sort out your
ugly looks. Sort out your [ __ ] Why
haven't you got no You You didn't say my name.
>> Did you hear me earlier when I dared
caress your life? Why have you got no teeth?
>> The police will bend over a [ __ ]
table and spank your daddy air with one.
>> What happened to your teeth? Ugly boyes
that you dick in the shoes. They will
spank your ass with it.
>> What happened to your dare say my name?
>> If you dare say my name, if you post any
content on me, if you look at me
directly or indirectly for that matter,
>> I stopped you going to your events. Oh,
>> you've never done that. Uh, but you're
not allowed to let me direct.
>> I stopped you going to your I stopped
you leaving your house for a month
because of fear. Oh. Oh.
>> You've never done that, Big. But
>> I made you stop.
>> But who was it that stuck posters up?
Who Who was it that sent posters to your mom's neighborhood?
>> Who Who sent posters to your mom's
neighborhood? Big news. I stopped you
going to your events. Oh, your baby.
event because you knew you was going to
get glass for being a
>> You mentally ill. None of these things had ever
>> made you stop going to your little
events because you were
>> I shared £13,000 big nude.
>> I am king of the money game. I I win the
trophy for the money game
Santa Claus. I stopped you leaving your
house for 3 weeks.
We all remember that.
You don't put any pictures of
>> When are you going to lose your
virginity, virgin boy?
>> When are you going to stop being a
virgin in your bed skin?
>> When are you going to finally meet
somebody and get some teeth in your head
>> and fix your ugly face?
>> I lose my virginity every night. Big news. You
>> You don't lose your virginity. You That
is your carer.
>> You've never lost your virginity. You're
still a virgin.
>> Okay, but you have a very big nose. You
can't deny that.
>> You virgin ugly bastard with the rat face.
>> Okay, but your nose is very big.
>> My nose is very big, but I've had more women.
And I've never had to resort to a
disabled girl like you. It's humongous.
So, I win.
>> You You can sniff around corners with
that thing. I've never had to resort to
a disabled girl because I'm so ugly like
you. There's no that is that ugly boy.
Can't grow a beard.
>> Why can't you grow a beard?
>> The baldy bastard. You ugly skin dad.
>> Your conk is enormous.
>> Oho. I stopped you going to your events
because of the posters.
I'm Father Christmas. Oh,
But you can't deny that is a big nose.
>> I'm so better looking than you. I've had
the women that you wish you could have.
>> No, you [ __ ] But your nose is very big.
>> Disabled in a bed sit like you.
>> I'm out of control.
>> Oh, you're making the noises. You're
making the autism control noises.
So why did your mom starve you and put
you in hospital, you little [ __ ] Why
did your stepdad strangle you like the
little [ __ ] you are?
>> Why did your stepdad [ __ ] have you up
against the wall?
>> Where was the big man then? Where was
>> Where was the big man when your stepdad
[ __ ] splashed your teeth down your [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Where was the Where was Where was the
big man then? When your stepdad had you
up against the wall.
>> You need professional
on that [ __ ] thing. That's big. Where
was the big man when your your stepdad
had you up against a [ __ ] wall and
your mom was starving you?
>> No, that never happened. These are
autism stories when your brain damage delusional mind.
>> You got some stories in your brain
damaged delusional mind
by your mother skinned boy.
>> Skinned boy in a bedit.
>> Am I lying?
>> You're mentally ill, you freak.
>> You need to lose your virginity. I don't
want you to die of virgin. It's not
fair. You're 31 and can only date
disabled, vulnerable girls that don't care. You
>> sound like your mom. Why do you sound
like lame when you're speaking like that?
>> Because your mom starved you and put you in hospital.
>> I can't believe how your mom abused you
and you done nothing about it.
>> You did. You got abused by a bugging
woman. That's why you hated animal [ __ ]
in the post and she knew what the smell of donkeys.
>> You hate people that's got a mother
because your mother don't want you. Your
mother abused you and don't want to know
you. Your mom just you and put you into little boy.
Your mom put you into cuz she couldn't
deal with you. You autistic virgin.
>> Someone sent us donkey.
>> I love it.
>> PJ, someone sent us donkey.
>> Your mother starved you cuz she didn't.
>> She knew you were the [ __ ] up from birth.
>> Your mother starved you and your dad's a [ __ ] skin.
>> And your dad's a skin. Oh no. Anyway,
>> your mom starved you and put you in
hospital like the little
Kenji sent you animal [ __ ]
>> This is going to take you [ __ ] that innocent innocent.
>> Yeah. Okay, be quiet. That innocent
little man you
>> that innocent little man working in
Tesco. Do you remember him?
>> you remember the innocent little man
working in Tesco's? He owned you.
He sent you animal
and good in hospital.
>> He [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> You remember that story you made up of
Hannah sucking your dick?
Never happened. You're still a virgin. Virgin boy.
>> You never got your dick sucked. You're
still a [ __ ] virgin in that bedset
and you'll die one.
>> This is actually live. Can people hear
this? Cuz this is very embarrassing. I
must say this is humiliating.
>> You're [ __ ] 30 years old. Listen to yourself, man.
>> You're 31 years old and you're in a
[ __ ] bedit with [ __ ] bed.
>> You're in a [ __ ] bedit [ __ ] owned
by the council cuz you're skin and you
got life and you got nothing.
Not quite a freaking bedset.
>> Quite. Yes. But you sound like Elaine.
>> 31 in a bedit. You have nothing. [ __ ]
>> Get it right. Big news. I'm in a rented
flat that I've lived in.
>> I'm in bed with my I'm in bed.
>> I'm in bed with my girlfriend.
You don't have one of those.
You don't have it's like you don't have that.
>> You will see my penis if I do that right now.
>> [ __ ] bed. You ain't got no bed. Virgin boy.
>> I sleep naked. You will see my penis. I
can't do that.
>> You don't have a penis. You don't have a
dick. You got erectile dysfunction.
That's why you're still a virgin.
>> You You showed a [ __ ] video of you
getting your dick sucked by a prostitute
and it was soft because you needed to
finish yourself up. I got my dicks up
and yes I got erectile dysfunction but you never
still a virgin cuz you're still a virgin.
>> Yeah. Okay.
But you showed a video you showed a
video of yourself.
>> My god. Can you let me speak? You
ignorant [ __ ] You showed a video of
yourself getting a [ __ ] and your
penis was flaccid. Explain that one. Big news.
>> What? Listen large. Your nose is on the
side is enormous.
>> Still a virgin.
>> Have you heard when you put your foot up
to your forearm, it's supposed to be the
same size, but when you put your nose up
to yours, it's bigger.
>> But isn't it funny how I've had to
resort I've never had to resort to a
disabled girl like you. I'm sorry.
That's not normal.
>> Listen, I don't care how many times you show
>> it's big. I don't care how many times
you show that disabled girl you've never
had sex. A lot of