[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] Reddit.
[ __ ] showing you. I'm not even
[ __ ] telling you, you [ __ ] idiot.
I'm [ __ ] showing you. Oh my god. I
swear to God. But I weren't even going
to come on this [ __ ] YouTube today,
bro. I swear to God. But these stupid
[ __ ] [ __ ] on [ __ ] Reddit. And I'm
a man showing you, not telling you. I'm
[ __ ] showing you my experiences. And
I'm a man showing you. Not telling you,
showing you. Cuz telling can't be [ __ ] believed.
How do they keep [ __ ] making excuses
for women every [ __ ] time on this
[ __ ] Reddit? Just ignore. They
literally, bro, ignore people's
struggles and make up stuff. So, I don't
even understand why they even asked you
to show anything. I don't even know. I'm
a I'm a woman telling you and I'm a man
[ __ ] showing you my experiences with
[ __ ] different [ __ ] women. I'm
showing you. I'm not telling you. It's
being shown to you because nobody can
actually believe. No one can believe
someone that just gets told stuff.
Do you know what I'm saying? I'm a man
[ __ ] showing you [ __ ] numb nuts.
Do you know what I'm saying? I'm showing
you. They literally dismiss, right? They
literally, bro, they literally dismiss
any bit of evidence that you show them
and they resort to making stuff up.
You've ignored all of my You've ignored
all of my evidence and result and
resorted to making stuff up and resorted
to making stuff up.
That's what you done.
I'm showing you. I am showing you. I'm
not telling you. I'm a man showing you.
You understand, idiot.
Stop [ __ ] dismissing people's
struggles. For [ __ ] sake. It's annoying.
It's [ __ ] annoying. Oh, women give
their numbers because they're afraid of
what? No, they're not because they have
messes back and they've arranged to meet
people. Stop making stuff up. I'm
[ __ ] showing you. You're ignoring
things that don't suit you.
You are ignoring things. You are
ignoring it because it doesn't suit you.
It literally does not suit you. You're
ignoring things that don't suit you and
you resort to making things up.
Stop making excuses.
Stop making excuses. You're not [ __ ] stupid.
You're You know what I'm saying? It
doesn't suit you. It literally No, this
is a woman I'm arguing with. I'm a man
and I'm showing you. I'm not arguing.
I'm not telling you anything. I'm
showing you. I'm not telling you. I'm
I've shown them like all the piss taken
and because it doesn't suit them. They
dismiss your struggles every single [ __ ] time.
You're just making up [ __ ] excuses
every [ __ ] time. Open your [ __ ]
eyes. I shouldn't have to send you this [ __ ] again.
[ __ ] madness, bro. What the [ __ ]
So all of that they give their number.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, none of that
excuses because they reply back to
people when they arrange to meet people.
That's not an excuse for all of the
people that's replied back. Excuse after
excuse after [ __ ] excuse. If I got if
I got a penny, right, for every single
time, right? It's it's almost like
they're trolling, isn't it? It's even
like they're normal people that it's
like they're actually trolling you.
Do you know what I'm saying? Where is this message? One sec.
It's like they dismiss anyone's struggles.
You know, if I was at back on this
actual YouTube thing, bro, I'd actually
like do a video on this, but I can't be
asked. But it's madness.
They actually dismiss people's
struggles. They actually do, bro.
I don't know why they do this.
Just these people on [ __ ] Reddit just
just women defending women. It's [ __ ]
annoying. Like, I've not shown her like
a million and one different [ __ ] things,
you know? I've shown her piss taking and
they're just not buying it. They just
make up stuff. You know what I'm saying?
It's pointless, bro.
They love defending women, whether it's
a man or woman. What is it with them
keep defending women even though you've
literally shown them [ __ ] You've
shown them the [ __ ] that they
[ __ ] done and all they do
is defend [ __ ] women every every
single [ __ ] time. It's [ __ ] annoying, bro.
It's mad. That's why they It's better
just to not say anything. That's why,
you know, when it comes to this, bro,
you're better off just not saying anything.
This is a woman and she says, "I'm a
woman telling you and I'm a man showing
you other women and I'm a man showing
you my experiences with other women."
this excuse after excuse after excuse
after excuse of the time wasting after
excuse after excuse after excuse after
excuse after excuse after excuse. I've
never heard so many excuses in my life.
Not even on this [ __ ] even on this community, lad.
Where's the other one?
Yeah, they're always going to defend
women. Just like when they say like
you're always going to that people
always going to hate women. They're
never going to stop defending women. So
there's literally no point in even
having to say anything anymore. Yeah.
Yeah. They just make excuses.
That's two right there.
Where's the other one?
That doesn't sound And it doesn't
They just make up stuff. That's
literally all they do is make up things. It's ridiculous.
Yeah. Yeah. It's madness.
Anyways, I'm not staying on here all day
anyways. I've got a life like some
people, but I don't know. This Reddit
thing makes me rage, bro. It's annoying as [ __ ]
They really think that women are never
the problem. I'm just on Reddit right
with this with this woman and um we're
talking about the cost of living in
London and that and then I was I was
thought oh this is this would be a
perfect example to um share my
experiences. You know what I probably
won't even go out this week to be honest
now because this has just wound me up
and I'm showing her like the piss taking
and all of the stuff that they do and
then they're making it excuse. She's
like, "Oh, you're coming on too strong."
Or, "Oh, they give their number because
they feel afraid." [ __ ] Some of
these people reply back and they
actually arranged to meet you. So, that
excuse is is thrown out the window. And
then she's like, "Oh, I'm a woman." I
know. I'm a man that's showing you my
experiences with women, different women.
That is not just one one woman. Do you
understand what I'm saying? I don't care
if you're a woman. I'm showing you my
experiences with different [ __ ]
women. And I'm not telling you anything.
I'm showing you. And it's no, it's like
no matter what you do, what you show,
they're just going to resort to making
up stuff. You might as well just not
even say anything. You actually, you
know what? You might as well just say
nothing. I feel like you should just say nothing, lad.
But no, it's not, Joe, because I'm
showing them messages. I'm not saying
I'm showing I'm showing where women have
arranged to meet me and then not turned
up. I'm showing my evidence. I'm putting
the fire in the evidence. So, you're
actually dismissing my struggles
because I am showing you. You're saying
that you're oh, everyone's saying the
same thing, but I am showing you what I
am experiencing. I am showing you the
bad experiences. I am showing you the
piss taken that you all clearly dismiss
and you keep ignoring, which is what I'm
saying. What is even stranger that
you're dismissing everything you've been
shown. That's what I find very very very
very very very strange and you resort to
making up stuff. You know what I'm
saying? That's what I find very strange.
You've literally been shown messages,
right, where someone has agreed to meet
you. We're going to the past and
suddenly on the day, oh, I'm going back
with my ex or oh, they block you or oh,
I can't come because of this reason, XY
Z. You have literally been shown that a
million times and you still resort to
making up stuff.
I I just want to know why you keep
making stuff up. I don't I don't want
anything. I just want I don't I don't
know what I want.
Do you know what I'm saying? I don't I
don't want anything. I just want to know
why you're I want an explanation why you
keep making stuff up.
Why do you keep making things up? That's
what I want to know. Why you keep
dismissing people's struggles?
you know, why are you dismissing
people's struggles? That's what I that's
what I want to know. It's almost as if
it's like trolling in a way
because, oh, women give their numbers to
get away from people, but that's not
true because all of these most of these
women have replied and they've actually
agreed to meet you. So that excuse don't
even wash in the washing machine
anymore, you know.
And furthermore, let's just say for
example, all of their messages, right,
that that is true what you're saying
when it ain't true what you're saying
because I've shown you where they've
replied back millions of times. Okay.
Well, then that that just goes to show
that what it's impossible to date then.
I feel like you're best off just having
no opinion. I feel like you're best off
just saying nothing now.
It's ridiculous. I I don't know what
what more they want, you know?
try to use the voice notes as an excuse.
I said, "Okay, well, what about these
two women? Let me get that one from
California. Let's see what she's saying.
Let's see what excuse she's got to say
about that one." You know, I'm sick of
people making excuses for [ __ ] women.
It does my nothing, bro. I swear to God,
you know, I weren't even going to
[ __ ] go on [ __ ] YouTube today, and
I'm not staying on this [ __ ] all day,
you know, but the point still [ __ ]
stands, bro. Like what the [ __ ] Coming
on too strong. No one's coming on too
[ __ ] strong. You've been shown a
[ __ ] million [ __ ] messages where
people have agreed to [ __ ] meet you.
Any excuse for the piss taken. You know,
you've not seen messages where people
have ignored. You've seen actual
conversations. You've seen people
arranging on to meet on dates. But
whatever [ __ ] you show them, that's
why you're best just saying nothing.
You're best just saying nothing. I I
think you're Yeah, I think you're best
just saying nothing. Now, let me get
this one from California then
that we were supposed to meet and then
all of a sudden they're they're not over
their ex that lives in a different
country. Let's let's show them some of
these ones. See what they've got to say to that.
They make up excuses and they dismiss
your struggles. It's [ __ ] I don't
know why they do it.
I'm so glad I don't have to deal with
this whole um
this dating thing anymore. You know,
anymore. I'm so glad. I'm so glad I gave
up. You know,
to be honest, I don't think I'm going to
be going out this week. I said I was
going to I said I was going to go out
this week, but I don't think I will now.
This is one of the reasons why I don't
I'm not dealing with that [ __ ] again.
[ __ ] that. I'm not dealing with their
[ __ ] their [ __ ] [ __ ] every [ __ ] week.
Yeah, stop talking about yourself.
So, you know what I'm saying, bro?
Where's this message anyways? Let me
show them this message.
And like I said, I'm not staying on this
I'm not staying on this YouTube today
anyways, bro. I don't entertain self-reflectors
and talk about themselves, but you know,
I just thought I'd come on here and just
I don't know. It make it it literally
makes you want to come on here and vent.
I don't know what it is, bro. I swear
it's like Do you know what this is? This
is like therapy sessions.
This is actually like therapy sessions,
you know? I swear if I actually had a
therapist to moan about all of this
stuff to, I don't think I'd ever come
back on here, bro. You know what? That's
actually like people go on here for like
different reasons. You know what I mean? Like
um people go on here to obviously most
of them they just self-reflect their
ugly fatkinned lives onto other people.
But I mean there's some people like me.
Oh, here we go. There we go. Lovely,
lovely, lovely. There we go.
Does my [ __ ] nothing. It does. Does I feel Yeah,
it's bad, bro. It It's really, really,
really, really bad.
Yep. So, I don't think I even will be
going out Saturday now to be honest with you.
We're going to go chicken shopping a
bit, bro. Get some pieces of chicken.
Have a couple of miles walk. I don't
even think I will to be honest. It's
just no point.
It's not even money either. I swear to
God it ain't even money.
It's just what is the point anymore with
it? You know what I'm saying? It's just [ __ ]
You proved your [ __ ] point a million [ __ ] times.
Jesus Christ. Could you imagine having
to worrying about money when you still
had hope? Yep. I watched it. Yeah, when
it first come out, bro, every time a
horror film comes out, I'm there
watching it. Bro, you should know me by now.
Could you imagine you still had hope and
then you had to worry about money. Oh,
you imagine, bro.
Jeez. Imagine having to worry about
money and you still had hope.
Imagine you got like£300 a month. Yeah.
And then you had to worry about these
women. Oh my [ __ ] god.
God knew what I was in for, mate, with
that house. I think it was. Uh, it was okay. Yeah.
Could you imagine, Joe, you had to worry
about money if you still had hope?
[ __ ] that, bro. Absolutely [ __ ] that. Do
you know what I would do, bro? If I won
like a big big big big big big football
bet or come into any kind of big money,
right, I'd just leave again. I would
even like I just leave. That's why I
wouldn't even waste money here. Did you
imagine you had to worry about money but
in all of these years? [ __ ] that.
That is depressing, bro.
But saying that, you probably would just
adjust to the money you got anyways, to
be honest. You'd probably have to
adjust. You'd probably adjust to the money.
I don't know.
So, I had to deal with their [ __ ] but I
never had to deal with any money
problems. You know what I'm saying? I
had to deal with So, why why do they
ignore what they're shown anyways?
Why do they ignore what they're shown anyways?
They make up any excuses for women. It's
not that they give people's numbers.
They they give their number to get away
from people because they actually troll
people. They actually reply back to
people. So, I mean, if you didn't really
want to give your number to someone, why
are you arranging to meet someone?
I was speaking about that the la uh the
last date I went on yesterday to someone
on um Instagram and I was saying it's
it's madness, lad. These people will
actually go on dates to actually waste your time
to go. They will actually go on your
dates and actually waste your time.
Yep. They will always run away when they
show money. You actually show them [ __ ]
you show um you they'll even go on
people's dates. They'll even go on dates
with people to waste people's time. It's a madness.
It's madness, bro.
[ __ ] I'll go on dates with people and
don't even kiss them.
It just annoys me, bro. Just thinking
about it annoys me, bro. [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] Reddit.
No one's coming on too [ __ ] strong.
You want to hear about It's like that
USA easy tried lying to my friend about
people coming on too strong. Yeah, like
you didn't take me back to your
apartment and start making advances
towards me and you're telling me I'm
coming on too strong. What the [ __ ] does
that even mean? You know what? I would I
would want somebody one day to sit there
and explain that to me. What does coming
on too strong mean? Because they tell
you to be uh assertive and then when
you're assertive, you're coming on too
strong. What the [ __ ] bro? Do they not
take any accountability for their You
know what? They just don't take any
accountability for their own actions, do
they? You know, someone made a video on
this. I haven't even watched the video.
And there's a title. There's a title
called It's their worst nightmare is
taking accountability. That's so true,
you know, even though I didn't watch it,
but the title is women's biggest
nightmare taking accountability. It's
the truth. It literally is the [ __ ]
truth. They don't take accountability
for anything that they do.
And other women don't take
accountability for anything they do or [ __ ] simps.
It's not like they say that you're wrong
and they're wrong. It's not like they
say you're wrong and also they're wrong.
They literally don't think they're wrong
in any way when they're literally a lot
of them are.
Accountability is literally their worst nightmare.
Yeah, you'd be screwed, bro, if you had
to worry about money in them years.
You'd be [ __ ] You would actually be
[ __ ] bro. It wouldn't even be It
wouldn't even be funny, bro.
I've already got a woman before. You've
seen me with many, many women. But I
guess you probably forgot that. Just
like you forgot all the time that you
got show money. Yeah, I did. But you you
probably forgot that you like to forget
things on here. Um when yeah, you like
you like to forget things. So I I don't
uh I don't blame you for it, man.
Yeah, you would be [ __ ] bro. You
would actually be [ __ ] It's not even a joke.
I might do a 500 pound on both teams to score, Joe.
What do you think of that? Nah. Do you
know it's tempting, you know? It is actually tempting.
But nah. [ __ ] that. Imagine losing 500
[ __ ] quid. No way, bro.
Nah. [ __ ] that, bro.
I wouldn't do that, bro. But yeah, if
you had to worry about money, bro, and then [ __ ]
I have to worry about this [ __ ] you
would be [ __ ] screwed, lad.
You would be screwed. [ __ ]
You might have even been a virgin.
You never know. It could have. Nah, cuz
I got laid in Manchester and that wasn't
I didn't have the house then.
>> Yeah, I didn't have the house then.
Don't ask me how I did it, mate. But we
seem to do do it, didn't we? >> Yeah.
Don't know how much I spent. Maybe 170.
I think I was getting like £100 a month.
But I don't understand what more they
want to be shown. And it's just
annoying, bro. It's just annoying.
This women [ __ ] is annoying, bro.
That's why I can't be bothered to go out
on on on Saturday. You really think I
can't afford to go out? Of course I
[ __ ] can. Go out now if I wanted to.
But there's no point in it.
And the only woman that I do I speak to
lives in [ __ ] Finland. So
the only one I speak to every day lives in Finland.
What do you mean get on with your life
without money and women? But you know
what's so mad is I've always worried.
Even when I had the house, I'm worried,
which was ridiculous. How can you worry
when you get three grand a month? I
mean, you can't even worry now. I mean,
I I probably have in London, right? I
probably have more more disposable money
than most people. Like this woman, this
is how um I was speaking to this woman
was like, "Oh, she said she has £1,100
left after like she's paid rent and
bills and stuff." And I said, "I've got
about 13." So,
if you win a couple of football bets or
you do some sort of delivery job, you're
actually better off than most people in
returns of like you don't get more money
than them, but you're left with more
money than them.
Um, and I was reading up, it was
interesting to see how much people are left with
how much people are left with and how
much people are, you know,
there's a life without money. Yeah.
Well, you don't understand, Joe. When
you've had it easy for so long, then
you know it's hard, dude. And and trust
me, I can go out I can go out every week
if I wanted to, bro. Trust me. If I
wanted to go out every week, I would go
out every week.
You know, I should blame You know, I was
thinking of this. Yeah. I started going
out when I was 21. No, 22. After I met
Izzy, I started going out when I was
about 22. LT was like, "Oh, you tried
the bars and you tried the clubs and
stuff." Bear in mind, I was on like
I think I was on about£700 a month.
I was on about £700 a month.
And um I still went I still done it.
Somehow I was still able to do it. So I
I done it from like 22 to about 28 next
month. And I'm completely bored of the
going out now.
I'm completely bored of it, bro. I swear
to God I'm completely bored of it. It's
not even like
You do, bro. I swear to God you do.
Yeah. Like I'm just bored of it, bro.
I'm bored of it.
I was going to go out this week, but I
don't know if I can be bothered, lads, honestly.
Where's she gone?
Yeah, I'm going to help I'm going to
help you stop watching it. I'm going to
I'm going to turn the TV off.
Yeah. [ __ ] bro.
How How is there a life without women
and money, Joe?
Well, yeah. Like I said, money doesn't
really matter unless you're struggling.
Money doesn't really matter unless
you're actually struggling.
So, I mean, yeah, it doesn't matter
unless you're struggling.
Money isn't anything as long as you're not struggling.
So, that's you know what I'm saying? So,
you are right, but just as long as
you're not struggling.
[ __ ] £100 in your [ __ ] You say you
had like £100 in your bank.
Yeah. I mean, as long as you've got like
a couple of thousand pound in your
[ __ ] bank, then you're good. If you
got no outgoings in it. So, yeah.
Well, I can because I don't try anymore.
Yeah. But I don't try anymore. The only
woman I speak to is that one in Finland,
and she actually seems all right.
So she actually doesn't ignore anything
and she always gets back to me. She
generally is busy. She's like a personal
trainer and [ __ ]
But women women's worst nightmare is accountability.
That is definitely the truth. Like
they're there it is accountability. They
can't take no accountability.
You know what I'm saying?
or their actions.
So, like I was saying to you, USA is he
saying that I'm I'm coming on too
strong. You literally made advances toward me.
You literally like you literally made
You literally made advances towards me.
You literally made advances towards me,
[ __ ] How can anybody come on too
strong? And then you got that Italian
one that's wasting your time and [ __ ]
Yeah, I mean I could do it. Yeah, obviously.
But that's what it will have to come
down to to be honest. [ __ ]
Why do you say that, bro?
So yeah, I I don't I don't bring up
money. These people are the ones that
bring up money on here.
The big These people are the ones that
come on here and bring up money. Not me, bro.
Going to get some pieces of chicken from
good old Lakers.
Bro, she's a catfish.
How can she be a catfish when I've met
her in real life?
I've literally met her in real life. I
approach her in a bar. How could she be a catfish?
Come on, Kieran. All of the women that I
speak to are people that I've met in real life.
She's no cactus. I've met her in real
life, you idiot.
I met her in person and I got her number
in person. There is some people I speak
to now online because I feel like I'm
old and I just can't be bothered going
out. So, there is people I do talk to now.
So maybe I was a bit wrong about like
LJ and stuff, you know, talking to women
online, but I don't simp like are you
still why don't you go out and approach
or why don't you go out and approach?
No, no, no, no, no. But I can't be
bothered. Even at 20 [ __ ] almost 28,
I can't be [ __ ] you know? I can
afford it and stuff. I just can't be bothered.
So maybe like maybe when they're old,
they just can't be bothered, do it,
but he actually like simps over women.
proper proper like simp I I can't even
be [ __ ] anymore with it, you know? I
can't be bothered, bro. [ __ ] boring as [ __ ]
Yeah, but no, listen. All All of the
women I speak to, Kieran, on WhatsApp,
they're all women I've met in real life.
Um, most all the women most of them are
are ones I've met in real life. You need
to be careful of Instagram, bro, cuz
there's some AIs on [ __ ] Instagram.
Yeah, there's some AIs, bro.
Yeah, there's some AIs on [ __ ] Instagram.
It's like where they It's like people
pretending to be models.
I think that's why I used to do the
approaching because I wanted to know who
I was speaking to was actually a woman.
With these dating apps and [ __ ] you
don't know who you're talking to.
That's that's the thing. You don't
actually know who you're speaking to.
Whereas when you approach someone um
you obviously know who you're speaking
to, you know what I mean?
Look at my face, bro.
Oh, do you know what I look like? I look
like when I was 23. Do you remember with
the little beard?
Definitely need clothes barbers, bro.
I'm going to go for a nice long walk today.
Going to go for a nice long walk.
Probably is a Chinese man. It [ __ ]
definitely ain't [ __ ] her.
But yeah, this Finland one's perfect,
bro. She's two months younger than me.
So, we're the same age. We're exactly
That's why it was a bit of a let down
when that Ukrainian one didn't meet me
cuz she was my age and I was older than
her by about 6 months.
We were supposed to meet and then on the
day they disappeared. I was like, "What the fuck?"
So yeah, some women might give their
number to get away from people, but
they're not when they're literally
replying to people and arranging to meet you.
You know, it's like that one in
Birmingham, for example. That one
actually pissed me off. There was one of
them that pissed me off. They were in Birmingham, right?
They were in Birmingham. I got their
number. We're speaking every day for two
weeks and they were properly like, "Oh
yeah, I'll let you know. I'll let you
know. I'll let you know and then all of
a sudden they're not interested in
dating." Why not just [ __ ]
not reply back to you or block you or
say within the or they could have easily
said, "Right, um, oh yeah, it was nice
meeting you." And then when you try and
then they'll say, "Oh, well, I'm not
really interested in this or that by the
third message maximum." But they
haven't. They sit there and they
literally lead people on. I don't
understand how people don't see it. You
know what I'm saying? It's a madness. Um
then, you know, you don't have an
argument. I feel like, you know, if if
if someone says it within the first,
second, or third message, then there's
nothing you can say. Yeah.
Who cares whose money it is, bro? It's [ __ ]
I don't even go on about money. These
people are the ones that go on about [ __ ] money.
But you get what I mean? Like, it's
like, what the [ __ ] man?
But yeah, they don't they don't seem to
they don't take any accountability.
I might do a video on that, you know.
They don't take any accountability at
all. That's the thing with these women caring.
I [ __ ] I watched an approach video
today. First time in a week. I don't
watch them anymore because it's just the
same old [ __ ] Oh, how old are you? Oh
my god. Same attitude. [ __ ] sake.
Same people. Same different people.
Different different people. Same [ __ ]
attitude. [ __ ] bor off, man.
Why I don't [ __ ] even bother anymore?
[ __ ] wasting my [ __ ] time.
Yeah. Okay. So, that's the excuse. So, I
showed this woman, this woman saying
that they were going to meet me. And on
the day they were supposed to meet me,
suddenly they're not over their ex. And
that's because they changed their mind.
Oh, right. So you change your mind in
the space of two days.
Oh, okay. Wow. So from saying sounds good
to all of a sudden changing your mind.
Wow. Change your mind that quickly? What?
No, that doesn't.
You don't listen. Listen.
Wow. They're just full of excuses, aren't they?
They just literally just make any
excuses for for them. It's pointless.
It's pointless even having an argument
with these people.
Well, yes it is.
And you know what I want to know? You
know when people sit there and say
things are not going to work out, why
aren't it? Why isn't it going to work
out? Have you always wondered that,
Kieran? Why isn't it going to work out?
Why is it not going to work out? Have
you ever No, because things don't work
out for There must be a reason why
things don't work. Do you understand
that? There's got to be a reason why.
They're always going to waste. They're
You can't win with them. You can't win
You can't win with them. You could
literally show them them and you could
probably show these people a woman
molesting a child and they'll be like,
"Nah." Well, they didn't really do it.
You can't win with them.
No matter what you show them, what you
tell them, what your experiences are,
they just make up excuses.
This is why they get away with so much.
Do you do you understand what I'm
saying? This is why
Yeah, exactly. They give
they give their numbers. Yeah. They give
their numbers and play games. And they
do it on purpose, bro. They do it on purpose.
They give their numbers and play games. >> Yeah.
I'm I think I'm going to do a video on this,
you know, even though I've not watched his video. Yeah,
they just literally make
Yeah, they they they literally play games
and that's what they do. They literally
play games. Literally, most of them like
only a few of them don't. Like
accountability is their is their worst nightmare.
They don't they don't take
accountability for anything.
They just make it. They just make it.
They're just not having any of it at
all, are they? They're not having it at
all. At all. At all.
They're literally full of excuses.
There's literally just no point. There's
just no There's no point because you're
always going to defend them. So, there's
no point. There's no there's no
because you're dismissing my struggles.
So there's no point.
Yeah. You know what I'm saying?
They literally just miss your struggles.
That's like that's literally the perfect
word for it.
You're just going to carry on making
excuses for them every single time
and then they try to blame you.
Then you're This is why I'm not going to
go out on Friday, you know? This is
exactly why I'm not going to bother with
this, bro. You know what I'm saying? I'm
not even Do you know what? I'm not even
going to bother with this anymore, bro.
Honestly, do you know why? Because it's
just pointless. They're just going to
keep making excuses for women. It's
pointless. This is a woman. You should
know better. You know,
yes, they're not interested. Yes. But
they're playing games and they're
wasting people's times. And I'm showing you. Yes.
showing you they play games and mess
with people's heads.
And why? And why the [ __ ] aren't they
interested? That's another thing at the
end. That's another thing.
Yeah. And I'm showing you them playing
games. Do you know why I'm saying that?
You know what I'm saying? Do you know
what I mean?
Yeah. You're telling me and I'm showing
you them playing games. And I'm showing
you. I'm not telling you. I'm showing
they're always going to they're never
going to stop defending women. They're
never going to stop defending them. They
could be the most com I'm going to do a
video on this. You know, I'm going to do
my version of this. You know what I
mean? I'm I'm I'm going to do Why are
you talking about my sexuality? Because
I'm talking the truth, Joe. Why Why does
the truth make me make Why would the
truth make me want to be gay?
You know what I'm saying?
>> Yeah. So why why would I be gay? Because
why? Cuz the truth hurts. So
why does it always go back to people
being gay? Bro, you sound like a kid
when you say that. Do you know that?
Always work on yourself. Work on
yourself. Oh dear. We do me.
You know what I'm saying? So, so they're
not interested, yet you keep telling
people that they're going to meet
someone, but you're saying that this
person's not interested, that person's
not interested, and this person is not
interested. Yet, you're telling people
that they're going to find someone, yet
you're saying that none of these people
are interested. So, then why would
anyone waste their time again?
Does it doesn't it doesn't it contradict
everything you're saying?
I've shown you my negative I've shown
you my negative experiences with women.
I've shown you my ne my negative
experiences experiences with women with
women that you're that that you've dism
negative because of them.
And it's not like they've said that
they're not interested, Joe. They've
literally playing games with people. Why
don't they want to take any accountability?
I'm going to do my own version of this
this video, you know, because I've not
watched this black guy's video. Um,
why do they dismiss people's struggles?
Why? Why? Why do they resort to making up stuff?
I don't understand what what more they
want. They just always It's like that
USA easy Joe. How could I be the one
coming? Let's just use that as an
example, right? How could I be coming on
strong if you are the one that is coming
on to me making sexual advances towards
me? They don't like taking accountability.
Uh they haven't
they haven't said they've changed their mind.
They've played games and took the piss.
Listen. Okay, I'll give you an example.
Right. Right. I'll give you an example
of of someone. Right. So, I met somebody
in Birmingham and they live in
Liverpool. So, we was talking talking talking.
Right. Um, and then they're like, "Oh,
I'm going to Spain." And then no, and
then they kept the they kept the
conversation dragging out and then I've
asked them to meet and then then I've
asked them to sort of meet again. And
then it was like, oh, using distance
distance as an excuse. You should have
said that from day one. People don't
change their mind that quickly. You
know, isn't it mad how all of these
people suddenly change their mind? No,
they're taking a piss. You know, they
like the attention from talking and then
when it comes down to actually meeting,
they don't want to meet. Like if someone
is truly truly not playing games, they
would just ignore you or they'd reply
once and as soon as and then they they
would reply once or maybe three times
and then they'll be like, "Oh, no, no,
no, no." But if they keep replying, then
they're playing games. They're taking a
piss. You know, the people don't change
their mind within two days, bro. Not all
of these people can change their mind.
You understand? It's ridiculous.
And if you do, then you seriously need
to [ __ ] get some professional help
because that is that is [ __ ] some
sort of bipolar. Um, yeah. Never ever.
It's just the same. It's just the same
argument. I don't know why they don't
like, you know what I'm saying? It's
like there was this Romanian one that I
met in um Birmingham. They thought, "Oh,
we'll schedule it this week. We'll
schedule it this week." And all of a
sudden, bam, they're not interested.
What What if you not if you're not
interested and it's not that you
shouldn't give your number because
there's going to be an excuse that oh
well, we were too scared we had to give
the number. So, I'm not even going to
use that because then their their excuse
is going to be well sometimes they give
their numbers because they're
uncomfortable around men. So, I'm not
even that's the excuse that they will
use. So, they wouldn't give their number
to then reply to somebody constantly to
then not meet them in the end. It's
literally piss taken. I don't know what
what what more you have to show. What
more you and this is why I don't bother
anymore. This is generally why I do not
bother with the [ __ ] anymore.
I think it's like two, three weeks
since I've last gone on here. I don't
know. Maybe something like that. But
last gone out and because I just can't
be [ __ ] with it anymore.
I'd rather just [ __ ] go to [ __ ]
Finland than [ __ ] have to [ __ ] try
here ever again. You know what I mean?
You get me? So yeah, it's [ __ ] madness, lad.
When are they going to uh when are they
going to take accountability for their actions?
I don't think they're ever going to take
accountability for their actions.
Or they'll do stuff like only replying
to negativity and stuff. When are people
going to wake up and smell the smell the
strong sugary coffee? I don't understand.
Madness, lad. Madness. What was Monty saying?
Also, another thing is, okay, back back
to this. Yeah. I never knew what they
were going to do to Monty. What the
[ __ ] They never done it to me. All of
the things that they've done to him,
they've not done to me.
They've literally not done to me. They
had done to me done to me this stuff
until after they done it with him. I
didn't know what they were going to do.
I did not know what they were going to
do at all.
Yeah. Um, being being on holiday, these
women, they weren't on holiday. That's
the whole point. They wasn't on holiday.
They literally wasn't on holiday,
you know. No, bro. I'm going to go all
the way there and beat Monty up for you
to pretend it never happened. Come on,
Joe. A wise man learns from his
mistakes. You know, I know what you
people are about on here, mate. You're
not going to fool me. You know, it's
like when you ask me to show money. Do
you really think I don't have money?
Okay, but I think I don't have money.
Whatever. Cool. You You think I can't I
can't go to Birmingham and smash money
Mike in for snaking me. Okay, I think I
can't do that, bro. But, you know, we
learn from our mistakes.
There's no point entertaining a biased
audience. It's literally a biased
audience. Think about like this, Kier.
You know that fatty bum bum that comes
on here? Yeah.
Has anyone sh has anyone spoke about
when I've gone to B when I've gone to
Manchester two times and he not shown up?
No, I wasn't the one asking to show
money. You people come on here calling
me skins and I stated that I've already
shown you money and you will run away
and that's why I'm not showing money.
You are the ones that come on here maybe
they calling people skin. Literally as
soon as you go on J's all you see is
skin skin your this person skin belly
skin your skin I get brain damage. I
literally get brain damage every single
time I go on that on on on that on that
uh on that channel. I literally
developed brain damage, bro. I swear to God.
I'm going to get some chicken and chips.
I'm going to get a three-piece meal, Joe.
Yeah. Three piece chicken and chips.
But you get you get Yeah.
that black guy Joe stabby guy he says
you want to do something where you never
ever have to work again in your life he
said you don't want to get out of your
cozy bed in the morning you know but you
know no one wants to work a job you know
getting out of their cozy bed in the morning
getting uh getting into getting uh
getting out of their cozy bed in the
That guy makes me die. You know, he's
he's not healthy to watch too much,
though. He says, "Yeah, nobody wants to
get out of their comfy, cozy bed in the
morning to go to work." But, you know,
you have to, in it,
it's true though, isn't it? It's true, Yeah.
No one wants to get out of their cozy bed.
That is a madness lad. Nope.
Go around approaching women, right, and
finding one and it's ruining their life.
just [ __ ] them and leave them. If I
really wanted to, I could do that. But I
ain't got the energy, mate. I ain't got
[ __ ] I ain't got the energy to [ __ ]
to do that, you know.
Um she said that she was on holiday.
Oh, it's some black um incel. He's a 37y old virgin.
He's funny, bro. Yeah, a lot of people
know know him already. Bye-bye.
Um, not good, man. I'm arguing with
somebody on Reddit. I'm trying to show
her my experiences and stuff and they
just keep defending women. It's some
women I'm arguing with on Reddit. I'm
showing her like where they've clipped
the pierce and how they're [ __ ] and
stuff and she won't have any of it. She
keeps making excuses saying I'm coming
on too strong. I've showed her my
approaches on my other channel. I've
shown her my messages and she just not
they're just not having any of it.
They're just not having any of it, mate.
Madness, isn't it?
Not having it at all. at all.
Not having it at all. At all.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
is all I'm seeing is excuses.
All they do is defend women and dismiss
your struggles. That's literally all they do.
It's crazy, isn't it? I hate women. I
do, bro. I actually hate them. This is
why I don't bother with them anymore.
I actually hate them. I don't know about anyone else. Oh yeah,
they they can't accept
accountability for anything.
We can't accept accountability for anything.
Yeah. It's just immature. All of this
gay talk is very very immature.
You know what? Because I'm stating
because I'm showing evidence and and the
truth hurts, I'm I should turn gay. Why
Why would I turn gay?
It's literally them that's the problem.
So why would I want to turn gay? It's
just immature. is very very very
immature. And to think that these people
are older than me as well.
They are literally all the same. All of
these women are literally all the same.
They say the same stuff. They do the
same stuff. None of them take
accountability for anything that they
do. But apparently they're not the same.
Man, it I'd love to meet this one person
that's not the same.
I would really, really love to meet
somebody that doesn't do any of these things.
I would really really love to meet them.
Where the [ __ ] are they hiding?
They're not in London. They're not in
Manchester. They're not in America.
Where the [ __ ] are these different women
hiding? I shall never know.
Talk is cheap. Very, very cheap. Talk is
cheaper than little and Audi.
You know what I'm saying? That talk is
cheaper than little and Audi, bro.
Talk is [ __ ] cheap.
This is why I don't even go out anymore,
Kier. Even bothering him with it because
all it's going to be is, "Oh, how old
are you?" or "Oh, I'm not interested."
Or, "I have a boyfriend." Or, "No, no,
no, no, no, no." It's just it's just the
same thing every time, lad.
It's not like they say you're wrong on
this and they're wrong on this.
Yeah. You won't find them on the street
either. They've all got boyfriends. I've
got a separate channel where I put all
my approaching videos on
and I've got loads and loads of them.
You You won't find them on the street.
You won't find them in a pub. You won't
find them in a club. You won't find them
in a library. You won't find them in a
shopping mall. You won't find them in a
store. Where are all of these different
women? [ __ ] hell. I'd have to ask
Frank. Maybe he'll give me the answer.
All women aren't the same, but every
single one that you come across seems to
be exactly the same. They say exactly
the same stuff. They literally do all
the same stuff as each other. I was
watching this approach earlier. The guys
approaching her. How old are you? How
old how old are you? That's literally
the most westernized thing somebody can ask
because what they're doing is they're
trying to use age as an excuse. So as
soon as you say, "Oh, I'm 2 years older.
I'm 2 years younger." Oh, sorry. You're
too old. You're too young for me. They
literally do exactly the same stuff
as one another.
This is what I could never understand
when I used to meet Virgin Boy. How he
used to say, "Oh, you don't know all
women. You don't know all women." I
mean, I've met a lot of [ __ ] women.
I've met a lot a lot of different women
from different countries and it seems
very similar what one does to the other.
It just seems that way, you know.
Yep. They've also told me to go to
dancing classes as well.
They've also told me to go to dancing classes
and it's constantly piss taken.
That's all it is is piss taken, but no
one ever ever says it.
I might you you might find one genuine maybe,
but very very very rarely. That's that
that's the best you you actually got
going to get.
They're not genuine. They're they're
they're piss takers. That's what they
are. They're absolute piss takers cuz
why do they give people their numbers
and literally do this if they're not
ever going to meet them? What's the
point of even replying?
It's [ __ ] ridiculous.
They just There's no way to describe
them other than [ __ ] Like, I don't
I don't even like using the word [ __ ]
you know? I don't even like using that
word. I just think [ __ ] just
describe them perfectly. That's what
they are. They're [ __ ]
It's like a lot of people in this
country are [ __ ]
This is why I I don't bother anymore.
Maybe I'll go back Saturday. Maybe I
will. Who knows?
Not in Not in the past. Not in the past
year. I haven't. Not in the past. Do you
not understand? It's gotten harder.
No. No, I haven't. Even that one I put
on the video, right? They said, "Oh,
yeah, you're not really my type." Yet,
they gave me their number. We was
holding hands and all sorts. Every
single thing in this country seems to be
like a dig. It seems to be a dig. It
seems like it really is a country
designed to annoy you, test you. That's
lit. This country, it does actually feel like that.
It feels like it's a country designed to
piss you off. That's literally it does,
bro. Like, have you ever have you ever
played that roulette
with a green bar and it's designed to
annoy you and get under your skin?
That's like what it is in this country, dating. So So
madness, mate. [ __ ] madness.
sorry there's no people there's no point
speaking there's no point going out J to
speak to people that aren't interested
you know what I'm saying
is it even worth going out Saturday probably Oh,
I mean that doesn't that just tell you
all you need to [ __ ] know, Bro,
if they really weren't into dating or
they really weren't into meeting anyone,
they wouldn't be wasting people's time.
So, I mean
I mean the distance as an excuse is so cute.
Distance as an excuse is so cute,
you know. That's a that's the cutest
excuse. It's cuter than King, you know.
It's cuter than King the Puppy.
Um, King the puppy, King the dog.
No, it doesn't matter about that,
Kieran, mate, because they give their
number and they message people back. So,
at the end of the day, it's like, nah,
that doesn't wash because they give
their number and then they message
people back. So, at the end of the day,
if they were given their numbers to get
away from people, they wouldn't reply
back or reply back that they're not interested.
So it doesn't really wash really to be
honest with you.
It doesn't really rush. It doesn't re
really wash to be fair. And also a lot
of women aren't scared of men funny,
believe it or not. So I mean that excuse
doesn't really wash.
It doesn't it doesn't wash in the washing machine.
Now the washing machine literally
doesn't even turn on because it's
[ __ ] because I have got people's
numbers where I've been speaking to
people and I've arranged to meet with
people and then on the day all of a
sudden they're nowhere to be seen
which puts that argument in the bin you
know so at the end of the day that's it
so and you know even if that is the case
and how are people going to date you know
and how are people going to Hey, so
that's why I don't do I that's one of
the reasons I don't go out anymore. You know,
what's the point when you already know the result? It's pointless.
That's the way I see it, bro. It But yeah,
so it just annoys me. The whole thing
just annoys me. It just all of it just
really really annoys me, lad.
So that's why I don't bother.
They've made their intentions clear.
They're not interested in this country.
So at the end of the day, what what's
there left to prove?
You know, they've already they they've
they've already stated it clear that
they're not interested in this country.
So what what's there left to do, bro?
So what is that? The argument is
ridiculous. They're not interested.
They're not interested. They're not
interested. They're not interested. So
no one's interested then. Okay. Argument
done. So what what what do you want, bro?
Like it's like because like they always
make excuses. They're not they always
make excuses, right? Oh, well they're
not interested. They're not interested.
They're not interested. They're not
interested. And then I and then I'm
like, okay, well, why are they not
interested? Because you're not fat.
You're not ugly. They've given you their
number. They're they're speaking to you.
Why are they not interested? And then it
goes back to the point where then if you
really believe that, yeah,
if you really really believe that, then
you know, then you should be telling
people to give up. If no one's
interested in this country,
you know, then then you you got your
answer in it. So at the end of the day,
there you are. Where did I have the most luck approaching?
to be honest with you, right, it was
it's pretty much the same everywhere.
But if you had got numbers out of
London, I'd find they'd reply more.
They'd still take the piss in the end.
But if I was to going to say one place
was easier, I'd say Newcastle.
No, Manchester Manchester is worse than London.
I would say either Nottingham and
Nottingham and Newcastle. No, not
Manchester. Manchester is just as bad as
London. Manchester is bad, bro.
Manchester is bad, bad, bad, bad, bad.
You know them 10 times I went back to
Manchester, I think I got like a kiss once.
I remember when I was staying there for
two days cuz I met this guy.
Yeah, I I I got a bird once out of the
10 times I went to Manchester. Yeah.
Yeah. That that tells you all you need to know.
Yeah. One bird out of 10 times I went there.
No, they're all stuck up there as well.
Uh, Brighton is No, they're all stuck up
there. I've done approaches there as
well. I've not been on a night out
there, but I've done approaches on the
beach and stuff. Not interested. Um,
so yeah, the reason why Newcastle and
Nottingham is probably easier is because
they don't have loads and loads of money
there. They don't think they're better
than they actually are, you know. Well,
you know, they're still probably [ __ ]
but obviously the reality is you are
decent looking. You are you are
good-looking. As much as these people
want to try and say that you're not, you
know, and obviously like you dress good.
So, you know, if you're going somewhere
where there's less competition,
something's going to give. Whereas in
London, they they truly think they're
better than they actually are.
You know, because they live in London,
they think they're better than everyone,
even more so. And they're really really
really not. And also add to the fact
that there's less competition.
You know, most people in England don't
have money, you know. So, you know, when
you go Nottingham, they're having less
money. But if you come and they think
you're from, you know, they see you're from London,
obviously something's going to give in it.
Yeah, it's basically it is pretty much
the same all over. But I mean, I got
approached when I was in Newcastle, bro.
Like, even when I went to Scotland, I
thought it was going to be a lot better
than it was.
I don't think I got I got a boyfriend
there, but I think they were very they
were they were still stuck up.
I even went drinking in Scotland and
they were still stuck up.
You know what I mean? So,
but there they all just they're just not interested.
Yeah, stop talking about yourself.
But yeah, they're just not interested.
So, but I might go out on Saturday just
cuz I need to get a haircut. I might
just want to go for a drink anyways.
Yeah. Yeah. This finish one is good, bro.
I can't believe you've never been up north, Kieran.
I can't believe you've like never been
to like a different city. That's [ __ ]
madness, bro. I'm not saying I'm any
better than you. I'm not better than
anyone. I don't think I'm better than
anyone, bro. But you know, like a lot of
these people in London. But it's just
mad to think at like 23, 24, I was
traveling the country
and you was in your little bedroom
drinking your little alien pops. Yeah, man. Yeah.
They literally are all the same. Women
Unless this finished one isn't.
But you could go there. She could be a [ __ ] It's horrible. [ __ ] horrible.
I think I'm getting addicted to Reddit again.
But yeah, Joe, you really need to stop
with the gay jokes, man. It's very immature.
It's very, very, very immature of you, boss.
I woke up at 1:30 today. Jeez, madness. Nope.
I'm going to mention you in my video as
well, Joe. You need to stop with that
gay thing. It's very, very immature.
You know, you're supposed to be more
mature than me
cuz it's sort of a way of you dismissing
the struggles, you know.
And you know what's going to happen as
well as soon as I do this video, Kieran,
you're going to get Virgin Boy saying,
"Why have I never had any of these
problems when he's literally been on
five dating apps? He's had to resort to
disabled girls. He can't even function
in a normal environment."
And then it's like, "What the fuck?" But
you just know Virgin Boy is going to do
that because that's what he does all the time.
Yeah, but why would you tell people to
be gay? That's ridiculous.
Oh, [ __ ] My phone's going to die.
Do not die. Do not die.
[ __ ] It doesn't matter if he's got a
girlfriend. He's got a disabled
girlfriend. Listen, Joe. You know, all
of this girlfriend thing. Yeah. Let me
let me tell you something. He's not in a
I can't even believe that he's happy
with her because every single woman that
I have been with, he's tried getting
with USA, Izzy, Sig, all of these other
women. So, you can't even say that he's
actually happy with her regardless of
whoever the [ __ ] it is. Because look at that whole
look at that whole uh USA Izzy thing.
That's not somebody that's happy in a relationship, bro.
And it's not to [ __ ] with me because
they don't understand that the stress
they're putting on them by doxing them.
You understand? It's nothing to me. I
know what I've done with a [ __ ] So at
the end of the day, you're just causing
issues in their life, which is why they
had to privatize everything. So I mean,
he's with a dis. It doesn't matter what
I say about her. He's not even happy with her.
You can't even say cuz there could be
somebody with a with there could be
somebody with somebody in a wheelchair.
There could be somebody with in a in a
[ __ ] wheelchair with someone and they
could be happy. But he's not even happy
with the [ __ ]
That's why he stalks all the women that
I've been with.
but then tries to call me ugly.
>> Yeah. madness.
What do you mean I get on better with
men? You need to grow up, lad. You need
to You need to grow up. Why would I Why
do I get on better with men? Because
they're not stuck up.
No, that's a universal thing.
I know. I don't just prefer [ __ ] I
actually like sex now and I like tits.
So, actually, that stage over with now, actually.
Yeah. And then Monty saying, "I asked
him for a blowjob." Yeah. I don't know
why he's making up lies like that. But
he actually did ask for an escort. That
is actually no lie. He actually wanted an escort.
He said, "Oh, let's get an escort." And
obviously I didn't have the money
because um I lost my car, didn't it? So
I had to get my sister to send me 150.
It was a nightmare and I had to give her
the money back.
Yeah, he did ask for one. Yeah, he did.
Oh, [ __ ] Yeah, he did.
He did. Yeah.
Yeah, he did. I never [ __ ] Why would
I ask him for a [ __ ] bro? [ __ ] mad.
You're talking about yourself.
Not nice. I really fancy some fried
chicken. Have you ever fancy that, Joe?
Just some nice fried chicken
from the chicken c.
Um, again, I have been in a relationship
with a woman and I've also been with
women and I've had chances to be in a
relationship with a woman. You've never
even been laid. You've probably never
even seen a woman naked.
So, I mean, you've never even been with
a woman ever in any kind of way. So, I
don't know how you're going to sit on
here and talk about me when I've pulled more women
than you would ever pull. You've never
even been seen with a woman. So, every
all of this projecting stuff is ridiculous.
You've never even seen a woman naked.
You've never even had sex with a woman.
cuz I generally believe that most of
these people on here are are virgins. I
gen No, I generally do. At first I
thought, yeah, they can't be cuz they're
30s and they're in their 40s. But I
generally believe that these people are virgins
and I have had and I have been in a
relationship with a woman and I've had
chances of being in a relationship with
a woman. So yeah,
again, you forget what you want to
forget. You've seen me with multiple
different women. But again, you remember
what you want to remember. Just like the
money thing, just like the meeting
people thing, just like everything you just remember.
Well, come on here and prove what you've
got then. Okay? Come on here and prove
what you got. Show everybody your
misses. Okay? Come on the hangouts right
before trying to speak about me never
being in a relationship when I've
literally been with more women than you
have. Come and show us what you've got.
I'm telling you that you ain't got a
woman and you've never been with a woman
in any other in in any way.
You're talking like I've not been with
more women than you. What? Because I
don't s because I smell the coffee
coffee and I tell you that they're [ __ ]
and they're [ __ ] That means what?
I've never been with a woman. What?
Because I'm not a s.
So come on here and show your misses.
I'm going to put your link. I'm going to
put the link up. Show us your misses.
Come on. You know, [ __ ] sake. Every
single time with these people in this
community. Come on. Let's see your Let's
see your misses. I'm going to put the
link up. Let's see your misses. Come on.
I don't want to see your kids. I want to
see your misses. Come on.
Show us your girlfriend. Stop coming on
here every day and [ __ ] projecting
every single [ __ ] day. Let's see your
girlfriend. Come on. Let's see your
[ __ ] girlfriend. Come and hang out
and talk. Come on. Let's see your
girlfriend. If you've got five kids,
let's see your girlfriend. Come on. Come
on. The link's there. Come on. Let's see
your relationship with your woman, you
self-reflector. Come on. Come on then.
This is why I weren't going to come on
here today, cuz it's just the same
idiots starting [ __ ] that they can't
[ __ ] finish every [ __ ] time. Let's
see your girlfriend. Come on. Stop self
projecting. Exactly. Then shut the [ __ ]
up then. Don't come on here and start
[ __ ] talking about [ __ ] other
people. Yeah. If you're not going to
prove anything your [ __ ] self, just
cuz I'm not a s and I don't defend women
because I believe that they're generally
evil doesn't mean that I've never been
with one. I'm not answering your
questions until you come in here and you
show us your girlfriend. I'm not
answering any of your questions. That'll
be after. I'm not answering any of your
questions until you show me your
girlfriend. I'm not answering any of
your questions. Simple.
You're not in a relationship. You're
single. You've never seen a woman naked
and you have to lie that you got [ __ ]
kids. Like, bomb, you're [ __ ] sick to
lie that you got kids. Five kids. Not
even believable. Most people don't even
have [ __ ] five kids, you idiot. Five
kids. I think the most common thing is free.
You don't have a relationship. That's
why you won't join the link. Stop
talking about other people
again. You remember what you want to
remember. You're all the same on here.
Right. And you're banned. Bye-bye. Now,
[ __ ] idiot. Not even going to join the link
because I don't simp. I'm apparently gay.
So, because I don't simp, I'm apparently
gay. That's never been in a
relationship, never been with a woman.
What? Because I'm going off by my experiences.
And you know, this is why I don't deal
with these women anymore.
This is generally why I don't deal with
them. I'm not contradicting myself cuz I
don't deal with them anymore.
I don't deal with them anymore. So, it's
not like I'm contradicting anything I'm
saying. You know,
I believe what I'm saying, which is why
I don't deal with them. You know, I do believe. >> Amen.
What the [ __ ]
>> What? What? Why are you letting these people?
>> Can't even hear. My phone's [ __ ]
>> What the [ __ ] bro? What's wrong with my phone? Right.
I'll be back later. I'm going to get some chicken.