Where I'm back,
that [ __ ] wed out of me. Reminded me
of bomb, mate. That's what bomb needs to
[ __ ] do. That can't. Oh [ __ ]
[ __ ] fat bastard.
Fat bastard bomb.
Oh, that was some love exercise. That
was it. Reminded me of Greasy.
[ __ ] hell. I best get used. I need to
[ __ ] start [ __ ] working too soon,
mate. [ __ ] hell.
I just thought that
when a [ __ ] three mile [ __ ] walk
just took it right out of me. Well, I
had some chicken,
which my favorite chicken shop, but
actually I never really
uh had a chicken from there cuz they're
trying to make me wait. [ __ ]
Do do I go out Friday? Do I not? Uh,
Saturday. Sorry. What's tomorrow? Thursday. Okay. Heat. Thank you. You You know,
we all [ __ ] up now. That's what we
are. We all [ __ ] up.
We're [ __ ] up.
That's what we all [ __ ] up.
Slow, slow, slow.
Oh, with the finish one, you're being a bit uh
you're being a bit forward. But we're
we're 20 we're 27, bro. We're almost 28.
We're running out of [ __ ] time here.
So, we need to be we need to be
assertive. We ain't got any time to waste.
Yeah. I was speaking to Finnish Izzy. I
said to her, I'm going to come over. But
we can get your nails done and you can
teach me some finish.
How lush is that? We ain't got any time
to waste here, man. Yeah.
Accountability is a lot of people's
is a lot of people's um worst nightmare.
Definitely. women's English.
Horrible, isn't it?
I feel like I've done so much there'd be
like no point in me even going out
on [ __ ] Friday and [ __ ] Honestly, bro,
it's just no point, is it? Friday, Saturday.
Oh, funny. It's weird. I fancy a beer
today even though it's raining.
I just don't see the point. Yeah.
Do you see any point in going out Saturday drinking
a lot, mate? I need to be I need to get
paid for this [ __ ]
I would go out Saturday, but I don't see
there to be a point. No, man.
But what's the point?
I don't know about it,
but my thoughts are they're all [ __ ] if
that's really happening.
So, I was on um Reddit today, Jensen,
and I was showing these people, this
woman, my bad experiences with women and
how they waste my time. They give me
their number and then, you know, they
waste my time and no, no, no, no, no,
no. And she just didn't care. She just
kept saying I was coming on too strong.
I showed her where they wasting my time.
She weren't interested. It's [ __ ]
depressing, bro. It's honestly so you know?
It's horrible, isn't it?
Yeah, they have shadowbanned me. They
have shadowbanned me, but I use a VPN.
Yeah, but they have shadow banned me,
bro. I use a VPN. So yeah,
it's bad in it, bro. Bad, bad, bad, bad.
They're just not interested in this
country, are they, Jensen?
What? What are these women
just not interested in this country? Are they
But people on Reddit say that you're
going to meet someone. You're going to
meet someone eventually.
That's what people on Reddit say.
>> Yeah. But then some people on Reddit say
that I'll meet someone eventually
and they said, "Oh, if you generally
think women are evil, you shouldn't be
dating." I generally do think that they're evil
and accountability is their worst nightmare.
Accountability is women's worst nightmare.
It was just some fried chicken from a chicken shop.
I walk two miles and walk two miles back. [ __ ]
I know. Crazy, right?
I probably will really cuz I've been
trying since I was 22 and I'm 28 next month and
That's horrible, bro.
Sometimes I feel like you should just
kill yourself cuz like the dating game
is like against you and [ __ ] It's like
stacked against men. You should just
kill yourself. I generally feel like
that, you know.
Yeah, Greg. I walk two miles and walk
two miles back.
You know, these women can go around
having sex with you they want and you
you have to deal with nothing but bad
experiences. It's horrible.
Think about it. It's depressing. Reezy
how the dating game is rigged against
men. It's depressing.
It's so bad. I mean, I don't know about
you, Steven, but whenever I think of
like the dating game and [ __ ] it makes me depressed.
How about you?
I already had fried chicken and chips.
It's [ __ ] depressing, bro. Even
thinking about it. Yeah,
it makes you it makes you want to kill
yourself when you think of the dating
game and [ __ ] and like all the [ __ ] that
you've been through in your life. This
is why I keep not going out, Grezy.
This is why I keep not wanting to go out
because it's too depressing,
you know? It's not even about money.
It's just too depressing, bro. Seeing
it, thinking of it, it's horrible.
You know, it doesn't change. Nothing
changes. Literally in this country,
nothing changes at all. It's [ __ ]
I think one day I will be doing it.
Yeah, probably soon.
probably will do it soon. To be honest,
I don't give a [ __ ] if I'm locked in
Mid. Stop comparing me to other people.
I don't give a [ __ ] who's worse off to
me, who's better off to me. I don't give a [ __ ]
just thinking of suicide to be honest
because of this whole dating thing,
you know, knowing that women have it
easy. All the bad experiences you've had.
This is why I keep not going out, bro. I
keep saying I'm going to go out and I
just don't end up doing it.
Kind of been there, done it, worn a
t-shirt sort of thing, you know?
I'm actually thinking of doing it, bro.
I'm not even joking.
It's [ __ ] depressing, bro. You know
what I'm saying? Just thinking about it.
And the people that are trying to give
you advice have it easy. They can get
whatever they want, whenever they want.
It's just depressing, bro. I'm in.
It's [ __ ] depressing.
with this woman on Reddit all day. They
didn't decide they wasted my time on
purpose, which is what I've keep
explaining. They never They decided they
wasted my time from the get- go. They
didn't decide they wasted my time on
purpose. We're having the same argument
over and over and over and over again.
I don't think I know that cuz I've seen
it. I don't think I know.
I know. I don't think I know.
I'm not thinking. I'm knowing. And I'm
showing. I'm not thinking. I'm knowing.
And I'm showing. Let me Let me reply.
I'm not thinking. I'm knowing and I'm showing.
I don't think anything. I know. You know
what I'm saying?
Women can't do wrong in your eyes. It's
a waste of [ __ ] time. It's a waste of
time going back and back and forth. You know,
I'm not thinking I'm knowing. I'm not
thinking I know him. >> Yep.
Simple. I'm not thinking I know him.
Yeah. This is what makes me want to kill
myself every single time I go on this
[ __ ] and people are telling me what I
know cuz I'm showing. I'm not thinking,
Gregy. I'm showing. I'm not thinking
anything. I'm knowing and I'm showing.
You know, that's one thing about me.
I'm knowing and I'm showing.
the same old [ __ ] every single time you
go on here. Every single time I'm
knowing and I'm showing and you're only
saying and I'm knowing and I'm showing
Now I'm angry there.
this [ __ ] to go get raped in a minute.
If she keeps winding me up, I'm just
going to tell her to go get raped.
If they don't leave me alone, bro, I'm
just going to tell them to go get raped
if they don't stop. Yeah, simple, bro.
I generally hate them grieving.
I generally generally generally hate
them, bro. I generally generally
generally hate all women. I'm not even joking.
You know what I'm saying? I generally
hate them. I hope they all get raped and
acid in their face. I'm not even joking, lad.
I generally hope they all get raped. I'm
not even joking.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] I hope they all get
raped. All of them
and their kids [ __ ] scumbags.
I hope them and their kids will get raped. Simple, bro. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
And that's it, bro.
It's depressing talking to these people,
bro. Very, very, very, very depressing
talking to these people. Yep.
You can't even have opinion without getting shadowbanned. Bye-bye. Yeah,
I feel like self harm and just talking
to this [ __ ] [ __ ] is just making me
want to kill I feel this reminded me how
bad the dating game is. You know what I mean?
It's [ __ ] depressing, bro.
No, but they get what they want whenever
they want and they're trying to
manipulate me and I don't like it. It's
not weak. How can you say I'm weak when
I've been up and down the country and
I've tried more than anybody in the
world? How can someone do that if
they're weak? No weak person can do
that. No weak person would have put up
with their [ __ ] [ __ ] for how many
[ __ ] years I put up with these
[ __ ] little [ __ ] Do you understand
what I'm [ __ ] saying? That is not
weak. That is strong to have dealt with
their [ __ ] over and over and over again.
I'm not your [ __ ] mate. Now go and get raped.
Go and get raped, mate. [ __ ] [ __ ] Stupid [ __ ]
mate. Go and get raped. I'm not your
[ __ ] mate. You understand, bro? Stop
calling me mate. Go get raped. Mate
rhymes with mate. You [ __ ] stupid little [ __ ]
I'm not your [ __ ] mate. You silly
little [ __ ] Now go get [ __ ] raped,
you silly little [ __ ] Yeah,
I'm not your [ __ ] mate, you silly
little [ __ ] Now go get [ __ ] raped,
you silly [ __ ]
I'm not your [ __ ] mate.
You women are evil [ __ ] [ __ ] I'm
glad I'm I'm I'm happy men go and rape
men, you know.
I'm so glad when I hear about these
women getting raped. You know that I'm
single because of you horrible evil [ __ ]
You deserve it for
being cons your life.
Being cons your life.
I don't give a [ __ ] I don't give a
[ __ ] [ __ ] I hope they get raped. I
hate them. I love it when men rape them.
I hate them, bro. They're [ __ ] They've
been [ __ ] all their life,
you know? They're [ __ ] to people all
their life. [ __ ] go and get raped.
That's [ __ ] nothing compared to what
I I just did wish it on them. Well, I
can cuz I just did. I hope they all get
raped. All of them.
I can because I just did. I hope they
all get raped. All of them. And I'll say it again.
ignore dismissing all my experiences
again. They just keep dismissing my
experiences every single time. You know
what I mean?
You're a narcissist. You're a
narcissist. Dismissing the normal and nice.
I'm not your [ __ ] mate.
I'm not your [ __ ] mate. I'm not your
I'm not no rape victim's [ __ ] mate. Yeah.
Listen, I'm not I'm not your [ __ ] mate.
Oh my god. Stop calling me your I'm not
your [ __ ] mate.
I'm not friends with rape victims. [ __ ] off,
mate. I'm not your mate. You silly
little rape victim.
For [ __ ] sake, I'm not your [ __ ] mate.
I'm not your [ __ ] I'm not with stuck up
little westernized [ __ ] that need to
get raped. I'm not your [ __ ] mate.
Go get raped, mate.
Go get raped, mate. I'm not your [ __ ]
Silly little [ __ ]
And I Yeah,
I'm not your [ __ ] mate, you silly
little [ __ ] You know what I'm saying?
I'm not your [ __ ] mate. Stop calling
me I'm not mate with rape victims. Scumbags.
You know what I mean? I'm not [ __ ]
I'm not mate with scumbags.
Evil time wasters,
[ __ ] rape victims, silly little [ __ ]
[ __ ] mate. I'm not your [ __ ] mate.
Stop calling me your [ __ ] mate
with evil scum.
[ __ ] stupid little [ __ ]
They're such narcissists. These [ __ ]
are such narcissists, lad. They're
[ __ ] such narcissists.
They're such narcissists.
Know what I mean?
Uh, leading somebody on and wasting
someone's time is
Yes, it is. Yes, it is. Leading someone
on and wasting
their time definitely is.
Uh-huh. Definitely is. We got We've been
arguing all day.
And a fact. And a fact.
You ignore normal nice messages
to negative. And you reply to negativity.
You're [ __ ] evil scum. Don't [ __ ]
sit there and tell me you're [ __ ]
not. It's [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying? They are truly
the scum of the earth. And a fact. And a
fact you ignore.
Yeah. A negative message. You ignore
normal nice message.
You reply to straight away. Scumbags. Narcissistic. Narcissist. Narcissists
dude [ __ ] know what I'm saying, bro.
Listen, Monty. No one want no one cares.
Look at your [ __ ] fat ugly [ __ ]
black [ __ ] flat [ __ ] ugly bird.
You've been turned down all your life.
Look at who you're with. The slag of
Birmingham. The biggest slag in Yeah.
They reply to negativity. You get turned
down. Look at that [ __ ] ugly [ __ ]
you're with. Look at that ugly slag
you're with. You was crying over an ugly
slag. Somebody that does not get [ __ ]
turned down. Don't [ __ ] do that.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] Look madness.
Ignoring normal messages. Yeah,
[ __ ] these women, bro. I hope they will
get raped. All of them. The [ __ ] lot
That's a red flag.
That is a [ __ ] red flag that they
only reply to negativity. Yeah. No. [ __ ]
off. I'm not giving If you got anything
to say, come to London today. Yeah. If
you've got anything to say, come to
London today and say it to my face. I'm
not going back and forth and back and
forth and back and forth. Anyways, I'll
be back later. Yeah, I'm all good with this