madness blocking me on Reddit. What a loser.
What a [ __ ] loser.
[ __ ] people on Reddit, eh?
Booking people on Reddit.
Do a video to this person later.
Bad, bad, bad.
I just come off Reddit for a bit. I
won't be able to stay on live.
Yeah, just these people on Reddit are
pissing me off.
People on Reddit are pissing me off, lad.
keep defending women. It's [ __ ]
annoying. I hate them, bro.
I [ __ ] hate women. I swear to God, I hate them.
Yeah, I'm going to do another video. Um,
Cory, I'm going to be back with another presentation
later on today. I hope you watch my
videos. I'm going to be back with
um I'm going to be back with another presentation.
I know you like my little presentations,
isn't it? Yeah.
Back with another presentation.
You like that? Then
she said she works for the police. I
said, "Come on then. [ __ ] you pigs. [ __ ]
the lottery you." That's what I said. Yeah.
Everything you're saying and everything
you're thinking is normal. Even Even
though it sounds like an extreme, oh,
you're saying, "Oh, women should get,"
but but it's actually normal because if
anyone went through half of what you've
been through, they would have ended up
killing someone. They wouldn't even be
saying [ __ ] bro. They would generally
not even be saying stuff. they would
actually have killed someone by now.
So, I mean, it's very, very, very
normal. Like, at the end of the day,
right? Have you ever heard of there's
only so much someone can take?
You know what I'm saying? There's
literally only so there's only so much
someone can take. They would have killed
someone by now, bro. They would have.
These are just verbal [ __ ] words
cuz they would have ended up killing
someone that they had to go around
dealing with [ __ ] women's [ __ ] for
[ __ ] years and years and years and
[ __ ] years. You know what I'm saying?
They would have ended up killing
someone, bro. It's not even a joke. So yeah,
they ignored all the text messages. They
resorted to making up stuff. It's madness.
And I was like, "No, they have literally
done it on purpose."
You know what I'm saying? Like they have
done it on [ __ ] purpose. What the
So what if you said a few vile words?
They're only verbal [ __ ] things. Look
at what these [ __ ] have done. They make
it out like it's not a big deal. But it
is a big deal. You know, actions speak
[ __ ] louder than [ __ ] words.
All of the piss taken that they've been
doing for years. All of the [ __ ]
What would have these people done? Oh,
would have they just been okay? Oh, it's
all right. Oh, that's fine. You know
what I'm saying?
No, they would have probably ended up in
prison or ended up killing someone.
That makes me depressed, bro. So yeah,
and they don't suddenly decide.
They've already decided they're going to
waste your time and mock you. That's why
they do this. That's what they they do
the [ __ ] they do on purpose.
They do the [ __ ] they do on purpose.
Stop. They They won't have any bad
things say about said about women.
Why? I never go out anymore. This is why
I don't go out drinking anymore.
This is literally why I don't anymore, bro.
Because of this exact reason. You know
what I mean? Because of this exact reason.
And then you got Greavesy trying to say
I'm weak when bro, I'd love to see
someone else put up with this [ __ ] for
as long as I have.
I would love to see someone else [ __ ]
put up with this [ __ ] as long as I've I have
one that once that day is proven, then
I'll be like, okay. But it will never be
proven because no one has put up with
this [ __ ] as much as I have. And then I
get called weak. I'm going to add that
into that into this uh presentation as well.
I'd love to see them going around the
country speaking to men for years or
speaking to women for years. I'd love to
see how they do.
Wow, that's crazy, bro. And they and
they say that you're weak. You're weak.
Wow. You was weak. You wouldn't have put
up with that [ __ ] for [ __ ] years, you know?
depression in it, bro.
Yeah. They said they work for the
police. I said, "Come on then. Call the
[ __ ] police. I don't give a fuck."
You know what I'm saying?
You think I give a [ __ ] about the police, bro? Stupid [ __ ]
What do you want to say now? Yeah.
I'm going to be back with another presentation.
I'm going to start copying S guide
videos now. You know, it's going to be w
uh accountability is women's worst nightmare. Yeah.
Accountability is a woman's worst nightmare.
Until someone's been in the exact same
position as you and dealt with all of
the [ __ ] that you've been with, they
can't they can't judge. They can't judge
what you should say or what you shouldn't say.
No, but Oh, that's lovely. Then if a
woman got killed on a bus,
that's [ __ ] lush. That's amazing. Lovely.
That is bloody bloody bloody lovely.
I never heard about it, but that's
[ __ ] lush. One scumbag off the street. Yeah.
One scum. Oh, I hope it was Was it USA?
Is he? I hope it was USA. Is he?
So what if you said, "Oh, you hope
someone gets raped." Bro, that's nothing
compared to what they've done over the
years. Saying Say saying something is
verbal. saying something verbal, right,
is nothing compared to what these piss
taken, stuck up [ __ ] have done over the
years, it doesn't even compare, bro.
Like, how many times has someone told
someone, and I know I'm right, like to
you, right, it might seem like, oh,
well, yeah, you might you need
professional help and no, but what a lot
of these people don't understand is
they've not been through what you've
been through. So, how can they tell you
what is normal? You understand, bro? How
can they tell you what is normal, what
is not normal if they have been through
half the [ __ ] you have? Think about it, bro.
So, what would they just be all dandy?
Oh, well, yeah, it's fine. Oh, women
don't owe me nothing. No, no, no, no. Is
that what they'd be like? Really? No.
No, they [ __ ] wouldn't, bro. So,
unless you've walked a mile and unless
you've walked a quarter of a mile in in
my shoes, don't [ __ ] judge.
That's the way I see it.
Richie, that's the way I see it, lad. Yeah. Good.
Good. I'm glad.
I'm [ __ ] glad.
Women are [ __ ] evil
and they try to use your reaction
against you. That's narcissistic. Like, yeah,
they do it on purpose. The leading on
the piss taken. Of course they do on
purpose. You silly goose. Don't be
silly. Don't be so naive. Of course they do.
They love getting getting a reaction out
of people. They love this [ __ ] This is
why I don't waste my [ __ ] time with
them anymore, you know?
So that's where we're at basically. Yeah, mom.
It's Thursday tomorrow.
Yeah. They just got no They've just got
no bad words to say about women. It's
insane, bro. They don't ever think
they're ever in the wrong that they
would not do any of these things on purpose.
And then she was trying to say, "Oh,
well, you've wrote like I said, yeah, I
wrote negative things to them to prove
that they reply back to negativity."
What the [ __ ]
All these people that sit there and say
that you need help, they've never been
through what you've been through.
So, how can they judge? If they've not
been through what you've been through,
how can they judge? You understand?
You understand what I mean, bro? How can they judge?
That's the way I see it. Yeah.
I mean, bro. Madness. Madness.
I [ __ ] hate women. I hate women,
Cory. I don't know about you.
I [ __ ] hate him.
And I'd love somebody to tell me one day
what coming off too strong means.
I would love to know what that means,
coming off too strong.
I'd love somebody to explain that to me
one day. What that actually means,
coming off too strong. I would love I
would love somebody to explain that to
me one day.
I hate them. I think they're evil,
narcissistic little [ __ ]
That's why I don't bother with them.
Once you've met one, you've met them all.
That's the way I see it. They're all the same.
Well, I shouldn't say they're all the
same really because, you know, you get
people on there, they do exactly all the
same stuff and they say exactly all the
same things for people that aren't the same.
They do exactly the same thing as each
other. Same mannerisms. They say the
same stuff, but yeah, apparently they're
not the same, but they just do the same stuff. Madness, it
not all the same.
they resort to making up stuff. So, I
feel like it's to the point now where
there's not even no point in you even
saying anything. There's no point you
going on Reddit.
There's no point you even having a a a a voice
cuz they will just call you all these
mad things like an incel that you you
can't even say anything, you know?
sit there and defend women.
Sitting online defending women all the [ __ ] time. Look.
You want to take my money, Cory? I'll
[ __ ] take yours.
You take my money, I take yours.
You want to [ __ ] take my money, I'll
[ __ ] take yours.
That's a banger line, is it?
I'm speaking to that woman that's a um
promoter for clubs.
Maybe she can get me a job or something.
Made like £300 a day doing that, matey.
Would I [ __ ] yeah, bro? What I [ __ ]
I'm going to start selling weed, Cory.
Yeah, I'm going to start selling weed.
No, I'm joking.
You know what I'm saying?
I'll be back later or tomorrow. Yeah.