Okay. I am
[ __ ] just just woke up. [ __ ] hell. Yo,
[ __ ] going start going bed like 600 7:00
in the [ __ ] morning me
[ __ ] lazy goose I am
well at least finish is you reply back
I forgot to say though it's finished is
There's been lots of them. [ __ ] Yeah, man.
The vibrator makes it more [ __ ] uh
realistic, is it?
Do you know the one I was with about two
weeks ago wanted to meet me?
Well, I can't be bothered meeting her. I
can't be bothered meeting them.
The other one I done a video with.
No way. That's two people that had been
up for meeting on Sunday, but obviously
one doesn't even live in the country.
But I mean, for [ __ ] sake, bro. Yeah.
Could meet her Saturday, but can't be bothered.
Can't be [ __ ]
be [ __ ] me in any of the [ __ ]
Sick of him, man. [ __ ] sick of him. Yeah.
See that n that
account? That's a bit odd. It'll
probably come back on another account.
That's what these people do. You see on
this community, that's what these people do. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
It always goes back to this [ __ ] gay
thing. You tell people your experiences
with women and straight, oh, it's be
it's be gay. It's be gay.
How about you just don't like any of
them? How about you just don't like men or women?
But no, straight straight to gay.
Straight to being gay. [ __ ] immature.
It's just immature. That is
I'm not sure.
Can't believe I wake up like 1:00 in the afternoon. Madness.
Some madness. Waking up one in the [ __ ] afternoon. Yeah, man.
It'll always be the same. It'll always
be the same old [ __ ]
You know that one in the video. They
want to meet me on Saturday, but I can't be asked.
I don't have one in my video, but I
can't be bothered.
I can't be bothered meeting any of the [ __ ]
I gave up a long time ago, bro.
I got that one in the video that wants
to meet me
Saturday, but I can't be bothered.
I leave the piss takers to themselves.
I'm good, man.
The only one I speak to is that Finnish
Izzy and that one.
I said to her, "I hate women." She
replied straight away, but she still
wants to meet even though I said that.
But she didn't get my other messages.
Yeah, bro. Gave up a long time ago, man.
Long [ __ ] time ago. Yeah.
[ __ ] sake, man. Not possible.
Stop bringing stupid rumors on my channel.
Stop making up stupid immature rumors in my channel.
Grow up, lad. Nope.
No, not at all.
Well, that's a bit hard considering I've
met her in real life. Stop making up
silly little rumors on my chat and like
your age. Actor age, not your shoe size.
No, not at all.
That one in that video wants to meet me, but
I'm not going to meet her.
I've actually given up on the [ __ ]
Bro, stop talking [ __ ] I've met her in
real life. Stop talking [ __ ] on my channel. Yeah, simple.
A mission just to set me up when I've
met her in real life. Stop talking [ __ ]
grow up, bro. You're [ __ ] probably
twice my [ __ ] age. That's that.
But yeah, she wants to meet Saturday,
but I'm not going to meet her. I don't
know when I'm going to be out drinking
again, bro. Probably never.
Probably [ __ ] never, to be honest.
Uh, it never happened. He's full of
[ __ ] End of that.
I'm not being sensitive, man. Just stop
making up stupid [ __ ]
What is it with you people making up
stupid [ __ ] [ __ ] You got [ __ ]
Monty saying that I I wanted a [ __ ]
off him. What the [ __ ] What is it with
you people, man? You're so immature.
Yeah, Monty made up a story that I asked
him for a [ __ ]
Yeah, he made up a story that I asked
him for a [ __ ] and that never
happened. But yeah, [ __ ] sake.
Well, someone said wrong.
I'm at the age now Tim loves drugs and
I'm too old for it to to go out and
[ __ ] I can't be bothered with it
anymore. dealing with their [ __ ]
I can't be [ __ ] I can't be [ __ ]
dealing with their [ __ ] bro.
So, I don't know when I'll be out again.
Like, like I said, probably never.
I can't be bothered with them. They're
all the same.
I was watching Oreo Man last night.
Yeah, I was watching Oreo land last night, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. Oh, yeah, man.
Nah, I'm all right, bro. I'm good. I
think I'm pullyully done in this country.
Nah, I don't think I'm going to bother
and I've got money and everything, but
it's not about that. Believe in me. It
ain't about that. I cut the going out
even when I still had the [ __ ] house.
And I've been going out a few times as
well. You know what I'm saying? It's not
even about the money. It's nothing to do
with the money.
No, it's not true.
So, um, nah, I don't think I'll go out
this week, bro, either. I'm tired of it,
ghosting. It's boring. It's just the
same [ __ ] with these women every time.
I'm bored of it now.
You know, the only one I'm speaking to
is that one from Finland and the other
one I met um, a few weeks ago.
I just can't I don't have the energy for
it, bro. Know what I mean? I don't have
the energy for it anymore. I was
watching the Oreo man, you know,
yesterday and a lot of the stuff he says is relatable.
Yeah. But it's not even fun anymore,
though. Not It's not fun.
I don't even find it fun anymore.
So yeah, I'll be staying in I think
that's good. Good for you, man.
But yeah, I'm just chilling. Probably
just go for a walk later and then come
back or a daily walk and that maybe do a
couple of miles. But yeah,
I can stay indoors all the time. Watch
me. I've been doing it for a couple of
weeks, so I can do it all the time. Watch me.
I can do it because I've been doing it
for a couple of weeks.
So, and I went for a walk yesterday for
like an hour or two.
Bernando is nice.
I'm going to have some chicken cooked
for me today. I think
life is [ __ ] [ __ ] You live, you get
bad experiences, you [ __ ] die.
It's [ __ ] Life is [ __ ]
Honest to God, life is [ __ ]
Life can do one. You know what I mean?
Life can absolutely [ __ ] off and do one.
It's [ __ ] boring, bro.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Yeah, I could go out today if I wanted to.
Go out if I wanted to.
Go out whenever I wanted to.
probably be [ __ ]
You know, wasting your time getting your
hair done. No thanks.
I ain't had I ain't had none. Well,
actually, I did have with my sister
actually maybe a month ago.
Actually, like a month ago, I think I
did. My sister bought me Nos. Oh,
no. I haven't.
Stupid question asking that when you
already know the answer to it.
You know this situation, you know it's
never going to change. So asking that is just ridiculous. Stupid question.
Stupid question you're asking there, lad.
When you already know the answer,
the only one I've got is someone in Finland.
on this other one.
Oh, I don't know, bro. And I don't give a [ __ ]
It's not even much money anyways, bro.
For [ __ ] sake. I don't know why you
keep bringing it up, bro.
See, no one's actually bought up money
today. And that's not even that much,
bro. You know, you know the money that
Bob's showing is like a couple of months
money. You know that or someone in London.
It's not It's hardly anything.
You know what I'm saying?
They need to actually show real money.
Like actual money, bro. Like actual money, lad.
You know what I'm saying? We're not
talking about money anyways on here. That's self-reflecting. Yeah. Self reflecting. Nope.
We're not talking about money anyways. Not self-reflecting.
The plan is to stay in all day.
Like every day is the same. Every day is
exactly the same.
probably hope I die in my sleep. Yeah,
this life sucks dick.
It really does. It sucks dick.
So that's what I can do.
The only thing I do is go for a walk
maybe every other day. It's pointless
doing anything to this life. It sucks.
It's pointless even trying to do anything
pretty much. Yeah,
this life sucks.
No, a job would make me more depressed.
A job would make me more depressed.
Nah, there's nothing to love life about. It's [ __ ]
There's nothing There's nothing to life
love. There's nothing
There's nothing to love about this life. It's dead. So,
there's nothing to love about this life, lad.
I don't need a job. I'm not talking
about getting a job.
I don't need a job. Yeah. Once you're
dead, you go back to before you were born. Yeah.
It's not even like I'm skinn or nothing.
I promise you I'm not. But you're not
going to believe me anyways. You know,
I'm really really really not.
Nah, I can't be bothered.
Can't be bothered, mate.
Nah, I'm all right. All I know is I'm
done in this country forever.
So that's what I know.
It's so good though in a way because
when the house stopped I had already
stopped before that. So I'd already knew
I'd given up before I was getting that
extra income. So it happened just at the
right time. It couldn't have been a better time.
It couldn't have been well I mean it's
no good time to lose two grand a month
but you know what I'm saying but [ __ ]
no matter how old you are but [ __ ]
still you get my point you know
that's actually [ __ ] scary bro
that's scary as [ __ ] seriously
Yeah. All of these people gave up the
same as me. Wow. Yeah.
All of these people gave up the same as
me at 27.
Well, at least I gave up before I even
lost the house, to be honest.
Do you know what I used to do when I
used to have that house? I never used to
go out for like 6 weeks. I would just
stay in, play GTA, go get some food. I
would literally go get some food, bro.
Like, I wouldn't even
um I would even go out and out and out.
So, it's not about money. Trust me, it's
not about money at all.
Cuz even that back then, bro, I [ __ ]
would not go out for [ __ ] ages.
[ __ ] ages, bro. for weeks.
Even even when I was at the old house,
it's not about money. It's I can't be bothered anymore.
When did I do that house at 23 24? So
that's [ __ ] ace, bro.
The only thing you're doing now is leaving. So yeah,
see when I was like 20, 21, I never used
to have anything.
We still used to go out drinking. I
never had nothing, bro.
I didn't blow the sublet and the the
landlord took me to court. well took it
to court after four years and it was
nothing to do with any of these people
on YouTube. So if they want to keep
thinking that it's them that's got my
money, they can keep thinking that but
it isn't. So you believe what you want
to believe. So yeah,
that that in itself is also depressing.
But then you also have to think that
there's literally most people that don't
even have anything. They don't even have
nothing. A lot of people can't even eat,
you know. So, you know, when you put it like that,
doesn't matter how much I get a month,
mind your own business. But still,
and I'm not getting into this anyways.
We're not getting into this chat about a
bit. Doesn't matter how much I get a month now,
but it's nowhere near what I was getting. So, Yeah,
I would have stayed in that house forever, bro.
I like that house, you know.
Um, but I just want to say that I swear
to God on my [ __ ] mom's life and my
dead dad, these people never stopped any
money of mine. Because if they did stop
any money of mine, I would have killed
them. But I would have killed whoever I
could get my hands on. Just believe
that, bro. Like, I might I know you not
I know you might not think that anyone's
about it or, you know, I might have to
kick some L's in the past or whatever,
but bro, there's a difference between
that and someone stopping someone's money.
You know what I'm trying to say? There's
there's a big difference between that
and someone trying to stop someone's
income. If you actually remember
correctly, when nonslegs tried to get
£200 a month stopped off my money, I put
up posters of the [ __ ] I put up posters
of the little virgin. That that was
because of that. That was literally
because of that. At first it was like
back and forth, back and forth, back and
forth. Then I had the [ __ ] benefits
[ __ ] calling me and I was like, "Oh,
you you want to try and stop my money?
Is that what you're going to do?" Yeah.
So then I went to the little virgin area
and then he went running to the police
and that was because I had the benefit
people calling me up.
But trust me, bro, if anyone stopped any
kind of money of mine, bro, they
wouldn't even this whole community would
be shut down, about it or not about it,
you know, at the end of the day. And I'm
sure a lot of people would be exactly
the same, you know. I'm sure any of you
that have got kids, right, if they if
they if these people like took your kids
away, uh, he didn't stop anything. He
went running to the police and he didn't
leave his house for 3 weeks. But yeah,
you probably forgot that because again,
you you remember what you want to
remember, what suits yourself. Um, but
yeah, I never done anything but stopped
him going to events for literally a
month and made him go running into the
police. But okay, yeah, he never done
anything. But anyways, it's like any of
you that's got kids. Um, it's got it's
like any of you that might have kids,
you know, if anyone stopped your income
for your kids or got your kids took away
from you, I'm sure you'd fight for them,
you know. you know, whether you're about
it or not about it, you know, they, you
know, there could be genuine [ __ ] out
there, but as soon as they tried to [ __ ]
with your real life, that's the end.
Three weeks. Anyways, we're not getting
into this anyways.
Um, but like I said, you people remember
what you want to remember. So, so yeah.
Um, so yeah, you take L's and then you
forget that you took the L's and you
come back like nothing's happened.
Which is why I uh which is why I don't
meet any of you people anymore. Like um
Money Mike, that's why I didn't go to
Birmingham last Friday because we all
know the story of what you people do.
You pretend it never happened and it's a
waste of time and it's a waste of money.
Like all of that [ __ ] I used to do with
with bomb as well, you know, going to
[ __ ] bombs there, like going to
Manchester two times and then they just
either they just come on there like nothing's happened.
So it's pointless, waste of time, you know. Nah,
but if I didn't have that house for
three, four years, I don't know what I
actually would have done, you know?
I don't know what I would have actually
done. I would have been [ __ ]
Well, you got to go out every week. No
one could go out every week on [ __ ]
benefits, bro. The [ __ ] I mean, I could
now cuz I've set like I've I've got a
bit saved up and stuff, but I mean,
generally speaking, you you just can't do it.
I've already pulled women, remember?
I've already pulled women that weren't
the wolves. Or did you forget that?
Probably forgot it. Like you forget most
things that you shown.
It doesn't matter, bro. I'm leaving a country,
so I mean, I'm leaving a country, so
I'll find a way to make more money. And
I'm leaving the country. I'm not going
out every week now. So,
I mean, that's what I'm going to do.
leave the country
and I've also got some money saved up a
little bit as well. So yeah, so I'm not
in a worse situation.
Well, I do hope I [ __ ] die. So yeah. So anyways,
I mean I would have been [ __ ] because
I was going out every week. That's when
I had hope. Now I'm older. I don't have no hope. So yeah.
Yeah. I said to her, "Oh, I can come and
get your we can get your nails done and
we can go for a steak." She said, "That
sounds nice." I said, "Oh, you can teach
me some fitness." She said, "I'd love
to, but it's a very hard language."
All of these people on Reddit, they talk
[ __ ] [ __ ] I'm good at approaching
and I'm good at texting.
So, and I used to go out even without
the house when I was on £700 a month. I
don't know how I done it.
I don't know how I did it, but I done it
in it. You do do it in it.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
That's a one in a million, though. I
don't think anyone from the age of 20
[ __ ] three to 20 [ __ ] seven had a
house to subnet for years. You got lucky, bro.
You know what I'm saying? You got lucky,
bro. Nothing to work for them years.
Jesus Christ. No wonder the [ __ ] Red
Star was so jealous.
No wonder these people, And they still
are jealous as well. I mean, the money's
not everything. But I mean, think of it.
You got someone that's better looking
than them, younger than them. I'm
probably four times as money, four times
as much money as them. But I mean, you
don't have to sublet to make these
people jealous. You know, I've, you
know, they're still jealous now. I'm
still better looking. I'm still younger.
I've still got money. You know what I'm
saying? But they um
no wonder why bro you know if they
actually you know when these people
troll right and they give their reasons
they can't even hold their jealousy so
actually the truth comes out when
they're writing stuff.
No I'm not going out today.
[ __ ] sake man. I could have had 100
pound more. You know I could have had
more. I could have had 100 pound more,
but I lost it on the roulette the other day.
[ __ ] 100 [ __ ] pounds.
All I need to do, mate, is win a£500
both teams to score, mate. And I'll be
laughing, mate. That's what I'll be doing. Laughing.
I can't put £500 on two teams, bro.
I'll put 500 pound on two teams. That'd
be sickening if it loses.
Well, I mean, think about it. It is. It
Think about it.
I'll get I don't get my benefits
tomorrow. I've got money now. You don't
know when I get my money. And you don't
know how much money I have now. Huh?
Yeah. What do you people do every day?
You you come online [ __ ] with people.
Yeah. If you worked every day for a
month, right, and you won a £500 both
teams to score, you would literally be
exactly the same as that house.
I mean, yeah, you'd have less money
coming in, but like where you've built
up so much, it wouldn't even make a difference.
Yeah, that's where she's from.
Would sort my night. Oh, would me right
out. Yeah. So, if you if you won that
and then obviously on top of working for
like a month, you'd be you'd be you'd be
sweet. You'd have more than enough. So,
more than enough is more than enough. you know,
that's the only thing you really could
do, you know. So,
but who knows? Maybe I'll get to be a
landlord again one day. If I win the
lottery, I'll just buy some [ __ ]
houses in [ __ ] Middlesbrough and
[ __ ] rent them out.
And I'll just [ __ ] rent the [ __ ] out.
You can get them for like 22k I think.
No, not gambling.
Peter belly can't afford to be gambling anymore, mate. Oh, man. You can't
[ __ ] sake. Um,
imagine you done a free correct score.
You're talking in the millions, isn't it?
It does. It does in the northeast, matey.
Yeah, exactly. I need to save.
So, it's one or the other. Exactly.
Oh, and another thing is another thing
is uh what was you just saying? Uh yes,
they do exist in the northeast. 22 to
about 26 grand. Yes, they do exist. They
don't exist in London. Yeah, but they
exist in [ __ ] the Northeast. You can
buy a house of about 26 grand.
Yes, you can. In Middlesbr, bro. Yes, You can.
And probably Hull. You can, bro.
Look it up. So,
you imagine Grevy being a landlord.
You're just lucky it stopped now and it
didn't stop years ago to be honest.
To be honest with you,
it'd be really bad if it stopped years ago.
It's still [ __ ] now. It is still [ __ ]
now, but you know, it would have been worse.
I wish I'd say raw, but you don't think
when you're young, you know, when you're
going out [ __ ] gambling, getting
escorts, [ __ ] going on dates, you
don't, you know, you don't think,
you know what I'm saying, Grezy? You
don't think of that [ __ ]
You know what I mean, Bara? And a lot of
people say, "Oh, like," and they didn't
understand that that when you're in
London, there's so much to do in London.
You know, that's why I was out in London
so much because there's so much to
[ __ ] do in London. You know,
he was probably somewhere else and he
I'd been to a lot of places as well.
How I would have done that Manchester in
two days. I would never know. But I
would have done it somehow, you know.
I would have done it somehow.
Yeah, John. Every time I show them
money, they run away.
Would you would have you killed
yourself, Benji? Might if you lost the house. Nah.
Every single time I'm back in this area,
my mental health is [ __ ] every time,
bro. Every time my mental health is
[ __ ] when I'm [ __ ] in this area.
It's so [ __ ] my mental health. Every
time I'm back in this area, bro. [ __ ] bro.
Well, you'd kill yourself.
Nah, you can't be talking like that, matey.
I already was [ __ ] depressed before
it to be honest.
Do these people think I've got nothing,
but I actually do.
But I actually [ __ ] do. That's the [ __ ] thing.
You should have saved like maybe £100 a week
maybe. No, let's see how much you could
save. You could probably You should have saved like
£500 a month. 3.2500 a month. So yeah,
you could have probably saved like500 a
month. Again, you don't think like that,
mate. when you're young and you [ __ ]
think that the shit's never going to stop. So,
but I'm better now than I ever was.
Like [ __ ] when I was like 21, 22, I
had [ __ ] all. I was like the skint
virgin in the bedsit.
[ __ ] one drink, two [ __ ] straws. I
was like the [ __ ] the skin [ __ ] in
the bedsit. The virgin bedsit.
I don't think you understand.
Yeah, nothing wrong with being
materialistic if you've got the money.
Anybody that's got money, anyone that's
got money, um,
progress is better in life. Everyone's
lifestyle changes when they get more
money. That's not materialistic. That's life.
You know, that's what Virgin Boy used to
say. He used to say that I was
materialistic when no people that's got
more money than you, their lives get better.
People adjust to what money that they
get. So what do you expect people to be
getting all of this money and and be
living a basic life? Why would they have
to? They don't have to. And if they
don't want to, they shouldn't be judged for it.
So say you see so say say you see like a
[ __ ] celebrity or a normal person and
then they want to buy designer stuff,
they can do that. They've got the money
to do that. Who are we to judge? That's
their life. We shouldn't say that they're materialistic.
£60 a week to me. Yeah.
Yeah. But my mental health is now [ __ ]
because of that house. It's not even
just the money. Cuz to be honest with
you, I done good last month and I done
good this month. I'm not going to starve
in the slightest. I'm not going to
struggle at all.
Not just [ __ ] income. It's loads of
different [ __ ] things.
And you want me to explain that? That's
them, bro. That's not me.
That's them. That's not me. That's
people that don't want to progress. You
see the money I get now, right? Let me
let me tell you something. The money I
get now is is enough, you know, is but I
I would want more because I want to do I
want to do more things in my life. So,
does that make me materialistic? So, if
somebody doesn't want to live off 60 a
week and they want to do stuff with
their life, does that make them
materialistic because they want more to
do stuff with?
I'm not struggling financially.
Yeah, but I'm not struggling
financially. figure it them people on£60
a [ __ ] week. What the [ __ ] bro?
So you I think you and Ngs has got it
confused. You think anyone that wants to do better
um because they have more money makes them materialistic?
I'm not showing you nothing. I'm not
showing you no money. I've said this a
million times. I'm not showing you
nothing. So there's no point you asking
me to show you money. I'm not showing
money. I'm not meeting anyone.
I'm not doing any of that stuff. So,
there's no point asking. It's pointless.
And if you want to say I'm skin, okay,
I'm skin. Whatever. You know, I don't
give a [ __ ]
There's people on six, mate. I've got
money and I'm not showing you nothing. I
do have money and I'm not showing you
any of it. Simple. I'm not showing you nothing.
Why don't you show me a tenner? Huh? I'm
not showing you nothing.
Why is it with you people bringing up
skin every single day?
[ __ ] madness, bro. What is it with you people?
Why are you asking me to show you a
tenant when I've showed you money plenty of times?
No. No. Let's get into it. Why are you
asking me to show you money when I've
shown you money plenty of times?
You've got 800k in the bank right now. You wish
I had more money now than I did when I
had the house.
But obviously I didn't have as much as I
did have as much coming in. So
I didn't have don't have as much coming
in now. But still, you know, the point
still [ __ ] stands in it.
Yeah. Who should you
do, matey? What should you do, matey?
Well, you can live off fucking£60 a week.
£60 a week. [ __ ] it.
That's funny, bro.
60 a week.
To be honest with you, I shouldn't even
be moaning to be honest. It's not like I
don't [ __ ] have money. It's not like
I don't even It's not like I don't
[ __ ] have money. You know what I'm saying?
I think this the whole thing is just
[ __ ] You know,
I can go out tomorrow, get my haircut,
get pissed, eat if I wanted to, but nah.
I know I know what you're saying. I know
what you're saying like about, you know,
people have less money. I get what
you're saying. You know,
I know what you're saying.
you know. Yeah, there is a lot of people
that live off £300 a month.
I think I got like 1.5 this month and
1.5 last month, which yeah, it's
obviously not as good as 3K, but I mean,
you got no [ __ ] responsibilities or
anything. You got all your bills paid. So,
that's how that's how this conversation
went on with this woman. She was like,
"Oh yeah, after work she's got like 1.1k
left." She's got 1.1k left. Um after like
after like bills and stuff. And
obviously I technically had more this
month and I technically had more last
month because of the um
[ __ ] because of the football in it.
Yeah, but how can people go out drinking
on60 a [ __ ] week?
Yeah. But Yeah. But even if you got 1.5k
a month and you don't work,
that's still quite a lot for um
that's still a lot for a single person
with no after your bills. That's a
that's a lot. That is still quite a lot.
If you got 1.5 if you got 1.5k right a
month and you don't like that's after
everything like that's disposable money.
That's more than probably most people
get disposable. I mean like disposable.
That's still quite a lot. Like
think about it, bro.
It is a lot. It's quite a lot for a
single person with no bills.
You know what I'm saying?
Think about that, bro. Just think about
that. It is quite a lot for a single person.
But I didn't need to win on the
football, but I won on the football a
few times and it and it just helped.
No, I'm just saying it is. It is. It is, man. [ __ ]
I mean, like, if you ain't got any bills
and stuff, then yeah,
that's more than most people have left
of people that work. It's more than most
people have left.
No, but I'm saying it is. It is. Of
course it is. Say you say, okay, say you
saved £400 one month, right? And then
you got paid again and you got £1,900.
What? For a single person with no bills?
That's quite a lot.
You know, if you took it over to the
next month, of course, it's a lot.
I mean, I don't get 1.5K a month. I got
it a couple of the these months, but I'm
saying disposable it is.
And I'm not complaining about money. I'm
complaining about [ __ ] women.
20 without bills, matey.
Yeah, I'm skint, bro. I got nothing.
you bro, you need to stop saying that
I'm skin. You know, you know yourself.
I'm not skint. So, I don't know why you
keep doing this, calling people skin
cuz there's nothing skint about me at
all. I don't know why you keep You've
been saying it for years. Like, bro,
think about it. No house. House. No
house. You've been You've been saying
this for years. Your skin, your skin,
your skin. And what happens every time
you get show money? You run away.
So, I don't understand. Like, that's
that's how we know that like you must be
calling yourselves skin because for you
to come online every day talking about
people that you don't even know. You
don't know their f you don't know what
they have right now.
You've been saying it for years. People
are skinned, bro. When are you going to grow up?
I think you need to grow up, lad.
There's literally I've not been skinned
for about 4 years.
Like literally about the only time I've
been skinned, I'll be honest with you,
in them four years is December when I
was playing them slots and I [ __ ]
myself up badly. That was the first time
in about four years.
Why do you come online and keep calling
yourself skin every day?
Like you, you know, this is not going to
help you in life. You know what I mean,
Liam? Why do they keep calling themselves skin?
There's literally nothing skin about us.
Like, do we have millions and millions
and millions? No, we don't. But we
don't. We are not skint. This is why
Liam, I don't go on that large age
channel cuz it's just full of self-reflectors.
It's just full of self-p projecting people.
It's a mad It's a madness. No, not
really. Um, uh, Johnny, do you know why
it doesn't you know why it doesn't you
know why it doesn't affect me, lad? Do
you know why it doesn't affect me?
Because A, that's probably not even his
money. That's his dad's money. And B,
okay, what? Did I actually get beat at
the money game? Well, I actually got
beat at the money game. Okay, fine.
Well, it took you two years. So, it took
you two years to save up that money. Congratulations.
It took you two years to beat me at the
money game. Wow. Nothing skint about
that, is it?
Doesn't matter how much I spend on food a month.
But yeah, I'm not skin at all.
So I don't know why you keep you saying
that people skin when they were getting
three grand a [ __ ] month. What the
[ __ ] was it with you and people being [ __ ] skinn?
I don't know what it is.
My bills are like £50 a month.
So I think I got like 1,400 last month,
1400 this month, you know, I won a
couple of football bets and all the
bills were paid for. So yeah,
I mean, yeah, Belly lives off [ __ ]
lives off 60 a week,
so this month will be Yeah. about 14 15.
How much do you spend when you go out
drinking? What about 80 100?
Don't pay rent.
I don't pay rent, matey.
I know I'm a [ __ ] Hey, start playing.
I just wish I didn't lose that 100 pound
on roulette to be honest with you. Then
I'd be even better. Then it' be about 16.
All you need to do is find some kind of
thing with a lovely football bet and
you're done. You're good, man. You're
very, very good. You're laughing then.
You're [ __ ] laughing then.
Simple. And that's the that's the best
you're going to get it. You know, that
is the best you're going to get it. So,
and then you would just adjust anyways
cuz you're older. So, yeah.
Now, anyone would think I literally have
nothing when I probably have more than
probably most people in this community
now. Maybe not everyone. Like, okay,
fair enough. Yeah, that Smokey Bee might
have money. Okay, one or two or three
people might have [ __ ] money. Okay,
but I got more than Timmy. I know that
for a fact. I got more than Timmy Eldridge
[ __ ] and you know. Yeah.
He [ __ ] lives off [ __ ]
Could you imagine putting £500 on three correct scores? Yeah.
Well, it was this month.
Well, it was this month, but it's not
how much I get, but obviously I won on
the football in it. So,
obviously it's one on the, you know,
obviously was on the football in it. Uh,
I won on the football,
but obviously the plan is I'm just going
to have to do some long ass hours working, bro.
Go gym for a whole month, try and win a
banging football bet and then bam, we
should be good to go, man.
We're good to go now. like anyone would
you know when I tell these people like
they always say to me like I tell them
how much I've got in my account and they
like I don't know why you're worrying
you've got more than enough
that's what they say like what the [ __ ]
but that's just me I always worry about stuff so
yeah that's obviously it's not as
obviously it's not as good as [ __ ]
three grand but
you know it's still if you actually
think about it if you've got no
responsibilities the house the
responsibility and you're getting 1,600
a month and you you don't have to pay
anything. That is it's quite it is a lot
especially for someone that's like
[ __ ] older now. A bit older now.
But it depends. You get used to any
money that you get. Like it was a point
where 3.2K a month was was not enough
and I had like no outgoings. I think the
only thing I'd pay is maybe £60 80
towards the electric, but
60 80 towards the electric.
£60 80 towards the electric. And that
was even getting to the point where I
didn't think that was enough
when it [ __ ] obviously [ __ ] was.
Obviously, three [ __ ] grand three
grand a month you're not [ __ ]
working. You you have no outgoing. It's
that is a lot.
that to me. Yeah. Put the link up.
But obviously it's not every month, but still. Yeah. One second.
So yeah, that's how it is basically.
So yeah, Virgin Boy just what saved up
two two months
two years sorry. So let's just say right
let's just say right that that that that
money is Virgin Boys even though it
probably is his dad's but let's just say
it is his two two years to save up that money craziness.
>> Hello CJ. Why have you got a credit z
credit rating of zero but you're calling everyone's skin?
>> Uh because it's funny.
>> You have got a credit rating of zero.
Tramodor's uploaded it.
>> Well, what you you asked me a question.
You want me Are you going to let me
answer it or
>> you said why can't you show 50 quid PJ?
But you're calling everyone.
>> I'm not showing you. I'm sure he's had 40 likes.
>> I'm not showing you nothing.
>> Are you going to let me Are you going to
let me answer the question? Ask me a
question. Can I answer
>> PJ? If you've got money, you wouldn't be
on YouTube constantly live.
>> Okay. Can I Can I ask Okay. Are you
going to let me are you going to are you
going to let me answer the question?
>> Go on.
>> Okay. So, I call people skin because
every time they get show money, they run
away. That's why.
>> Is that Are you happy?
>> But PJ, that was years ago. You It
doesn't matter if it was years. You
haven't got that. I've got five and a
half grand put away in one account, right?
>> You got No, you got money a few months.
You got showed money a few months ago.
It wasn't. And get a paper statement to own you.
>> You got showed money a few months ago,
PJ. Have you got five grand? Yes or no?
Just answer the question. PJ, we'll find out.
We'll find out on your credit rating,
PJ. Have you got more than five grand?
Yes or no?
>> Timmy, do you remember last uh where was it?
>> Talking about
>> One second. One second. One second. Do
you remember? Do you remember in the
pub? Do you remember in the pub a couple
of months ago when I showed you um uh
what was it? £1,200
>> the next day, PJ?
>> No, you got £1,200 and you ran away.
That weren't years ago.
Why can I I'm trying to be nice here. Why?
>> Stop asking people to buy money. I'm not
showing you anything. PJ, why are you
obsessed with money? Money's not
money is not going to get you a nice
girlfriend. Money is not going to get
you [ __ ] A lot of women these days
want a gentleman. They don't They're not
bothered about money. PJ, you do know
that, don't you?
>> Timmy, you're obsessed with money.
>> No, I'm not. PJ, do you hear me talk
about it every day? No. Do you hear me?
Okay. If you don't care about If you
don't care if you don't care about
money, if you if you don't care about
money, why do you go out drinking?
>> PJ, I can afford to do it. I don't talk
about my life like you on YouTube. I
don't talk about the women I've had. I
don't talk about the people I've argued
with. I don't talk about the fights I've
had, PJ, because I don't tell the world
my business anymore, PJ. You tell the
world everything. You tell them when you
cut your toenails. You tell them when
you're having a [ __ ] blowj. I mean,
PJ, why on earth do you want to prove to
a bunch of strangers that you've had sex
>> to stop people like you calling me a virgin?
>> But but why do you care, PJ? Why do you
give a [ __ ]
>> Because it's funny.
>> Cuz you haven't got any [ __ ] friends.
That's why you care.
>> Yeah, I've got no friends, Timmy. The
only friends The only friends that
you've got is the friends that take the
piss out of you,
>> PJ. I've got friends. I don't give a
[ __ ] what Bander says or [ __ ] B says.
I've got a lot more friends than you and
I got a lot more [ __ ] than you. Put it that way.
>> Tell me your Okay. When do you like have sex?
>> Even [ __ ] Shauny Longlegs, the
[ __ ] man who's going to get robbed
all his money one day. He's got
>> That's not his money. That's his dad.
That's his dad's money.
>> No, he's not his dad's money. If I leave
his addresses anyways, God [ __ ] help that one,
>> bro. Listen, that's his dad's money.
>> PJ, you know his address. You could go
and rob him right now,
bro. Rob somebody for 13 grand. It ain't
even that much money.
>> PJ, I [ __ ] You are so delusional.
Timmy Timmy's address is with 13 grand
in the house on the window back and
cover the CTV camera
is about four months of money.
>> PJ, you are so [ __ ] delusional. It's delusional, bro.
>> PJ, but if you went around six houses
with 13 grand, it's a lot of money. You
are talking about [ __ ] dicks.
>> We're talking about one house to me.
>> Sean has got 13 grand in that house.
Now, if I lived up the road like him and
I [ __ ] hated him as much as you, cuz
I don't hate Sean. He's done [ __ ] all to
me. You hate him. Why don't you [ __ ]
go and look for him? And
>> it's nothing. 13 grand is not that much.
>> Sean, don't give excuses. It's not much.
13 grand. If somebody put 13 grand in
your hand, you would not say no, PJ.
>> I mean, who would say no? But it's nothing.
>> Exactly. So, why don't you go and get
your skin, PJ, you at the food bank.
Your only option is to rob
>> Okay. How much How much How much money
do I have right now?
>> He might get the police, but [ __ ] it.
You make out your account.
>> Okay. Okay. How much Okay. How How much
money do I have right now? >> Pardon?
>> Okay. How much money do you have right now?
>> I'm going to the bank, PJ. Cuz I
>> Wait, wait. How much money? How much
>> It's not about who's got
>> No, listen. How much do you think I have right now?
>> PJ, I can show more. But do you know why
I don't show it, PJ? because it's
[ __ ] YouTube and I don't give a [ __ ]
what people say. Listen, but how much
money do you think I have right now?
>> About 50 p.
>> Okay then. So you go. Okay. Okay.
>> So show us some money, PJ.
>> Okay. You have to Okay. You have to go.
Okay. So do a video. Right. Okay. So do
>> Said on my video earlier if even though
I don't want to. I'm going back to the
bank to take £300 out. PJ.
>> Yeah. Timmy, I've got 50 pound. If only
this guy knew you.
>> PJ, I said you got 50 p. It's not £50.
>> Yeah, you wish I did. You wish.
>> All right, PJ, I know you better.
You would show money if you've got it to
>> me. You've been shown money multiple
times and you run away. That's why
people don't show you money.
>> You don't need to put I'm not I'm not
prove myself to [ __ ] strangers. I'm not you guys.
>> Every time you get show money, you run
away. That's why I don't show it. Listen
to me. I'm only showing 300 to humiliate
you. Timmy, why do you think I don't go
to Birmingham and smash you and Mike?
Because you're all smash in PJ. You're
[ __ ] PJ. You ran away from a ran away.
You ran away from a yam yam PJ.
>> That's why people don't waste their time.
>> [ __ ] seriously.
>> That's why people don't waste their
time. Anyways, you're kicked now.
Repeating. If I had money, I'd show it.
No, I wouldn't show it because every
time you get show money, you [ __ ] run
away. That's why I don't show it. Just
like why I don't come to Birmingham and
smash you up. You and Mike up.
[ __ ] sake, bro.
Bro, listen. Listen to me, Ghosting.
Yeah. No, I'm not going and slapping
anyone silly because what what it is
with these people on here, right? Every
time you meet them, you know, you waste
your time, you waste your money, bro.
They just [ __ ] act like it never
happened. There's I'm not I'm not
slapping anyone, bro. I'm not doing nothing.
I'm not doing nothing, matey.
If I I wouldn't show money if I was
skin. If I wasn't skin, bro. How many
times have you been showing money and
you run away? [ __ ] skin. It's all
self projection on it, lad. I'm sick of
it, man. I'm sick of this whole skin
thing. And then you're saying if
somebody Yeah. If somebody gave me 13
grand, of course I'm going to take it.
But bro, he's going on like it's a million pound.
He's going on like 13 grand is a million
pound. It wouldn't even last half a year.
It wouldn't even last half a [ __ ]
year. You know what I'm saying? Ghost then.
That wouldn't even last half a year.
And one would think it's like a [ __ ] million pound.
Nope. I'm not slapping anyone on here.
No, it's not half a million. It's 13
grand. No, no, no. We're talking about
13 grand, not half a million. And he's
like, "Oh, you should go and rob him." I
said, "Bro, it's only 13 grand. It's not
even like it's not even a lot of money.
You know when I had that six grand,
right? And that seven grand when I was
going out all the time, bro, that didn't
even last that long. Drinking, escorts,
gambling, designer clothes,
bro. It's not that much money.
See what I'm saying? Oh, [ __ ]
I'm not going to sit there and say it's
nothing like these delusional people
here, but it's it's not that much, mate.
in London. Trust me, it isn't.
So, yeah. And think of it, Ghosting,
right? It took this nons legs two years
to show that money. Does that not scream
skint to you?
Two years to show 13 grand. Does that
not scream skint to you, bro?
That's a [ __ ] madness.
Does that not scream skin to you, lad?
Two whole years
of living a boring life to show that
money. That is a madness.
That is a [ __ ] madness, bro.
Not really. I sh I save three grand every month.
No, I saved three grand in a month. Back
when I had that house, I saved three
grand in a month.
Not even joking, bro. I saved about
three grand in a month.
3.4 grand in a month.
I could save that in about four or five months.
Probably now again if I started working. Yeah.
Yeah, he doesn't have bills either.
He doesn't have bills either.
I don't know, bro. I wouldn't I wouldn't
buy anymore. I've got That reminds me. I
need to get my Stone Islands dry cleananed.
That's the thing, Ghost. And I have
money. I don't know why these people say
I'm skinn when I'm literally nowhere
near skin, but they seem to keep calling
me skin for some reason.
when there's literally nothing skint about me.
What the [ __ ] bro?
Madness, isn't it?
I've got two bills. I've got a phone
bill and I've got Franklin. I got two bills. So
13 grand ain't even that much money. But
the reason you're saying it it it's that
much money is it's because it's the
virgin showing it. You know I could show
20 grand and you'd say oh no it's
nothing. Like that's the whole point of the biasness.
That's the whole point of the being biased.
So there's a few there's a few ways to
look at it. I show money. You say it's
nothing can forget you're shown it a
million times and then when somebody
shows a silly 13 grand which even a lot
of money. Oh, it's so much money. No,
no, no. It's all part of the biasness.
This is why people don't waste their time.
They don't waste their time with
anything anymore on on this because yeah,
in any way you're best off just having
your own doing your own content on here
and just not entertaining any of it. You know,
I could show 20 if I showed 27 grand
right now, they'd be like, "Nah, you
didn't show it." And it's and it's
nothing. You know, you can't even buy a
house with [ __ ] 27 grand. We'd hear
all of these excuses
because it always goes back to when
you're not fat and ugly on this
community, you're disliked. So, when
you're disliked for being younger than
them and having more hope than them,
they will find reasons to not like you.
And then when they don't like you,
they're never going to take their L's.
So, it's just a complete waste of time
even saying anything.
when it comes to that. And we're not
just talking about money. We're talking
about different things. We're talking
about women, meeting people. Um, it's
not even just about money. It's it's
about various different things. Um, so
they I strongly believe, now I could be
wrong, right? The reason these people go
for you is because you're younger than
them. You're better looking than them
and you've got hope unlike them. So when
they see you, they kind of feel like,
okay, if we bring this person down like
us, then you know we're
it will make us feel better about ourselves.
Something similar to that, you know,
like they they that's why they do it.
And it's not things you said because
they like things you've said. So So
yeah, that's how it is.
Yeah, that's what they're like that
you're best off just like creating your
own content on here if you want to
create your own content or whatever.
But you're never going to win with these
biased people. Never. None of them. Cuz
when they're jealous of you, you got
understand when people are jealous of
you, right? then no matter what you do
because it is jealousy. You know what
that [ __ ] red star done? He tried so
hard to get my money stopped and it
never ever worked. Like that's not
people that's angry with what people
said. That's bitter jealous old age pensioners, lad, you know.
So it's just they're w they're a waste
of time, bro. They're literally a waste of time.
They want to waste their life away.
They want to do this. They want to do
that. Let them do it, bro. You know,
leave them to it.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, I saw that L J was live. I don't
know why I'm not even sub to the [ __ ]
Didn't even click on it. There's not
even any point clicking on that [ __ ]
channel. All it is is 40year-olds that
call other people skin when they're
skin. It's boring, bro. Change up the
content now. Let's start talking about different things, you know.
And you know the funny thing is is that
you know this is going to sound mad to
you lad is that uh even if someone shows
more money than me it doesn't trigger
me. It doesn't bother me like these
people because at the end of the day I'm
better looking than them. I'm younger
than them. You know I've got more than
enough money to do what I need to do.
Um you know what I'm saying? I mean if
you were skinn maybe it would affect
you. So I don't give a [ __ ] bro.
cuz I've got I've had a better life than
them. You know what I mean?
I don't give a [ __ ] whose [ __ ] money it is.
Oh yeah, Monty block uh Monty blocked me
as well. Monty blocked me on um Facebook.
By the way, Kieran, if you're watching,
I want 50 pound this I want 50 pound for
my birthday this year, matey.
Yeah, I want 50 pound for my [ __ ] birthday.
You know what I don't understand, right,
is I I know a lot of people like this,
and I know someone else like this, and
I'm not going to bait them to give
people ammo, but
they they're very tight with money. They
have money. I know people, and but
they've got like no life. no life
experience. They don't do anything with
the money. And and I was saying to the
person, I'm not going to tell you who it
is. I said like, you need to do
something memorable, you know, something
that you're never ever going to um
forget, you know, like whilst you still
got it or maybe you should invest some,
maybe like you should go on holiday or
something. And it's crazy. It's Well,
Nonflex thinks he has money. He doesn't
even have money. Um he thinks he's got
money, but he don't. But I mean there is
people out there that actually have
money and they don't and they live like
a skimp person with nothing in life. It's mad. Yes.
I can smell cooking. Yeah, bro.
[ __ ] Yeah, these people are obsessed with money.
These people are obsessed with money
because they ain't got no money. Virgin
boy, money, money, money, money, money.
Where's your money, Virgin boy?
And now they're going out. They're going
on like 13 grand is a million pound
because it's someone else showing it.
because it's somebody else showing it.
They talk like they're millionaires on
here, but in reality they got [ __ ] all.
Cuz the thing is, right, if you really
want to get into this, bro, I shouldn't
even be talking about this. But did you
hear what he said? We're going to change
some of this to euros. So what? You're
going to you're going to change some of
£13,000 into euros?
Uh, that's what made me think it's got
to be his dad's money because literally,
bro, I don't even think millionaires
talk like that.
And it's it's mad. So, you're going to
you're going to change some of £13,000 into euros
for a week in Amsterdam?
What the [ __ ] Like, that's that just
goes to show that, bro. They just And
you need to go by your, you know, their
life experience. They've got no life
experience. If someone's got all this
money, why are they sat there in a bed
sit with nothing?
Didn't go abroad until they were 30.
They've got no assets. They've got literally nothing.
Like the person I know, they've just
kind of got come into money. So, you
know, it's if someone's got skin, why
have they literally got nothing? Not
even life experience.
It just doesn't just doesn't add up as
well. It's like L J, right? He tries to,
you know, convince people that he's got
money when in reality he literally has
nothing because what? He buys a a a new
pair of trainers. Bro, I'll be real.
Trainers are not even my thing. But that
doesn't they they they go on like they
have this life that in reality they don't have.
I don't know why they don't just like be honest.
You know what I'm saying?
Bradley, they go on like they've got
money, but in reality they got nothing.
It's madness. It's a madness, lad.
What? When did he lose 300 today?
Let me see.
Yeah. Okay. Let me watch.
>> Yeah. One sec. I'll be back later. Yeah.