No.
Woke up a bit early. Oh [ __ ]
I woke up a bit earlier today.
Yeah. Wish I didn't wake up at all.
[ __ ] hell. Every day is the same.
Every day is a depressing same. That doesn't change.
Watching some Oreo, man, before I went to sleep.
Don't know why that guy always reminds
you of LT. [Music]
He always reminds you of LT, you know.
person on Instagram.
Sounds about right.
Yeah, man. Just Saturday depressed.
I woke up about 10 minutes ago.
Another day of being [ __ ] angry at
the world. What a life, eh?
What a [ __ ] life, eh?
Yeah, that's nice. But he'll never say
anything to my face, so it doesn't matter.
That's all right. He'll never say
anything to my face, though.
That's all right, bro. He can say what
he wants by his keyboard. Yeah.
Yeah. No one's asked.
It's just the bad experiences with women
that don't change. It's enough to get
anyone depressed. I'm gonna waste this
person's time on Saturday. I'm going to
make them meet me and I'm not going to
show up. Gonna give them a bit back of
what they've gave me over the years.
I'm going to make them buy me a drink
and never drink. I'm going to I'm going
to [ __ ] give them a bit back what
they've gave me over the years. Any
opportunity I can, I'm going to give
them back what they've given me. The
waste of my time, wasting my money, the
piss taking, the [ __ ] behavior.
Oh, I got banned on Instagram as well,
by the way, for um seven days. Well, I'm
banned of typing for seven days. And
it's not good because someone's actually
messaged me. Some guys messaged me. One
of my army friends. I can't reply back.
See what I mean, bro? So, it's all right
for them to be a [ __ ] but then as soon
as you react, they report. They're
[ __ ] losers. Women are actual losers.
And then they act and then they report
you and you react back to them. [ __ ]
losers. I hate them, you know.
I hate them, bro.
There was I was speaking to this person
in the buyer. I told her, "You're not
[ __ ] better than me, you silly little
cunt." Yeah. Asian people are supposed
to be [ __ ] nice. Don't [ __ ] talk
to me like you're [ __ ] better than
me, you [ __ ]
She was trying to give that [ __ ]
behavior. You know how they all do that
[ __ ] shitty behavior? I put the [ __ ]
right in her place, bro. The [ __ ] do
they think they are?
You know, I [ __ ] hate them, bro. I
actually hate them. Like, you don't
understand. Like, who the [ __ ] do they
think they are? I was asking my [ __ ]
self this who the [ __ ] do they think
they are? These silly little rape
victims. Who the [ __ ] do they think they are, lad?
I don't know who the [ __ ] they [ __ ]
think they are with their arrogance and
their NPCess. Don't [ __ ] talk to me like that.
You know what I mean? [ __ ] stupid little [ __ ]
I'd love to just bottle one over their
face, bro. You don't understand. I swear
to God, I'd love to just get a bottle
and smack one of them around their face.
You don't understand. I hate them, bro.
I genuinely hate them. It's part of the
reason why I don't go out anymore.
It's part of the reason why I don't go
out anymore, bro. Because of them.
Know what I mean? because of them.
That's why I don't even go out anymore, you know. So, yeah.
Stupid little [ __ ] Who the [ __ ] do
they think they are? Huh? Who the [ __ ]
do they think they are?
I said, just because you live in Dubai,
Yeah. and you think you got money, Yeah.
it doesn't mean you're [ __ ] better
than anyone. come back in 20 years when
you've hit the wall because we all know
that Asian people age very quickly, very
quickly. Especially women, and then come
back with your attitude. Stop being a [ __ ]
Uh well, considering I don't gamble. Uh no,
wrong channel, buddy. Wrong channel.
Yeah, you got the wrong channel. It's
Timmy's channel. you want,
Davin? I don't even like drinking
anymore. Why the [ __ ] would I gamble? Yeah.
Yeah. Very rarely, but I don't do it every week.
So, probably going to jack that in as
well to be fair. Yeah,
I hate these women. I do. I really hate
I really, really hate these women, bro.
I felt like really going and doing
something to one of them, you know, bro.
Yes, I'm not even joking.
Yeah, good luck. I won't be, you know
what I'll be doing tomorrow? Nothing.
Always talking about women. I [ __ ]
hate them. I hope they get raped. I hate
I was thinking of Virgin Boy yesterday,
but I was going on my gallery. Yeah. And
I was looking at all of my traveling
videos and where I where uh Yeah. Yeah.
I'm going to stand her up. I'm going to
waste her time and make her buy me a
drink and not show up. I'm going to give
them [ __ ] some of what they've gave me
back over the years. If I can [ __ ] them
[ __ ] in any way, [ __ ] them over, I'm
going to do it. I was looking at my
traveling videos and my steak, my 1266
pound steak. I was like, bro, this is
the life Virgin boy should have been living.
Three years of not doing this was not
worth 13 grand.
3 years I would not take them back. I
would not take that them experiences
back for 13 grand, bro. No way.
Like the salmon, the I got everything. I
literally got everything, you know.
You know, I have left the country and
even if I didn't leave the country, it's
still going out doing stuff and having a
life. There's people on YouTube, they
don't leave the country. There's people
on YouTube, they go up and down the
country, then they don't leave the
country. It's still traveling. You're
still you're still having a life. You're
still doing something.
You know, you're still doing something.
And obviously, it was even just that, it
was the food, the women, and stuff. I
wouldn't trade that for 13 grand, bro. I
would not trade them memories for
£13,000 cuz memories memories you take
to the grave with you and money you
don't. But I would say it that is good
discipline. I couldn't do it. I couldn't
do it lad. No, no, no. I couldn't do I
couldn't I couldn't have discipline like
that, bro. So, you know, fair play to
him. I couldn't have discipline like that, bro.
I have it now because I kind of have to
and I've already done it all when I'm
older. But I mean, like back when I was
23, 24, 25, I couldn't uh I couldn't I
couldn't have discipline like that, lads.
I just hate women. There's nothing wrong
with my life. I hate women. I think
they're all evil [ __ ] The women are
all the same narcissistic. I was
watching Oreo man yesterday and I I
agree. They are literally all the same.
There were no good women out there. He
said that he used to go to church. He
used to be a Christian and he's no
longer a Christian because of it. That's
the truth. There is no good women out
there. I knew that years ago, bro, when
I used to meet non-sligers that there
was no good women out there. They're all
the same. They're all pissy takers.
They're all scum. But people kept
saying, "Oh, there's good ones out
there. There's no good women out there.
They're all the same. All the [ __ ]
same." Just like what Ario man says. I mean,
yeah, I could do, but
you know, I don't know his address.
It's not even a big amount of money anyways.
Yeah. Good. Good. You reported him. I'm
glad you reported him, bro. That's good.
Even if you're a millionaire, report
him. Good. Yeah. He [ __ ] reports
people to the [ __ ] police and and and
they report people to the benefits.
Yeah, bro. Yeah. Yeah. You can report
him all you want. That's fine. You're
allowed to do what they do. They're
never going to meet you. So
yeah, you should be a reporting, bro.
Yeah, why not, man? You might even be a millionaire.
Yeah. Any I mean, anybody would be good, haven't it? So, yeah.
And we notice that these women start
ignoring eventually as well, but as soon
as you write negative things, they reply
straight away. I'm going to get this
[ __ ] to meet me on Saturday and I'm not
showing up. I'm going to get her to go
far out and then buy a drink and I'm not
showing up. I'm going to give them [ __ ]
some back what they've gave me over the years.
I'm going to give them [ __ ] some of
what they've gave me back over the
years. Dad, the time wasting, the money
wasting, the [ __ ] I'm going to I'm
going to start getting my own back now.
I'm going to start getting my own back
before they have the chance to take the
piss again. Watch, bro. I'm going to
say, "Can you get us two drinks each? Go
to this location." And I'm not even
going to show up. So, they're going to
look like a complete and utter [ __ ] Yeah.
It's going to be a laugh like it's going
to be a laugh.
Oh, just that one in the video. Do you
know the one in the video from a couple
of weeks ago?
I'm just going to waste her time and
[ __ ] with her.
Bit like them. They're [ __ ]
I wish I had USA or her dad right in
front of me now. I'd smash them in, bro.
I would. Well, if a white knight finds
her, then they find her, isn't it?
That's That's on her, is it?
Hey, he's not the only virgin.
Virgin. What about Dodge? He's a virgin.
Timmy's not the only virgin, you know.
Yeah, there's a white there's white
knights everywhere. Yeah. I mean,
yeah, that's the thing. I'm wasting her
time, man. I'm wasting her money.
Nah, I can't be bothered. I'd rather be
a coward like them.
Oh, mate. I wish I had that USA in front
of me. I would love to smash her up in
front of her boyfriend.
I would love to [ __ ] smash the [ __ ]
up in front of her boyfriend. Why didn't
she Why didn't she accept my offer?
[ __ ] two months ago. Bro,
why didn't you accept my little offer,
big woman? I said, I'll do it in front
of your boyfriend. I said I will come
the same week and do in front of your
boyfriend, big man. But they weren't
interested in that cuz they know that
they they're not about nothing but being a coward.
But a s would never pull it on me
because I'd smash a glass glass over
their head. So that would never ever
ever ever happen.
I would get a glass and I would smash it
over their head. So it would never even
happen. Like no one defending the woman
in front of me, bro. Trust me. And I'm
not even I don't even claim to be about
it. But that would never ever happen.
I don't like men that try to defend women. Yeah.
Uh, nope. I literally have given up my
life. I've already said I'm about going
out ever again.
Nah, I'm good, thanks.
Uh, I haven't done that. Okay. Yeah.
Every single guy that's tried to s a
woman in front of me, I've told him
about themsself. Just like that American
guy. I told him about himself. I said,
"I'll talk to who the [ __ ] I want." And
yes, I'm a big man when I'm talking to
you. Yes, I have. And they were in a
group. I stood up for myself.
So just sick of women. Just sick of
women and their cuntiness. That's what.
Yeah, he was going in on me. That's
good, bro. Like I said, I'm not going to
Birmingham because we all know what you
people do. Just like with the money game.
So, I mean, he's more than welcome to
come to London. I'll meet him anywhere.
same same thing as I said the prime but
I won't be um
I won't be doing anything else
that they're all the same the yeah
they're all the same these women I had
this woman this Asian woman in Dubai
started that like a [ __ ] right and uh
she's in Dubai and she is like a four
out of 10 bro and she thinks she's
better than people cuz she lives in Dubai
But the thing is, in 15 years, no one's
going to want you. You're going to have
nothing. Do you not think? Do you not
learn from each other's mistakes? Who do
you think you are? I was complaining to
her about women, you know, and she was
acting like a [ __ ] like they always do.
They've got this cuntiness about them.
There was one in America as well. Um,
apparently always busy, but soon enough
to reply to negativity.
We know a few of them that do that, don't we?
She will be married with a family. I
don't think so.
Yeah. I don't think so.
Well, you think every woman ends up
married with a family? I don't think so.
So, yeah. I hate women. I hope they all
get raped. Honestly, I I hope they all
get raped. That's why I don't bother
with them anymore. I only I only
complain about them, bro. I complain to
them and [ __ ] with their heads.
I have a I do have a I do have a regret
in my life. Yeah, of course I've got
regrets in my life. You'd be in denial
to not admit that you've got regrets in
your life. I've got I've got regrets in
my life. I've got [ __ ] regrets in my
life, bro. I wish I gave up sooner.
Well, hopefully I won't be alive in 15 years.
So nothing. I wish I gave up sooner, lad.
That's what I wish I gave up sooner. Bad.
I'm not meeting a woman. I'm standing
her up. I'm going to [ __ ] her before she
[ __ ] me. That's what I'm going to do.
I'm going to [ __ ] her in the ass. Not
literally. Before she [ __ ] me. I'm
going to get her to meet me somewhere
and then not show up. I'm going to get
her to order the drinks. I'm going to
[ __ ] take the piss out of her before
they take the piss out of me. That's
what I'm going to do.
I'm going to [ __ ] her and her ass before
she [ __ ] me. And I'm not even into anal watch. Yeah,
that's what I'm going to be doing. Silly little [ __ ]
That's what I'm going to be doing. Yeah,
women need to stay away from you. Yeah,
women need to stay away from me. They
don't need to give me any more bad
experiences. [ __ ] hell.
I don't want any more bad experiences.
Please do stay away from me. [ __ ]
hell, silly [ __ ]
Yeah, that's the one.
Uh, probably. Yeah,
they probably do. Yeah.
And they don't just leave people on the
They act like [ __ ] They act like
they're better than people. Their whole
persona, their whole mannerisms. Like,
who the [ __ ] do they think they are? I
said to this woman in the said, "You
know what you need? You need a hard
punch in your face to get your ego in
check. That's what you need. You need
that. You need a hard punch in your face
to get your ego in check
cuz she didn't get it.
Yeah. Oh, well, if you had the same
experience as I have, you would blame
women as well. If you had the same
experiences I have, you would blame the
whole entire gender because I've met
more women than anyone in the world. So,
yeah, it literally is the women. I don't
need to look in the mirror. I know my
experiences. I know who I've met. I know
who I'm speaking to on a daily basis.
I'm definitely definitely starting to
think it's women after all these years.
So that's what she need. She needs a
punch in her face, bro. Who the [ __ ]
does she think she is?
But yeah, it is. It is. Listen to me,
Sim. It is right. You've never had you
you haven't had Well, I have had the bad
experiences and I'm not an incel either.
So yeah, that incel thing is very boring
now. You've never had the same
experiences cuz you've never been with a
woman. You've never seen a woman naked.
I don't give a [ __ ] I know women are
all the same. I don't need to meet I've
met enough of them. I've met enough of
these women. I don't need to meet every
woman. I literally know I know them all.
Once you've met one, you've met all of
these rape victims. Once you've met one
of these rape victims, you've met them
all. They're all [ __ ] I can
literally tell you, bro, every single
day I've been on, they're all [ __ ]
Not even [ __ ] [ __ ] Like I I know
like people hate the word, you know,
[ __ ] They are absolute [ __ ] lad.
You know. Yeah. Exactly. Why am I going
to go out to get more bad experiences
with these rape victims? Taking out
taking it out on me the fact that
they've been raped. So they have to be
[ __ ] up in their [ __ ] head to
[ __ ] take the piss. All because men
rape them. All because other men raped
them, you know. [ __ ] hell. And then
they take out on me because they've been
raped, you know.
Yeah. You keep telling yourself that
simp. You keep telling yourself that
simp. S is never going to get you laid.
S is never ever ever going to get you
laid. And that's what I'm saying. Uh
Parthro, that's why I don't go out
anymore. That's why I'm not meeting this
person on Saturday because there's no
point collecting more negative
experiences. the collection is already full,
you know, just these [ __ ] women. I'm
[ __ ] sick of them. But yeah, like
what you said, there's no there's no
point collecting any more negative
experiences. They're all the same.
They've proven to be all the same over
the years. They're all [ __ ]
Yeah, you are a s. You are a s, mate.
I've had more women than you and you
don't see me sing. I've had more women
than you and Do you know how you how I
can tell someone's a [ __ ]
Uh, let me tell you something, bro. Do
you know how I can tell you these women
are [ __ ] So, the last date I went on,
right? Let me let me give it This is how
experienced I am with these [ __ ] Um,
you are alone forever and I've already
had more women than you. I just don't
think um like you. Um, I already knew I
had a feeling there that it was going to
be a waste of time, a [ __ ] date, uh, a
dig as you will, a dig. And, um, so I
was like, "Oh, well, let let me buy you
some wine." Because they were drinking
wine. And they was like, "Oh, that's not
really necessary." I knew from then they
were going to be a [ __ ] And guess what?
They were a [ __ ] You can tell with
their mannerisms. It's It's hard to
explain. They think that they're better
than you. their [ __ ] behavior. Like,
do you know what I'm saying? Uh, yes, I
have had a relationship and I've been
with more women than you and you don't
see me sing. Yes, I've never been in a
relationship. I have been in a
relationship, but like I've said, you
people in this community like to believe
what you want to believe and remember
what you want to remember. But yeah, I
knew then that they were going to be an
absolute complete [ __ ] And I was right.
It doesn't take Einstein to figure out
when you've been dealing with these
people for so long.
You know what I'm saying, bro? That in
itself, that word,
only a [ __ ] would say that. Oh, it's not
really necessary. You can see the ego in
it when someone's saying that. A normal
person would be, oh, you don't have to.
No, don't. Don't no don't no don't no
don't no don't no don't no don't no
don't no don't no don't no don't bother
it's fine I can pay for it. Like it's
hard to explain it lad. It's hard to
explain it. I know what I'm talking
about with these women.
Uh, no. About 4 months ago.
Another time waster. Just like all
women. It doesn't matter who I was in a
relationship with. Don't worry about
that. Go self-reflect your life onto someone else.
Go and self project your life onto someone else. Yeah.
Doesn't matter who I've been in a relationship with.
You're just going to say I haven't. So
what's the point? So yeah.
No, not recently, bro. Months ago. It
was months ago.
I generally hate women. And they all say
the same thing, mate. I'm not your
[ __ ] mate. I don't know how many
times I've had to say to these little
[ __ ] I am not your [ __ ] mate. So
drop the [ __ ] attitude. Yeah, I'm not
your [ __ ] mate. Do you know how
horrible that sounds? Do they not
realize how horrible that sounds? You
know, do you know how horrible that
sounds when a woman starts trying to
call people mate? It sounds horrible.
Like it's bad enough when a [ __ ] man
says it. It's horrible, bro. It's not
even nice. It's horrible.
Like, do you know what I am? I'm I'm the
one that stands up to these women women
that put these women in their place just
like this USA is. I'm not I'm not bad.
I'm somebody that just put her in her
place and she didn't like it. They don't
like being put in their place, you know,
because all women are narcissists.
That's another thing you need to
understand. They're all narcissists.
They're all [ __ ] Yeah.
I hating me. Hate them.
[ __ ] hate them. I do. Yeah.
And what makes me laugh is when you get
these little simps defending them.
That's what makes me die, bro. When you
get these little simps defending them. Yeah.
At least you've accepted. You've never
had anyone. You're Mr. Lonely. You're
Mr. Lonely. You've never had anyone Mr.
Lonely. You're the same as me, Mr. lonely.
Yeah, like you, Mr. Lonely.
A simp is basically somebody that um
licks women's asses just for the sake of
licking women's asses.
Think of it. Why would you ever deal
with women again? They're all narcissists.
But yeah, I'm going to get this one to
meet me and [ __ ] with and I'm going to
[ __ ] with her.
To be honest with you, I'd probably do
it with the Finland one, to be honest.
It'd be a bit harder for me to do that
because I'm not narcissist like them.
Uh, I mean, that just goes to show that
you're a s. Licking a woman's ass.
You lick a woman's ass, you disgusting little s.
Yeah, I'll rest my case. So, yeah.
So yeah, that's what they are basically.
It'd be a bit harder for me to [ __ ] with
the Finland one,
but then a part of me would be like,
"Maybe she's different." But nah, then
they're no different. None of them are
different. None of these women are
different. They're all the same. You've
gave them every opportunity to prove you
wrong. Just, you know, the thing about
it is you get all of these people right
you'll go at you, right? But you have
gave these women every chance and every
opportunity to prove you wrong
without paying. Well, that's
self-reflecting because we've already
seen you have sex with women without
paying. Again, self-reflecting.
Just like when you tried to call people
skin, self projecting is not going to
make your life any better, buddy.
Yep. That's self projection. I've been
laid more times than you without paying.
Just because we don't lick women's
asses, it doesn't mean we've never had
sex with one. We're just not a simp. We
just don't have that condition that you've got.
We just don't have that condition that
you've got where you feel the need to
lick women's asses. I just don't have that condition.
Doesn't mean people have never had sex.
I see things for what they are. You know
what I'm saying?
Nah, I'm not going to scare the [ __ ] I
should just meet her and pour a drink
all over her face.
You've never been in a relationship, Mr. Lonely.
You know what makes me laugh? Um,
uh, bro, these there was these two women
on Reddit. There was two women on
Reddit, right? There was these two women
on Reddit. Yes, I am a big man
threatening women and you're not going
to do anything about it. Just like USA
Izzy's boyfriend is not going to do
anything about it. I'm a very hard man
threatening women and you're not going
to do nothing about it. And Prime's not
going to do nothing about it on Monday. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm a very big man threatening
women and ain't no one gonna stop me.
Trust me, loads of people in O'Neal's
tried, mate, over the years with the
army, lads. Yeah.
Um, now you made me forget what I was
going to [ __ ] say now. So, yeah.
I hate women, bro. I [ __ ] hate them.
part of my court case. [ __ ] off. No one
cares. Get your grass and out. Get your
grass and ass out of here, you little
grass. [ __ ] off, you little grass. [ __ ]
women. I hope they all get raped. How
about that one? Is that Is that nice
enough for you?
Let me Let me make it clearer. I hate
all women and I hope they all get raped.
Yeah. How's that one? Is that clear
enough for you, you silly little s? You
little ass licking [ __ ] Yeah.
Is that clear enough for you? Is that
Is that clear enough for you, [ __ ]
Do you know what? How I never done
anything to these people in these years,
Harto? I shall never know. You know,
bro, the [ __ ] I've been through with
these women, I'm surprised I didn't
[ __ ] smash one of them in cuz, you
know, when I used to go out and [ __ ] I
have I had to do with their attitude,
you know, a lot of the time. You'd get
one awkward [ __ ] that would think
they're better than everyone. I'm
surprised, bro. I'm I'm surprised I
haven't ended up killing someone, bro. I
really, really, really am.
That takes a lot of patience, you know.
Wow. I'd love to see what other people
would have been like if they were me.
Probably would have ended up on the news by now.
But yeah, I blame my whole entire agenda.
I blame a whole entire gender. I think
they're evil. I think they're arrogant.
I think they do stuff on purpose.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Anyways, bye-bye now.
Yeah. I want to [ __ ] her before she [ __ ] me
cuz that's what's going to happen.
They're going to [ __ ] you over. They're
going to be [ __ ] That's their life.
Yeah, that's their life, bro.
Oh, that's what I was saying. Uh,
there's these two people on Reddit
saying that they're in London and they
can't find a relationship. And then I
messaged them just for the LS and lo and
behold, they reply once, start replying
again. And the other one replied. So, I
feel like they're mocking the average
man. These women that say they can't get
a relationship or get a man, they're
mocking men. They're actually mocking
men because they can get a relationship.
They can get sex. They can get they can
get people that don't do these [ __ ]
things that they do. They're mocking the
average man. You know that they're
actually mocking you. They're mocking
men when they're saying that they can't
find someone. They're mocking They're
mocking you cuz they can find someone.
We've done experiments on this multiple times.
Nope. I'm not offended with that, Peter.
No, I'm not that
friend of that, lad.
Yeah, I'm going to figure out a way to
try a way to [ __ ] over her ass. Yeah.
I [ __ ] hate women, bro. I swear to
God, I hate them.
Where the [ __ ] is Joe, man?
No, I'm all right, mate. I'd rather stay
in bed and give up.
Like, at the end of the day, you know,
these people that say that you need
professional help and stuff, they don't
understand that they're not in my shoes.
Like, there's you don't need
professional help. You're in the right.
Everything you've said, you're in the
right. Look at what they've done over
the years, they've done. They've not
just said, "So what if you said some
disgusting things?" That's why that
woman on Reddit blocked me cuz she knew
she knows what I'm saying is the truth.
She had to change her settings so I
couldn't message her anymore because she
knows what I'm saying is the truth. Bro,
if anybody else was me, they would have
killed someone. I swear to God they
would have killed Tom by now, bro. Trust
me. Like you might seem that, oh, like I
overexaggerate and I'm not patient and
[ __ ] bro. If anyone had been through
10% of what I've been through with these
little [ __ ] they would have ended up
killing someone. Believe Peter Bennett
when I'm telling you that. So why how do
you need professional help? Because the
truth hurts. You know what I'm saying?
Like what the [ __ ]
It's like that one the last one on the
date saying, "Oh, it's not necessary to
buy you a drink." Who the [ __ ] do they
think they are about it's not? Who the
[ __ ] do they think they are? What is it
me to constantly go out and and put
these people's egos in check? I'm not
[ __ ] It's not for me to do that, you
know? It's not for me to do that with
these [ __ ] slaggy women.
They are literally mocking the average
man. When they sit there and they say
they can't find someone, they are
mocking the average man. Like any anyone
that goes on Reddit and says they can't
find anyone, they are mocking them
because they can find someone. We've
done that. We've done um we have done um
dating experiments where we've pretended
to be women and stuff. We have we have
done them dating experiments
and look how many [ __ ]
likes they [ __ ] get.
So there's no way no one no one's
believing you anymore.
No one's believing you can't find no
one. There's no way you can't find
someone out of all of them men. There's
no way all of them men are just looking
for sex. Get the [ __ ] out of here on
these dating apps that you go on.
It's like that Italian one. The last one
I went on a date with. Just went on a
date to waste my time.
Just went on a date to literally waste my time.
But we're an incel. We're this. We're
that. They literally go on dates to
waste people's time. Did you ever Did
you ever know that?
Did you Would you ever thought that in a
million years that they go on dates to
actually waste people's times?
I would have never thought that until it actually happened.
You know what I mean?
I wish I robbed that USA easy, you know?
I wish I really robbed that [ __ ] and
took her passport off her. No, I should
have robbed her phone, bro. If I knew
she was going to be a little keyboard warrior.
Oh, tell me how it went. I'm intrigued.
Come on, tell me how it went.
So, at least you know that then there's
not even no good women in church. That's
why that's why Oreo Man's no longer um
that's not that's why Oreo Man's no longer Christian.
Oh no. Why? What happened, bro? Did she
just leave you?
I wish I saw that USA Izzy's phone.
He's not loaded. 13 grand is not a lot
of money. That's not loaded. Loaded is a
millionaire, mate. 13 grand is not a lot
of money. And it wouldn't even take you
say it wouldn't even take you long to
even save that amount of money.
13 grand is not a lot of money.
So, I'm not going to sit there and say
that it's nothing like these [ __ ]
fantasists, but it's nowhere near as
much as But again, we all know why
you're saying it's it's it's a lot of
money because it's who's showing it. So,
again, the biasness.
Oh, do they? Well, they find you more
repulsive. That's why you've never been
with a woman. They find you more repulsive.
Yeah, but it's not even a lot of money.
Yeah, but Yeah, but Yeah, but 13 grand
is not a life-changing amount of money.
It's literally But to be honest with
you, I have to give him credit where
credit is due, you know? Like it was it
must have been hard saving that money.
You see, I'm not biased,
you know. So, you know, at the at the
end of the day, credit where credit is
due. It doesn't matter if you like
somebody, you don't like somebody.
Saving that amount of money that must have took
that took I could I could have done it,
bro. Because there's no way I could have
not went out and went to restaurants and
[ __ ] over 13 grand. I couldn't have done
that, bro. Not over 13 grand. So, you
got to understand, bro, it's also about someone's lifestyle. You understand?
You know what I'm saying, bro? It's it's
about a lifestyle that someone has where
people would would envy.
So more money, better life. He has had
no life in 3 years.
I don't even think I could save that
amount of money if I had the house
again. Well, now I could cuz I'm out.
I'm done with it going out and [ __ ] but
I don't know, bro. Like
3 months is easy to save. The winter is
easy to save. like January, February,
March. But I don't know how he saved how
he stayed bar that long. But obviously
that's why he's still a virgin.
Obviously obviously like he he he's
still a [ __ ] virgin. So I could I
could have done that, bro. I swear to
God I couldn't have done that.
I like to have a drink and I like to go
out and stuff. I like to not anymore. But yeah,
that must have been um hard. Very hard.
Trust me, 13 grand is not worth life
experiences, bro. Like I said, I was
looking at my channel where all of the
dates I went on, the places I travel to
with my suitcase,
clubs, food, planes. I wouldn't trade
that for any money, bro,
because you can't. It would have to be a
big amount of money for me to So that's
that's another thing, bro. When you
actually look at what you've done in 3 4
years, you actually become less depressed
cuz you're like, wow, you actually done that madness,
you know? It's crazy. Like it's how we
never how we stayed in for that long. I
shall never know. Like
cuz don't forget it's also what I done.
Like I I lived, you know, going casinos,
clubbing, you know, all of that [ __ ]
Like it's I lived a better life. That's
where the jealousy come from because I'm
better looking. It's like when Ronald
Pump said, better looking, more money,
more money and a better life. But the
more money thing only that's only to a
certain extent, you know, like if you got
say you got four grand or three grand
and you got £1,500 a month, that's
enough. You don't need loads and loads
of I don't like it's not the point of
the whole money thing. It's the point of
the whole lifestyle.
Uh, all of these women are [ __ ] Um,
Definitely. I didn't even need to think.
Definitely all of these women are
[ __ ] I know. I've dealt with them.
I've dealt with their time wasting.
They're ignoring them going on dates to
waste people's time. Uh yeah, definitely
all of these women. Definitely
definitely definitely all of these
women. I I know it's women. You can
think it's me. Uh but I know it's women.
And it's what I was saying to this woman
on Reddit. She says, "I'm a woman and
I'm telling you." And I says, "I'm a I'm
a man and I'm showing you and I'm
knowing you. I'm knowing and I'm
showing." You know, which rhymes, "I'm
knowing and I'm showing." It's you women
that are definitely the problem cuz I
have met literally so many different
women and they're all the same. Yeah.
They are all [ __ ] That's why I
don't bother with them anymore. And yes,
I was at one stage. Yeah.
Worst mistake of my life
being friends with that virgin.
He's a proper proper narcissist. He is him. Bomb.
Uh I don't think LJ is a narcissist, but
he's a horrible person. But um yeah,
nons is a narcissist and bomb is a
narcissist as well
because [ __ ] that they say only can come
from someone that's been someone that is
a narcissist like some of the [ __ ]
they've actually come out with and but
the whole nonsense he's a narcissist
because he's come on the he's come on
act like the big man and then he's
playing the victim when someone gives it
back to him. That's a narcissist. That's
that's a narcissist right there.
So, I mean, everything he does is a narcissist
cuz he starts [ __ ] and then as soon as
you you you say [ __ ] back, he runs you
the police. That's a narcissist.
But again, no one would say it cuz they
don't like me. So,
but no, these women definitely are
[ __ ] They definitely definitely
are [ __ ] I wouldn't say it if I
didn't believe it.
I wouldn't say it if I didn't believe
it. I'd be out now. I'd be out now on
the drink. It's [ __ ] 1:00. If I
didn't believe it,
I wouldn't be saying it.
Nope. Never with that [ __ ]
I hope that Prime meets me on Monday.
I went to Birmingham last month. I
called Prime out, didn't show up. Called
Timmy out, he didn't show up. But again,
everyone forgets it. That's why I don't
meet people. They're like why I don't
show money. That's that's the reason I
don't waste my time anymore. But
obviously if B obviously Prime comes to
London, obviously I will meet him cuz
he's in London. But as far as like
wasting my time, waste wasting my body,
wasting my body going through great
lengths, I'm not doing that. If someone
wants to come to London, they can come
to London, lad. I'll meet them.
But I'm not going to like the only
reason I went to Birmingham is to meet
Monty. But I thought, oh, let me call
them out whilst I'm there
cuz it's never it's just going to go
round and round in circles.
But yeah, no, realistically women are
the [ __ ] I just told you a few
dates that I [ __ ] went on.
The Italian one saying, "Oh, it's not
necessary." Who the [ __ ] do they think
they are? I I was even depressed before
that date, you know, cuz I knew what I
was in for. I literally knew what I was
in for with these every single It got to
a point that where when I'd go on these
dates, I knew what I was in for with these women.
I literally knew what I was in for with
these women. I knew exactly what it was
going to be.
Like when I went on a date with my foot
injury, to be fair, I didn't think they
were going to waste my time
because they didn't give any
opportunity. Like, but then they they
they all they all end up being the same.
What happens when you're making three
grand a month or not working, Daz? You
get to go around a lot of places and you
get to meet a lot of women. You get to
meet a lot of women, bro.
But they all turn out to be the same.
They all turn out to be the same, lad.
Yeah, I was getting three grand a month
for 4 years for not doing nothing. That's
literally doing nothing, mate.
Just subletting this house. That's what
I I used to go to Manchester, bro. I
read Liverpool with Firehouse, but I
used to just travel around the country,
bro. [ __ ] around, drinking,
[ __ ] doing madnesses, bro.
It took them four years to get the house
back. That's unbelievable, bro.
Unfucking believable, lad. Literally
took them four [ __ ]
It took them four years, bro, to get
that house back.
That four years.
That's a madness, bro.
So you you done all your prime years
with that house? [ __ ] That's a madness, bro.
I wish I'd saved like a £100 a month
though, man. But you don't think, mate.
You don't think when you're young,
you're [ __ ] around. You know what I mean? Yeah.
You should have saved like 80 pound a
week, 100 pound a week,
and then you could have maybe started
your own business or something. But you
don't ever think it's going to end
cuz we're saying it now cuz we don't go
out much now.
Right, guys? I'm 28 next month and I'm
bored of the going out, bro. I'm bored
of the [ __ ] going out.
I'm bored of the going out drinking and
[ __ ] around with these [ __ ] Like
go out today if I wanted to spend £300.
I could go out today and spend £300 400
if I wanted to, but what's the point?
But I I should have really had a plan B.
you don't do you. So,
but I don't right anyways on the
football this month. So,
once you have about 2K and you've got
regular money coming in, you're good.
You're [ __ ] good, bro.
It's just the same in it. So, well, not
the same, but you know what I mean. Yeah,
it is what it is, isn't it? Uh, so 3K a
month and you're not I think it was
actually 3.2K a month.
3.2K a month, I think it was.
And then um
yeah, the house kind of [ __ ] up. So
see you don't see things until they're gone.
The thing is, you know, you can get
three grand a month and it could be a
point where it might not even be enough.
I was getting three grand a month and
[ __ ] at one stage it weren't even enough.
cuz you get used to any amount of money
you get. Like I get a lot less now, but
I feel like I still have enough to do
what I want to do,
which is insane to be honest with you,
bro. Like, so you just
you just adjust to any amount you get.
If I still had a house and I was doing
Uber, bro, I would be [ __ ] rich. Trust me.
What I probably would have done if I
still had the house, I'd probably do the
Uber for probably two days a week,
make some money to go out. Bro, you
would be rich.
Uh oh. But then it was a case of you
don't need to do an You don't need to do
the Uber if you got the house. You don't
need to do the Uber, do you?
You don't need to do the Uber if you got
the house, do you? So
that's why but now I like that's why I
didn't take it serious. But I do
actually need to actually
put some hours in some kind of work,
bro. Just to build myself up a little
bit more and then I'm fine, you know? Oh man.
Yep. They've never had a woman, but yet
they defend women.
But yet they defend women. Yeah.
I mean, I wouldn't sit here hating on
women if I didn't believe the [ __ ] I was
saying. It's a waste of my time. I would
be out now. I could go out today and
realistically I'd probably spend about
£100 drinking. But I already know the
result. I know what these women do.
And you might think, "Oh yeah, you just
can't afford it, bro. I can afford it. I
can afford it." You know, and and not
and and another thing is, bro, I could
start work tomorrow if I wanted to and I
could make any money that I spend back
if I really wanted to. It's not about
that. It's about I already know the result.
And it turns out a lot of other people
stopped drinking when they were 27, 28
as well. They stopped going out doing this.
So, you know,
I could go work and make that money
back. Any money I spent, it's not about
the money. It's about I know I'm wasting my time.
You know what I'm saying?
I could win 25 grand right now and I
still wouldn't go out. You know what I'm saying?
Because you know what they're like here.
You know what these women are like?
So, in a way, you can't really blame
them because you know what these women
are like. You you've been knowing what
they're like for years. You know these
women, these [ __ ]
So actually it is your fault. You are the problem
because you've kept going out and
dealing with them knowing what they're
like. You know,
stuck up [ __ ] entitled
their attitude. I can't even speak to
one without them having some kind of
attitude. You know what I'm saying? I
know it's all of the ones I speak to,
they've got some kind of I can't explain
it, bro. It's hard to explain
except from the one in Finland.
They seem okay. Just okay. But these
other ones that you would speak to, I
was like, "Oh yeah, you've been
ignoring." She, "Oh yeah, that's not
what's been happening." Like I can't
explain it. Like you can
sense the entitlement from the way
they're talking. It's hard to explain
it, bro. It's hard to explain.
You can't even speak to someone that
thinks they're better than you. Like, do
you know how mad that is?
The only one that's not like that is
that [ __ ] Finnish one.
They've all just got this cuntiness
about them. It's hard to explain it.
It's hard to explain the vibe. It's hard
to explain what I mean.
But you get me. madness.
Are you pissed off with the MP Zippy? So, yeah.
So, you can't even speak to one without
having an attitude.
They just talk like they're better than
you. I hate it. You know what I mean?
Yeah. Yeah. Sometimes. Yeah. I go and
give him a little walk. I wish he was
still here, man.
He's so cute, you know. He's so cute.
Franklin King is all someone needs.
I want to get myself a little dog to be honest.
So yeah, the house was getting like 3.2K
a month. So I basically lost two grand
now cuz of the house. Yeah,
but I've still got enough money. More
than enough money.
That's the way I see it, bro.
Still got more than enough money, mate.
All you need to do is make two 250 a
week and then you're basically like 900 pound down
football bet 500 down maybe. So
yeah, but don't forget I won some money
on the football as well.
So it was like 14.
But not having the responsibility is
nice. Like it's nice. Obviously it's not
nice to lose the money, but knowing you
ain't got that responsibility anymore
when you win a football bet and you're
like, "Okay, it's actually 1,400 a month
now. I mean, yeah, you lost 1,500, but
you're older now. You're not really
going to go out drinking much anymore
anyways. You know what it's like. It's
just not It's just nice not having that responsibility.
responsibility, you know, anymore.
Um, I paid like £60 a month.
Yeah, I paid about £60 a month.
Yeah, 60 a month.
And I think the internet bill was had to
stop paying obviously cuz I moved. So I
think the bills was like 100 and
something a month.
No, I don't pay anything now. I pay like
30 a month.
So I pay like 30 pound a month Franklin
and the football uh football the [ __ ]
um phone bill. So
I think I got realistically Yeah. You
know when Timmy's trying to say, "Oh,
you ain't got nothing. You ain't got
nothing." Bro, realistically, I've got
about £1,200 that I can actually touch
and some in my other account, but bro,
I'm not showing them anything because
every time you show them money, they run away.
You understand? And I get money every
week as well. And I get money every
week. If I wanted to go out, I could go
out, bro. I could go the [ __ ] out.
I wouldn't even need to pre-drink. But
I'm not wasting my time, bro.
I don't need to show these people no
money. I don't need to show them anything.
I don't need to show them nothing, lad.
But I'll never be like I was eight years
ago. Like eight years ago, I had [ __ ] all.
But I still used to manage to do stuff.
I used to have nothing, bro.
Like, [ __ ] all. Literally nothing.
Before that house thing, I was always
like, I had nothing, bro.
Yeah. And obviously with a with a
football. So, the plan is I'm going to
put some hours in this delivery thing.
I'm going to put some crackhead like
some crackhead hours into this [ __ ] And
I mean crackhead hours, bro. Like every
other day. I'm going to go to the gym
for like a month and I'm just going to
do it nonstop
and then just build myself up and then
Yeah, you're laughing at it, bro. That's
That's as good as you're going to get. it, bro.
And the thing is, you know this um
nonss, Timothy, let me tell you
something. Yeah. If I saved all of that
money that I got Yeah.
and and and I didn't go out and enjoy
life, I'd have a lot more. But I went
out and I and I enjoyed life cuz life is
for living. That's why I don't have
loads and loads of savings.
Yep. Same sim. Yeah. Sounds like English women.
Yep. They're all the same.
Yep. Sounds about right. But yeah, I
could have had a lot more than that. Um,
Timothy, I was just living the life,
lad. You know,
designer clothes, gambling, drinking,
escorts. I wouldn't trade it for the world, bro.
I wouldn't have tra I wouldn't have
traded it for the world, lad.
The only thing I wish I' done is saved a
little bit every week. But who doesn't
have some kind of regret, eh? But yeah,
so I couldn't I couldn't live that like
that, bro. I couldn't stay bored.
So, I'd rather have the life experiences
that I did have. You know what I'm saying?
You know how it is, bro.
See, when see when these people try to
call me skin, I laugh cuz they don't
know what I have.
I just don't show them money because
it's self projection. Them calling
people skin is just [ __ ] It's just them
self projecting. That's why I don't show
them nothing, bro.
You got me.
So, what happened when you bought the uh
the food anyways, John? You didn't answer.
What did she do when you bought the
food? Did she just [ __ ] leave you? What happened? That's mad.
same old. Same old. That's why I don't
go on dates anymore.
That's why I'm going to stand this woman up.
because I already know the result before
I'd even gone out and tried
I think all women are evil.
That's why I don't bother with them.
They really are scum.
Scumbags, don't it? Peep
going to get Chinese today.
madness in it. Madness, matey.
So, did you even get to kiss her? Imagine
going on a date where you hold hands with somebody
and then you try to kiss them and then
they don't want to kiss.
Wasting your time and wasting their time.
So every date you go on, you're just
collecting more bad experiences because
it's never ever going to be different.
So, you're just basically
you're basically doing it to yourself
now. You go out and you deal with any
more of these women, you're doing it to yourself.
No one can give you sympathy cuz you
know what they're like. You've known
what they're like for years. You know,
wasting people's times on purpose,
then moaning that they can't find someone, complaining,
you know, mocking the average guy
when they can get one.
I think this is not even a phase, John.
I think I'm never ever really going to
try again over here, bro. I don't even
think this is a phase at this point.
If you actually feel like if you
actually think about how much you put up
with with these women, you'd be a fool
to even try again, bro. You'd be a damn
fool to even try again, thinking that
it's going to be different.
You were [ __ ] mad. Yeah,
giving up with life is probably the best
thing to be fair.
I lost the house just at the right time.
Just at the right time, matey.
Wonder what I'd be doing if I still went
the house now. Probably I would probably be
probably saving or probably gambling to
be honest. One of the two. Wouldn't be going out.
No, I definitely wouldn't be going out.
No way, bro. [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] that, bro.
Well, I was looking where I was like
staying in hotels and [ __ ] and it's good very strange.
But I've had it as well. I've gone on a
date where I paid for someone's food and
then they were given like one word answers.
They were giving like one word answers
and stuff. Yeah.
So, yeah, I've actually had it as well. Yeah, man. Yeah.
What do you think, Timmy? What do you
think, Timothy? John Aldridge.
Women are all the same, eh?
We we women are all the same.
Now I say they're all all of them are scum.
They've all got the same attitude, the same mannerisms.
I'd love to know where these 10% Oh,
I've never found one. That's okay.
I've never found a woman that's okay. Never.
I'd love to know where these okay women
are cuz I've never come across one.
Have you noticed how they start ignoring?
No, I'm all right, bro. I'd rather stay in bed.
I'm retired, mate. I'm retired.
No, I'm all right, mate. I'm retired.
I'm retired, matey.
I'm retired, man. Going out to do what?
deal with shitty scum women. Nah, I'm
all right, man. I'll go to the Chinese
later, but I'm going to go Chinese
later, get some Chinese, but that's about it.
No, there's no reason to go out. I
already know the result with women.
Giving up with life is so much more easier.
It's much more easier. I I normally wake
up at like 1:00. Bye-bye.
Get a life. Your low life.
That rhymed in it. Low life.
So yeah, I just stay in bed. I think
I can't even speak on Instagram now for
6 days cuz some [ __ ] reported me. Huh?
Because some [ __ ] reported me, mate. So yeah. So yeah,
there's nothing to go out and do.
I go for like a walk every other day,
but that's about it.
[ __ ] Reddit's addicting, bro.
Reddit is addicting, lad.
Bro, Reddit's actually addicting, you know, lad.
[ __ ] a dick.
I just spend all day [ __ ] with people
on Reddit, lad. You got lovely.
There they are.
Lane is such a good mother. You know,
you know, the only time I'll go out is
probably my birthday.
I feel like, you know, your birthday,
you kind of have to go out.
Like, I can't, you can't stay on your
birthday. But I remember like I was like
this 2 years ago.
I was too depressed to do anything.
I was too depressed to think of anything
to do anything. Um
but I had to go out on my birthday. I
was going to go Manchester on my birthday, but um
I done a U-turn
and thought I'd done this [ __ ] before.
Yeah, I'll do something on my birthday
or the weekend before my birthday, but
yeah, I'm not doing anything. Sorry.
Yeah, I want to give them [ __ ] some back
of what they gave me over the years
though. For real. For real.
I'm going to do a video on this, I reckon. Yeah. Oh.
Uh, I'm going to get her to show up cuz
there's no point meeting these women
that all they want to do is make you
feel bad. That's all these women are out to do.
They're out to make you feel bad.
They're out to waste your time and make
you feel like [ __ ] and try to make you
insecure. That's what they're about. I'm
just going to get her to meet me, order
the drinks, and not show up.
I want to give them I want to give them
a bit back, you know? I want to give
them a bit back of what they've gave me
over the years. Sir,
I could even go there and pour [ __ ]
wine all over the [ __ ]
I could do that. Just pour [ __ ] drink
all over her
being a [ __ ] I hate them. The [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying? So, I could do
that. Could just like buy a drink and
then just throw all over her.
You know, when you hang around with
narcissists for long, they make it like
them. They generally generally make it like them.
But I feel like doing another presentation, you know?
like that uh like that Oreo man
talking about how when women say they
can't find anyone,
Yeah. They go on dates to waste people's times
and add and give you [ __ ] and add more.
They go on dates to waste your time. You
know, they've got no intentions of being
with you or staying with you.
They just want to waste your time.
That's what these women do. So yeah. So yeah,
they go on dates to waste your time. And
then they played a victim. They tried to
say, "Oh, you should stay away from women." You know? So yeah. One second. So yeah,
all of these people talk about oh
blaming an entire gender. Uh they're
just simps. That's all they are. They're
I got this L trying to contact me. Must
be over the phone.
Must be over the [ __ ] phone, isn't it?
Must be over the phone, lad. So, yeah,
Chinese should be open today. So, let's
go get Chinese.
Had McDonald's yesterday.
Oh, my [ __ ] arms, bro. They're
[ __ ] hurting me, man.
My back and everything.
When they tell people to work on
themselves, you can work on yourself
till the cows come home. You're still
going to get negative experiences.
It's always going to be negative. So yeah,
I need to start doing that jump thing
soon because if it becomes too cold,
it's going to be hard to do it. Yeah. Do
I'm not doing anything. I'm not gambling
tomorrow. I'm not going out drinking
tomorrow. I'm staying in bed just like today. Yeah.
Oh my s should s should s should s
should s should s should s should s
should soldiers bro. [ __ ]
Oh man. Arms, bro.
That's from lying. That's from being in
bed too much, you know. That's from
being in bed too much.
So, I'm not doing any teams. I'm not
doing any drinking.
I've decided against it. I'm just going
to stay in bed. Yeah. depression
all them bad experiences from women.
It's enough to make anyone depressed.
Bad experiences with women is enough to
make anyone depressed.
It's bad, is it?
Yeah, my arms are hurting, bro.
giving up with life.
It's lush, bro. It is lush.
It is [ __ ] lush.
My [ __ ] arms are hurting now.
Just chilling, bro. Yeah,
I'm going to get a Chinese later.
I got this date on Saturday, but I'm not
going to show up. I'm I'm just going to
waste her time. I'm going to make her go
to this place and order drinks and then
not show up.
Yeah. Give them [ __ ] some of what
they've gave me back over the years.
they've gave me over the years,
you know? Give them a little bit back of
what they gave me over the years.
Isn't that right, Candy?
Yep. I'll be saving myself a bad
experience again. The [ __ ] collection's
already full. I don't need any more bad experiences, you know. Yeah. Yeah. Um
cuz I already know what they're going to
do. I'm going to dress up. I'm going to
look good. They're going to waste my
time. They're going to waste my money.
You can [ __ ] right off.
Let me let me let me speak to you. away.
>> Yeah. I just said to her, "Yeah, let's
go and meet at uh Waxies on Saturday.
Let's give these [ __ ] give them [ __ ]
a little bit what they've been giving
you over the years."
Know what I'm saying? Yeah.
So, I was thinking of approaching every
day and getting one initially using them
for their body.
I mean, she's got work around that area
at that time, so maybe I might make her
get out the area.
Maybe Liverpool Street.
Yeah, Liverpool Street.
Yeah, you know, like Liverpool Street
cuz it's still a bit away from Central
in it. Huh?
Yeah. Morgate. Yeah.
Cuz we know what these women do. We know
what they're about. So Yep.
Yep. I have
no Why did you say you hate women? I'm
just going to make an excuse saying piss
me off. I'll just say
I'll just say um
I'll just say um yeah, my mom's pissing me off.
Yeah, I know. Colana, bro.
What's the other one called? could pay
as well. Would it?
No, I've already tried it. I never got accepted.
Oh, yeah. I don't need GS. I got enough GS anyways.
No, they won't accept you. I didn't get accepted. [Music]
You must had good credit score, you lad.
me. I'm not going to give this another
chance opportunity to waste my time like
all of the rest of them have. So, so yeah.
That's what I want to do. Yeah.
I wonder why people don't go out much anymore.
Probably because they can't afford it, is it?
What do you think, Timothy? John Aldridge,
you want to see the beard game, lad? Oh, what?
Why don't I do some Uber? cuz I need to
buy a new phone that's not blocked
and it's not Uber anyways and I can't be
[ __ ] and I don't need extra money
right now. But yeah, look,
the beard game is strong, bro. Look,
I could probably get like a knot now. And it
could probably get a knot in my hair, bro. So, yeah. Nah,
I'm all right with money, bro.
Don't let these skint self-reflectors
make you think otherwise.
Don't let these little skin self-reflectors
make you think otherwise, lad.
You know, they call people skin cuz they're skin.
Cuz they're skin. I know people skin cuz Yeah. Yeah. Cuz
that's funny, is it?
I got Izzy's boyfriend texting me, her
ex-boyfriend. So, how does it feel to
know that I have everything you want in
life? Everything I want in life? You
literally have nothing, mate. Have you
seen what I've done in 3 years? I've
been to restaurants
that cost more than your whole life. So yeah.
So yeah, man.
It' be cool. It' be more of a top knot.
I don't know why this guy's messaging me, bro.
I said, "Stop being a keyboard warrior
and come to London like he's dead." True. It
stop being a keyboard.
Um, not really. No, because you're not
going to show up.
Cuz if he was going to show up, he would
have showed up in Birmingham despite all
of these excuses that he makes.
There's nothing to be ready for. It's
not going to happen.
Just like the same old [ __ ] games on here.
Ready for what? Somebody to not show up
again. Yeah, I am ready actually. Yeah,
I am ready. I'm ready as I can ever be.
I went to Birmingham. Timmy never showed
up. Prime never showed up. But again,
people like to forget about them things.
I already said I'm turning up a million
times, bro. Are you [ __ ]
Are you a [ __ ] I've literally said
about a million times I will meet him. Yes. But then yeah,
but everyone's just going to forget that
it never happened.
It doesn't matter if I didn't arrange
anything. He lives in Birmingham and he
got called out and I was there for a
long time. It didn't need to be arranged
and Timmy was online as well. Timmy was
on the chat. See, this is what I mean
with you. You people. You make excuses
every time. You make excuses.
He did know I was there. I was live
calling him out. This is what I'm
saying. Excuses. Excuses. This is going
to be exactly the same thing right on
Monday. This is going to be exactly the
same thing on Monday, right? But when he
doesn't show up, there's going to be a
load of excuses. This is exactly what
This is why I don't waste my time
traveling to Birmingham anymore. This is
exactly why I don't waste my time
because you're full of excuses. You got
hundreds of them,
you know. And he did know I was there
because me and Monty was live several
times. So, he did know I was there. You
just make excuses. And then Timmy was on
the chat as well. Excuse. This is why I
don't waste my time. This is why I don't
waste my money anymore.
Dude, it's just a waste of time for you
people. You're full of excuses every time.
[ __ ] full of [ __ ] excuses. It does
my nothing, bro. I swear to God, it
annoys me with the excuses that you come out with.
So, you're just making excuses. Everyone
knew me and Monty was in Birmingham. We
was live several times for a long time.
You knew I was in Birmingham.
Everybody knew I was in Birmingham.
You're just making excuses, which is why
I didn't go to Birmingham last Friday
because I because you people are just
full of excuses every time.
You're full of excuses every time.
That's why I didn't go to Birmingham
last week to call out that snake Michael
because we all know you and your little
excuses and it makes me look a [ __ ]
wasting my time going back up there
cuz you're all full of [ __ ] excuses.
You're full of a million and one excuses.
Just like Trevor Dawson, just like Bomb.
You're all full of [ __ ] excuses and
you just remember what you want to
remember. It's [ __ ] annoying as [ __ ] bro.
Feel like my [ __ ] shoulder's
dislocated. It's annoying as [ __ ]
No one could ever ban me from anywhere.
Who the [ __ ] is that m Yeah.
So why do you people remember what you
want to remember anyways?
Why do you people remember what you want to remember?
Why do you do that anyways?
Why do you have a million and one excuses?
Just like the bombing the Mark Samson
one. Why do you do that?
Entertaining a [ __ ] biased audience.
What the [ __ ] Interesting.
And you're biased, Candyman. And you're
full of excuses.
And you're biased. And you're full of excuses.
Yeah. You're biased and full of excuses, aren't you?
You are though. That's why people don't
do it. That's why I don't waste my time.
The only reason I'm going to meet Prime
if he turns up is cuz he's going to be
in London and I'm going to give him a
big fat L and I'm going to ruin him for
the rest of his life.
Do you know what I'm saying, bro?
So why you why are you biased anyways? Huh?
You know who actually is his boyfriend.
You actually messaged me first
trying out the big man.
So that's the only reason I'm meeting his prime.
And that's only if he comes to London as
well. That's the thing. I'm not going
[ __ ] Birmingham again. I would never
waste my time with these people.
Uh yeah, funny. Funny how you didn't see
me go to Manchester and Bomb not show
up. Funny how you didn't see me in
Birmingham last month and Prime and uh
Prime and Timmy never showed up. Funny
how you didn't see me in Mark Samson's
area and he didn't show up. Yeah. You
must have not been on YouTube them times
though to be fair. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. And when I went to
Middlesborough and Trevor Dawson didn't
show up. Yeah. That never happened as
well, did it? Nah, must have been
someone else. Maybe it maybe it's me.
Maybe I never actually done them things.
Yeah, maybe it was someone else.
Yeah, it must have been someone. I must
be dreaming. It must have been someone
else. It must not have been me. It must
have been somebody that just looked like me.
Bomb didn't show up twice. Mark Samson
didn't show up twice. Trevor Dawson
didn't show up when I was in
Middlesbrough even though he was on YouTube. Um,
what else? Nons didn't show up. Um,
Terry didn't show up when he called me
out of his area. He didn't show up.
There's been a lot. You took a lot of
L's. I mean, you know, I've took a lot
of L's, but a lot of people here have
took a lot of L's as well,
come to think of it.
But obviously it doesn't suit you. So
it don't suit you.
It don't suit you to remember it.
Yeah. Okay. What about nonslegs and what
about Arsenal? You know what the the
most biased one is? Is that Arsenal Mark
one? Why has no one ever ever ever ever said
that I've gone to his area twice live
and he's not showed up when he was
literally on YouTube. That's how you
know you was wasting your time with
these with these biased people. It's not
even just bomb. It's a few of them.
It's not even just bomb. It's actually a
few of them.
It's bomb. It's Arsenal Mark. It's
Trevor Dawson as well. I went to
Middlesbrough. He didn't show up.
There's a few of them. Doesn't matter.
We're not talking about what he is.
He's a wann to be big. And what about nonslegs?
You people remember what you want to
remember. That's that's what I'm saying.
That's the whole point.
Wonder where Joe's gone. He must be
away. He seems to go away on the weekends. Here we go.
You want to take my [ __ ] money, I'll take yours.
Why does Reddit ban you? I don't understand.
Not yet, but I'm going to
Why does Reddit ban you?
I don't understand why Reddit banned you.
They fear different opinions in it. They
fear different opinions.
I don't know why these women even reply
back if they're just going to be
ignorers to be honest.
I don't get it. I really don't.
We already uh
So annoying why R keeps banning you, lad.
It's annoying, man.
Yeah. In a bit.
I bet mom [Music]
women are bad people. Okay.
Oh, there we go. Starts lagging again.
Be back later. Bye.