Oh, how you going to lose it, mate? How
you going to lose it?
Oh, [ __ ] sake. How you going to lose it?
How are you going to lose it? Don't know
why I got [ __ ] fig.
Right, so I'm going to go to the thing at 7.
Free steak for me. Big up.
I can't wait to get a free steak. I a
steak in ages.
That was show little [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. No one been laughing after today,
mate. Let me tell you that.
They've agreed to it, by the way. So
that's a good thing. Teach them to be a
[ __ ] [ __ ] all their life,
you know, completely legally, matey.
Yeah, I saw I saw
madness. Yeah, I saw it.
This madness, bro. What the [ __ ] Absolute madness. [ __ ] madness.
It's mad, isn't it?
Yeah, I've seen it. I've seen it. Going
to go on this date today and not pay for
it. Leave over with the bill. I'll teach
them for being cancelled their life.
Well, he best not be coming back to me.
I'm not interested.
I'm not interested in the snake.
Yep. I'm not interested in the snake.
So, you better not try to come back to me. [Laughter]
You can [ __ ] You can [ __ ] You can
go back to [ __ ] Virgin boy and
[ __ ] leave me alone.
He can [ __ ] leave me the [ __ ] alone, mate.
He brought it on himself. He's a [ __ ]
He brought it on his [ __ ] self. So yeah.
Yeah, he will do.
He will do.
That is madness.
I got a steak dinner today that I'm not paying for. Yeah,
I'm not your mate. I don't know why you
call me mate. I'm not your mate. But
yeah, I'm on a I'm going on a steak meal
today that I'm not paying for.
I'm not your mate. I don't know why
you're calling me your mate. I'm not
your mate. Uh uh. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, you
can [ __ ] off
with a [ __ ] I'm not your mate. I
don't know how many women I've had to
tell I'm not your [ __ ] mate. Um, hate
being called mate. It's very common,
you know. But I'll be saying mate today
when I have the steak meal that I don't
pay for. I'm going to be like, I don't
owe you [ __ ] mate.
I'm going to try and say it in like a
proper proper proper cockney um slang.
Um, I'm gonna have to learn my cockney
because I'm not a cockney. I mean, I
don't know you [ __ ] mate. That's what
I'm going to be like after today when I
use this [ __ ] for this food and not pay
the bill. I got to leave at uh 7. I'm
going to be there for 7. So, yeah.
No, I don't know you, mate. I'm not your
I'm going to get this [ __ ] to order
like the biggest steak of wine. I'm just
going to walk out, bro. I'm going to eat
it and walk out.
I don't know you [ __ ] mate. It's about
time these little [ __ ] get taught a
lesson. Get taught a nice legal lesson,
you know? It's about a good oldfashioned
time with these [ __ ] You know,
I'm not your [ __ ] mate. So yeah,
I'm not even doing the football today.
Anyone's doing football bets?
It's not the league I want to bet on.
No, no bets.
Nah, I don't want I don't whine and
dine, [ __ ] Piss taking [ __ ]
Nah, I don't like [ __ ]
I don't like piss taking [ __ ] that
they're better than people. Nah, I don't
like [ __ ] women. So, nah, I'm going
to get them back, bro, for all the [ __ ]
that they've done over the years. Give
them a bit back.
Oh, bringing up money again. Bringing up
money again. Here we go. Bringing up
money again. Look who's bringing up
Look who's bringing up money again.
Oh, look who's bringing up money. Here
we go. Self-reflecting.
Self-reflecting off money again. Uh, no.
The reason I'm not doing a football bet
is because it's not the league that I
want to bet on. I like to bet on the
National Northern League and there's no
National Northern League today. It's
next week. But bringing up money again,
but bringing up money. Self-reflecting.
Self-reflecting little [ __ ]
But yeah, I'm I'm going to make her
order the whole place and I'm [ __ ]
off. I'll teach them to be a little
steak and [ __ ]
You know, they say that you can't hit
women and you can't do this. Okay, well,
we'll just we'll just get by the pockets.
Nope, I'm not doing a bet. Nope.
Yeah, just getting by the pockets.
That's a lovely site.
Lovely site. These [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] women.
Yep. That would teach these little
[ __ ] would it?
For all the [ __ ] they've done over the years.
Money doesn't trigger me at all. You're
the one that's bringing it up because
you ain't got none. No one's No one's
talking about money. Money doesn't
trigger me at all.
I'm just stating the obvious that
everyone that anyone that brings up
money ain't got it themselves. Doesn't
trigger me at all. Why would it trigger me?
You know, the reason you're bringing up
money is cuz you ain't got none. No
one's on here talking about money. We're
talking about Monty and we're talking
about how we're going to [ __ ] over this
woman and you're talking about money. So
that must mean you are skin. for people
to keep bringing up money. They must be scared.
No, I'm not going to do that, bro. I
just want the steak. I just want the
steak, bro. I want to do that.
Nah, I I've got my own money. Thank you
very much. I've got enough of my own
money. I'm good. Thanks.
Thank you anyways. All the same.
No, I'm not going to do that. I just
want the [ __ ] steak.
beats them for being a [ __ ] It
been to a steakhouse for ages, man.
Yeah, I've not been to a steakhouse for
[ __ ] ages, lad.
So, I'm looking forward to it. [ __ ]
Uh, well, I'm going to go on this date at 7:00.
But other than that, nothing. Just like every day.
I'm only going out today because of this [ __ ]
Going to [ __ ] one of these women over
for all the [ __ ] they've done over the
years. The piss taken, the leading on,
the ignoring. [ __ ] them, bro. I'm going
to give them what for today, bro. I'm
going to give the [ __ ] what
going to give them a nice couple pound bill. So, yeah.
Yeah. For you people to keep bringing up
money, it must mean that you asking cuz
no one's talking about money.
No, I'm going on a date to [ __ ] this
woman over. I'm going to leave her with
a bill. I'm going to leave the [ __ ]
with um the bill. Now, teach her for
being a [ __ ] Just like that one in the
buy. I mean, I literally done a whole
video on this. I'm surprised you don't
know. I done a whole video on this, bro.
They want to keep being [ __ ] all their
[ __ ] life and play victim. Oh, it's
all right, man. I'll get a nice steak
out of the [ __ ]
Going to get a couple of wines as well,
you know. Get a couple of wines in there
and leave the [ __ ] with the bill.
Yep, I seen it.
I hate women.
No, I don't. There's no league I want to bet on.
No, obviously not. I'm just going to I'm
just going to say I'm going to go join
it and then [ __ ] off.
That'll teach them for being [ __ ]
[ __ ] I'm not betting on the It's not
the leagues I want to bet on. I want to
bet on the National Northern League.
Let's stop playing today. So, playing next week. yeah,
oh my goodness.
So yeah, I'm just going to go to I'm
just going to go toilet. Uh say I want
to go toilet and then [ __ ] off. That'll
teach them for being ignorant little
piss taking little [ __ ] stuck up
[ __ ] That'll teach them, mate, when
they've got to pay that [ __ ] bill,
you know? Sick of their [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
No, she's not a nice. I've already
spoken to her. She was trying to say,
"Oh, yeah, we're going to meet up as
just friends. We're not going to be an
item." Like, she's talking like she's
better than me. And I don't even like
her. That's a funny thing. But I feel
like if I can get a steak out of
someone, it's better than nothing. She's
not a nice last. None of them are.
They're all the same. Once you've met
one, you've met them all. She's not a
nice last. Once you've met one woman,
you've met all of them.
You know, once you've met one woman,
you've met all of them. She's not nice.
She's a [ __ ] Just like when I met her
and just like via text, which is why I'm
obviously doing it cuz she's a [ __ ] So,
it's all right. Anyways,
so I can't wait till today.
You might get a ride. Did you not listen
to what I just said? Or have you got brain damage?
I'll give you I'll tell you exactly what
the stupid [ __ ] said said as well.
She's like, oh, she said, "Baby, ain't a
day. I don't want to get your hopes up.
I'm excited to go waxies, but we aren't
going to be an item." So, in other
words, she just wants to use people for
money and drinks. But I've got a better
idea. So I told her, "Yeah, I've won
some money. I want to I want to be your
friend. I want to take you out for some
nice steak and stuff because I have no
friends and stuff and like I'm really
lonely." And obviously she said, "We're
going to So we're going to go to the
steak place and I'm just going to walk out.
Say I'm going to go toilet and then I'm
just going to walk out."
Yeah. And leave her leave her with a bill.
That'll [ __ ] teach you for [ __ ]
trying to make people insecure about
themselves. You know, you should That's
another thing. When I met her, she's
like, "Oh, yeah, you should have your
hair like this and you should go on a
weight training program and like, bro,
mind your own [ __ ] business."
[ __ ] off. You should mind your own
[ __ ] business. There's [ __ ]
nothing [ __ ] wrong with me, dude. I
never ask you to [ __ ] judge me just
because I'm wearing a t-shirt and I'm
wearing shorts. You don't judge me. Judge yourself,
you know? [ __ ] not even God can
[ __ ] judge me. So you think you can
try and judge me? And she was just being a [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying? So yeah,
but it's all right, bro, cuz
she will pay today anyways when she got
paid for that bill. That's fine.
I [ __ ] hate these women, bro. I need
to do this. If I can find a little
loophole more often and do this, I will
do it. Just [ __ ] them over for being
such a [ __ ]
You know what I mean? like we're never
going to change it. But if we can get
free food out of them, then [ __ ] it.
And then I'm just going to be like, I
don't owe you [ __ ] I don't owe you anything.
I don't owe you anything, mate.
Well, well, she doesn't take money out
with her, then she's [ __ ] She ain't
leaving until she pays that bill.
So, yeah, she will be [ __ ]
She will be [ __ ]
So yeah, if you can get free food out of
them, then there's no reason to hate on
these women. If you can get what you
want out of them, free food, yeah, big up.
That's what I'm doing.
No teacher for being a little [ __ ]
You know, who the [ __ ] do these women
think they are trying to tell you that
you need to [ __ ] your hair needs to
be styled like it was before or, you
know, you need to There's literally
nothing wrong with you. There's what?
Cuz you're wearing shorts and a t-shirt, lad.
Um, she's been a [ __ ] She's been a
[ __ ] Uh, just like all of these other
women, she's been a [ __ ]
Yeah. She was trying to say, "Yeah, when
I when I was with her, she Oh, yeah. You
you should go on like a weight training
program and you should have your hair
like how it was before. You you are you
to judge me, you know? It's for me to
work on myself. It's not for you to tell
me what I need to do." And I hadn't been
to the barbers for only like two weeks.
You know, I was looking casual. There
was literally nothing wrong with me,
bro. You know, trying to be an absolute
judgmental little [ __ ] when who are you
to judge anyone? You're not God. You
know what I'm saying? If God exists,
you're not God. You know what I mean?
You're not another [ __ ] You're not
even another man. Who are you to try and
tell me what I should be doing? You know
what I'm saying? Um, and the fact that
she's trying to like friend zone and
[ __ ] like, and I don't even like her.
That's the thing. I don't even like her.
She's not even my type. But the whole
point, it doesn't matter what they look
like. They could be a [ __ ] fat, obese
woman and I would still do it. It
doesn't matter what they look like.
You know, what has she done? What
haven't they done? You understand what
I'm saying, Sydney? It's hard to explain
what she was doing. She's trying to be
like judgmental and trying to be a prick.
Like, you know, there's you don't need
to go [ __ ] to the gym. You don't need
to get your haircut again. There was
nothing wrong with the way that you was.
You was just more casual. a person is
still the same person. Beard, no beard,
you know, it's you're still the same
person. People can have preferences like
for example, say, "Oh, I I think you
look better with that haircut." Um, you
know, or, you know, I think you look
really good with muscles. Like they can
they can give a they can give opinions
on on but there's been there's given
opinions and then there's being
judgmental. There's a big difference. I
think there's a fine line between the
two. Like you could say to your mom or
your sister, "Oh, your hair look I liked
your hair better like that." Um, you
know what I'm saying? But it's not a
necessity. You know what I'm saying? So,
it's hard to explain. It's hard to
explain what they do. That's how [ __ ]
up it is.
At the end of the day, whether you've
got a long beard, a short beard, no
beard, you are you. You are the same person.
You can suit, you know, when I used to
have that terrorist beard, I was still
the same Peter belly.
Shouldn't be telling people that they
need to [ __ ] get their hair done and
[ __ ] go [ __ ] gym
when you're not even overweight. Who are
they? Who the [ __ ] are they to try and
[ __ ] tell you what you should be [ __ ] doing?
Trying to [ __ ] take the piss? Well,
they won't be taking they won't be
laughing today, mate. When I take one
big piss out of them, when I take one
big piss out of them, they're not going
to be laughing today.
So, yeah, let's not talk about hitting
people. Nah, let's [ __ ] all that. Let's
just let's just get them by the pockets.
Like, I don't owe you [ __ ] mate. And
let's see if that washes with them, you know? Yeah.
I hate them. I do, bro. I hate them. It
doesn't matter how they look like. Like
I I generally hate them.
I ain't had a steak in ages, bro. I was
looking at that USA Izzy steak and the
steak I took to go see my mom and that
uh when I went to go get my see my mom.
Yeah. Uh when we had steak in, I was
like, "Bro, I kind of miss it, you
know." And obviously I don't want to pay
for it myself. I don't want it to come
out of my pocket. I don't want it to
come out of my pocket sort of thing. So,
you know, let it come out of these women's pockets,
you know, nice little 200 bill. Lovely.
With a couple of wines. Yeah. Yeah, I
see that. Yeah.
Know what I'm saying? You know,
people can like trust me, I know like
you know, people can have preferences
and there's people that have
preferences, but that that wasn't that
that wasn't that, you know, that was
just being judgmental.
And who are they to friend zone you? You
look better than them. There's nothing
wrong with the way that you look. And I
didn't even like her anyway. So, you
have people that you don't even like.
There's women that you don't even like.
No, I'm not even fat. No, I'm not even
fat, bro. Like, I walk every single day.
I'm not even fat. She just said, "Oh,
you should get your head how it was
before. You should dress like that. You
you should go on a weight training
program. There's literally nothing wrong
with you. You're not even fat." No,
that's what I'm saying. There's there's
not there was nothing wrong with me. And
there is nothing wrong with me. Yeah, I
didn't go to the barbers for 2 weeks,
but bro, like that's that's a casual
look. Like that's a casual um
rough look. That's normal. It's
completely normal. There's nothing
wrong. Why are they trying to make you insecure?
when you know what I'm saying? When it's
not going to work.
No, I didn't shave it, bro. And I'm
going to be going to the um to the to
the to the um restaurant in the tracksuit.
Yeah, I'm going to be um going to the
restaurant in a tracksuit.
Yeah, I know. I'm not fat, bro. At all.
At all. At all. I don't know what the
[ __ ] she was going on about.
She was just being a [ __ ]
like they all are [ __ ]
I mean, my hair was curly. I didn't
style it. It was curly. There was
nothing wrong with my hair.
Nothing wrong with the way that I look
that that I looked. I should have to go
get my hair done. What the [ __ ]
Cuz they're self projection.
Uh, for the millionth time. No, I've got
no bets on for the millionth time. But yeah,
that's what I'm saying, bro.
I hate women.
All of these people that sit there and
say women aren't all the same, they're
[ __ ] delusional. They are absolutely
delusional, bro. I hate them.
I [ __ ] hate them. The more I think
about it, the more it annoys me. Can't
wait until today, bro. So, yeah. Yep.
I saw it all last night. I saw it all.
It's one of them things, isn't it?
But yeah, I'm going to be a [ __ ] today.
All women aren't the same. All women
aren't the same. They say, "Yes, they [ __ ] are."
Yes, they [ __ ] are all the same.
28 next month yet to be proven wrong.
Yeah. 28 next month and I'm yet to be proven wrong.
I don't think I ever will to be honest.
Talk is cheap. Actions speak louder than words.
There's no good women out there. Talk is cheap.
Talk is [ __ ] cheap.
I can't wait today, lad.
I can't wait today, bro. Oh, 100%. I'm
not standing her up. I'm using her for food.
I'm using a [ __ ] for food.
So, I'll teach you to try to be
judgmental and try friend-zoning people.
People that don't even like you. You
know what I'm saying? I'll teach a
little [ __ ] a lesson today
when when she has that big fat [ __ ] bill.
Now, standing up is not good enough,
bro. Her buying a few drinks ain't good
enough. We're going to get them where it
really hurts in the pocket, bro. We're
going to burn a hole in their pocket.
So, yeah, I am old, bro. I am old.
I'm an old [ __ ]
I will do Yeah,
I'm going to make a pay. I'm going to
walk. I'm going to walk out.
I'm going to be like, "Sorry, mate. I
ain't got it."
In reality, I do, but I'm not going to
[ __ ] I ain't paying [ __ ] for my
food. I can go out today and get a nice
juicy steak if I if I wanted to. A
lovely juicy steak. No thanks.
I'm not paying for it. No thank you, matey.
Yeah. But don't forget, all women aren't
the same. Arty. Yeah. All women aren't
the same, so they say. Mhm. So they say,
huh? All women aren't the same. So yeah,
I don't know why she's being a judgmental [ __ ]
to people that she don't know. you don't
need to do anything, bro.
That's what exactly what I'm doing.
I said, "Please, I want some money. I
really want to take you out. I want you
to be my new friend."
And she said, "Are you sure?" I said, "Yeah."
That teach them for being a [ __ ]
Yeah. I hate these women, bro.
Don't let these bastard Don't let these
bastard women win, you know.
Yeah. Yeah. Exactly. No violence, no
nothing. Just just use them. Just [ __ ]
them over in a legal way.
If I could rob one of them, I'd rob one
of them, you know? And I would never rob
anyone. Like, I I hate thieves. I don't
need anyone. I've got my own [ __ ] I've
got my own money. I've got my own stuff.
Like I don't like thieves, but even if I
if I had a chance to rob one of them,
I'd rob one of them.
Like if I was um how I was now back in uh
the last October with that Somalian, I
would have robbed her. I would have
robbed everything, the cocaine,
everything. And I would and I would have
just sold it. If I was like how I am now
with them, I would rob everything they
have, bro. It's not even a joke.
Anything I could fit, I would rob. I
would have took the cocaine
and gave it to like one of my army
friends or something cuz I don't do that
[ __ ] Or maybe I would have just sold it.
I would have completely robbed them.
Like it weren't even going to be like
taking I would have took the lot, mate.
Trust me. So if I find like a little
loophole where I can rob one of them,
I'll rob one of them. Simple.
You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
That's what these women do. They put you
in a bad place.
That's what happens when you deal with
these women all over the all of these years. You know,
they make it like that.
Yep. They make it like that. And the
thing is, I'm not even skinned. I've got
money. I've got my own money.
There's just no hope in this country.
There's literally no hope in this country, bro.
Yeah, I know. I was very patient.
I'm just lucky I've got some money left
when I finally leave, you know? I feel
like I done good, bro. Have some money
left, bro. Know what I mean? Yeah.
Yeah, I hate women. Really? Really? You
don't understand how much I hate them.
If I knew that USA Easy was going to do
what she done, I would have walked out.
I don't give a [ __ ] about her body. Her
shitty body. If I knew she was going to
do that, I would have walked out.
It was It It would have been between
walking out or stealing her phone and
stealing her passport. Yep. Exactly.
Yep. I hate them, bro. I [ __ ] can't
stand them. You really, really don't understand, bro.
And just because we speak home truths
about women, it doesn't mean we want to
give a guy a [ __ ] I know the truth
hurts, but you don't have to start
calling people gay.
Yeah. Yeah, they would have Yeah,
exactly, bro. They would have killed
someone. They definitely would have killed someone.
They would have killed someone, bro.
100%. They would have killed someone.
Yeah, that USA is I would have either
walked out or I would have robbed her.
And I don't need to rob anyone. But you
know, when you rob somebody, you you hum
when you rob somebody, you humiliate them.
It's one of the worst things, you know,
to be robbed is humiliation.
It's nasty. It's a nasty feeling to be
robbed. It's worse than me beating up.
So, I mean, if I have a if I had a
chance to rob one of them, I'd rob one
of them. Bro, you say we can't hit
women? Okay. Well, nothing says we can't
rob women. Nothing says we can't, you
know, you want to [ __ ] take my
[ __ ] money, I'll [ __ ] take yours.
Like what Ant-Man used to say. You want
to take my [ __ ] money, I'll [ __ ]
take yours. Simple. Yeah.
I love that saying. You want to take my
money, I'll [ __ ] take yours.
I'll take yours. Yeah.
Want to take my [ __ ] money? I'll take yours.
>> Madness, bro.
But they would be. Yeah.
But yeah, I do feel old, lad. I do feel
old. Definitely feel old.
Definitely feel old, mate. The piss
taken on purpose. There's no good women
out there. I wonder how long
uh I wonder how long it's going to be
until this finished one acts like a [ __ ]
cuz she hasn't gave any signs yet of
being a [ __ ] She seems normal.
So, who knows how how long it's going to take.
If it was this finished one still here,
would I [ __ ] her over?
To be honest with you, I probably would.
And she hasn't even done anything to me.
But I probably would [ __ ] her over to be
honest because I'm so deep in it with
this this [ __ ] with the women now. To be
honest with you, I probably would. I pro
I would probably [ __ ] her over before
she had a chance of [ __ ] me over. But
this [ __ ] has actually done something to me.
You tried to make Peter Belly feel
insecure about himself when there's
nothing wrong with Peter Belly, you know?
You can have a preference. You can have
We have preferences how people look, but
people don't say it in that way.
That's like me saying, "Why don't you
gain some weight? You're skinny as [ __ ]
You look anorexic."
Do you know what I'm saying, bro? You
would You wouldn't say it to a skinny
person. You wouldn't say it to a medium
person. You wouldn't say it to a fat
person. because it's none of your business.
You know what I'm saying?
That's like me saying, "Why don't you
get a boob job?" Cuz you ain't got no
boobs. Why do you gain some weight? Cuz
she wasn't even my type anyways. It was
just a funny video. But you know, that's
like you saying, "Why do you get a boob
job? Why do you gain some weight?" Could
you imagine? Huh? You can imagine the
the tables were turned
just taking [ __ ]
So glad I gave up,
you know. I'm so glad I gave up.
I started before the house, carried on
throughout the house and quit when I
lost the house.
Is that a madness?
You know, when I first went out Yeah. I
used to love it, you know, when I was like 22,
before I even had the house. I used to
love it, you know.
I used to love going out.
back when I first like when LT told me
back like with the little cog bottles. I
used to love it back when I was like 21
20 I think I was 22.
I used to love it the drinking and [ __ ]
Did I have the house when I met Fraser?
I don't think so. No.
Yeah. I used to be a maniac bird with a
little boss t-shirt.
Yeah, I've had enough of him, Kieran.
I've had enough of him, lad. You know
what people say, oh, you can't hit women
and stuff. Well, nothing says we can't
rob women. Nothing says we can't take
the piss out of women, you know.
Yep. And I'm going to be like, I don't
owe you [ __ ] mate.
I don't owe you [ __ ] mate. That's what
I'm going to say. Give them a taste of
their own medicine.
Give them a taste of their own special medicine.
Specially made by Peter Belly. That's
what I'm going to do. I'm meeting her at
um 7. So they'll teach her to be a [ __ ]
A judgmental little time wasting [ __ ] You know,
I [ __ ] hated me K lad. I hate them,
bro. I generally hate these women. I
don't think you understand. Like I don't
really think you really understand, lad.
But I can't hate them cuz I'm getting a
free steak today. So yeah,
that is exactly what I'm doing, bro.
I've had enough of them [ __ ] stupid little [ __ ]
So that's what I'll be doing.
Yeah, they're always going to do that,
bro. They're simps. It's like me. No one
cares about what I've been through with
these women. And I've showed them my my
experiences and no one cares. Yeah.
They're always going to do that. They're simps.
Yeah. They don't Yeah, exactly.
You know, I met her three weeks ago,
Kieran, in this um bar, right? And she's
not even my type, but I thought, let me
just put it for the lows. And she was
saying, "Oh, yeah, you should have your
hair like how you had it before. You
should go on a weightlifting program.
No, no, no, no. You should dress like
this." I'm thinking, who are you to
judge me? There's nothing wrong with me.
You know, there's there's having
preferences, but you know, people say
them preferences when they're in a
relationship with somebody or they
actually know someone. You don't go
around throwing what people should do.
You know, you don't see me saying, "Why
don't you get a boob job because you
ain't got no tits?" Or, "Why don't you
gain weight cuz you're [ __ ]
anorexic?" You don't. You wouldn't do
that, would you? So, why do they feel
it's okay for them to judge people that
there's nothing wrong with them? It's
literally my hair was like curly and stuff like
or they insecure about themselves or something.
So yeah, she was just being a [ __ ] She
was just being a [ __ ] So I'll be a
[ __ ] and I'll be a [ __ ] today.
I don't even want their body. I don't
even like them. I don't even want their
[ __ ] I just want that steak. That's
all I want.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] To be honest with
you, Kieran, I'd probably do it to that
one in Finland as well. I'm so far deep
in it with these women. I'll probably
just [ __ ] any of them over now at this point.
Any chance I get,
even though the one in Finland hasn't
done anything to me, I'd still [ __ ] her
over as well.
She will show cuz she works around that
area. She will show.
And even if she doesn't have a steak and
I have a steak, then I'm not paying for
it. I get a free 80 steak. I know how
expensive them stakes are now. Kieran,
you know what I mean? Lad,
I hate these women. I actually hate
these women, bro. So,
yeah, just to lead people on and use
them and friend zone them. You should
record her face. No, I'm not shouting at
anyone. I'm not I don't have the energy
to do any of that. I just want free steak.
Like I was saying, if you know that
Somalian K and I would have robbed her
blind if I am how I am now. Not
financially. I've still I've got money.
It's not about financially. But like how
I am with these women, I would have
robbed I'd even robbed the cocaine and
gave it to one of my army friends. They
do co they do cocaine. I don't do
cocaine. I would have took all of that
money. I would have robbed that whole
place, bro. I'm not even joking. But I
thought, let me just allow her in it.
But um yeah, if you get any find any
kind of loophole,
just rob them. Don't hit them. Don't
threaten them. Just rob them. Yeah.
Like she was trying to say how I need to
have my hair how I had it before. I was
like, who are you to judge me? You
barely know me. You get what you're
[ __ ] giving. You don't see me [ __ ]
saying you should be doing this, you
should be doing that.
You know, if you if you was if you saw a
woman for a couple of times, Kieran,
right, and they're like, "Oh, I prefer
your hair like this. It looks better
like this." Yeah, people can have an
opinion, but she was clearly being
judgmental. She was clearly trying to
make me insecure when there was nothing
wrong with me, bro. Like, she was
clearly trying to be a [ __ ] about
it. You know, I know a fine line between
judgmental and someone having
preferences. Like when I used to be that
19-year-old, she's like, "Oh yeah, your
hair looks I like your hair better
without products." Yeah, that's a that's an opinion,
you know, like you there's nothing
wrong. And if even if I I could have
been [ __ ] more morbidly obese, that's
nothing to do with you. You know, you
don't know me. You know what I'm saying?
You don't talk about people that you don't know,
especially someone you've met for 5 seconds.
You can have people can have
preferences. Oh, I like your hair better
like this or yeah, you kind of I like
that style a little bit better. You
know, people could do that, but don't
try to give people a le it was like they
were trying to give you a lecture. I
think that's the word for it.
She was she was she was trying to give
me a lecture
if that makes sense. I don't need to
join no gym. Like I I I I need to join
the gym because I want to get muscles
again. Yeah. But I don't need to. I'm not overweight.
You know what I'm saying? You don't
There's nothing wrong with my body.
There's nothing wrong with like it's
just average. I don't even have a beer belly. So,
um, she was trying to give me a lecture.
I think that's the word for it.
That's what they all do.
I hate them, bro. I hate them. I really,
really hate them, bro.
I really do, bro. I really hate them. I
don't even want her body. I don't even
want her [ __ ] I just want her money. I
just want her state, bro. That's all I want,
bro. I ain't even got a Bro, I ain't
even got a big belly. That's the funny
thing about it. I'm just like average.
I'm just like I would say I'm just average.
and she was about, "Oh yeah, we're going
to meet, but we're not going to be an
item." I'm thinking, bro, like I don't
even like the girl and I'm better than
her in every way and she's trying to
talk to me like she's better than me.
You know what I'm saying? She's a [ __ ] bro.
Like, she is an actual [ __ ]
And you know that one in the park before
that I was shouting at, she actually did
do something. She was actually going to
waste my time just like they all do.
They were going to She was going to
waste my time like all of them do. So
she actually did do something. So yeah,
I hate these women, bro. You don't
understand how much I hate them.
This what why I don't go out drinking anymore, Kieran.
And I've got the money for it. I've got
the money, lad. Trust me, I have the
money. I'm not rich, but I have enough
money to go out and do what I want to do
cuz I'm careful with money now. I put
money aside now. You know, I have to be.
I don't get as much. You know, I won a
couple of football bets, didn't I? So,
you know what I'm saying, bro?
So, I'm very like smart with money, you
know? So, I I have money. I can do, you
know what I mean?
I wish I robbed that USA Izzy. I I I
wish I knew she was going to be a [ __ ]
I would have took her phone and passport.
[ __ ] her body and her tits wasn't
worth it. It wasn't worth it, bro.
I would have rather just robbed her and
then just got an escort.
Like that one, Greavves. You know,
Gregy, to be fair, she was being a [ __ ]
She was being a [ __ ] to be honest with
you, Gregy. She was trying to be
judgmental and give me a lecture and try
to make me feel insecure when there's
nothing wrong with me.
Um, it's, like I said, it's hard to
explain. You don't see me saying you
need a boob job. You don't see me saying
that you need to put on some weight
because you're [ __ ] an because you're too skinny,
you know? You don't see Can you imagine
you went around doing them things,
Greasy? Oh, the double standards, eh?
Oh, the double standards.
I think I'm going to save about £,000 this month. Yeah.
Yeah, that was years ago. Yeah, I
remember that. That was years ago. That's
Yeah, I'm going to I'm going to [ __ ]
this woman over today.
And you know what I might do to them? I
might pretend I've got cancer
to some of these [ __ ] I might
pretend I've got cancer and that.
Yeah, I might just pretend I've got cancer.
that's what I'm going to do.
Nope. I'm going to a steak. I'm going
for I'm getting a nice steak meal paid for me.
I'm getting a nice um I might get a
I'm going to a steakhouse today, bro.
I'm getting a steak paid for me.
All women are the [ __ ] same. They
I've met more women than anyone in the
world. Do you believe when I say that?
100% I have, mate.
I'm going to pretend I've got cancer, bro.
You know what I mean? Yeah. But I don't
want their bodies. I don't want their
[ __ ] I just want their money. I just
want their food.
You want to [ __ ] take my [ __ ]
money, I'll [ __ ] take yours.
It's like that solicitor. Oh, I could
have done it to her as well when she was
trying to be a [ __ ] and start started
giving one word answers. She wanted to
meet me in central London. Oh, yeah. But
she wouldn't have been able to eat that
steak cuz it's not halal.
You know, if you have find a little
loophole with these women, you know, you
can [ __ ] them over anyway. Do it.
[ __ ] do it.
Yeah, it's to that point now I don't
even want their bodies. I don't even
want them. I just want to [ __ ] them
over. Just like this one I'm meeting
today. I don't even like her. I don't
even like her body. I don't like She's
not ugly. She's just not like my type.
It's not about that. I just want the steak. You know,
give these consultation their own medicine, you know.
See, when I had this house kid when I
wasn't I was I was living in the moment,
you know, now I don't have the house,
you know. I see a lot of things for what
they are and stuff and I've changed a
lot, you know, and you know, it's really
start it's time to really start getting
back at these women.
It really, really is.
I mean, to be honest, I could just go
around London and and and say, "Oh, let
me take you on a date." And then just
[ __ ] them over. If I had the energy,
Kieran, I would literally go out and
purposely [ __ ] with them. But, bro, I
ain't got the energy for that. I ain't
got the energy for that anymore, bro. I
would just go around being [ __ ] to them
for all the [ __ ] they've done to me over
the years on purpose. And they've done
it on purpose as well.
Um, yeah. I, bro, there's there's a lot
of things I miss.
Well, I mean, the money is one thing,
but I mean, I miss the the cooking and
the I miss the cooking, the tenants. I
miss the house. I miss the area. It's
not even just the money, bro. There was
ages sometimes I had to wait for [ __ ] rent. Um,
but I didn't even have an estles in in
Albert Square. I was sleeping on a
mattress. I was sleeping on a mattress
in some guy's room.
Yeah, I like that area, bro. I like the
the house and stuff. Wasn't just the money. But yeah,
surprised that never gave me a mental breakdown.
So, I'm actually very patient,
Greavvesy. I didn't realize. You see,
the thing is, Grezy, you like to try and
say that, oh, I've got ADHD and stuff,
but yeah, but I mean, I've got more
patience than most people.
That's crazy with somebody that's got
ADHD to have that amount of patience.
Yeah, cuz obvious No, because the thing
is with the with the house, right, it
wasn't just it's not even just about the
money anyways, you know? So I always had
like people around me and [ __ ] So and
even with the house I never went out for
like 3 weeks. I never went out every
week. Even with the house
even with the house I didn't go out
every week. I stopped like
seven months ago bro like I was like oh
there even before I knew that it was
going to end. I still didn't go out
every week. I was just chilling bro like
playing GTA getting food cooked. Like I
swear to God, bro. I was just chilling.
Weren't even about the money, bro. It's
not about the money. Trust me. Why I
don't go out now? It's not about the
money. I could easily go out today and
spend £400 if I wanted to, £500 if I wanted to. Easily.
Not that you would even spend that, but
you know, you you get the point.
Yeah. I miss the cooking and stuff and
then I miss going to lanies on the weekends,
you know, but
so yeah, it's not just it's not just the
money, but it's different things.
So I used to get some nice food cooked,
used to have a laugh, the escort was
just up the road.
I don't know, bro. It was just it was
just nice to and I got over with the
neighbors as well. There used to be a
scrap guy. Used to be a black guy.
And we used to say to each other, "All right, captain."
Yeah, it's a black guy. Oh, remember
this time, bro? We had so many jokes,
right? So, you know what I'm saying? Uh,
so this one of the tenants, right? He
wanted to get a woman. uh he wanted to
get a woman live with him and he didn't
know what she looked like and we were
all making jokes saying, "Oh yeah, what
if she's fat? What if she's fat? What if
she's fat?" You know, and he didn't know
what she looked like because she didn't
have a photo. And um he didn't have a
photo, right? So what happened was is
she come on the door, she was as big as
a [ __ ] house and we were all saying,
"Oh yeah, yeah, I think you should you
should move in and that." Yeah. We were
all laughing like we were having jokes,
mate. Like the scrap guy was there and I
was like, "Oh yeah, I think I think I
think yeah, that that would do you
good." And then literally all of the
rest of the tenants was up in the room
and I'd have to keep going up in the
room and start [ __ ] pissing myself laughing.
It was [ __ ] funny as [ __ ] bro. She
was as big as a [ __ ] house. And I
think, yeah, this this house suits you
knowing damn well that he doesn't like her.
Um, bearing m knowing damn well he
doesn't like her because she's [ __ ]
fat as [ __ ]
You know what I'm saying? And we were
all like in the room just laughing, bro.
Like it was a madness. It was a madness.
And then I got and then I got and then I
was I was used to all the pubs again cuz
all the people in the pubs even though I
never went out drinking, I'd go get my
breakfast in the pubs.
So it was a nice it was a nice life,
bro. It wasn't just about the money. It
was a nice life, you know.
Easy access to everything.
It was bad, bro. Then [ __ ]
now I'm in this [ __ ] place. So it's
it's bit [ __ ] in it.
Well, someone stole the after shave.
There's no doubt about that.
I would have stayed there forever if I
could. I would have stayed there forever
if I could, man.
Trust me, it's not just about the money,
bro. It really isn't. You know, all of
the people in the pubs like they knew me
like because I went for breakfast and stuff.
It was good, bro. It was good.
It was a feeling of being independent in
a very accessible area
here. And it's hard to explain it, you know.
I just liked it there. I just cuz I I
always say I hate Stratford.
Yeah. I'll never go back to Stratford.
It's It just reminds me of like you can
go there and anything can happen to you,
you know? And
you know, anything can happen to you.
You get [ __ ] killed without anyone
knowing about it. You know, it's
different than where my mom lives. But
then I grew to love the area and I feel
like that area suited me more. Um, and
it see it seemed to have built me
stronger as well because, you know, I
lost my phone and that I got kicked out.
I didn't have anyone,
you know, but like the tenants and [ __ ]
like I didn't have anybody, bro. That's
why I don't have anxiety cuz I've been
through the worst. So, it's like it's
hard to then have anxiety after you've
been through all of that [ __ ]
Yeah, that was hilarious, bro.
That was hilarious. All over YouTube, isn't it?
What about the windows getting smashed here in?
I wonder I wonder what the neighbors
used to actually think when all that LG
[ __ ] was going on.
That's why I was saying to Tra, you can
send the letters. Everyone knows me in that area.
So, I'm not at my mom's
and yeah, that's not going to happen.
Um, but the thing is, bro, the thing is,
Kieran is that, uh, I wonder what they
used to think when all that, like I
said, like you can send letters, but the
neighbors know me, so it'll be a way.
That's why I send them to do it, but
everyone knows me, so no one's going to
start coming and starting trouble
because people know me, you know? So,
it's like my mom's neighbors, they all
know me. The only one that said one
thing was the one that I already had a
problem with. But all of the others,
they all know me.
There's an old woman up the road. They
all speak to me. They all know me.
Yeah. They all know me, bro. So, it's
like anyone looks at me, they're hardly
going to think I'm a nons, bro. They're
hardly going to think I'm a n. Hardly,
bro. Hardly. You know what I'm saying?
I even have kids talk to me, bro. So, I
mean, [ __ ] hell.
You know, I was thinking of doing Kier
and buying that Chucky outfit on Amazon
and running after the kids. You know,
there's like some kids near where my mom
lives, isn't it? I was thinking of
dressing up as Chucky and running after them.
Just like in the movies, is it scared of [ __ ]
Imagine that, Kieran. I dress up as Pennywise.
Oh, mate. No, you couldn't do that,
mate. You'd scared them. But saying
that, you probably wouldn't even scare
them to be honest, mate. It's a
different game now. You know, these kids
have seen Chucky. These kids have seen
clowns. They're probably not even scared
of them, you know. Yeah.
Yeah. But saying that, they probably
wouldn't even be scared. See, like when
we were when we were when we were kids,
bro. There was none of this whole
finding this stuff on YouTube, you know?
Like they're not it doesn't technology
technology is different now, bro.
Doesn't scare kids now, you know? It
used to scare us as a kid because, you
know, but not now.
You remember that time, K, when I was
pissed off with the women [ __ ] and I
come back and I started pissing on the
floor during Ramadan. I smashed the
[ __ ] glass. Yeah. On in the kitchen
and I was and I pissed all over the
floor and the tenants cleaned it all up.
I don't know why I done that, bro. I was [ __ ] mad.
Madness, bro. Madness.
That was a crazy camp, bro. And the s
and the whole house was like 5 minutes
away from the house. So I always used to go there.
So yeah, I was living it was a good life there, man.
Then I had that foot injury. Oh my god,
that foot injury was bad, bro.
That foot injury was bad.
Nope. There's never been a night where
I've never got one number. That's
impossible. You can't go out and not get
a number. That's impossible.
That's never happened.
You can't not get one number. You'd
always get a number.
Nah, you'll always get a number, bro.
I think the most numbers I ever got in
one day was about nine
and none of them replied. And then I get
three numbers and then they all reply.
It's just a waste of time.
You remember that foot injury, Greavvesy?
No. I've never gone out and not got one number.
That's never happened. It's impossible.
That is impossible, bro.
That is impossible. Impossible. Matey,
isn't that right, Grezy? There hasn't.
Trust me, there hasn't.
So, what do you think of the Natalie G
thing anyways, Grezy?
I don't know why he's blaming people. He
knew what was going to happen if he went
back on YouTube.
Why is he Why is he trying to blame
people? I don't understand. Well, you
didn't see it. She got locked up for hitting him.
Oh, she got locked up for hitting him.
She smashed his uh face and he's
bleeding and then he got her arrested. Yeah.
You didn't know about it? What the [ __ ]
Um, I don't know if No, he was live. You
didn't know. You didn't know about that?
No, he was live. I don't know if there's
a video, but I'll I'll try and find a
video. One second.
One second. Let me send it to you.
There we go.
The same website you can watch little
Scooby on, Greasy. The same website you
can watch Scooby-Doo on.
Imagine that. The same [ __ ] website
you can watch Scooby-Doo on.
How mad is that?
That is a [ __ ] madness.
So I bless Peter Belly if he won on the
football then. Ain't it grievously?
Bless little Peter Belly if he's one on
the football then. A
Oh, I had a McDonald's last night.
Grezy, I had some nuggets. Some chicken
That's some chicken nugos.
Let me think. Franklin.
Oh, Franklin's gone flying.
I need to get to the toilet before I just cad.
Yeah, exactly. Yeah.
Yeah, exactly, mate.
Do you remember I was thinking of your
comment, you know, the other night when
you was like, "Don't let these [ __ ] women win."
I love it, bro. Yeah. Yeah, you could do
that. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Just leave them there. Yeah.
I want revenge after all the [ __ ]
they've put me through all over the over
the years, man. Yeah.
Yeah. So if I get like a steak out of
them and [ __ ] right,
then obviously that's winning. That's
getting some back as well, isn't it?
That's getting your own back as well, would it?
Yeah. Anything like that, you know, steak
causing them inconveniences. Yeah.
It's true, is it?
It's true, bro. It's true.
I'm not going to win, mate. I'm going to
get a lovely steak today.
A lovely steak.
That's what I'm going to get. I was
watching Oreo Man yesterday.
Yeah, I I've been watching him a lot lately.
Oh, bro. Do you know what he was saying?
I was dead. Oh. Oh my god. I forgot to I
forgot to I forgot to tell you. You know,
I I was going to tell um LT this, but I
was forgot. He said, "Valentine's Yeah,
is a day to poke fun of people that
ain't wanted." Yeah. Let's poke fun out
of the people that ain't wanted by nobody.
I swear to B on the toilet and I was
dead. He said, "Valentine's, whoever
made Whoever made Valentine's is cool.
It's It's a day to poke fun out of the
out the people that ain't wanted by nobody.
I was dead, bro. I swear to God, I was
dead. Let's make fun out of the people.
Let's poke fun out the people that ain't
wanted by anyone.
I knew I forgot to to send something. I
swear to God.
Oh, bro, I was dead. I was [ __ ] dead.
Let's Let's poke fun out of the people
that ain't wanted by nobody.
I agree with you. No Valentine's. Yeah.
It's just a holiday to mock mock the
people that ain't wanted by anyone. To
poke fun at the people that ain't wanted by anybody.
Is it? Yeah. Let's make fun out of the
people that ain't wanted by nobody.
That's what Valentine's is for, is it, Grezy?
It's a day to poke fun out of the pe
Let's poke fun out of the people that
ain't wanted by no one.
Yeah. Yeah. There's this black guy
watching America, Greasy. And he does
his He said, "I'm back with another presentation."
Yeah. Let's make fun out of people. They
want to invite nobody.
He said, "Best believe there's going to
be a lot of love making tonight."
He said, "This day there's going to be a
lot of love making."
Yeah, there's going to be a lot of love making.
Let's poke fun out of the men that ain't
wanted by nobody.
I love these videos, you know. I love these videos.
Yeah. It was last night. Well, it's
actually early. I was in the morning.
4 5:00 in the morning. Yeah.
This is to poke fun out of the people
that ain't wanted by nobody. Yeah.
Let's poke fun out of the people that
ain't wanted by nobody.
You think that's funny, Grezy?
Yeah. You think that's funny to poke fun
out of the people that ain't wanted by nobody? Huh? Nah, nah, ain't
that's a horrible holiday, you know,
Valentine's. Let's poke fun out of the
people that ain't wanted by anyone.
I was dead, bro. When I heard that, I
was But it's true though, is it? It is true.
I think this Valentine's is going to be
a lonely Valentine's for me as well.
I think I'm going to be alone this
Valentine's. I mean, all of the
Valentine's up to 27 years I've been
alone. So, I think this is going to be
this is going to be no different.
This ain't going to be no different, is it?
You see my little video I done for you,
Greavves? I went to the chicken shop. I
walked to the chicken shop
to get some delicious chicken. Did you
see that video?
Let's poke fun at the Let's poke fun at
the guys that ain't wanted by nobody. Mhm.
Back with another presentation.
Back with another presentation. Let's
just poke fun of the guys that ain't
wanted by nobody.
You think that's funny, Grezy?
Oh, I'm getting a lovely t-bone, mate.
I'm getting a lovely Australian t-bone, you know.
and hearing what they've done to Oreo
man as well, like standing him up as well.
Yeah, I used to do uh good steak videos.
I was looking at my stakes, you know, my
memories, you know, from yesterday.
Uh not yesterday, the day before
yesterday, I was looking at the stakes.
Good memories. Hey, so I've got some
good memories, you know. That's what I
was saying to Virgin Boy. I wouldn't
[ __ ] change their memories for 13
grand. You can't put put a price on
their memories. You know, the Scottish
salmon, the steak.
Valentine's is just a is just a day to
poke fun. Poke fun at the men that ain't
wanted by nobody.
It's just a cruel It's just a cruel [ __ ]
It's just a cruel um
day, you know?
Let's poke fun at the men that ain't
wanted by no one. It's [ __ ] cruel, isn't it?
Yeah, I used to love them steak houses.
I don't do it anymore cuz I can't afford it, mate.
No, I can afford it obviously, but you
know, I'm saving cuz I'm leaving. So,
can't be buying them steaks every day
now, you know, matey.
Let's poke fun at the guys that ain't
wanted by nobody.
Yeah, that's whoever made Valentine's.
It is cool though. He's right.
He wears a lot of lacrosse which I'm surprised, you know.
Yeah. I hate [ __ ] seeing couples. I
hate seeing pregnant people. I hate it, bro.
That's why I don't go out anymore, really.
Yeah. That's why I don't go out anymore.
Yeah. And I know I can't go to the
cinema anymore unless I go on a Monday.
So, I've got to change the time around for um cinema. Yeah.
Whoever it is, they're a [ __ ] coward.
You know what made me laugh about Bobby?
He was like, "Oh, I'll never see over a
grand again." Huh? Little does he know,
eh? You don't know what people have.
See, this is what makes me laugh about
this community is they don't know what people have.
You know what I mean?
And I was watching his video yesterday.
Oh, man. It's like they always will
blame you as a man. Like, no matter what
you do as a man, it's your fault.
They'll always put the ball back in your
court. Which is true. Like some of the
stuff he says is true.
Like as a man, they will always blame you.
They will always blame you as a man.
It's the truth. It is. That that is the
truth. Some of the things he says is
actually true though.
But he still didn't help himself. You
know, he's 36. He is. He's 36 O man.
There is things that he could have done,
you know, he could have used escort for
one. He could have went to Thailand at
36. Think about it, bro. He's
he's like 9 years older than me. You
know, there is things that he could have
done, but he is writing these videos.
I'm not saying he would have ever met
anyone. Obviously, he probably wouldn't,
but you know, like
he didn't help himself with a lot. You
know, he did help himself. Yep.
Yeah, I do like Pepe's chicken.
It's just a day to poke fun at the guys
that ain't wanted by nobody. Yeah,
I was laughing at that Thai woman from
Dubai saying, "I'm confident I've got a
better life than you. You don't know my
life. I could be a multi-millionaire.
You don't [ __ ] know me, you stupid
little [ __ ] And then when I told her
about herself, she shut up. She looks a
[ __ ] as well. You can see the Westinity
in her eyes. She's got Instagram. It's 7:00.
Yeah, 7:00 the date. Well, it's not a
date. It's just some [ __ ] trying to use
me. But little does, you know, I beat
her to it. You can see the westernity in
her eyes, mate. Just cuz you live in
Dubai. Why is it that when women think
they've got more money than people, they
think that they're better than them? Or
if they've got a few more options, they
think that they're better than people.
I like, mate, I could be a
multi-millionaire. You don't You
literally don't know me.
You don't know me, idiot. You understand?
She looks like Yeah, she actually looks
like a [ __ ] if you go on their
Instagram. They do, bro. They do. You
can They've got that Westinity in their
eyes, bro. They do.
You can see the westernity in their eyes.
It's the truth, bro. It is actually the
truth. You laugh at it, but it's true.
Yeah. You want to [ __ ] take my
[ __ ] money, I'll [ __ ] take yours.
Yeah. That's the truth.
That's exactly what I'm doing. Yeah.
Exactly that, bro. Exactly that.
Exactly that, lad.
Let's poke fun at the guys that ain't
wanted by nobody. Yeah.
And I'm going to get a nice wine as
well. I want a nice wine.
[ __ ] take my [ __ ] money. I'll
[ __ ] take yours.
I had a dream of Conrad, you know. Funny
you should say that. I actually had a
dream of Conrad. I had a dream that I um
saw him on the train again.
Oh, yeah. And dessert. Yeah. Don't let
me forget about that. Yeah.
Yeah. A dessert. Yeah. Yeah.
Like when USA is he wanted a dessert. Yeah. Yeah.
I had a dream. I had I saw Conrad on the train.
Oh, [ __ ] yeah. Don't make me forget
about that. Wine, dessert, and the steak.
No, I met him in the pub. I met him in
the Stratford Weather Spoons,
but I I had a dream. I met I saw him on
the train. Weird. Don't know why I'd
have a [ __ ] dream about a [ __ ] guy. Yeah.
Yeah. They're not going to take the piss
out of me anymore. I'm fighting back.
Yeah. I'm not let I'm not going to let
these [ __ ] win. I'm fighting back.
[ __ ] evil women. Yeah. I'm fighting back, lad.
I think I've got his number somewhere, but
Yeah, I think I got it somewhere, but
maybe I don't. Nah.
Yep. You best believe. Yeah. But you
guys love this, isn't it? That's why you
know these people that troll me, Grezy,
they they love this. They say, "Don't
let these [ __ ] women win cuz they
know what I'm like, Grezy."
Yeah, I do remember it, man. I think it
was I don't know. I think it was Mark
Samson. Yeah, with the tenant. Yeah, I do remember.
Yes, I remember, bro. Yep.
Is that red sauce still going? Um, I
don't even go on that channel anymore,
lad. See, the thing is they think I go
on their channel. I don't even go on
their channel. They're sat there wasting
their life stalking me and recording me
and I'm laughing.
Yeah. Like, and I'm laughing, lad.
Yeah. Yeah, I was looking at my life
experiences about 2 3 days ago and I was
like this is lust, bro. To look back on this.
I would not trade that for 13 grand.
I would not trade that for 13 grand,
bro. No way. 13 grand ain't worth it to
take back all of them life experiences
cuz that you can take to the grave with
you. Money you can't. That's the difference, you know.
Yeah, go on. Give it a little whirl.
I like pepp. It's quite delicious, actually.
Don't let these [ __ ] women win. Yeah.
Yeah. Exactly, bro. Like, think of it, man. Like,
I've had stakes. I've traveled, you
know? I've [ __ ] been with [ __ ]
I've stayed in some nice hotels, you
know? Like, I'd rather that than [ __ ]
have the money, you know?
What the [ __ ]
Like, save what now, bro? What? I could go
I can go to America now if I wanted to.
It's just going to take longer to save
for it. You know, it's like there's not
really, you know, like you can't I swear
to God, I probably banged about 300 escorts.
I banged about 300 escorts. So, think
about it, bro. You know, 13 grand in 3
years, that's skin. That is actually skin,
you know. That is actually skin. 13
grand in Well, we say 3 years, it's more
than 3 years.
That's why whenever you show money, they
couldn't show you anything because they
didn't have anything.
Think about it, right? How How long were
they being shown that money and they all ran away?
Huh? Because they didn't have any money.
That's what I'm saying.
No money, no life experiences, no
nothing. You remember when I stayed in
Manchester for two nights?
You remember that?
Uh, a lot.
Know what I'm saying?
You get me though, bro. You get me.
These people don't have They call people
scared because they're scared.
Monty, why does Bomb call me ugly?
Because Bomb's ugly. Yeah, madness.
But they still think that you've got
hope for finding Mrs. Riot. It's crazy, isn't it? No.
You remember the hippid drone casino?
Oh, when I used to rinse them.
I used to rinse them [ __ ]
Oh, bless you. Did you like it?
Did you like when I used to rinse them bastards?
Did you like it?
Yeah, it was lovely, bro. It was lovely.
I know. It's madness, isn't it? It's a
[ __ ] madness. All of that trying and
you still didn't find anyone.
It's horrible. That's That just goes to
show that it's impossible in this country.
At least I've still got money, you know.
It might be a bit slower, but I've got
enough money to do what I need to do
when I want, you know. Um,
but yeah. So, when I was having them
life experiences, think of all of these
other people. would ever happen to work
for money and still deal with this women
[ __ ] you know? I had it easy, bro.
Like, I didn't have to [ __ ] work, you
know? I still don't have to work. >> So,
>> it's a madness, bro. Is it?
No, I didn't. Imagine having to work and
deal with this [ __ ] It's mad, bro.
That is insane, bro. That is insane. That's
That is actually insane, man. What the [ __ ]
You got to work and [ __ ] deal with this. Imagine.
That is insane, bro. So yeah.
See, Virgin Boy ain't got no life
experiences, does he?
Sing a [ __ ] bedit. That's no life for
any anyone of [ __ ] when you're 23, 24, 25.
Sing a [ __ ] bed suit with no [ __ ]
bed in it.
s a [ __ ] bed suit with no [ __ ] bed in it.
What [ __ ] What [ __ ] life
experience is that?
Mad, isn't it?
It is a madness, bro. Yeah,
but people on Reddit say that you'll
meet someone ret.
So they say, huh?
So they say. Hey. So they say.
Let's poke at Let's poke fun at the guys
that ain't wanted by anyone.
Well, at least I get a free steak today.
Banned off of Instagram for 5 days. So,
they start [ __ ] these [ __ ] and
then they report people when they can't take it
outwards. Women are such cowards, you
know. Have you noticed how much cowards they are?
They are cowards, lad.
This person's not replied for a couple
of days. Why are they ignoring for this
person on Instagram?
This [ __ ] isn't it?
Same [ __ ] E
They look like NPCs.
Do you remember? Let's end the night
with some lovely roulette.
Do you remember that one? Hard.
Let's end the night with some lovely roulette.
Yeah, that's funny, bro.
Funny as [ __ ] Do you remember that?
Yeah. We was talking. I met them on
Reddit and all of a sudden they haven't
replied. I mean, what the [ __ ]
Same old [ __ ]
Why are they such [ __ ] Why these
women such [ __ ] Huh?
Why are they such [ __ ]
I'm thinking about doing something dark.
Yeah, I'm doing something dark today at
7:00. Getting a steak and not paying for it. Yeah.
I can't wait.
I mean, I could technically even just
run out the place,
you know? I could technically just run.
You know what I'm saying? >> Yeah.
Yeah. They refuse to pay out.
So I smashed the shop up. They refused
to pay out.
Yeah. It's horrible, isn't it?
Seeing couples and pregnant people and [ __ ]
I'm not going out. I'm Well, I'm going
out to the to the state place, but I
mean I'm not going out drinking.
Waste of time. Waste of money.
You already know the result.
You already know the result. They ain't
interested in this country.
Yeah. They're just them old it same old story.
Go out. Yeah. Why don't
Why don't you go out? Why not?
I'm going to be going like this, by the
way. I'll show you what I look like. Look,
I'm actually show you what I'm wearing.
This is what I'm going to be wearing.
One sec. Let me get out of bed.
I want to look a [ __ ]
I'm also going to look a [ __ ] as well.
Oh, lovely. It's here.
My little tracksuit is here.
Virgin boy in the basement.
Sometimes I wake up when I say that. You know,
it's like, you know how Tom, you know
how Tom used to get called? You know how
Tom used to get called by um Biggy?
Remember how Tom used to get called by um
Tom used to get called by the woman and
Tom and De.
This is what I'm going to show up like.
I'm even going to show up like a [ __ ] Oh, [ __ ]
How are you going to show up like a CL?
Look, I love this track suit, man. Oh, [ __ ]
Boy can't do that.
Look, I like wearing this, bro. This is
like a combo.
I love this combo, bro. This tracksuit
and this coat.
I need to brush my hair, actually.
But yeah, I look [ __ ] Trumpy, bro.
Like Trumpy as in like my beard and
[ __ ] Look at my [ __ ] hair, bro. What the [ __ ] Yeah. Madness.
Yeah, could do. Yeah,
I'm just going to turn up like this
with a nice Hilfiger coat. You remember
the good old Hilfiger coat, don't you?
I'm going to go for a walk in a minute,
I think. Little stroll. Yeah.
Why don't Virgin Boy have a beard? Uhoh.
Virgin boy can't grow a beard.
I was going to go for a walk. Actually,
I can't be bothered to go for a walk.
I don't know. I like Franklin. Frankie. Franker. Oh, Frana.
No, I like Frana.
Could you imagine as I went out
approaching like this?
Could you imagine I went out approaching
like this, bro?
Oh my god, bro. Look at that beard.
Virgin boy can't grow a beard.
But there's no reason to groom. It's
kind of like winter now almost. I'm just keeping warm.
It's what you need to keep warm, you know.
Yeah, it's what you need to do, bro. You
need to keep [ __ ] warm, lad.
Put my nice body track on.
Life could be worse. You could be skin
like the virgin with no life experiences. Yeah,
it's not about being worse or not being
worse. These women are [ __ ] I'm I'm
looking forward to put that that steak today, bro.
Yeah, I got an Ami track suit on. I'm
looking forward to that steak. I want
that steak, bro. I want that nice cow. No,
nothing wrong with me. Nothing wrong
with my weight. She was just being a judgmental [ __ ]
Nah, not really.
Look how long my hair is, bro. I could
actually get into a knot now.
Can get my hair into an actual knot.
Almost. Almost. Almost.
Yeah, that's a little bun. That That is
That's a bun, bro. That is a bun.
That is a bun, lad. Well, it's a little
bun. It's a top knot. It's not a bun.
It's a top knot. But I I I want to I
want a mullet. I want a mullet. And that
takes ages to grow. Like an actual mullet. Um
Yeah. I want a mullet, lad. Nah,
you give it another like few weeks, it
could probably be a bun, I think.
But apparently I'm boarding apparently.
I didn't know that.
You learn something new every day.
Apparently I'm bored.
I didn't know I was bored.
Yeah, I didn't know I was balding, bro.
That's news to me.
The reason I don't wash my hair every
day is cuz I like the grease. It helps it grow.
Gives your hair like some volume, you
know. I didn't know I was bored.
News to me.
News to me, Red Star. I didn't know I was bored.
LJ isn't rich. LJ's got no money.
There's nothing that suggests that he's
got money. He doesn't have money. If he
had money, he wouldn't be sat on YouTube
begging for money every day. He's not
rich. He's actually very, very poor.
But he likes to convince people that
he's rich. But there's nothing rich about him.
There's nothing rich about him. Anybody
can buy a new pair of [ __ ] trainers.
For [ __ ] sake, I can go out right now
and buy a,000 pounds trainers. Does that
make me rich? Nah,
he's not rich. There's nothing rich
about him. He ain't got no money. He's on benefits.
I know he likes to try and convince you
people that he's got money, but really
he has nothing.
Trust me, brother. I can read people
like a book. You know,
he ain't rich. He's got nothing.
Doesn't own properties like he says he
does. This is all makeelie.
It's a makebelieve life.
You know, it is a makebelie life. He
doesn't have any of that stuff. He
doesn't do any of them things that he
says he does.
Why does he just not admit that he ain't
got nothing? I don't pretend I'm rich. I
got more. I got enough money to do what
I want to do or whatever, you know? But
I'm not [ __ ] I don't pretend I'm
rich. Why does he go on like he's got
money when he doesn't? I don't get some
people in here.
their their lifestyle doesn't add up to their finances.
Do you understand? Their lifestyle
doesn't I mean with me, I've given up
with a women and [ __ ]
And that's why I don't go out drinking.
I can afford it, but I don't want to, you know,
cuz I'd rather make more money. I'd
rather save more money than waste it
cuz more money makes money. So, I feel
like it's that's I mean, I've got a
reason, you know? I've been doing this
[ __ ] for years, you know.
Nope. Not doing any more approaches. I'm
done. Done in this country.
I'm not interested.
So, yeah. I'm not interested, bro.
No, I'm all right. Thanks.
No, waste of time. I already know the result.
They're not going to win. I'm getting a
steak out of one of them today, bro.
They're not winning. I'm getting a
lovely steak and some dessert.
And you know what I'm going to Oh, you
know what I'm actually going to say to
her? Are you Aren't you getting any
dessert? I'm going to mock the [ __ ] by
saying, "Oh, aren't you getting any dessert?
Are you getting any dessert?"
Oh, did you see that [ __ ] uh Ricky
Milling's new photo, bro? That scrawny
guy thinking that he's got muscles. Did
you see that? That little snake's
profile picture, bro. I would slap him
from one corner to the other, bro. From
literally one speaker's corner to the
other. Look at me, bro. I'm a big
[ __ ] bro. In the past two years
compared to some of these people, lad. I
got Jimmy Neutron's hairstyle, but
still. Have you seen these new photos?
That's some scrawny little [ __ ] thinking
that he's got muscles, bro. He would get
He looks like one of them noring skinny crackheads, bro. Yeah,
I'd [ __ ] the [ __ ] up, bro.
That little s. You remember that Ricky
Millan? That little s.
That little s that's never seen a woman
naked defending women. What a loser.
defending women. What a [ __ ] loser, eh?
What a loser.
She She wanted to go for drinks at first,
but um yeah, I had to convince her to go
to the steakhouse, which was quite hard to do. Yeah.
Now, have you seen that? Do you remember
that Ricky Mington
sat there defending women? Must be
autism, is it?
Must be autism. Must be.
Must be autism, lad.
Who's that messaging me?
>> Yeah, but why is he singing over women?
Why is he being a s? Why is he defending women?
Why does he snake people and defend
women like he's even been with a woman
ever? See these people, these simps,
right? Like this Ricky Milling, they try
to make it seem like you are the one
that's not been with these women when
you have when it's in fact they're the
ones that have not been with these
women. Why do they make it seem like
you're the one that's never been with
women when it's them that's never been with women?
It's like they try to reverse the psychology.
Why do they sit there and defend women?
I'm trying to like I I just want to know
why they do it.
I just would love to know why they do
it. If they could answer me then what
what do they get out of doing it?
Like when I'm doing these videos on
women, I'm not lying because I get
nothing out of lying. I generally think
they're all the same and they're all [ __ ]
I generally believe it. I don't get
paid. I don't get no sponsorship to lie. You know,
they are all the same evil [ __ ] So,
it's cuz they're skinned and they ain't
got a life. Oh, [ __ ]
It's because they're skinned and they've
not got a life, mate. That's why. Yeah.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
He doesn't have a life. He's a fat, ugly virgin.
He ain't got nothing. That's why he does
what he does every day. Cuz he's a fat
ugly virgin. That's why I don't bother
with them, bro. Sat there stalking cuz
they ain't got a life.
Fat ugly virgin with nothing.
That's why they do that. Because they're
little sad little bully victims with
nothing in their lives. And guess what?
It still doesn't stop me showing my face.
They sit there and try to make you
insecure, but bro, they've never made me insecure.
Look, show my face.
These people, throw my hairline. These
people can't show their face. These
people can't show their hairline cuz
they're the ugly ones.
Know what I'm saying? They have got
nothing to life. They're sat skinned on
YouTube every day. Bro,
that's it, man. Nope.
Not at all. I'm going as I am. Getting a
steak and ditching the [ __ ]
I'm getting a steak and ditching the
[ __ ] Steak, dessert, wine. Well,
probably won't even have wine to be
honest. I don't fancy drinking to be
fair. And I'm just going to ditch her.
Teach you to want to be a little
judgmental [ __ ] [ __ ]
Little [ __ ] I've been dealing with your
[ __ ] for [ __ ] years now. I just want
some [ __ ] food. That's all I want. Yeah,
it's about [ __ ] time. So, you best
[ __ ] come today, mate.
You know what I'm saying? 7:00 I need to
go. Don't know why I'm changed now. It's
the song I put into it.
Uh yeah, that's exactly what I'm going
to say. I'm going to say, um, why don't
you get a boob job? Why don't you gain
some weight and get a boob job?
That's what I'll say. Why don't you gain
some weight and get a boob job? Yeah.
Yeah. That's what I'll say. I said, "Why
don't you go get a boob job, go gain
some weight, and then come back to me."
No, I'm I'm turning up in a tracksuit, mate.
I'm turning up in a tracksuit.
You know what I might do?
I might not even just I I might go I
might just go go for the steak here and
say, "Listen, it's been a long time
coming. Thank you for the steak. Thank
you for the dessert. And before judging
people in the future, maybe you should
go get yourself a boob job cuz you ain't
got no tits. And maybe you should gain
some [ __ ] weight. See you later.
See you later. I don't know your [ __ ]
mate. That's what I might just do. I
might just say it and just walk off. See
you later, mate. You know,
cuz people can't c catch up with Peter
B. Maybe I'll just say that before leaving.
Yeah. See you later, mate.
See you later, mate. I don't owe you
[ __ ] mate. That's what I might say.
Yeah. I'm actually saying that, bro,
without even just like ditching. Yeah. [Music]
Do you know what you could also do as
well? You could say that you forgot your card, right?
And um let her pay for it and then do it
again and make her pay for it again.
There's a there's a few things you could do.
There's a few things you could do.
Yeah, there's a few things you could do, man. lad.
Nah, but that that's fine. That one's good,
you know. Yeah.
No, there's no point even wasting my
time. I don't want a [ __ ] off her. I
just want the food. And we all know what
she would say anyways. I don't need to
make sure. I'm already sure of what her
intentions is. I'm already sure. I don't
need to make sure. I already know. I'm
already sure. I don't need to make
double sure, you know.
And mate, even if she was going to give
me a [ __ ] I'm not paying over100 for
a [ __ ] I want the steak. Simple.
My whole interest is not trying to get
with her. I don't want her. I want the
steak off of her. That's the whole
thing. So, I don't need to make sure
what I'm already sure of. I know I'm
very sure of what she's already trying to do.
You know, you're talking to me, bro.
Someone that's met more women than
anyone in the world. You understand?
Yes. I'm already sure what she's trying to do.
And even if she was offering a [ __ ]
I still wouldn't I still wouldn't pay.
So, it wouldn't make no difference anyways.
I'm sick of a [ __ ] and [ __ ] you know,
to last me a [ __ ] whole lifetime.
And she said that, "Oh, it's not a
date." You know, she just wants to um
have fun and be friends and how we're
not going to be an item. She wants to be
like a stuckup [ __ ] even though I don't
like her. So, she's going to see a stuckup [ __ ]
Simple. It's not going to cost me anything. You know,
it's not going to cost me anything at all
to go there and [ __ ] I mean,
I'm not going to eat until then cuz I
need to fill my appetite.
Um, I'm not going to speak about anything.
Do you know what I'm going to do whilst
I'm eating a steak?
I'm going to say to her, do you know
what would look better on you if you had
a boob job? Yeah,
you should get a boob job. That's what
we're going to talk about on the date.
We're going to start talking about her
appearance. She's like, I'm going to be
like, you know what you should get? You
should get a boob job.
You should get a boob job. You should
gain some weight. You should change your
hair. That's what That's what I'm going
to be talking about on the date.
I won't pay, mate. Trust me, I am not
paying. No matter what happens, I am not
[ __ ] paying at all.
So, I mean, that's as far as that goes.
I am not paying nothing no matter what happens.
So believe that. Yeah. And she's not
going to leave before me, mate.
It's not going to happen. And I wouldn't
be gooed and I won't pay no matter what happens. So So yeah.
So I won't be goose because I'm not
paying no matter what. That's that.
That's as far as that goes.
No, the bill won't be mine because I'll
run off. Nope. The bill's not on me,
bro. Because, bro, I'll run off.
Nope. Because I'll run away.
I'll run away and get the train back.
So, nope, the bill's not on me.
Not at all. because I'll just run off. So,
if that would happen, which is not going
to happen, I'll just run off. So, yeah. Yeah.
If she leaves, I'm leaving with her. So,
simple. I ain't [ __ ] paying you mad.
You must be [ __ ] mad if you think I'm
[ __ ] paying, lad.
Doesn't matter what the circumstances
are, I am not paying.
Yeah, I see it, bro.
I see it.
I'm going to a steakhouse today. This
woman's paying for me, Timothy. And by
paying for me, I mean I'm literally
going to be walking off when um
when the bill comes and stuff. I'm going
to just ditch her. But going to get some
nice dessert, some nice steak. Yeah,
that'll teach them for being little
[ __ ] in it.
Well, then she doesn't return. I'm
walking out. Simple. So, that's it.
Yeah. They want to start being [ __ ] to
me, Timothy. They want to be a [ __ ] to
me their whole life. I'll be a [ __ ] to
them. They want to be a She was like a
proper [ __ ] I met her and she was like
a proper proper [ __ ]
trying to say, "Oh, wow. It's not going
to be a date. We're not going to be an
item." I'm like, who do you think you
are? I'm way better than you will ever be.
I'm way better than you. And I don't
even like her. The thing is, Timothy,
these are women that we don't even like.
These are women that we don't even like
and they've got an attitude.
You know what I'm saying, lad?
There's a nice little steakhouse I know of. So,
because she says that she wants to be
friends and um we're not going to be an
item, but she wants to meet for a drink, but yeah,
she wants to meet for a drink and [ __ ]
but we're not going to be an item. And
no, no, no, no. Uh, it's not going to
happen. And I would say no.
So stop talking about things that's
never going to happen, you know.
You know, yeah, that's not going to She
said, "Oh, yeah, we're not going to be
an item. It's not a date, you know. I
just want to go and see waxies and have
a few drinks and stuff, so she wants to
go around being a [ __ ] I'll be a cunt."
And I don't even like her. That's the
funniest thing. I These are women that
you don't even like. They're not even
women that you do like. They're women
that you don't even like. That's the
That's the craziest thing, bro.
Want to be a little time wasting [ __ ]
She wants to be a little [ __ ] Just like
that Italian. The last date I went on,
she was a [ __ ] as well. Timewasting
Yeah. I'm going to get a lovely T-bone.
And if they don't have T-bone, which
they might not have, I'll get a lovely fillet. Lovely Phillip.
Yeah. Do you know what she was saying as
well, Timothy? Right. When I met her,
she was like, "Oh, yeah, you look better
with your hair like that and you should,
you know, she you should go on a weight
training program and ret t um you know,
and it's like, who is she to judge? You
don't see me saying, "Oh, you should go
get a boob job. You should gain weight."
Who are you to [ __ ] start [ __ ] judging anyone?
Well, cuz I was wearing shorts and a
t-shirt and my hair was curly. So,
what? You're still the same person? You
want to be a little judgmental little [ __ ] Watch.
I'm not even fat. That's what I'm
saying. I know. I'm not even fat. I
wasn't even fat then either. You was
just being a [ __ ]
trying to say, "Oh, yeah, you should you
should um get a weight training program
and you should have your hair like it
was in that picture." I mean, it doesn't
matter what my hair's like, I'm still
the same person. He said, "Oh yeah, you
should go back to that look. Who are you
to tell me what I should be looking like?"
You don't see me telling you to go get a
[ __ ] boom job, you [ __ ] silly
little [ __ ] And I'll be taking the
[ __ ] piss out of her bank account today
when she shows up. Yeah.
Stupid. I hate these women, Timothy. I
[ __ ] hate them, bro. Why do you think
I don't go out anymore?
Why do you think I don't go out anymore?
Drinking, approaching, and I'm not doing
violence. There's no shouting. There's
no nothing. There's just me taking them
taking the piss out of them.
Yeah, there's nothing wrong with my weight, lad.
There's literally nothing wrong with my
weight. This is what I mean. It's insecurity.
Yeah. Trying to tell me that my hair
should be like how it was before. I
never asked you about my [ __ ] hair.
Don't think you're [ __ ] better than
me. And these are people that we don't
even like because you imagine the people
that we actually did like. Yeah.
Don't [ __ ] be a [ __ ]
I'll teach her for being a [ __ ] all her life.
Yeah, [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] Don't try to
make people feel insecure just because
you hate the way that you look. You know
what I'm saying? What the [ __ ]
Yeah, she's a proper wronging, bro.
Proper wronging. Like most of them.
I want to get a bit back over the years,
Timothy, that I've dealt with with these
[ __ ] is I want to get a bit back.
Just a little bit back over the years,
you know? I just want a little bit back.
You know, the money that they've wasted,
the time they're going on dates to make
you feel bad about yourself, you know?
Oh, there's no if I actually do this. I
am doing this. Look, I'm all dressed up
for it as well. I'm coming out in I'm
going out in a track suit. I am doing this.
It's not if I do this. I am doing this. Lad look. So yeah,
I am doing this matey. Oh [ __ ]
No, they don't make me feel fat and
ugly. It's just self projection. Nah.
No, not at all, bro. I don't feel fat or
ugly. Not at all, bro. You can ask Red
Star. He's been projecting his ugliness
and boldness onto me for years. Doesn't
affect me one little bit. I still show
my face. He would never show his face
cuz he's fat and ugly.
They don't make me feel fat and ugly. I
just don't know who the [ __ ] they think they are.
Trying to tell talk about you and they
ain't even got any tits.
And they look underweight. What the [ __ ] Yeah. Yeah.
So, I'm definitely doing it, bro.
Yeah, they try to. Yeah, they try to. Of
course. Yeah, obviously. Yeah, they try
to cuz they're evil. They're all the
same. They're all narcissists. That's
why. You don't know how excited I am for this steak.
Oh, mate. I I ain't been to a steakhouse
in ages. I think it's got me like a year
now. So, I'm looking forward to it. Nice
bit of t-bone steak. Oh, mate. Bit of onion rings.
I can't wait, mate. I can't wait. Yep.
I hate women.
And you're going to discover that as
well today when I get this [ __ ]
this steak out of them, lad.
Get by the pockets.
I think the steak's going to be about 80 quid. Yeah. Five.
They tried to make you feel that that way. Yeah.
All cuz I was wearing t-shirt and shorts
cuz it was hot.
Yeah, I'm going to meet her. Obviously,
they are evil. They They generally are
all evil. I mean, the one from Finland
is just okay. Yeah. Oh, [ __ ]
I can't even message that person. Why? Yeah.
It doesn't let me message this person. Nice.
Yeah. Yeah, it is still one. [Laughter]
It definitely is still on.
Oh, but after two. You can't listen to
someone after two. Strange.
Yeah, it is still one.
Maybe. Maybe not.
Maybe, maybe not.
Depends if I get chance to, but hopefully. Yeah.
I need to go to that same one that I
went to before cuz I know where the
toilets are and [ __ ] So, yeah.
I'm not going to drink though cuz I
don't want to drink. But I'm just going
to have like two Cokes,
dessert, onion rings,
just a lot, mate. I'll just get as much
as I can eat. Oh yeah.
What about if I done if I done a video
in America? Would you see that one?
Like everyone everything's gone quiet
and then all of a sudden bam.
I'm just going to stick it on her before
leaving. Actually, I'm not even going to
go toilet. I'm just going to stick it on
her before leaving.
I might just stick it on the [ __ ]
before actually leaving. Eat her food.
Yeah. and then stick it on her and then
just [ __ ] off. Yeah.
Stick it on the [ __ ] and then [ __ ] off.
Might just do that. A good oldfashioned
ownage, you know.
Yeah. [ __ ] silly little wrong [ __ ] Yeah, [ __ ] [ __ ]
So, yeah, it's going to be fun, bro.
It's going to be fun.
And even if she offered a [ __ ] I'd
still say no cuz I don't like her. It's
not the point of liking someone I don't
like her. Even if she offered it, I
would say, "No, I want the state, bro.
[ __ ] the blowjob."
Yeah, that's what he does. I think some
of them accounts, right, that [ __ ]
they troll me, bro. They're sat around
with their little mates. They're sat
around with their little mates having a
little laugh at my content. Yeah.
What if I have too much anxiety to go to
central London though? Nah. Nah, mate.
Too much anxiety to go to central
London. Nah, mate.
Not me, matey. We're not large. E.
I want a nice bit of red steak, you
know. Medium. Well done. Medium. Medium.
Bit crispy, you know. Oh, mate.
Yeah, they're all going to have a little giggle.
They're all going to have a little
giggle, ain't it?
I'll tell these little mates. Yeah.
Never had agrophobia, mate. Never had agobia.
You know that, don't you, boss?
Nah. Peter belly don't have agrophobia matey. No matey.
She's probably still in bed cuz she she
works as like a club promoter.
My phone's blocked. I'm going to have to
meet the [ __ ] outside of a place that's
got Wi-Fi. Hopefully the station does.
Yeah, Valentine's is just a day to poke
fun out of them people that ain't wanted by nobody.
What a way to poke fun out of the people
that ain't wanted by nobody. Madness, it
a day to poke fun out the people that
ain't wanted by nobody.
That is a madness, bro.
A working SIM. The phone's blocked, you
[ __ ] [ __ ] It's not about a working
SIM. The phone's blocked. Doesn't matter
what SIM you put in it, bro. What the
[ __ ] The phone is blocked.
You can only use on Wi-Fi and [ __ ] and
call on Wi-Fi and
the phone's [ __ ] man.
So, why does these Reddit mods block
anyone that's got a different opinion anyways?
Why they block anyone that's got a different opinion?
What's all that about?
I haven't got a working phone. The
phone's blocked. Probably want to buy a
new one. Don't need a new one.
You know, I mean,
yeah, the the mods block anyone that's
got a different opinion. Who's that? So yeah,
I don't know why these people defend
women. I'd love to know why they defend
them. I really would love to know
why these virgins sit there and defend
women. I would love to know, bro. I'd
love to know.
I would really love to know why they sit
there and defend these women.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Sat there defending women their whole life.
Yeah, that's totally going to get them
laid, isn't it? Yeah. Badness.
Whoa. Franklin's gone flying.
Oh, Franklin's gone flying.
You nasty virgin.
This person on [ __ ] Is this person on
Reddit going to [ __ ] reply or what? Anyway,
I'm going for a walk. I'll be back soon.
I need to go through seven. Oh god,
it's gotten really cold outside, hasn't it? [ __ ]
>> Yeah, man. Back in a bit.