These people are proper [ __ ] sers. Oh
my [ __ ] god.
Jesus Christ. You know what? Yeah, I
thought that was a thing, but I didn't
realize they were that [ __ ] sad and
[ __ ] that they actually go on that guy's
channel. Wow. They're actual stalkers.
That must mean they actually must have
went on every single one of his channel
to find me. Whoa. These people are
actual losers. Like when you when you
think right they can't do anything worse. They do.
Whoa. Madness, bro. These people are
actual stalkers. Pointless. I'm just
going to make another channel now and
put all them videos back on my other
channel. [ __ ] absolute stalkers.
I went on my other channel and I saw
[ __ ] fast subscribers. You know what?
Right. I'll let some more people join. Yeah.
I'll let some more people join before I
say this, bro, because I don't want to
repeat myself and have to say it all over again. But yeah,
these people found my other channel.
They're [ __ ] stalkers, bro. They're
absolute [ __ ] stalking little low
lives. They must have went on the Oreo
man's channel and went on every single
video of his. These people are actual
stalkers, bro. They actually are. These
[ __ ] fat ugly people ain't got no
life at all. They really really ain't
got no life. Like I made another channel
to get away from these mongos, these all self-reflectors,
you know? I put content on there
specifically for unbiased people. and
let these fat ugly mongos find me.
They're [ __ ] stalkers. I've deleted
all the videos and I'm gonna make
another channel. No problem. I'll make
one in a bit.
All my approaching videos saved. Like
I've done it like to show people like
the dating game in this country and I've
got these fat ugly little weirdos
[ __ ] coming on. You know what I mean? Weirdos, lad. That's it.
You know what? After I beat up Prime
tomorrow, if he shows up, I'm coming off
this community, bro. I've made up my mind.
You know, at the end of the day, right,
before they even found me, these little
stalkers, right, I was thinking about
this. I went to go car was too busy, so
I just went chicken shop and I was
walking back. I was like, "Bro, do you
know what?" Yeah. Ah, [ __ ]
Someone stuck in my tooth. I'm coming
off this [ __ ] after tomorrow, bro.
I'm coming off this [ __ ]
I am coming off the, you know, this
[ __ ] with these little [ __ ]
self-reflecting little mongos. Ain't got
a life. Like, that's it, bro. I'm I'm
I'm I'm coming off this [ __ ] after
tomorrow, bro. I'm going to own that
prime cuz he's been pissing me off. And
then Tuesday, I'm done. I made up my
mind now. Final, bro. I've had enough of
these people to last me a lifetime.
There's no point to this community.
They're just fat, ugly, jealous people
that ain't got no life. Self-reflecting
every single day. There's no reason to
be on it anymore. There's literally This
is before I even found out that they
actually found me. Um, so this is even
more of a reason. Yeah,
I'm I'm off of here Tuesday, bro. So,
good luck to you. That's all I've got to
say. Good luck to you.
Stalking. Absolute stalking. That must
have mean they went on every single
video on his channel to find me.
Stalkers. This is what I mean. This is
how you know it's jealousy because think
of how many of these middle-aged people
gravitate towards me. Gravitate towards
me. Think about it. I'm better looking
than them. I'm younger than them. I've
got hope unlike them. I've got all of
these middle-aged wankers gravitating
towards me. Do you not that think? Do
you not think that looks a bit sus, bro? You know,
no, they just found me and it's just the
self-reflecting every day, you know.
It's just not it's not that. It's like
you go on a channel skin.
You hear the same [ __ ] every day, the
same repeating every day, you know?
You're skin, you're this, you're that.
No, no, no. It's boring, bro. It's
boring. They're weirdos. They're a
lesson to learn from. They're not to
they're not to associate with. They're a
lesson to learn from. These people are a
lesson to learn from. They're not to be
associated with. They're to they're
there to be learned what you don't want
to be like when you're their age. Sat on
YouTube, ain't got no life, ain't got
nothing. Trying to talk about people
half your age. You know, they're a
[ __ ] wakeup call, lad. They're a
[ __ ] wakeup call. That's what they are.
Weirdos. Absolute weirdos.
I'm making another channel, you know.
I'm coming off this [ __ ] on Tuesday,
bro. After I own this prime tomorrow,
I'm coming off this [ __ ] Hold me to it,
bro. Hold me to it. Yeah,
the repeating and the self projecting
every day. It's weird, bro. It's [ __ ]
weird. You know, I was thinking about it
when I was walking back.
They're [ __ ] losers. Absolute losers.
So, yeah. On Tuesday, I'm done. So, you
won't see me on here Tuesday. Once I
embarrass that prime tomorrow,
um I'm done. So, they can do what they
want every day. Self-reflect their life
away. Don't want to do that, bro. That's
fine. Now, I'm going to have to make a
new channel now and put all of my videos
back up because of these people
[ __ ] stalking. What the [ __ ] Why are
they stalking someone half their age,
bro? Do they want my dick or something?
What the [ __ ]
All of what they do is self-reflect. And
all they all what they do is
self-reflect, bro. They're sat sat
online every day ain't got nothing but
YouTube calling other people what they
are themselves. Skin, ugly, no future,
no prospects, all of their own lives
that they're talking about cuz they're
good at talking about themselves.
They've got a degree in it.
No. What do you mean? Because I don't
want them on my channel. Because I don't
want them on my channel. I don't want
these little mongos on my channel. As
soon as I see one or two of them on my
approaching channel, I don't want them
on there. I don't want these little
self-reflecting, fat, ugly people
watching me. Simple. It's okay. This
This is a live stream. I'm not doing
content for them. I don't want these
fat, ugly, self-reflecting, skinned
people on my [ __ ] That's on my That's
my choice. Simple. I don't want them on
my [ __ ] channel, bro.
So, I'm going to have to make another
channel again because they found my
other channel. What the [ __ ] bro? They
can watch this channel if they want to
stop them on my other channel. Simple,
you know? [ __ ] hell. It's weird. Proper weird.
I don't care if it's two of them or
whatever. I don't care. I don't want
them on my channel. They can get gone.
So, they've definitely watched that
Oreo, man. They definitely been watching
him cuz that's how they found me.
They're [ __ ] self-reflectors.
They're [ __ ] self. And I shouldn't
even be on here, bro. You know, I'm 28
[ __ ] next month. I'm getting [ __ ] old, bro.
You know, I haven't got long left before
I'm [ __ ] really, really old. So,
don't know what I'm going to do, bro.
Just not going to be on here. They're
too weird. These people are too too too
too weird. They must have been on that
[ __ ] Oreo man's channel.
They must have been on his channel and
found me that way.
So, I need to make another [ __ ]
channel. Put my coaches back on that.
What the [ __ ]
Good for you, bro. Yeah.
I don't know, man. I don't care. I don't
care about any of these people. I just
want this prime to show up tomorrow so I
can smash his face in and I'm done with
this [ __ ] by Tuesday, bro.
Leave for a very, very, very [ __ ] long time.
You know, it's a madness. An absolute Really is.
What is that?
Valentine's Day is just to poke fun out
the people that ain't wanted by nobody. Richie
is um to poke fun out of the [ __ ]
people that ain't chosen by nobody.
It's [ __ ] mad, bro. That's actually
[ __ ] It's actually true. You know, we
laugh at it, but it's the truth, isn't it?
Some people are just not meant to have a good life.
You know, that's
how it is. Some people are just not
meant to have a good life.
Some people are meant to have a [ __ ] life.
Like, no. You know,
a depressing life, ain't it?
Nope. It was too packed. So, I just went
to get some chicken.
This life is really depressing. Hey,
bro. So, I'm not even going to say after
I'm gone on Tuesday, my life's going to
be perfect because I don't know. I might
end up [ __ ] doing myself in.
No one's going to say they've got a
better life than anyone, but I [ __ ]
don't want to entertain these freaks
anymore. They found my [ __ ] second
channel. They're weirdos. What the [ __ ]
Got to start that [ __ ] all again now.
just putting my approaches up on that
because I have videos of my approaches
because obviously they're memories and
[ __ ] and then they keep they must have
been watching the Oreo, man. They must have been
stalkers. Absolute stalkers.
[ __ ] fat old ugly men online every
day taking out on the world that [ __ ]
their lives are [ __ ] That's why they do
all of this self-reflecting bollocks
every day, bro. It doesn't matter what
it is now. I've deleted all the videos.
I'm making another one.
That's what all of this comes down to.
This whole [ __ ] your skin, you ain't
got a job, you ain't got nothing. It's
because they're the ones that are like
this at their age and they hate it.
That's why they do this. That's why they
do this lowife [ __ ] every day on the
internet. Year in year out, year in year
out, year in year out. Madness. It's
absolute [ __ ] madness.
They don't know what money people have.
They don't know what money people don't have,
you know? Just so weird.
Oh, it's just some black guy in America
that talks about dating and stuff. Yeah.
Valentine's Day, um, Cory, is is a day
to poke fun out of the people that ain't
wanted by nobody,
that ain't chosen by no one. Yeah.
No, I was actually starting to like
think like, oh, I could start the gym
and stuff, but I don't want to do
anything in my life, bro.
I feel like just completely giving up
with it all. I've done enough in four
years. I don't I've got nothing left to
prove in this life. I got [ __ ] all left to prove.
Like nothing, bro. Like literally
nothing left to prove.
You get what I mean, bro?
Like absolutely nothing for real.
You know how it is.
It's a boring repetitive life, bro.
It's [ __ ] It's wank. You know,
that's why I've got all of these old men
that gravitate onto me.
These old men that gravitate towards me.
cuz you're younger than them. You're,
you know, you're better looking than them.
They ain't got no life. So they get
angry at people that have some kind of hope
or think they've got some kind of hope.
Do you get me, bro?
Jeez, look how young I look there, man.
was really young there, man.
I didn't go because it was too busy.
Yep. I'm skin. This is exactly why I'm
coming off of this [ __ ] on Tuesday. I'm
going to leave these little
self-reflectors to their little [ __ ]
life. They can go self-reflect on
another channel. I'm just going to go on
my own channel, bro. The one that I make. Um, again,
I'm going to make a new channel, put all
of the approaches back on that, and I
think I'm just going to stick on that channel
and make my own community. I reckon, bro,
I'm going to leave these little self-reflectors
to talk about themselves.
Yeah. You don't even have £1,000 to your name.
So, yeah, I'm gone on Tuesday. Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, man.
Yeah, talking about yourself again.
Yeah, you're talking about yourself again.
Yeah. This is a community where angry
40-year-old gamblers come and
self-reflect their life onto you every day. Yeah. Nah,
nah. You people talk about kids every
day when you're not self-reflecting your
skintess onto people. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm going to leave this
narcissistic weirdo [ __ ] skin
community to keep talking about
themselves every day. They ain't got
nothing better to do. Clearly, lad.
Clearly. Just self-reflect there. That's
why I don't go on L J's.
That's why I don't go on L J's. Cuz it's
just the same repeating self-reflectors. Boring, bro.
I have to start a whole new [ __ ]
channel cuz of these [ __ ]
And even though it was two only two of
them that found my new channel, I don't
want them on my channel.
I literally don't want them on my channel. Simple.
Yeah, I leave these little low lives to it.
People like Red Star and [ __ ] the
skin virgin and the bed [ __ ] might have
all day to spend on YouTube arguing with
people they're never going to meet, but
that ain't my life, bro. That ain't
[ __ ] my life. So, I'll leave them to it.
But the side those they are.
Yep. Whatever. You keep telling yourself that. Oh, [ __ ] Yeah.
Madness. Mad. Madness.
This life, this life is [ __ ] dead, bro.
This life is actually dead.
Really is dead. It's a dead life.
What do you think, Candy? Man, it's a
[ __ ] life, isn't it?
Well, cool, man. These [ __ ] stalkers
found my um other channel. So, I'm going
to have to do a new channel now and put
all of my approaches back on that channel
cuz they found me. So,
they discovered me. So, yeah.
Some things have gone on, but I'm not
going to explain why cuz it's personal.
But I've told the people that I um speak
to in person.
It got four subs,
but it was videos I would send people on
Reddit. I'd send it to people on Reddit,
you know, like to show my experiences
with dating and [ __ ] Yeah,
because they commented. You [ __ ]
idiot. Because they commented
that it was bombing someone else. You're
asking, you're this, so same repeating
[ __ ] So, after I own uh
after I own this [ __ ] tomorrow,
I'm leaving this [ __ ] bro, for a little while.
Don't know what I'm doing. I was
thinking of starting the gym again, but
I can't be bothered. I feel like I've
lived my life, bro. There's nothing left
to prove. There's nothing left to
Yeah, he is a virgin. There's nothing
there's nothing left, bro, to even do or prove, you know,
and then some stuff that's made even
worse as well. I'm not going to talk
about it. is personal. But yeah,
feels like you're constantly constantly
being mocked in life, tested in life.
The thing is you you know
if you was a [ __ ] in your life and you
was a bully you would have had a good
life. I mean a good life you wouldn't be like
you wouldn't be single. You wouldn't be
sexless. If you were a [ __ ] if you was
like a bully. Have you noticed that
bullies get rewarded?
Nasty people get rewarded and good
people die young or good people suffer.
Yeah. It doesn't matter, bro.
Sick of being mocked.
Sick of being laughed at. It's horrible, horrible life. So, Yeah,
it doesn't matter.
[ __ ] I'm sick of seeing couples. I
went out today and I think I saw a
couple. I hate seeing couples. I hate
people. I hate seeing pregnant people.
There's a proper trigger, Kevin.
You know, like when people when people's
anxiety gets triggered, you know, people
that's got anxiety and their anxiety
gets triggered. Mine gets triggered. My
anxiety, but I get triggered. You know,
this life is dead. I'm sick of living, bro.
It really is a [ __ ] life.
It really is a sick life, bro. Sick life.
Uh, I'm not jealous. I'm not jealous of
anyone, but it's just mocking.
It's just a It's just to be mocked.
It's just to poke fun out of the people
that's had bad experiences. I don't
care. It's just mocks you.
It's to poke fun out of the people,
you know? They ain't chosen by nobody.
So, you sit there and you actually
laugh, but it ain't even funny. It's [ __ ] depressing.
All of it's depressing, bro. That
either way, there's no life in this
country, bro. There's no life in this
country. There's no future in this
country. You see the thing is I was
looking a lot of the people on Uber was
saying that they're um they live in
America and they're making like $3 $400
a [ __ ] day. That's crazy. Yeah.
Well, obviously I've got a history with
these women, so that's why it bothers me.
Would that annoy you? Greasy seeing
couples and stuff. It annoys me.
It depresses me.
I just give up with life, man. Me, I
completely give up with life.
cuz I feel like if I died then people
can have some of the money that I have.
Well, it's not a lot of money but it's
the money. Money is money, you know,
like so it will help them out. There's
no point living this life. It's torment.
It's torture. It's been going on for years.
It's been going on for years. this life.
It really, really is. You know,
it's not a life for anyone, mate. It
ain't a life for anyone.
Nah, it's just depressing, bro. I went
out early seeing couples and stuff. It's depressing.
It is a depressing life.
Depressing. Depressing life. I want out of it
generally, bro. It's depressing as [ __ ]
This life never changes. Depressing as [ __ ] Yeah.
It's just a way to poke fun out of
people though. Is it Greasy?
Poke fun out of people that ain't chosen by nobody.
Nope. Life isn't what you make it at
all. I've tried to make it the best and it's failed.
absolutely failed. I want out of it,
mate. I'm going to do myself in at some
point. You watch. I am going to [ __ ]
do it. I don't give a [ __ ] It's depressing.
I want out of it. Generally want out of
Really, really want out of this life.
Ain't no life for anyone, mate. being tormented.
I mean, look at this [ __ ] look at the
weather today. It was [ __ ] raining, lad. Nah.
I'm not going to tell you it's personal, but yeah,
just another thing to basically poke fun
out of people like me
and Mario man and all of these people.
It's just a way to poke fun out of people.
To be honest with you, I was laughing at
it, but it ain't even funny when you
think about it. Huh?
It's just madness.
just a just another day to poke fun out of people.
And then these people found me because of him.
That's how they discovered me.
I'm not ready for a relationship. Um I'm
not skin actually. You don't know how
much money I have. And also I have lived
by myself and I've had loads and loads
and loads of money. So, stop making
excuses. Sorry, I just clocked onto that
comment. You don't know how much money I
have. And this is one of the reasons why
I'm coming off this on Tuesday as well,
cuz of the repeating, the
self-reflecting and the repeating.
Sorry, I just read that comment, bro.
Yeah, the self-reflecting, the repeating.
I feel like it's actually gave me like
proper like brain damage, bro.
Proper proper brain damage.
And I'm just going to go on my other
channel and just try and build a
community up on that at least for a very long time.
You know, you don't know how much money
I have and you don't know who I live with.
Just self-reflecting every day.
Just the same repeating every day. You
don't know how much money people have.
You don't know who people live with.
You know, skin skin. Oh my god. My
brain. [ __ ] hell. My brain, bro. Help me.
It's just the same repeating people.
Skin. Skin. Skin. Skin. Skin. Skin.
No, I've already explained to you why
I'm not showing money. No, I've already
explained why I'm not showing money.
I've again, we're having the same
conversation over and over and over again.
Um, no. I've already explained to you
why I'm not showing no money anymore.
Because whenever you get show money, you
run away and then I'm going to have no
one to [ __ ] show anything to. Yes,
because I don't gamble anymore. I'm not
showing you no money.
I'm not showing, bro. For you to keep
calling people skin, you must be skin.
You are the ones that keep bringing
money up. So, you are skin. You must be
for you people to keep bringing up money
every day because it's cuz you keep
looking in your bank account. That's
what it is. That's why you keep calling
people skint every day because you are
skin. You You are the ones bringing up
money every day because you ain't got
none. It's obvious. It's obvious. The
people that keep bringing up money every
day. It's people that ain't got no
money. This is not This is exactly what
I'm saying. It's self It's self-reflection
with these people. This is what I'm
saying. It's self-reflection with these
people. They go on about money cuz they
ain't got none and they try to
self-reflect that their skin lives onto
you. This is what I'm saying.
No, they didn't, bro. Yeah, okay. I've
got no money. Whatever. Keep
self-reflecting. We've all seen you
people. When you get show money, you run
away. Every time you get show money, you
run away. So, why do you want people to
show you money for you to I'm not
Anyways, I'm not I'm not doing this
again. Anyways, I'm just going to let
you keep you people keep
self-reflecting, calling yourself skin.
I'm just going to let you people keep
self-reflecting. I'm not even going to
answer it anymore. I'm going to let you
keep bringing the money up cuz you ain't
got none. I'm not even going to answer it anymore.
Oh, must have been must have been my
must have been my by mistake.
Must have been my mistake. My bad.
Anyways, I'm not bringing up this whole
self-reflecting money thing anymore. Anyways,
always talking about anyways about life
being [ __ ] Yeah.
Nah, nothing like that.
Close though. He was close. Wow. Someone
must have been reading my mind almost. But no. Anyways,
we're not we're not talking about money
no more anyways with you people.
Well, I'm not. So,
so yeah, we're not talking about money
no more. I'm not talking about money. Yeah.
I don't even know what the point of me
being born was. Nope.
I I don't even see what the point of me
even being born was to be honest with you.
It's like what some of these people
these videos say. If you're a bad person,
you have a
you have a good life if you're a bad person.
If you're not a bad person, then you
either die young or you suffer in life.
That's what happens.
Something like that. Yeah.
This a sad sad life, bro. I want out of it.
Cuz then I die.
[ __ ] people then get my money.
What money I have left and then everyone
wins. You know what I'm saying? Everybody wins.
Life's just not meant for everyone. It's
a bit like what that Oreo man says. Life
just ain't meant for anyone. Everyone.
I like watching these videos, you know. So, yeah.
Well, I don't want the link. That's all right, bro.
I'm not putting anyone up on the front
panel for a bit, but yeah.
Um, I'm not answering that question. So, yeah.
No, I'm not letting anyone on the panel. Oh, wow.
Yeah, exactly, bro. You're right. I've
never shown six grand and you've all run
away. I've never shown me with women. I
know. You're completely right. Yeah.
You're right. I've never shown six
grand. I've never made you all run away.
I've never shown women and made you all
run away. Yeah, of course you're right,
man. Obviously, it must have been
someone else, not me. Duh. So, yeah.
And I'm coming off this [ __ ] on Tuesday
anyways cuz I need to deal with that prime tomorrow.
It might send me over the edge. It won't
send me over the edge. I've got more
than three grand. That's not going to bother me.
No, three grand is not going to send me
not even slightly over the edge. Keep dreaming.
So yeah, I'm uh I'm not showing you
nothing. You I'm not showing you
nothing. I told you this a million
times. I'm showing you [ __ ] all.
You know, I'm only meeting this prime
tomorrow cuz he's coming to London and
he's been winding me up. I'm not showing
you [ __ ] all. I'm not even showing you a fiber. So,
yeah. You've never had a woman.
Yeah, but you've never had a woman.
You've never had a woman. So, you're
still a virgin. So, even worse.
Imagine that. Imagine you've never had a
woman and you're still a virgin. That's even worse.
You're worse than me. You're still a virgin.
But yeah, I'm coming off this [ __ ] on
Tuesday. Yeah, cuz we arranged this for tomorrow. So
yeah, I haven't got 30 and you keep
telling yourself that.
Yeah. I mean, it says it all that you
people are on here every single day
trying to put other people down. It says
a lot about your lives and what you
people really have.
You know, you're like older than me,
right? You say you got all this money
and everyone else's skin and no,
you're sat on here doing what you do
every single day. Make it make actual
sense. Make it make actual sense,
please. If you are going to do
something, at least make it make sense. [ __ ] hell. Anyways,
I'll be off this [ __ ] Tuesday. Anyways,
I'm going to build this channel up later.
No, what you do is you come on here to
make yourself feel better. The fact that
you are in your 40s and you got no money
and you ain't got no life and you want
to try to bring other people down to
your level and you ain't even got any
hope. That's why you come on here
because you're nobody's in real life.
You ain't got no life. You ain't got no
money. You ain't got no bird. You ain't
got [ __ ] all. That's why you come on
here every day trying to
start on people that's half your age
that's actually got hope unlike you.
That's what you do. [ __ ] obvious. Anyways,
I'm going to start banning these [ __ ]
Right, we're going to buy these self-reflectors.
Badly self-reflective bastards. Yeah,
my coach in a minute.
Well, I'm not going to be on YouTube
calling people half my age, that's for [ __ ] sure. Yeah.
It's my birthday next month as well.
Probably won't even be alive for that to be honest.
He wants to live anyways. It's
depressing. It's a depressing life.
It's not even about money either. It
ain't even about money at all.
That's the funniest thing about it.
Um, a big fat heart attack.
That's what I'd like on my birthday. A
big fat heart attack.
Can't type on Instagram for like 4 days. Five days.
Hopefully I drop dead this year, bro.
It's always bad around October time.
You know, no um September, October time.
I'm ready to die, bro. Like, I've got
the memories. I've lived my life. No regrets, bro. No regrets. [ __ ] depressing.
And then I was thinking, oh, I should
just hit the gym and then just leave, you know,
which is what I'm doing anyways. I hit
the gym and leave. What is to do? Yeah.
Probably see a lot of pregnant people
around December as well. probably
that's where they con that's when they
conceive a lot of people.
All of these holidays are just designed
to poke fun out of people.
Just to poke fun out of people, you know, two weeks Yeah. Two.
Yep. They do it on purpose.
They do on purpose.
But I generally do think women are evil.
What have you got to lose? There's no
life here. Life ain't worth living here.
This is why I don't do anything every
day. I just lie in bed cuz there's
nothing worth doing. Yeah.
We will never have a Valentine.
Like I say, it's a holiday just to poke
fun out at people.
Poke fun out them. And they ain't wanted by nobody,
not chosen by nobody.
You know, I wish I wish I came out like
a [ __ ] dwarf or like a Down syndrome
because at least I know I'd be
guaranteed to die in like 10 years, 15 years.
I'd be like guaranteed to die in like
10, 15 years.
No, it can't be worse, mate. It can't be worse.
Cuz if my mom had me in like a year or
another year, then I could have I could
have had like maybe a dwarf, maybe down
syndrome, maybe something. And obviously
they don't live that long. So
no, it can't be worse. This life is dead.
I want out of it. [ __ ] I want out of it ASAP.
It's a [ __ ] life.
It's a [ __ ] life being mocked.
Oh yeah, true. But you know what I mean. Yeah.
Nah, it's just mocking seeing couples, seeing [ __ ]
kids and [ __ ] I saw it today. I saw it
today. Toby uh the Toby Calvary.
Well, I couldn't stay there cuz it was
too busy, but yeah. Yeah.
The m thing is I've got money. It's not
even about money. That's That's the
funniest thing. It ain't even about money. >> Yeah.
So the person lost.
You always get mocked at the right time as well. Yeah. Oh, [ __ ]
It's a depressing life. Is it?
Depressing. Depressing. Depressing life. Yeah.
Do you think it's funny what I done to that? Um,
they don't get me down. These people do
not get me down. Nothing they do or say
has ever got me down.
It's nothing to do with them. They don't
get me down. They just they're just
self-reflecting ugly people.
We're not talking about them. These
people have never ever got me down. I
don't know why I' I have to keep
repeating myself. I used to say [ __ ]
I used to say to Lisa all the time,
"These people do not get me down. They
never have done and they never will."
So, I don't know why you think it's
them. These [ __ ] losers on YouTube.
Yeah, they're stalking. That's their
life. It's got nothing to do with that.
It's about seeing couples and [ __ ]
[ __ ] like that. It's nothing to do with them.
Because we know why they do what they do.
It's nothing to do with them.
Nothing to do with them, bro. It will
never be anything to do with them.
We already know why they do what they
do, bro. It's obvious jealousy.
So why why would they make me feel down
when they're It's obvious what they're
doing would make me feel better about myself. If anything,
cuz they spend all their life, they
waste their life away on someone that's
apparently skinn and someone that's
apparently all this. They talk about themselves. So,
but yeah. No, it's not that. It's just
like the couples and [ __ ] you know?
It's like seeing couples and
[ __ ] You know what I mean?
seeing pregnant people and whatever.
No, it was too busy.
No, it was too busy, bro. It would like
an hour wait, so I just went to the chicken shop. No.
Nothing ever gets better though. Nothing ever changes.
That's one thing for certain in this
life that we know.
That's one thing we know for sure is it
never changes life.
You're just born to be mocked.
No, there's no decent women out there.
They're all the same.
They'd rather give their bodies to
crackheads and drug dealers and [ __ ] and mock you.
It's been the same for years. Don't see
it ever changing now.
They're all the same.
It took me a lot of money and a lot of
time wasted to realize that that they
are generally all the same.
All of them are the same. Madness.
Going to take some cocoa more in a
minute, I think.
No, even women in church are the same.
No, even even women in church are the same.
That black guy in America, he used to go
to church and he was a Christian and he
said they're all the same there as well.
Nah, all women are the same.
All women are the same.
They generally are all the same.
Doesn't matter where they are, what they
look like, all the same.
Just like that [ __ ] yesterday who I
stood up, she's another [ __ ]
You even get ugly women that think
they're better than you. What has this
world come to? Eh, you've even got ugly
women that think they're better than you.
Yeah. They give their bodies to [ __ ]
crackheads and drug dealers
and abusive people.
You're very much being mocked in any
kind of westernized country.
You very must be a mock.
I wonder what how I wonder when somebody
would have killed themselves if they had
been through what I've been through. You
reckon two years ago, a year ago, two
years maybe people would have really killed themselves
or gave up a life,
probably two years ago.
I reckon they would have killed
themselves a long time ago.
I think so, bro.
There's no reason to be alive.
Yeah, I hope I die in my sleep. Anyways,
my diet's not been the best lately, so fingers crossed
this life can end once and for all.
It can it can stop once and for all.
It's either between suicide or leaving
him. You got two options. What which one
you want to do?
You want to live you want to move out of
here forever and start a life some in
another country or you do yourself in.
They're the only two options you've got.
I don't need a football win, mate. I've got money.
I've got enough money to do what I need to do.
It's not about money. Nothing. None of
it's about money.
None of it's about money at all.
Not at all. At all.
Nah, it can't be worse, mate.
Getting mock, seeing couples. Nah,
it could be better. I could be I could
be a millionaire. I mean, it depends how
you want to look at it. Well, it doesn't
matter. But it's not even about money.
It's not Nothing's about money. So like,
no, it couldn't be worse. It should be
better. It's not that it could be worse.
It should be better. You You put the
time in. You put the effort in. It
should be better.
Why do you think I don't go out drinking anymore?
cuz I can't be bothered. Waste of time.
It will never change.
Grey, it will never change.
How do you feel about that? It would never change.
It would never change, mate.
It will never change.
I'm not skin at all, matey. And the
reason I don't gamble anymore is cuz I
learned my lesson.
That's why I don't gamble. Because I
learned my lesson
to not make any more regrets in my life.
You know what I mean?
No, thank you. What's Huh?
It's just a day to poke fun at
Valentine's Day. Is just a day to poke
fun at the men that ain't wanted by no one.
Ain't it grievy?
They ain't chosen by anybody. >> Yeah.
There we go.
Better get myself a drink. That'll be my bungle.
n they're all the same in church. All
women are the same.
They're the same everywhere. Same attitude. Same.
Same look in their eye. same attitude.
You know, I didn't watch it. Why is it
greasy with these people having the same attitude?
Same attitude, eh?
Who's your money on tomorrow, Greavesy?
I bet London Taylor £1,000 that this
guy's not going to show up. So, I want
my four grand tomorrow when this guy
don't show up.
[ __ ] pound, man.
Is it depressing? I've never stayed in a
shared room. So, no,
it's actually good living with people.
I preferred living with people. introvert.
I'm not an introvert. I just give up the life. Yeah.
He's going to get [ __ ] smacked up
tomorrow if he comes out, bro. I swear
to God he is sick of this little [ __ ] Yep.
I know. I know. It's sad, isn't it? But
you would if you had experiences I have.
If you had experience as I have, you
would have gave up your life a long time ago.
I think most people would have killed
themselves to be honest. Yeah. [Music]
Something like that, mate. Something like that.
All right, I'm getting a drink. I'll be right back. that
uh I'm nowhere near 30 years old.
So yeah, I feel like my whole
I have to start a new life in another
country. I think that's my only thing otherwise
suicide there's nothing else.
I mean, you can't even go to the cinema
without being annoyed.
Even a simple cinema trip is enough to
trigger me, you know?
Really no life for anyone, mate. And
that's why I don't gamble anymore, cuz
I've learned my lesson.
Save money, save my money, leave. You know,
cuz this ain't no life for anyone in
this country, mate.
That's why I like the old house. I was
away from drama. I was in my own bubble.
Now look, [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] shite, bro. You know
It's a dead life though. It is a dead life. We
seeing couples is very very triggering.
Very very triggering. Yeah.
Sad life ain't it?
Sad sad life.
Going to watch some more Oreo man later. Yeah.
Yeah. Seems so
I don't have no connection to this
country. So when I'm gone, then that's good.
I'm gone forever and
I never have to see any [ __ ]
anymore. No, nothing. All the problems
in this country goes away.
They never have to see it again. You know,
bad it kind man. I should have found
someone a long ass time ago.
I should have found someone a long ass time ago.
You know what I mean? A long time ago,
bro. I shouldn't still be having these problems.
Yep. Man, is it how you can be
good-looking and fail?
Think about it, bro. I've been at this
for like what, four or five years?
[ __ ] how the [ __ ] can you be
good-looking and have money and fail? It
don't even make sense, bro. It don't
even make no sense.
How can you be good-looking and have
money and bail?
You know, in them four or five years, I
was never ever skin, you know, that
ever. Never. Not once. Like never.
How mad that is.
I could be skinned one day again in the
future, but I don't think so, bro.
That's what I'm saying. It's not like
you never had money.
So, I'm saying it's not like you were
skinn or you know you you you know you
were ugly or anything like that. So,
there's not really no reason for it
which makes it even worse. And obviously
you had time cuz you you never worked.
So, you know, it's not like there's
there's there's no reason for it.
You know what I'm saying?
There's no actual reason for it. You had
money, you had time,
you know, you dress good, you look
decent, whatever. There's really no
excuse for it.
But yeah, I feel like I need to start a
life somewhere else. I think
permanently like permanently somewhere else
away from everyone. I got no connections
here. I basically ain't got no family here. So
obviously it's what's best. You know
what I mean?
just doing what's best.
So, I'm 28. I'm not getting any younger.
You know, I had good experiences in this
country with the food and stuff. It's
time to move on now. So,
Bad, bad, bad, bad.
So, I need to go I need to go gym again.
I need to get that hairstyle, the bun hairstyle again.
And I need to leave, bro. ASAP.
Yeah, I might not get as much money
anymore, but I can still save, mate.
Even if it takes twice as long, I'll do
it. It say twice as long.
This ain't a This ain't a life for
anyone in this country, you know?
Then you get [ __ ] news that just
mocks you. You understand, Grezy? It's
like anything, everything in this
country is designed to mock you. You know,
it's like it's designed to mock you, this country.
It's it's a it's it's a country to poke
fun out of you.
That's what it is. You're either lucky
in this country or you're not. And
Antman wasn't and I'm not. So,
nah, you can't. I wish you [ __ ]
could. Nah. Nah, you can't. You have to start working.
If you if you got pip abroad, mate,
you'd be laughing. You went Thailand
with [ __ ] £1,100 a month, you'd be rich.
All you need is like £500 a month to
live there. Perk, you can live like a
king. £500 a month there. Now, you'd
have to start working unfortunately. But I mean,
it's better than being here, you know
what I mean? It's better than being in
this depressing country, you know?
That's the way it's got to be. That's
Yeah. But you can't live out there. No,
but you can't live out there. You can't
because it comes up on your passport and
they inform you know from your passport you can't
just can't believe all these years I
couldn't find someone bungle it's mad
anyone would think you're fat ugly and skin
and I had money as well like I still
have money it's not even like I was ever skinn
I actually had money. That's the thing.
And have money. I still have money, but
you know, like I had mad money worth.
That's the thing.
It's mad, bro. It's madness.
But you lived it. You done it. You knew
what this country was like. You failed. So,
and I also lived by myself for a very
long time as well. Um, I actually lived
by myself for a very long time.
I lived by myself. Do you not remember,
bro? I lived by myself a couple of
times. I lived by myself, then I lived
with tenants, then I went to my mom,
then I lived with the tenants. I
literally had a routine when I used to
go to the gym every day and I was living
I had my own room, bro.
I used to get rent. I used to get rent.
I was living like a king, bro. I was
living the dream. Living that [ __ ] dream, bro.
That's why I don't have £13,000
because I was living the dream, you know?
So, I mean, I was living by myself.
making money. So, at the end of the day,
there's not really no reason for it. You
know, I had a huge responsibility as well.
So, I've lived I've lived every life you
can imagine. I've lived broke. Well,
I've not been broke for a long time. I'm
still not broke, but I've lived [ __ ]
well off, independent, not independent, middle,
cuz I'd say, you know, that life I was
living is quite well off for someone my
age to be honest with you.
So, you go on it now on any Reddit, most
people can't even afford to go out and drink.
They can't even afford to go out and
drink. Most people not even go for a
drink. That's how bad this country is.
So you was living a very very had your
[ __ ] together kind of life, you know.
You really had your [ __ ] together.
I had my [ __ ] together, bro. I had money. So
there's not really no reason for it. really. So,
I don't I don't want donations. I've got
my own money. I get my own money, bro.
I'm good. I don't need money. I've got
my own money. I don't want money from no one.
I've got my own money.
I'm good, bro.
So, but I'm just saying. So, I kind of
It's kind of unbelievable really.
Used to go gym, used to live by myself.
I lived the [ __ ] good life, bro. and
you still can't get nothing. So,
but yeah, they want to try and tell
people that you will meet someone and
I'm not Why would I buy perfume and
clothes for approaches? I've given up.
I'm not interested.
I'm not interested anymore.
I've already approached about 7,000
people. I don't need I don't need
donations. I've got my own money. I got
my own after shave. I've got my own
clothes. I don't I don't need any of that [ __ ]
Approaches. I'm not approaching here.
What the [ __ ] What am I approaching here for?
Been there, done it, worn the orange and yellow t-shirt.
Because it because it will never change.
That's why I've given up. because it
will never change.
It's in my DNA, but it will never change.
And I've got perfume. I bought a new
perfume about a month ago.
Yeah, I'm not interested anymore.
Once you've met one, you've met them
all. I've got a new I've got after shave
I bought a month ago. The same on the
tenant style. Got thrown island clothes.
I got some nice clothes.
You know, I don't I don't need to go out and approach.
I've got enough money to go out approaching.
Uh Dr. D Sage, my favorite one. But we
all know how women are. They're all the
same. So why torment yourself?
If you didn't get anything worthwhile in
all them years, then you're not going to
get anything now.
So that's the facts. So,
I got Dr. Savage right there. It's been
used once cuz I don't really go out much anymore. Uh,
got some nice clothes as well. Got some Ralphies,
but there's no point.
Did you already know the result? So you
already know the result before you even
try. I mean [ __ ] god knows how many
times have we gone out and we have
tried. How many times have we gone out and tried?
How many [ __ ] times have we gone out
and we tried?
Jesus Christ. How many times in four
years have we tried, bro?
Yep. I remember that. That's what the
guy in the toilets used to say in the O'Neals.
>> Yeah, I remember that. Yeah, he used to
say that. Some guy in the O'Neals in the
toilet. He was a toilet assistant.
>> Yeah, I know. I know. The same, bro. I
used I used to go to O'Neal's all the time.
Yep. Like I've gone out probably
drinking probably more than anybody in
the world my age.
Like it's not even a joke. Literally,
That's how I know there's no hope in
this country for me.
Yeah. And you just know
some people are meant to suffer in life
and I'm one of them. So yeah.
Yeah. I got some Ammani jeans. I got
some good clothes. I still got some nice Yeah,
kind of uh
dark road. Yeah, this office save I
think it cost me £80.
Yeah, cost me 80 quid. Yeah.
I've just given up the life, bro. I was
thinking of suicide earlier.
Heard some stuff. Not going to get into
it. It's personal. So,
just another thing to mock the man
that's tried everything.
to poke fun at the man that's tried everything.
You know what I'm saying?
Poke fun out the man that's tried everything.
Just like the holiday Valentine's. It's
just a day to poke fun out of the men
that's tried everything.
You know, it's depressing, bro. You see
couples. I went out earlier. I saw
people with kids. I saw pregnant people
last week. It's depressing, bro. It's so
It's like It is It is literally like It
is mocking you.
It is literally like It is mocking you, bro.
I mean mocking you in it mocking you.
Yeah. Just to be mocked. Mocked.
That's what you get. You get mocked and laughed at.
H I've still got designer closure though.
I've still got designer clothes. Yeah.
From all that money back in the day I
won. So, I still got designer clothes
and [ __ ] but don't make a difference.
Not without sex, and neither can they.
They can't live without sex either.
Women can't live without sex, so why should we?
They can't live without sex, so why should we?
That's the way I see it.
If they can't, why should we?
Not women. They get sex all the time. Yep.
Yeah, they they have sex all the time. They do. No,
you should go and tell these women that
have sex all the time with men that they
don't need uh they don't need someone in their life.
Cliny, man. You should tell these women
that have sex with that sleep with men
all the time that they don't need
someone in their life.
Why don't you tell women that have sex
with people all the time that
they would know the struggles?
I wish Laney had me 15 years before.
I really wish she had me 15 years
before. You know,
I wish I [ __ ] wish.
You know, why did you have me in this
[ __ ] up society? Why?
Why the [ __ ] did you have me at [ __ ]
Why did you have me at [ __ ]
I wish Laney had me 15 years before. I [ __ ] wish
then we would have we wouldn't be having these problems, you know.
So, kind man, why don't you tell them
women that they don't need men?
The ones that they give their body to
all the time. Mhm.
And the women that go and I was thinking
about like they go on dates with people
to to to make them feel bad as well.
They go on dates with people to make
people feel bad about themselves.
Yeah. They go on dates to make people
feel bad about themselves.
There's a lot of
Yeah, like I I want to go to Do you know
why I want to go gym? Because I want to
I want to gain muscles. I want to be
like how I used to be before. Not I
don't need to go gym. There's nothing
wrong with me. But I I want to go to a
gym because it's a good thing to do. Go
to the gym. You know, it's a good hobby.
It's good for you. You know, you want to
look like John Cena, man. You want to
have a good body like John Cena, you
know. But I don't need to go to the gym.
That's my preference.
She said I needed to like change my hair
when there was nothing wrong with my
hair. There was nothing wrong with the
way that my body looked just like
there's nothing wrong with my body now.
And then she say it's okay for her to
give me a lecture about my appearance
when I'm better than her and I don't
even like her. But you know, this is
what I mean. This is what I'm talking
about in this country.
This is what I'm saying. This is exactly
what I mean.
That's what I'm saying, bro.
So, basically what happened was I met her. Yeah.
And she's like, "Oh, yeah. We're not
going to be an item and no, no, no, no,
no, no." Talking like she's better than
me. Saying, "Oh, no, no, no." And she's,
"Oh, you should have your hair like you
had it before and you should go gym and
go on a weight training program." But,
there's nothing wrong with me.
You're not Angelina Jolie, mate. You
don't tell me what I need to do. So,
it's okay for them to take the piss and
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Like, that's what I'm saying. And it was
done out of spite. It wasn't, you know
what I mean?
And I'm better than her. And I didn't
even like her. That's what I'm saying.
This is the whole thing about this
country. This is what I mean with these
[ __ ] women. They think they're
better than they are.
And we can't even blame simps because it
ain't the simps. There's something wrong
with them. There something is. There is, bro. So um Yeah.
He knows that.
You like my hair?
Do you like my beard?
Yeah. Thank you.
Thank you, [ __ ] Mhm.
Thank you. Come
do just use Huh?
What do you mean?
I started going out at 22 and I gave up
at 27. Well, 28. Basically,
the house thing just come at the right
time, didn't it?
It just come out the right time.
What do you mean? I don't get you.
What do you reckon the Stone Island
jumpers will look like when they've been
dry cleaned? I think they'll look
perfect. What do you think? Yeah, I
think they'll look perfect. Me
get a nice dry clean and ironed.
Be brand new again.
Uh, bail out.
Yeah, I choose bailing out. Yeah. eventually. Yeah.
The women [ __ ] is depressing.
The women [ __ ] is too depressing. Yep.
It's too depressing, bro.
Way too depressing.
Yeah. Well, not anymore.
Not anymore, matey.
Too many bad experiences. Just had a lot
Just like the last date I went on. Bad experience.
They went out with me just to try to
make me feel [ __ ] about myself. Yeah. So yeah.
Oh, mate. I will. Trust me, I will.
sick of seeing couples and pregnant
people just [ __ ] mocking you. Is it?
It's just mocking, isn't it? Mocking. Yeah.
Uh, mock you for It's mocking though,
isn't it? It's mocking you.
Do you know what made me laugh? The
Monty video to Rice and KK.
He still won't get off YouTube, will he?
Nope. Never donated my clothes.
I've got four stonies, one round rest stops.
Neither. They're both stinking.
And my dad My dad's dead.
My dad's dead as well.
Don't know if you forgot about that. My
dad's also dead.
No, I've already tried it.
There's no one for me.
No, I never grew up with my dad.
Never grew up with my dad.
My mom brought me up. So, yeah.
No, I live with my mom.
Yeah, my mom brought me up. Not my dad.
My dad visited me. Um
16 years ago and then one week later he died.
Funny how life changes, huh?
We still don't know how he actually
died. didn't come up on the death certificate. But
no, it's not about having a male
influence. I'm the way I am because of
my life experience. There's no male
influence that can tell me otherwise.
I've had men try to tell me [ __ ] But
there is no male influence cuz I know
I'm right because of my experiences. I
don't need a male influence.
I self taught myself this [ __ ] So >> yeah.
>> So yeah, that's the story basically.
No, not really. Yes.
Yeah. I'm sure he did. But
that's why I thought my mom died like
last month. I was I was panicky. That's
why I went to the house at like 5 in the
morning cuz I thought she died. I was
like, "Oh no. Laney died.
Yeah, you can ask. Was it?
Well, hopefully I'm dead before her.
Hopefully I'm dead before her.
Nah, I give up my life.
Boring. That insult thing is boring now.
That word is boring.
Incel. Boring. We need to think of a new word.
We need a new word.
>> We need a new word now, bro.
That incel thing is getting really
boring. We need We need a new word. I
think they need to make up a new word.
No. Just because I don't lick women's
asses and I speak the truth, it doesn't
mean I'm an incel.
Just cuz I don't lick women's asses.
No, that doesn't make me an incel. That makes me
uh an honest person.
What is it with you people in that word incel?
Never been spanned from Strapford
station in my life.
You'd actually call me a I'm actually
more closer to a misogynist.
I'm actually more closer to a misogynist
than an incel. So yeah,
you would actually call me a misogynist.
That's what I'd actually
be classed as.
Well, I'm allowed to rant about women,
but that would make me a misogynist.
Yeah, I rant about women because they're [ __ ]
what they do to people and stuff,
but then I'm the one who's I'm the
blame. Really, you got no one to blame
but yourself cuz you know what they're
like. You know what these women are
like. You've known what they're like for
years. These women, these nasty [ __ ]
women. So, at the end of the day, you
really got no one to blame but yourself
really by by still going out and dealing
with them. You know what they're like.
You know what they've been like for years.
these [ __ ] women. So
really, I've got no one to blame but
myself now. So
You got people in relationships being
being fathers. I feel like I never grew up.
I actually feel like I never grew up.
I feel like I never grew up, bro.
I swear like I feel like I never grew up
in all them years
despite what I done, what I tried. I
feel like I never grew up. I just became old. Yeah.
Became older. Yeah.
I feel like I never grew up.
Like these people have like
some people have went on to have
families and stuff.
I feel like I never grew up, you know.
I've got more life experience than you
will ever have. Sunshine sunshine.
Back to Lia. [ __ ]
I've got more life experience than you
would ever have.
Believe you me.
But you know what women are like. So you
know you got no one to blame but yourself. Really.
If you go out now, you got no one to
blame but yourself.
Cuz you know what women are like. You
know what they've been like for years.
[ __ ] trying to make people feel bad
about themselves. You know what they're
like. You know what they're like,
you know. It's not like you don't know.
Stop blaming other people. You know what
they're like. You know these women are
all the same.
And then when you actually put it like
that, it's like, "Oh shit." Yeah. You
know what these women are like, mate.
These can'ty women.
It's so bad. I used to even hate it when
my family was in relationships,
which sounds sickening and stuff
cuz obviously it's not like that. But it's like
it's it's that it sounds weird, but like
it's not until later, man. It's not
until the evening.
It's not till evening time, but
you need to start a new life somewhere.
That's what you need to do.
Jealousy. Nah, I'm not jealous of no one.
Why would I be jealous of my family? I'm
not jealous of anyone that's got more
money than me, less money than me. I'm
not jealous for anyone. It's more you're
being mocked. It's not being called
jealousy. It's being called mocked. And
why do you keep coming on my channel as
well? You little law J simp. I'm not
jealous of anyone.
It's just you being mocked. That's all
it is. It's just you being mocked. Yeah.
But obviously I had it better than them
in other ways as well. I didn't have to
work for [ __ ] years.
I was making more money than both of them combined.
And they were always struggling with
money. See, I never had to struggle with
money for 4 years or anything.
And I'm still not struggling now.
There's nothing to be positive about.
Where is this guys?
There's nothing to be positive about, mate.
Yeah, I'm young. And what? Nothing's
going to change just cuz I'm young.
You'll still get mocked by women. You'll
still get took the piss out of.
The only way this is going to change is
if you change
and you and you start a life somewhere else.
It's having to come to them extremes now.
That's madness, bro.
That's why I don't go out anymore.
But at least I I go to going out drinking stage. Uh
so yeah, I should have to start a life
somewhere else though. I should find
someone here. I should have found You know,
you should have found someone here years ago.
You know what I mean? Madness.
I already had chicken. I I already had chicken earlier.
My body count should be about 100
with the way my looks were and amount of
money I [ __ ] had and what I used to
wear. My my body count should be [ __ ]
100, bro. My body count should be 100 excluding escorts. [ __ ]
Yeah. You can't be settled because you
can't find someone.
No one's interested in this country. No,
I must. But no, because I went around
the country [ __ ] approaching people,
so I should have had a higher body count.
Think about it, Timothy. Yeah,
think about it like this, bro.
The only good thing about my life, bro,
is I never had to work for four years,
and I was making three grand a month for not working.
So I didn't have to ever worry about
money, you know, the going out drinking and [ __ ]
Oh, bro, it's just funny, isn't it? Like
I think God felt sorry for me because he
knew what I was in for.
That's why he let me have the house.
That's why God gave me that house with
the money because he knew what I was in for.
It's like he setting me up to fail.
You know what I mean, Grezy? It's like
they were setting me up to fail. But
then he was giving me a bit of clues now and then.
Leave the country. Leave the country.
And I didn't listen with them years ago.
It's like they
It's like God set me up to fail in a way
if you think about it, you know.
God set me up to fail. He gave me that
house knowing it would make me be a fool
to do things. Then when I do things, I
got [ __ ] over. Madness.
I'm old now, bro. old.
How would have I afforded to going out
drinking all of them years without the house? Grezy,
you wouldn't. You would be [ __ ]
I I stopped going out drinking about
probably like seven months ago. Six,
or six, seven months ago. I um
I calmed it down a lot
about 6 months ago, I think. Yeah,
cuz I'd rather just chill in and have
people cook for me.
Yeah, for four years
traveled up and down the country, [ __ ]
escorts, went to nice restaurants, been abroad,
and now I'm done with it going out
drinking. Now the money stopped.
So it come just at the perfect time, is it?
That's actually mad, you know, when you
think about it. Yeah, basically.
No, but I was done. No, but I'm not
living that life anymore cuz I've
already had that life
and making money is impossible.
But you know, no, because I've already
had that life
and it's impossible to make money as
well. That's another thing.
Well, you know what I mean? Like fast
money and that.
Nah, bro. I'm good.
I still haven't started it yet cuz I I
don't need to do it. I've got money so I
don't need to do it yet.
But who knows in the future. So yeah,
I don't have any disabilities. I'm not
disabled like you.
I don't come on YouTube calling people I
don't know like what you do.
No, we're not all disabled like you.
We're not disabled like you and LJ, unfortunately.
Oh, [ __ ] me.
Hey, listen. Just go back to LJ's, you sloppy [ __ ]
Just go back to LJ's and worry about
your own life, you sad bastard.
I love the fact that you come on here
and you call people skin and you don't
know what people have.
That's what makes me die. You don't know
what people have and you talk like you do.
That's the thing that makes me die. That
makes me die, bro. That's [ __ ]
hilarious. You don't know what people
have and you talk like you do.
That's the funny thing. You don't know
what people have. It's funny.
Yeah. I Okay, bro. You don't know what I
have. Cuz if you knew what I had, you
you would be calling me skin.
Greasy lives off £1,200 a month. Don't you, Grezy?
Greavvesy lives off £1,200 a month.
Don't you grieve.
I never said I couldn't go out because I
lost on the football. I never ever said
that. I could go out every week if I wanted to.
Yeah. I don't have rent. I don't have
nothing. I don't have rent. I don't have
I only got Franklin.
I must him. So
I never said I can't go out. I lost my I
never said that.
Never said that.
I said it made me depressed now. I
didn't want to go out.
I don't want to go out. I don't want to
go out again.
Bro, I don't go out drinking much anymore.
I don't go out much anymore. What the [ __ ]
I don't [ __ ] go out drinking much anymore.
And the reason why I'm not going out
this month is cuz I need to save money.
I'd rather build my money up. And I used
to do the same thing as well when I had
the house. Rey, even when I had the
house, I'd rather I'd rather build my money up, you know.
Yeah, that's what people do. If you want
to save, that's what people do.
Well, I actually spend about £80 a week, but yeah,
I need to save money, bro. I'd rather
build my money up rather than waste it.
Well, I don't have any plans what I'm
doing except going to Thailand. But I
need to save money, matey.
I'm not showing you nothing.
Why am I Why don't I show you my bank
account? Cuz I'm not showing you nothing.
So you can jog on. Yeah,
I don't have all this money. I'm just
not skin like you people. I'm not just
I'm just not skin like you and Lar a
being on £1,200 a month. Well, no it
won't because most people that work are
not even left with £1,200 a month off
the bills. See what a lot of these
people don't understand, Greavvesy.
Yeah. It's cuz they're so ignorant is
that you know when you say that you get
£1,200 a month, right? That's literally
all yours. You don't have to pay
anything out of that. These people that
work are not left with £1,200 disposable
money each month. They're [ __ ] so
stupid. These people are so stupid.
They're very, very stupid. They don't
understand anything, do they?
Like, bro, there is not many people,
bro. Let me tell you this. Obviously,
there probably is some people. There is
not many people in London. I don't know
about anywhere else. I don't know about
anyone else, but there's not many people
in London, bro, that's left with £1,200
off the bills.
Believe that, bro. Believe you me. There
is not many people after rent that's and
and [ __ ] that they pay out for is left with £1,200.
They're not, mate. Trust me.
Yeah, they're not. There's no way there
is because you I I've gone on things and
I've looked at what people wrote and
I've scrolled down and Yeah.
So yeah, I've never I've never had a job
and no bills. Yeah, mate. I had a house.
I had my own responsibility. You [ __ ]
People don't save. So basically,
people don't save.
I mean, I saved £500 last month, but I
went out a couple of times.
But in London, people are not left with
£1,200 a month, mate. Trust me, these
these tenants, right, that I used to
live with, obviously they they had a bit
less than most people, but they had
nothing. Every single month they'd get paid about
7800 pound. Yeah.
And they would have nothing, bro.
Nothing. Sometimes they have like £80 to
last them a month.
So if you've got like
Yeah. Like you got,200 pound disposable
money, bro. That's good, you know.
Yeah, it's expensive, bro.
It is expensive.
There's not a lot of people with £1,200 disposable.
Nope. They were
working in security actually. So, yeah.
But yeah, you need to [ __ ] I don't know, bro.
I don't know. I had that house for
years, so I never knew the struggles.
So, and I still don't know the struggle
now cuz I'm smart with money. So, yeah.
You need to [ __ ]
And then you read up about people as
well. And then a lot of people say they
can't go out drinking anymore cuz they
can't afford it.
I'm surprised most of these pubs ain't
gone bust to be honest
cuz people just can't afford it. People
are saying now how they can't afford it
and no no no no no
they can't afford it. So they say,
"Yeah, you save £500." Greasy
a month. 600 a month.
But don't forget I won some football
bats as well. So I'm all right, bro. 12.
Yeah. So if you got £1,200 disposable money,
then you're laughing. Really?
which most people in London at work does
not have 1,200 pound
spare. No way. Some people might do but
most people don't. Bye-bye. So, yeah.
Yeah, I've got about 1,500 lb disposable.
I was careful in it, bro. I was very, very careful
with what I done.
I mean, yeah, I could go out every week,
but what's the point? What is the actual
point? There is no point.
I need to save money. I need to go to
the gym. I need to leave.
You understand, bro?
And I need to leave,
matey. I can't be going out every week
getting haircuts and [ __ ] wasting money.
£1,500. What? Without bills? It will
last [ __ ] more than a month.
It will last more than a month, matey.
It will [ __ ] last more than a month.
I tell you that much. Oh yeah.
So yeah, I just need to basically stack
money up. That's what I'm basically doing. So
cuz you're not going to you're not going
to progress in this country. You're
never going to progress in this country.
You know what I'm saying? So um
just blocked. Yeah.
Yeah, she's [ __ ] blocked, man. The [ __ ]
save 600 pound a month.
That's funny, bro.
That is funny, mate. Yeah.
Yeah, I need to build my finances up, bro. Proper. Like,
you know what I mean? So,
that's just it, is it? That's why I
don't Gab anymore, bro.
You couldn't [ __ ] kill me to put 150
in them machines anymore.
You couldn't kill me to do that, bro.
You couldn't. You literally couldn't.
I was tempted to gamble 100 today, but I
never Yeah, I lost 100 last week. Yeah.
So, yeah. But that was roulette. That
was online roulette though. That's a bit different.
And I want a football bet too. So
yeah, I need to start stacking money up, bro.
Yeah, I could go out every week. Yeah, I
could go out drinking every week, but
there's no point, bro. I need to do
other things in my life now. You know, I
need to start a new life somewhere else, you know. So,
I lost 100 pound on roulette. Yeah.
[ __ ] hell, man.
Oh, [ __ ] me.
Yeah, I lost £100.
I could have had a night out with that £100. [ __ ] it.
Yep. Could have had a night out with
that [ __ ] 100 quid.
But I don't give a [ __ ] I'll try to win
like 20 grand.
I try to win like 20k, bro. Hello. [ __ ] me.
Do you remember the casino day, Steven Howard?
Oh, you can kiss goodbye to them, matey.
Oh, you can kiss goodbye to them.
Kiss goodbye to them days, matey. travel.
I would travel with it
and maybe try to start some sort of business
if I could. Yeah.
traveling and tried to start some sort of business.
I won 120 grand. Yeah.
Yeah, just stacking up one now.
Going to try and stack up some money. Yeah.
Yeah. It's good, bro. It's good to have
them good days.
At least I was able to travel and [ __ ]
[ __ ] and [ __ ]
Obviously, I can't get in a
relationship. I can't have kids. So I
mean that paid for it really in it.
I know it's difficult, bro. I know it's difficult.
Of course it's difficult.
But you know even with like Uber Yeah.
If you don't Uber in like New York,
they're they want like $500 a day, bro.
They get paid mad money over there.
I was thinking of [ __ ] getting my
bike and bringing it over there and
doing it there. Buy a bike, but they ban
my Uber account,
just rent a [ __ ] condo for a month,
go over there with a bike
or buy a bike, and then just [ __ ]
[ __ ] work over there, bro. on like
the Uber thing is it?
They make a lot more bro over there than
they do here.
Even in Boston and [ __ ]
New York, Boston. [ __ ]
Move to Yam Yam land. No thanks.
Why am I going to move to yum yum land? Nah, [ __ ] that. You know,
at least I've got some money left in it.
At least I've got At least I had a lucky
escape with the house in it.
I don't see my family often. Well, I see
my sister and I see my mom. I don't see
my other sister. Well, I saw my other
sister the other day. First time in like a year.
I kind of got a lucky escape with the
house in there, bro. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, but you still got to be single.
But you're still going to be single even
if you move that
I got all them designer clothes and the
traveling and the dates and that.
Yeah, it's madness, isn't it?
Do you remember that last date I went on
with that Italian woman?
You went out with me to try to make me
feel bad about myself. Remember
wants to hold hands but not kiss.
[ __ ] I walk. [Music]
Do you remember that last date I went on?
Tim John, did you remember that last
date I went on?
Why do these women even go on dates with
you if they're not going to even want to
date you? I don't get it. Why they waste
their time and why they waste yours?
Like, bro, honestly, I don't get it.
No, no, no. There was one before, uh,
bro. There was one four months ago, you know.
No, no, no, no. The one before, the Italian one.
There was someone I went on a date with
months ago, right? And we was holding
hands, drinking wine. I tried to kiss
her. She weren't having none of it.
They go on these dates to try to make
people feel bad about themselves. Yeah.
You can be good-looking and have money
and you still get took the piss out of.
And then the other one
who was holding hands, I tried to kiss
her. She didn't want to kiss.
Uh well, yeah. And a lot of people on
dates kiss people.
I mean, yeah, but they also kiss people as well.
I hate America. I hate [ __ ] American.
I hate women. I generally generally hate
all of them, bro.
I generally generally do.
I really do.
Yeah. But bro, you don't understand that
like back in the day I had a lot of
money compared to them. That's what
you're not understanding is that I had a
lot of money compared to them.
I obviously I wasn't considered rich,
but I would say you was considered
I don't know what you'd be considered
because you wasn't average and I
wouldn't say you was well off, but
I don't know what you you had loads and
loads and loads of loads of money, bro.
So, at the end of the day, that never
made a difference. That never made a
That never made a difference at all. So,
No, I know. But I'm just saying I'm
using it as an example. I'm using it as
an example. Like even when you have
loads of money, you're still not going
to meet anyone. Yeah, I know. I know. I know. Obviously,
it's not about that anyways cuz even if
you I was just saying even when you have
loads of money, you're still not going
to find someone. So,
that's what that's the point I'm trying
to make to that's the try that's the
point I'm trying to make, mate, is that
even if you have money and you got your
[ __ ] together, it makes no difference.
That's what I'm trying to say to you.
And the reason why that 19year-old kept
coming back is cuz bro, she probably
thought I was rich.
That's why she kept coming back for so long.
She thought I was rich, bro. That's why
she kept coming back to me. Think about
it. Someone that's just 18, they're
seeing someone with all this money, bro.
She must have thought I was rich. And
she's not been shown that by anyone
else. That's why she used to come back.
But then she turned out to be a [ __ ] in the end.
She turned out to be a [ __ ] in the end.
So Oh my god. Is that rain?
Yeah, she turned out to be a [ __ ] in the end.
I used to give her £50. She used to just
give me a [ __ ] Simple.
Then I couldn't deal with her in the end. So
yeah, they're [ __ ]
I hate him.
No, it's just a wind. I thought it was a
rain. Sounded similar to the wind.
Yep. No, no condom. And I used to come
in her mouth and she used to swallow it.
I remember one time, bro, she was being
a [ __ ] I'll tell you the story, right?
I remember, right? I met her and um
play around. She gave me a [ __ ]
before when I [ __ ] her. And I met her
again. I think it must have been I think
it might have been March. I think it
might have been February or March. Used
to be February or March.
Um and uh she was being a [ __ ] There
was one day she was being a proper [ __ ]
Like she said, "Oh, I only give a
[ __ ] if I'm with the person or no,
no, no, no, no." And she come around the
house where the tenants were like in the
room and that and uh no, it's a different one.
And she was um she said um
she said uh um
that she wasn't going to do anything in
it and I said oh I had some money on the
side so I offered her money and she was
like oh um yeah I'm not a prostitute but
how much? And I said oh I'll give you
£50. So I thought that was a fair deal
because she done it about three times
after that. But I couldn't deal with her
attitude anymore. She turned more and
more westernized as she was getting
older. Started calling me mate. I was
like, "I'm not your mate. Stop calling
me your mate." I don't know what it is
with these westernized women. They like
calling people mate more than actual
men. I'm not your [ __ ] mate. I don't
know how many times I've said that. And
she was just being a [ __ ] She was
becoming more and more entitled. Like
when I first met her, she was all right,
you know, but then over time she just
become a [ __ ]
So yeah, I used to just give her 50 and
she used to just suck my dick. I came in
her mouth. She swallowed it. So I
thought that was cheap. So
yeah, she's a common. Yeah, they that's
what I'm saying. They're all the same.
All these women are the same cuz I've
spoke to like se six w six women and
they've all said the same thing. mate
this, mate that. They're all the same.
That's what I'm saying. They're all the same.
No, she didn't friend zone me. It was
always purely transactional. I give her
40,50, she starts my dick.
That's it. It was always that. So, we
weren't even friends. We kissed and
every We used to kiss and everything.
Nah, I couldn't deal with her attitude, mate.
Nah, I couldn't deal with her attitude.
She'll come back.
No, she wasn't a foreigner. She was from England.
She just had Russian in her.
And she used to make me like wash my
dick before sucking it.
She was a proper proper proper [ __ ]
Yep. I did. I [ __ ] her in in my mom's gaff
to work up the whole neighbors. Long
story, but yeah,
even the girl tenant I had was a [ __ ]
Even that girl tenant I had, she was a
[ __ ] as well. proper [ __ ] So,
she thought she was all right.
No, I don't want I don't want them, bro.
I don't want them. It's just the whole I
don't even want them. It's just a
they um it's just mocking. It's mocking.
I've got some news today. I'm not going
to tell you because it's personal, but
it's just mocking. It's not even that
you want these women. It's just mocking
because obviously I've been through so
much [ __ ] with them. Nope.
I'm not giving her nothing. No. So yeah.
>> No, I didn't like her attitude.
You get triggered when you see pregnant
people, Timothy. I get triggered when I
see pregnant people.
It used to annoy me when I like my when
my sisters had kids as well. When I'd
hear about it,
it used to annoy me.
used to annoy me. It did.
Which sounds weird to you?
£50 for a takeaway. I've never spent £50
on a takeaway. Bit bit of an exaggeration.
She had a few. Yeah. And it used to
trigger me. It used to be a trigger.
I remember before, right, that um
my sister was met this guy.
She only had one person before and she's
she met this guy and stuff and that I
remember that being a trigger
because I saw as I like you can go up
and down the country, you can't find
anyone. You can't even get laid and then
your sister can just go and and and just
get someone else and get sex and then
the other guy gets sex. It would just
[ __ ] with my head.
That's why I feel like I never grew up.
You know what I mean?
I hate women, bro.
I really do hate women.
I don't think you understand my hatred
towards them, you know, which is
understandable because of your
experiences with them. Obviously,
whatever someone says, it doesn't
matter, you know. Yeah.
Wouldn't that annoy you? Like if your
sister's had like a few kids and stuff
and then you're still single and you
can't even get laid and that wouldn't
that annoy you?
Yeah, that is annoying.
That's horrible, bro. Horrible.
It just goes to show that there's women
out there giving people the their [ __ ]
giving people the goods.
Obviously, you don't want your [ __ ]
sister. Obviously, bro, like it's not
we're not talking about that. But it's
still indirectly the same thing. You
know what I'm saying?
It's horrible, bro. Really, really bad.
It's really bad.
It's really really bad.
Yeah, I used to hate it, bro.
depressing. It's depressing hearing it.
I used to see it on Instagram as well.
And it would always get you at the right time.
It always get you at the right time
where you think, "Oh, uh, yeah, let's uh
let's let's let's do something. Let's go
gym. Let's move on with our life." And
then, "Oh, your favorite YouTuber's had
a kid. Oh, this person's had a kid. Oh,
this person's having a kid.
So, it's like it's it's it's torment. It's torture.
And it's always going to be like that in this country.
And no, she's not. So, yeah.
How would you feel, Timothy? How would you feel?
Even though you don't like your sisters
and that obviously bro but it's depressing
like you feel people you know you know
people get happy and stuff and you know
but then and it's not even like you're
jealous because you're not jealous it's
just it's just like it's mocking you.
Does that make sense? It's like people
think it's depressing. You're jealous,
but you're not jealous. You're You're being mocked.
That's what you're being. You're being mocked.
You're being laughed at.
Do you understand? Like you're actually
being laughed at. You're being mocked.
But at the same time, you're obviously
not jealous. Obviously, I'm not jealous
of anyone, but you know, you are being
mocked. You are being tormented.
which is why I don't really like going
out anymore cuz of the the this problem, you know.
Trust me, you wouldn't want sisters.
It's not nice. It ain't nice, bro. Trust me.
I've got two sisters. I don't have any
brothers. My brother was a half brother
who I did who I saw once. He's like a
half brother and he was basically just
didn't even count anyways. So I I don't
have any I only have sisters, you see.
But even if I had brothers, I'd still
feel the same.
It's depressing, bro. It actually is.
And it always gets you at the right time.
Right time. It's like it knows, you know.
It feels like the whole world is against
you, bro. It actually does.
There's nothing anyone can say or
anything can actually anyone can say
anyone can do bro is what it is.
You know what I mean? But yeah, it's depressing.
Why would Why would it make you feel
good? Why wouldn't it make you feel
Basically, someone people some people
are just meant to suffer in life, bro. That's it.
Some people are just meant to suffer.
That's just the way it is, you know?
I don't feel like I could ever deal with another rejection.
That's the honest truth. God's honest
truth why I don't ever go out anymore.
I don't think I could deal with it. I
think it'll drive me well over the edge. [Music]
This is far that goes. Nah.
Why wouldn't it make you feel good
hearing about people having kids and [ __ ]
Let me see.
Why would it make you feel good?
I just see it. Yeah. What the [ __ ]
Yeah. And the fact other people are
having sex as well.
Isn't that right, Timothy?
And the fact that other people are
having sex as well. And it feels like
you're being mocked.
It feels like you're generally generally being mocked.
Yeah. Yeah, I see it. I see it.
Oh, so that's why they call me ugly.
Self projection, huh? Yeah, but still.
But obviously because I've got sisters,
I can tell you how easy it is for them
and how hard it is for me.
That's probably what never helped in
life as well, you know.
My life is [ __ ] bro.
You know what I mean?
And would you believe I've met more
women than anyone in the world?
That's the sad part about it.
See, if you look at that black guy in
America that's 36 that moans, he's never
tried anything. I've tried everything.
I've tried everything, bro. That's the
[ __ ] up That's the most [ __ ] up
thing about it.
Cuz he never really knew cuz he never
ever tried. Whereas I've tried. So,
nope, not yet.
I'm good, bro.
So, yeah, the only option is giving up in life.
Seeing couples is depressing.
Seeing couples is depressing in it.
Seeing couples is depressing. Uh Timmy John Eldridge.
I probably won't go I go to bed at about
7 in the morning. Me
I go about 7 in the morning. I eat once
a day and I go about at 7:00 in the morning. Yeah.
No word of a lie. About 7 in the morning, bro.
I'm very ill.
with my diet and [ __ ] Yeah.
Look at that beard. The [ __ ] is that? Jeez.
I've been through it all with these women, mate. [ __ ] women.
Yeah, now I need to start a new YouTube
channel. Put my pros up.
I just spend all day on Reddit. Yeah.
The only one I speak to is this woman from Finland sometimes.
I said to her, "Hi, I was thinking when
I come to Finland, I take you on a date.
We could go to a steakhouse and I could
take you to get your nails done. It
would be so cute. you could teach me
some Finnish, too. She's like, "Oh,
well, that sounds really nice. Finish is
so difficult that I would be surprised
if you even learned anything.
I know I'm crazy in it. So yeah,
so many women's numbers I've got,
but they're just not interested in this country, Timothy.
They're just not interested in this country.
Like what Ant-Man said.
Good thing though is I made loads of
loads of friends, you know, going out
drinking. I didn't make a load of
friends and stuff. Good.
Nope. And even if I did, they wouldn't be interested
cuz none of them are interested in this country.
Who is that?
I had a tenant before. I said to her,
"Why don't you give me a [ __ ] instead
of paying the rent?" She was a tenant, right?
I don't think I ever told my mom this. I
told her says that the rent was like 350
a month she used to pay
and she was like, "No." I said, "If you
give me a [ __ ] I won't charge you
for the rent." Obviously, I was her landlord.
So yeah, but then she'll suck a black
guy's dick for free.
Remember that one, Mr. B? This country
is designed to just
poke fun out of you.
That's what it is. No, she weren't even
my type. I just asked her cuz why not in
it? I didn't need a £350.
I had other tenants. So
yeah, it's just a way to to poke fun out of people.
But no, she said she said uh she said no.
All the tenants couldn't believe it.
They said, "Oh, you're better looking
than that. You're better looking than
them guy." Cuz the black guys used to
come around, Mr. B. The black guys used
to come around. We used to hear them
[ __ ] bro. I remember one Oh, bro. I
remember one day. Yeah.
They kept us up all night, mate. They
literally, bro, I woke up about 4:00 in
the morning. Yeah.
4:00 in the morning.
And there was a black guy. They were
talking. And bro, they woke us up at 4.
They woke They woke the whole house up.
And I didn't wake up suddenly cuz they
weren't shouting. But they were talking.
They were talking all day, all the morning. Bro,
it was funny. It was funny, but it was
annoying at the same time.
No, you could hear it. I was above them. But yeah,
it's just the [ __ ] I've dealt with with
these [ __ ] in this country. I'm
surprised I I haven't killed someone.
I'm surprised I haven't killed someone.
I'm really surprised, bro.
Yeah, she's from Italy.
Yeah, she weren't even good-looking or
anything, but it's still the point.
Like, it's just another dig, isn't it?
It's just another poke.
She said no and asked the other tenants.
They just said no, bro. What the [ __ ] Uh
yeah, she did. Yeah. madness.
Yeah, I told the other tenants they
couldn't believe it. They was like,
"What? She turned down 350? You're good
looking and all of the guys that she
gets with are ugly?"
That's what That's what they said.
Yeah, that's what they said.
Yeah, that's what they they couldn't
believe it. They're like, "What?"
They laughed, but I was like, "I've
actually got a video where one of the
tenants asked her for sex for money."
I've actually got it recorded.
Nah, I wouldn't have, mate.
But yeah, that's another dig.
I wouldn't, mate. I've spent I paid 250
for a [ __ ] before,
mate. I used to be made of money, mate.
I wouldn't have cared about 350 quid.
Trust me, mate. I wouldn't It's just
somebody not paying you rent for the month.
Trust me, it's just somebody not paying
me rent for the month. I wouldn't have
cared. Believe you me.
But it's just another dig someone.
Yeah. 250 no condom. Yeah. All it was is
somebody not paying rent for the month.
I wouldn't regret that. I was getting
other [ __ ] people paying me rent.
So um £100. No. I I said to him, "I'll
give you £100 if you go in and you offer
her money for sex." And he did it.
Oh, we had some jokes in that house. Yeah,
fair play to the black guys. They get
what they want. Can't blame him.
It wasn't £300. It was 250. Yeah, that's
what I'm talking about.
Yeah, I did pay him. Yeah. £100.
Yeah, I paid him £100.
It's just a way to poke fun out of people, you know.
I took her to Nando as well and she
[ __ ] me over. Yeah, I took her to
Nando. She shout she shout on me as well.
So what I have what I would advise my um
nephews my nephew when he gets a bit old
and he can understand I'm going to say
whatever you do in life son you be a
[ __ ] You be a [ __ ] to women. You be a
[ __ ] to people because God rewards bad
behavior. You don't want to end up like
me. You know, cuz this is all partly for
being a good person. You need to be a
[ __ ] That's what I'm going to say to
him when he's old enough to understand
maybe 2 years. I'll say to him that you
don't want to end up like me. You want
to be a nasty bastard to anyone you
meet. God will reward you. Trust me.
Yeah, I done it. Yeah, bro. I took her
to Nando cuz I was bored and I wanted to
go with somebody. And I took I took a
tenant to Nando as well and he was a guy.
So I used to do a lot of them [ __ ] for
Yeah. It wasn't cuz I was trying to [ __ ]
her. I just said that to her cuz I was [ __ ] horny.
She was a [ __ ] So
but you live and you learn, you know, to
be a nasty bastard. See, I wish I was a
bully. If I was a bully, God would have
rewarded me, you know.
Yeah. I wish I was a nasty bully, you know.
Bob, if I was black, they [ __ ] you on
the first date if you're black.
Good on these black guys, bro. They get
what they want. Yeah.
And she still said, "No, that's a madness."
Three different ones.
Three different black guys.
Yeah. About three.
But you should also have love for your
own people as well.
You should always You should also have
love for your own people.
People can get with who they want, but
they should have love for their own people.
It's just another dig up me.
Yeah, it was just another dig at me.
It's like what? Uh, I'm not a Caucasian
lad. Well, I think you find I am because
I'm only caught a Turkish. So, I mean,
I'm very much Caucasian.
It's like what Antman said. He said when
I was when I was when I was going up and
down the country,
um, only like two of them.
He was telling me that he was crying.
The tenant was telling me the other
tenant was quiet was crying. I said, "He was crying?"
Yeah. He told me he was crying. And I
said, "What the fuck?" He was crying. I
don't think I cried.
No, I didn't cry. I just realized I
would have been I'm completely [ __ ]
But uh I didn't cry. I say crying. I
[ __ ] lost money. Look how much
[ __ ] money I've lost every month.
But he was crying because the house got
took Look at [ __ ] Look at me, bro.
You don't I wasn't crying.
I almost cried today cuz it's depressing
hearing what I heard.
Yeah, it was depressing hearing what I
heard. But [ __ ] I didn't cry over the house.
Well, yeah, cuz they repossessed the
house. Well, she was in Italy. She was
in Italy, so there was a complete
different story there.
Basically, um, one of the tenants told
her and I was going to keep taking rent
off of her every month. And I took her
stuff and I was planning to like give it
to her when she come back and not not
not tell her. So, I was obviously going
to get that £350 Yeah.
Yeah. Well, think of the the amount of
money I've lost on that house.
You don't see me crying, bro.
Look at the amount of money I've lost on
that house, bro. So,
we're all [ __ ] if you think about it.
Well, not [ __ ] but you know what I
mean. Everyone got affected by it. Not you.
I don't know. Ask yourself cuz you're
alone in your skin. Bye-bye.
But um I put it in my mom's
and I sent it to her and then she
started being a [ __ ] saying I I owe her
150 and that and
Yeah. Yeah. They all ended up on the streets.
I shouldn't even be laughing at it cuz I
lost money on the house.
I don't even know why I'm laughing cuz
I've lost money on the [ __ ] house. Nah, nah.
Yeah, I did give them notice. Obviously,
I wish I never gave them notice though.
Yeah, I would have gave her stuff, but obviously
I wish I never gave them notice now.
Imagine the baiffs just turning up. Mhm. [ __ ] hell.
That is mad. Nah, I didn't I didn't
really like the way she looked,
but a [ __ ] is a [ __ ] you know,
they didn't drink because they were
Muslims, but we had barbecues and stuff.
Yeah, they would have had a shock.
But no, we had barbecues and stuff, but
so I lost out on that. Then the money.
Now I'm here and now I'm dealing with drama.
Well, it wasn't just the money either.
It's not just about the money.
So, but you know, it's
she was Italian, but the rest of them were Muslims. Yeah.
[ __ ] knows. [ __ ] knows, mate. I don't know.
Yep. Curries, biranis, the lot, mate. Yeah,
he was crying.
Uh, yeah. Not anymore.
Nope. I only speak to two of them.
Yeah. After losing the house, I didn't
really feel like there was a reason to keep living
cuz I lost the food. The house was good.
the brothel nearby, lost the money from
the house. Like, but then I then
realized that it's not even about that.
It's just the whole women thing. Like, I
have enough money now. Like, I've got
money. It's not a problem. But it's
still not the It's the whole women thing.
I'm not saying where I live and how what
happened and that, but yeah.
But yeah, it was [ __ ]
So I feel like I went forwards and I
went backwards again.
It's not bad.
It's not good at all, man.
It's always the point of actually living
to hear about other people in
relationships and other people having
sex and other people having kids. Nah.
Yeah. And it's going to be harder to
afford the Bruffles now as well cuz I'm
on less money. Madness.
You'll meet someone when they least when
you least expect it, they say. Nah.
No, I don't know what that is.
But they tell me that I'm going to meet somebody eventually.
I'll meet someone eventually, they say.
They shall meet someone eventually, Timothy.
28 years and counting.
28 years and counted. Mad.
No. Next month.
28. Next month.
I don't know, bro. I don't know what I would do.
Well, I should probably just move away
from my family.
I was away from them for so long as
well. So, anyway, so
It could be worse, but it should be better.
No, I don't meet up with my friends anymore. I'm isolated. No.
Yeah, I don't think I'm going to get past it.
Nope. I've never seen that snake again.
Yeah, my Christmas was [ __ ] I got my
phone robbed. Well, actually, that was last year.
So yeah, that's why I don't have anxiety
because I know I've been through so much
mad [ __ ] It's impossible to now.
No, it's not looking good.
It ain't looking good at all.
No, it's not looking good at all at all. Yeah, women
can have sex all the time. Is that mad, Timothy?
Valentine's Day is going to be the worst.
It's not even that far away. Another
lonely Valentine's Day.
for the 28th year.
Shocker, right? Shocker.
Valentine's Day is a is a holiday to mock men,
to poke fun out of men that ain't wanted
by no one.
Yeah. February is not far away.
It's to mock. It's to mock men that
ain't wanted by no one.
Yes. To mock fun out of um
2026 ain't going to be much different.
Every year is the same.
Nope. Not this year. Never.
Last year, sorry.
Hearing people having kids and [ __ ]
Very depressing. Very, very depressing.
No, I don't need a makeover. I need to die.
I've looked Max millions of times and
it's made no difference. Used to go gym,
wear designer clothes.
Really? Why is that?
What the [ __ ] Why is that?
Why? Why did that happen, bro? Oh, [ __ ]
I had a roster this burger for years.
I don't need a makeover. I've looked
smack him many times and it's made no difference.
Makes no difference whatsoever. What? Um, no thanks. Nah.
Nah, I'm not getting on with nothing, bro.
Hopefully, I die in my sleep.
It will never change. Things will never
change in this country.
Things will never change. This year was
[ __ ] Last year was [ __ ]
The year before that was [ __ ] Every
year's been [ __ ] Time wasting women
getting took the piss out of.
I doubt it.
I doubt it, mate. Pigs might fly. Nah.
It will never change.
No more approaches. Nope.
I haven't watched that Billy Moore for
ages. I need to catch up on his videos.
I didn't know he was in London.
Pretty much. Yeah,
I shouldn't even have to [ __ ] go Thailand.
I shouldn't even have to go to Thailand.
I should find be able to find someone in
my own country.
Hopefully I drop dead in my sleep today.
I can't wait.
The only thing to good The only thing
that's good to look forward to in this
life is that this life ain't forever.
The food I I doubt. You doubt I can
handle it. Yeah, I have vending to lose
all the time, mate.
I'm pretty sure I can handle spice. Yeah.
Why are some of these contacts That's weird.
Oh, [ __ ] Yeah,
that's why I That's strange.
One second, bro. Please hold on. Um
What is it? The USA today.
USA is he
while I'll always be in the same
position for women with women forever.
I'll always be in the same position with women forever.
That's for sure.
That is madness.
One second. What?
Yeah, it's sad, isn't it?
Right, let me make a new YouTube channel now. Anyways, Come on. [ __ ] Virgin. Oh, freak.
in the bed.
You'll be you'll be missing that if I'm
[ __ ] when I'm [ __ ] dead, mate.
Won't you, mate?
You'll be [ __ ] missing that, won't you, mate?
If I'm [ __ ] dead,
you [ __ ] kid in the bed. You'll be
missing that, won't you? [ __ ] magnam.
No one can say that me
skin in the bed sit with no money.
Who is that?
When you going to lose it?
all over you.
>> Nah, I'm good, mate.
Nah, I'm all right, lad. Who's that?
Nah, I'm good. I've heard enough. I have
a boyfriend to last me a lifetime.
I'm good, thanks. You can though,
but I won't be there.
You can if you like, but I won't be there.
No, I'm all right.
Nah, I'm all right, mate.
I've had enough bad experiences to last
me a lifetime. No thanks.
I'm good, fam.
You can die if you want.
I'm not wasting money in this country anymore.
just to hear. I have a boyfriend. I have
a boyfriend. I have a boyfriend. [ __ ]
that. [ __ ] that again.
I'll leave some other clump to it.
You know what I mean? [ __ ] that.
No, I'm all right.
If something was going to happen, it
would have happened by now. Another day
doesn't change that.
Another day doesn't change that. So, No,
another day doesn't change that unfortunately.
That's where I met uh the Finnish one in
Maxis. I met her in Maxis.
I'm at home, Maxis. Oh yeah. What? No.
Anyways, I'll see you later. Yeah, I
need to make a new channel and [ __ ] See
when I see you
tomorrow we [ __ ] our prime.