[ __ ] hell. Here we go, man.
Yeah, there we go.
man. It's nice to see how people still
obsessed with Peter
Belly, but you know, I don't I don't
take it personally cuz, you know,
uh jealousy is a disease. So, you know,
they can't help it. Bless
them, you know. So is what it is,
bro. It's a disease, dude. It's a man.
Man, been out [ __ ] smashing it, man.
been out [ __ ] sending
it. So and [ __ ] drunk,
man. It's been
ace. [ __ ] ace, bro.
Yeah, but there's only going to be
content now uh on the main channel. Not entertaining these
weirdos. Nah, bro. I'm not even wasting
my time talking about them or responding
to them ever again, bro. So,
yeah. They need some help. That's what
they need to do, man. They need to go and get
help. That's what they need, mate.
Literally, there's something wrong with
them, man. I'm telling you.
Weird. Yeah, it's strange. Very, very
strange. I could just like never Yeah.
imagine someone living in my head. Like,
I I couldn't imagine it, bro. Honestly,
like I could never imagine,
right, somebody living in my head
rentree every moment of every day. I
couldn't I literally could never imagine
it, bro. It's to me it's so different.
It seems so weird to me, you
know? You know, it's
mad. Like, I get why they, you know,
people used to do it to Timmy and [ __ ]
cuz like the reaction's funny, isn't it?
But there's a difference between people
doing stuff for a reaction and people
actually being obsessed and jealous.
There's there's there's a huge
difference. There's a fine line. And
also when it becomes very dangerous as
well, which it is [ __ ] dangerous,
bro. You know, like these people's
obsession with me is a [ __ ] hazard,
bro. I swear to
God. It's crazy, mate. Crazy.
Oh, my [ __ ] nose is [ __ ] bro.
Weird. Oh, it's thing you change his
picture as the
Y. Oh, is that the day? Okay, let me
see. Beef Town main there, I reckon. Okay.
Yeah. Yeah, bro. [Music] Good old
Gims. Yeah, man. Just been
uh got the old
passport. It smells lush. Yeah, that's
for another 10 years. So that's nice.
Should have my old one coming back,
dude. Yeah, it's crazy, bro.
This guy lied about what his uh funny. Yeah. France,
Belgium, Amsterdam in regards to
different country. Well, Netherlands,
Amsterdam's not a country,
lad. Don't know. Don't care. Don't bring
it on my channel. I just said just a
minute ago, don't bring these weirdos up
on my channel,
bro. Stop bringing it on my channel. I
don't care about them. They're going to
do anything and everything to try and
get my attention, and I'm not giving it
to them. So, don't bring it up on my channel. Like,
purposely don't don't bring up keyboard
warriors on my um bring keyboard
warriors up on my channel. Otherwise,
like you can do it once and I warn you.
Do it again and I'll block you. Simple.
That's it, bro. We're not doing this on
this channel no more with these with
these weirdos. Yeah. Simple. Yeah. That's it.
And that's it. Yeah,
simple. Uh, yeah, I did go there, but I
didn't get a passport stamp for
it. That's why I went. Yeah, but I
didn't get a passport stamp for that one for some reason.
Yeah. So, yeah. Don't bring on my
channel, lad. Bye-bye now. And you're
gone. Damn. Same repeating people.
[ __ ] me, bro. Honestly, it feels like
I've gone for a year and it's just like
the same repeating people. Yeah, and
I'll do I I'll do what I want. [ __ ] off,
you weirdo. Get blocked. [ __ ]
keyboard lawyer. You don't know where I
live and you will never know where I
live. Get that in your head. You will
never ever ever ever know where I live.
And certain people will never give that
information. And another thing is why
are you even trying to find out where I
live? A that's just weird and that's
just obsessive. And B, even if you knew
where I lived, you still wouldn't do
anything. So, man, you're obsessed, bro.
Get a life. I'm just waiting for genuine
people to to join now. Anyways, simple,
bro. Yeah, [ __ ] weirdos. Same same
projecting spackers ain't got nothing in
life. Oh, man. What have we come back to,
eh? Yeah, what have we come back
to? Weirdos. Absolute creeps. Yeah,
man. Don't bring Don't [ __ ] bring it
on my [ __ ] channel, you [ __ ]
weirdo. Any of them people get
mentioned, I'm going to ignore it. So,
there's no point you even like bringing
it up cuz I'm just going to ignore it
because they're not what like think
about it, man. Yeah. You you you know,
you've only got one life. Yeah. One
life. Like, you've only got one life,
bro. And these people are not even worth
talking about. They're not even worth
responding to. Like that's that's that's
the way you you got to actually think
about it, bro. You know, they're not
even worth the time a day. They do what
they do every day cuz they're obsessed
with you. They're jealous of you. So,
bro, you're already winning. You don't
need to reply back to these people.
They've got a mental obsession with you
as it is. What are you replying for?
It's mad. Crazy, bro.
You know what I'm saying? Weirdo
[ __ ] Oh, who's that? Stalking territory. Yeah, literally.
Yeah. Yeah, bro. Going to be some
content on this channel now anyway as
well. The the main channel. Yeah.
things to try and get an explanation or
to try and get my attention is not going
work. So, try again. Yep.
Oopsie. No, it's actually the same channel. Yeah. Yeah,
bro. Come on, Jerry, bro. [ __ ] hell.
But yeah, it's weird,
man. I need to get some
uh went live in the nightclub the other
day. It was [ __ ] ace, bro. It was [ __ ] ace.
What was that?
Yeah, man. Come on, bro. [ __ ] Where are
you? See, that's what you do with these
clowns. You just ignore them. Simple, man.
Let them waste more of their life on you, bro.
Yeah. That's it. Is it really?
Yeah. Like these people do what they do
to get attention. They'll make up stuff
to try to get you back on explaining
this, that, and the other. It's not
going to work. My IQ is a little higher
than well, it's a lot higher than theirs
will ever be. So it's it's like when
like say you're on YouTube, right? So
say you're not on YouTube for like two
days, right? They will make up stories
like, "Oh, you've been arrested." All in
hopes to get your attention because
that's the whole point of why they do
what they do because they want
attention. They have nothing in life. So
that's why they do all of these things
every single day. Nothing, man. Just
just chilling. I just said that I'm not
responding to these clowns anymore. you
know, there's going to be like content
on my main and and that's it. They're
not going to get my attention. They can
make up stories that I'm living here.
They can make up stories about this and
that and the other. I don't give a [ __ ]
you know. I've had I've had a good two
weeks, bro. And I'm not entertaining
these little clowns. Simple.
Yeah. Been smashing the approaches as
well. I got my passport two days ago, so yay. Yay.
And yeah, it's it's
weird. And have you have you noticed
something, Joe, as well is that like
these people still do this even when
you're not on
YouTube? And how I know this because
people tell me
people write me on [ __ ] Instagram.
They write me on Instagram and they tell
me like that's that's how you know that
it's obsession and it's jealousy and
it's not because of a somebody reacting
to someone because people used to do it
to Timmy because Timmy used to react to
people so they oh will [ __ ] trigger
Timmy and that's why people used to do
it to Timmy but these people will do it
regardless if they get a reaction or not
because they're mentally obsessed and
jealous with you. It's a disease. Do you
not understand it? Whether you whether
you're on here or whether you're not,
whether you react, whether you don't, it
doesn't stop a disease that they've got.
So, and that's all it is, bro. It's
Yeah, I've done loads of approaches.
I've been getting some women as well.
I've been getting some [ __ ] bro.
Been out a good few times, man. Good few
[ __ ] times. I done some sober, too.
Well, a lot sober, but
yeah. Got some mad numbers,
bro. This is a lot, bro.
So, probably give this week a mister. I
still need some films I need to watch,
but ain't got round to doing
it. Yeah, bro.
So, I look like a bun. Yeah. Yeah. Okay,
bro. We've heard it all before now. And
you're blocked. And this is exactly what
I'm talking about, bro. You come back
and it's just exactly the same old. This
is why people don't want to come on here
anymore. You know what I'm saying, bro?
It's boring as [ __ ]
Same repeating people, same fat lossers
that have got nothing going for
themselves that try to bring other
people down because they they The thing
is with these people, right? If you if
you see what most of these people look
like, yeah, when when when they put
their camera on, they're all fat,
they're all ugly, they're all skinn,
they're all hopeless. So what they do is
they stumbled across a community and
they've stumbled across a community to
try to bring other people down to their
level because they know like they look
at themselves and think [ __ ] like I'm in
my 40s. I'm too old to change and that's
why they do what they do every day on
YouTube because anybody with quarter of
a brain cell would be like I'm packing
this [ __ ] up and I'm leaving but they
can't leave. Why can't they leave? Why
could other people leave but these
people can't? because it's everything
that they have. No frenzy videos. No,
man. I haven't been playing it to be
honest. One sec. Someone's calling me.
They all look the same, bro. You're
saying that bomb trolling pie only two
look like seaside mo call me on
Instagram. Yeah, bro. Because they're
all the same. Do you not understand? All
the people in this community are all the
same. Fat, ugly, no life, no money.
They're all the same. They're self
projectors. Jesus. They've been doing it
for years now, bro. And they're autistic
as well. That's why they're going about
money over and over and over again.
They're going about money. They're going
about other people's appearance. But
then the people's appearances that
they're going on about is better looking
than them. So, I know it makes no sense,
right? But that's they've been doing it
for [ __ ] years, bro. Absolute years.
Like, I won't I won't even be coming on
here every day now, bro. I just post
some content videos on my main. That's
it. You know, and I was thinking I was
thinking, bro, hold on a minute. Why
does nobody else get this treatment?
Timmy doesn't. See, Mark
doesn't. All of
these other people don't. They're
jealous of you, PJ. Like, that's what I
was saying to myself. They've got to be
jealous of you. Like, no one else has
ever got this treatment. And no one else
has ever got this treatment when they
were off at YouTube as well. They're
jealous of you, bro. Think of it. They
know that you got more money than them.
You're better looking than them. Listen,
as much as they want to say that, oh,
you know that you are better than them
in every way, shape, or form. That's why
they can't get you out their [ __ ]
head. It's a bit like when you're
[ __ ] in love with someone, bro. Look,
because I'm thinking, bro, like there's
other people on here and they've never got the
same. I'm out on the road. So, they're
definitely jealous. It's definitely
jealous. Trust me, bro. Despite them
calling you a M, despite them calling
you skin, they're only calling
themselves, bro. Come on. Deep down,
we've seen these people now, bro. Like,
look, it's embarrassing at this point.
They need to pack it up. Pack it the [ __ ] up,
bro. No, he said, "La, I'm out on the
road." That's what he actually
said, you know.
And then these people are so obsessed.
They're trying to find out where I live
and they don't know where I live. They
get everything wrong. That's obsession,
bro. That's obsession. You know, like I
said, there's a difference between um people
like doing stuff for reaction and
there's and there's people just being
[ __ ] obsessed and
jealous. So, that's the difference. Yep.
I've had loads of success the
past nine days. Yeah,
actually. Yep. I'm not going into
anymore as well, but I'm not telling
these people anything. You know, they're
obsessed enough as it [ __ ] is. Yeah.
A lot of them's reply, bro. I'm meeting
some as well. I've already met another
one. It's all good,
bro. So, yeah. I would go this week, but
I need to uh I'm not going into it, bro.
I'm not getting into
it. I've got two scheduled, but like
I've kissed some people and [ __ ] as
well. But yeah, bro, I don't need to
blast my life all over this [ __ ] you
know? Right. Book a holiday soon as
well. I got my passport. So, there we go, bro.
These people could never approach women
and get numbers and get kisses and get
dates. These people never can. These
people can't do anything but sit on
YouTube and hate every day, bro. Think
about it. [ __ ] that, bro. That's a
[ __ ] [ __ ] That's a full-time
[ __ ] job, lad. Like, I'm going to
tell you where I'm going,
bro. Like, I'm going to tell you where
I'm actually going. Are you [ __ ]
mad? Yeah, bro. fat chance of that
happening. You know, you will see when
the videos are out there. You will just
see. You're not going to know nothing
until I'm back from where I go. And then
you're just going to see the
videos. I might even go somewhere
Saturday. I was thinking of flipping a
coin and [ __ ] off somewhere. But you
will see the videos when they're there.
You You know, and that's
it. That's That's the end, bro. Yeah.
So yeah, of course he did, bro. Yeah,
fantasies on it. He als he he also said he wasn't
boredom. Yeah, he also said he wasn't bored,
but I mean
Yeah. But yeah, I've spat on uh I
shouldn't even say this, Joe, but I've
actually uh been gambling on like 20
pound on the roulette machines and I've
been spitting on them. I've actually got
two videos of me actually spitting on on
the machine. I'm not even joking cuz I'd
send it to Ant-Man that and it was only
20 pound on that. I just [ __ ] spat on
it twice. Bro, I had to get out of that
[ __ ] shopping center before I got
nicked. And you know what? If it was
actually a normal community and it
wasn't full of grasses, I I would
actually upload it. You know what I'm saying? But
yeah, I was on a football bet yesterday
as well. 90 pound just needed Newport to
score but they never I put 90 on a on a
double both teams to
score. Nah, never saw it,
bro. Yeah, machines are getting worse,
bro. At least I got my passport for 10
years in it. So, yeah.
But yeah, these people are very um very
strange. And it makes no difference
whether you're on here or you're not on
here. They're always going to be
obsessed. Now, you can see, Joe, these
people are the ones that are obsessed.
You can see I've not been on for a week.
I've not replied to any of these people
and they're still obsessed. So you go
figure you and go tell me who's who's
the one that's obsessed.
Yeah, they're [ __ ] weirdos, bro.
weirdos. But I've been sending the
approaches, man. They're [ __ ] sick,
bro. They're never going anywhere, bro.
Even if you listen Listen. The
difference with Timmy, right, is Timmy
used to do it for reaction. People do it
to Monty for reaction. The whole point
of them doing this stuff is for
reaction. Whereas these people, even if
they had even, bro, they can go 10 years
without getting a reaction and they
would still do it. So, it's like they're
obsessed and jealous of you. Obviously,
bro, think about it, bro. Come on now,
man. Think about it. Think about it
logically. They will be doing it. Even
if they don't get even if they don't get
a reaction. Even if I was banned from
social media and I literally couldn't
even go on it, they would still do it.
They're [ __ ] bro. I swear down. Their lives are
[ __ ] Don't know why they why why they
do this, bro. It's
weird. So, yeah.
Well, I I do know why they do it cuz
obviously they're jealous, bro. Of
course. You know, it's [ __ ] common
sense. We've seen no evidence of people
on here doing anything with their
[ __ ] lives, have we?
Yeah. You know, but it's such a grassing
community. Like I'd love to say like
more and stuff, but these people are just such
grasses. It's crazy. Crazy,
man. But like I said, compare Timmy and
then compare me.
Yeah. Yeah. I was I was trying these
women, bro. It's [ __ ] madness. I went
out with my
friend. Yeah. Ace, bro.
You see how like these people like will
get will get stuck on that one for
Manchester and think that it bothers me.
Doesn't bother me. I could just go and
meet other people, bro. I've already
gone out and met other [ __ ] people. I
would say in about the past week, I've
got about 13
numbers, loads of replies, dates
scheduled. It's nothing to beat a belly, mate. You
know, nothing to me, man.
I don't know about
you. The funniest thing is I don't even
really have much of a sex drive
anymore. It's crazy, isn't it? It
doesn't really bother me
anymore. See, that's the thing. I can
accept the women [ __ ] I can't accept
the gambling [ __ ] That's the
difference, bro. You know, I can't be
like, "Oh, well, you go out, you try,
and if you get lucky, you do. If you
don't, you don't." That's not the
problem. The problem is is with this
gambling, you know, even when it's 20
pound, it's impossible to calm down,
bro. It is literally I'm lucky I didn't
get [ __ ] nicked today, you know, and
that's it, man. It's crazy.
It's It ruins the whole day. I didn't
even get to go to the cinema. I actually
went out to buy a tracksuit and then I
was going to go to the cinema.
And I was, "Oh, let me like kill a bit
of time cuz I had like 40 minutes to wait. Wait, you
know, but gambling it's impossible to
come down with, bro. It ruined the whole day
again." Yeah. Well, time's changing it,
man. I've got other things to be doing
in my life. I don't really care, bro. I
don't even use escorts
anymore. If I If they reply, they reply.
If they meet, they meet me. If they
don't, they don't. I'll just keep going.
I'll just keep I'll just keep going on
to the next and the next. Simple, bro. I
don't give a [ __ ]
man. It's nothing to me, bro. But the
gambling thing is impossible to come
down with. That's the only thing cuz
it's not the women thing, bro. I can
accept the women thing as like it's
always going to be against you. You do
it as more like a hobby thing, fine. But
the gambling thing, it literally
controls your whole body and your whole
[ __ ] mind. It literally does. Even if it's 20
pound. Yeah, but a penny will never drop with gambling
though. Yeah, I just do this approaching
women [ __ ] as like a hobby. I got loads
of replies, man. I've got meats coming
up. I've just been chilling, bro. I've
just been doing other things. But the
pain will never drop with
gambling. It will never drop with
gambling, you know? Never with gambling.
It will never. Cuz I like I'm just one
of these people that just shouldn't be doing it.
Simple. 90 yesterday
returned 340 and I just needed Newport
to score and they got their ass whooped five [ __ ] nil. It's
like actually it's not it's not even No,
it's not even a football bet actually.
No, actually now it's not even a
football bet. If I lose 20 on a Foggy
machine, I'm putting a [ __ ] chair
through it. Simple. It's [ __ ]
annoying. It is annoying, bro. I swear
to God, the other day I put two pound in
the machine. I got it to10 and I lost
it. I was going [ __ ] mad. You don't understand,
bro. It's the way it is. I don't think I
will ever be different with it. I don't
care about the women [ __ ] anymore. I I
really don't care, bro. I've got other
things to be doing, bro. I've got
numbers. I've got replies. I'm meeting.
I don't really care, bro. I've had
[ __ ] but the gambling thing.
Yeah. Yeah. It was a good day on um when
I went out last week. Yeah. But again,
what I'm trying to explain to you, Joe,
is it's not that quantity of money. It's
[ __ ] annoying. Losing is annoying.
It's not an option. It is annoying. It
doesn't matter if it's 20 pound. It's
[ __ ] annoying. It gives you mood
swings. Yeah. I approached Thursday. I
done I got some numbers there on
Friday. Yeah, I got a video of me
spitting on it. It's [ __ ] vile, bro.
It is nasty, bro. I done it twice and
they're both over 20 pound as well. It
was [ __ ] pissing me off,
bro. I swear down. It was only over 20 pound as
well. But yeah, that's the thing with
Yeah, I'm not going to go out this
week. I got some more numbers, too.
Yeah, I was talking to this one for like
15 minutes, bro. I think I'm in love
again with two people. I think I'm in
love with two
people. Yeah, I think I'm in love with two
people. Yep, we got a few different
ones. I think I'm in love with two
people. We was actually speaking for like 15
minutes. Yeah, it was a lovely site.
But yeah, man. I got I'm trying to think what
else. Yeah, I met my friend on
uh sat last Saturday. I've been out a
few times this
month pretty much. He was like proper
looking at me and chatting and chatting.
Man thinks he likes old Peter Belly.
And then the other one, there's a few of them as
well. There's a French one as well. But
the thing is, but no, no, no. But to be
fair, yeah, it is it is the same [ __ ]
but we just do it because we just do it
in it. Like what I mean by the same [ __ ]
is whenever you go out in England, it's
the same [ __ ] I don't mean like, oh,
they say they've got boyfriend. No, no,
no. I'm speaking about it is literally a
replica of the last time you went out.
For example, you go out on Saturday
around five, six, and you do I do eight
approaches sober because eight's my
lucky number. One of them. So, out of
them eight numbers, you'll probably get
about you'll get one number. Yeah. Yeah.
Bye-bye. Yeah. You'll probably get one
number and it will always be a French
woman's number. Don't ask me why, but it
would always be a French woman's number.
It will never be English. It will never
be American. It will always be French.
So you've got that. So you've got one.
So you've got one number, right? So then
you go to the bars and clubs and then
you see the same women with the same
attitude, with the same men that's got
the same attitude and the same hipsters
and then you go through like, "Oh, I've
got a boyfriend." And then you get some
numbers and then normally the next day
they don't go anywhere. That's what I
mean by it's always it's it's a replica
of the last time, not just the stuff
that they say. I mean, even when you're
walking about you see the same people
everywhere with the same attitude.
Yes, she turned out to be a [ __ ] man.
That was a few weeks ago. That that
bartender, bro. We're on to some new things.
Yeah. But yeah, it is a replica um of
the last time you went out. It's like
they It's like
dear. It's always the same thing that
ends up normally happening most of the time.
Yeah, I bought it. That was a few weeks
ago. Said to her, if I give you money,
would you suck my
dick? Didn't uh take kindly to that. So,
yeah. Yeah, I do remember
that. I didn't like her that much
anyways, but yeah, that was one I did
like. They liked me, too. So, we see
Yeah, it's St. Patty's Day on the 17th
is in it. Guinnesses are £3
pound. But yeah, I don't care about the
women's [ __ ] no more. But the gambling
thing is just impossible. I don't know
how people it does people how it doesn't bother
people. I just don't know how it don't
bother people losing. I'd love to be one of them
people. Like the women think I can
accept it. Okay. Yeah, you'll get some,
you get n some. You just go out and have
fun anyways. It's not really an issue.
But the thing is like the gambling thing
is just impossible, bro.
Like, but yeah, on Saturday, I was
thinking I was actually thinking of
waking up like 6:00 in the morning and
just flipping a coin, bro, and either
going to Blackpool or [ __ ] Glasgow. I
either go to Glasgow to see my dada or I
go to Blackpool. But I don't really want
to be wasting money in this country
anymore. But I'd have to wake up like
6:00 in the morning cuz if I've got to
go [ __ ] Scotland then it's We need to
put up videos like that, bro.
Content. Not [ __ ] replying to [ __ ]
Kent virgins with no teeth with rat
faces. How are you going to get the
views in, bro? How are we going to get
the revenue if you know we're not going
to get the revenue, bro? If you're
[ __ ] replying to these little virgins
on YouTube. Come on,
man. Any chance of getting [ __ ]
revenue? We're [ __ ] not going to do
it replying to these [ __ ] clowns, are
we? Yeah, I can't find him either, mate.
He's not a [ __ ] runner. No wonder I
was so [ __ ] up in my head, Joe. I got
a mummy in
America that left me and I've got a
daddy in Scotland that left me. No
wonder you were so psy psychologically
[ __ ] up in your head, you know. Of
course, man. What the [ __ ] bro? you
your parents literally have left you and
they're not even in the same [ __ ] country as
you. Imagine that. That's a
madness. But no, the last time I went
mad Yeah. I think it was about I don't
think it was last week I went out. It
was a week after I started messaging
that [ __ ] Morgan's mom. Yeah. I was
like, "Listen." Yeah. How immature do
you have to be to make group chats to
people? Let me tell you something right
now. Yeah. That you are the keyboard
warrior. I was saying, "You are the
keyboard warrior. You're the one that
has to make [ __ ] group chats with
people." In their absence, I was like,
"You are the keyboard warrior." I was
like, "Listen, mate. If you've got a
problem, I'll come back. You know, I get
my passport in in a couple of days. I've
got it now." But yeah, like it's
nothing, bro. I was I was pissed though,
to be fair. It was annoying me, bro. I
was walking back home. Yeah. And it was
it was I was like, "Hold on a minute.
You're going to call me a cable boy?
You're the one that's making group chats
of me. What? [ __ ] off,
man. You know, making group chats of me.
But yeah, it's weird, bro.
Um, yeah, I spoke to [ __ ] Izzy. She's
in Birmingham, by the way. Steven Howard. Yeah.
That man's moving to Thailand. He's back
soon. And then when he goes again, he's
living there. I was like, "Well, we're
never going to see each other again."
Like, if you go, we're never going to
see each other ever
again. That's a madness, though. Like,
that's a whole risk to just go there and
live there and never come back. Like,
don't get it twisted. I hate
England. Like, I hate the women in
England. I hate the gambling. I hate the
weather. I hate the government. Like I
hate [ __ ] everything about this
country. Don't get it twisted. But I
mean, moving to a third world country is
a madness. But I guess he's happier
there, you know? Like
Yeah. You know what I mean,
bro? Everything sucks here, bro. It
feels like it's like a it's like a it's
like a double um double negative country
like with the gambling and like you know
you know what I'm saying like it's like
it's a double negative. He's going to
get a job there. Yeah. He's going to be an English teacher. But
yeah, but I need to get into something,
bro. Like this this gambling [ __ ] is is no good, bro. You
know, but it's so easy. It's so
accessible. It should be illegal like it
is in Thailand. See, in Thailand, you
can't gamble. Think about it, bro. Think
about it. Yeah. Compare the two. Yeah.
You're in Thailand. There's no
gambling's illegal. The weather's nice
and you can [ __ ] whenever you
want. So, think about it, bro. No wonder
people there are so happy. No wonder
people there kill
themselves here. Like, the people are
just [ __ ] [ __ ] And then the
gambling [ __ ] and the weather [ __ ] So
it's like the complete
opposite. Even in America, gambling's
not as big as it is here. Unless you
unless literally unless you go to Vegas.
Yeah. Or [ __ ] Salt Lake City.
Gambling is not even a thing there like
it is here. You know, betting shops
every other [ __ ] there's there's
betting shops that are next to each
other. The same company. It's a madness,
bro. That's why people are so unhappy, you know.
Yeah, but younger people are doing it
now, man. Younger people are doing it now. But
yeah, younger people going in now, bro,
cuz how it is, you
know. Yeah. I really want to have a baby
with this French woman, man, and call it
Pierre. I'd call the baby
Pierre. And his first words would be
bonjour. Yeah, good point. But they
don't have any money. They're all
skin be like his first words would be
bonjour. Oh, bless you. Oh,
man. Do you remember friends? Izzy with her little
dress. Do you remember French Izzy with
with her little dress? Oh, [ __ ] hell,
bro. Do you know what? I've actually
come across a few of them that are
trolls. It's been
about I've had a few of them,
bro. I've had a few of them, bro. Trust
me, they That's the mad thing with these
French women, right, is that they'll
always reply and they'll always troll
you. That's the difference. You're
guaranteed. They'll always reply and
they'll always troll you. It's [ __ ]
up, bro. Like, they're mad. It's crazy
because it's like, oh, like it's like
the French people are rude. Yeah,
they're very, very rude. Then as soon as
you come across a French woman, she'll
be nice, but like she'll troll you. It's
proper like it's it's like they'll go
out of their way to troll you. It's a
madness. It's a madness. It's like
they'll go out of their way just to
troll you, bro. It's [ __ ] isn't it? Yeah. [Music]
Yeah. Did you hear
um Nunch Legs's um video? Stephen King
uh Stephen Steven Howard. I was I say
Stephen King. He was like, "Oh,
masturbating quite a few times a day.
That's something a virgin would do." I
was like, "Well, yeah, you would know
all about being a virgin. You're the
biggest virgin going." Is it Stephen
Hour? You're the biggest virgin to known
to mankind. So, you'd know all about
virgins. virgin boy. I don't know why
that was just stuck in my head, but I
love that you would know all about the
tailtale signs of virgins because you're
a virgin yourself,
obviously. I don't know why that just made me
laugh. That just [ __ ] made me laugh,
bro. I don't know why it did make me
laugh, you know.
Jesus, it is
funny. Yeah, it is funny,
bro. I can't be bothered with any of
them, bro. They're just obsessed.
They're just obsessed. It's funny how
they say, "Oh, he can't be a virgin
because he's got a girlfriend." He is a
[ __ ] virgin, mate, because his dick
still don't work whether he's got a
girlfriend or not. But nobody defends me
Steven Howard, even though I've proved
I've had sex. When people call me a
[ __ ] virgin, no one [ __ ] backs me
up and I've proved I've had sex. But
[ __ ] when I called a virgin boy a
virgin, he [ __ ] he he people say,
"Oh, you can't be a virgin because you
got a girlfriend." I like, "Well, that
can't be right because I've actually
proved I've had sex. I've got a video of
me shoving my dick up a woman's gob."
For [ __ ] sake, Steven Howard, lad. But
no one defends me.
Oh, I think beef chowine is on the
agenda today, bro. I'm getting really
into that beef chowine, bro. Oh, it's lovely. Yeah,
bro. You know, if I show like the women
that I'll be meeting soon and the women
I'm speaking to, he would be so jealous,
bro. Oh my god, he'd be so
jealous. He already gets about, bro.
Trust me. He would get super jail, man.
I'm telling you. So I have to keep these
things secret. A secret de
lad. I love beef tail. It's sexy, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm never telling you. Yeah, exactly,
bro. Exactly. Like you're best off Yeah.
just doing traveling videos. Like even
the G. Do you know if you you know how
you would trigger these people, bro? I
tell you, do you know how you the the
the way to trigger these people up,
right? Is if you go to a gym and you
travel, it doesn't matter where it is.
It could be anywhere in England, bro.
You will literally destroy these people
even more. Why? Because the gambling
thing Because the gambling Because the
gambling thing Because the gambling
thing it's not going to work, bro.
Because when you lose money, they get
off on it. Even though we'll never be
skinned like these people. We've got
more money than these people ever will.
You know, they see it as you've lost
money, so it's a loss.
Ret. And obviously, we can't only show
wins. So, if you if you scrap the
gambling Yeah. And you don't just like
gym videos and [ __ ] just going to
different places. Just anything, bro.
Like even chatting up a woman and
getting her number. Even if the number
didn't go anywhere, bro, you'll destroy
these people, bro. They'll end up in
hospital. I'm telling you. Like that's
how you could really destroy these
people, bro. I'm not even joking, lad.
Or like steak restaurants, any anything
like that, you
know? But the gambling's no good, bro.
Because obviously if you lose it gives
me mood swings and it winds me up. So
like it's not uh it's not feasible really. So
yeah. Well I don't know man. Like if
when I flip the coin and it goes on
Blackpool I'll be like I've always
wanted to go back but then I don't get
to see my dada. But then if I flip it
and then it goes Glasgow and I go to
Glasgow it's like oh I get to see my
daddy but I kind of wanted to go to
Blackpool. You get what I mean?
So yeah, it's mad, bro. It's crazy. So I
mean, yeah, I mean, you could do both. I
can't Well, I can't do both cuz if I go
out drinking on a Friday, I'll be [ __ ]
Saturday, so I won't be able to do two and
one, but at the end of the day, Stephen,
I still need to find my daddy. I want to
know why he
left. Why he [ __ ] left
me. I was messaging this woman I kissed
from Edinburgh, bro. from Edinburgh. I
was like, "Oh, um, do you know some guy
called Tam in
Glasgow?" She said, "Yeah." I was like,
"Okay, well, I'm trying to locate a guy
called Tam." Tam the Celtic
fan. You can hear that [ __ ] uh accent
a mile off, you know.
Yeah. He's hard to find, bro.
I love these I love doing these
approaches, bro. I love him. I just send
I got a models number as well. I got
this woman's number that was a model.
Yeah, they all called that, bro. It's a
[ __ ] Scottish name, isn't
it? Yeah. But if I had a baby with that
French woman, I'd call it Pierre because Pierre is
um is Peter in French if if you didn't
know. So it's Peter in French. So I
would call it Pierre.
Yeah. Good old Pierre. Okay. [ __ ]
me. Yeah. What's the chances though,
man? Yeah. Lots of Scottish go there cuz it's the
north. It's the northwest, isn't it? So,
they would do
Yeah. Oh, do you know what? I might just
get a curry. I don't know. But I don't
know if I can be bothered to go out,
bro. That's really bad, isn't
it? But I don't know if I can be
bothered to go out, lad.
No, I'm going to go out. [ __ ] it. I was
going to go out yesterday, but it was
actually closed. Yeah, I'll just get a
beef tail, man. Only cost a tener, man.
We need to be smart with money, bro. You
know. Yeah. So, it will be Baby Pierre
from France, Steven Howard, and you
could be its uncle. Ah, what a lovely
site. And you can you could be the
baby's uncle, right?
How do you feel about being an
uncle to baby
Pierre? A what a lovely site,
mate. Look at you just sat there waiting
for a Peter belly upload. You're just
sat there just waiting, aren't you? Just
[ __ ] waiting, bro. You
know, he's already found his
mama. You remember, bro?
Yeah. Pet can't get attached because
he's already found his mama.
Because he's already found his
mama. Who's going to pay? Yeah. And
who's going to pay for the baby
grows? If I was getting the grind a
month like [ __ ] nons legs [ __ ] how
the [ __ ] can I afford them [ __ ] Sony
baby grows. [ __ ] me,
bro. I'd have to get back on the [ __ ]
I'd have to [ __ ] deliver some peaches or some
[ __ ] Yeah. B. Yeah. Yeah. Popcorn
chicken. I'd have to [ __ ] deliver
pizzas or some [ __ ]
Yeah. Madness, isn't
it? You could live on a grand a month.
It would be [ __ ] It would just be
[ __ ] I say that. You'd probably just
adjust to it to be fair. That's what I'm
going to do. Build the main channel up, bro. Of
course. And all of these people that are
obsessed, just leave him to
it because you got to understand,
Stephen Howard, is whether you're on
here or not, they're always going to be
obsessed. When Timmy is not on YouTube,
people leave. And when I'm off YouTube,
people still do it. Even if I don't
react to them, they still do
it cuz they're mentally obsessed, isn't
it, bro? You know, it's what it is, isn't
it? Can't wait till the summer, man. I
got some nice summer gums from last year
when I won that four grand. I bought
some nice clothes, bro. Remember? I
bought some nice clothes. Remember,
bro? Uh, I'm not subletting, mate. And
you don't know where I live. So, try again,
buddy. Try again.
And also, you don't know where I live
and you'll never know where I live. So,
yeah. Try again, buddy.
Yeah. And you also took a bit of
information about what I'd said about uh
6 months ago. When I said something
about six months ago, you kind of took that
information and you just worded it like
you found stuff out, but you didn't. So, yeah.
Yeah, I've got a card for a certain
person. I need to send it to them. Not mentioning any
names. Not mentioning any names. Do you
want to see my ad re? I'll show you my
ad revenue, but I can't make no money on YouTube,
bro. I'll show you
mine. I'll show you mine. One
sec. Mine's [ __ ] bro. Look.
Yeah. What is that? Some pain [ __ ] One second,
bro. That's going to annoy me. One
sec. Yep. Uh, no you don't. No, you
don't know where I am and you don't know
where I live. Also, another thing is um
the only reason you knew that is because
back when I used to have the house seven
months ago, I told everyone on YouTube
that. So, shut up. You don't know
anything. Try again,
buddy. Isn't this the same [ __ ]
that tried saying that he saw me in
Plasto, bro? Stop talking
[ __ ] It's embarrassing now. You took
information about what I told people
seven months ago. You don't know where I
am. You don't know how I make money and
you will never know. Get yourself gone,
buddy. Right. I'm trying to find this um
earning thing. Hold
on. Right. Here we go. Look. So,
this when I'm trying to make money from
YouTube and I'm
nowhere at all near [ __ ] eligible,
bro. Look. Like, nowhere near.
Look. Look, bro. Look at the look at the
bottom one. I
need 3 million public short views. Yeah.
Look. And it's like nowhere
near. So I'm [ __ ]
basically. Look at that. See the blue
one? Look at the two. That's before I even become
eligible. Why is your ass licking, man?
Because who wants the ass lick, bro? My
ass tastes nice, man. Leave
him. Leave him, bro.
Yeah. Why do you people tell people to
get jobs every day when you ain't got a
job yourself? But yeah, as you can see,
I'm not even the slightest bit eligible
to even make money. I wish, mate, I wish
I could make money on
YouTube. I [ __ ] wish I
could. But yeah, Sean, the only thing
reason you knew about
that female tenant is when I told
everyone seven months ago when I still
had a house where I don't have anymore.
So, stop going on like you know
things. You made up a story where you
called a housing association pretending
to be me. You need to get some [ __ ]
help. You need to get some [ __ ] help,
man. You're [ __ ] in your
head. I think this is a clear sign
anyone who's watching this is why you
don't meet somebody with
autism. You should never ever meet
somebody with autism.
You know, should do a background check
on the [ __ ] [ __ ] Ah, bye-bye. Bye-bye now. Bye-bye
now. See you later.
Toodles. So, as you can see, I'm not um
the slightest bit eligible. One
second. Yep. Basically, slim. Basically, mate.
Yeah. He's trying to make up stories
about how he knows where I am when he
doesn't know where I am. [ __ ] sad little
bastard. [ __ ] sad little [ __ ]
weirdo. Yeah, the flip the flip the flip
in the coin could could um kickstart the
channel, bro. On a Saturday. That could Yeah,
Slim. Aren't you from Scotland, Slim? If
recall, you're from Scotland, aren't you, buddy? Oh,
buddy. If I if this is the right person I'm thinking of. [Music]
Yeah. You are Why is it raining? I need
to go get some [ __ ] Chinese. And it's
[ __ ] raining, bro. What the [ __ ]
Bro, I'm I think there's ghosts in this house,
bro. I'm not even joking. I actually
think there's a ghost in this [ __ ]
house. Do you believe in ghosts?
You're going to think that I sound
[ __ ] crazy, but believe you me, bro.
There's [ __ ] ghosts in this [ __ ]
house. I'm telling you, there is, bro. You
know, I believe in them,
bro. Enough. Did you hear that,
bro? Definitely heard that. I definitely heard that,
man. I think there's ghost,
bro. I think there's ghosts, bro.
Oops. Yeah, I think there was ghosts,
bro. Do you believe in ghosts, Stephen?
How? I think there was
ghosts. I know there was ghosts, bro,
cuz I [ __ ] heard
it. Did you hear that?
I need to go in a bit to get some
Chinese, but I'll be back later. I'll be
later. Yeah, I'm gone again for a week or two
weeks. Can't stay on this place, bro. [ __ ] these
people. I think these people need a hobby lad.
The reason you think the weather in
England is so
bad. Um, well, no. I think the weather
in England is so bad because it's spring
and it's pissing down with rain, you
[ __ ] virgin. That's why I think the
weather is so bad. One
second. Call me. Why am I getting a beef
chain? That's the best thing.
No, there is [ __ ] ghosts, bro. There
is. There is. And it always does it when
you're by yourself as well. There is
ghosts, bro. I'm telling you, there is.
Bro, I'm telling you. Yeah, my friend
was around earlier. Sometimes I bring my
friend around. Yeah. You don't hear
it. I'm telling you there's a ghost,
bro. Cuz I hear this every single time I'm by
myself. Yeah. I'm telling you, there is
such thing as
ghosts. It always happens when you're by
yourself, bro. As well. Yeah.
It always happens when you're by
yourself. It's the voices, bro. I'm
hearing [ __ ] voices from the [ __ ] garden,
bro. And yeah, it always happens when
you're by yourself. And I know all the
people that live. I've met so many
people and it's not in my [ __ ] head,
bro. Cuz when my friend was wild earlier
and my friends were around the other
day, you would ne never hear it. Never
it, you know? And then when you're by
yourself, you hear it
again. I'm telling you, there's a ghost,
bro. I swear to [ __ ] God. I never
used to believe that at first. I'm not
the only one cuz when my friend was was
was here and I was gone, he heard it
when he was by himself as
well, you know.
No, it's definitely a ghost. It always
happens when you're by yourself. It
does, bro. It does. It
does. I'm not scared of no ghost. I love
the [ __ ] all of
you. I love the [ __ ] all of you. I'm
not scared of no ghost. I love you all.
You know, I'm not a [ __ ] coward, man.
know, you know, I love the [ __ ] all of
you. I love you
all. You know, I love you all. Look at
that one. That's That's old school. That
is, bro. I love all you. And
apparently ghosts have [ __ ] babies as
well. Apparently ghosts have babies.
They do, bro. Apparent. Yeah. I'm not
even joking. I swear now,
bro. And every time I'm trying to record
a voice, it stops, you
know. I love you all. I love the [ __ ] all of you.
Bye-bye. Bye-bye. You don't know where I
live and you will never know where I
live. And nobody told you where I live
either because if you called up that
place, well, that house doesn't belong
to me and I'm on the teny.
Possible to tell you where I am. My name
would even know where I am. Shut up,
man. You little
virgin. Sean, instead of doing these
silly little videos, man, you need to
pop that virginity. You're almost a
30year-old [ __ ] virgin. Imagine that.
Steven Howard, a 30year-old, never been
on a plane, never been
abroad, still a [ __ ] virgin. Like, imagine that,
bro. Yeah, I just told my friend,
"Fucking leave the room as soon as
possible. I'm not scared of you, you
[ __ ] ghost. Come on. Come on. Come
on. You [ __ ]
[ __ ] I'm not [ __ ]
scared. It feel It actually feels like a horror
film. It actually feels like a [ __ ] horror film,
bro. You know, it actually it feels like
a horror film because don't you
understand what they do? They go for
houses that they think are [ __ ]
abandoned. Do you not
understand? They go for houses that they
think that are [ __ ]
abandoned. That's what they
do. That's what they [ __ ] do. They go
for [ __ ] h They go for houses that
they think are [ __ ] abandoned, bro.
madness. I'm not scared of no [ __ ] ghost, bro. Oh my
[ __ ] of a of a horror
movie. What's odds once dying a virgin, Steven
Howard? What's What's the odds on that
he's going to die a virgin?
Oh, that sounds like a virgin thing to
say that you masturbate too much. You
masturbate too much. Ah, bro, you would
know all about being a virgin because
you're the biggest virgin
going. You're the biggest virgin going, you little
virgin. You know, because why why the
[ __ ] does this always use virgin as an
insult? you know,
uh, you're not coming in and you don't
know where I live and you will never
know where I live. Um, how about Okay,
how about this? How about this? You You
really think that I'm there, Rat Face?
Okay. Well, why don't you go live on
that road and I will be there in half an
hour? Why don't you go live on that road
and I'll be there in half an hour? If
you really want to tell me, if you
really want to tell me how you know, get
going, you ratfaced [ __ ] virgin. Stop
trying to seek attention on my channel.
You don't know where I am and you will
never ever ever know where I am, you
know. But yeah, feel free to go there,
man, and and and wait 30 minutes. You
don't know where I am and you'll never
know where I am. And even if you did
know where I am, you still wouldn't do
anything cuz you're [ __ ] So shut
up. Shouldn't you instead of [ __ ]
stalking me? Yeah. On YouTube every day,
shouldn't you be working on losing your
virginity, losing your vcod? Like that's
what I would be doing at 29, 30 years of
age or whatever [ __ ] age that virgin
is. I'd be working on losing that virginity of
mine. But that scared the [ __ ] out of me,
bro. He will die a virgin. He's the He's
the biggest virgin going. He used to say
to me when I was 17, I used to tell him
about all these escorts I [ __ ] and he
used to get jealous and he used to say a
virgin. I was like, "You are a [ __ ]
virgin. The biggest [ __ ] one going.
Speak for your [ __ ] self, virgin
boy. And do you know what he used to say
to me? He used to say, "I wish I was a
virgin." I said, "Why would you wish
something that you already are? You're
the biggest virgin
going. Why would you waste a wish, a
wish upon a jackpot when you already are
a virgin? That's like being a
millionaire, wishing that you're a
millionaire, but you're already a
[ __ ] millionaire. It makes no [ __ ] sense.
That [ __ ] will die a virgin. He
will [ __ ] die. What? He will die a virgin. Die
one. He will die a virgin. the madness. You
mean Oh, yeah. Yeah. That he said that
to fit in. It's the [ __ ] name, bro.
It wasn't to do with her her face or the
way she looks. Nah, bro. It was all to
do with the [ __ ] name. It was all to
do with her name, mate. He's a He's a
copycat. He's a He's a He's a copycat,
mate. That's why he said she was
good-looking because he's a copycat and
he wanted to follow the trend. It's it's
quite often uh it's quite common with uh
people with autism um to copy people,
you know, like and and and follow trends
and be obsessed with it's like the Sher
Co thing. That's his autism.
Imagine, yeah, a little virgin in a [ __ ]
hole or a Kent trying to call me gay
because I don't find a five out of 10
attractive when I have literally been
with more women than him and he's four
years older than me. Imagine that. Like
think think about that. Some little
virgin that don't even have a bed that's
got no [ __ ] money [ __ ] all in his
life still a virgin trying to call
me [ __ ] gay. Even though I've had
more women than him and there's proof of
it because I don't find some [ __ ]
slag that's a five out of 10 attractive.
[ __ ] off you copycat. It's the name. The
the name Chev. It's the
name. He He's a copycat. He is a
copycat. He's a [ __ ] copycat.
I'm going to go get this uh Chinese now
anyways, bro. And
um yeah, [ __ ] eat it cuz I'm Stop,
dude. I'll be back later,
bro. I'm not scared of no ghost, mate.
I'm not a [ __ ] virgin from Kent. I'm
a big [ __ ] Turkish man from London.
Not a [ __ ] Kent virgin. String of
piss physique. You understand me, Steven
Howard? I'm not a [ __ ] virgin from
Kent with a string of [ __ ] That looks
like a [ __ ] string of piss as a
physique. [ __ ] virgin. I'm 30. Big
man grow beard, bro. Still no [ __ ] 30, lad.
Do I look like some little rat face from Kent?
Sh. You don't find her attractive.
You're gay. Do I sound like that [ __ ]
rat face virgin? Do I sound like that
ugly virgin who's never put his dick up
no one? The country's on a grand a
month, which is why he's trying to
[ __ ] find out what where people live
and how they make money. The day I'm a
one grand a month rap boy from Kent is
the day I start looking in the [ __ ]
mirror, mate. Especially if I can't grow a [ __ ]
beard, that's just bad, bro. You know?
Yeah. That's it, lad. He's like, "Oh,
this is how I know this. This is how I
know that." He's a [ __ ] [ __ ] No
wonder he's still a virgin. Like,
imagine, look at the approaches that I
do. Yeah. And do you see how I'm like
just cool with it? Could you imagine
that little autistic virgin trying to go
up to a woman or anyone trying to
socialize? He doesn't even have normal
friends. Steven Albert, he doesn't even
have normal friends. And all of the
people that he has met don't meet him
again, is he? Kenji, Chase. I talk to
Chase every day. And even Chase don't
want to do with him. He can't even
function in a normal environment with
normal people, let alone lose his
[ __ ] virginity. [ __ ] virgin. You
know what I'm saying?
Yeah. The virgin Mary
delayed. Me and PJ went to the Chinese
restaurant once and
um yeah, we got some Chinese people. Not
the not the busiest time of day, but quite
busy. I'm I'm going to come back later.
Yeah, I'm just going to um go get some
food and [ __ ]