So I was doing something.
Sorry matey. Yeah, I was doing something.
People on [ __ ] Reddit block, man.
They're [ __ ] cowards.
I'm going to do a video on dating later. I think
I got some few I got a few things to talk about.
But every single time you go out, it's
like a trigger.
It gives you things to start talking
about and [ __ ] Yeah.
It's a madness.
It is a madness.
It's so mad how women have the dating
game so easy. Timothy,
this woman was like, "Oh, I can't find
anyone. I'm 28." And then she says she
goes on multiple dates a month. I've not
been on a date since
5 months ago. Madness.
It is a madness. It is a madness.
as you're going back to um doing that,
you know, going out approaching and [ __ ] I mean,
no, I don't I don't agree with that. I
I don't I don't agree. I don't agree with that.
No, I don't agree with that.
You know, you can leave the country, you
know, at the end of the day. I don't I
don't agree with that
cuz that's a cycle. See, that's you know
when you're saying that's all you can
do. That's a cycle. That's the thing.
You know, that's a cycle.
There's nothing else you can do here but
try. Yeah, that's the cycle, though.
That's what I'm trying to say. That's the cycle,
you know? That's the actual cycle that
you need to break.
You understand? That's the cycle that
needs to be broken. You need to leave.
That's the whole thing.
I don't agree with that, you know.
No, I don't agree with that at all.
No, I don't agree with that.
He says, "Oh, you're going to go out and
try again?" I don't think I will, bro. Oh yeah.
the white cards. [ __ ] hell, bro. madness.
It's a madness, bro. It is a madness.
Right, I'm gone anyways. I'll be back tomorrow.