finally got um an upload. Yeah. Be the
last time I'm addressing this as well
because I I actually want to address it.
Um because I want to.
So yeah. Um wait to join. Yeah, man.
That's why I leave these people to it.
That's why I don't even respond to them
because it's just that's literally their
whole life is YouTube and self-reflecting.
This is why you don't see me on here
every any anymore every day cuz it's
just the same little low life people
that ain't got nothing.
I Red Star, I these people, they
literally live to be a keyboard warrior.
[ __ ] me, bro. Imagine having that on
your deathbed. And I'm not reacting. I'm
telling you what they are because I want
to tell you what they are. I'm not
reacting. I'm telling you what they are.
What they do every day. They're sad
bastards. Cuz to me it's quite funny.
You know, sad funny. Would I should I
say it's funny? Not really. Cuz I feel
sorry for them. The fact they have to
sit on YouTube all day being a keyboard warrior.
Sad little bastard. But that's why I
don't entertain them because the more
they do it, the more they show that
they're the ones that are skimmed.
They're the ones that are lonely.
They're the ones that have no money. See
what I'm saying? Like the more they do
this, the more you laugh at them because
it shows what they are embarrassing themselves.
That's the whole like that's the good
thing about it, you know? So yeah,
creepy. It is creepy, but it is funny at
the same time.
Peter Belly's got a lot of uh a lot of
middle-aged stalkers, don't he? [ __ ]
You know, I got a lot of middle-aged men
gravitate towards me. It's creepy, but
you know, it's does feel good, you know,
know you're doing something right, but
it is creepy at the same time. What's that?
[ __ ] hell, bro. Yeah.
M is it? Peter buddy's got a lot of middleweight stalkers
that [ __ ] wrong or some [ __ ] Yeah.
Nice to see Red Star still embarrassing
himself on YouTube.
Still embarrassing himself on YouTube.
He ain't got a life. He's got no life
but stalking Peter Belly cuz Peter Belly owns him. Yeah.
You have to laugh at these people, bro.
Sat on YouTube every day recording everything, stalking
shows what their life really is, you
know? It gives it gives their life away, you know.
It feels kind It does feel kind of good
to have that many people jealous of you,
but in a way it's kind of weird cuz it's
like people that are a lot older than me.
It's mad to have so many people jealous
of you, isn't it?
It is really, really weird.
jealous of good old Peterbelly.
They spend a lot of their life on
someone that's supposedly a skin munter.
Is it the [ __ ] hell? They they waste
a lot of their life on someone that's a skin m.
Uh it makes you wonder who the really
who the real skin actually is, doesn't it?
For these people to sit on here doing
what they do every day, it must it shows
you who really is the skin mun.
They give themselves away.
But I'm not entertaining these people
anyways. These little stalkers, little
low lives. Ain't got a life.
Yeah. [ __ ] them, bro. Just wanted to
talk about it, you know?
So weird, is it?
Obsessed with people that they don't
even know. Madness. [ __ ] madness.
It's mad. I feel sorry for them, bro.
These these people clearly have been
bullied their whole life. That's why
they come on here, you know, and [ __ ]
It's obvious, isn't it? obvious.
I'm going to again tomorrow
Oh, I love that, bro. Madness.
I'm [ __ ] tired, bro.
Do you know what? Yeah, I just said I
just said Izzy's name. X's name in quotation.
I just said in quotation brown.
[ __ ] funny, bro. Oh, man. SH Brown. do.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Red star, why do you keep stalking me? You weirdo,
do you want my ass or something? You
[ __ ] weird bastard.
Imagine being Imagine having his life.
[ __ ] sat on YouTube stalking every
[ __ ] day. madness.
Peter B. He's got so many middle-aged
people obsessed with him. Gives me the EBG beats.
I couldn't imagine being jealous of
someone, bro. I could never imagine
being jealous of someone.
I could never imagine being sat on
YouTube jealous of someone every day,
bro. I don't even know.
That's a [ __ ] madness.
That is a madness.
Sat there recording everything all day,
every day. What a loser. They got
nothing but YouTube.
It's all these little weirdos have. They
can't take a day off of it.
[ __ ] can't take a day off your job.
It's all they have.
Not even one day. Not even one day off
of YouTube. They can't take Can't say
that about me, mate.
H just that red star being a stalking weirdo again.
He's got nothing in his life. But
YouTube, that's all he has to skin little M.
All that skin m has got in his life is YouTube.
It's it's it's so obvious now, is it?
It's so obvious now, Stephen. Howard,
that they've got nothing in life but
YouTube. Is it? It's obvious. It's so
Sat on YouTube stalking every day. [ __ ] madness.
Whoever it is, it's a [ __ ] coward.
You're a [ __ ] coward, bro.
Yeah. Yeah, I don't think I'm the skin
mon, bro. I don't think I am, man.
No, I don't think I'm a skin mon, bro.
Cuz if I was a skin mon, you wouldn't be
wasting all day, every day of your life
on me. Yeah, I don't think I'm the skin
mon, bro. I think I think it's you. Yeah.
Who do you reckon it is? Yeah, man.
Are you proud of me for not drinking for
3 weeks? Has it been 3 weeks? Maybe two
weeks. No, no, no. When was Laney's
birthday? a second. One sec.
No, it has been about No, it's been 3 weeks. Yeah,
3 weeks. Big up me.
Been sober for 3 weeks. Yeah. Yeah, man.
I can't wait to join this um porn thing.
[ __ ] knows, bro. Probably a long time.
Yeah, I probably won't be on it for a
long time to be fair, bro.
Nah, I can't be asked. I can't be [ __ ]
Nah, I can't be bothered anymore, bro.
The [ __ ] I have a boyfriend [ __ ] and
that, bro. That's why I stopped
drinking. That's why I stopped like
going out and [ __ ] I mean by going out
I mean going out drinking, you know. I
can't be asked with it, bro. I can't be
annoyed with it.
Not for now, bro. I can't be annoyed with it.
Yeah, I did. I I applied. I did apply.
They're going to email me.
Nah, you don't, man. You don't. That's [ __ ]
It's not It's not a con at all.
No, I'm not. All right, stop being negative.
All that Red Star still stalking me,
Timothy, John Eldridge.
I leave them to it now, bro, because
they show everybody that who the Skint
Mer really is when they're sat on
YouTube doing this all day, every day.
Yeah. I just leave them to it because it
shows everybody what they really are themselves.
So, I just leave them to it. Me, lad. Yeah.
Who do you think that Red Star account is, Timothy?
[ __ ] weirdo. That's who it is.
[ __ ] weirdo, lad. madness.
Well, whoever it is, they're a sad bastard.
Yeah. Three weeks sober, three weeks not
going out drinking. Timothy John Aldridge,
I hope you um I hope you're proud of me.
Hope you're proud of me, lad.
You all right, Grezy?
How you doing?
Yeah, you red star greasy.
Can't wait to get my stonies out the dry
cleaners tomorrow. Greavesy. I can't
wait to get my stonies out the dry cleaners.
Yeah, bro. I'd [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah, I told I told Laney that I was
thinking of joining the industry. She
wasn't very pleased. [Music]
Look at these little snakes on here. Bro,
this is what makes me think these
people. Of course it is his mom. He's
not mine enough to survive. He's just a benefit bum.
You don't know nothing about me, matey.
This Ricky million account is another coward.
Self. Another little self projector.
You know all the You know these people, right?
Yeah. These people on these on these channels, Grezy,
it's so mad that they they have to come
on YouTube every day and self-reflect
their misery onto other people
cuz they're old, lonely people that are wanted. So,
they will um it's just mad like they are
actual losers, bro. Now, if anyone ever
have kids, you should show your kids.
These people on YouTube,
these little losers.
Do you remember that Ricky Millan
account stopped coming on Grezy?
Do you remember? He used to come on my
channel and then when I told him about
his snaky self, I told him about his
snaky self, he stopped coming on here. You remember
Yeah, that's why the brothers just stick
to my channel now. All the brothers, all
the BRs stick to my channel now. Yep.
All the brothers on this channel now. Yeah. I know.
Did that one know you? Oh [ __ ]
Need to make some make a drink in a minute. Yeah.
Do you still think of USA? Is he greasy? Bless you. that shot.
Uh, I'm going to tell the production
company that I'm a virgin.
Nah, I'm not you.
Nah, bro. I'm not you. If I was you, I
would tell them I'm a virgin. We're not
all like you, son. [ __ ] hell.
We're not all like you, matey.
Nah, you got me mixed up with yourself.
If I was you, I'd tell them I'm a
virgin, but there's no need for that.
No, we're not all you, sunshine.
Still using virgin jokes in your 40s.
You people really have got some growing
up to do.
Really got some growing up to do.
Yeah. Yeah. Just back for the day, man.
Just back for the day. You can't even
take a day off of YouTube about [ __ ]
back again. You can't even take one day
off of YouTube. Bye-bye, Timmy. Uh,
you can't even take a [ __ ] day off of
YouTube, mate. Don't tell me about being back again.
You people on YouTube every [ __ ] day. Yeah.
[ __ ] you hell. This is lovely, man.
And the nest calls. That's a B of
Jerry's yesterday. Gre. [Music]
No, that's you people. You live for the
tubes. That's yourselves. You're talking
about yourself. Self projecting.
You people can't even take one day off of YouTube.
That's yourself. You got yourself
confused with me.
You Red Star, right? And like Lord J's
followers without hating and self
projecting on YouTube every day, you
would have nothing. You would literally
have nothing if you couldn't come on,
you know, here every day talking about
yourselves, you know, skin, manta, all
of these things that you are yourselves.
I think you'd actually kill yourselves.
I actually think that you would kill yourselves, bro.
Cuz you ain't got no money to go out and
do anything. You got no friends. You're
scared to leave your house. You'd be
[ __ ] without YouTube and self
projecting. You would be [ __ ] Like it
wouldn't even be funny. Yeah.
What would you do? You got no money to do anything.
You would be [ __ ] man. You would
actually be [ __ ] Really, bro? Yeah.
>> Yeah, it is good. Yeah, I get to save money. Yeah,
I get to save money. I'm not skinn like you people.
So, yeah. I'm not skinn like you people though.
I can go out whenever I want. Can get
what food I want whenever I want. can go
out drinking whenever I want,
but I'd rather just chill, play some Franklin
if that's what you was hinting.
[ __ ] hell. I feel 100 years old, bro.
What the [ __ ] is wrong with my bones,
bro? I feel old, man. Jesus Christ.
Wonder how you people [ __ ] feel.
No, I don't look ill. Nah,
I'm good, man. I'm just tired.
I'm just [ __ ] shattered, mate. Oh,
my little [ __ ] arms all achy. And uh
might be uh I look skinn and depressed.
Self projecting again. What did I tell
you about self-reflecting?
We don't have this. We don't have this
on our channel.
We don't have self projectoring on my channel, son.
That's what I'm saying. Without self
projecting on YouTube, you people would have nothing.
Yeah. You'd have nothing without talking
about yourselves every day, man.
Yeah. I got go dry cleaners tomorrow and
stuff. I got a busy day tomorrow. Should
I do a football back to mine? I can't be bothered.
I'm good, bro. I'm just going to chill,
man. No drinking uh probably asked. Yeah.
May as well lose again. I don't know
what you're talking about. The past two
bets I've won.
No. Past two bets I've won. Don't know
what you're talking about.
You're watching someone else, matey, cuz
you're not watching me.
Do500 pound on the both teams to score.
Now I'm skint mate. I ain't got no money, remember?
So you say,
"Oh, I had McDonald's greaves. Yeah, I
want a McMuffin and a um coffee." Yeah.
Yeah. I'm skint, bro. I've got literally
nothing. Not even £5 to my name. I'm completely skinn. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm completely skint, bro.
Yeah. I've got like not even£5.
Nope. Don't have £5.
I've got about 10p in my bank account.
I've got literally nothing, mate. I got
10 p in my bank account. Oh man, what am
I going to do?
Grez, you want to lend me some money? Nah. Would
they even let you do a 500 pound? Both
teams to score in the in the shop.
Griezy, do you want to um
lend me some money, bro?
Yeah, I've got nothing, bro. Yeah,
I got literally nothing, bro. Like 5 p.
What am I going to do?
You know what? [ __ ] I got enough money
to do what I want to do, mate. And for
me to knowing you to never find out,
I don't bring up money on here. That's
what self-reflectors do. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, I've got nothing. Yep. You keep
telling yourself that. Uh, bye-bye.
Skittles, man. Self projecting again.
I don't even know why I bother coming
back on this self projecting place.
Grievy, I'm gone tomorrow.
Just thought I'd come and say hi to you,
Grezy. Just same self-p projecting skin
people every day talking about themselves.
Uh, what do we get ourselves into, bro?
These people call people skint cuz
they're skint. That's why I don't bother
with this anymore, Grezy. I just find I
just watch like a lot of GTA videos and
stuff cuz it's always the same
atmosphere on here.
It's the same atmosphere, bro. That's
why I don't really come on here like much anymore
cuz of the same repeating and that.
That's why I just go on different communities. I'm 27
Nah, not me, man. Not me. It's just the
same [ __ ] every time you go on here.
Skin people trying to call you skin.
Stealth reflectors stalking red star.
It's just the same atmosphere.
It's the same [ __ ] every day.
It's the same [ __ ] every day on this
man. [ __ ] same repeating people.
500 on both teams to score. [ __ ] hell.
I can keep away. I can take a day off of
YouTube. You can't.
But I can take a day off of YouTube. You can't.
That's already been proven.
Now self projecting.
I've took days off of YouTube, weeks off
of YouTube. You can't take one day off
of YouTube talking about yourself again.
Talking about yourselves again.
Shows how bad your life is. It shows how
bad your lives are that you you people
in your 30s and 40s, right? And you and
you talk about people every day that you
don't know. You sit on YouTube for
[ __ ] years all day every day talking
about people that you don't know because
in reality you are the ones that are
skin. You are the ones that have got no
life. You are the mongos. That's why you
sit online every day for [ __ ] years
doing the same old boring [ __ ] cuz you
just got nothing. Yeah. So yeah,
anyways, I'm gone. See you next week. Bye.