But I'm telling you, yeah, it's [ __ ]
packing [ __ ] Sans. Seriously,
boy in the bed in it. I can't stop
saying that, you know, but I don't know
what's [ __ ] wrong with me. I feel
something wrong with me. That's like
stuck in my head. That is, bro. I don't
know why, but it [ __ ] is.
I'm born in a bed with no bed in it.
I don't know why I keep saying that,
bro. It's stuck in my [ __ ] head.
Yeah, the merch is coming soon, by the
way. And I'm not selling it. I'm just giving it, you know,
[ __ ] hilarious, bro.
In the bed [ __ ] man. It
love it, mate, bro. Love it.
In the [ __ ] bed [ __ ] man. [ __ ] it.
How do you even come out with these things? Still virgin.
You're still [ __ ] virgin.
Where is it?
>> Yeah, he always self projects. He calls
me skin and I've got money and he calls
me [ __ ] skin. Yeah, all of it self
projecting, bro. But to be fair, he's
not the only one that does it. He's not
Yeah. He says that um he's the one with
the gambling problem. That's why he
tells me that I've done my balls, but I
don't even [ __ ] gamble in anything
but the [ __ ] football. It's all self projection.
Yeah, it's all self projection, bro.
All of it is. But he's not the only one
that does it.
[ __ ] I ain't drunk for [ __ ] ages, bro.
Yeah, [ __ ] ages. Going to go collect
that wind them in a bit and then
probably get some food.
Probably get some chicken. Yeah,
probably get some chicken. Yeah.
skin in the bed sit with no bed in it.
Bro, I can't stop [ __ ] saying that,
you know, bro. It's stuck in my [ __ ]
head. Yeah, I've got I've got £59 to collect,
so I'm going to collect it later when I
go get some food.
Yeah. When I go get some food, I'm going
to collect it.
What's the day today? Sunday. What's Sunday? Um, yeah.
Yeah, bro. [ __ ] love it.
All right, Timmy. Why do I have a lot of
stalkers on here, bro? A lot of people
on here stalk me.
Why do I have a lot of stalkers? Why do
I have loads of old men that gravitate towards me?
He gives Peter Belly the EBGBs.
So creepy, isn't it? It's a creepy community. Yeah, man.
You got Timmy calling people [ __ ]
skin and he doesn't know what people
have. This is what makes me laugh with
this [ __ ] community, bro. And they
don't know what people have.
So, you know, every time they call you
skin, they're talking about themselves.
Virgin, you're the only virgin and
you're the only skint one. Well, not
you're not the only one. Non selected is
also a skin virgin, but you know, you're
talking about yourself to me. You really
really really are just talking about yourself.
Talking about yourself, bro. You're
virgin and your skin. Talking about
yourself. I've been shown with more
money, more women, but you call me the
virgin. Timmy, have a look in the
mirror. Please have a look in the [ __ ] mirror,
mate. I've got more money than you'd
ever have. You're the one that's
addicted to gambling, not me. Self
projecting again. That's all you, Lord
Jay, and his followers do is talk about
yourselves. You are the one that's a
gambling addict with no money, not me.
And you're also a virgin as well. Yeah,
you're talking about yourself again.
And the only reason I don't show you
money is because every time I show you
money, you run away. So I'm not
entertaining your little self-projecting
games anymore. Been there, done that,
won the t-shirt. I'm not showing you
[ __ ] Every time you get shown money,
you run away and pretend it never
happened. That's why I'm not showing you [ __ ]
I ain't showing you [ __ ] all. So yeah,
you can keep saying that I'm skinn. You
don't know what I have deep down and you know it.
Yeah, exactly. I'm not showing you no
money. I already showed you money and
you ran away. I'm not showing you [ __ ] all. Oh, [ __ ] Yep.
I'm not showing you [ __ ] all, mate.
I am not showing you. [ __ ] all
you little selfreflector.
You've been shown money before. You've
been shown 1,300. You've been shown
thousands. I'm not showing you nothing
ever again. I'm not showing you no money.
Yeah, he really is at rock bottom. Bro,
I don't even gamble in anything but the
football. I'm not even addicted to gambling.
You know, I play roulette like maybe
once every 3 months, if that. There's no
time limit. I don't even play that [ __ ]
He's just self- projecting.
That's what I'm saying. He's self projecting.
I think it is sad at 42 that you're
still playing them machines. Didn't you
learn, Timmy? Didn't you learn from [ __ ]
when you got that IVA?
Like, I can't believe you're still
playing them machines. Like, if you're
playing online, okay, I mean, it's still
bad, but fair enough. Like, I don't,
bro, I don't touch any of that [ __ ] The
only thing I bet on is the football
occasionally, bro. And that's literally
it. You should have known about them
machines and that roulette.
I gave up because of the mood swings.
They weren't giving me It weren't making
me skin. I just didn't like the m You
know, I just didn't like the [ __ ]
mood swings. You know, there's a time in
in life where, you know, you have to get
your priorities straight.
And it seems like at 42, you still ain't
got yours straight.
Why do you think I don't go out drinking
much anymore? I can afford it. I can go
out now if I wanted to. I could go out
all week if I wanted to. But I have
other things to be doing, other things
to be saving for, other places to be
going. You are still playing them
machines. You will never learn. Never
ever ever ever learn.
You know, fair enough. If you went to an
actual casino Yeah. after a night out
cuz I And trust me, Timmy, I've gambled
more than you. Trust me, Timmy, I have
gambled. I have gambled more than you. I
don't care if you're 42, Timmy. I have
gambled more than you. Trust me, I've
gambled a lot of money. I've lost a lot
of money. I've won a lot of money. Yes,
I have, Timmy.
Yes, I have. You know, I live in London.
How many times I used to hit them
casinos and I just kind of got bored of
it. Yeah, same [ __ ]
No, it's not fair to tell stories,
Timmy. I have gambled more than you literally
but if you go to casino after night out
I mean yeah I mean that's different you know
but you would have thought at a stage in
life you would have you know learned but
you don't so
virgin boy is going to end up like you
skin at 42 still a virgin like yeah till he
really [ __ ] mate.
Yeah, more lies. I have gambled more
than you, Timmy.
Yeah. Why do you still play the machines anyways? Huh?
I'm going to collect this 50 odd pound.
Buy some food with it.
Well, you need to seriously grow up to
me. Seriously grow up.
Did you have like no goals when you was younger?
Like I know you got disabilities and
[ __ ] but like didn't you have any goals
when you was younger?
You're wasting your life playing them machines, you know?
waste wasting your life playing them
[ __ ] machines for [ __ ] sake.
that I mean I done 100 pound the other
day there in roulette over a week ago
because bro like I hadn't done it for
months and I thought [ __ ] it why not 100
pound like it's that's not you know it's
mad what you do what you do is mad
what you do is mad I don't you know I
don't even get urges anymore to play the
machines or play with it I don't get
urges I don't get gambling urges
I swear to God I don't
cuz it's Like
I'd rather [ __ ] go out with the money
drinking or you know book a holiday with
the money and stuff. You know what I'm
saying? Like when you some people some
people need to learn the hard way, you
know, like I did. But this [ __ ] [ __ ]
got an IVA and he still hasn't learned.
So I mean even learning the hard way for
you didn't work. So,
and then you just realize how much time
you waste doing it. Like, it's not even
just money. Like, time and [ __ ] Like,
it's madness. [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] that, bro.
But then I've gambled a lot. So maybe I
just outgrew it. I don't know. [ __ ]
Yeah. I used to love gambling, bro.
[ __ ] them casinos. Used to love gambling.
But, you know, it was part of our lifestyle.
I never dumped my [ __ ] balls in. Yeah.
Yeah. I can't believe you're still
playing them machines, though. No.
I can live off £500, but to be fair, I
don't drink. And
he says, "Like you, not anymore.
I don't go out anymore. [ __ ] hell.
I don't go out anymore, matey. No.
Do you know what? I was speaking to my
um Indonesian friend. I said, "Oh, we
going out drinking and stuff." And he
was like, um, he said, "No, no." So,
really? He's like, "Nah."
I said, "Oh, to be fair, I haven't
really been going out either. We must
have outgrew it.
I feel like I, you know, you could do
other stuff with the money and and [ __ ] you know,
and whatever, but
he was agreeing as well." So we kind of
don't even go out anymore. Investment
holidays, whatever. Like I just it
and I need a break from the dating as well. So
So obviously, you know,
so we must have gave up at the same time.
Like I said, it's not about the money. I
used to go out drinking on a lot less. Bro,
when LT start first introduced me to
these things where I started [ __ ]
I used to go out with a lot less. Trust
me, I used to go out with a lot less.
So, it's not it's not that it's not that
bad at all.
So yeah, Timmy, when are you going to
stop these? Uh, that made me laugh when
you said £50 for a night out. Oh, that's
another thing you said. Oh, I wanted to
pay for the night out. £50. Yeah.
£50 for a night out. Jesus Christ That's interesting.
I didn't know a night out could cost £50.
It normally cost about 70 70 80 78.
I like that woman from Finland, you
know. I was really thinking about her
last night. I've got to save us. Well, I
need to change it to uh Finnish Izzdy.
She seems really nice, you know. No stuckupness,
mature, no [ __ ] behavior.
seems nice, you know.
Very rare you meet a woman that's not a [ __ ]
to be honest.
Very, very, very rare.
I spoke on a bit though.
But the thing is is that like I can't um
say something without coming across as too forward.
I wish there was people like that here, bro.
And just the way she types, you can just
tell that she's not stuck up.
She doesn't think she's the [ __ ]
Like, I don't know. It's hard to explain
cuz she's [ __ ] other women do. It's bad.
I also like the fact that they're the
same age as me. I'm two months older than them.
It's always good when you're two months
older than someone same age as them.
I think I was the same age as that
Indian before who I went on a date with
on my birthday
and then she was nowhere to be seen.
She was nowhere to be seen
after she left. Another
time waster, huh? [Music] Madness. Madness.
You need to stop this whole uh
[ __ ] roulette [ __ ] bro. You
seriously seriously do it. You know,
back at the old house. Yeah, I was still
doing it every two months. Every two
months, I think I chuck like 250 on the roulette online,
but I remember not playing them machines
for like 6 months.
[ __ ] months, bro.
So hard to get money now. I wouldn't
want to waste it, you know?
Feel like I didn't waste a lot of money
with the house. I feel like I still done
what I wanted to do. I still done all I
wanted to do, you know? What's up? One time.
What you need sometime is a nice break.
A nice break from drinking on women.
It's so nice. It's so so lush.
Oh man, it's nice having a break.
I want to go Manchester again.
This is weird cuz I've been a [ __ ]
million times. I don't know. I just want
to go Manchester again, man.
for like two days.
That'll be [ __ ] ace, bro.
cuz yeah, Timmy, you keep going back on
to me. But the thing is is that
everybody knows I don't gamble anymore.
So it's like I don't know why you keep
trying to tell people that I gamble. I
don't even gamble.
Like I said, just on the football,
but I don't even, you know what I mean?
I just gamble on the football for extra
money and fun.
Think about it. I won four bets out of seven.
Four out of seven. I've done about seven
bets since the season started and I've
won four of them about seven. So Yeah, man. [Applause]
Just going to go pick up my winnings and
go get some food.
go for a long walk.
I need to stop going to bed at 5, man,
cuz I keep [ __ ] waking up at some ridiculous times. So,
just get some chicken to be honest. Yeah.
Yeah. I want to go Finland and see that
woman, bro. I might go.
I might go and see that woman.
Anything in castle? That's where I met my mommy.
I was thinking of her boobs yesterday,
man. [ __ ] hell. She had some [ __ ]
nice boobs, bro.
She had some nice [ __ ] boobs, bro.
Well, obviously. Duh.
Then I want to go see her, man. See what
she's saying. Is it
It's so weird. I met on a Sunday.
Touch them, squeeze them, suck them, everything.
Virgin boy can't do that. He's too skinn.
Yeah, I want to go to Manchester again,
Wadley. I don't know why. I just get I
keep getting this urge to go Manchester.
Every time I see these things on
Instagram. Yeah. Where they're doing
like interviews. They're interviewing people
and [ __ ] it's on nights out in
Manchester. It just looks so lit. I
don't know why I just miss Manchester, man.
It was fun, you know. fun, bro.
Manchester's fun, bro.
Remember when I got when I got um when I
got stuck in Manchester cuz of the train strikes?
So, I went there Friday. I was supposed
to come back to Saturday, but I stayed
the Saturday. It was a madness.
I think I had actually almost run out of
money to be fair.
No, maybe not. But I don't know what
happened there, but it was fun.
Yeah, I don't got much no more, but I'd
rather save money.
really would rather say buddy matey.
Timmy said it's £50 for a night out.
That's [ __ ] hilarious, bro. £50 for a night out.
No, it's like £80.
I don't know, man. Mine have all been different.
Normally, it's about 60 to 80.
There's been a time before when it was
120, but I was really hammering the
drinks. And there's been a time before
when it was 250.
Yeah, it's about 250, but that was
really hammering it, bro.
Yeah, 250. Really hammering it.
[ __ ] hell, man. I remember that time
as well. That was with the army lads.
Yeah, it's normally about
It's normally about 80.
Normally about 80.
[ __ ] 50 [ __ ] pounds.
Nah, it's madness.
Whoa, this guy is an idiot on Reddit,
bro. He says, "I'm not going to sugar
coat it, bro. I think you're coming on
way too strong with them." When can
somebody tell me what that means one
day? Coming on too strong. I'd love to
know what that means. Still, no one's
ever explained it to me. Having gotten
this many women's number them
responding, that always a good thing.
But from my perspective, I do think you
are dropping the ball by asking for a
date immediately. Need at least a week's
worth of text cover just for her to feel
comfortable enough to meet up and that
date. Well, honestly, I'm coming to
learn that. No, you're not. I don't
agree with that at all because you try
to keep somebody interested for like a week.
I don't agree with that at all because
there's been women that agreed to meet
me and they never. So, what you're
saying is complete [ __ ]
cuz there's also women that actually
agreed to meet me
and no, you meet someone, you text them
for a few days, and then you want to
meet them. That's it's not a dating app.
It's approaching them. There's a there's
a big difference.
You've met them, you've spoke to them,
and then you're texting them. Yeah. 3
days is enough. You don't need to be
texting somebody for [ __ ] weeks.
What the [ __ ] bro?
No, that is [ __ ] That is absolute
bollocks because you can't you can't
see they see what they're trying to do
again. They're trying to put the blame
on to you, you know.
Look, you need to get people when
they're interested whilst they're still
interested. You texting someone for a
week, they're going to lose interest.
That gives them time to find other options.
I don't I don't agree with that.
Um it shouldn't be at least a week. It
should be a week maximum.
That's the longest. Obviously, just
Finland lives in a different country, so
it's different. But no, I don't I don't
agree with that. You know, London,
London's a big, you know, London's a big
place. You know, if you speak to
somebody and you get their number, then
within 10 messages, you should be
arranging to meet cuz you've met them in
person. You've not met them on a dating
app. You've met them you've met them in person.
So, no, I don't agree with that.
I don't agree with that at all. Sorry.
Yeah, that is bollocks.
That is absolute bollocks, bro.
So what you get? So say so say you
approach a woman's number. So say you
approach a woman, right? And you get her number.
I So you're supposed to speak to her for
what? Two weeks before meeting her. What
the [ __ ] What? When you when you've met
someone in that in person,
believe what they want us believe.
Look, banned again.
to me what coming up too strong means. I
don't know what that means. I've heard
it a million times, but I don't know
what it actually means.
Can somebody explain to me what that means, please?
I'd love for somebody to explain to Tell
me what that means.
So, you get a woman's number, right? And
you're supposed to talk them. You're
supposed to speak to them for two weeks,
which is [ __ ]
half of a month. So, let's just say that
we went out today, right? And we got
someone's number. So, what we're
supposed to speak to them for two weeks,
which is half of a month before meeting
them. That does not make no sense whatsoever.
Like, that literally makes no sense
at all. Like, unless it's on a dating app,
that's why I used to go out the Thursday
and try to meet somebody on a Saturday,
Sunday. That's enough. Once you've spoke
to someone for [ __ ] you know, I I
don't agree with that at all. It's not a
dating app. It's meeting someone in
person. They're they're two different
things. There's literally two complete different things. It's
that is that is that is [ __ ] madness.
A week's minimum.
It's because back in the day, right, I'd
have people that
wanted to meet me, right, and I never
had the money, you know? Maybe I done my
balls or whatever, like seven years ago,
eight years ago, whatever it was. I
never used to get as much money, whatever.
And um and obviously
I couldn't beat them again because they
obviously found someone else. I don't
agree with that.
A week minimum. So you go out to a bar,
you meet a woman and what? You're going
to be talking to her for two weeks
before meeting her. Yet she lives in the
same city as you.
I don't agree with that. No.
I don't agree with that at all.
love for somebody to explain to me one
day what coming on too strong means
just one day I would love somebody to
explain that to me
yeah it's okay for a woman to want to
meet you straight away double standards
I would love one day for somebody to
explain that to me.
Coming on too strong.
I would love to know what that means.
what coming on too strong means.
I would love to know what that means. [ __ ] sake.
Coming on too strong. I would love to
know what that means.
Can somebody explain it to me, please?
Cuz it's just doesn't seem to have any
substance behind any of it.
I don't understand it. Okay. Coming on too strong.
But it's okay.
But as But if a woman wants to come on
too strong, that's completely fine. If a
woman wants to meet you straight away,
that's that's completely fine.
Interesting. But you you you you don't
message someone and try to meet them
within four days. [ __ ] you're coming
on too strong. [ __ ] hell. I would
love to know what that means one day.
I'm paying some really good money for
somebody to tell me that. Coming on too [ __ ] strong.
Any excuse in it.
for [ __ ] half a [ __ ] year, 10
years before meeting them. It's not a
dating app. This is not a [ __ ] dating app, bro.
Try that out.
I would love to know what coming on too strong means.
I would love for somebody to tell me one
day what coming on too strong means.
I'll pay some good money, you know, to
to know what that means.
But it's okay for [ __ ]
But it's okay for a woman to say
straight away that she wants to meet you
on Tuesday for a steak meal. If you done
that, mate, all the simps would be
[ __ ] chasing you with a [ __ ] axe.
I would love to know what coming on too strong means.
I would love to I would love to know, you know,
but it's okay for women to [ __ ] say
they want to meet somebody within the
first message. Oh, that's fine. Nah, but
you you trying to meet somebody within
four [ __ ] days, mate. You [ __ ]
coming on too strong. What the [ __ ]
You You try to meet somebody within four
days, mate. You're [ __ ] coming on too
[ __ ] strong. It's enough of that. You
don't want to speak to somebody for two
weeks wasting your time.
You You You're coming on too strong.
That boy, I need um I need your advice on something.
I need your advice on something, please, son.
So, I was speaking to this guy on
Reddit, right? And um I was showing him
like messages from women that I've
approached um and obviously some that
arranged to meet me and didn't. He he
chose to ignore them ones because that
didn't suit him. That didn't suit the
the tie he was wearing for some reason.
And he was saying about how I was coming
on too strong, whatever the [ __ ] that
means. I don't think we'll ever know
what that actually means to this day. Um
and he said, "Oh, you need to speak to
them for a minimum of a week." I said,
"What?" So what? You approach a woman in
a bar and you get their number and
you're supposed to speak to them for
what? Two [ __ ] weeks before meeting
them even though you've met in person. I
mean, what the [ __ ] I said, bro.
Yeah, but bro, that's that's what you
need to do before they lose interest.
Yeah, but no, no, no, no, no, no. But
but but the difference is that's not
coming on too strong. Wanting to meet
somebody in 4 days. What do you want
somebody to do? speak to someone for 10
years before meeting them. Like, I don't
understand. Like, what the [ __ ]
That's what you're supposed to do. Show
interest and try to meet them. Well,
what what are you supposed to do to
speak to someone for two weeks? There's
no need to speak to someone for two
weeks. You want to be meeting You want
to be trying to meet somebody within
them first five messages of people that
you've approached. I'm not talking about
people you've met online.
And no, you want to be meeting somebody
within 4 days maximum. You don't need to
wait a week. You don't need to wait two.
You've met them in person. On a dating
app, like I said, it's different. You
know, it's it's it's a bit different.
You know, there's no first impression,
but bro, that is [ __ ]
And another thing is, right,
what the [ __ ] And another thing is that
boy. Yeah. Is you know when I met USA
Izzy, right? Do you know what her first
message was to me? Do you know what her
first message was? Oh, do you want to
meet up Tuesday? Let's go for a steak.
But me, you try to [ __ ] meet somebody
within four [ __ ] days. You're coming
on too [ __ ] strong. But any of these
women, they can do whatever they [ __ ]
want. They can meet you when they want.
They can come on too strong as much as
they want. But you, mate, you coming on
too strong, mate. If you're [ __ ]
speaking to somebody for [ __ ] 4 days,
you know what I mean? The double
standard is insane.
Bark it out. I I don't even think it
means anything. I think it's just
something someone says, you know, coming
on too strong. So what? You get a number
and what? You want somebody to text
somebody for 10 years before meeting
them? Is that is that what you want?
Like it's ridiculous, bro. They've
always got excuses.
It's like you don't need to try to keep
someone interested for 2 weeks. You
don't need to do any of that. You know,
you meet someone on Thursday, they
should be happy to meet you the Saturday
or the Sunday the latest. There's no
week minimum two weeks. No, bro. You've
approached them. You don't need to
[ __ ] What? What are you talking
about? You know, like what the [ __ ]
The double standards is mental, bro. I
swear that is just something someone says.
Coming on too strong. I think it just
me. It's just something some people say
in it. It's got to be just what some people say.
I've had someone [ __ ] come on to me,
make sexual advances towards me, and
they were trying to tell people I was
coming on too strong. Could you imagine
you done any of that [ __ ] Could you
imagine you done any of that [ __ ] You
The simps would kill you. The simps
would [ __ ] go mad and kill you.
Bro, you're coming on too strong and
[ __ ] ribbit. You know, you know what
they're doing it, bro. You know what
they would do.
Simps are insane, bro.
So, you want me to speak to someone for
what? What? You want me to speak to
somebody for a month?
Yeah, I live in London. What the [ __ ]
I don't understand it, bro.
So, you want me to speak to somebody for
for a month before meeting them?
Oh my god.
If I done what if I done what that USA
Easy done, bro, I'd never hear the last of it
saying want to meet straight away. Um,
if I want to meet her straight away and
I come on to her straight away, bro, it
it's okay for them, but it's if you want
to meet somebody within 3 days and not
waste your time, apparently you're
coming on too strong.
I hate that saying, bro. It's so
[ __ ] You know,
it doesn't even make any sense. You know,
you're [ __ ] coming on too [ __ ] strong, matey.
That's perfect, bro. You meet somebody
on a Wednesday, Thursday, you meet them
on a Saturday. What's wrong with that?
Oh, you know, you agree to meet and you
text every day until then. There's
nothing wrong with that. You want to be
meeting these people as soon as you can,
you know? It's that's how it is.
It's madness, bro. How they try to use
you trying to meet them,
you know, and not waste your time as as
an excuse. It's [ __ ] madness.
I'd love to know what that means, Mom.
I'd love to know what that means.
But a woman, a woman can come on too strong.
A woman can try and beat you straight
away, and that's fine. Okay.
Madness. And another thing I needed to
address as well was that how if you
don't eat if you don't eat [ __ ] they
they call you gay, but if a woman
doesn't suck dick, there's nothing
there's nothing wrong with her.
I don't know. I'm thinking of doing
another video, you know. I think some
things needs to be addressed.
If you don't eat vagina, you're gay. But
if a woman don't suck dick, then she
doesn't suck dick.
Makes you wonder and it makes me wonder.
What about you people? [Music]
This madness, bro.
It is [ __ ] madness.
So, we can't try and meet somebody
within 3 days because we're coming on too strong. Wow.
It really is madness, isn't it?
Madness, bro. Madness. [ __ ] hell.
Right, I need to go out soon, man. I
need to [ __ ] go get some food.
Well, I'll be back later. Yeah.