Lovely. Oh, lovely matey.
Yeah. Went for a lovely little stroll today.
Went to the pub to have a Coke.
Yeah, man. Still not drinking. [Music] bro.
Yeah, it's getting boring, bro.
Yeah, I went for a walk today. Picked up
these [ __ ] winnings
and went to the pub. had a coke and got some chicken.
Uh, you want 450? That's nice.
Going to spend on an escort. You You get
more escorts. You'll get a few escorts with 450.
Oh, it was just £40 on a football bet.
Yeah, it was only £40 on a football bet. Weren't much.
Yeah, it for the lows. [ __ ] escort.
Yeah, exactly. Yeah, that's what I mean. Yeah, man.
You say is that it? But it paid for the
dry cleaning. The dry cleaner was £30.
I put 20 in
and I won £59.
So I paid for the dry cleaning, isn't
it? So yeah.
Yeah, the dry cleaning was £30. I got my
Stone Island jumpers dry cleaned and my
and my Ralph Lauren top. So yeah.
So [ __ ] it.
Oh man. Yeah, I went to the pub and had
a pint of Coke because supermarkets
closed early Sunday in it. So,
I went to get some chicken, bro.
Need to go cinema. Oh, I need to go
cinema in a couple of days.
How did you win that 450?
How did How did you win it?
Yeah, I'm going as well. I need to watch
The Strangers chapter 2. [ __ ] hell.
I'm up about£500 from the football in
the past two months.
Yeah, I don't touch them machines anymore. Me?
I don't touch them anymore.
Oh, that's good, man.
Yeah, I don't touch them anymore. I
don't touch the machines. [ __ ] that.
Absolutely [ __ ] that. You've been watching Timmy.
Absolutely [ __ ] that, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. [ __ ] that, bro. [ __ ] that.
I'm not playing that, bro.
I'm not playing them machines again.
I don't think I'll ever play the machines again.
Do you play online roulette or no?
Yeah, I had some pork chops.
or some pork making some sandwiches and [ __ ]
They're the They're the way to lose fast money.
Yeah, they're the way to lose fast money. Yeah.
Nah, they're the way to they're the way
to lose money.
Lose money fast.
Still a lot though. So you lost £300 a
week. It's still a lot, isn't it?
That's a lot though, isn't it? lose. Yeah.
No, I only do football bets.
Yeah, I only do football bets, man.
I don't get the buzz for gambling
anymore like I used to, you know.
Nons legs is skin as well. He's skinned
a skinn. He's not the only one that's
skinned. Nons legs are skin there.
Non legs skin. Yeah.
Yeah, I've not drunk in like a month, bro.
Yeah, I'm not drunk in a month.
I'll go again at some point. Not going
to be bothered.
Yeah. How much are they?
Yeah. I don't need to buy any more
clothes for a very long time, bro.
I got some nice Stone Island jumpers,
nice trainers. I'm good, bro.
Yeah, you're mad paying that. You're mad
paying that, bro.
I would never pay that.
[ __ ] that, bro. You're mad if, bro, even
paying £310 for Stone Island jump was a
lot to be fair.
You're cray bro. I'd never pay that. No way.
[ __ ] that, lad. [ __ ] that. See, with me,
I'd rather go on holiday with that money.
I just rather go on holiday with that money. Yeah,
you can though cuz that's ridiculous.
Even you know and I've got Stone Island
jumpers. You can. That's ridiculous.
Trust me. No, that is ridiculous.
I'd rather go on holiday with that, bro.
And I'd never pay that. Even when I had
like loads more money than I do now, I
still wouldn't do that. Bro, [ __ ] that. You're mad.
But the Stone Island jumpers are nice,
though. I mean, they last forever, so I
think they're worth the money. But
that's ridiculous, bro.
Gambled more than 2,000, bro.
There's only I've only gambled more than
a thousand once. So,
and it doesn't justify it because when
we was gambling, we were trying to win more money
and we didn't plan to lose a,000. We
were chasing it. That's the difference.
And I've only lost more than a thousand once. Yeah.
No, I'd never play that. [ __ ] that.
It's I guess. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, that's fair enough then, bro.
That's fair enough.
No, that's never happened. You've never
seen me lose over a grand. I've only
ever lose over a grand once and that was online.
No, you haven't. You really haven't.
It's never happened. Never.
Not in one go.
No, you really haven't, bro. You really
haven't. Cuz it's only ever happened once online.
And then I've lost £1,000 before as
well, but not over that. I've only lost
over £1,000 once.
When should I go drinking again? [ __ ] knows.
All right. Bye, bro.
[ __ ] knows, bro. I'm trying to hold it
off until my birthday to be honest.
Who knows? Who knows?
Yeah, I've got perfume.
I got perfume. Nice, man.
I need to take my stuff out the wash. Oh, [ __ ]
Yeah, I've got after shave as well. Dior
Sage after shave. Yeah, man.
Yeah, they did steal it. So, I bought
another one. [ __ ]
That's the whole reason why I bought another one. You [ __ ] Obviously,
I swear some of you people on here
really are spasticated. [ __ ] hell.
That's why I bought another one. Hello. No.
I learned to speak to him.
He called me the other day. I was kind
of pissed off. I don't want to hear
about these people anymore. Like [ __ ]
Skint Knobs legs and [ __ ] all of
these people and [ __ ] I mean, [ __ ] that. No,
that [ __ ] skin [ __ ] nons legs.
I sure am.
Well, you can't have me.
What do you reckon would have happened
if I went out drinking today approaching
Timothy John Eldridge?
What do you think would have happened?
I like flying. [Music]
I know. He's a skin bastard, bro. He's
such a skinned [ __ ] And yeah, bro. 13
fucking,000 pounds in in three years is
[ __ ] skin. That's not worth [ __ ]
no life experience, is it?
I would pull. I don't think so, bro. I
don't think so.
If it was going to happen, it would have
happened by now. I'm sure, John.
Yeah, I'm sure. If it would have
happened, it would have happened by now. Would you agree?
Yeah, he stalked all my sloppy seconds in.
No, I definitely wouldn't have bought.
If it was going to happen, it would have
happened by now.
You seem to think it makes me laugh that
you just think one day you're going to
go out and it's going to change.
That's what makes me laugh
is that you think that you're just going
to go out one day and it's going to change.
Oh, you seem to forget the past. You know,
you seem to think that like one day it's
just going to change.
>> How how can it change? It would have
changed by now. It's been years. Things
don't just change like that all of a sudden.
Oh, use my beard.
Use my beard as an excuse. Oh my god.
Use my beard as an excuse. What the
[ __ ] I would say that's a new one, but
it's not a new one.
Using my beard as an excuse.
Jesus Christ. That's just desperate, bro.
Makes me look stinky. No, it doesn't.
Cuz every time I go out, I get my beard
I get my beard groomed.
Nope. Every single time I go out, I get
my beard groomed.
Nope. There's nothing wrong with my
beard. I get professionally. Uh, it's
definitely not the reason
because I've gone out without a beard.
So, it definitely isn't the reason.
What's the story? [ __ ] all, bro. Just
chilling, man. Take the watch out. Uh,
it's definitely not the reason cuz I'
I've actually shaved the beard before
and tried. So, it's definitely not the reason.
I never asked for your opinion. I just I
just said it's never going to change. I
never I never asked for your opinion,
bro. Why would I ask for your opinion? I
never asked for your opinion. It's never
going to change trying to blame my
[ __ ] beard. It's not nothing to do
with a beard. It's to do with these
stuckup [ __ ] in this country. It's
nothing to do with a [ __ ] beard.
What the [ __ ] bro? Blaming a beard.
Yeah, [ __ ] off. No one's getting
offensive. And I haven't even asked for
your opinion anyways. I said to you, how
the [ __ ] is it going to change all of a sudden about?
That's good for you, bro. Uh,
no one's getting defensive. I never
asked for your opinion either. Why would
I ask your opinion when I know more than
anyone how it's like in this country
with these women? Why would I ask Why
would I be asking for an opinion?
I know what they're like.
I've known what they're like for years, these women.
So why why would I ask for your opinion?
That don't make sense.
I didn't ask for your opinion.
I know what they're like. [ __ ] up
They're [ __ ] timewasting [ __ ]
stuck up [ __ ] That's what they
are. Give the [ __ ]
>> Why not ask your opinion?
Blaming my [ __ ] beard. Oh my [ __ ]
god. That's such a desperate attempt.
Take the blame off of women. It's madness.
I don't know why we're having this
conversation cuz I'm not even involved
with the whole thing anymore.
The whole dating thing. I'm not asked
with it, bro. I don't give a [ __ ] about it.
You know what I'm saying?
Bringing it up, bro. Madness.
Oh, it's cold, isn't it?
It has got cold. Oh man.
[ __ ] mad. [ __ ] mad. [Music] always.
What is it with me in that [ __ ] skate
with my beard though? That's a madness.
I'm pretty sure there's people out there
that like beards,
you know. There's got to be people out
there that like beards.
You would have thought, so
you would [ __ ] thought there was
people out there that [ __ ] likes
[ __ ] beards. You know what I'm saying?
What a desperate lame excuse.
to take the blame of all women. Oh,
[ __ ] hell, bro. [ __ ] be dead. [ __ ] hell. [ __ ] [ __ ]
That Timothy John El is just a [ __ ] troll. Obvious.
They seem to wake up one day and seem to
forget all of the things that's
happened. They're [ __ ] Hey, little bro.
[ __ ] blaming someone's beard.
So what? No one's in a relationship with
people that have got beards. Is that
what you're saying, lad?
So you So
So no one
So no one um So no one's in a
relationship with people that's got beards.
Think about what you're saying, bro. cuz
you compare me all the [ __ ] time.
It's just excuses. Just excuses. [Music]
Mudly excuses for women.
Yeah, well, go save up.
He's trying to say my beard is why I can't pull.
Nope. I've worked before.
And people even people with cars and
jobs don't get women.
Yeah, pretty much. No, they don't. Women
don't care about people that's got jobs.
Most people have got jobs.
Most people have got jobs, do they?
[ __ ] Women don't care about people that
got that have got jobs because most
people have got jobs. Most people work.
I was a landlord. Used to have loads and
loads of money. still have money but
just not load loads that I used to have.
Never change anything.
That's [ __ ] That's cap.
Anyways, I don't know why we're talking
about this, bro. I'm going Thailand to
get away from all this [ __ ]
I'm [ __ ] I'm like I'm leaving. So, I
don't even know why I'm talking about this [ __ ] anymore.
How did it even come up in conversation?
What the [ __ ]
I'm leaving to get away from this [ __ ]
You know what I mean?
You know how it is. Yeah.
Girls ain't to be all and
I never said they were.
I never said they were, Bob.
I went to the pub today to drink a coke.
I just went for a long walk. I didn't
drink or anything.
Just trying to save a bit of money, you know. Yeah. Yeah, man.
But yeah, even if you have a job, you're
still not going to meet anyone. So, yeah. Oh, [ __ ]
But like I said, I was tempted to go out yesterday.
Yeah, I was tempted to go out yesterday for sure.
Only cuz the stonies Oh [ __ ]
I have moved on with life. I have moved
on with life, bro. What the [ __ ] I
don't approach anymore. I haven't drunk.
I have accepted it. It's never going to
change. I'm not the one moaning about
it, bro. I've accepted it's never ever
going to change. You know,
for real, I've accepted it. It will never change, you know.
I know it will never change. Never,
ever, ever change.
You need to accept it that it's never
going to change. You need to stop
thinking that one day you're going to go
out and all the things that's been
happening in to you for years is going
to stop happening. You need to accept
it. I've accepted it. I've not been out
for like a month. I know. Where the [ __ ]
have the month gone, bro? But yeah. And
when I was tempted to go out yesterday,
I was going to I just wanted to go and
drink wearing the Stony. I wanted to
wear the nice Stone Island and go for a
drink, bro. It weren't even about that.
Obviously, I would have done some
approaches because just [ __ ] it. Why
not? You know, why not do some approaches? But
no, it's not eating me alive at all
inside. No, it ain't.
No, no, bro.
I'm actually all right. I actually feel
good. I feel better, man.
When you give up, you feel better.
Yeah, you generally feel better. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm good, bro. I'm good.
I just don't know how people on Reddit
can be so stupid. Candy, man. Yeah,
I don't even know who that Andrew Tate
guy is. All I do is hear about him, but
I don't know who the [ __ ] he is.
[ __ ] hell. You just hear about him, but that's it.
No, no, no.
What do I get? I don't, bro. It's just
addicted as [ __ ]
It's actually [ __ ] It's just
addicting as [ __ ]
to be fair.
just addicting. Yeah.
Yeah. I know. It's mad, isn't it? Oh,
you're going to laugh at this one,
right? There was this guy. Yeah. Uh
earlier, right? And I was showing him
like messages where like I've agreed to
meet people and I've tried to like meet
people, whatever. And you know, he was
he was saying to me about how like um
you know, you're coming on too strong.
You need to wait a week minimum before
trying to meet them. I was like, no, you
don't. What? You're supposed to what?
[ __ ] So, you're supposed to approach a woman and
[ __ ] what? So,
you're you're supposed to approach a woman and
wait a month before meeting her even
though you've already met.
There's so many idiots on that side,
bro. That only That's only if you met someone online. But yeah,
it's [ __ ] It's [ __ ] up, bro.
feel really hungry, bro. I don't know why
the weather makes you hungry as [ __ ] isn't it?
That's what I'm saying. That's what I
was trying to explain. You got to try to
meet them within 2 or 3 days.
That's what I was saying as well. But he
just kept making excuses and excuses and excuses. Um,
you know, you need to be arranging
something within about four or five
messages, you know, but he was like,
"Oh, no, you got to wait a week
minimum." So what? So you're supposed to
sit there and speak to someone for 2
weeks when you live in the same city?
Why? For what reason?
You know, it doesn't make sense.
But yet when USA Izzy wanted to meet me
straight away, oh that's all right.
There's no rules for them, but there's
rules for us. Oh, oh, let's meet up on
Tuesday. Oh, that's completely fine. You
know, so they so it's like they can they
can they can um
it's like they can [ __ ]
um break the rules all they want, but we
do one little thing. Uh nah, you're
coming on too strong, mate. A week minimum.
Like it's it's [ __ ] up. Like it's mad.
And there the double standards still
exist. Like literally her first message
to me was, "Oh, let's meet up on
Tuesday. Let's meet up on Tuesday." That
was her first message. Let's meet up on Tuesday.
Like, if I done that, I would get a
bunch of [ __ ] simps chasing me with
an axe. Like, you know, strangers. Have
you ever watched strangers where they
come in people's door wearing a mask?
That's what would happen if I [ __ ] if
my first message was, "Oh, do you want
to come and meet me Tuesday?" I'd get
attacked by a bunch of simps. They'd
probably kill me to be honest.
No, no, you don't need to do that
because you've already approached them.
You've already got to know them when
you've approached them. That's the whole
point. You've already met them. You've
already kind of got to know a little bit
more about them. And then the whole and
then the date is to get to know more about them.
So on a dating app, yeah, a week, two
weeks, 3 weeks, but not when you've
already met them.
[ __ ] madness. So yeah, and it's like
the double standards thing still exists.
It's like when I say I don't eat [ __ ]
cuz it's disgusting, you know? It's
frowned upon where I live. You know, I
live in, you know, London. you know, you
get frowned upon if you eat [ __ ] You
know, they you literally will get
frowned upon. It's frowned upon. And um
you know, if you say that, people say
that you're gay when if a woman doesn't
suck dick. Oh, it's all right. So, the
double standards is still disgusting.
But, you know, these people want it
things to be equal.
You know, it just doesn't make no sense.
It makes no sense.
I try doing it with a
Yeah, it doesn't make any difference.
But it's good to have this break, you
know, not drink and stuff cuz it it you
know, it's good because the long you it
it gives you time to change the way you
think. Okay, it's not going to change.
You know, we'll go out for a drink, but
we go out for a drink just cuz we want
to go out for a drink and it's fun.
you know, and it's fun to go out for a drink.
Um, you know, it's the longer you go
without doing this, the more you have
time to think and stuff. It is never
going to change, you know. At the end of
the day, you go out drinking cuz you
want to go out drinking, you know,
whatever, whatever it is you want to do, you know.
But it's funny cuz my I was speaking to
my Indonesian friend and he was saying
the same thing like, "Oh, I" I said, "Do
you you still go out drinking?" I said,
"I ain't been out in ages, bro. I've
just been saving money and just can't be
bothered with it." Uh, and it turns out
he was the same as well. He says, "Oh
yeah, I'd rather spend the money on
other things." And this guy used to go
out a lot. I was like, "Yeah, that's the
stage I'm at now as well, cuz I can't be
bothered with it."
I think that's happened. happens when
you get to 27 28.
So yeah, I was like, "Okay, yeah, that's
what happened basically with me as well."
Happened with me. So yeah,
that's it, isn't it?
But the thing is, I used to have chances
like four or five years ago, Bob.
I used to have chances years ago, but
not now. Now it's dead. You can't get anything here.
So you can't get [ __ ] all here.
You can't get anything now, bro.
And even if you get a day, the woman
just wants to waste your time. So,
I still like that woman in Finland,
though. She's nice, but
she seems she seems all right.
But that's it.
But yeah, if you if you say you don't
eat [ __ ] you get called gay. But if a
woman doesn't want to suck dick, then
that's okay. Nothing wrong with her.
So, I'd say that what I used to do is I
used to go out on the Wednesday,
Thursday, and try to get a date for the
Saturday cuz I used to like drinking on Thursdays. So, yeah.
And then what happens when you don't go
out, you get into this routine and you
get addicted to trying to save money and
then you just don't want to go out for like ages. So
it's just dead in it. It's [ __ ]
boring, bro. The same [ __ ]
So that's it, lad.
What do you mean? Have I tried a busy Friday night?
I've literally tried. What do you mean, bro?
I've tried more than anyone in the
world. What do you mean have I tried a
busy Friday night? I've tried every day.
And they all have boyfriends, apparently.
What the [ __ ]
One night stand. Yeah, cuz that totally
happens when you go to nightclubs that
you, you know, you get a one night
stand. Yeah, totally.
Have I tried a busy Friday night?
Yes, I have, funny enough. And they all
have boyfriends, apparently.
Yeah, they're not interested. It doesn't
matter where it is.
Yeah, it doesn't matter where it is.
Where do you live?
Where do you live, man? Uh,
never been there. Yeah, they're not
interested in this country.
Yeah, I got this £50 by the way from the
football bet. I spent the other money on food. Oh, [ __ ]
Oh [ __ ] man. Yeah,
I like that woman from Finland, bro. But
I don't know, man.
She's a personal trainer as well.
Yeah. No, not even 10 years, bro.
I used to get women [ __ ] three years
ago. Two and a half years ago. Three
Not 10 years ago, bro. Like 10 years ago
was obviously easier than two years ago. But bro,
even two years ago, I used to get [ __ ]
Now you can't get [ __ ]
I used to get [ __ ] back like two
years ago. Now I can't get anything.
Only a [ __ ] woman that just wastes your time.
if I'm lucky. So,
even two years ago, there was a
difference than than there is now. You know,
last date I went on was 5 months ago and
she wasted my time.
Don't even know why she went out with me
to be honest.
Nah, don't use that as an excuse for their dickheadness.
Don't use co as an excuse, bro. They're just [ __ ]
Don't make up silly excuses for them.
You know what I don't understand, Bob?
Why they go on dates just to waste your
time and to waste their time.
That's the bit I don't understand why
they go on dates with people
to you know Yeah. Oh,
I like this blood from Finland. Yeah,
I got so many women's numbers, bro. It's
not even a joke.
I've done so many approaches in my time in it.
Crazy bastard. E.
Yeah, but I need to make sure she's not
going to waste my [ __ ] time before I
go over there. That's the problem, you know.
Do you understand what I'm saying, bro?
Yeah. It doesn't matter if long, bro.
Long distance, it's not even that bad.
You know, Finland is only 3 hours away
on a plane. I mean, most I mean, a lot
of people now are going to [ __ ] Asia.
So, what do what would you prefer?
[ __ ] Thailand or [ __ ] Finland, you know?
take a flight tomorrow. Obviously, I'm
not going to do that, am I?
Don't be stupid.
Don't be stupid, bro.
I need to go on holiday before that in
November. Why am I going to do that?
Take a flight tomorrow.
You're crazy, bro. No. climb up. Yeah.
Cuz I need somebody to be serious. So I
don't want her to be like that Italian
one [ __ ] going on dates for the sake of it.
So last day I went on was that with that
Italian and she was a time waster
holding hands and then when you kiss
they're not kissing you. What the [ __ ]
Don't make no sense.
Does not make no [ __ ] sense, bro.
It's wild, isn't it, bro? Wild.
But I'd rather just have it as a
connection. I might as well just go
there and then just call her out when
I'm there cuz you got nothing to lose by
doing that. I'm sure you can do
approaches in Finland. I'm sure there's
places to drink in Finland.
You know what is it?4500 for the trip. So
yeah, that's true as well.
Yep. Yeah. You get these women that go
on dates with people to waste their time and yours.
It's mad, isn't it?
Understand? Why? Why do these women go
out just to tell everybody that they've got boyfriends?
Like, don't forget, drinking nowadays is not [ __ ]
It's not even like
cheap. It's like quite an expensive
thing to do, you know what I mean? And
then you get these women that go on
these dates, sorry, you get these women
that go out just to clubs just to tell
everyone they've got boyfriends. It's [ __ ] madness.
Why do they go out just to tell everyone
they've got boyfriends? Madness, bro.
Virgin boy is getting in a bed [ __ ] with
no [ __ ] money on it.
Who knows, Bob? Who knows?
How' you manage to do that?
That's a madness. Jesus.
Can't even message anyone on Reddit,
bro. What the [ __ ]
What do I get? What do you mean do I get
much action off YouTube? What are you talking about?
What do you mean? Never.
When should I go out drinking again? I
don't know, bro.
Nah, I don't think I'm going to go next weekend.
No, I don't think so.
It's not long enough, bro.
Even though it's been a month. I think
it's actually been a month. No.
How much did you used to spend in the pubs?
I think when I go on a night it cost me about 120.
70 to about 120.
Yeah, about 120.
Yeah. So, if I went central London, it
would cost about 120.
It doesn't cost 200 like [ __ ] L makes
out. He's talking absolute [ __ ]
You haven't got the funds. Why? Why not?
Why ain't you got the funds? Why not?
London's It's all harder to pull. The
whole country's dead.
I mean, it's not just London. It's the
whole country. Why Why ain't you got the funds?
Why haven't you got the funds?
So you got no money to go out drinking?
I can I can go out.
I'm not as rich as I used to be, but I
could still do it.
But I didn't give up because of because
of the money, bro.
Well, it was part of the reason I wanted
to save, but not cuz I couldn't afford
to do it.
It wasn't because I couldn't afford to do it.
It was more like, you know,
I'd rather take a break from it and just
I don't know. I don't know, bro. I don't
So, your skin in other words.
Yeah. I haven't I don't gamble. I I The
only thing I gamble on is [ __ ]
roulette. Sorry. Um football bets. When
I gamble, I [ __ ]
So you're skin like you have absolutely
no money whatsoever. Madness.
Mad. Yeah, I don't I the only thing I
gamble on is football, bro. I don't play
roulette. I might play it like every
three months, maybe, but nah, I got
bored of it, bro. I used to go when I I
used to go out. Yeah, I used to go out [ __ ]
two [ __ ] I used to go out literally
two um two days a week, bro. I Well, I
used to go out Thursday, Friday,
Saturday. The amount of gambling and
drinking I used to do, bro, escorts everything.
And yeah, just outgrew it.
Obviously, I don't have as much money
now, but I can still drink every week if
I wanted to,
you know, but just can't be [ __ ] bro.
You know? Yeah. I used to gamble all the
time, bro. Roulette, [ __ ]
So, how much would you need in your
account to like go out drinking? How
much would you want in your account
before you before you went to the pub?
Yeah. You say 100.
Nah, bro. I went on another account.
Mine ranges honestly from about 70 to 120.
My night out. It's about 70 to 120.
Yeah, but you don't need 2K to go out drinking.
That's ridiculous. You don't need 2K in
your account for you to go out drinking.
That doesn't make sense
if you spend £100.
That doesn't make any sense though.
Yeah, I'm building my money up.
So, you're going to start with two grand
and then you're going to go out drinking again
when you have two grand Yeah.
Yeah, I do. But it's just the women [ __ ]
It's the women [ __ ] that gets me down.
I used to love it as well, but it's just the women, you know, Virgin boy
getting in a [ __ ] bed [ __ ] with no
[ __ ] bed in it. You like it when I say that.
Skint virgin boy
in a [ __ ] bed. No [ __ ] bed in it.
It's getting virgin boy.
Yeah. But you know, the longer you stay
in, the more you enjoy it when you
eventually go out.
the more you'll actually enjoy it when
you go out again. And you get to save
money, too. Well, when I go out, bro, I
used to I just go out normally every two weeks.
About every two weeks.
Yeah, about every two weeks. Who's this every day?
fighting every day. You mad bastard. Guinness Yeah. Goodness.
Oh, same piss taking [ __ ]
What's wrong with these women? They
really need to grow up.
They do the same [ __ ] I just had
someone message me randomly out of the blue.
What the [ __ ] bro?
Try a different city, bro. I've been to every city.
Uh, bro, I've been literally all over
the country. I've tried every city
except from Glasgow and Blackpool. I've
been everywhere but Glasgow and Blackpool.
It's all the same everywhere. They're
all the same. Piss takers, westernized.
I've been to so many cities, bro.
Multiple times. Same [ __ ]
I used to have a rail card. I used to go
to a new city every week.
So, you must be new on my channel, bro.
You would know this if you've been
watching me for a while. Yeah,
I mean, yeah, but Manchester was the
same. I went to Leeds, Sheffield,
Liverpool. Same [ __ ] They said they got boyfriends.
Newcastle was a little easier, but it's
been to Cardiff. Why would a new city be
different? They're all the same. They're westernized. It's
it's it's the country, bro. It's not the
city. They're westernized. They're [ __ ]
Going to a different city is not going
to change change anything. It's the
women in this country. What the [ __ ]
You're mad, bro. be mad.
Yeah, all the same. These women are all
the same, bro. I just had one randomly message me
starting to be a [ __ ] Oh,
they're all the same.
sending me some picture of a guy. Same
old [ __ ] Same old piss taking [ __ ]
Sending me a picture of some guy
being a [ __ ] Same old [ __ ]
Same [ __ ] different woman.
These women are all the same. Then
they'll send you a picture of like a guy
smiling. Same old [ __ ] Had it before.
They're all the same, bro. Yeah.
I would I would be I would be 100% I
Why wouldn't I be, man?
Why wouldn't I be?
I'm stopping YouTube soon.
I'm stopping YouTube soon, bro.
Nah, not even.
I can't believe you're broke.
That's a madness, isn't it?
That's a madness that you're broke,
isn't it, matey?
So, when do you get paid again?
Where's that JF account? I wonder
Well, I'm going in a bit.
All right, I'm out of here. See you later.