Good boy.
In the bed with no bed in it. No better.
No money in it.
Virgin boy skin in a bed [ __ ] with no
[ __ ] money or bed in it.
Merch is coming soon. Give me some time.
Give me a little bit of time. I haven't
forgot about anyone, anything like that. Yeah.
Oh, what have you done?
Yeah, man. Good to see you back. Oh,
wait. You can't leave YouTube cuz it's
all you got. It's your whole life. Oh, Franklin.
No, I can leave. I've already left
before. I can leave whenever I want. You
can't leave, though.
No self projection on my channel.
No 40-year-old mongos on my channel, mate.
[ __ ] off. No self-reflection on my
channel by you angry little 40-year-old
no hopeer gamblers. [ __ ] off.
Oh, shoot. Oh, lovely.
No, I'm not relaxing. I'm having a blast.
You can ever leave YouTube. It's all you
have. I've left YouTube for a week, two
weeks. I'm not going out at the minute.
So, I mean, I can go live and talk some
[ __ ] if I want
whenever I want.
I don't know what I'm going to have for
tea today. I'm not sure. H.
I might go to McDonald's. Got some vouchers.
I've had girlfriends as well. You've
never had a girlfriend? You've never
even been laid.
I'm the only one on here that's been
seen with money and women. So, I mean, that's self-projecting. Self-projecting.
Even if you paid a woman, you'd still be a virgin.
You've never even been laid, you're
still a virgin.
Like, virgin legs. Are you right, Mike?
I'm bringing out some merch soon,
but I'm giving it away for free because
I'm not skintike. them up skin like them.
I'm bringing out some merch, lad.
No, but you are a virgin. I'm not a
virgin, but you are. Yes, I'm bring I'm
going to be bringing out some merch, bro.
Yeah, I'm going to be bringing out some merch.
Um, basically it's going to be some
t-shirts and some hoodies
and it's going to be said uh
um virgin boy in a bed suit with no bed
and no money in it.
And you know when you're going to lose
it, how you going to lose it? I'm just
going to have like that on like t-shirts
and hoodies if you're interested. I'm g
I'm going to be giving them away. I'm
not going to be selling them. I I might
I might wear it, you know, for when I
next go to a nightclub. Yeah.
Virgin boy skin in a beduit, you know,
like just just a few different things, mate.
Yeah. You know,
you know what's so funny? I've actually
got some money here, but I'm not showing
because do you know what? You know why,
Mike? The community is already dying as
it is. The community is already dying as
it is, lad. I don't want any more I
don't want any more people to run away.
I don't want any more people to run
away, lad. You know what I'm saying?
We've already got people [ __ ] running
away and [ __ ] We don't want any more
people running away. You know, so yeah,
I'll never show money again on it ever.
I don't need to do anything. You need to
mind you need to mind your own business.
You need to mind your own [ __ ] business.
If I wanted you to wait rate my [ __ ]
looks or give me advice, I would have asked.
I don't need anything, mate. I'm keeping [ __ ] warm.
Yeah, of course you do. Yeah, cuz you're
all millionaires on it, aren't you?
Yeah, I forgot about that.
Oh, of course, bro.
Why wouldn't I believe you got all of
this money? Of course you've got all of
this money. You're a millionaire. All
this money but sat on YouTube every day.
I know. Totally. Yeah, man.
Yeah, I know, man. You got all this
money but sat on YouTube every day.
Makes you wonder, don't it?
Makes you wonder. Makes me wonder.
Yeah. You'd rather try and take the piss
out of someone on YouTube, but you got
all this money.
I don't know. Not sure I believe you.
But as long as you believe your own
lies, you know, that's all right. I
guess I don't need benefits. You don't
know how I get money. You don't know how
I make money. That's what makes me laugh
when Timmy tries saying about how I'm
skinn. I just laugh at it.
Like I laugh at it because he doesn't
know what I have. That's what makes me laugh.
You don't believe, bro. You're disabled yourself.
You You have to be disabled at your age
coming on YouTube trying to troll
people. You are the disabled ones. The
only people that get bullied is you and
you're disabled. So, you're disabled and
you get bullied. You don't You can never
bully a guy like me. And you're disabled
yourself. Skint, disabled, low lives.
That's all you people are on here. Literally
s on YouTube with [ __ ] all. No money, no life.
Me, I'm I'm I'm on a detox. I'm
chilling. I'm just straight chilling,
bro. I'm on a detox.
Should I go out next week? This week?
Sorry? Nah, maybe next week. That would
have been six weeks. Sometimes I do six
weeks. Some people do [ __ ] six
months. [ __ ] that.
Yeah, I know, man. I'm keeping warm. I'm
not going drinking for a bit, so Yeah.
Yeah, man. I know. It's mad, is it?
No, not at all. I'm I'm all right. I I
haven't given up on life at all. I'm
just chilling, bro. No.
Nah, not at all. I just haven't been to the barbers. Yeah.
Yeah. I just ain't been to the barbers
to be fair
cuz I can't be asked.
I haven't gone out drinking for a bit. So
yeah, I'll go at some point.
Really, really hungry yesterday, man.
You know what I'm saying? So
yeah, I won't be out this week and I
don't think I'll be out next week
either. I don't know. Depends.
I don't know. Call me [ __ ] man.
Nice to have a good detox, you know.
I didn't eat yesterday. What do you mean
I didn't eat yesterday? Of course I ate
yesterday, you [ __ ]
You [ __ ] [ __ ] Of course I [ __ ] did.
What the [ __ ] Why would I eat?
Oh, [ __ ] man.
Yeah, cuz I already had chicken and chips.
Now I'm going to have McDonald's today.
I'm going to have McDonald's.
Macdonald. Macdonald McDonald's.
Bro, I don't give a [ __ ] what any of you
people say about my appearance. I'm not
the one that's scared to show my face
like you people,
you know? I don't give a [ __ ]
Like you people can't even show your
face. Anything that you say about me, I
don't give a [ __ ] It's like when people
come on here trying to call me skin.
They don't know anything what I have and
what I don't have.
Like I don't give a [ __ ] bro.
Like you people are so irrelevant that
your opinions don't even count as an
opinion. That's how bad it is.
So that's literally how bad it is.
Like it's that it's that bad. Like
you're so irrelevant that your opinions
don't mean nothing.
I mean most of it I mean to be fair I
mean to be fair like most of it isn't
even an opinion is it? Most of the time
it's just self- projecting.
Bit like what Timmy does calling people
ski even though he gets shown money then
he runs away every single time. You know
what I'm saying? So it's kind of like
most of it is just self projecting.
I don't need to prove any of you people wrong.
No, I'm not going off on what at all.
I'm being for real, bro. It's most of it
is just self projecting, you know.
So yeah, just like when Timmy tries to
call me skin, that's just
self-reflecting. That's just him
projecting. Just like Nons when he calls
people skin, self-p projecting. Most of
it is just self-p projecting to be
honest. Talking about their own lives,
their own selves. They know themselves
better than anybody. So
why do I go live? Because I'm just chilling.
I use it as therapy sessions, to be honest.
You know what? I actually use this as
therapy sessions. Maybe I need to get a therapist.
Speaking of that,
Yep. And I'm not showing Yeah. I don't
need And I'm never showing you anything
ever again. Not 4 pound, not four grand,
not one grand, not I'm not showing you
nothing. I will never show money ever
again. I've got money right there. I
could probably beat people with the
money game right with that money right
on the side right there. I'm not showing
nothing. Never again.
Yeah, simple. That's it.
You've conned me one too many times with
that [ __ ] you know, where you've
got people to, you know, show you money
and then when they've shown you money,
you've run away. I'm not falling for it anymore.
Yeah, it is a choice. Of course, it's a
choice. I'm not going out drinking until
I don't know when I'm going to go out again.
[ __ ] knows. I can't be bothered with it.
Yeah, my beard's looking crazy. It keeps
me warm. It's keeping me warm, bro.
What you need in the winter, matey?
It's the winter. It's [ __ ] cold. Do
you need this [ __ ] to keep you [ __ ]
warm? It is a bit long though, is it?
I need to start waking up early. I need
to start going to bed earlier and waking
up earlier, bro. I'm waking up at like
1:00 and it's it's horrible, bro.
Yeah. I don't care.
I don't give a [ __ ]
Like I said, I'm not going out drinking until [ __ ]
I don't know
a while, bro.
Hairline missing. Nah, that's self
projecting. You people already bored.
That's why you can't come on camera.
My hairline is just fine. And my hair is
just fine. Nope. Self projecting again.
That's why I said most of it is not even
just most of it's not even an opinion.
It's um it's self projecting most of
what you people do on here. You know, I
can show my face, but you people can't.
But I really need to start going to bed
earlier, bro. [ __ ] I need to start
going to bed earlier because I wake up
with a [ __ ] nasty taste in my mouth
and [ __ ] headaches and [ __ ]
I need to really start going to bed earlier.
Going to bed at 5 and then Oh, bro. I
used to always wake up like 8 9 in the
morning, but because I don't really
do much anymore. So like, yeah, it's
horrible. Oh my god, it's horrible.
No, it really, really is horrible.
It's [ __ ] horrible, mate. Nothing.
Look, can you hear that?
You can hear the money, but you can't
see the money. You understand?
Oh, [ __ ] Where's Monty? Why hasn't he
come back on here? H [ __ ] bro.
Peter Belly needs to get drunk again.
Yeah, he's never coming back, is he? I
bet he still watches though it 100%.
I bet he still watches.
Yeah, my eyebrows joining together.
I need to go to the barbers, man. But yeah. Oh [ __ ]
My life is better than yours though.
Yeah, but my life is still better than
yours. Think about it. In three years,
I've done more I done more in three
years than you were doing you will ever
do in your whole life.
No, this time last year. No, not at all.
I've still got more money than you. I've
still got, you know, I've still got um
I've got a better life than you. I'm
better looking than you. I can do what I
want to do whenever I want to do it.
There's every chance in hell, bro.
There's every chance in hell.
Like, think about it. You people don't
even leave your house. Think about that.
You don't even leave your house.
You know what I'm saying? You don't even [ __ ]
You know what I mean? I haven't left
London this year. Try again. I was in
Birmingham last month. Try again. Bro,
you don't even leave your house.
You don't even leave your house. And
you're talking about my life. You people
can't even leave your [ __ ] houses.
And I have actually left London twice this year. So
yeah, of course you do, bro. I'm sure if
you was all of them things, you wouldn't
be on YouTube trying to troll um Timmy
every single day. I'm sure if you had
all that money and you had all of these
women, you would not be on YouTube
trolling Timmy every single day.
Your YouTube activity gives you away. I
mean, we can say that much.
Um and I don't complain about women. I
just said that they're [ __ ] Yeah, cuz
a lot of them are [ __ ] Oh well, who's
the one that brought it up? You did. So,
at the end of the day, I'm sure if you
was all of them things, you wouldn't be
sat on YouTube trolling a [ __ ]
disabled person every day.
Cuz think about it, you people ain't got
no life. Every single time I'm live,
you're straight on my live stream. But
you got all of this money and all of
this life. Not a chance,
mate. If you're going to if you're going
to lie, make your lies sound believable.
I've done more in three years than
you've done in your whole life. How mad is that?
Jesus. That's That's insane.
Open the door.
Yeah. Yeah, I know, bro. It's okay to be
me. I'm younger than you. I'm better
looking than you.
Yeah, I know, bro. It's It's fine. It's
not bad being me when you actually
compare it to you people. Old, no hope,
ugly on YouTube every day.
It's a madness, isn't it? Sat on
YouTube, old, ugly on YouTube every day.
Not even a bit of hope to your name.
Yeah, maybe he's all right. Could be
better, could be worse. Could be like
you people ain't got a life, you know,
s on YouTube every day. You know what's
so funny? I have literally been off of
YouTube for weeks before and you I come
back and it's the same people that can't
even take one day off of a YouTube
cuz you ain't got a life. You ain't got
no hope. That's why you gravitate
towards people that are younger than you
that's got that's got better looks than
you. That's why I have all of these old
men gravitate towards me because I'm
everything they wish they were. And my
life's far from perfect. And I'm not
saying my life's perfect, but when you
compare it to a bunch of old [ __ ]
skint men on YouTube,
it kind of is, you know.
Bro, why are you on YouTube? Listen,
even [ __ ] left. Why are you on YouTube?
Why are you on YouTube? Why are you on
my YouTube right now? Let me talk to
myself. You can't leave YouTube. You
can't even take a day off of YouTube.
You can't even take a day off of YouTube.
It doesn't [ __ ] matter. You're still
on YouTube. So, you know what I'm
saying? Same question goes to you.
>> I don't know what to eat, bro. I'm [ __ ]
I wouldn't be stressed. I'm not stressed
at all. You know, you need to go to
trolling school because you suck at it.
You suck at it.
Get off of YouTube and go to trolling
school because you suck at it. Um,
I am [ __ ] starving, bro. Um,
I don't even know what I want.
This the only thing I hate about winter,
you know, is how like you get hungry.
Makes you so hungry, don't it? Um,
I don't know what I want, bro.
Yeah, I'll just go McDonald's. [ __ ] it.
Oh my god, bro.
Yeah, I'm just going to go McDonald's. I
don't know what I fancy.
I've got some vouchers for McDonald's.
So, let's go McDonald's. [ __ ] it.
See, that's another thing is, you know,
when you don't go out, you get into this
routine of saving money. You get
addicted to saving money cuz it's
something better than going out and
[ __ ] approaching [ __ ] [ __ ]
That's what happens.
That's what happens. You see, you just get addicted.
See, cuz you get into a whole new routine.
That's what I mean. Um,
Thailand in November. Yay.
Virgin boy can't do that. He ain't got the funds. Where boy do that? What?
I can't do that.
Can't do that.
You can't do that.
Just catchy sayings, bro. Just catchy sayings.
It's got cold outside, isn't it? Going
have to start wearing my turtleneck. Yeah.
Oh my god, bro. [ __ ] your eyes up as
well. This weather, bro. It's [ __ ] In
a way, I do I do like it, but
I don't know, man.
But know I've not gone downhill from
last year. I just don't go out as much.
That's all. I just don't go out as much.
I can't be [ __ ] Yep.
Go out every day.
Maybe. Maybe not.
Yeah, maybe. Maybe not.
I need to get [ __ ] drunk, bro. Again.
Can't be bothered with it anymore though.
You go out every week if I want to, but
I don't want to. So, yeah.
Yeah, I already went to America.
I don't need to prove anything to you little mongos.
And why do you want proof anyways? When
people show you stuff, you deny it
anyways. Like when I've shown more money
than everyone on here. Like when I've
shown more women than anyone on here. I
don't know why you want to see these things.
Nah, even when you see proof, you don't
believe things. [ __ ] off with that
saying, bro. You've been shown money.
You've been shown women. You've been
shown [ __ ] everything and you still
pretend you ain't seen it. So, I mean,
yeah, stop talking [ __ ] You know,
you know what I mean? You've been shown
money, you've been shown women, and you
still talk [ __ ] So, that's why we don't
waste our time on you people
anymore. That's why we don't get into it
with you people anymore. That's why we
don't meet people as well. That's why we
don't meet people, too, cuz we all see
what you people do. So, complete waste
of time trying to argue with a bunch of
middle-aged jealous people that ain't
got no hope, you know? So,
no hope, no future, no life, no money.
There's no point trying to get into it
with these kind of people, you know?
So yeah, I didn't come back because I
paid everything by my bank card. You [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah,
I think it's too cold to wear stonies, isn't it?
Yeah, whatever. Go back to LJ's. Go back
to L J's and suck his dick. Why are you
coming on my channel, you little [ __ ]
Go back on L Js and go suck his dick.
Yeah, there's nothing There's everything
lies about me, but there's nothing lies about him.
Yeah, he's got all of this money. Yeah,
he's sat on YouTube begging people every
single day, but he's got all this money.
Yeah, it takes him 10 years to go to
Vegas. Oh, [ __ ] me, bro. You know what?
I I don't know who's who's more of a
[ __ ] him or the people that actually
believe him. Like that guy has got absolutely nothing.
[ __ ] all. And he betrays like he's got
money. I don't understand why people do
that. He's got literally nothing. And
you can tell they've got nothing because
they keep trying to tell you that you've
got nothing. He's try he's he's they're
trying to tell you that you've got
nothing but they don't know what you
have. So, it just goes to show that
they're the ones I've got nothing cuz it
takes somebody to know someone, you know?
Yeah, I can I can I can afford to go to
Vegas. I don't need to prove anything to
you little mongrels.
I don't need to [ __ ] prove anything
to you little mongrels.
But that's why like they say that you're
skin and [ __ ] cuz cuz they're skin.
Obvious. So that's why they call other
people skin cuz they're skin.
They're the ones that have got no money.
That's why they bring up every single
day about money cuz they ain't got none.
You know what I mean? Because these
people ain't got no money. So
that's why they call other people skin, L, etc.
Dude, you know what's so bad is like
when I used to go out twice a week. Yeah.
No, not even whenever. Whenever I'd go
out, whenever I would literally go on I
would literally go on L's
around Well, I used to go out quite
early, so maybe like 5, bro. I'd come
back at like 10 at night and it'd be the
same people on there. I'd be out on a
session drinking, gambling, socializing.
I'd come back and it'd be the same
people. That's how you know they've got
no light. They've got no money. They've
got nothing. Literally, [ __ ] all, you
know. It's not We're not in the pandemic anymore.
Uh yes, I have.
I done that a couple of months ago.
And that's how you know, you see. So, yeah.
Oh [ __ ] man.
So yeah, I'm not showing you nothing.
Why don't you come on? Why don't you jo
Why don't you come in the panel? Why
don't you come on the panel and show and
talk and show your face and then I'll
show you the booking confirmation.
I don't need to show any of you self-reflectors nothing.
I'm not showing you nothing. Unless you
want to come on a hangout to talk, then
I'll show you it. [ __ ] off you little Mongols.
You [ __ ] absolute [ __ ] spastnics.
[ __ ] show [ __ ] booking
confirmation. You really are a [ __ ]
[ __ ] aren't you?
You don't Well, you live on YouTube.
YouTube's your life, so you might as
well put your life on YouTube.
well put it on YouTube.
Yeah, it doesn't matter if you put your
life on YouTube or not. I said I'm going
to Thailand. I don't need to prove
anything. You believe it or you don't
believe it. I don't need to prove anything. Simple.
And you might as well put you might as
well put your life on YouTube because
you live on YouTube so you might as well.
He lies about everything. Pretending
that he's got money when he doesn't.
Pretending that he's got properties when
he doesn't. It's ridiculous to just lie.
It's just ridiculous lying, bro.
I don't know why people need to lie, man.
I'm not telling you where I'm stopping.
Cuz everyone knows what you're trying to
do. You don't need to know that. He lies about everything.
Pretends that he's got money when he
doesn't. Pretends that he's got friends
when he doesn't. Um,
pretends he's got property when he
doesn't. There's literally nothing about
him that's not skin. Oh, well, you can
buy a pair of trainers. Anyone can buy a
pair of trainers, bro. People on
benefits can buy a pair of trainers. So,
you know what? I've never been into
trainers, you know, but I was looking at
this guy on Instagram and he does some
nice Air Jordans. I might buy myself a
pair of Air Jordans,
even though I've never really been into
trainers, but I don't know, man. I've
never really been into them. I just buy
like the nicest black pair and that's it.
But I don't know. Some of them Jordans look good.
But yeah, anyone can buy like [ __ ]
Air Jordans and [ __ ] You know what I mean?
You know what I'm saying, bro? So,
some of the Air Jordans are nice. I like
them, but they're just not for me.
Trainers are just not for me. Like, I'll
just buy black vapors. What I do is I
buy the nicest vapors in the summer and
in the winter, white in the summer,
black in the winter, and then done, done deal.
I'm feeling one of the best trainers
going. I don't understand the whole hype for it.
I just don't understand. I never been
into trainers. Only white pair and then black pair. So,
I don't understand the hype for these
trainers, but people some people like them.
How much are they like 180? Huh?
What? They 180, huh? No. No.
Cuz you're not going to join. 250. Three.
I've got some Air Max trainers. I don't
know which ones they are.
I don't know which ones they are. But
yeah, now anyone can buy a new pair of
trainers. is like Lord J. I don't know
why he's No, I don't have Vapor Maxes
anymore. I worn them out.
I don't know what ones they are. I'll
show you them. I don't know which ones they are.
Oh my god, bro. It's getting cold, man.
These ones. I don't know which ones they
are. Oh [ __ ]
I don't have Vapor Maxes.
I've got these. All I got is these and Hachis.
I've only had these a few months. I only
have these and Hachis.
So, when I go out next, I'm going to wear those.
I'm going to wear those. And I'm going
to wear this
with the badge. Obviously,
the badge needs putting on
be looking sexy again.
Or might wear the other Stony. Who knows? E.
Oh my goodness.
What the [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm going to wear that Stony with it.
Ah, I don't need a trim, bro. I'm not
going out for a bit.
I'm not going out for a little while, matey.
No, I love Stone Island, matey.
I love Stone Island.
I love Stone Island, matey.
Yeah, another trim when I go out again drinking. Oh [ __ ]
Oh my goodness, bro. It's cold in it. [ __ ] freezing. Oh, [Music]
sure don't know what to eat today. Yeah, really.
I might get a biryani actually.
Yeah, I might get a biryani
since it's so [ __ ] cold. Yeah. Ro boy
skin in the bed [ __ ] with no money in it.
That's why they start that [ __ ] at like five.
Virgin boy skin in the bed with no money in it.
With [ __ ] all money in it with [ __ ]
nothing. No money. No nothing. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm going to wear my blazer and my
turtleneck when I go out drinking again
and I can be asked [Music] Nice biryani. Every on
chill. Please it
Reddit mods love banning people doggy.
They need that power.
They need You not understand, lad? They
need that power.
Without that power, mate, they'll go insane.
They do not understand. They need that power.
Without that power, mate. Yeah. Like I
say, they they will go [ __ ] me mad. Yes.
They'll go [ __ ] ape [ __ ] without it, bro. Yeah.
Doo doo doo. No. I'm hungry. Right.
I'm gone. Yeah. See you.