Yo yo yo yo.
Okay, we got
[ __ ] it now.
Sorry, mate. I just I just don't know. I
didn't really say anything to be honest, bro. Yeah,
cuz that in itself just tells you
everything that you need to know to be honest. Yeah, man.
[ __ ] hell, bro. That is a madness.
Imagine being on holiday with somebody
and you're still obsessed.
It's madness. It's actually madness. I
actually live in these people's head
rent free. It's not even a joke, but I
actually feel bad for them, you know. I
actually feel really really bad.
It's really really It's just It's
actually shocking, bro. Like,
it's bad, bro. It's [ __ ] bad, man.
But I'm definitely going to donate you a
[ __ ] Stony, mate. You need a [ __ ]
You need a new wardrobe. [ __ ] hell.
Jesus Christ. You need a new wardrobe,
mate. I don't know what's more ugly, the
face or the or the clothing. I don't
know which which is more ugly, to be honest. Oh, mate.
[ __ ] But then again, you can't really
afford stuff when you're skin like that,
can't can you? So, I mean, when you're
skint like that bastard with no money, I
mean, you can't really afford anything,
can you, matey?
On holiday and still obsessed. It's
madness, isn't it? That is That is
[ __ ] I swear I went live one time. I
went on holiday, ain't it?
think yeah I went live once that's how
you know you truly live in someone's
head rent free
I mean people can people can do videos
people can do videos on the holiday bro
people can take pictures on holiday but
this [ __ ] is live streaming talking
about me that's how you know I live in
east head rent free definitely
definitely definitely one million% bro
who the [ __ ] pays money right who
actually pays [ __ ] money out of their own pocket
to to to go on holiday and then start
talking about someone on YouTube all
day. That isn't madness, bro. That is
crazy. Took a [ __ ] long time to save
up as well.
No, things are fine. And you need to
stop trying to troll because you suck at
it as well. I've told you this a million
times. You need to stop.
You suck at it.
Things are great. Things are fine.
That is [ __ ] bro. Like, you're
actually on holiday talking about me.
You really are jealous of me. And trust
me, that that really is that like you're
on Wait, hold on, [ __ ] You
saved up money for a long time because
obviously you're skin and you've you've
gone on holiday, actual holiday with
someone and you're doing live streams
about me. Bro, look at your life. Please
look at your life. You know, I mean,
people would argue, you know, before
that, but that that is that is insane,
bro. That really really is insane. I
mean, yeah, you can take pictures. You
can It's not even like you're going
live. It's like you're going live
talking about somebody else whilst
you're next to your fat, ugly girlfriend
with special needs. It's [ __ ] bro.
It's actually That to me is crazy.
That's how you know, bro. Like, you
wasting your life. You arguing with them
now. You're just wasting your life cuz
they're clearly jealous. Anyone doing
that, bro, is clearly jealous of
something you have. You know, it's it's
clear every day now, bro. It's clear
now, bro, for somebody to go on holiday,
right? That's why I don't react to them.
That's why I don't bother because why
would I waste my time, bro, argue with
jealous people? But I I have to say how
sad it is. At the same time, it is sad.
It goes to show that he's an insecure
little virgin. It just goes to show it
even more. For someone to go on holiday
and start doing a live stream about
someone, you just know that he's just an
insecure little skint virgin that ain't
got nothing in his life. And yes, skint
cuz 13 grand in three [ __ ] months,
three years is [ __ ] skint. Yes,
you're skint. Simple. Like, it's done
deal, bro. You know what I mean? Just
goes to show that you you know, you can
see in face how ugly he is as well. an
ugly bastard. That's why he does all of
this [ __ ] on YouTube because he knows
the fact that he's an ugly bastard. I've
got a better life than him. I've had
more women than him. I'm better than him
in every way. This is why he does all of
this YouTube [ __ ] I'm not reacting. I'm
telling you why they do it for those
that that aren't wondering. I don't give
a [ __ ] I'm telling you why they do it
in case someone didn't know.
Cuz it's like that is mad.
I'm not trying to troll him. I'm telling
him what he is. He's an ugly skinned
bastard with no life. No, I'm not
reacting. I'm telling you what they're
doing. I'm not reacting. I'm I'm I'm
telling you it's sad what they're doing.
That's not reacting. That's stating
facts. There's a huge difference between
reaction um reacting and stating facts.
I'm stating facts. He's a sad, jealous
little bastard. But nothing in life.
It's hardly reacting telling someone
what they are. Anyways, moving on now.
So yeah, and you're banned. Bye-bye now. So yeah. Yeah, man.
So ju just because something is
unbelievable to me, I can't I can't help
how something is so unbelievable.
It's unbelievable. It's hard not to say
anything. It's that unbelievable.
You know, how could you not say
anything? You got some little skint
virgin that's paid money to go on
holiday that took him a long time to
save up for cuz he's skinn. So you're on
a holiday with your fat ugly girlfriend
and then all you're doing is going on
about me. That's how you know she's
disabled. You know how people sit there
and say about how um how do you know
she's disabled? Because no normal woman
would allow that. That's how you know
that she's disabled. It doesn't matter
whether she spoke or she hasn't spoke.
even though she hasn't spoke. It's not
about that. It's about the fact that
look at all of what this weirdo has done
in these years. No normal woman would
would tolerate it and no normal woman
would go with someone as ugly as him
anyways. But you know what I'm saying?
It's um it just goes to show that she's
got special needs.
It's so clear. It's obvious because no
no one would sit there and allow that.
Just ordered some peppers by the way. So
can't wait to eat. But yeah, that's just [ __ ] bro.
That is a madness.
I'm going to donate you one of my
stonies, mate. You need a new [ __ ] wardrobe.
I don't know what's more uglier, your
style or your face. That's a hard one,
bro. That really, really is a hard one.
It's so funny that it's sad that you
literally have to say something about
it. You literally have to say something about it. Madness, bro.
So yeah, the more you continue doing
this, the more it just shows how jealous
you are. And I don't even have to say
anything. I don't even have to say
Yeah, I don't even need to say anything, bro. Yes. Oh [ __ ]