Uh, virgin boy
skin in the bed with no bed in it.
Obsessions come to a next level, bro.
A next [ __ ] level.
This is insane, isn't it?
I feel sorry, bro. I actually do feel
sorry for him. I was thinking of doing a
video. Should I do a little video to
him? Cuz I kind of feel bad.
Oh, bless him. He's so insecure. It's uh
it's insane, bro. Should I do a little
video? Should I do a little cute little
video to him?
Like a last one cuz I want to give him,
you know, I want to give away a Stone Island
stone island jumper, you know.
[ __ ] hell. That's lush. Poke in the
winter is lush. Well,
that's where Santa Claus come from, you know.
I actually really [ __ ]
I actually feel sorry for this virgin, bro.
I swear to God, I actually do. Uh,
[ __ ] even copying my holidays.
Even copying my [ __ ] holidays I went
on since I was [ __ ] 23.
I mean, you say that, you know, you
didn't copy my holiday and you didn't go
there because I went there. I mean,
yeah, bro. Totally. I mean, your your
your the first place you went abro just
happened to be Amsterdam, is it? Yeah.
Yeah, totally. Uh, that just happened to
be the first place you went to is Amsterdam.
Yeah, I'm skin. Good for you.
We don't acknowledge self-reflectors. Um,
yeah, no self-reflection on my channel.
Anyways, um so yeah, you you just
happened to go to uh
you just happened to go to Amsterdam,
didn't you? Yeah. The first place you went. Uh-huh. Uhhuh.
You see, probably 1% of the population's
first trip was probably Amsterdam,
and you went there just cuz I went
there. You were literally obsessed.
Like I get I get the windups and stuff, but
you know, you're taking it to the next
level now, bro. You seriously need to
get laid. That's the only thing I was
watching when I was uh
when I was watching that video. You
seriously need to get laid, bro. This is ridiculous. Now,
I I'll do a video. I need to show the stonies.
[ __ ] hell. And then you done it
again. Yeah, you're definitely copying
me. You're obsessed.
You are literally [ __ ] obsessed. You
need to get laid. Oh my god. You need to
get laid. And I feel I feel sorry for
you as well because of um how insecure
you are about your looks. The fact that
you're trying to call me ugly when
everyone knows I'm better looking than
you and I've had more women than you as
well. But yeah, I'm ugly. Okay. But
anyways, you know, I'm going to give
away this Stone Island jumper
to you. Anyways, um it's got dry clean nicely.
I I was watching that real I couldn't
believe what the [ __ ] you're wearing.
What the [ __ ] are you [ __ ] wearing
them virgin clothes? What the [ __ ] bro?
Get a Sony on. You might lose your virginity.
Seriously, you seriously need to get
laid. That is that is next level.
Sorry, bro. I just can't believe it.
It's just [ __ ] up.
You literally copied my holiday.
You literally copied my holiday as well.
Yeah. I'm going to do a video to you as
well, Virgin Boy.
Um cuz I need to give away this one of
these stonies to you and I want you to um
pick what color you want cuz yeah, you
seriously need to get laid.
You're actually taking the biscuit now.
You've you've paid for for for a holiday
with someone and all you're going on
about is me. Are you taking a piss?
You you taking the piss, Virgin boy?
No, no, no, no, no. You You generally
are obsessed now.
Well, you got what you wanted, mate. You
got a reaction now cuz I can't believe
how sad you are. So, congratulations.
You really really are a You need to You
need therapy. I think I generally think
that you need therapy. You generally
This is getting sad now. Really sad.
Yeah, you literally uh
you need to get laid. You need to go to
therapy as well. You're so insecure
about the way you look. I don't know how
many times you talk about my looks every
day because you're jealous that I'm
better looking than you. But whatever it
is, you seriously need to you seriously
need to get laid.
You seriously seriously need to get laid. Honestly,
I'm like, you're still [ __ ] talking
about my looks when I'm a million times
better looking than you and I've got
teeth in my mouth, unlike you.
And you're and you're calling me ugly
when I'm a million times better looking
than you. What the [ __ ] I've been with
normal women. I've never had to resort
to disabled girls like you. I've never
had to resort to dis I think what you
mean is you're ugly. I think that's what
you mean. I think you what I think what
you mean is you're you're the ugly one.
That's why you tried to get with all of
my sloppy seconds cuz you couldn't pull
them yourself. Yeah. I think I I think
you'll find that you're you're the ugly one.
As much as you try to like call me it,
we all know that you are literally
you literally are the the ugly one.
Cuz if I was, you wouldn't waste your
time. Especially on holiday. [ __ ]
hell. Especially on a holiday that you
paid for. Yeah. It just it goes to show
yeah what you really really really are.
Jealous skin insecure virgin.
It just goes to show now now you've done
that on holiday. It just goes to show
what you really are. Skin ugly virgin.
No life. No money in a bedit with no bed
in it. It's so obvious.
It's so [ __ ] obvious what you are
now. You need to get [ __ ] laid and
lose your [ __ ] virginity.
You need to stop convincing yourself
that I'm ugly. It's not going to change
the fact that you actually are ugly
yourself. It's just you're just wasting
your time. All you're doing is wasting
That's generally all you're doing is
wasting your time. Yeah.
I don't waste my time on you because I
know I'm better looking than you. I know
I've got more money than you. I know I'm
not a sad virgin like you are, so I
don't waste my time on you usually, but
I just find it was funny that uh you
paid for a holiday and you're still obsessed.
You're still obsessed even on holiday.
I mean, it was hard not to say anything.
You are [ __ ] skint. You are skint.
You even said that the [ __ ] train was
70 return. Yeah, you are skint skintter
than a skint flint. And if that 13 grand
is really yours in three years, that is
skint. Do you know what somebody gets up
to in 3 years? You are skint flint.
You literally are skint flint, lad.
I don't have autism, mate.
I can't relate. I don't have autism. So,
you even said that the Euro stock cost
£70 in return. Yeah.
Nothing skint about that. Hey, copy of
my holidays now.
Yeah, if I was there any longer, I was
in Amsterdam for 3 days, you [ __ ]
But I was in Amsterdam for 3 days and my
train cost me £350.
Yeah, my train cost me £350. So yeah, £70
and so what? So it cost £1,200 for two
people? £600 each. Okay, you're still
skinn. It took you until 30 to go
abroad. You You literally are skint.
Look at them [ __ ] virgin clothes that
you wear. No wonder you're still a
virgin in them shitty virgin clothes
that you got on you. That's why I'm
going to [ __ ] donate you a Stone
Island. You're going to die a virgin
wearing that. No wonder you never been
laid. You [ __ ] virgin with them
charity shop shitty clothes. Have you
ever heard of a [ __ ] dry cleaners
[ __ ] walking around in them virgin
shitty ugly clothes? I don't know what's
more uglier, the clothes on your face.
I don't know honestly what's more uglier
than face on clothes. That's That's a hard one.
[ __ ] hell. You [ __ ] skint, mate.
You skinted in a [ __ ] skin, mate. You
skimp, mate. Generally [ __ ] skint, A
you you [ __ ] skit, mate.
You You [ __ ] skip, mate.
You You [ __ ] skin. You [ __ ] skit.
You You [ __ ] skint, mate.
You [ __ ] You're [ __ ] skint.
You're [ __ ] skint, mate.
Uh you you're [ __ ] skint, mate.
That's what you are.
You're scared. Yeah, I stayed in a
hostel cuz I wanted to stay in a hostel
cuz I was by myself. What's wrong with
staying in a hostel, mate? I've stayed
in hotel rooms that's worth more than
your whole Amsterdam trip. When I used
to go around England, mate, my hotels
cost more than your actual trip.
Yeah, when I used to stay in hotels.
The [ __ ] dude?
What the actual [ __ ]
You really are skin. You really are.
You're skinting in a skin flint.
Nah, mate. Them clothes are ugly. No
wonder you're still a [ __ ] virgin.
You remember when them black guys threw
wall at you that day? You was in strap.
They probably saw you [ __ ] mine off a
[ __ ] stinky lanky virgin who's never
had it. Stinky virgin, mate.
Stinky white virgin. No wonder they
threw water at you. They don't like
virgins in this city, mate. We don't
like [ __ ] lanky virgins who's never
had it in our city, mate. We don't like
them kind of people. We don't like them
kind of people, mate. You seriously need
to get laid there, mate.
You seriously need to get laid. And
besides the point, you would have went
to Paris. If you actually was going to
go somewhere, you would have went to
Paris. It would have made more sense.
You're even copying my holidays now.
You're copying my little holidays.
Why are you copying my holidays for?
Yeah, you even copy my [ __ ] holidays.
It's wild. You would have went somewhere
like Paris cuz obviously you're scared
of flying. You never You've never been
on a plane, mate. But I have.
No, you never been on a plane. I have, mate.
You would have went somewhere like
Paris. Speaking of Paris, but you went to Amsterdam.
I wonder why you went to Amsterdam. Cuz
I went there. Copycat. You're a little copycat.
Just like when you were saying Chev was
attractive. You didn't want to feel left
out. Bless you. You didn't want to feel
left out. You wanted to copy the trend.
You wanted to copy the trend, mate.
Bless you. Then if you wanted to to copy
the trend, you didn't want to feel left
out, did you? You didn't want to feel
left out, did you? You didn't want to
feel left out, did you? Did you? Did
you? Did you want to feel left out, did
you, mate? I had to follow the crowd.
Had to follow the crowd.
You literally had to follow the crowd, mate. Didn't you?
You didn't want to feel left out, did you, son? Jesus Christ.
Nah, mate. You You You dress like that
because you can't afford designer clothes.
You can't afford designer clothes cuz
you're a skinned little bastard.
Skin little [ __ ]
You're a skinned little [ __ ]
Skid bird in a bed [ __ ] with no bed and
no money in it. Working hell.
Oh, [ __ ] boy. He's a [ __ ] nons.
He's about 90 years old now, mate.
You went to Amsterdam to copy me.
You little copycat. I could tickle you.
I could. You little copycat. Just when
you were saying Cole was attractive, you
was copying. You're a copycat.
You've got no originality. All you do is
copy. Copy people's holidays. Copy the
Sher Cole trend. Do you ever stop copying people?
Stop. Why are you such a copycat?
Why are you such a [ __ ] copycat?
Why are you such a [ __ ] copycat, mate?
Oh, it is [ __ ] nons is a proper
copycat. Mike, he copies my holidays. He
only went to Amsterdam just cuz I went
and the Chevel Cole thing. Oh, that's
definitely copying, mate. Let me tell
you something. She's not attractive and
I've been with more women than you and
it's been proven on videos. You're
copying. You're copying the crowd.
Copying the trend. Copying the crowd.
Know what I'm saying?
Well, I kind of like winter, you know,
but it is a bit cold. It's definitely
getting winter now. All I do in this
winter is [ __ ] drink hot chocolate
and eat food, bro. It's [ __ ] mad. I
do like it and I I don't know, but I
don't know. It's a tough one, isn't it?
You went to Amsterdam just cuz I went to
Amsterdam. You're a copycat. But listen,
Mike, what's the chances someone's first
holiday is Amsterdam?
What's what's the what's the what's the
chances someone else My first holiday
was Belgium. What's the what's the
chances someone's first holiday is Amsterdam?
5%. Cuz I'm pretty sure in England most
people's first holiday is [ __ ] Spain
or It's never Amsterdam. It's never
Amsterdam. But Virgin Boy went to
I wonder why. And I know you, you know,
you're scared of flying and stuff, but
you know, there's Paris. I've never been
to Paris, but you didn't go to Paris
because I didn't go to Paris, you know.
Yeah. A holiday. A holiday abroad. Yeah.
You You could have went to Paris. It's a
city of love, you know. I was going to
take Izzy to Paris once, but she was
being a bit of a [ __ ] But nonetheless,
you know, it's a city of love. You know,
you could have easy went to Paris with
your the wolf fat ugly girlfriend.
Uh but you went you didn't go to Paris
cuz I hadn't been there.
You hadn't you didn't go to Paris
because I didn't go there,
you know. So you had you had to go to
you had to go to Amsterdam. Yeah. You
had to be a copycat.
And you remember everything I did there
as well. You you obsessed.
You're obsessed, mate. I don't even
[ __ ] remember all of them things. I
know I banged two escorts and done some
weed and drunk a lot of wine, but yeah,
you're definitely you're definitely a copycat, mate.
No one's first. My sister's boyfriend's
been to Amsterdam, but that was nowhere
near his first holiday. It's rarely
someone's first holiday, especially if
they're in a relationship.
Yeah, you went there cuz I went there.
Obsessed with me. You know,
sad, bro. [ __ ] sad.
Well, yeah, I pissed in a canal. I
stayed in a hostel. I [ __ ] escorts. I
smoked weed. Duh. But I don't. Why? It's
weird that someone remembers all of them
things. He's obsessed with me, bro. Why
is this [ __ ] so obsessed with me?
Oh my god. You're copying my holidays
and [ __ ] all sorts.
That is insane.
I don't know why this guy is so jealous
of me, Mike. What the [ __ ]
It's crazy, bro. He is so [ __ ]
jealous of me, man. Because think of it,
bro. Yeah. Who the [ __ ] pays to go on
holiday and starts talking about someone
else? You say that I'm [ __ ] ugly and
I'm this, that, and the other. all the
things that you are yourself, you're
self-projecting, but you know, you
wouldn't say them things. You would just
get on with your holiday. But you're on
holiday talking about me. You're obsessed. Jesus Christ.
You really are obsessed.
You really are really really obsessed.
He couldn't even wait until he was back
on holiday off of holiday, Mike. He
couldn't even wait until he returned.
No, he is definitely definitely
obsessed. Like there there's there's no
doubt about it. You copying holidays? [ __ ]
Oh, man. You You [ __ ] You need to get laid, mate.
Dude, you're saying that with a woman?
I've been with more women than you've
ever been with.
It's [ __ ] insane, mate. Oh my god.
You need to [ __ ] you need to get laid.
Why does Coke taste so good in the winter?
In the summer it tastes stinking, but in
the winter, yeah, it just tastes so
good. You know, like Coke, chocolate, and stuff.
I don't need to go I don't need to go
abroad with a woman.
I'm going to Finland soon to see a woman
who I met in London. Last time I went
out drinking, the Sunday I went out drinking. Yeah.
going to Finland soon. Somewhere you
can't afford, mate.
You can't afford to go Finland, mate. [Music] Gin boy.
Yeah. Everything they say is projection, bro.
He call He calls me ugly. Yeah. I'm
better looking than him. I've been with
more women than him. Calls me skin. I've
got more money than him. I've got more
life experience than him. Literally
everything is projection.
I haven't bet on the football since Saturday.
Like everything you do is self-p
projection. You're insecure.
You're on holiday talking about my
[ __ ] looks. What the [ __ ] I'm better
looking than you. I've been with more
women than you.
Literally all the women that you wish
you could get with cuz you're too ugly
to get them yourself. And then you're
saying I'm ugly. It's crazy, man. What the [ __ ]
You seriously [ __ ] need to get laid, man.
You really, really, really need to get
laid. I'm not even [ __ ] joking. [ __ ] madness.
No, I don't play that.
No, I don't play that [ __ ] bro.
No, I don't play that. I only football sometimes.
I done a football bet on
Saturday. I put 20 on£ 159.
pay £39. £39. It paid for the dry
cleaning. So the dry cleaning was
expensive, bro. Had to get my Stone
Islands dry cleaners, you know, and [ __ ] So yeah,
I don't go on the FB TE's.
Yeah, of course I'll be getting new GTA, mate, obviously.
But no, I don't play them FBOT TE's, bro.
I just play the [ __ ] football and I
Yeah, I can be boss.
Yeah, man. That virgin's going on about
me on holiday, Bob. He's so obsessed.
First he copies my holidays
and then he he's copying me, bro. Like,
he's [ __ ] copying my holiday and he
keeps calling me ugly when everyone
knows I'm better looking than him.
The more that the more he does this,
Yeah. the more it shows what he really is.
Bin them Stone Islands. Ah, bro, I've
had more birds than you would ever have.
I don't need to been anything. There's
nothing wrong with my Stone Islands.
Don't bring your negative [ __ ] on my channel, lad.
I've had more birds than you've had hot dinners.
Shouldn't tell me to [ __ ] chuck my
stonies just cuz you can't afford them.
So, um, yeah, I am getting GTA 6.
You set with Hundreds Bird. Yeah.
Why would you tell somebody to [ __ ]
Why would you tell somebody to chuck
their [ __ ] Stone Island jumpers?
Stone Island sick.
There's nothing wrong with them Stone Island jumpers.
So riding sick and I I haven't worn them
for eight. I've not worn snow riding for
about a year
cuz I had to be dry clean. So I haven't
worn them for a year. So
yeah, you've been rejected. Yeah, you've
been rejected a lot as well. You ain't
even got the balls to approach.
Yeah, you ain't even got the balls to
approach. That's why you haven't been
rejected because you ain't got the balls.
You ain't got the balls to go out there.
And I've also been with more women than you have.
Yeah, you got five kids. Of course you do.
Yeah. You ain't even got the balls to approach.
Yeah, I got some nice Stone Island
jumpers. Why' you tell me to chuck my
Stone Island jumpers, bro? Just cuz you
can't afford them.
What an idiot.
Yeah, bro. [ __ ]
Everything is projection with these people.
Everything is projection. Everything, bro.
Everything is projection with them. They're self-reflectors
as Monty would call them.
Look at these. I can't stop looking at
these, bro. Bro, if you go on if you go
on uh if you go on [ __ ] Lord Jay's
channel, you will lose brain cells, bro.
Look at that little stony with the badge
on it. Oh, that is lush.
Obviously, the badge needs to go there.
You're telling me that's not a lush shot
fight? Look at that. They look brand new.
Jesus Christ. And then you wonder why
I'm so [ __ ] happy to win30, bro.
I don't know what would look better on
Virgin Boy cuz obviously I'm going to
give Virgin Boy one because obviously
he's skinned so he can't afford these
kind of things. So I was thinking of
giving him that color.
They still look brand new.
They still look brand [ __ ] new.
They still look brand spanking new.
There's nothing wrong with these Sony's.
So, I don't know which one to give the
virgin. The skin virgin in the bed with
no bed in it.
They were £300 each.
I got this one here.
as well, but I don't really like this
one as much. But it's still nice.
They're all nice. They're stonies. They
look brand new. I go to a top dry cleaners, matey.
Yeah, they were £300 each. One of them was 310. Um,
yeah, bro. A lot of money. My clothes
cost a lot of money, bro.
So that's why I was like, "Oh yeah, I
won £30. It paid for the [ __ ] uh
of course I bought them brand new, you
[ __ ] idiot." What the [ __ ] are you
talking about? Of course I bought them brand new.
They look brand new now because I've had
them for over a year when I bought them brand new.
What the [ __ ]
No, they look No, no, no. Basically what
happened was well I had left them in the
dry cleaning bag for so long they were
getting creased up and they had some
stains on them like one had like a white
stain. I don't know what the [ __ ] it
was. They had these weird stains and
then when it come out the dry cleaners
it just look they look brand new.
Yeah, they look brand new like I just
got them. Yeah, they were in the the
laundry bag for about No, I come stay. I
don't know what the [ __ ] it was.
They were in the bag for like [ __ ]
almost a year, bro. I just didn't get
around to. So yeah, 30 pound. They look
brand new. So when I go out again, I'll
be wearing one,
but I don't know. Like I said, I don't
know when I'll be out again, Mike. I
can't be bothered.
I can't be bothered going out.
Yeah, they're proper fresh, bro.
Nice dry cleaners.
Yeah, they [ __ ] better, dude. £30.
Three stonies and one Ralphie.
30 worth it any day of the week.
Nah, they don't. Look at Nons. He's
still a virgin.
Sharp dressed men know they [ __ ]
don't, mate. I had more success when I
used to go out approaching in a tracksuit.
Do you know what it is? I just can't be
bothered with it anymore, bro.
I just can't be bothered with it, Mike.
Going out drinking here and I have a
boyfriend. I just can't be [ __ ] with it.
I can't be bothered, bro. [ __ ]
hearing the same [ __ ]
when everything's done. That's why I
always just like brush it off and just
don't even bother going, bro.
Uh, mate, I've been with women that you
wish you could be with, virgin boy.
Anyways, bye-bye now. Yeah.
And it's always the same [ __ ] with
the women, Mike.
You go out drinking and [ __ ] It's
always the same [ __ ] isn't it?
It's always the same [ __ ]
Yeah, I haven't been to a restaurant for
ages, bro. A nice restaurant. I need to go, bro. Yeah,
I used to live near the side men.
Nah, mate. Yeah, I used to live near the
side men. Mike, I used to see some of
the sidemen in Westfield.
You know who that is? Sidemen. Calreezy.
Yeah, I used to see them in the Westfields.
Yeah. So they so they used to live in
that tower, right? So
I used to uh when I used to go
Westfield, I used to see Kreezy and
stuff. Big [ __ ] he is in real life.
Big [ __ ] bro.
He's a tall [ __ ] He is.
But I think I've grown since then to be fair.
Yeah, the FIFA lads,
they don't live there anymore. But
you watch you watch Sidemen. Uh, Sunday's mic. Oh [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah, bro. They're [ __ ] um they're millionaires, lad.
Well, no, I haven't had any luck because
I don't play them.
I think you've got the wrong channel. I
don't play that [ __ ] I don't play fobies.
I don't play that [ __ ]
That's Timmy that plays them, not me.
No, he didn't.
No, I never say I've lost money on the
faulties. I haven't played faulties in
months. So, like I said, you've got the wrong channel.
I think you you you got me confused. But yourself
or another channel cuz I ain't played them for months.
I don't play them fories. You literally
have the wrong channel, matey.
I don't play them for these, bro. I
think I No, seriously. I think the last
time I played one was maybe three weeks
ago and I lost 50 pound 3 weeks ago. I
don't play them. You have the wrong person.
I don't play online roulette. Um
I don't play online roulette. I don't
I wish I could win big on online
roulette, Mike, but you just can't do it.
You just can't do it.
You can't even win big anymore on like,
you know, online roulette. Come in. No.
What do What's the best chance you got
of winning on gambling nowadays? I think
it's the football, is it?
Yeah, I've won some good bets the past
two months on the football.
That 120 to [ __ ] That 120 to [ __ ]
380 was a good win.
387 from 120 on two teams. That was a nice win.
Oh, I did put 40 on the FBY then
actually. When was that? Yeah, but that
was almost a month ago.
Do you know why the only Do you do you
know the only reason why I done it,
Mike? You You know the only reason why I betted?
But yeah, it is a waste time. You know
the Do you know the
only reason why I betted on [ __ ] my
mom's birthday, bro?
I went out, bro, and I [ __ ] had like £300 left
until the next week. Like I I would have
been all right. I would have still got
money, but it's like I needed more
money. I had like £200 left. So, I was
like, "Let me try and win a football bet
and build me back up." But
yeah, bro, it was mad. I just put 120 on
a [ __ ] football bet. I drew 160, but
[ __ ] I only put 120 on the bet cuz I
lost 40 on the roulette. Bro, I don't
[ __ ] It was only cuz I was kind of
like short of money
that Sunday crucified me, bro.
That Sunday when I met that Finnish
woman, it was bad, bro. Bad bad. Nah.
Is casino a waste of time?
Would you say? I think so. Yeah.
Would you say casino is a waste of time?
Yeah, all of it is
how much would you say like how much do
you say is proper loaded?
But depends how much you'd say is proper loaded ear.
I used to be [ __ ] I used to have a
lot of money, bro. Not a millionaire,
but I used to obviously I was never a
[ __ ] nowhere near a millionaire, but
I used to have a lot of money, bro.
That's probably why, Mike, I don't get
like urges to gamble anymore, cuz I
think I've gambled so much in my life.
I've drunk so much. I've gambled so
I've got more life experience than the
average 27y old.
You know what I'm saying? Not with like
traveling the world and [ __ ] but you
know what I mean? That's probably why
I've done it so many times.
I used to love gambling on the roulette
though when I was drunk in the casinos.
Oh man, used to love it.
It was It was fun, bro.
But yeah, I just bet on the football now if that Yeah.
But yeah, I went out that Sunday, bro,
and for some reason I had like 200 pound
left until the next week. then I would
have had a thousand. So, it weren't
going to be as bad, but I wanted more money.
So, that's why I done the football bet.
I just put the 120 on the two teams and
it come in.
Otherwise, if it didn't come in, then
it wouldn't have been good.
Would have still had money and [ __ ] but
Never done never done the lottery, you
know. I've never done the lottery. Yeah.
Yeah. I said I was going to go out last
week when the Stonies were looking
fresh, Mike, but then I was like, nah,
I can't be bothered. I'd rather just
stay in. You know,
it's the same [ __ ] with the women in it. So, yeah. Yeah, man. What you
do? You know what this is for now? Do
you know what the weather's for now? Um, Mike,
the weather's for [ __ ] Guinness.
to have some nice Guinness.
Oh, I could kill for Guinness in this weather, bro.
I love Guinness.
I do like nice Guinness, bro. Yeah, man. Oh [ __ ]
I wonder if Monty would ever come back on YouTube.
What do you think? He's gone it.
Well, I'm going there. See you later.