in the bed with no bed. No money in it.
Jesus. Just Just wanted to see who's on
the YouTubes today.
Yeah. I just want to see who's on
YouTube today. Hopefully I'll be talking to myself.
So hopefully I'll be uh
talking to myself. Like I said, Yeah.
Yeah. Like I said, hopefully I'll be
talking to myself.
Isn't that right? Eh,
I'll be talking to myself
cuz everyone's got a life but me on
here. So, yeah, I'll be talking to myself.
This ain't that bad, you know.
What day is it today? Tuesday, it
is playing today, isn't it?
No, that's a different league.
Yeah, I saw Rice's window getting
smashed or Katie's window getting
smashed. What a [ __ ]
showed me. I didn't even know that happened.
What the [ __ ]
I was like, what a fake. This YouTube
just gets mad mad and murder, lad.
It gets [ __ ] mad and murdered. This
tubes first. So you got some [ __ ]
skint in the bed [ __ ] with no money in it [ __ ]
copying my holidays and going around a
different country talking about me. And
then you got some [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
windows getting smashed,
man. I didn't even [ __ ] know. I
didn't I didn't hear anything about it
until Barquest um I was talking to
Barquest yesterday and he he showed me
Yeah. What the [ __ ] bro?
And you got some [ __ ] skin virgin
[ __ ] in a bed [ __ ] with no money in
it. No bed in it. [ __ ] um
copying my little holidays. [ __ ] hell.
Imagine only going to Amsterdam just cuz
I went there. Creepy.
It's so creepy. Sheep. It's creepy. It
gives me the EBGPS.
It's so creepy,
bro. I swear to God it gives me the EB jebies, lad.
Copy my holiday. You copied my holiday
copied it. You wanted to relive what I done.
Sad bastard. Leave me alone. You virgin.
You've heard gun. You know what I mean?
Yeah, I showed it to Monty. He didn't
reply. I don't think me and Monty will
ever talk again. Not that I want to cuz
he's a snake, but I just thought I'd
just show him the thing.
But yeah, Monty's a proper proper snake. Yeah.
I need a trim, bro. Oops.
I need a [ __ ] trim, lad.
I've got the money here to do it, but I
can't be [ __ ]
Yeah, I've got um the money there to do it.
Do need a [ __ ] trim, bro. Jesus Christ.
Madness, isn't it? Could you imagine
trying to go to the airport like this? Jeez,
imagine trying to go to the airport like that. Bro,
I remember when I went to the airport
with a long beard, they asking me
[ __ ] a million and one questions, bro.
They were really asking me some mad questions.
I swear to God, bro, they thought I was a terrorist.
Like at now, at first I thought, you
know, um, you know, they were just like,
it's just procedure. But then I
realized, oh [ __ ] Yeah,
they were asking me, why are you going
here? Why are you going there? Then they
were trying to make me trick up and [ __ ] son. >> Yeah. Madness.
That is madness, bro.
This beard is getting nasty Man. Jeez,
it is getting nasty, lad. Right. Did you
see that um thing with rice getting the window smashed?
I got the money on the table. I can go
to the barbers when I want, but I can't
be [ __ ] bro. I'm keeping warm, you know.
Did you see that with [ __ ] um rice in
the windows getting smashed? I didn't
even see that until yesterday, bro. [ __ ]
See, when they done letters of me that
people knew me, they knew who I was. So,
none of that stuff happened. I moved cuz
I had a problem with a neighbor anyways. And um
obviously I was making too much noise.
So, my mom didn't want me there. But the
neighbors I never had problems with the
neighbors ever. They knew they knew
about they knew about me. They knew who I was.
They knew what I was about. So, it
whenever they try to send letters, it
would never happen because people know me.
you know, and you can tell by looking at
someone, you know, if they're a numps or
not. Like when I was in Stratford, I was
saying like, "Send the letters. You can
send the letters. No one's going to do
anything cuz people know who I am.
People know me. People know who I am.
So, it's a waste of time, bro.
But that's a mad reaction, you know,
getting your window smashed.
That would never ever happen to me, bro.
Cuz they know me. They know about me.
Did you see the skinned virgin's [ __ ]
live stream we took down? Daz.
They're skinned virgin only going to
Amsterdam just because I went. That's no
fun, is it? Copying someone. Who likes a copycat?
Who likes a copycat? as if I was in a
relationship with somebody and I was
going to take someone somewhere. I would
take them to Paris. If I was scared of
flying, I would take them to Paris. I
mean, [ __ ] what the [ __ ] would you be
going to Amsterdam? I mean, yeah. Okay,
couples do go to Amsterdam. Okay. Yeah,
they do. But I mean, it's not the first
place they go.
He's a little copycat.
He's a little copycat. I swear to God, I
can just grab him. Yeah. And just do
this. I swear to God, and do this. Look,
you're a little copycat, aren't you? You
little copycat. Like, grabbies. It' be
much easier to hold his cheeks cuz he's
his He's face looks like it's melting,
you see? So, yeah.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
You little copycat.
You're a little copycat, aren't you? You little copycat.
You little copycat. Just like the Sher
Cole thing. You little copycat, are you?
Little copycat. Little little copycat.
Little copycat. You little copycat,
mate. Copying the crowd. You want to fit
in? Bless you. You feel left out. A bless you.
You went to Amsterdam just cuz I went to
Amsterdam. What the [ __ ]
and it wasn't good enough. He had to go
a second time.
I'd never go to [ __ ] Amsterdam ever
again, bro. Don't Don't get me wrong,
there's some nice places in the
Netherlands, but Amsterdam was like, it was
I don't know, man. It was not, you know,
Dutch people are very nice and
some, like I said, some parts of the
Netherlands are nice, but [ __ ]
Amsterdam just was a [ __ ] out to be fair.
And here's the thing, you know, you talk about um
staying in a hostel. I would stay in a
hostel again. If I went to Amsterdam, I
would stay in a hostel again because
it's that experience you get staying in
a hostel. You meet people that are doing
exactly the same thing as you. Like I
would I would choose a hostel in
somewhere like Amsterdam. I would I
would stay in a hostel again definitely because it's
it's not far away, you know? It's it's
good to stay in a hostel. You know what
I'm saying? Like there's nothing wrong
with staying in a hostel. You meet
people that are solo travelers like
yourself. So, it's uh I think it's good
me staying in a hostel.
Honestly, like you won't know unless you
staying in one, but
at least staying there for a night. If
you go there for like 4 days, just stay
in there for a night. You know,
it's not bad a hostel.
Trust me, it ain't even bad.
You might meet a woman as well.
So bad staying in a hostel.
I I still have this guy on Instagram who
I met when I was in Amsterdam years ago.
It's good, man. That's good.
When should I go for a drink again, Daz?
When should I go out for a drink again? All right.
Who knows, mate? Who knows? [ __ ] never.
Not going to lie, this detox feels good, man.
Feels [ __ ] ace.
[ __ ] ace, bro. [ __ ] ace.
But yeah, shouldn't be copying people's holidays, man.
[ __ ] first went abroad when I was 23.
We have much skin for that version can.
Oh, [ __ ] me, bro.
Nah, not at all. I've got the money to
go right now and stay in a hotel if I
want to. Nah, it's good staying in a
hostel. You get to meet people doing the
same thing as you.
Yeah, I'm going to go to McDonald's.
Not necessarily. Look at [ __ ] legs.
He's [ __ ] skint [ __ ] skinned flex.
Skinner than a [ __ ] skinnier than a
[ __ ] skin flinch. Skin flinch.
No, I'm just saying there's nothing
wrong with staying in a hostel in if you
go to Amsterdam.
Nothing wrong with that.
I just can't believe nons copied my
holiday. He's a copycat.
Copycat. He's a copycat. He's copying.
He's copying the crowd.
We copying the crowd. He wants to fit
in. He wants to fit in. She
says that he didn't go there because of
me, but he definitely definitely
definitely definitely did. Trust me,
bro. No one just goes to Amsterdam as
their first holiday.
Trust me, they they they don't. They
really really don't, bro. Like, no one I
know and I know a lot of people that's
been to Amsterdam as the first place
they've gone is Amsterdam.
Trust me, bro. He's He wanted to copy
me. You want to feel left out.
Yeah. Literally only went there cuz I
went there. Cuz if you're in a
relationship and you're scared of
flying, the first place you would go to
is probably Paris.
Uh, you know, if I was going to take
someone somewhere, I would take them Paris.
>> Nope. Never going on dating apps ever
again. Waste of time.
No, bro. Yeah, literally only went there
cuz I went there
and it was bas I mean I went to Belgium
first, but I only went to Belgium
because I couldn't go to Amsterdam
because of um do you remember the
restrictions because of CO? So, I was
supposed to go to Amsterdam um
and I couldn't go because of uh
because of the restrictions. Do you
remember? So, they gave me a voucher.
So, I just went to Belgium with the voucher.
Yeah. So I went to Belgium with the
voucher and then um then I went to
Amsterdam after that in the space of
like 2 months.
So yeah, he's he's literally copying my holidays
cuz obviously I would have went to
Amsterdam first but I couldn't the
restrictions but I booked to go to Amsterdam.
Well, I remember them CO days.
I remember them CO days. So yeah, he
definitely is copying. Definitely
definitely definitely is copying
because if I was with a woman, I would
say let's go. I said to it, funny
enough, I I said to Izzy as well when we
was on talking terms, let's go to Paris
together. Remember a few years ago when
she come back, I had like I had a
voucher. Do you remember they gave me a
voucher? And um I said, "Oh, do you want
to go to Paris?"
And um she didn't want to go. So I just
went to Belgium.
So, so I know what I'm talking about
because I was actually going to go to
Paris because I because I couldn't go to Amsterdam. So,
yeah, it was a mad one.
Going all the way to Scotland to [ __ ]
escort and then come back. Yeah, that
was a madness.
I got money on the side for my haircut.
But yeah, like I said, I don't know
whether I will be uh
going out again, lad.
Look at my beard, bro. It's so long.
It's so long. Oh my god.
Do you reckon I'll be scared? to
approach when I go out again.
You reckon because I've not done it for
so long, I'll be scared now. Nah. Nah, mate.
Nah, bro. Not at all. No way.
No way, matey. Never.
You only went to Amsterdam because I
only because I went Oh my god. Copycat.
Copycat. Are you? Yeah.
I went on this um casino yesterday
and uh yeah, they have roulette.
I'm not going to lie, I was slightly tempted,
but not really. I was tiny bit tempted.
It's more of a case that if I'm low on money,
and by low on money, I mean have £500,
which still isn't really low on money.
Yes, I'll probably just gamble to be honest.
But it's not going to happen.
Oh my goodness.
But it's not going to happen. So
just like I found
there if I ever need it, you know,
if I have like 600 pound, wherever I'm
whenever I'm down to like 600 pound,
I'll just [ __ ] gamble, bro, and take
that risk of it. Cuz
you can gamble £400 and still have 200
pound left if you had 600.
You know what I'm saying? But nah, not
really. I hate gambling, but I actually hate gambling.
Yeah, there's a site that has roulette on it.
Yeah, I love my little nesticles as
well. It's too cold to go out drinking, isn't it?
Way too cold to Oh, I ordered a [ __ ]
uh chicken mac last night.
Yeah, I was hungry, so I just ordered a
nice chicken mac.
I need to go watch the strangers in a
couple of days. Um,
I don't like women, bro,
for the fact that they're [ __ ]
You know, they're nice to look at and
stuff, but they're really not worth [ __ ]
to be honest with you, bro.
They're just they're just [ __ ]
That's what takes the fun out of it.
They're just [ __ ]
But I don't like gambling. I only use
gambling when I need [ __ ] money,
which is why I hardly gamble because I'm
not short of money. But
I don't know, bro.
I [ __ ] like women their [ __ ]
to be honest. They ain't [ __ ] They
really aren't [ __ ] bro.
Women aren't [ __ ] Really, man.
It's mad. You get these accounts coming
and say, "Oh, when did you last how's
the gambling?" Like I've said a million
times, I don't gamble. I don't play [ __ ] roulette.
Once every 3 months, maybe [ __ ]
Yeah, cuz I had loads of money. I didn't
spend a lot on them.
Not at all.
To be honest with you, I don't even
think I'll ever get an escort again. To
be honest, I I ain't got no sex drive. I
can't be bothered.
Where's that Joe F account? He's disappeared. Yes. Yes.
There's only ever been one. Yeah. It was £45.
Yeah. And she gave me her body. So, good
transaction, isn't it?
Her body for £45.
I say £45 because the other £45 was my
stake. So, you can't really count that.
You can't count £100.
That's cheaper than an escort.
That's way cheaper than an actual escort
as well. That's like 20 cheaper than an
escort. So, but I didn't want to just
have sex and [ __ ] off. I wanted to
actually meet someone.
So yeah, if you look at it's a good
transaction, but I actually wanted to meet someone
and they [ __ ] lovebombed me. So,
but yeah, it was a good transaction
cuz it was 90, but like I said, half of
it was mine. So, yeah,
half of it was mine, so you can't count
yours, can you? Really?
So your meal and their meal was only £10
more than an actual escort.
So it worked out perfect really in it.
But obviously half of it was yours. So
but I don't like women. They're just [ __ ]
I don't like women, bro. They're all the same.
And I don't like gambling either. So,
do you think you could still win on that
online roulette on that? I don't think
so, bro. I don't think so. What do you think?
This is This is going to sound mad to
you, bro. But if I was actually going to
put money on roulette again, I'd
probably play the one in the bookies. I
know it sounds so mad cuz it's a bar
roulette, is it? But I feel like you got
more of a chance with that. And
obviously I can't get in casinos
anymore. I feel like online is just super rigged
which is probably why I don't even play
anymore to be honest with you. I played
it about two weeks ago. I put £100 on it
but I mean come on you know
what do you think about the online
roulette? It's got to be fixed it.
It's got to be fixed it. It has to be.
The online one's got to be fixed in it
cuz of this. How many numbers that I
cover and how it just continuously misses.
Yeah, I remember before I put 60 on the
bar roulette and I took out a thousand,
but I was 260 in. Yeah.
No, I've not played that. I played at
bar weeks ago. Like I said, I'm not like
Timmy. He's prop he's a proper addict.
I'm not addict I won't get addicted. If
I lose, I won't chase my losses because
I don't want to risk going broke.
That's just one thing I don't want to do
is risk going broke
no matter how much money I get. I mean,
I can't like see when I lost that 100
pound, I could kind of justify it. Oh,
it's only £100. You know, I won football
bets and that.
But it's like,
you know what I mean?
Yeah, that bar roulette. You probably could
probably got more chance of winning on
that to be fair.
So yeah, I don't like women to answer
your question. They're just [ __ ]
They' be nice if they weren't such [ __ ]
But a [ __ ] can't even offer me nothing.
You know, I was actually thinking about
this, bro. Like what what what's what
can they offer you? They can't offer you
nothing. They can't offer me money cuz I
got my own money.
They can't offer me independence cuz I'm
already independent. They can't offer me
[ __ ] all. I mean, yeah, they can give
you sex and [ __ ] but I mean, they
really can't offer me [ __ ] So, it's
like I don't need anything from them.
But if I go out drinking, I know what
people say like, "Yeah, you can just go
out drinking for yourself." But you got
to you got to approach cuz it's just like
who the [ __ ] would go out drinking and
not even meet anyone new. That's just
ridiculous. I mean if you're drinking
you [ __ ] you are going to speak to
people cuz I don't know you might just
like the look of someone whilst you're
drunk. I don't [ __ ] know. But bro, I
know a [ __ ] can't offer me nothing. So
I mean that's that it.
That's the way I see it.
They literally can't offer me anything.
So, except sex. Oh, [ __ ] well. Who
cares, you know? So,
that's why I don't really care for for
them, bro. I don't really give a [ __ ]
And the fact that they play all of these
mind games, it's just not worth it in my
my opinion. It's just not worth it.
They were actually nice people. They
weren't time wasters.
Then, you know, maybe I'd see it a bit
different, but they have they got
nothing to offer me, bro.
They can't offer me [ __ ] these women. So, Cuz
you always hear about, oh, what have you
got to offer? What have they got to
What have they got to offer? Don't want
kids. Never wanted kids. So, I mean,
my sex drive's gone down now as well.
So, I don't really have a sex drive. I
don't really give a [ __ ] but to be honest, So yeah. So yeah,
if you'd asked me back in the day, I
don't know, bro. Probably
Yeah. They got nothing to offer me. So,
it's just not worth it.
It doesn't matter what I'd answer, bro.
They've got nothing to offer me, you
know, and they and and the fact that
they play all of these stupid games,
it's just not worth it, bro.
It's just it's just not worth it, bro. I
don't I don't even think I'll use an
escort again. I don't even give a [ __ ]
for sex. I don't care, bro. Honestly,
cuz you realize Yeah. Like at a certain
point, you've done all of this [ __ ]
before. The gambling, the women, the
[ __ ] It's boring now, bro.
Like I said, that's probably why I don't
even gamble much anymore cuz I'm so
bored of it. I've done it so many times
and I have done it more than Timmy as
well. Don't let him think that, oh, cuz
he's [ __ ] 42, he's gambled more than
me. He ain't got he ain't gambled more
than me, bro.
You know, I've got a lot of I've got a
lot more life experience than a lot of
people. Not everybody, obviously. Not [ __ ] everybody.
Like, for example, Seven Neighbors, he's
gambled more than me. There's no denying
that, you know, but like
I feel like I've got a lot of lot more
life experience than a lot of people.
I have been in a relationship. And also
another thing is I don't know why you
keep trying to use that against me
because a I have been in a relationship
and another thing is you know when
you're in a relationship you're in a
relationship with one woman you're not
in a relationship with all of the female
population. So I don't know why you
think that just because someone's been
in a relationship with one person they
seem to know everything about every
woman. A relationship is with one woman.
That's not 90 That's not 99% of the
female population. So why do you seem to
think that people that's had a or two
relationships know everything about
every single woman? That does not make
any sense at all. I've been with It's
like me. I've been with [ __ ] way more
women than nonslegs. I don't need to be
in more relationships to know what women
are like. You don't need to be in a
relationship with a woman,
right? You don't need to be in a
relationship with a woman to know what
they're all like. What the [ __ ]
That don't make sense. So,
and that is one woman. That is one
woman. That's not [ __ ] multiple
women. You don't need to be in a
relationship with a woman to [ __ ]
know what women are like.
So, and I have had a relationship.
So again, it's just self-p projecting.
We're trying to have a normal
conversation and you're coming on here
self- projecting again. Yeah, bro. Just
like people ain't got no money and they
show you money and you run away. Just
like people ain't got no friends and
they've showed you. It's just self projection.
You need to grow up, bro. You're older
than me now.
And what I was saying, Greavesy, is that
um yeah, I had a chicken mac last night.
We're going to go McDonald's in a bit to
be honest. I've got some vouchers.
We was just saying before this [ __ ] um
rudely interrupted is that uh basically
a woman can't offer me anything.
Like when you think about it, right, I
don't really have a sex drive anymore.
They can't offer me anything.
Most of them are not nice people. So,
it's like they can't really offer you
[ __ ] all if you think about it.
except headaches. The only thing that
they can offer you is headaches.
And then the fact that they play all of
these stupid games, then it's not worth
it, bro. In my opinion, it's just not worth it.
The dating game is just not worth it anymore, Grezy.
I don't think it I don't think it's worth it.
I don't know about you, but yeah, they
ain't got [ __ ] all to offer me. So, I
don't give a [ __ ] about them.
But yeah, I'm going to get a um going to
go to McDonald's in a bit.
They can't offer you [ __ ] all you know.
I'm all right by myself, bro. I'm all
right by myself.
No, even if I still had a sex drive, I
still wouldn't give a [ __ ]
No, it's not fact. I've got more I've
got a better outlook on life than you.
What? Because my whole life don't
revolve around women. Shouldn't you be
back on L J's channel?
What I think is [ __ ] is that you're
coming on here talking about people that
you don't know. That's what I think is [ __ ]
You know what? Because my life don't
revolve around women. Whoa, bro. What?
Because a woman can't offer me nothing.
My outlook is [ __ ] Oh, okay, bro. Yeah, whatever.
You know, I can be happy about myself. I
don't need to be like Nlegs with a disabled girl
[ __ ] copying people's holidays.
Imagine having to copy someone's holiday.
That's that's a new one, you know. But yeah.
So yeah, but yeah, they can't offer me
nothing. Women can't offer me [ __ ] all. So yeah,
but it's I find it funny how you think
just because you've been in a
relationship with one or two women, you
all of a sudden know about women. I know
more about women than non-flex. I've
slept with more women than him. I've
been on more dates than him. I've met
normal women. Just because he might have
had two relationships, that doesn't mean
that he knows more about women than me.
That's two relationships
with two two women. Well, two spastics,
but you you know what I mean?
Ah, he can't afford it. Ah, he can't
afford it, lad. I was actually going to
give him one of my stonies
to um to help him lose his virginity.
Now he can't afford it.
He can't afford it. That's why I'm
thinking of giving him one and buy myself one.
Buy myself another one. I was actually
thinking of giving him a Sony.
Maybe he'll finally get a laid. I'll
just go to the shop and buy myself
another one. It's not a problem.
Not a problem at all, you know. But
obviously he can't afford Stony. It's
bit out of his price range.
Bit out of his bit out of his budget,
you see. So
I know it's so Oh, it is bad, bro. Do
you think you'd see me on on the street
wearing them [ __ ] ugly skin charity
shop globes? No wonder he's still a virgin.
I do feel bad for him for him in a way though.
You could just tell he hates the fact
that I'm better looking than him. Like
at first, right, I thought like, yeah,
it's just taking a piss, isn't it? At
first, I thought it was um but his style
was very very very very bad.
And you know, he he will die a virgin.
His style was very very very bad. And I
feel sorry for him because all of these
videos that he does, it just goes to
show how insecure he actually is.
It just proves it, you know, grieves
you. Like you've got somebody that's
paid that you you've got someone that's paid money.
He's got someone that's paid his
clothing is not nice at all. He looks
[ __ ] weird. He doesn't know how to
dress. No, he's he's his clothing is not
nice, mate. I'll show you nice clothing
when I go out next. And I don't mean
Stone Island. You want a slick look,
I'll give you a slick look next time.
Yeah. And I'm not talking about designer
clothes. I'm talking about non-designer
clothes, bro. He He can't even dress properly.
He can't even dress properly, bro. But anyways,
back to what I was saying. So, you
actually paid money to go on holiday.
You've actually you've actually paid
money to go on holiday. Right.
And you're coming on YouTube talking
about me whilst you're on holiday, bro.
It just shows that he knows I'm better
looking than him. That's why I don't
waste much time on him because I know
I'm better than him. I know I've got
more money than him. I know that I've
had a better life than him. I've got a
better life. And so then if I waste my
time on someone, then I'm contradicting myself.
He says that you're this, you're that,
but he still wastes all of his life
talking about you.
So it what he's saying can't be true.
And he's on holiday doing it as well.
He's on holiday doing it as well. So you
can't even say that he's doing it for
reaction because he's actually doing it on holiday.
So I mean that in itself is just sad. So
but no, he's his style was [ __ ] gay.
He ain't got no style. It's why he's
still a virgin.
And you know when when he always says,
"Oh, I'm trying to convince people." I'm
not trying to convince anyone anything.
I'm telling you, you're the biggest
virgin going and you'll never get laid.
And I don't care what disabled girl you
show. You will die a virgin.
You will die a [ __ ] virgin, mate.
Jesus Christ. You'll die one.
But yeah, he he's he he's literally
self-p projecting. He was saying that
like a woman would a woman's got to be
out of her mind,
right? Out of her mind to go near me.
But I've been with more women than he
has. That's self projection. If you
actually listen carefully, right, to
these little gay virgin videos, it's
just self projection. A woman's got to
be crazy to go anywhere near me because
I'm ugly. Bro, you're not even believing
what you're saying. I've been with more
women than you. I've been on more dates
than you. Not not to sound immature. And
I've been in a relationship. And I've
also had chances to be in relationships.
More relationships. So what what what
are you getting at? I don't understand.
You call me ugly because I'm a million
times better looking than you are.
Think of it. You tried to get You tried
to get with every single woman that I've
been with. USA is Izzy. Um, you've
messaged Sig. You've literally tried it
on with women that you can't get due to
your ugly looks that I've already been
with. So, everything you're saying,
you're just it's just screaming insecure
now. Every time you're doing this, it
doesn't matter how it doesn't matter how
long my two relationships was, you know.
So, you don't need to be in a
relationship with a woman either to know
what women are like.
That's not how that works. Like, you get
these people that are in a relationship
with one woman and they think they know
everything about all women because
they've been in a relationship with one person.
One [ __ ] person.
That is insane. What the [ __ ]
That doesn't mean you know that means
you know [ __ ] all, you know.
I think I would know about more more
about women than a lot of people because
I've met thousands of them.
I've met [ __ ] so many of them and
they all seem to be the same.
So, they're all exactly the same.
You know what I'm saying? They're all
literally all the same.
And it's not about what I say. It's not
about what you say. It's not about I'm
right, you're wrong. You're right,
you're wrong. It's about the fact, this
is the way I'd put it, that you have
gave these women multiple chances to
prove you wrong to prove that they're
not the same and they couldn't do it.
That's that. There's no, oh, you know,
[ __ ] you're right, I'm right, I'm
wrong, you're wrong. There's none of
that. It's you have gave them the
opportunity to prove that they're not
all the same and they can't do it.
So, it's there's no argument to be had
really. It's no, oh, well, I've been in
a relationship. Well, you No, it's not
that. It's about you've gave them
chances. They can't prove you [ __ ]
They can't prove themselves to be different. So,
you know, concerning, is it really?
So, yeah, they are they are all the
same. Definitely. Of course, they're all the same.
They've all got Tik Tok brains. [ __ ] ridiculous.
But yeah, he's, you know, he's not even
happy in his relationship.
That's why he tried to get on to all of
my sloppy seconds. But yeah, I'm the one
that's too ugly to get with a woman.
[ __ ] hell, bro. That's crazy, bro.
That is insane.
I've had sex with more people than him.
I've had more [ __ ] than him. And I'm
not in and I'm not including escorts.
He hates the fact that he is the ugly
bastard that has to be with Sarah,
you know. And do you know why I say that
she's disabled? Not because she can't
talk. She's disabled because do you
think a normal person would let their
boyfriend start messaging random women
about their sex life? Do you think a
normal woman would allow their boyfriend
to keep talking about somebody whilst
they're on holiday? No woman would do
that. That's how you know she's disabled.
You know, you remember when Monty used
to get a bollockin for doing certain
[ __ ] things by from [ __ ] Kaye. So
that's how you know she's she's
disabled. Not about talking or not
talking. That is one of the reasons. But
you know like Yeah.
Everything he does is self projecting.
When he calls people skin, he is skin.
Don't care if he's showing 13 grand.
That's skin. Three years of saving,
that's skin. Um, you know, ugly. You're
I don't care what he says. I I just
think it's mad.
I just think it's mad how someone's on holiday.
Um and can you stop calling him that as
well? I hate it when people call him that,
you know. Um
he doesn't deserve that um sort of
nickname, that little cute nickname. So,
could you stop calling him that, please?
Just call him by his first name. I I
don't care what people say. I'm telling
you why he's doing it. He's self projecting.
Ugly skin. That's literally him. That's
what I'm I'm not asked. I'm telling you
why he's doing it.
You know what I'm saying? So, it's cuz
he's the one that's skinned. He's the
one that's ugly. He's the one that can't
get nothing normal. Just telling you
that in it like straight in it. So,
nope. It seriously doesn't. He's the one
that's got a channel on me. He's the one
that went live about me yesterday.
No, not at all. I don't even waste my
time on that virgin because I know I'm
better than him. I don't waste my time
because I know that I'm better than him.
People that waste their life on people
that they're calling every day shows
that you're not better than them.
You know, like he tries to say that I'm
skint and I'm this and I'm that, but he
wastes his life on me every day, which
the more someone does it, the more the
arrow goes back onto them, you know. So, yeah.
No, he's the one that's got a channel
obsessed with me. You might want to open
your eyes, buddy. He's the one that's
got a virgin channel. He's the one
that's copying my holidays. He's the one
that's talking about me on holiday. I'm
not doing any of that [ __ ]
He's the one that's got a channel
dedicated to stalking me, going on holidays
that I've been on, talking about me,
stalking all the women that I've been
with. Nah, bro. That's not me. That's
that virgin boy. And then you ask
yourself the question is that
how long is this going to go on for?
Because you need to understand like that
how long is this actually going to go on for
and then you think oh it's going to go
on forever like they're never going to
stop in it. So that's how you know that
you're not the one that's you're not the
one that's the ma these people are the
one that are these things because if
they wasn't they would live their life
and just never go on about you ever again.
But the fact that they do,
it just shows everything that you need to know.
You know what I'm saying?
It's literally He is obsessed with me. Literally obsessed.
No, I'm not obsessed with him. He's the
one that's obsessed with me. He's the
one that's gone on holiday talking about
me on holiday.
No, I don't think about that ugly virgin.
The only thing I think of sometimes is
when the [ __ ] is he going to leave me alone? So
yeah. No, no, no. He's the one that's
definitely definitely obsessed with me.
Definitely. Definitely. He's the one
obsessed with me. Yes, because he ran to
the police playing the victim.
Yes. Because he went to the police
playing the victim and went crying to
the police when I put posters up cuz he
tried to stop my income. Yes. Yes.
Yeah. Anyways, we're not talking about
this. I know what you're trying to do
anyways. It's not going to work. Moving
on. Um Yeah, moving on. Anyways,
my phone needs charging anyway, dude.
So, yeah, I know what you're trying to
do. Like I said, when when these if
you're not fat and ugly like these
people, they get jealous of you. And
when they're jealous of you, they're
biased. We'll move on from this now. We
see where this is going. We're moving
on. And I know what you're trying to do
and it's not going to work. So, we're
having the same argument over and over
again. It's not going to work. I know
what you're trying to do. Anyone with
two brain cells can see that he's the
one that's obsessed with me. And I'm not
answering any more questions. So,
But yeah, it will never ever end. But
apparently I'm the skin m apparently.
Interesting. Well, let me tell you
something, Grezy. These people waste a
lot of their time on someone that's
apparently a skin m every single day.
>> They spend an awful lot of their time on
someone that's a skin bun. Let me tell you that.
Which goes to show that, like I said,
you're not the ski bun. And the reason
you've got so many middle-aged men that
gravitate towards you is because you're
younger than them. You're better looking
than them. Um you got hope unlike them.
Had a better life than them. These
people are no hopers. So they gravitate
towards anyone that's
in a better position than them.
Why do you think you got so many old men
obsessed with me, bro?
Why do you think you've got so many old
men that's obsessed with me, Grezy?
Answer that question.
I was speaking to Barquest yesterday on
WhatsApp and I fell asleep.
But no, that [ __ ] is the one that's
obsessed with me going on holiday
talking about me. [ __ ] hell.
I don't understand what it is with
people with um autism.
They just don't seem to understand. When
somebody don't want you, they don't want you.
And they go on and on and on and on and
on and on and on and on and on. [ __ ]
hell. Don't meet someone with [ __ ]
autism, mate. Jesus Christ.
Don't meet someone with [ __ ] autism. Yeah.
Did you see Rice's window get smashed?
Well, Katie's window gets smashed.
Grieves. I didn't even know about it,
lad. I didn't even [ __ ] know about it
until [ __ ] Bathquest showed me it. Yeah.
Um, I'll send you it now. One sec.
Mine and LT's rivalry.
It It reminds you of mine and LT's rivalry, bro.
One second, bro.
I got barbers, bro.
People think I'm a terrorist. [Music] Yeah.
This phone's almost had it. Mark Quest.
This phone has almost had it.
No, no, no, no.
Yeah. Did you watch it, Grezy?
I don't know how I didn't know about
that. I didn't even hear about it.
Yeah. Madness, isn't it? Bring it on.
Bring it on,
Ruby. Bring it on,
you vegetable bastard. Yeah, Madness, eh?
Can't believe nonslegs copied my [ __ ] holiday.
I was going to do a video about this. Grezy
[ __ ] copied my [ __ ] holiday. He
copied my holiday. Grezy, little copycat. Little copycat.
Yeah, I don't owe no one money, mate. If
you actually listen to what I said
properly, you would have known that.
Never been in debt to the barber shop.
Stop talking [ __ ] Never been on in debt
to the barber shop and I never ever said
I was in debt. If you actually listen
properly, you [ __ ]
I was nowhere near a pass point because
they only accept cash. So then I went
the next day because I couldn't be
bothered to go back round. So stop
talking [ __ ] If you're going to tell a
[ __ ] story, at least get it right and
stop making stuff up, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, you are skin. Yeah, we know you're
skin. I know you are, but what am I?
Yeah, you are skin.
Yeah. Yeah, you are skinn. We know you are.
We know you're skinned, mate. We know you are.
Stop talking about yourself.
It's not nice. It's not good for your
mental health, matey.
Yeah, you need to stop calling yourself
skin. It's not nice. You just stop
talking about yourself.
I've got money right here actually next
to me, greasy, funny enough. But I'm not
showing nothing. I don't show self-reflectors money.
I don't show projectors money.
Been there, done that. More than a t-shirt.
Yeah, I don't have money. Yeah, yeah,
yeah. You keep telling yourself that. Listen, Grezy,
is this not the sound of money?
Grezy, is that not the sound of money?
Come on, tell us, Greezy.
Is this or is this not the sound of money?
I think you would know, mate, if you
rubbed it. You know, I'm not showing you
nothing. You little self-reflectors.
Every single time you get show money,
you run away.
Every single time you get shown money,
you run away. And the community is
already [ __ ] dying. I don't want any
more of you little mongos to run away.
You all run away.
Anyways, we're not responding to this um
[ __ ] now. Anyways, this little self projector. Yeah.
Anyways, so I said to Bquest, I will
forgive you uh if you buy me GTA 6.
Yeah, if you buy me GTA 6, I'll forgive you.
I'm not even blocking this account. I'm
going to let them continue to self-reflect. Yo, [ __ ] sake.
Yeah, man. So [ __ ]
um I can't believe you got people
[ __ ] copying my holidays now.
I can't believe that. Greasy
trying to say that you wasn't copying my
holiday. He literally was copying my
You literally are a copycat.
Any normal person that's got a
girlfriend would go to Paris.
This is where I was supposed to go.
So, yeah. Again, we're ignoring your
little self-p projecting comments. We're not interested.
We're not interested in your little
self-reflecting um comments. go
self-reflect on another channel.
You would go to Paris.
You would actually go to Paris because
that's where I was going to go
originally. Well, I was going to go
Amsterdam, but because I couldn't and I
went to I wasn't going to go Paris
cuz I was speaking to someone. So, I was
actually going to go Paris, you see. So,
yeah. I can't afford Yeah, bro. I've got
more life experience than he would ever
have in a year. More money, more
clothes. I've been with more women. I've
been abroled more times than him. I've
been to more places.
The guy is literally skinn. He don't
even have a bed.
You literally don't even have a bed.
He's [ __ ] skint.
And you don't know what I can afford and
what I can't afford. You don't know how
much money I've got.
So yeah, keep self projecting. You're
not going to bait me into showing you
money again? Yeah, 13 grand. Listen,
listen, listen, listen. Before I get
into this, yeah, 13 grand is nothing.
That's not even 6 months money.
13 grand is nothing. I would not trade
£13,000 for a year of my life
experiences. So what? Whilst I was
living life, going to restaurants, going
on dates, traveling, he was in his
bedset with no bed, with no money in it,
trying to save that 13 grand. Bro, I
would rather [ __ ] I would rather have
the life experiences than the 13 grand.
You know, life experiences take to the
grave with your money you can't. So, at
the end of the day, yeah, you got no
life experiences for 13 grand.
Congratulations. It shows how skinn you really are.
So, at the end of the day, no one no one
cares about that, bro.
And 13 grand is [ __ ] nothing.
You know what I've done in 3 years?
Do you know what I've done in three years?
A lot of [ __ ] Grezy, you saw all the
[ __ ] I've done in 3 years.
So mate, I'd rather have life
experiences in 3 years than be sat in
that shitty skin ugly bed sit and in out
of London with no money. [ __ ] that, bro.
Yeah. I don't have life experiences.
Yeah. Okay. Yeah. You keep telling yourself that
13 grand wouldn't even last you a [ __ ] year.
wouldn't even wouldn't even last you a
year. You're going on like 13 grand a
million pounds. [ __ ] hell, bro. Crazy.
Anyways, I'm going to ban these little mongos now.
Bye-bye, mongos. You can go selflect and
repeat on another channel. Bye-bye you little mongos.
It's true. This is what I'm going to do
now, Greavvesy. Right. When I do this video,
after I show the Stony, right, I'm going
to make myself right here because I'm
going to say, "Okay, well, after this video,
let's um see who goes on about who first
and then we will see who the jealous one
is." So, I have all of these things
apparently. Okay. Well, then if that's
the case, then you're not going to waste
your life on me anymore. You've got all
this money, but in reality, you don't
have anything. But you got all of this
money, all of this life, then you're not
going to do any more videos and you're
not going to do any more community posts.
Simple. And if you still do it, then
everything you're saying is not true
because Grezy, people don't waste their
life on people that they're better than.
It's like these little mongos here,
right? These little bongos here,
they are the ones that are skin. They
are the ones that ain't got no life.
That's why they are on here doing this.
You don't understand? Because they have
nothing but YouTube. Literally, they
have nothing but [ __ ] YouTube, bro.
It's literally all they have. This This
YouTube is all they have. This is their
lives. It will always be their lives.
Just like virgin boy is a low life. Who
goes on holiday to go on about someone. So
you can tell it's jealousy because
people just would leave people alone.
I'd hate to be the bear. I hate to be
the bearer of bad news bad news. Greasy.
You know I hate it when people use the
word jealousy. But what else is it?
someone. If you're sat there calling
someone every day what they are
apparently and then you keep going on
about them every day, it doesn't look
good, does it?
It doesn't look good.
But I don't know who I'm trying to I
mean, we know all of this stuff anyways,
but no one's going to admit it cuz
they're jealous of me. So, I mean, it's
it is jealousy as well, which it takes
it takes the bigger person. what what
this virgin does it is it is jealousy.
That's why I don't really waste my time.
But sometimes I get like I get too deep
in, you know, Skin Boy and the Virgin
with no bed in it, you know, cuz it's
funny. But it is it is jealousy. Cuz if
it wasn't jealousy, Mike, they wouldn't
do this. If they were all of the things
that they're trying to call you,
um, then they would just live their life.
they would say it and then live their
life. But if they can't and they keep
doing it, then it's jealousy. There's
nothing else it could [ __ ] well be.
You know, there's literally nothing else
it could be.
Yep. They call me skin even though every
time I show them money, they run away.
I'm not showing them nothing, bro. I'm
not showing them no money.
You got some little virgin copying your holiday.
Literally copying your holiday. What the [ __ ]
And they keep going on about this
£13,000, bro. I would ra I would not trade £13,000
for a year of my life experiences, let
alone three years. Do you not understand
what life experiences are?
You take them to the [ __ ] grave with
you. You know,
there's no point being sat in in a
[ __ ] virgin shitty bed with no
[ __ ] bed in it for [ __ ] 3 years.
You know what I mean? Bye-bye.
Made another account just to get
blocked. It says a lot about these people's lives,
bike, doesn't it? It says a lot about
these people's lives, son.
Exactly. It It's because I went He's a copycat.
He's a copycat. Well, Mike, I actually
went to Belgium because I was supposed
to go to Amsterdam,
but he doesn't remember the Belgium one.
I was supposed to go to Amsterdam, but I
couldn't go cuz the restrictions. So,
they gave me a voucher, and then I was
going to go to Paris with Izzy, and then
she said she didn't want to go. So, I
was actually going to go to Paris with
someone. Then, because she didn't want
to go, then I I had to pick Belgium. And
then I went to Amsterdam cuz with the
restrictions and [ __ ] So if you were
scared of flying, your first holiday
would be Paris.
If you was in a relationship with
someone, you would go to Paris. He went
to Amsterdam just cuz I went.
Literally just cuz I went. Uh-uh.
Yeah. It's literally 1% of the
population's first holiday was Amsterdam. Yep.
He's a copycat. He's He's obsessed.
He's an obsessed copycat virgin.
That's what he is, bro. No one's first
[ __ ] holiday is [ __ ]
Amsterdam, bro. You know what the [ __ ]
My mind was, but I was probably in the
1%. But what's the chance that he's also was
It's cuz he's copier. He's a copycat.
I don't think he remembers the [ __ ]
Belgian one. Nah, it's like when he says
if you don't like Cheryl Cole, um,
you're gay. Yeah, that's copying. He's a
copycat. He's a little copycat. Little copycat.
Do you like cats,
Mike? Do you like cats?
But yeah, I can't afford to go to Amsterdam, bro.
And he said, "I stayed in a hostel
because I couldn't afford." Yeah, I
know, bro. Because it took me to 31 to
go abroad, isn't it? Because I couldn't
afford it. Yeah, it it took me till 31
to go abroad.
Or was that him? H I think it was him, wasn't it? Yeah.
Trying to say that I couldn't afford to
stay in a hotel, my man. And it took you
until 31 to go abroad. That's how skint
you was. You literally had to sacrifice
your prime years of living for 13 grand. For £13,000.
Mike, I can't tell you how many designer
clothes I've got, restaurants I've been,
escorts I've [ __ ] places I've
traveled to, the amount I've gambled,
the amount I've drunk.
Do you understand, bro? Like, I wouldn't
trade that for [ __ ] no 13 grand. I
wouldn't even trade it. Trade it for 26
grand. Why the [ __ ] would you?
You know what I mean, Mike? Why the [ __ ]
would you, lad?
It took you to [ __ ] 31 to go abroad
and you're talking about people not
being able to [ __ ] afford things,
mate. What the [ __ ] I mean,
who's got a point? Nah.
So, yeah, you're showing 13 grand, but
bro, I've lived the life. This is
probably like why I'm so bored of
drinking. This is probably why I'm so um
bored of going out drinking and
approaching because I've done it so many times.
I've done it so many [ __ ] times. You
know what I mean?
More than most people my aids probably,
you know, even if you're even going to
bars in [ __ ] London, bro, it's still life experiences.
[ __ ] the steak restaurants. You think I
would trade that for 13 [ __ ] grand,
bro? You mad? Wouldn't even last you
[ __ ] 8 months? 13 grand. But yeah,
way more than a thousand.
Stayed in some nice hotels. Went
traveled around the country. Went
abroad. I went abroad when I was 23.
I went a [ __ ] broad when I was 23.
That's the first time I went abroad when
I was 23 and I went twice in a month.
No, I think I went March and April. I
think I went So, March and April and
that was the first time.
Obviously, he would have copied a lot
sooner, but obviously he didn't have the
funds cuz he skinted.
So yeah, mate, you didn't have the funds
cuz you was [ __ ] skimp ski bastard.
What the [ __ ] did you do in them 3 years?
Went to a few [ __ ] virgin fence, you know?
Yeah, I just can't be bothered with it
anymore. I can't be bothered with it anymore. Mike,
I don't know when I'll be out again drinking.
I need to get a haircut, bro.
I got some money on the side to get my
haircut, but I can't be asked.
And I Why? And why do you think he
[ __ ] got jealous with all of these
women that I got with USA? Is he and
stuff? Because he couldn't afford to go
on these dates. He couldn't afford to um
go to these bars in London cuz they're
not [ __ ] cheap, mate.
They're not [ __ ] cheap.
So, I mean, he says that you're this,
you're that, you're this, you're that,
but he's the one that waste his life on
you every day.
It doesn't look right, does it?
I fancy a t-bone. You know,
I actually fancy a t-bone steak.
Now, we're talking about restaurants. I
actually fancy t-bone snake, but I'm
nowhere near the [ __ ] butchers. Oh,
what time does it shut? Six. No,
I'm nowhere near the I'm nowhere near
the butchers anymore. That's the
problem. I used to live up the road. I
want to see if I don't know if I would
be able to get there in time, but he
can't afford it. He's [ __ ] skinned in
the fy skin.
What do you think will happen, Mike, if
I go out on Friday drinking and
approaching? What do you think will happen
if I go out in the stony and do some approaches?
What do you think would happen? Yeah,
I could probably guess what would happen.
I fancy a t-bone, bro.
No, no, no. What? What do you think will
happen? Obviously, I'll groom before I
do it. I'll go to the barbers before I
do it, obviously. But what do you think will happen?
I mean, it doesn't matter if you get
groomed or not. You're still going to
get the I've got a boyfriend.
You're still going to get rejected. Even
when you look to Max, you're still going
to get rejected.
But I don't know. I really fancy going
and drinking some Guinness, you know,
man. It's It's getting cold now. I love Guinness. So,
I mean, believe it or not, if I look
like this and I look groomed, it's going
to be the same result. I know. It's a
hard one, isn't it?
It's a hard one to believe, but even if I groom Yeah,
I can wear my nice after shave, be
nicely groomed, then you still won't get [ __ ]
But I mean, I expect I think it's
happened so many times. I just expect it now, bro.
I've got my after shave as well, my my
Dior Savage after shave. I don't think I
could live without it to be fair. So,
I'm going to get McDonald's, I think,
cuz I got some vouchers.
I got some vouchers. So, you look at me
like this. I'm way better looking than
nonsense. But he calls me ugly.
He calls me ugly, but I'm way better
looking than him even like this. [ __ ] madness. [ __ ] hell.
Way better looking. Had more women. Have
more money. More life experiences.
I wonder why he goes for me every day. H some people.
I mean, let's look at the facts. Mike,
I've been with more women,
got more money, shown more money. He
hasn't shown 14 grand. That's in his
head. He's never shown 14 grand. more
life experiences, better looking, been
with better women. I wonder why he goes
from me every day.
Who's going to buy a mystery box?
That's a big mystery, isn't it?
I wonder why, Mike. I wonder why he goes
for me every day.
More money, better looks, better clothes, more women.
H I wonder why. Maybe it's because I'm
the skin bun.
Yeah, maybe it's just that, isn't it,
mate? Yeah, I mean, he already tried it
on with USA Izzy.
He tried it on with USA, but she didn't
want him. She didn't want to know. Bit
like Britney did didn't want to know
him, mate. Yeah.
No life. He's literally stalked every
single woman that I've been with. But
I'm so ugly, bro. Oh, can you help me,
mate? Can you help me?
Yeah, I'm so ugly, bro. I'm so ugly that
it takes you going all the way to
Amsterdam to to do a video on me. Yeah,
I'm pretty sure I'm the ugly skinned
one, mate. Not you. Yeah. Yeah, mate.
Yeah. Yeah, right, bro. Yeah, [ __ ] right.
See this little bit? Oh, no. I don't
want to show money. I was going to show
money, but obviously I don't want to
show these people money. Obviously,
I don't like showing these people money.
Grezy, you know what I'm like, mate.
But I was just going to say this is my
haircut money. This money right here is
just to get groomed.
Yeah, I would. Yeah, definitely, mate. Definitely. Yeah,
because I've got better looks, better clothes,
you know, better looks. I would. Yeah,
believe it or not, I would.
Did you see that girl that I [ __ ]
over? Like, I got her to go to the pub
and I didn't show up. She's lucky that's
all she got, bro. [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] going around trying to be a
[ __ ] I told her that I done um Uber,
right? And I earn 90 in a day on Uber
and she was trying to say, "Oh, like you
know, you're better than that. You're
better than working all day for that." I
was like, "Bro, who are you to judge anybody?
If people want to earn £100 a day, they
can earn £100 a day if they want. Who
are you to [ __ ] tell people what the
[ __ ] they should be earning? Who are
you, man?" And I only done the Uber
thing for a laugh. I just done it cuz
I mean I didn't need the money but I
just thought why not just do it. You know
this is what puts me off going out and
doing it again. Mike I can't be bothered
bro with them. I I can have a man bun now. Look.
Oh, don't forget by the way I'm balding.
Don't forget I'm bored.
Don't forget I'm bored, lad.
Yeah, is a waste of time and money. And
we don't have money to be wasted anymore, matey.
We're not as rich as Well, it's not even
just that, lad.
It's more I'd rather do other things now.
I mean, most normal people get tired of [ __ ]
I mean it would only if I went out
drinking it's only going to cost about £80
but like I feel like no you should still
go out you know every month or every two
months you know for like a relief like
just you know what I'm saying
how much weight I've put on I've not put
on any weight fatty bomb I've not put on
any weight fatty bomb you're looking at yourself again
fatty bomb You're looking at yourself
again. You're the one that ran off.
You're the one that ran off of YouTube
when your ugly face got out there more self-projecting.
You are the ugliest thing I have ever
seen. You and nonslegs are the ugliest
things I have ever seen in my life. This
is what I'm saying. It's all self
projection. This is ex This is exactly
what I'm saying, mate. With these
people, it's self projection. This is
why I don't even bother really coming on
here much anymore because it's just a
fat ugly people that hate that you're
better than them. But listen, listen.
Let me tell you what it is. Yeah. These
people like Bomb, they're fat. They got
no money. Don't believe what he shows
you, bro. When he gets a win and he
shows they've got no money, they've got
nothing to live for. They've got
nothing. And they realize that they're
nobodyies. So they look at themselves
and think, "Fuck, ugly. No money." and
then they log on to YouTube and then
they go for people that are younger than
them, better looking than them, and they
try to bring people down to their level
because if they can bring somebody down
to their ugly, lonely skin level in a
way that's them winning, it's jealousy.
There's no reason there's no other
reason why all of these people would
keep going for you if they had a better
life than you. Listen, bro, people that
have got a better life than someone
don't waste their time on someone. This
is this is the key point you need to
remember. It's like think of people like
KSI and all of these big YouTubers,
these these people that have got, you
know, that that that get haters. What do
they do with these haters? They ignore
them because they realize that they're
not worth time. So, if these people are
saying that you're this, you're that,
you are this, they wouldn't waste their
time on you. They wouldn't give you the
time a day, let alone going on holiday,
keep going on about you every single
day. It's jealousy. And the fact that
they don't stop, it's jealousy. That's
literally why they do it.
Because they're fat, ugly, and lonely
and old. That's why they do all of this
[ __ ] this shitty atmosphere on YouTube
every single day. They do all of this
[ __ ] because they hate the fact that
you're younger than them and you're
better looking than them and they got
more and you got more money than them.
That's what somebody told me [ __ ] a
year ago and I never believed it. They
said you're better looking than them,
you got more money than them, you got a
better life than them and it kills them.
It's so true. It's the truth though. It
generally generally generally is so
true. Even if it even if it takes like a
year Yeah. to figure these things out
because think about it, bro. It doesn't
matter about jealous of what you are the
one doing this. So you would only know
what you're jealous of. Do you
understand what I'm saying, Mike? Only
you would know what you're jealous of.
That's not for me to say.
Like all of these it it it's all I'm
saying, bro, is it looks a bit suspect
when you've got middleage people going
for somebody that's the youngest and the
best looking on this community.
Do you not find that to be a bit dodgy?
Do you not think that is a bit dodge?
Now you've got all of these middle-aged
men lining up to have their say every
single day. And from what we've seen,
you are younger than anybody on here. I
mean, even Kay's older than me. You're
better looking than people on here.
I mean, I wonder why they go for you.
Huh? I wonder why out of all people they
go for you. See, if they went for
everyone else, then I'd be like, well,
they're just trying to [ __ ] with people
in it cuz they got no life. But it's
very suspect when they go for one um
they go for one person. It's jealousy.
That's what it is. It's literally jealousy.
That's why they do what they do. It's
jealousy. Jealousy. Skimness. Just like
the bomb. Fat, ugly, trying to say I've
gained weight, bro. When I'm 1% [ __ ]
like you, you fat ugly bastard, that's
when I'll get myself in the gym. When
I'm anywhere near as fat and ugly and
desirable as you in your ugly little
shitty bedsit, that's when I'll start
consider going to the gym. When I'm as
fat and ugly as you people, I will start
thinking about my life, bro. Like, and
I' I've always said that when I'm 1%
like these people, fat and ugly, because
that's what they are. They're fat and
ugly. Every single time. Yeah. Their
cameras go on, they're always fat and
ugly. And it explains why they do all of
this [ __ ] You remember Gray Cat? Fat
and ugly. Talking about someone again.
Oh, Kaye looks like this. Kaye looks
like that. And she turned out to be fat
and ugly. Bomb. Case in point. Bomb.
You're bold. You're this Sha Manta. He
got out there bold, ugly, fat skinned.
Isn't it a trend now with these people?
Isn't it a trend with these fat, ugly
people? Every single time they get out there
fat and ugly every time they're fat and
ugly. Isn't that mad? Every single one
of them that's done this. No young, no
averagel looking, always fat, old and
ugly. Huh? You learn something new every
day, don't you? You know,
and then you got people [ __ ] showing
what [ __ ] [ __ ] six [ __ ] seven
[ __ ] grand, bro. You can burn through
that. And do you know the amount of
money that I used to go through?
Do you know the amount of money that I
used to go through? And you know what I
say to these people, Mike? I say, "Show
the money again in 3 months, then they
can't do it." And then they can't do it.
See, the thing is, right, with money,
bro. It doesn't matter how much money
you have. It's how much money you have coming in.
That's that's the thing. It's it's about
how much money you actually have coming in. You know,
anyone can show one grand, two grand,
three grand, but if they ain't got much
money coming in, it's just
pointless, you know? You understand that? So,
these people are really, really fat and ugly.
How can that fat ugly skint [ __ ]
organ m try and talk about anyone? That
makes me [ __ ] laugh. That does, bro.
You need to get a [ __ ] life, bro.
[ __ ] lying that you got [ __ ] kids.
Lying that you got kids. Like anyone
would have kids with that fat ugly bastard.
Oh my [ __ ] god, bro. But the self
projection is strong.
Trying to tell me I'm gaining weight but
you're [ __ ] obese.
What the [ __ ] These people, bro.
This is what they do. Do you know these
fat ugly people? They get happy when
someone gains weight cuz they think that
you're going to be fat and ugly like
them. Like fat ugly bomb. Yeah. They get
cited as like, "Oh, he's going to become
a fat and ugly like me." That's what
they do, bro. That's literally what they do.
These people are fat and ugly. People
like the Bob, people like Graycat,
they're fat, ugly, and they got no They
got nothing. They got no money. Show me
that same money in [ __ ] two months,
bro. Show me that same money in two months.
You can't cuz you ain't got it. That
shitty little [ __ ] £10,000 that ain't
even going to last six [ __ ] months.
Throw some serious money for a [ __ ] change, bro.
Well, duh. That's why they do what they
do every day.
I know you're taking a [ __ ] piss, but
it is the truth because they wouldn't do
this to people that they're better than
who me the best looking on this
community. Well, let's look at the
evidence. Been with more women than
anyone on this community.
I've literally been with more women than
anyone on this community, but yet I'm
the one that's ugly. Apparently,
I'm ugly. I've been with more women than
everyone on this community that tries to
call me. Isn't that a funny Isn't that a madness?
Yeah, bro. Isn't that a [ __ ] madness?
And then you got Fatty Bomb. Big fat
ugly bomb trying to tell me that I'm gaining weight
when he's big, fat, and ugly and skin in
his little bed suit. Pretending that
he's got kids, mate. The day I literally
I need to go out in a bit. Let's go back
to the Lord. Literally, the day I'm as
fat and ugly as you is the day I'd kill
myself. The day I'm as ugly as these
people, like ugly bomb, ugly virgin
bomb, ugly virgin [ __ ] nonss,
I would literally kill myself, bro. The
day I'm as ugly as them and as fat as
them, bro. You can you can come to my [ __ ] funeral.
And the thing is,
like I said, they wouldn't do this every day.
They wouldn't do this every day. If they
weren't jealous of somebody, they
wouldn't do this every day. I'm going to
mention this in a video um later as
well, and this is going to be my last
response to this [ __ ] as well. So,
we're going to see now who really is the
skin ugly manta when you're the one that
can't stop talking about me. The more
they waste their life on you, the more
it shows what they are themselves.
Skint, ugly, nothing, lonely. The more
they do this, the more they give
themselves away. They don't even need to
be exposed. It's obvious what they are
because they wouldn't waste their time doing this.
They don't they're never going to get
this time back. Think of it, bro.
They're sat there, right, trying to say
that you're skin and you're ugly and if
you was all of these things, they
wouldn't waste their life on you. And
the fact that they do it it raises
alarms. It raises that jealousy alarm
because there's no way people that are
better looking than you, that's got more
money than you would waste their time on
someone like that,
you know, and then that's what gives
them away. And obviously they get
exposed as well, but what gives them
away is their YouTube activity. Like I
told you millions of times, non legs
says I'm all of these things, but he's
sat on YouTube talking about me all day,
every day. Wasting your life on someone
that's a skint.
Nah, mate. That's not looking right.
That's definitely definitely not looking right, mate.
Sorry, two and two don't add up there.
And then when you realize it's jealousy,
then when you when you react back to
these people, then you're as bad as them.
Cuz you're arguing with people that are
jealous of you. And then you're
and they are jealous of you. And before
they keep saying, "Oh, um, what's there
to be jealous of?" They're the ones that
are doing it. So only they would know
what they're jealous of. Do you
understand what I'm saying? And so then
it's like you got jealous people that
are jealous of you wasting their life
and then if you argue back with them
you're no you're just as bad as them.
You are literally just as bad as them.
I mean in society what am I a normal person bro?
Just a normal person. But on here you're
like royalty. You got everything they
don't have. Looks money. You're not fat
like them. You know you're not hopeless
like these ugly mongos. You know, you're
everything that they're not. So that's
why they gravitate towards you.
They hate the fact that you're better
looking. You got more money, better
looks. Look at Bomb's ugly face. And he
look at Bomb's ugly weight, ugly life on
YouTube every day. Just look at these
people. Look at Graycat. They're all
fat, ugly mongos that take out the fact
that they're skint and they got nothing.
So they come on YouTube to make
themselves feel better. Why do you think
they call people skint every day?
Because these people are skint. They've
got nothing. I don't know how many times
someone has to repeat this to these
people. They are skint fat ugly people
that look down on people that are better
than them, younger than them, got better
looks than them. They hate anyone that's
not fat and ugly like them. Why do you
think these people get on with each
other? Cuz they're all the same.
middleage, fat, ugly, and then when a
new kid [ __ ] comes on, a new person
comes on the [ __ ]
a new person comes on the scene, they
hate. They find any reasons to [ __ ] hate people.
You know what I'm saying?
So yeah, that's what it is anyways.
So yeah, that's why they do this whole
YouTube [ __ ] every day as well. So bro. Yeah, man.
They hate the Yeah. So they look down on
anyone that's got that that's not like
them basically. Yeah.
Yeah. They look down on anyone that's
not like them. Fat and ugly.
Skint like them.
You know the amount of times I used to um
go out on a Thursday.
It was a Thursday or Friday. No, it used
to be Fridays, Saturdays cuz that's when
they used to it used to go live, right?
I used to go out drinking for eight
hours and I used to come back and guess
what? It was the same people. It was
exactly the same people in all of them
hours yet they call everyone else skin.
They tell everyone else they've got no friends.
It's just this is a community where
basically failures come on.
failures. They ain't got nothing. Come
on here. No other community will have
them. No other community will have them.
That's why they gravitate towards That's
why they gravitate towards the youngest
and the best looking.
That's why they do what they do. It's so obvious.
[ __ ] so obvious.
I mean, you got some people going for
Tibby, but not the way they they go for me
with me. They make up actual excuses why
they actually go for me, cuz it's all
jealousy. So, that's what it is.
Yeah, it's the truth. It generally
generally is the truth. And what makes
me laugh is when that stupid fat ugly
bomb fat ugly bomb
was trying to say, "I'll never see over
£1,000 again." Bro, I've got more than
£1,000. You don't know what people have
again. They don't They only know about
their own skin lives,
which is why we do not go on their
channels and stuff because they're just
self-projecting fat ugly people that
ain't got no life. fat, ugly skin mongos
that aren't even [ __ ] worth entertaining.
They do this all day, every day cuz
they're jealous. They want people to be
put down to their level. You You
understand? They want Do you understand
what I'm saying? So,
Am I lying about what I'm saying, Mike, or no?
I fancy a t-bone, bro.
They clos in 2 hours and a half.
Oh, I don't think I can make it, bro.
Bro, I don't think I'll be able to make that.
Yeah, it's true what I'm saying. It
definitely definitely is true what I'm
saying. Otherwise, they will just stop their [ __ ]
They would just stop their [ __ ]
bro. It's obvious now. Yeah, it's not CO anymore.
It's literally not CO anymore, bro.
There's no excuse. You know, you can go
out and do things.
You know what I'm saying?
They're fat, ugly people that ain't got no life.
Literally what they are, bro. It's crazy.
I proved it [ __ ] millions of times,
bro. When I show money and they all run away.
That's why I don't show money. I don't
need to show anything to these people.
They can keep self-reflecting.
Millions of It's like Timmy. He
self-reflects as well.
Everything is self-reflected on here.
All about their own lives. Cuz they only
know themselves. They don't know other
people. They don't know what people
have. They don't know what people don't
have. That's why they can only talk for
themselves when they're calling people's skin.
You know, like Timmy, it's just self-reflection.
That's all it is.
Just like Ugly Bob. He's still a virgin.
40s ugly. No money.
Come back and show that money now. Come
back and show that money now. Exactly.
You can't. And then they're sat on
YouTube arguing with people that they
don't even know. It's such a [ __ ]
community, isn't it? It really is a such
a [ __ ] community, bro.
It is really just a [ __ ] big fat [ __ ] community.
That's what they are. Fat, ugly little
bong gun. I'm I'm going to come off this [ __ ] bro.
It's the same atmosphere.
It's the same [ __ ] atmosphere, bro.
You know what I mean? Yeah. It's the
same atmosphere with these mongos. Yeah.
I'm going to do a video about that as
well, actually. And I'm going to say
that this day forward, I'm not going to
be mentioning you. And if you mention
me, it just goes to show how jealous you
are and not me because you're the one
that's going to keep going on about me.
And I'm not going to keep I'm not going
to go on about you.
And the thing is, Mike, do you know what
annoys me when people say they do it for
reaction? They don't do it for reaction
because if they had a better life than
you, they wouldn't want a reaction. And
also, if you don't give them a reaction,
they will still do it. So it's like I
hate like that little excuse to say,
"Oh, well they're not jealous. They do
it for reaction." They don't do it for
reaction because even if you don't react
to them, they will still do it. You
could ignore them for 2 years and they
would still do it. They don't do it for
reaction. They literally do not do it for reaction.
So that's just like an excuse to just
cover up their jealousy. Well, we do it
so you react. It's not that at all, you know.
It's not that at all at all.
[ __ ] sake, bro. My top.
He's got all this money. Yeah, it's
because he doesn't have any money.
That's the whole point is because he
doesn't have any money.
He's skinted. He's like L. He wants to
[ __ ] try to convince people that he's
got money, but he doesn't have money.
None of these people have got money on here. Yeah.
It's like LJ trying to [ __ ] tell
people he's got money when he [ __ ] has nothing. Yeah.
They don't have money, bro. The skin.
I don't think I'm going to make it, bro.
I don't think I want to make it, man.
I really want the steak, but I don't
think I'm going to make it. Maybe.
Oh, [ __ ] sake. No,
not at all.
No, not at all. At all.
I don't know what I'm going to eat, bro.
Well, you only know what you're jealous
of because if you wasn't jealous, you
wouldn't be doing what you do every
single day. I know somebody that I'm
better than I'm better than. I don't
waste my time every single day. So, only
you know what you're jealous of?
Yep. You're talking about yourself again.
No friends, lonely. Yep, that's
yourself. But to answer your question, I
don't know. Only you would know what
you're jealous of because people that
aren't jealous don't waste their life on
someone all day every day. So you do. So
only you would know what you're jealous
of, you know? Yep. Talking about
yourself again. Yep. That's just self
projection. Yeah. You're talking about
yourself. And to be honest with you, I
don't know what the [ __ ] you're jealous
of. You are the ones that keep arguing
with people every day that you don't know.
And the only thing is you don't know
what people have. You're talking about
yourselves. You are the ones that are
jobless. You are the ones that are
skinned. That's why you do what you do every day.
Skin. Yep. You are. That's why you do
all of this. Cuz you are the ones with
no money. Single, lonely, Mr. Loner. You
That's Yeah, I know. Yeah. Yeah. I know.
No one's jealous. That's why you sit on
YouTube doing what you do all day every
day. Cuz you're not jealous. Because
you've got all of this money, but yet
you'd waste all your life on me. Yeah.
Not jealous, right? Not jealous. Okay.
Yeah. Because somebody that you're not
jealous of, you waste all your life on. Yeah. Okay.
That makes sense. Yeah. Yeah. Think of
this, Mike. Have you ever been with a a
woman before and like she was a scumbag
and you know that you don't like her and
you're not jealous of? Nothing screams
you not being jealous more than you
wasting every second of every day of
your life on people. That will show them
that you're not jealous. You show him,
my boy. You waste every second of every
day doing this because you're not
jealous. That will show him. That will
definitely definitely show him. Or would
you just live your life knowing that
you're better? Would you would you waste
all day every single day on someone that
you don't know cuz you're apparently not
jealous because there's nothing to be
jealous of. Or would you um Yeah, you
don't have one friend in your life.
You're talking about yourself. You're
exactly what we was talking about
earlier. Self projectors. Old
self-projecting skid people. Yeah,
yourselves. We're talking about you. We
was talking about you earlier.
Friendless, no money. Yeah, you. That's
yourself you're talking about. That's
why you get jealous of people like me.
Better looking, better money. That's why
you do all of this. Because you've got
nothing. And the more you do this, the
more it shows you got nothing. So, I'm
not even going to block you. You keep
typing away and your little keyboard
with your no money life and your skint
life and no friends. And I'm going to
leave you to it. I'm not even going to
react to you anymore. Keep
self-reflecting. Show everyone on
YouTube what you're about. Show
everybody on YouTube what you're about,
my boy. You show them. because I'm not
I'm not reacting no more. You're not
jealous, then you're going to stop
typing then, aren't you? If you're
really not jealous and you got all of
this money, stop typing. Let's see if he
stops typing. Right. Yeah.
Let's see if you stop typing. Still typing.
You're still typing.
Still [ __ ] typing. Oh my god. Type type
type. Oh my god.
What could you possibly be jealous of?
Oh my god. You know I was wrong about
you, bro. Yeah, you're right. You're not
jealous. Yeah, you're so right, bro.
Yeah, you're so right.
Yeah, you got all of this life yet
you're sat on YouTube arguing with
someone that you don't know. I'm sure
you do, bro. I'm sure you do.
I'm sure you do. You got all of these
things, but you're sat on YouTube all
day, every day. I'm sure you do, buddy.
I'm sure you got all of these things.
Self projecting on YouTube every day.
That's one way to show that you've made
it. Self projection.
Oh my god. Do these self-reflectors ever get bored?
Okay. People no money. How would they
pay their car Morgan? No. Well, they
don't. Oh, sorry. Well, they they don't.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no. You people literally don't have
money. That's why you come on YouTube
every day calling people skint cuz you are skint.
It's [ __ ] obvious. It's so obvious
why you come on here every day and call
people skin. It's because you are skin. You know,
you don't pay car insurance. You people,
most of the people on here don't have
nothing. Yeah. Okay. Some people might
have there might be a few people with
normal lives and [ __ ] but you people
are just fat, ugly, skimp people that
take your failures out on other people.
It's so obvious cuz you wouldn't be on
there doing what you do every day.
There's no content. There's no nothing.
Yeah, I can't afford, bro. I pay all my
bills. And no, I'm saying that your skin
cuz every single time you get shown
money, you run away. I'm I'm showing
everyone your skin. All of my bills are
paid. My phone bill, my virgin bill. You
people call people skin. It's cuz you
are skin. Every single time you get show
money, you run away cuz you ain't got no
money. It's the same conversation. It's
the same argument every single day. It's
the same. It's because you are the ones
that have got no money. That's why you
talk about people having no money
because you ain't got none. That's why
you people like you, Timmy, and stuff,
you're always asking people to show you
money cuz you ain't got none. And you
think that people are skintike you, you
know? That's what it is. You want people
to show you money cuz you ain't got no
money. and you want to take [ __ ] your
failures out on someone that's younger
than you and better looking than you and
got more than you. That's why you do
what you do every day.
You know, you have been shown £6,000 and
you will run away. You want to [ __ ]
pretend that you you know
that you don't remember it, but I
remember it. You know, no one cares
about a [ __ ] credit report, bro. If
my credit score was so bad, why have I
shown you all money and you've all ran away?
Ask yourself that question. You think of
credit reports being mean someone's
skin. Why did that money have you all
running away? And why if I was to show
you money again, you'd all run away? Cuz
you're self projecting. It's all self
projecting, bro. There ain't no [ __ ]
way. All of these people on here let me
show money for that long and you all run
away. You did because you ain't got no
money. See, it always goes back to the
same thing over and over and over and
over and over again. It's the same argument.
You know, I don't know why you're sat on
YouTube arguing with people that you
don't know every day. You've got all of
this money. You're millionaires
apparently. What are you doing on
YouTube doing this? Come on.
You know? Yeah. And do you know what I
say different? I've shown you money and
you've all run away. But you keep
ignoring that fact. You come on here and
you call people skin. Every single time
you get show money, you will run away.
That says it all. There's no need to go
back and forth. There's no need to keep
arguing back and forth. Like Timmy, I
said to Timmy, you keep calling people
skimp. You got showing money back in
March and you ran away. That's why I
don't waste my time because it's self-
projecting. You asking people to show
you money because you're because they're
skin. It's your way of self-p
projecting. I don't play self-projecting
games. Do you understand? I don't play
silly little self-p projecting games
with old people,
you know, because I'm I'm more mature.
Been there, done that, wearing a [ __ ] t-shirt lad.
And even him, he comes on him and still
asks me to show money even though he's
been showed money
because it's a it's a spasticated
[ __ ] [ __ ] community.
That's it. That's what it is. You all go
on about money cuz you ain't got none.
That's why I let you like go, you know,
you bring it up because you ain't got no
money. Well, I got money right here.
Look. And I'm not showing you [ __ ]
I could probably split some£5 notes to
be honest and show you5 and it would
make you run away. I don't entertain skin people.
I don't entertain skimp people, bro.
Sorry, man. Are you doing that? [ __ ] that, bro.
I would have got a steak today, but I'm
going to I won't make it. So, you call
people skin because you are the ones
that are skin. What have you people done
in 3 years other than come on YouTube and self-reflect?
Answer me that question.
What have you done in 3 years other than
come on here and self-reflect?
Self-reflect your life. What have you
actually done? Come on, tell me. Tell me
like the truth. What have you actually
done in them years but self-reflect?
Nothing. Literally nothing. Yeah.
Oh, I'm [ __ ] man. It goes to show
what you people are about every day on
here, man. So obvious. It's so obvious.
[ __ ] mongos, lad.
Yeah. But anyways, why are you changing
the subject? You come on here, you're
calling people skin, right? When you've
been shown money, you've run away. Why
are you changing the subject? Why did
you all run away? If you've got all of
this money, right? Why did you run away
when you got shown money? Tell me why
you all run away. You run away. Nonsense
run away. Why did you all run away when
you got shown money?
Another thing that gets dismissed. I can
tell you why. Because you ain't got no
money. I can say it in the clearest way
possible. It's because you ain't got
none. That's why you talk about other
people not having money. Because you
ain't got no money. You don't know
people's lives. You don't know what
people have in their bank accounts. You
only know about your own skint lives
that you like to project on YouTube for
some reason. You know what I'm saying?
Well, you did run away when you got
shown money. You got run away. You ran
away when you got show money. You ran away.
Well, you ran away when you got shown money. So,
yeah. It's cuz you ain't got no money.
Just like the skinned virgin in the bed
suit with no bed and no money in it. You
know what I'm saying? Yeah.
I can't believe I have to go to [ __ ]
McDonald's, man. Oh, no. Actually, I'm
going to go get a biryani, actually.
No. What's Tuesday?
Is that the excuse you're using? Cuz
your skin. So you come on in here every
single day calling people's skin and ask
them to show you money. It's a [ __ ]
community. I'm losing brain cells again
cuz this [ __ ] community.
So you ask people to show you money. And
then when you you ain't got nothing to
show, it's oh, we don't need to show
money. We don't need to show money. It's
a bongo community. I'm losing brain cells again.
Every single time I go in this
community, I swear to God, I've become
disabled like them.
You do need to prove it because you're
asking people to show money. And the
only reason you don't show money is cuz
you ain't got none. Cuz you ain't got
none. That's why you're on YouTube all
day every day. Cuz you ain't got no
life. You ain't got no money. As much as
you like to talk about other people,
right? Is it because you ain't got none?
This is why you're on here every single day.
Then no, he didn't.
Anyways, I'm gone. I'll be back later.