Yeah, exactly. That it doesn't let me
exit the home screen for some reason.
But yeah, it just goes to show, bro,
that these people have got nothing.
Yeah, these people have got no money.
They've got no life. I love this six
weeks proving this, you know. I love
this six weeks proving this, bro.
It shows that these people have got
nobody and no life. They can't even come
on. They can't even come on the
hangouts. It's the truth. It's the
[ __ ] truth with these people. But
they've got nothing in life. They're
old, ugly, skint, low-life people.
That's literally what all that they are
on here. I had to went off because
[ __ ] this guy put a nude up. It
doesn't let me exit the home screen for
some reason anymore. It doesn't let me exit it.
It doesn't let me exit it for some
reason. That's why he was able to put
the nude up. It doesn't let me do it.
So, like I was saying, it just goes to
show that these people are the ugly
skinned ones in life that ain't got
nothing. No one's joining. No one's
showing anything. No one's showing their
face. It goes to show that they're all
talking about themselves. Let's talk
facts now, bro. Come on.
They've got nothing in their life, these
people. They've got literally [ __ ] all
in their life. That's why they do this
every single day.
Even if I do this three times a year,
bro, it proves it. Sat on YouTube every
[ __ ] day. Ain't got no life. Nah,
bro. I've got got millions in the bank.
I I wish I had millions in the bank, but
I'm not [ __ ] ugly and skint like you
people. I'm nothing special. To the
general public, I'm nothing to be
jealous of. I'm a normal person. But to
you people, fat, ugly, low life, no
money, you would be jealous of someone
that's younger and better looking than
you. It's so obvious. You make it so
obvious. How many times did you get the
link put out there? Right. Yeah. And you
won't join. Show us your face. Show us
your money. Show us your face. Show us
You know, every time I'm trying to put
this up, they keep putting nudes up and
it's not letting me exit the home screen.
So this is why this is what I mean with
these mongos. They're all 40year-old
ugly people that ain't got a life. I've
got an excuse why I've been on YouTube.
I was taking a break from the dating and
I took an opportunity to save money.
So I mean that's my excuse. What's your
excuse? Cuz you have nothing. You ain't
got nothing. That's why you people come
on here every day doing what you do. Cuz
you ain't got a life. Cuz you ain't got
no life. That's why you do what you do.
You know, I do this sometimes January,
sometimes I do it February because I
just want to. But the fact that I've got
all of these and you know what? I'm
going to prove it after today as well.
I'm going to prove it. I'm going to
[ __ ] prove it even more so. Yeah,
I'm going to prove it even more so. You
people are mongos.
You latch on to anyone that's better
looking than you.
Uh, I've already had a girlfriend. Nice
try. I've already had a girlfriend and
I've slept with normal women that
weren't disabled. Try again, buddy. It's
not going to work. We're talking about
you little mongos self- projecting every
day on YouTube.
We're talking about you skint [ __ ]
self- projecting every single day on YouTube.
Come on, join the hangouts. Come on.
Come on. And really, it is ridiculous as
well. I need to come off this [ __ ] now
cuz I'm back into this game now. You
know, you people are jealous of me. That
is what you are. You are the ones that
are jealous of me. You are the ones that
won't shut up about me. You are the ones
that stalk me all day every [ __ ] day
because you are jealous. And I'm [ __ ]
not buying them [ __ ] time that I'm
getting back arguing with these little
self-reflecting people. Do you know what I'm saying?
Nah, you're talking about yourself. It's
all you people have. Listen, bro. In
them three years when I was traveling,
getting birds, you mongos were sat on
YouTube skin, bro. YouTube is all you
have. YouTube is all you mongos have.
You can't take one day off of YouTube.
Anyways, you're asking me jealous of
what? Okay, the link is there.
Link. The link is there. Join and show
us your face and I'll and I and I'll and
I'll explain to you what you're jealous
of. Okay, join the link and put your camera on.
You You literally, bro, join the link
and show your face and I'll show you
what you're jealous of and I'll show
everyone what you're jealous of. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Join the hangouts. The
link is there. You ask me a question and
I'll prove what you're jealous of. Put
your camera on, show everyone your face,
i.e. you're fat and ugly. So there's
every reason to be jealous of somebody
that's younger and better looking than
you. So you're not joining. So you can't
show what you look like and you can't
show money. That's what you're jealous
of. So there you go. To answer your
question, bro. You not understand that
you people are not normal people, bro.
You're not normal people. You're fat,
ugly mongos with ugly looks. You're not
a normal person in the public. You're
ugly fat Mongs.
You're jealous of anyone that's better
looking than you.
You know what I'm saying? That's got a
better life than you. You're sat there
on YouTube every day old. Why wouldn't
you be jealous? You've got nothing in
your lives. You've got nothing in your
lives. I know, [ __ ] bro. I couldn't
believe it. Yeah. When they're trying to
say that I'm jealous of them. I've got
more money than them, been with more
women than them, traveled to more places
than them, and I'm apparently [ __ ]
jealous. What the [ __ ] Jesus Christ.
These [ __ ] absolute mongos, bro, are
a joke. I'm telling you. And bro, if
there was nothing to be jealous of, stop
acting like you're jealous, then. Have
words with yourself, bro. Don't have
words with me.
Do you know what I'm saying? Have words
with yourself, bro. Don't have [ __ ]
words with me. No, I'm not angry. It's
just you little mongos need to get a
life. When are you people going to get a
life? Get off of YouTube and get a life.
When are you little mongos going to come
off of YouTube and get a life? Yeah.
Nah, I don't have it all, bro. I'm just
younger and better looking than you.
That's enough to get you people jealous.
Younger, better looking, actually got a
life that you people don't have.
You know what I'm saying? You people
ain't got no life. You are the ones that
can't take one day off for YouTube. I
already told you why I'm on YouTube and
what I've been doing for the past couple of weeks.
It doesn't matter if you don't stream or not.
Yeah. Really? Yeah. You Okay. Well, join
the hangouts and show us what you look like. Exactly.
Yeah. You're talking about yourself
again. Another self-reflector.
That's yourself. You're talking about
your middleage and you're ugly. Again,
case in point, that's what I'm talking
about. Yeah, bro. You people in your 40s
and you're skint. Your lives are at the
pits for [ __ ] sake. You got no job, no
money, no friends. You're in your 40s.
You're talking about yourselves.
Everything is about your own lives.
Faulty, ugly, no friends. That's why
you're on YouTube every day. Everything
you talk about is your 40-year-old selves.
That's why I don't block any of you. You
are all fat, ugly, skinned people in your 40s.
And that's why every single time I say
this [ __ ] lad, bro, listen. You don't
need to talk about my looks. My looks
are better than yours. My looks actually
got me laid unlike you. You are the
virgins that are sat on YouTube every
day. You know, Harry, I could be like
you people. No friends, no life, no
money, ugly, in my 40s. I could be like
you people. H yes, I do have savings.
Again, you don't know how much money I
have. So, are you going to come in and
show us your face? Bro, you won't come
in and show us your face cuz you are the
ugly ones. You are the big ugly ones.
That's why you go on about people's
looks. Cuz you are the ugly ones. Skin
and ugly. You people are so ugly. Every
time you try to go out your house, you
get bullied for being so ugly. That's
why you've never been with a bird, never
had a girlfriend, cuz you're all ugly.
This is my whole point. You are in your
40s. You've never been with a bird.
You've all been bullied your whole life.
You're all very ugly. That's why you
spend all day every day on YouTube. Cuz
you're all fat, ugly people that ain't
got no life. And that's why every time I
say these things about you, it's the
truth. You are in your 40s. You're ugly.
You got no money. You got no bird. You
ain't been anywhere. You're all ugly.
You're all ugly 40y olds. That's what
I'm saying, bro. Like, you could try and
say what you want about me. I'm younger
than you. I'm better looking than you. I
got more money than you. I got more life
experience than you. I've put all of my
life experiences on YouTube. Better
women, better looks, better money,
better clothes, youth. Something that
you can't do because you ain't got
nothing. Do you understand what I'm
saying? Yeah. No house that you own, no
car, no pension, no kids. Yeah. That's
yourself that you're talking about.
Yeah. But you're in your 40s. Yes. But
you people in your 40s. That's yourself.
You're talking about ugly people in your
40s. Ugly 40year-olds. Bro, listen. You
people are so ugly that you come on
YouTube every day because you're bully
victims. You want to feel wanted. That's
why you people do what you do. You talk
about my looks. Well, why have I had
more women than you then?
Why have I been with so many women and
you're still a virgin if I'm so ugly?
Self projection. That's what I'm saying.
Bro, listen. [ __ ] all of this
good-looking [ __ ] bro. [ __ ] all of this
[ __ ] man. Right. [ __ ] all of this
[ __ ] I'm going to put the link up
again. Right. [ __ ] all of this.
Right. Let's look at you people.
Right. Come on. The link is up now.
Let's show each other people's faces.
Come on. Come on. Let's see who the ugly
one is. Come on. The link is up. You're
more than welcome to join.
I'm going to show everybody how ugly you
people are. Join the hangouts.
and show your face.
Right. Anyways, link is up there. Join
Hangouts and show your face.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. The
link is up. The link is up there. Come on.
Right. The link is up there now. So, put
your cameras on and we'll see who the
ugly one is.
Come on. You join. You join the hangout.
Right. You talk. I'll I'll put my camera
on first. I'll start and we will see who
the ugly ones are.
Come on, the link is up there.
Come on, the link is up there, right?
So, we'll talk, right?
So, you're just going to keep repeating
yourself, repeating yourself, repeating
yourself. You're not going to join Hangouts.
So, you're just going to keep repeating
yourself over and over and over and over
and over and over again.
Bro, listen. I put the link out. Can you
join the link?
You know, the reason you people don't
show your face is cuz you're ugly. And
you know, and you know how you know
these people are ugly as well. Because
if you join a community, right, say you
joined any kind of community, it could
be any kind of community, and you're sat
there calling people ugly, right? And
somebody comes on here and says, "Well,
yeah, um, you know, show your face. You
would just go and show your face." These
people can't show your face because
they're ugly. Every single person that
has come on here before Grievy and said
they can't show their face for various
different reasons, they've always been
very ugly. Um, and it would explain why
they've been trolling people for these
years. These people are but ugly. It's
not because, you know, they can't uh
show their face because they're going to
get caught out. They won't show their
face because they're ugly bastards. part
of what the reason why they do what they
do on here every single day. It's pretty
self-explanatory really. These people
are one of the most ugliest things
you'll ever see in real life. That's why
they're trying to talk about my looks.
And like I said, talk is cheap. We're
not talking. I'm putting a link up.
Join, show yourself.
Join and show yourself. They can't do
that. So, it doesn't really matter what
they say, you know?
Right. Think about this, bro. Yeah. Anybody
could easily just come on here and show
their face. They can't show their face
cuz they're ugly. Remember Pat Mustard?
Remember Bomb? Do you remember Pat
Mustard? And do you remember Bomb? How
they always used to go on about people's
looks? Plat. You remember? They always
used to go on about people's looks. It's
people's looks. They're this, they're
that, they're this, they're that,
they're this, they're that. I heard it.
You heard it. The whole of YouTube heard
it. And when their faces got out there,
they were very, very much ugly.
Isn't that a surprise? Everything that
these people say on here is about their
own lives. Skint, ugly, no misses, no
money. Everything that they talk about
is themselves. This is the This is the
point of this live stream is to prove
this, you know? Like, think of it, bro.
Yeah. If you was roasting a community,
Yeah. If you was roasting a [ __ ]
community about their looks, you would
show your face if you weren't ugly. The
only reason these people don't show
their face is cuz they are ugly. And
they know that as soon as they show
their face, you're going to have
something on them. Just like the bomb.
Why do you think the bomb don't come on
here and say anything anymore? He
doesn't even talk because he's been
owned. These people are very, very ugly.
They've got nothing. Look at all of the
women that I've been with in my life. So
many women. So many women I pulled. So
many women kissed women on camera. None
of them was escorts. But I'm the ugly
one. Bro, you know it's unhealthy to
convince yourself these things every
single day. You know what I'm saying,
bro? It really, really is.
So, um, so you're not going to come on then?
So, you're not going to you're not going
to come in and show your face or show
any money, right? Okay.
So, you're not going to come in and show
your face and show any money? So, yeah. Uh,
never had sex more selfjected. So, is
anyone going to join or what?
So, any of you going to join or not?
Nah, I've already shown you people money
multiple times. I don't want you running
away again. So, you're on here trying to
say I'm this and I'm trying to say that.
You're trying to say that I'm this and
you're trying to say I'm that, but you won't join.
Bro, I feel sick, bro. What the [ __ ] I
actually feel sick, man.
like a [ __ ] headache, bro.
One second. So, none of these people
going to show their face? No. Jesus Christ.
Sorry about that. So, none of you are
going to come in and join and show your face.
I wonder why that is.
Nothing suspect about that.
You people are such self-reflectors.
Oh my [ __ ] god. You people are such self-reflectors, bro.
It's unbelievable. Sat on YouTube every
day ain't got no life
trying to call me ugly, bro. When I'm a
million times better looking than all of
you people, you can't even show your
faces. You can't even join the panel,
bro. You're that scared you got you
can't even join the panel. Imagine that.
Imagine being scared to join a panel.
Imagine being that bullied, bro. No, I
can't imagine it.
I'm 27 and I had and I have had a
girlfriend. Um, and you're 47 and you've
never been laid. Again, self-
projecting. These people in their 40s,
they've never even been laid. This is
what I mean. It's all self-reflecting on
here. This is why no one can be bothered
with it anymore. Vi like I know we I
know we've had like um you know uh
things in the past you know where we've
had arguments but this is why people
don't waste their time on here anymore
because it's just self- projecting. This
is what I mean. It's just a bunch of
40year-old losers coming together
projecting their lives onto other
people. This is why no one can be asked
anymore. Why do you think the community
is dead? Why do you think no one comes
on here anymore, bro?
because it's just a bunch of fat, ugly
losers that ain't got no life that talk
about themselves. It's [ __ ] waste of
time, bro. Really, really is a waste of time.
So, yeah, you have no friends.
Everything they say is themselves. Bully
me, bro. If you bullied me, I wouldn't
be on here. I bully you people. You
can't meet me. You can't tell me where
you are. You people don't bully no one,
bro. You people can't even join a panel.
For [ __ ] sake, you can't even join a
panel. You're that scared, you can't
even talk. Like, you don't bully no one.
The only people that get bullied is
yourselves. You know what I'm saying?
You know what I'm saying, bro? Like, you
bro, you people don't bully no one. Who's this? Hello.
>> Hello, PJ. How you doing?
>> I'm good, man. So,
>> how you doing?
>> Yeah, I'm good, man. How are you?
>> How you doing? [ __ ] women, eh?
>> Yeah, man.
>> You can You will never get a girlfriend
because women hate you.
>> I've already been with more women than you.
>> I don't know, DJ. Women hate you.
>> I know, but I've been with more women than you.
>> Now, the thing is I mean I mean, Davey,
listen. Davey, here's the thing that uh
>> I'm listening, bro. I'm listening, bro.
Wait, no. Let's get one thing straight.
We're here to talk. We're going to have
a communication. You talk to me, I'll
talk to you. We'll talk to each other
like adult. Yeah.
>> Do we should we do it one by one? Okay.
>> Okay. Firstly, firstly, you've got black
teeth, so sort your teeth out before trying to
>> I agree. I agree, PJ. You're right. I do
have black teeth.
>> I'm better looking than you. I'm better
looking than you. And I've been with
more women than you. Women hate you. But
bro, listen. When was the last time you got laid?
>> Uh, last week.
>> No, listen, Dave. I have been with more
women than you, bro.
>> How many women?
>> I know. I've never had to simp. Women
will never like you, bro.
>> PJ, how many women have you been with?
>> Multiple different women.
>> No women hate you. You're the one that you're
>> Bro, you're the one that can't even get
a bird. You ugly bastard.
>> No, PJ. Seriously, I I've had a moment
I've had a moment in my life where I've
had women literally fighting over me.
>> I'm fighting over you, you ugly bastard.
Put your camera. It's crazy, but it has
literally happened. Let's put our camera
on again. Let's put I haven't had a
shave or anything, but put your camera on again.
I'm not even groomed. You've got a head
start, bro. You've got a head start on
me. Come on.
>> You got a head start on me. I am way I'm
way better looking than you.
>> Come on, bro. And I'm not even groomed.
I'm not even [ __ ] groomed.
>> I'm going to turn my camera off, but I
know people are going to screenshot that
and I'm going to I'm sure people will
make up their own minds. That's what I'm saying.
>> Turn the camera off. I'm eating, bro. I
don't eating. I'm better looking than
you, you ugly bastards. But you know
what? Fair play, Davey, for coming in
and, you know, showing your face and
stuff. I mean, we've already seen you.
>> I've done that for saying we've already
seen you. But the thing is,
>> but Davey, we've already seen you before, though.
>> Exactly. Exactly. That's what I mean.
You seen me years ago cuz I've never
Yeah, but you're not the one. Yeah, but
you're not But you're not the one that's
doing this. These are That's the point.
>> I'm I'm not a crow, but I will come on
and tell you that you need to sort your
life out and I'll do it. You know what I'm saying?
So, come on PJ, where what's going on
here? Like, we need to get you laid,
mate, mate. We need to get you laid.
>> I've been laid more times than all of
you people, mate. You don't need to get me.
>> No, no, seriously. Come on. I'm speaking
to you like from like a semi friendly
point of view here. Like, let's I want
to be I want to be your wingman. I want
>> I can get my I can get myself laid if I
want Davey, bro. I mean,
>> at the end of the day, I would like to
be your wingman. And I reckon I could
make you [ __ ] get some good [ __ ]
that actually wants you.
>> Yeah. Well, you need to get yourself
some [ __ ] reluctant to suck your dick
and then like film her reluctantly
sucking your dick. That's That's not a
good look, PJ.
>> Really, bro? Well, how comes we've never
seen you with a bird then? But we've
seen me with plenty birds that weren't prostitutes.
>> I I don't know. I'm guess I guess I'm
just a virgin.
>> Oh, well, you took you little bit of
time to think about that, didn't it?
Exactly. Like I mean like do would you
would you video record every sexual
interaction you had?
>> No one saying record sex. I never said
record you having sex. I said we've
never seen or heard you ever with a
woman. But we've seen and heard me with
a woman. That's a bit strange, isn't it?
>> What? So you think I'm a virgin now?
>> I never said you're a virgin. When did I
say you're a virgin?
>> Okay. So why would I upload
with TJ? Come on. Why would I upload
foot footage of me with women in this
community especially? Why would anybody do that?
>> No, but like we've never seen you like
speak to a woman or whatever. You know
what I mean?
>> Well, go and put your mom on the phone
and I'll speak to her.
>> Yeah. Very funny. Very, very, very
>> No, PJ, I can speak to women. >> Yeah.
>> I don't upload every interaction I have
with women because that makes you look
like a bit of a freak. I'm not going to lie. Like
>> really? Thank you, ma'am. Fair enough.
>> Oh, it does PJ if you're uploading cold
approach. Literally, you've uploaded 500
different videos of you being rejected
by 500 different women.
>> Yeah, but
the thing is Dave,
>> but the thing is Davey, you would get
rejected as well. And you have been
rejected and and most of these people in
here, I have been reject I have been
rejected and I'll admit that. There's
nothing wrong with being rejected. Take
it on the chin. move on to another woman.
>> But you seem to be you seem to be
rejected by every woman, though.
>> Yeah, I know. Like, I've never been on
dates. I've never had sex with anyone.
Yeah, you're right. I've never never No, no,
>> I've never actually seen a cold approach
video of you actually have a successful.
>> You've done 200 cold approach videos and
every woman has been scared of you, PJ.
They wanted to run away from I'm sure.
I'm sure I've put videos up where I've
got their numbers and slept with them.
>> You in you instill fear into women. You
literally instill fear into them. >> Uh
>> they're scared of you. They want to run
away from you.
>> Davey, I've got a video of a woman
giving me a number and sleeping with me
the same way.
>> They literally are trying to run away
because they think you're going to kill
or rape them. PJ
>> Dave, I've
give off to women. You give off this
impression to every woman. This is why
you have no success.
>> Please. No. Seriously, PJ,
>> this is real.
>> I'm speaking to you as well.
>> But literally, I'm No, you're ignoring
the fact why you get rejected so much.
>> It's because you look like you want to
rape and kill them, PJ.
>> Just realize, stop being so rapey and
murdery and maybe you'll get some money. Simple.
>> Dave Davey, I've shown me approaching
women and getting success multiple times.
>> Okay. So, I don't know what what you're talking about, >> PJ.
Most women are scared of you, PJ.
>> Oh, and do you know what? Let me tell
you something as well. Most women are
not going to sleep with you just because
you're defending them. I don't Do you
know Do you know what? Can you Can you
answer me this? I'm generally curious.
What? No. No. Seriously, like, no take
of the piss. Why do you simp and defend
women? It's not going to make women like
you saying about PJ, I agree with you.
All women are [ __ ] They're all [ __ ]
and they want the biggest blackest [ __ ]
they can get. But >> okay,
>> at the end of the day, Fanny is not that
hard to get. PJ, you're just uh you're
struggling. You're struggling in life.
>> I mean, I'm not trying for like I mean
>> I agree with you on one point. It might
be hard to get an honest relationship
with a woman. That's one thing that is
actually hard to get. A woman is
probably never going to be honest to you
nowadays. So that is like yeah to to
meet a woman and have to be honest and
loyal. Good luck with that. I agree with
you there, PJ. But it is not hard to get a shag.
>> It's not hard to get a shag. Okay.
>> Well, you sounded like that was impossible then.
>> Like the way you just said it's not hard
to get a shag. Like
>> Yeah, cuz you just got out and then you
>> So you think it is really hard to get a shag.
>> It's nowhere near as easy as people make out.
>> PJ, do you know why it's hard for you to
get a shag? It's because you come across
as desperate and >> Okay.
Uh, it's nowhere near as easy as people
make it out to be, but I'm not lying.
>> PJ, I can walk around pissed out my
head, piss with piss in my pants, and
still get laid. Of course you can.
>> Yeah, of course you can. Well, we'll
come to London and do that then. Do you know what?
>> I'll be here in London, you [ __ ]
>> Okay. Do you want to do you want to meet
up on Saturday, go to a club?
>> Go on then. Where do you want?
>> No, seriously. I'm I'm We'll meet We'll
meet up and go to a club.
>> Where do you want to meet? You want to
meet at King's Cross and then we'll go from there?
>> No, let's meet Lester Square.
Go on then. Go on then.
>> No, seriously. I'm being serious.
Saturday I'll meet you there. Cool.
Saturday. Saturday at
>> Saturday night. 9 9:00.
>> 9. Okay. 9:00. Yeah. Fair. Fair enough.
Yeah. I will meet you then. Cool. And
you can show me how we'll go. Bring
Brid. We'll go clubbing and we'll
[ __ ] I'll show you how it's done.
>> Show me how it's done. I want to learn
from the best.
>> Exactly, PJ.
>> Yeah. I want
I'm going to record it as well. Yeah.
Can I record some of what we doing?
Well, just try not to get my face in it
and we'll be all right.
>> Well, everyone's seen your face.
>> Yeah, but I It doesn't mean I want it
all over YouTube, CJ.
>> Yeah, but your shown your face now.
>> If I can record you the whole time and
upload you the whole time as well, then
yeah, we have a deal. How about that?
>> Yeah, fair enough. Yeah.
>> All right. You don't You don't even live in London.
>> All right, I'll get there.
>> You live in Norwich, is it? >> No.
>> Where do you live then? How do you know that?
>> I just assumed.
>> Why? Why would you assume that?
>> Cuz that's where you're from.
>> Well, how do you know? I never said it.
>> So, where do you live then?
>> I'm not telling. >> Enfield. >> Wow.
>> You're a [ __ ] don [ __ ] You are.
>> How's that? >> Wow. >> What?
>> Why do my dogs do,
>> bro? That's a bit of a dox to be fair.
>> How my docks are gone.
>> You're a mug PJ.
>> No. No. I'm not a doctor.
>> Where? Who told you that?
>> No one, man.
>> Someone. Yeah, mate. Don't say someone
told you where that. Someone told you Enfield.
>> No. No. Do you know what it is? It's
like, you know, I used to go to Enfield
all the time when I was younger to go to
the Crispy Cream Donuts. So, I know.
>> What? You've seen me in Enfield, have you?
>> No. I just guessed.
What? So is that where you live, right?
>> Because you went to Enfield for donuts.
You know that I'm in Enfield. How does
that make sense?
>> I I I don't I don't know. You're in
Enfield. I guess you're in Enfield.
>> I don't know, man.
>> So you're in Enfield? >> No.
>> There you go then.
>> None of your business, is it really?
>> Okay. Well, Lester Square Saturday. Yeah.
>> Yeah. 8 9
bring a passport or driving license.
We'll go clubbing.
>> Well, obviously I know to bring ID. I'm
not stupid. I am from this city, matey.
>> All right. Well, relax.
>> You know, it's all good, man. All good.
>> No, it'll be good.
>> The thing is though, don't go all
weirdo. Don't start threatening to
[ __ ] bum kids and [ __ ] because I'll
punch you myself.
>> Yeah, I'd like to see you try, matey.
Pete, do you I tell you what, do you
just want to meet up for a fight? No.
No. Do you just want to meet up for a fight instead?
>> No. I want you to show me how it's done.
I want to know if I'm the best.
>> Well, all right. Well, how about you
watch your mouth then?
>> Okay, fair enough.
>> Say sorry. Say sorry to me now.
>> No. No.
>> Okay. So, when I meet you in Enfield,
uh, can we're going to fight
>> Lester Square.
>> It doesn't matter.
But listen, um, what I was saying to you
is, um, no cocaine. Yeah. >> Why?
>> I know you're a bit of a gear head
because why? Why? Why? You know, you
don't want a little line. >> Nah.
>> You sure? >> Yeah.
>> DJ, it would be like if you put 20 quid
in, I can get us like an eight bag.
>> No, I'm not cracking like you, matey.
>> No, it's not crack, mate. It's just a
line. A line of code.
>> Yeah, but it basically is crack, is it?
Man, it's it's literally not m crack.
Cocaine Cocaine is a rich man's drug. >> Huh?
>> Cocaine is a rich man's drug.
>> Yeah, but we're not rich, we're poor.
>> Yeah, but we'll still do rich man drugs.
>> That's That's
PJ. PJ, that's how we get the funny,
mate. The girls see us with cocaine,
they'll be like, "Whoa, let's go."
>> When did you last do it?
>> Yeah, like few months ago now, to be fair.
>> Yeah, you used to be bad on that, didn't you, Dave?
>> I did. I did, Pedro, mate. I used to be
[ __ ] bad bad on that.
>> Not tried it for 4 years, mate.
>> Well, we'll get on it Friday.
>> I done it in slow. Do you remember Fraser,
>> mate? You know how the girls go for that
[ __ ] It's easy. Easy [ __ ] mate.
>> But how do you remember Fraser though?
>> Fraser? Oh, you doxed him. You doxed him over 30.
>> Yeah, but he No, but he was being a
club, but he was trolling though. He was actually trolling.
>> No, no, you doxed him over 30 quid. I remember Fraser.
You literally fully doxed him because he
didn't give you 30. That's mental, DJ.
>> Yeah, I didn't even need it. I was
testing him in it.
>> Yeah, you still doxed him though.
>> Yeah. Yeah, he was a trolling [ __ ]
>> Yeah, he was a bit of a troll to be
fair. I think I think I think he was I
think he was taking you for a ride.
>> Yeah, he was. >> Yeah.
>> So, have you um have you been to um slow before?
>> Yeah, of course I have.
[ __ ] [ __ ] I used to live in Ricelet.
>> Oh yeah. Okay. Yeah, that's right. The
end of the central line. Yeah. Yeah, I
know where it is. Yeah. Slow is a [ __ ]
man. Is it? Yeah.
Yeah. You live in um you live in Enfield, [ __ ] What happened? Jeez.
What's happening? I can't hear him. What
happened to him?
Could have some salmon instead. Bro, I
think I'd be sick if I eat back the lords.
What happened, bro? I can't hear this
guy. What the [ __ ] is he talking?
Good old Davy. E,
we need to go to the barbers. Man,
I can't hear this guy.
Good old Davey. Hey,
Davey. Trust me, bro. You're not better
looking than me when I get groomed. You
had a nice little uh head start on me.
But we've already seen your face before.
We've already seen your face, Davey.
Bro, that's [ __ ] nothing.
Yeah, it just
honestly I need to get on with life
anyways after today. So, I'm going to
leave you people to it.
I've got a holiday I'm going on soon. So,
unblock my main account. Smokey, why
don't you come in and show us your face? Took it.
It took me bottle. Why did it take me
bottle to put my camera on? Oh [ __ ]
bro. Smokey, why don't you come in here
and show your face?
And then we'll play the money game.
Davey showed his face.
Bro, listen. Listen. Come in and show your face. You know,
I'm going to have to have the salmon.
I'll be sick if I have McDonald's
that come over 48. Yeah. 20. Let's see
your face. Let's see what you people look like.
Yeah. Let's see what you people look like.
What holiday should I go on next year?
Um, Smokey H. I'm trying to uh I'm
trying to think, lad.
The state of it. Why don't you come and
show your face? You say the state of it.
Let's see your face.
That's all right. I don't mind. I'm not
insecure about my looks. That's fine,
bro. I can I can keep my camera on.
Let's see your face. Let's see what you
people look like.
Come on. Davey showed his face. I've
showed my face.
I mean, let's see.
Let's see what you people look like.
Come on. Exactly.
Ah, self projecting. Self projecting.
The face of depression. No, I'm not
depressed at all.
Nope. Not depressed at all. I'm completely fine.
I just feel a bit sick. Yeah,
it's funny how you people have a lot to
say about people's looks, but you won't
show your faces. I wonder why. Huh.
So, back to what I was saying. So, you
know how I said I was taking a break for
four or five weeks and that's why I've
not been out, take a chance to save
money, go on a detox. So, what's the
reason you people on YouTube every day?
So, obviously, what happens when you
don't go out? When you're saving money,
you obviously you don't go out and you
you know, you you you save you save.
Yeah. Well, oh, that's why you won't
show yourself because you're ugly. Well,
thank you. Thank you. You've just
admitted it yourself. Um, you know.
Yeah. That's why you won't show your
face cuz you look worse than me. Yeah.
Thank you. Exactly. Proves my point.
Thank you. Just what I was saying. If
these people generally wasn't ugly, they
would come in and show their face. They
generally would come in and show their
face. If they weren't ugly, these people
done it. I've done it. If they generally
weren't ugly, they would come in and
show their face. Trust me, they would.
They generally generally generally
would. If I joined a new community right
now, I'd show my face. Why would I want
to stay anonymous? I don't need to stay
anonymous. No one's going to. So,
yeah. It's because you people are too
ugly. Just like this fat um this fat
cop. These people don't show their face
cuz they're too ugly.
That's why they try to call people that
like me that are better looking than
them ugly cuz they're ugly themselves.
He has nothing. Talking about yourself
again. Can't drive, can't work. Talking
about yourselves again. You are the ones
sat on YouTube every day cuz you ain't
got a life. You can't say the same thing
about me, bro. I've already told you why
I've been on YouTube. I mean, I've
already explained myself. Yeah, I ain't
got this. I ain't got that. Yet, you are
the ones that sat on YouTube every day
ain't got a life. Make it make sense.
Sat on YouTube all day, every [ __ ]
day. But you got all these things, don't
you? You keep telling yourself that.
Yeah. Everything is about your own lives.
We already know what you people do on
here, bro. It's It's not a problem.
You're a bunch of 40, 50 year olds. Got
no life, ugly, got no money, sad with
your lives. So, you come on here every
day to try to make yourself feel better
about the fact that you people are ugly
and you ain't got no life. That's why
you do this whole YouTube [ __ ] at your
age. Cuz you're all fat, ugly, bongos
ain't got no life. It's so obvious. It's
so obvious why you people do what you do.
It's so obvious. The fact that you do
this [ __ ] all day, every day.
Who the [ __ ] is that?
Oh yeah, it's so obvious. You people are
not living your best lives. Sing YouTube
all day every day. Got no life.
So obvious, bro. So obvious. Nah, don't
feel sorry for me, bro. Feel sorry for yourselves.
You are in your 40s. You ain't got no
life. You ain't got no money. You ain't
You ain't got no hope.
You know, you people ain't got no hope.
You're in your 40s. You're all old, fat,
ugly people. You ain't even got any hope, lad.
Like, don't feel sorry for me. Feel
sorry for yourselves. You ain't even got
hope. You can't even say you got hope.
You're all old, fat, ugly people. They
ain't got nothing. And you ain't even
got hope either. At least you'd have
hope if you was younger. But that's why
you do what you do every day on YouTube. Makes sense.
You were talking correctly about Yeah,
but it's not just them. It's other
people. So, you won't see me tomorrow, lad.
You sit in your room all day playing
Xbox all day and night and watch shitty
life. Um, actually, um, actually, lad.
So, what do you people do? Sit on
YouTube all day with your ugly self-p
projecting. Whoa. Some life you've got
sat on YouTube all day self-reflecting
every day cuz you got nothing. Whoa. I'd
love to be you people
sat on YouTube jealous of people every
day. Whoa. Your lives are so great.
Where do I sign up? Where do I sign up, bro?
No. You people call me ugly cuz you're
ugly yourselves. That's why you can't
show your faces. All ugly losers sat on
YouTube all day, every day. Everything I
do is spit facts about these people.
These people are losers.
They got no life. They got no money.
They [ __ ] got nothing. And I'm going
to prove it. I'm going to prove it
tomorrow when these people can't come
off of YouTube. You know why these
people go for me? [ __ ]
Um um Eldridge. Know why these people
are Yeah, exactly. You know you're ugly.
Exactly. Yes. self projecting. Exactly,
bro. You know you're ugly. I know you're
ugly. That's why you come on YouTube
every day doing what you do cuz you're
ugly bastards and you're jealous that
I'm better looking. Thank you. I know
you're even admitting it yourselves.
You're even admitting it yourselves,
bro. I'm better looking than all of you
ugly people. I'm the one that's been
with women and I've shown it a million
times. You ugly people ain't had nothing.
We know you people are [ __ ] ugly.
It's obvious why you come on here doing
what you do every day. Cuz you're
[ __ ] ugly. Ugly people. Ugly. That's
why you come on here every day. Cuz
you're [ __ ] ugly. Never been with a
woman. That's why you try to put
everyone down. Because you're all ugly.
No life, no hope. That's why you do what
you do. Cuz you're all [ __ ] ugly.
Disabled on benefits talking about
yourselves every day.
you know, and yeah, man, I hope you
people find peace as well. I hope one
day you people actually get a life.
You get off of YouTube, you get laid,
you get some money. I really hope you
little lowife mongos get off of YouTube
before it's too late. I really do, bro.
I really hope you ugly virgins get a
life when I'm off of YouTube. Yeah. From
tomorrow, bro, I really hope you mongos
get laid. But saying that, you're too
ugly. Can't get a woman.
Think about it, bro. I'm 20 fucking7.
You people are in your 40s. You got
nothing. You're losers, bro. You're
literally what? Yeah.
Should be used in primary schools.
[ __ ] don't end up like these people.
40, no bird, no money, no life. They
show it every day when they're on
YouTube. These people never been with a
bird. They're in their 40s.
Bro, I'm 28 next month and I've had a
girlfriend. You're in your 40s and
you've never had a woman. Self-project
him cuz you're ugly. You've even
admitted it yourself. You're ugly. I'm
28 and I've had more of a life than you.
More women, more sex, more money. Yeah.
A better life than you. Which is why you
people go for me. Yeah. 28 and been with
more women than you and you're still a
virgin in your 40s. Woo. Embarrassing,
isn't it, mate? [ __ ] embarrassing.
You people in your 40s and you you've
never been laid and you're talking about
someone half your age.
This community is a a community where
people have come together
40 ugly, no money, no hope, no they
don't even fit into society, these
people. Um so they come on here to feel
special because they got no life, no
money, no hope. That's why they're on
here every day. I mean, wait, wait, hold
on a minute. Is any of you people saving for anything?
Did you just come back on holiday? Wait,
sorry, I shouldn't say that. Sorry.
Sorry. Actually, um, bro, you people
don't bully me. Do you think you fat
ugly virgins bully me? You little bongos
that know where I live. Bro, you've
known where I've lived for years and you
can't do nothing. Bro, I bully you. The
fact I'm better looking, got more money
than you. I've wasted years of your life
being obsessed with me. I've made you
obsessed with me for years and you're
never getting that time back. In all of
them years when I was up and down the
country. Yeah. Think about it. You was
wasting your life. Wasting your life on
me. You don't bully me. You [ __ ] ugly
spasticated mongos. Don't bully me. You
waste your lives on me because I'm
better looking than you and got more
money than you. But yeah.
Yeah, I know. They want my ass. It's
because they're fat and ugly. That's
what I'm saying, bro. They latch on to
anyone younger and better looking than
them. Let them try to say anything they
want about me, bro. The fact is I'm
younger than them. I'm better looking
than them. I've got hope unlike them.
They got nothing. That's why they come
here every day. They're sad, ugly, fat
people, bro. They don't even leave their
house, bro. Honestly, bro, they don't
even leave their house.
These fat, ugly mongos don't even leave
the house. They're that ugly. Every time
they try to leave their house, bro, they
probably get slapped in their ugly face.
That's why they come on here every day
because they're no hopeer ugly people.
Yeah, man. It's mad.
These people, what they do all day,
every day, it proves it, bro. What they do.
These people are [ __ ] These people
They go for you cuz you're younger and
better looking than them.
That's why they go for you. The truth
hurts. The truth really, really hurts.
The reason these people go for me is
because I'm younger and better looking than them.
It's It's so obvious. It's so [ __ ]
They don't even try to hide it at this
point, bro. It's insane, lad.
They do this um because they're lonely
old ugly people. That's why they do this
every day. Christmas soon and it will be
another lonely one for PJ. Again, self
projecting. Everything that comes out of
these people's mouth is just self-p
projecting their own lives.
A selfie. Um everything these people do
is about their own lives. All in their
40s. All ugly. All skin. Says it all.
Absolutely says it all.
They got no life. They got nothing. Do
you know what? These people actually
drive me to do better. You know what I'm
going to do? I'm going to book another
holiday when I come out. When I come out
from Thailand, you know, these people
make me want to do better. You know,
don't want to end up like them. 40s, ugly,
no life, no money, never been laid. You
know, they really strive you to do
better, man. I swear to God, I can't
even explain it.
It's absolutely a madness. It really, really is.
It makes you appreciate something that
they don't have a life. Money, a life.
They ain't got [ __ ] nothing, bro. It's madness.
Yeah. Do you know what's so mad,
[ __ ] is like I've explained like
everything that they've asked. I've
tried to answer them as well. This is
why I'm coming off here. [ __ ] bro. I
was only on here for a couple of weeks
cuz I was just trying to save some money
and go on a detox. You know, I do this
three times a year. Um maybe, yeah, two,
three times a year. I do this, lad. And
the thing is is that it shows what these
re people really are. Like low lives sat
on YouTube every day. Um, it shows what they are.
It shows what they are. I'm not letting
you up cuz you're going to put a nude up
like you did last time. [ __ ] off. Like
it just shows what they are, bro. Every
day on YouTube.
You can't teach them real life.
You can't, bro. There's there's no um
there's no helping these people.
You know what I mean? It's just self
projection every day with them.
But I'm off here tomorrow anyways, bro. So
these people, I really hope they get a
life when I'm off of here.
Can't believe they go for me just cuz
I'm younger and better looking than
them. It's mad.
They talk about women. Yeah, I've been
with plenty of women who they've all
seen. They tried to say that I'm skint.
I've shown more money than all of these
people. It's like, bro, you could be a
millionaire. You could be Brad Pitt and
they'd stalk you because their life's
losers, their life's failures.
Do you understand?
They latch on to anyone younger and
better looking than them. It's like a
magnet. It's like a fridge magnet. If
you seen with these people, bro. So
mad. It is mad.
And if they really had a life, they
wouldn't be calling people every day on
YouTube that they don't know. Fax in it.
Yeah, you're going to, you know, the
longer you stay on it, like I said, the
longer you you lose brain cells as well, bro.
I swear they've actually given me a
headache, these people.
They actually give me a headache.
They're so [ __ ] [ __ ] on here. But
I mean, it was entertaining for
a couple of weeks, bro.
It was entertaining for a couple of
weeks. At least I was able to save
money. Never slept with any bird. Self
projecting again. Everything these
people do is self- projecting.
Everything they do is self project.
It's [ __ ] mad. Yeah.
[ __ ] hell, lad.
They're trying to sit there and say that
I've never had a girlfriend even though
I've proved I've had a girlfriend. This
is what I mean with these low life
people. There's no point even being on
here anymore, bro. But I can say thanks
for um keeping me entertained.
Um, YouTube is not my life like it is
these people's life. Um,
so and I'll prove that tomorrow one
million trillion billion%. The only
reason I've been on YouTube is like I
said, I haven't been going out cuz I've
been saving money. So
yeah, it shows what they are about.
Shows what they are about.
people are mad, bro. Mad.
They need to focus on their own lives.
They need to be um Hey, [ __ ] off. 5
years. I've been off of YouTube for
[ __ ] 3 weeks. You people can't take a
day off of YouTube. It's all you have.
If you didn't have coming on YouTube and
talking about yourselves, I don't know
what you would do. You would be [ __ ]
Like you people literally wake up every
morning, look at your [ __ ] selves,
look at your ugly faces, and think,
"Fuck, I'm going to start on someone on
YouTube today that's younger and better
looking than me." That's literally what
you do every single day. You got no life.
and your skin as well
cuz I was living like a skin person
obviously cuz I was saving money. You
know what I mean, bro? Yeah.
Anyways, I'll be back later. I'm going
to eat some salmon bite.