It's true. Yeah, bro.
Y [ __ ] gen people, bro. Yeah.
[ __ ] s three [ __ ] percent.
Oh man. I was going to go out tomorrow,
but I can't be [ __ ] bothered
with my clothes in the wash and [ __ ]
but I can't be asked, bro. It's depressing. quickly. Jeez.
Um, no ma'am.
No, I was going to go out tomorrow, bro.
I washed my [ __ ] clothes, but nah, I
don't want to go out, bro. It's too depressing.
It's too depressing this country, bro. I
washed my clothes and everything. I was
going to go out drinking, but nah, it's
too depressing. It's too depressing, bro.
I was going to, but no, it's too The
more I think about my experiences more
and more and more, the more it's just
not worth it.
It's just not worth it. It's depressing, bro.
I said the thing as well. We need to
stop talking about this. It's depressing.
Yeah, it's proper depressing, man.
It's It's depressing as well, bro.
And you got to deal with the hangover as
well. It's so depressing.
Nope. Still got it. Just chilling, bro. No.
Yeah, it is a waste. [ __ ] bro. It is a proper waste.
Yo, I was going to go out, but it's pointless, bro.
I'm I'm just going to stay here. I'm
going to go cinema.
I'm not doing any bets
today. I go out every day.
When was the last time you took a day off YouTube?
Oh, sorry. Sorry. When was the last time
you took an hour off YouTube?
>> I go out every single day.
Nah, not me, mate. But yeah,
I'm not really going to be on here much
anymore anyways because it's just the same atmosphere,
same repeating jealous people. So, I'm
only on here for a bit in it cuz I
thought, [ __ ] it, why not?
And I need to prove what I'm saying
about these people is right,
you know. So, that's another thing. And
obviously them being on here every day
doing what they do proves I'm right.
Who else would I talk to? My friends, my
family. YouTube's not my life like it is yours.
Bro, my YouTube ain't my life like you people's.
That's the difference.
Without this app, you'd be [ __ ] But yeah,
what the [ __ ] What's that?
Why this woman on Reddit has started
being an ignor Howard? So I messaged her
showing my approaches on my other
channel saying, "Have you seen the
approaches yet? Have you seen them? Have
you seen my approaches?" And she didn't reply.
She She didn't message. She didn't open
a message the whole day. Then I made
another account pretending to be a woman
and she opened it straight away. Jesus.
[ __ ] ignore users on Reddit. [ __ ]
ignore users, lad. >> Yeah.
Yeah. I can't be bothered, bro.
buddy right there to get my haircut, go
out drinking. But
nah, I don't think so, bro.
See, the more like you think about it,
the more you actually talk about it with
people, the more depressing it is.
It's so depressing.
You know what I mean?
It is depressing, bro. Oh, [ __ ]
I just can't justify it anymore.
Going out trying and [ __ ] I got my
clothes there to go. I just can't
justify it anymore, bro. The effort,
the [ __ ] the hangovers, just
wasting money. I just can't
I just can't justify it
to meet a bunch of people that can only play games. Pointless.
[ __ ] pointless, bro. I was speaking
to this woman on Instagram. She's 38 and
she's got a kid and she's being picky.
I'll say it as many times as I want to
[ __ ] say it.
I'll say what I want and I'll do what I
want as many times as I want to. So yeah,
you can't even meet people that don't
play games. What the [ __ ] bro?
How depressing is that?
Well, we gone to anyways. So,
nah, I'm not betting on the football either.
Can't be asked. >> No. [ __ ] man.
Make some bacon in a bit. I think
>> it's so depressing, isn't it?
Dating in this country is depressing as [ __ ] is it?
It is depressing, eh?
It's [ __ ] got cold, man. [ __ ] me.
Someone said, "If you're looking for a
hookup, go on Tinder.
[ __ ] They said go on Tinder. Wow.
Do these people live in the real world though
or they just taking a piss on purpose?
Go on Tinder. Wow. Yeah. [Music] Very good.
It's [ __ ] depressing, bro. It Yeah.
Why are they still telling people to go
on dating apps, Stephen Howard?
Why do these people on Reddit keep
telling people to use dating apps when
they literally don't even work and they
haven't worked for about four or five years?
Why they keep telling me to go on dating apps?
still telling me to keep trying.
I give up, bro. You can't get through to these people.
still telling me I'm going to meet
people. [ __ ] sake. Still telling me I'm
going to meet someone. This is the
depressing [ __ ] Them giving you this
shitty advice that don't work.
still telling me to keep trying.
What these people
What these people do is they dismiss your struggles.
and they resort to making stuff up
for various different reasons. They
could be a s. They just might not have
the answers or whatever. But I noticed
that they that they um they like to
dismiss people's struggles and make stuff up.
I've noticed that that's that's all they
really really do is just make up things
of match. Good man.
Is this dismiss your struggles?
What's my opinion? I don't care about it.
Why are they telling me to use Tinder
when Tinder doesn't even work? Oh, madness.
Yeah. I don't think I'm going to go out tomorrow, bro. No.
Where's that one? Did I do
Yeah, they dismiss your struggles.
That's what they do.
This is what people on Reddit do. They
dismiss your struggles.
Like for example, you show them like 10
approaches and you'll show them like 10
different conversations. They'll just
miss it all and make stuff up like
you've come on too strong or they will
just not acknowledge anything that
you've shown them and then they'll just
resort to giving advice like they've not
just seen a load of [ __ ] that you've shown them. So [Music]
>> yeah, bro.
I I wouldn't I wouldn't I wouldn't
accept your bet because I know you'd be right.
No, cuz I know you're right. So I'm not
going to bet when I know I'm going to lose.
If there was a market right in William
Hill to bet on this, I would be rich.
Exact. If I could predict exactly what
would happen, when it would happen, and
what the numbers would do that I get,
I'd be a millionaire. If I could bet on
what would happen every time I go out,
I'd be a millionaire, bro. No, no joke.
I could actually, you know, like correct
score. I could actually say what will
happen, when will happen, etc. Yeah, I'm
not [ __ ] betting. [ __ ] that.
Yeah, that's why I'm not going out.
But that's the only thing you can do is
approach and it doesn't work. I mean,
yeah, it's insanity, but it's the only
thing you can do cuz dating apps don't
work. So, I mean, yeah, it's insanity,
but it's the only thing you can do. But
obviously, I'm not doing it anymore. But
that's the only thing you can do.
Well over 200 times, bro. I've done it
over [ __ ] two million times.
Two million times.
I've done it about two million times.
[ __ ] over 200 times. Over 200 [ __ ]
I've probably approached 200 people
[ __ ] New Year's Eve.
[ __ ] well over two million times. I
think you'll find.
Yeah, it's well over two million times.
>> 200 [ __ ] times. What the [ __ ] It's
been more than that, bro. Forgot about
200 numbers on my phone.
38 with a child. She's picky.
It depends what you class as success.
Um, well, it depends what you class as success.
Leave his age. Bro, you people in your
40s, I'm still [ __ ] young compared to
you people. What the [ __ ] You people in
your [ __ ] 40s, 50s,
bro. Even when I'm 30, I'm young
compared to you people,
bro. You people in your 40s and 50s
again. I think you're getting yourself
confused with me again.
28 is not old.
But yeah, obviously that is a thing as
well. That's probably why I probably
don't go out anymore. If you Yeah, in
that sense. Yeah. But what do you class as success?
Yeah, I've not had much success. So
basically, if I didn't approach, I'd be
a virgin. So everyone's advice is
[ __ ] then, isn't it?
I mean, yeah. It's just
Yeah. Yeah, I just can't be bothered
with it anymore, bro.
Yeah, I mean, you can still approach on
the street. Yeah, I know what you mean.
I mean, you could still approach on the street.
You can still do it on the street,
though, obviously. But I ain't got time
to be doing that, bro.
Yeah, I don't think I'm going to go out
tomorrow. I'm going to save my money, I
think, for my holiday. Yeah,
but yeah, I know what you're saying. Yeah, obviously. Yeah,
it's probably why I don't want to go out anymore.
going out getting rejected every
weekend. Yeah, [ __ ] that.
Quitting. Yeah, it the positives
outweigh the negatives when you quit.
Uh yeah, the negatives outweigh the
positives when you quit. Trust me,
the negatives outweigh the positives.
not going to go out tomorrow.
I think I'm going to go to my sisters
or something. Yeah, I'm not going out tomorrow.
No, [ __ ] that, bro. No way.
This woman was like, "But for I think
you're good chances since you're not
afraid to even approach women on the
street. Some men can barely do it." I
said, "I have good chances. I've
literally shown you me approaching a lot
and getting rejected. Are you trolling
me?" This is what I'm saying. They dis
um they're dismissing my struggles. This
is what I'm saying. They they like to
dismiss people's struggles
and um make up stuff.
They love making up stuff.
I don't know why they make up stuff, but
they love doing it.
>> So, how old are you? How old is being
too old to go out to me? >> 27.
I kind of called it at 27 to be fair. Yeah.
Yeah, they're definitely trolling. Definitely trolling.
Cuz when I still at the house, I didn't
go out when I stole at the house when I
was 27. As soon as I hit 27,
I stopped doing it as much.
And I feel like now if I went out for a
drink, I would just wear my hoodie and
my coat. I wouldn't even make effort.
Um, you know what I'm saying? I would
just wear like a coat and a hoodie.
Obviously, I get my haircut, but I
wouldn't even make effort like I used
to. You know what I mean? My hair, like
the the dress sense. I wouldn't even make effort. Yeah.
you you become the Jesus Christ.
Yeah, that's probably why I just don't
get tempted to go out much anymore. I've
got the money. I can go out whenever I
want and go every week if I want, but
it's it's not that, bro. It's just it's
just too depressing, you know? Yeah.
Oh, Reddit's banned me again.
They love banning people. Timmy, the
mods love that power.
They love that power.
They love that power to me.
They love that power of binding people and it
that the mods need that power.
My birthday to be fair.
Well, I have to go on my birthday. Um, yeah. Yeah.
Going to make some piggies.
Oh, that you never guess what that uh
finish Izzy said. Steven Howard,
you never guess what that finish Izzy said.
She said um
I'm see uh she said I found someone. Oh no,
not you as well.
It's all the [ __ ] you say.
Yeah. See the barely found somebody that quickly. >> Yeah. [Music]
Come downstairs to make some porkies.
But yeah, I'm not going to You know
what? I don't want to save my money,
bro. Just put it towards my holiday.
Honest to God, bro, I'd rather just
like, yeah, [ __ ] this.
I said to her as well, stop saying that
I'm a nicel looking man or whatever.
I'll come to you. You said, "Oh, I don't
even live in England. I'll come for you.
I don't mind coming. I don't pay pay the
money going to wherever you are to prove
that you're [ __ ] full of shit." Don't
give me advice
and try to manipulate me saying, "Oh,
I'm this and I'm that yet you would get
with me if I was the last man on [ __ ]
Earth." I hate that idea. I [ __ ] hate
that. I generally hate that [ __ ] bro. I
[ __ ] hate that [ __ ]
I [ __ ] hate that [ __ ] bro.
cuz they'll just make you go to wherever
the [ __ ] they are and call their blood.
Okay. Well, you're not in the UK now.
I'm where you are now. So what? I hate it, bro.
Get on the bed. Sit. No bed in it. Bro,
that's so catchy. I can't stop saying that, bro.
It's literally on my mind, man.
Virgin boy getting in the bed with no
money in it. No bed in it. I can't stop
saying it, bro. Why? It's so patchy.
Boy ain't got no money. Oh,
you a scheme bastard.
You ain't got [ __ ] all £13,000 peanuts
to stay for three years and not have a
bed and no life experience. You're born
from well off, mate.
I've never seen someone.
I've never seen someone so skinned all
me life. He's skinned with a skin flu.
people to feel powerful virgin boy
in the dancing.
You think that's [ __ ]
How the [ __ ] could that little ugly rat
face with no money try and call me
[ __ ] skink when I've always had more
money than him?
How is that little ugly bastard with
ugly clothes and no bed going to sit in
his virgin [ __ ] bedsit council beds sit
and try and [ __ ] tell me I'm skin?
He's gonna sit there in his virgin
shitty bed suit with no bed in it with
his fat disabled girlfriend and none of
them got any money and try and [ __ ]
talk about me, bro. Are you [ __ ] mad?
You're going to sit in that [ __ ] bed
suit and no money and try and [ __ ]
talk about me? Are you [ __ ] mad, bro?
[ __ ] hell, lads.
I'm not going to Thailand next week. I'm
going to Thailand next month. Well, not
next month. November.
Where your boy go of all that? He ain't
got the money. No money. No money. No
No money. No money. No money. No money.
They used to kill it at the£50. Show us
your money. You ain't got no
>> I might do it again, you know, to be
honest because it shows Timmy up in the
Virgin and I'm not going to Thailand
next week. I'm going Thailand in November.
Nope. I never said I'm going to Thailand in October.
Definitely definitely didn't.
always been November.
You must have the wrong channel.
No, it doesn't change all the time. No,
it doesn't. I never said I'm going in
October. Everybody knows I'm going in
November. Try again. You got the wrong channel.
It's always been November for the past
four or five months. Try again
and you're banned. My passing. Yeah.
Well, you don't think that's the
You don't think that's the skin of a
virgin in the bed? You reckon that's bomb?
And just And even showing £13,000 is
peanuts. That's not even a year's money,
bro. £13,000, no life experience, no
bed, no teeth, no clothes. I don't know
what is more skint than that to be
honest lad. That is [ __ ] skint.
He is [ __ ] skint.
What age do you think you get bored of
going out clubbing and drinking Steven Hour?
What would you say about 20 uh 27?
I mean, you might do it every two or
three months, but I mean, this is the
age where you should be setting them
down with someone and obviously if you
haven't met anyone, then you haven't met
anyone, but that's the end of that.
Like, now I'm thinking of all the places
I can go now. And I'd rather put money
towards that. You know what I'm saying?
I think like obviously most people
settle down at this stage and obviously
if people don't have anyone then,
you know, that's just that in it. They
just live with it. They just live with
it. Is it? So,
I just can't justify trying anymore,
bro. I just can't justify it.
It's like it's ingrained in my skull now.
It's It's just like it's just ingrained
in my skull.
Like I'll go out on my birthday cuz like
I said, it's my birthday. It's a special
occasion. So, but I won't be going out again, bro.
cuz I don't mean I have even more money
to do what I want to do and I might as
well just save the money, you know,
makes more sense and waste it, get nowhere. So,
it just doesn't make sense.
And I find that even speaking about it
is quite depressing.
Even when you're talking about your
so depressing, bro.
[ __ ] I don't want to go and get
[ __ ] rejected. [ __ ] that. Y bro. Yeah. Uh,
how we doing? [Laughter] [ __ ]
The Reddit mods need that power.
I mean, Cory need Reddit mods. They need that power.
They need They have to ban people to feel powerful.
They need that power. Without that
power, mate, and go [ __ ] mad.
I think it's a load of bollocks, mate.
When I'm trying to watch [ __ ] pool,
then it's [ __ ] You know what I mean? Yeah.
Where's the skin virgin in the bed with
no money and no bed in it?
C's been quiet. [ __ ] hell.
>> That's a McDonald's day, by the way.
That's some vouchers.
It's going to be lush.
Where's the skin virgin?
Where's the skin bastard?
No better. No life experiences.
You know me, Cory. I'm a [ __ ] mad
[ __ ] mate. I'm not to be [ __ ] with.
I'm a mad [ __ ] mate.
When did I meet Wiggy? [ __ ]
I trade in Wiggy. I think it was a
pergo, was it? Yeah,
where's the [ __ ] skin in the bed with
no money in it?
Where's the [ __ ] skin bastard?
Oh, my thing cost me over a grand.
[ __ ] you skin bastard. Is that all?
You probably [ __ ] paid off for it as
well. You [ __ ] skin bastard
with the ugly face and the ugly clothes
and no mayonnaise. You know what I like
to I'm a crazy clut. If you weren't
skinned, you would be dressing like a
[ __ ] drunk in them ugly clothes and
you have some [ __ ] teeth in your
[ __ ] mouth. You [ __ ] skinned bastard.
Oh, if you're watching this Ricky Mill
as well. Yeah, suck your mother, you
northern ugly, weak little [ __ ] bastard.
We little skinny arms. You little naky
geeky little simpy little virgin. You
little neat talking [ __ ] behind my back.
You scorny little ugly white kid. No
money, no life. I'll have you know I've
been seen with more money and more women
than any of you [ __ ] [ __ ] You've
been seen with nothing cuz you ain't got nothing.
No. What's happened now? I know the
window got smashed.
Yes, I know the window got smashed.
Just turned my little bacon. No.
[ __ ] in England. What a loser.
Where is it?
What channel? What am I looking on?
You see that Ricky Millan account, lad.
I don't know what Shaggy's channel is. Ricky Millan.
Ricky Milling has got no money, no life,
and he's got skinny arms.
Did you see that [ __ ] video? See that
picture where he's trying to flex his arms?
Skinny little white knicky geeky little virgin.
That's why he gets told we non flex so
much cuz they're both skin virgins. Both
screwy as [ __ ]
attention to [ __ ] arms, bro. Like my
arms are [ __ ] bigger than these.
That I don't go to gym anymore. That's
muscle, mate. Not what you would be like
this. Look. [ __ ] weak little bastard.
Right. Let me have a look
what's going on here.
One second. One second.
it. Jesus Christ. What the [ __ ] Yeah, I
just see it, bro. [ __ ] There's money
going to the dam. I've already been to
Amsterdam when I was 23
and £13,000 is nothing. I've shown more
money than that and I've spent more
money than that in two months. Try
again. £13,000 is nothing. I used to
spend 67,000 a month and I've already
gone to Amsterdam when I was 23, not 31.
£13,000 is peanuts, mate. To have
sacrificed your [ __ ] life for three
years, doing nothing, no bed, sat in a
bed sit. You think £13,000 is a flex?
Allow it, bro. Allow it, bro.
Allow it, bro. Please stop it. It's embarrassing.
It's embarrassing, bro. £13,000 with
peanuts. To save £13,000 in three years
is absolutely no amount of money to
sacrifice your youth. Yeah. But
this is quite nice.
Anyway, you go a fantasy. That's why they're [ __ ]
What happened to money? Nah,
just some bacon. Some bacon.
£1,000 is not a big amount of money.
Trust me, bro.
Does that provise your life for three
years? No design, no bed, no life
experience. I wouldn't trade it for fighting ground.
I would not trade it for fighting grand,
bro. Not worth it.
I would not trade that for £13,000. All
the life experiences I've had
cuz they're things to look back on
sometimes, you know.
My experiences, things to look back on.
No, I'm not saying that, bro. Just freaky bacon.
£13,000 is not owning anyone
to me. Right.
I've got more money than him. I've got
designer pes. I've got a bed. I've got a
mom that don't stop me. Been with more
women. Been to more countries. Been to
more places. I've got teeth in my mouth.
But apparently I'm the one that
explains that to me.
He has less money than me, less life
experiences, been to less places, less
country, less restaurants, less women.
But I'm supposed to be dead. What the [ __ ]
See what? See that video? I don't know
about backing up your statement. I mean,
you're mad then.
Um I I I sound slightly obsessed.
Um he's got a YouTube channel stalking
me every day. I don't know if you missed
that, but um yeah, he's kind of got a YouTube channel
stalking me all day, every day.
Um yeah, I don't know if you knew about
it, but yeah, he's got a literal He's
got an actual channel dedicated to me.
Like an actual channel channel dedicated
to stalking me.
But yeah, I'm the one that's obsessed. Okay.
Trust me, I'm far from obsessed with that version.
Who's got the channel on who?
He copied my holiday. Come here.
[ __ ] He copied my holiday, bro.
He went to Amsterdam just cuz I went there.
He went somewhere just cuz I [ __ ]
went there. That's crazy.
I thought the [ __ ] sh thing was bad.
Copy him. I don't know. I don't know
people that copies people's holidays.
And you can try and say all you want
about how your holiday is better than
mine and it costs more. It's not about that.
It's the whole you went to somewhere the
exact same place that I went.
No, but you didn't answer my question.
Can you at least ask my Can you at least
answer my question before you go? That
was very rude of you, sir.
Can you at least answer my question
before you go? That was very rude of you, sir.
That was very, very rude of you, sir.
Very rude of you indeed. You know, you
said that I'm obsessed, but then I told
you that he's got a whole channel
dedicated to me.
How rude of you.
You are very rude, sir. Very rude.
Sorry about that, brother.
Yeah, he needs to get laid. I'm not
going to let him die a virgin. I'm not a
narcissist. Do you not understand, Timmy?
Right. I'm not going to sit there and
allow him to die a virgin. No one should
be a virgin at that age. Why do you
think sometimes I bring them up? Because
I don't want to see someone I've met die
a virgin. You know what I mean, bro?
We're not all [ __ ] narcissists like you people.
You want me think I want to see him out
there never having a woman, never having
sex, never been with a [ __ ] woman.
Don't [ __ ] try and tell me he's got a
[ __ ] girlfriend, son. Don't you
[ __ ] try and tell me he's got a
[ __ ] girlfriend because that is not a [ __ ] girlfriend. You know
that ain't a girlfriend, bro. Don't even try.
Get off him.
>> Yeah, that's good, bro. Anyways, yeah,
make sure you [ __ ] get that cup
benefit stop. Hit the virgin where it
hurts in these pockets. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. And I'm not into grassing,
but he's a dirty grass. I try and find
out who that red star is as well, Timmy. Whest
has blocked me on everything. That's a
bit sus, isn't it? I've noticed with Bar
Quest, he's uh blocked me on everything
randomly. I was speaking to him the
other night, normal conversation and
whatnot, and then out of the blue,
[ __ ] just [ __ ] banned me.
Blocked me. Sorry.
Bam. He [ __ ] blocked me. That Yeah,
that was a bit dodgy.
We was only talking over there. I woke
up. They come to block me. Deleted all the messages.
I've got a feeling that Red Sauce chased me.
It's something definitely something to
do with that virgin.
Yeah. Defer death.
I think it is as well. But I don't know
why Red uh I don't know why um Bar
randomly blocked me on everything.
That's weird, bro. We were talking and
then I I got a couple of these blocks.
What's your opinion on that? Yeah, man. Oh yeah.
Why do you think um randomly blocked me
on everything, Timmy? Bit strange. He
blocked me on everything and deleted all
the messages and stuff.
Bit strange, is it?
Get the stuff. Yeah.
We need to try and get non snakes laid.
What do you think to me?
We need to try and get him [ __ ] laid.
Help him lose it. Stop being the [ __ ]
virgin of your life.
I don't want some of the [ __ ] dire
virgin. You know what I mean?
I don't want someone die of virgin.
I'm not like you people in here. You're
out to [ __ ] ruin people. I don't want
I don't want him to die a virgin.
Someone never know what a woman feels
like cuz he's too ugly to get one.
You know what I'm saying?
I'm having a nice cup of [ __ ] in my Belgian mug.
But one second.
might not be able to see it properly.
There we go.
Oh, sorry. That's my sexy face in it.
It's actually this. Yeah.
That's the one, boss.
But how are you going to lose it? When
you going to lose it? When are you going to lose?
How are you going to lose?
How are you going to lose it? When you
going to lose it,
you [ __ ] virgin. Oh, the charger is
[ __ ] downstairs. You [ __ ] virgin Huh?
Yeah. You know what I said to Chase as
well? I said, "You could bring that
virgin. You and that virgin come both
come to London. I'll slap you [ __ ] both up."
I said that uh to them to me. You can
both come to London. I'll slap you both up. You know,
you know, I send you back to Kitty and
the Gallivan in the valleys.
I send you in the valleys,
you [ __ ] Welsh [ __ ]
Oh, it's fine, mate.
Yeah, it's fine.
Giddy in the gallivan.
So, uh, Timmy, do you still, uh,
do you still drink
hiddy in the gallivan up the valleys?
That's how he talks. Yeah.
I don't think he needs to get laid
or he [ __ ] dies one.
How often do you drink? What? Once a month.
What is it? Once a month, e
ain't drunk for a month. Me, bro.
I want to drink again. To be fair,
go out, get rejected by women.
Depressing, isn't it?
I'll take the bit boredom over the
depression any day of the week. So,
yeah, I used to go out every two weeks.
Now it's like,
yeah, I don't know when I'll be out
again, bro. I was going to go out
tomorrow, but nah, I can't be your ass.
It's too depressing.
Have you ever been a month without drinking?
So what do you do? Just drink indoors, huh?
I'm guessing you just drink indoors.
Yeah, that's good, man.
Yeah, I should be settled down at this
age. I'm 28 next month.
a month and two days.
I should have been settled down by now, bro.
This is the age where you start thinking
about what you want to do like goals and
stuff and you know what I mean at this
age or if you're if you're not settled
down. You see?
You see what I mean, bro?
But yeah, it's mad.
Yeah, bro. See, when they sent letters
to my mom's neighbors, that never
happened. None of that happened. What's
happening to him?
Where's Monty gone? I want I want to
send him the video. I'm going to send
My bad. No, money. Bro, you're 48.
You're still a virgin and you ain't got
no money. Again, self-projecting.
No one cares about you self-reflectors.
I'm younger than you and I got more
money than you and I've had more women
than you. Go self-reflect on another
channel. No one cares. What's Shaggy's channel again?
No money. No money. Oh, if only you knew
how much money I had, boy. I just let
you keep self-reflecting. Cuz the thing
is, Timmy, with these people, right, you
need to let them keep self-reflecting
because they're only talking about their
own lives when they're trying to tell
people that they've got no money.
They're just talking about themselves
cuz it takes one to no one. They're only
talking about their own lives. They
don't know what people have. They don't
know what people don't have. That's why
when Timmy says, "Oh, your skin show me
money." I said, "I'm not showing you nothing."
And I say, "Okay, I'm skint. I'm not
showing you nothing. I'm not playing
your silly little self-p projecting
games. I just laugh at it now cuz it's
just self projecting.
It's like what L does.
These people in their 40s skin nothing
to life. I laugh at them, bro.
at Big Shagger.
Yeah, they're just self-reflectors.
Fake laugh. Never ever had a fake laugh
in my life.
Never had a fake laugh in my life. Never.
So, where's um
where's um anyways, I'm going to ignore
the self-reflecting comments now.
Anyways, um so where's Monty then?
He's on a runner in it.
It's good, man.
It's good. It's good.
He should have done a runner to be
honest. These people are just self-reflectors
projecting bastards every day on YouTube. Deled
Yeah, of course he's watching.
I find what happened to Rice funny, you
know, cuz they tried having that happen to me,
but it never worked.
Never had homeless.
Yeah. I can't believe that, you know.
Oh, man. So, the whole thing with Kaye
getting with Rice, it all kind of
backfired if you think about it. Yeah, backfired.
That's hilarious, bro.
Uh, I didn't get I didn't get caught
letting out some Albert Square.
You know, again, self projecting. You
live off Pip, you bum up. Self projecting again.
Anyways, we're not acknowledging self
projected now. Anyways, was the last time
Stop self projecting.
Yes, I am still here.
The food's nice in Thailand. Anyways,
all right now.
So, yeah, bro.
So, you stopped going out drinking at what, 25? Nah. 25. Yeah.
Yeah. I done my clothes ready for
tomorrow, but I ain't going out, bro. No way.
Nah, it's too depressing. Yeah. Oh, really?
Where's Ronald Pump?
Where's Ronald Pump gone?
I like Ronald Pump. I don't know where
he's gone. I don't know where that JF
account's gone as well. He's not been on
for a while.
might be dead.
I think that's Steven Howard. Yeah.
Ronald Pump said to me, "You're better
looking than these people. You've got a
better life than these people, and
you've got more money than them, and it kills them."
and he said, "Get off of YouTube and
live your life."
I always thinking that guy,
he was so right about that. He said that
they will never leave you alone. And a
year later, these people have not left me alone.
H guess Ronald McDonald was right, eh?
Yeah, I guess he was right, bro. I guess
he was right.
Yeah, I think he was right, man.
Cuz they haven't left me alone. They
don't leave me alone. They don't leave
me alone, bro.
He was right though about get off a
YouTuber live your life though that cuz
these people never leave you alone. He
was right though is it
boy old pump. Yeah. [Music]
But yeah, that rice thing is mad.
Nothing mad, bro.
Anyways, I'm gone yet. See you.