[ __ ] hell. Jesus Christ, man.
I'm [ __ ] wasted, bro. Still. [ __ ] Damn. Jesus Christ.
Oh my god.
To be fair, I woke up earlier than I
than I normally wake up.
[ __ ] it. I I wake up normally early and
only wake up.
I normally [ __ ] wake up like 2:00. So
I feel it's okay. Oh [ __ ]
So I got a football bat.
No, I can't be asked
if it will be I can't be asked, bro. [ __ ] [ __ ] me.
H over ass. H over [ __ ] ass. [ __ ]
Oh [ __ ] I need to reply to the virgin, don't I?
Bro, I sent it hard, bro. I got 10
numbers. I didn't I haven't even
messaged any of them yet. Match in a bit.
Hey, don't be so negative, man. Just cuz
you're too fat and ugly and skinted to
go out. Don't [ __ ] spread negativity
on my channel
just cuz you're fat and ugly and got no
life. We're not having that kind of
negativity on my channel on a [ __ ]
Saturday. Sorry, mate. You have to be blocked. Um,
bro, Peter Bell is always looking crisp
when Peter belly goes out, bro.
That's That's how I go out, man.
Although I look like a skinned virgin.
Like virgin eggs.
Oh, bro. Did you see I spent £40 on just
rounds? Yeah, that's it, bro. I have
money. I have enough money. I just don't
show money on YouTube because I don't
entertain self projectors.
Like I said to you, bro, a wise man
learn from his mistakes. But yeah,
[ __ ] yeah. Next thing we know, Virgin
Boy is going to be Thail going to be going Thailand. Yeah.
Next thing we know, well, I haven't even
got out of bed yet. So, how can I bust
my team? I haven't even got out of bed.
[ __ ] V. Virgin boy is going to be
going Thailand. Sage
Frank, he's going to end up going Thailand.
He's a little copycat. You like
He chat so much [ __ ] in that video.
So much [ __ ] [ __ ] in that video, bro.
It's unfucking believable. Um,
well, that's that's impossible cuz I've already been.
Um, yeah, I'm going to do a video
replying to that. And we're going to
we're going to address the virgin thing
as well. Um, because you said I'm a
virgin. Now, remember what people what
you said about people convincing themselves
The thing is, there's actual proof I've
had sex. There's none that you've had
sex. You know, you can show you with a
disabled girl all you want, but there's
actual proof I've had sex. I put a
[ __ ] porno out there. I mean, what's
more do you [ __ ] want? Do you understand? So, yeah, man.
I mean, there's actual proof I've had
sex. There's no proof that you've had
sex. Whether you have a girlfriend or
you don't, I mean,
that's where we're at. That's just how
it is. So, yeah.
Yeah. These people on YouTube ain't got
no life, bro. I just went live yesterday
to see how many people would come and lo
and behold, all on YouTube.
Huh? Is that a thing?
I was only on YouTube once yesterday and
that was at the end of the [ __ ] night.
I know he's obsessed.
I'll do I'll do a response video anyways
because there's a few things I need to say.
And then he said,
"Oh, um, jealous."
Huh? jealous that you went somewhere
that I've already been that I would
never go again. I would Why would I be
jealous of [ __ ] somebody going to the
same place as I went? Why would I be
jealous of a copycat?
What the [ __ ] I can go Amsterdam today
if I wanted to. I would never go to
Amsterdam again. I didn't like
um it was overpriced and to be fair,
yeah, Netherland, the Netherlands is a nice country.
Um, and there's some nice places in the
Netherlands and the people are nice, but
Amsterdam is not nowhere near the nice
nicest place in the Netherlands.
It's nowhere near the nicest place in
the Netherlands, bro. There's so many
nicer places and the people are nice
there, too. But I just didn't like Amsterdam. simple.
I preferred Rotter.
Well, I'll be jealous of um a holiday
that I've already been on.
What the [ __ ] I mean, I went I done
that same thing when I was 23.
Yeah, I was that young. I was 23, bro. I
weren't even in my mid20s when I when I went abroad.
Do you know what I'm saying? So,
but yeah, he's got all this money.
You're right. All this money, but no life experience.
Yep. Uh but then when I went again, the
lockdown got lifted. So,
I can't believe I got 10 numbers yesterday.
Was mad, bro. I was doing them sober as
well. That guy who I was with yesterday,
bro, he's never going to approach. I
bought him [ __ ] two rounds and he
still wouldn't do it.
He still wouldn't do it.
I've met that guy several times, man.
But he ain't never going to do it, so he's scared.
really really scared.
It doesn't bother me. I've been doing it for years.
These two um 20 year olds yesterday.
Oh, the prostitute story was the funniest.
Well, obviously I went to the barbers. Duh. Um,
yeah. I was with these two 20-year-olds
and they're like, "Oh, it's annoying me
that I can't do it and you can." I said,
"I didn't start doing it until I was 23.
I couldn't do it before I was 23." But
they were drunk as well. I said, "What
have you got to lose?" Nothing, bro.
Yeah. I've never got 10 numbers before,
bro. I think I've got eight before. I
haven't got 10.
Let's just hope one of them meets, but
I'm not expecting them to
to be fair. So,
yeah, that escort thing was a mad story yesterday, bro.
Cuz let's face it, there's a high chance
that one of them is not going to meet.
It's so obvious, bro. like cuz
I you know when I was doing it yesterday the
bro I wasn't getting nothing and I was
using pickup lines as well they weren't
having any of it like they just weren't
having it at all at all and then it's
like well hold on if you can't even get
a conversation out of someone
um how you going to meet someone I mean
I don't know it just popped in my head
but we went on anyways
Yeah, 10 numbers. I'm going to message
them in a bit.
Yeah, 10 [ __ ] numbers. I don't [ __ ] approaches.
Yeah, but a lot of them like
paid on a Thursday. I never got paid on
a Thursday. You don't know when I get
paid and you don't know how much money I
have. Um, again,
I don't know who you're talking about,
bro, cuz you're not talking about me.
I don't get paid on Thursdays and I have money,
you know. I'll be out next week as well,
to be fair.
You don't know when people get paid
and you don't know how much money people
have as well.
That's what makes me laugh. In a way, it is entertaining.
So, you must be talking about yourself
because I've never been paid any money
on a Thursday. So, I know it's your self
projection, Mike. I went live at the pub
yesterday with this guy and all of these
people's on here. Hy. So,
oh my god, bro. [Music] I'm fat.
I'm just going eat some food later.
I'm not doing a football asked. Yeah, I
got 10 numbers yesterday. Mike,
I've never been paid on a Thursday before.
No. Any football bets? No. I can't be asked.
Are you doing any football bets, Mike?
I could go and put 20 pound on on a
football bet in it. Might as well.
You don't know how much money I have again.
Oh, Jesus Christ. Right. Um,
how much did you put on the aka?
Oh, [ __ ] me, bro.
How much do you have on him?
Quite the walk.
It's quite the walk, bro.
I don't know if I can actually be bothered. Oh, bye-bye.
So many self-reflectors on this community, bro.
It's unbelievable. So many self [ __ ] reflective.
Did I put 80 pound on two teams or
what do you think?
What do you think, Mike? I put eight
Yeah, that's what I was going to do as
well. I'm I'm going to bet on the other
league. I'm bet on that league. [Applause]
>> I'm going to back up the other league, bro.
want to move there.
Yeah, I know. I need to
I don't know if I can be bothered though, bro.
I can't be asked, man. I can't be bothered.
I'd rather go cinema, to be fair. I'm
going to go cinema.
No, I go send them all, bro.
I can't be bothered.
No, I wasn't going to bet on that one. I
was going to bet on the National League.
I've been thinking of giving up betting,
you know, Mike. It's just a waste of
time, isn't it? Betting.
Just a waste of time.
I don't know, bro.
I don't need to win any more money. I
have money and
yeah, I just can't be asked minute bike.
Waste time betting, huh?
What do you think, bro? It's a waste of
time, isn't it?
And I like best I like betting on the
National North League.
Well, I need to do a video to this
Virgin, by the way.
Make him right on a couple of things. To
be fair, I don't feel that bad now.
That'd be okay to go cinema, I think. So,
I mean, there's so many showings today. So,
I can't believe I got 10 numbers, bro.
I'm [ __ ] mad, bro. I am mad bastard.
I'm a mad bastard, man.
Yeah, bro. 10 numbers.
Bad ass [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
Yeah, I got [ __ ] bro. I got really, really [ __ ]
I got [ __ ] up.
Waiting for the TFL charge to rape in the ass. Yeah, TFL charge.
Buy some new jeans. Some new Ammani
Oh, that's another expense.
My my jeans ripped yesterday, bro. You
know the button. What do you mean how I
approach women? So, I got numbers.
Um, my Marley jeans are [ __ ] the the the
button [ __ ] It come off. Luckily, I
had a belt, so obviously you couldn't
notice it because the belt blended in.
But if I didn't have that belt,
I would have been [ __ ] bro.
Seriously. Cuz I was thinking, should I
buy a belt? Should I not? If I didn't
buy, I would have been screwed. The
button just come off.
Yeah, I just sent it, bro.
I'll be out again next week.
sending it again cuz um
my I got my haircut so it'll still look
good next week and then done for like
another two weeks.
He's um pension like no one's
interested, bro. No one cares. You don't
know how much money I have. You don't
know how much people have. This guy is
[ __ ] obsessed. Honestly, he is obsessed, bro. Yeah.
Um, I could do it. 200 people.
What do you mean where I'm not focused?
What do you mean?
What do you mean? I done it not focused.
That doesn't make sense. You wouldn't
That doesn't make sense. But yeah, on the Yeah.
No, you can get numbers on the street,
but maybe two maximum, not 10. You know,
it's hard. The street's harder. I didn't
get any on the street to be to be fair.
No, I didn't get any on the street to be fair.
I normally get about three or four. I
don't know what come over me. I just
thought, "Fuck it. Let's just send it."
To be fair, I was nervous to do the
first one to be fair because I hadn't
done it in like a month and I was using
pickup lines as well. So, to be fair, um
the first one I was nervous, but then
after that I just smashed it. So,
I had done it for a while. So, I mean, yeah,
I'll message them in a bit. Yeah,
I can't believe that prostitute story,
bro. I was going to [ __ ]
I was going to smash that window in,
bro. [ __ ] take the piss out of me, you [ __ ] Yep.
I'm not telling you my pickup line, bro.
No, I was happy to get half the money
back cuz I still got the [ __ ] and
[ __ ] what I wanted. So, no, I just
wanted half the money back. So, I
actually saved money. I actually saved
£20. So, yeah, man.
I don't want to.
But that's what happens in this country.
You get [ __ ] over. That's England for
you. But I I mean I didn't get [ __ ]
over, but I mean like you get people
that tried to take the piss and annoy you. Um
that's what I mean. Yeah. [ __ ] it. Anyways,
see most of the escorts are [ __ ] now, you know. So,
virgin boy can never approach.
Yeah, virgin boy can never approach. He
ain't got it in him.
You ain't got the minerals.
Shame. You ain't got the minerals, mate.
You know, everybody's made differently.
I'm made a [ __ ] crazy [ __ ] That's
what I am.
So, yeah, we'll message these numbers in a bit.
And yeah, let's hope we
I'm not holding up much hope to be fair,
bro. It's [ __ ] hard. So
anyways, I'm going.
Don't know when I'll be back, but I