Mhm. Yo yo.
Oh, this is nice.
Probably be a nice big curry from the Chinese. Bash
new video coming later on.
Yeah, have a few things to talk about. Hello my pain. [Music]
I went cinema.
Oh come out boxing day. Remind me.
Yeah. Remind me of that one.
[ __ ] hang over and [ __ ] man. Oh my should.
yesterday. I saw that one second. [ __ ]
Oh [ __ ] man.
I don't know. Oh, [ __ ]
Is that all these doors? Was
it 11 years?
Oh, I'm just having this beef curry.
It's absolutely lush.
Beef curry from the Chinese mushrooms.
Went to the pictures today.
rather a productive day for somebody that
is hung over as [ __ ] Nope.
Never. Cuz the thing is right with a dog
they stay with you forever.
They're good for your mental health.
They're good to be around. What the [ __ ]
Especially not a [ __ ] slag.
Dogs are loyal and they'll be loyal
forever. Women aren't. Women are [ __ ] [ __ ] Don't
What the [ __ ] They're lying,
cheating [ __ ] bastards.
What the [ __ ] bro? What the [ __ ]
Yeah. Where is he anyways?
What you people been up to today? Been
on YouTube all day?
You been on YouTube all day or Oh,
yeah. I went out sending it um
yesterday. Rip diesel and Yeah. Not
good, bro. Not good.
No replies back yet, but I mean I expect
it, you know. I expect it in this
country. It will never change.
I mean, I should be
more pissed off than I am. But at the
end of the day, it's never going to change. So,
it's the way it is, it like societyy's
not going to change but us. And that's
it. It will never change. I sent it
hard, bro. sober, tipsy, drunk. So, at
the end of the day, I didn't spend too
much money. I didn't stay home. So, I
tried to see like the positives. And
yeah, it's just it just gave me a
reminder how bad it is in this country.
I look sick as well, bro.
Look, I got my hair done as well, but
I've been out all day, so a bit sweaty. So, yeah, man.
I'm a bit tired, so don't mind that.
Baby Guinness, Sambuka, Guinness,
[ __ ] had loads of different drinks to be fair, you know,
not until next week or
two weeks or whatever, man. Probably ask.
There's no point, bro.
I'll probably go out next week to be
fair cuz I had my hair done but maybe not. Yeah,
that was my first time out in a month
cuz I was um just putting some money
aside for when I want to go out of that.
But um it's nice to be reminded how bad
it actually is here,
you know, like you know, even if we
didn't have a history of this [ __ ] and
we just went out yesterday and it's
first time going out doing it, that show
that tells you a lot. Like it tells you
a lot. And the only reason I'm bringing
it up is because the amount of numbers
we got. It's not like we got two or
three numbers. 10's a lot of [ __ ]
numbers. And at the end of the day,
right, you should have a date for next
week. Like, don't know where the date
will go. Who knows? But you should have
a date for next week. And I mean, if you
can't even get a date for next week,
says it all really in this country. I
mean, it says it all in it. Like, how it is.
It is [ __ ] up though. It is. It is
[ __ ] up. For whatever reason, you got
them 10 numbers. It is It is [ __ ]
It will never change. So,
but I want to do a video talking about
this, but I want to talk about something
else as well that's not related to dating.
Um, so you'll get to see it later. Not
with dating or women. It's just
generally something else. But
yeah, it's [ __ ] bro. It's [ __ ] I
talk about an escort thing and Yeah, bro. It's [ __ ]
But at least I tried in it. Can't say I didn't try.
And that's the main thing, you know.
If you can say you tried, then you tried in it.
Just come back from
eating this Chinese now. Going to make my bed,
do this video, and then go to bed. Thanks.
Yeah. But I I don't feel I know most
people would be human, but yeah,
it is [ __ ] up though. It is. It is
And I feel like any anyone that happened
to they would complain because it's
disgusting, bro. It's not two numbers.
It's not three numbers.
It's 10, which is which is quite a lot,
you know. Well, 10 numbers is madness.
They're all real numbers, too.
So, it looks like I won't have no luck
until I'm in my um 40s.
That's the way it seems. Until I'm in my
40s, I don't think we really have much
hope here. Well, we do in Thailand, but
you know, I was speaking to um [ __ ]
Izzy yesterday as well.
So, yeah, I need to do a video, bro, to
discuss some topics.
It's really [ __ ] though. It is really
It is [ __ ]
And like I said, like I said, it will
never change. So,
it is bad. It is bad. That
should have a date for next week.
But I guess like I said, it won't change
until we're what 40s maybe.
But obviously I get you go out to have
fun and we did have fun. We said it like
it was fun. But
you still should have
you still should have a date for next week.
You know what I'm saying? Like what?
No, I'm good, bro. I'm good.
And it makes me laugh when these women
say they they can't find someone that
they go on all of these dates, but none
of these guys are good enough for them.
And I can't even get a [ __ ] date. So
yeah, it is.
It is what it is.
But yeah, man. [ __ ]
We had some fun though. It was fun. [ __ ] Yeah,
we have some blue here too.
Oh, can't be a nice kind of coke with a curry.
Um, they're in the street, bars, pubs. I
didn't get any numbers from the street
though, to be fair. Um, they were just
in like Weather Spoons and [ __ ] clubs
But, um, yeah, I'm not not that pissed
off, bro. I mean, I could have done with
a date next week, but it is what it is, bro.
It's all good, man. I w going to be
doing anything anyways, but again, we
sure need to know how [ __ ] up it is. So,
it wasn't it wasn't a new video. I can
understand three numbers yet. Danger approached.
I don't [ __ ] know, bro. Six women,
seven women. No, they didn't block me.
No, they blocked me. They just didn't reply. Um
I can understand like you know if
sort of like you approached seven people
and you got three numbers and then
well no because I tried on the street.
That sounds like Jo by the way that
Jamie James account.
Um I did do on the street sober 10 times.
Um, so like I was saying, um, if you
done like six, if you done about seven
approaching and you got three numbers,
then okay, it's fair enough. It's only
three numbers. That's typical when you
go out, but 10 numbers is a lot, bro.
I mean, I looked hard yesterday, so it
tells you all you need to know about Nathan. Um,
I don't hard like I spent a lot of money
in that barbers, bro, cuz my skin was
kind of [ __ ] for my diet. So, I wanted
to look my best before going out. Um, it
is [ __ ] though, is it?
It is [ __ ] It is [ __ ]
Even if one of them replied and met, but no.
Which brings me to the point of how
people can be so optimistic.
You know what I'm saying? How they can
be so optimistic about it?
It's mad for anyone that would be mad.
Even if they didn't have a history like
me, even if they didn't have the same
history as me, it would still be mad.
That's crazy, bro. Anyone going out
doing that and they can't even get a
date is [ __ ] That is That is not normal, bro.
Don't let anyone else tell you that.
It's not normal.
That is not normal, bro.
cuz who else really could do that?
That's what you are think.
I was just saving money, building my
money up. So, I didn't really go out
much, but now I thought yesterday, might
as well, [ __ ] it. I don't want to stay in. But
who knows, who knows?
That's me done, I think,
until like I next week cuz I've already
got my hair done, but after that, I'll
be done for another six weeks.
That's why I don't I didn't feel
pressured to go out today drinking because
um because of um cuz obviously
um cuz obviously I tried enough so I'd
already got 10 numbers.
So I mean I didn't need to go out again but
obviously we still message them again in
a week or whatever see what what the
score is but
it don't look good. I had a bad feeling
to be honest with you. Um, I h I did
have a bad feeling to be fair. I don't
think any of them are really gonna get anywhere. But because
that's just how how it is, isn't it? But
like I said, I didn't expect it with 10
numbers. Three, four, you know, whatever.
But I I didn't think it would have been
like that with 10. What the [ __ ]
Oh yes, I'm going to do a video talk
about this [ __ ] Man,
it reminds me to be honest. Why don't
you go out much anymore about other things?
Good loves a try. E
that is mad. I know.
about from the cinema. one of them would
have would have replied.
So, I went cinema
which that's another thing I need to do
a video about the cinema as well, but
we'll add that in there as well.
They just [ __ ] bed. Cool.
Yeah. I'm never telling what I'm never
telling what [ __ ]
uh holidays I'm going on ever again. You
can get [ __ ]
I'm never doing that again.
You know, one one second.
Still calling me ugly when I'm a million
times better looking than him. Damn, he
really is insecure about his look. After
aditting it was a wind up. Never aditted
it was a wind up ever. Just like him in
Boston. But yes, big nose. Keep telling
yourself I went to some copy. You see?
No, you literally went to copy me. You
was you was copying me.
No, you literally went there because I
went there. It's not what I'm telling.
It's what I know. Because someone's
first holiday abroad would not be Amsterdam.
So I'm not telling myself. I'm telling
everyone how it is. That's what you
done. You went to copy me
and it's the way you went. It was your first holiday.
You're a copycat. You know
he's a little copycat. Little copycat.
He's a little copycat.
[ __ ] [ __ ] He went there cuz I went there.
And Amsterdam is not nice. You know,
like I was saying in my video, Eland is
a very nice place. Dutch people are
nice. Like, they really are nice people.
But the thing is is Amsterdam is not the
nowhere near any of the one of the
nicest places to go. You know, you got
Rotterdam, you got other places that
we're not even aware of.
You know what I'm saying? Like, bro,
Amsterdam is [ __ ]
He just went to Amsterdam cuz I went to Amsterdam.
Then he said, "I'm jealous, bro."
Jealous of what? Everything I'm doing,
you're doing like 10 years later that
I've already done. [ __ ] idiot. Um,
well, I need to train this [ __ ] bed now.
I think these people have reported me
somewhere, you know, so I can't get into
um a certain club. There's a certain
club I can't get into now.
I think one of these [ __ ] grass me up, bro.
Sure they did. Won't get into it, but
that's why I don't tell anyone what I
do, where I go. You know,
mate, I am [ __ ]
Excuse my French.
I already had a shower, so I don't need
another. I'm good, bro. Yeah, just
copy my holiday copycat.
It's a [ __ ] copycat.
See that people that thumbmed up my
video that they genuin
calling me ugly when I'm better looking than him.
Cuz the thing is right Steven Howard get
like get this. Yeah. He sits there and
tries to say that I'm ugly, but he's the
one that sits online obsessing and
stalking over me every day. But I'm the
ugly one. That really makes sense, does it?
Like you you're saying that [ __ ]
I'm ugly and all of these things. So why
are you obsessing stalking me every day?
just doesn't really make a lot of sense
to be fair. Well, my
>> Yeah, my [ __ ] ankles are hurt, bro.
Like my shins, you know, my shins.
[ __ ] Like, [ __ ]
My shins are actually [ __ ]
Oh jeez. It's not even a joke. Think
it's all that from all that walking and
approaching, bro. I'm going to add that
in the video as well. My actual shins,
my actual like ankles and my shins are
all hurt me from all the walking I've done.
But these people think that
one day you're going to go out and it's
all going to change.
Interesting. I could be that optimistic.
Wish I could be that optimistic, but I
mean it's not being not really being uh
realistic, is it? Oh,
in the bed with no bed, no money in it.
In the bed. Oh, what?
And I'm going to make myself hot
chocolate and do this video and take
some pills as well
cuz this is depressing. What we're going
to be talking about do a video, man.
Been on a video for ages.
I don't see as me complaining. I've got
a right to. I [ __ ] got 10 numbers
yesterday. [ __ ] sake. Unless one of them
replies in the morning, but I don't
think so. I to be honest, like I said, I
don't know why I had a bad feeling about
it, but I just did.
I did have a bad feeling to be fair. Um,
one second. Let me do this [ __ ]
skin in a bed. [ __ ] with no money and no
bed in it.
It's just it's just catchy saying that's all.
So only catchy sayings
in the bed sit with no bed. No money in it.
Just getting the bed with no money in
it. Can't stop saying that, bro. What's wrong?
It's addicting as [ __ ]
I'm saying it.
Get in the bed. Nobody
game is [ __ ] now. relating gamers. But actually,
I'm talking about the country as well.
But the reason why it didn't like
piss me off as such is cuz at the end of
the day, I'm young. I've got money. I
can make money. You know, we know what
they're like in this country. It's nothing to
really It's It's shocking. It's It's more shocking,
but at the same time, like
it's bad that I kind of expected it cuz
it is it is shocking though. That's a
word to uh
um to um
to say. Okay, one second.
Who do you think's more intelligent, me
or Virgin boy?
Me definitely, bro.
I'm far more intelligent.
I'm far more intelligent than the virgin.
Yeah, I'm far more intelligent than the virgin.
The skin virgin. Yeah.
Do you know what it is? Let me tell you
what it is. I've I've I've found out
what the problem is.
When he's ugly himself,
he has to come on YouTube every single
day trying to call me ugly to make
himself feel better about the fact that he's ugly.
He's insecure and he's in a he's not
happy in the relationship that he's in.
I mean, bro,
that's why he does
all of this bollocks.
I might start putting this stuff in the
in the drawing.
Doesn't look good, does it?
>> Hey, Ghosting. I got a story to tell you, lad.
I don't know if you want to hear it or not. Um,
I suspect you probably do.
You want to hear it or
one sec? So, I went out yesterday. Um
Oh, got some change here. Um went out
yesterday, right? First time in a month
cuz I thought, "Fuck it. Why not? Why
not give it a try?" And I hadn't been
out for a month cuz I just wanted to
save money and not waste it. Didn't want
to deal with the [ __ ] what you
went out, bro. And I [ __ ] sent it,
brother. I got 10 numbers. I got 10
and none of them replied back.
Yeah, I know. Crazy, isn't it? And then
I went to the cinema today and now I'm
back. So, I didn't do bad for a very
hung over person. But yeah, I got 10
numbers, bro. And nothing.
No thanks at all.
It's crazy, bro. Is it?
Not a single reply, bro.
Not a single reply.
And I've done a lot of approaches. So, I
even recorded one and they just weren't
interested. Some just walked away. Some said no.
One said they had a boyfriend.
Um, I didn't think I was going to get 10
numbers to be fair. But this is why Ghosted,
we think that this [ __ ] is never going to change
because of this. Do you understand, bro?
Like, I'm not saying like, "Oh, yeah, I
want to have sex. I want to do this. I
want to do that. I had fun yesterday.
The whole point was was having fun." But
at at the same time, bro, I should still
have a date for next week. You
understand? Cuz obviously I tried a lot.
I got 10 numbers for [ __ ] sake. What
more was I supposed to do? I looks
smacked everything. So, at the end of
the day, bro, like the thing is is that
it's not like you got three numbers out
of seven approaches and they just didn't
reply or played games or whatever. You
literally got 10 [ __ ] numbers.
So, I mean, it's
it doesn't look good, does it? You
understand? It doesn't look good, mate.
Even if, like I said, you you have no
history and someone just went out and
done that. That is insane, bro. I look
sick yesterday. You missed it, bro. I
had my hair done. I got my haircut, by
the way, bro. I was looking fresh. Got
my skin done. Went to the barbers.
Like, proper looks, Max, bro. I'm a bit
hung over to be fair now, so I was a bit
tired. But, bro, you won't even know. It
was bad, bro.
But yeah, it's just
how it's always going to be here, is it? I guess. So,
but the way I see it is ghosting is like
I was going to be staying in anyways. I
didn't spend that much money
and you know it's and then I had a
problem with the escal as well. Oh,
Jesus Christ. I don't want to talk about
this on a video. So,
um I'm not going to give away the title
cuz I got a banging title for it. But
yeah, this is why people feel the way
they do though. Ghosting. Me, I'm used
to it now. I don't give a [ __ ] But you know, um
that's why No, they didn't block. They
just they just haven't replied. No, they didn't block.
No, they just haven't replied to be fair.
They blocked to be fair. They just didn't reply,
which I thought that would happen to be.
I don't know why. I just had this bad feeling. Um
to be fair, bro.
Oh, they didn't block me, you know.
Yeah, of course they would. That's
that's that's what it's like ghosting,
bro. That's that's how it is, isn't it?
But at the end of the day, like
societyy's not changing for me or you.
That's the thing you got to understand.
Like it is it is it's more than [ __ ]
up. Like 10 like 10 numbers is [ __ ]
But like the thing is society is not
going to change for me and you
know what I'm saying but like it's not
about them anymore. It's about us. Well
me and you know that like and it's been
the same old for years. I mean I know it
sounds mad but I kind of expected it
bro. Does that sound bad? I kind of did.
Like what else would I expect? I'm not
new to this [ __ ] bro.
I was I was using some good pickup lines, too.
Um but yeah.
but we're not only going to be talking
about that in the video. We'll talk
about other things. Yeah, they didn't um
they didn't block me. They just didn't
reply to be fair.
Yeah. Well, it's happened before. It's
happened before. I've got eight numbers
and they haven't replied.
They were good approaches as well, bro.
I was really confident, too. I've done a
lot of them sober. I didn't get any
numbers sober, though.
>> Yeah, but at the end of the day, bro,
I was expecting it to be honest with
you. We're talking about England, bro.
Like, I was expecting this [ __ ]
Yeah, I look sick, bro. I'll show you
what I was dressed as. Hold up.
I'll show you.
So, I'm pulling a face cuz
um I've had to screenshot, but you'll
get the you get the you get the gist. Anyways,
um I was wearing this.
This was me yesterday, bro. I look sick.
Yeah, that was me, bro. Turtleneck, blazer.
Yeah, bro. Got stuff on my skin. Looks
maxed the [ __ ] No difference.
I had like £50 right on the side. I was
like, "Fuck it. Just give the 50 to the
barber. Get the full service. Ain't been
out for a month." And yeah, made no difference.
So, it is what it is, bro. But I was I
was expecting it. You might have not
been expecting it, but I was expecting
it to be fair.
Um, but yeah.
Yeah, I look sick. I smelt good as well,
bro. All my clothes were clean and
everything. There's a lot more I could
have done than what I already done. I
was surprised I was confident to be
honest, but I was I was [ __ ] myself
the first one I done cuz I had done it
for a month. But after that, I was just
a natural again.
And yeah, it made absolutely no difference.
But now, you see, if you voice this opinion
um ghosting, people will say that you're
negative. You understand? And this is
how it goes round and round in circles.
It's because what can they blame? They
can't blame my looks. They can't blame
what I smell like. They can't blame my
approach cuz my approach was good. I'll
send it to you on Snapchat if you want.
I recorded one of them. The text
messages was good. So, I mean, there's
nothing they can really blame.
I was straight out of the barbers, bro.
I'm saying I went on the session. So, I
mean, but like I said, if you was to
voice that, they would say that you're negative.
So that's why it's just
what what do you say? What do you do,
bro? You know what I'm saying? Like,
and the thing is, I don't think we go
out ghosting because we've got hope. I
feel like we go out cuz there's nothing
else to do. I was bothered just staying
in. So, I thought after a month, let me
go out um because there is nothing else
to do. I don't even think we go out
because we have hope. Um,
so yeah, but yeah, it is what it is.
That's why I don't really go out much
anymore. And it's not even just the
women. It's the other things as well
that happened and today as well.
Yeah. That they have no life ghosting.
None of them has got a life. None of
them have got a life. They're all sat on
YouTube skin every single day. Hey, they
ain't got no life.
You know, I was out drinking yesterday
live, bro, with my friend, but he wasn't
on here. Yeah, they ain't got a life.
It's just like that nonsleg. He's
jealous of me, bro.
Says that I'm ugly and all of this, yet
you you're obsessing over me all day,
every day, bro. Make it make sense. But
I'm the jealous one, yet you're the one
that's got a channel dedicated to stalking me.
Doesn't make any sense. Did I go
gambling yesterday? Well, considering I
don't gamble, no.
Well, I don't gamble, so no.
Nope. Didn't do any football bets. Um, I
don't need to win money. I've got enough
money and I'd rather stable income.
So, nah, didn't do any, bro.
No, I'm I'm good.
Yeah, I was having some good
conversations with them. It's a shame that uh
none of them reply back or whatever.
What's your opinion on it, Ghosted? Do
you think it will ever change? I don't
think it would ever change cuz of how
long it's been going on for and
you know what happens when you go out
and [ __ ] I don't think it will ever change. Nah.
Yeah, there were repeaters. That's why I
don't go on there anymore. They're just self projectors.
People on this channel don't tend to go
on there because they're just self projectors, lad.
It's like I had virgin boy by the
bollock. Hold on a minute. I'm saying
you're a virgin. You're saying I'm a
Well, where is that woman then? Because
we've been approaching for years. So if
all it takes is one woman, where is she?
Cuz we've approached, we put ourel out
there, we put the effort in. So I mean,
I'm sure you would have found that
someone in 5 years.
I mean, is that not logical? What I'm saying?
I mean, yeah, it takes one, but that's
like saying it takes one number to win the lottery.
That doesn't really narrow it down
without being a dick, to be fair. So,
I mean, they're all exactly the same.
They have the same attitude. They do the
same stuff. They say the same stuff as
you know. So, I mean,
I'm sure they told me that four or five
years ago as well that all it takes is
one woman, but here we are.
Take a break, bro. This is my first time
out in a month.
I mean, I don't know, man. I'm I'm a big
believer in there's not someone for
everyone generally. I don't think there
is someone for everyone. I don't believe
that. Especially now with like social
media and [ __ ] um Tik Tok and whatever, but
I mean I stopped for a month.
So I mean that's a long time to have not
went out drinking. So I mean I already
took a break from it and I come back and
it's just the same old [ __ ] again.
And then I had an escort that tried to
scam me. So you just
you can never go out. I'm going to save
this for the video later. Um yeah,
and it's just not it's not only just
going to be about women, it's going to
be other stuff as well. But if there was
that one woman, you would have found her
by now. 100%.
Like it's just obvious.
Like take yesterday for example. You
know, you ain't even got a date next
next week. I mean, date a date is the
first step. And you ain't even got a
date next week. It doesn't look good,
does it? It does not look good. If you
can't even get a [ __ ] date for next
week, despite approaching all them
women, I'm not a believer, bro. I can't
say I'm sold, lad.
You don't have a bird.
It's really really bad.
But I I just find it funny how people
think one day it's going to change.
That's madness, bro. That they think one
day you're going to go out and it's just
going to change.
I I don't know if they're lying to
themselves or whatever
because again, it would have happened by
now. Four years is a long time. Four or
five years is a long time. If you was
going to meet somebody, you already you
would have already met someone by now.
It's the truth.
Like it's what else is there to to say?
So you would have already found someone.
That's the way I look at it. 4 years is
a long ass time.
[ __ ] that is a long time, bro, to be
out not working, approaching and [ __ ] Sir, it's mad.
I [ __ ] found someone by now.
so many stuck up women in this country, bro.
That virgin boy is a virgin. Um,
you know, I'm saying you're virgin
because we've never seen you have sex.
We've actually seen
me have sex. So, I mean, there's no
evidence that you've had sex. There's
evidence that I've had sex. So, how can
I be the virgin when I've proved I've
had sex and you haven't?
It doesn't make any sense. There's no
proof that you've had sex
at all. There's proof that I've had sex.
As immature as it sounds, it's what it
is. My two thumbs up are [ __ ]
genuine, bro. You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, man. So,
we're going for a roast tomorrow. No, I
need to save money, bro. I'll probably
get a joint of pork to be fair. Nah, I'm
I'm saving money. I'm leaving soon, bro.
Nah, just the same old [ __ ] People not
interested. Got a lot of numbers. They
didn't reply back. But just England, is
it? It will never change. I need to do a
video later as well. And it's not just
about women, it's about other things as
well. Almost being scammed by an escort
today. It's just different things as
well. We need to we need to um
I feel like honestly Yeah, this is a
troll country. I've got a banging title
for this video. Yeah, but you know,
he hasn't never He's never had sex. He
has never had sex ever. So, I just read
that. No, he has never had sex. I don't
care if he's in a relationship or he's
not in a relationship. He's never had sex.
And no one's going to tell me otherwise.
At the end of the day, I've proved I've
had sex. So, you know, you've seen it.
So, at the end of the day, he definitely
definitely definitely had hasn't had
sex. Um, which you say it's weird,
right? Because he's in a relationship,
but think about what he does on YouTube
every day trying to call me ugly when
I'm a million times better looking than
him. Calls me skinn. Yeah, I've got more
money than him. [ __ ] talks about my
clothes when I've got better clothes
than him. It seems like it's a bit like
what Pat used to do. It very much seems
like another Pat Mustard.
I know that might sound strange, but do
you remember what he used to do?
Do you remember what he used to do?
Um, you know, self-project and it turned
out that he was very unhappy in life.
That's the same as Virgin Boy
cuz somebody must be unhappy to do this
every single day. I'm not [ __ ]
obsessed with you, you [ __ ] ugly bastard. You know,
you're [ __ ] obsessed with me. You've
got a channel dedicated to me and
stalking me. Why am I jealous of you
doing things I've already done 10 years
before you? What the [ __ ] It doesn't
make sense. So, Pat Mustard used to do a
similar thing to this. So,
oh, I need to check the scores as well.
Jesus. What? The Premier League.
Five both teams have scored in a row
and four of them was both score no draw. Damn.
[ __ ] wish I had money on that.
A fleet would cold. Oh, damn. Same, bro.
I was going to do Darlington and slow as
well for [ __ ] sake. I was going to put
120 on that today, but I never
bastarded. They [ __ ] scored as well.
Please don't tell me that was a both
score, no draw, though. Was it?
I was going to do them two as well, bastard. You know,
the thing is, Ghost, I don't want to
really be gambling anymore, bro.
I don't really like gambling to be
honest with you, mate.
You know, I only gambled last month cuz
I was a bit um not low on money, but I
wanted a bit more money. I'm not really
like wanting to do that anymore, bro, to
be fair with you.
Like, it's not stable income. I need a
That's not a st like 1020 pound
obviously that's different like yeah
that's different obviously like 10 20 or
100 like every now and every week or
whatever like 100 a month okay yeah
that's different but I mean like it's not really
you know I should have put 120 on them
two teams you know last month but I
needed to win the extra money.
Yep. I know I looked smart last night
and I got absolutely [ __ ] all. Absolutely nothing.
Well, it's got 10 numbers, but none of them replied.
I mean, [ __ ] me. It is really impossible
in this country, in it, bro. Trying to date.
But yeah, obviously you probably you
probably bet like 10 20 pound, don't you? Um,
I don't know. I think I spent like £200
to be fair.
Yeah, I think I spent about 200.
Creeps up in it. But you probably only
do 20 a week in it. So
yeah, it was a good night. But it just
reminds me how impossible it is to get a
woman in this country.
Yeah, it's bad, is it? It is [ __ ] It
is really bad.
That's why I don't really try much
anymore. Ghosting. Like I said, that was
my first time out in a month because um there's like
I don't know, bro. You couldn't do that
[ __ ] every day, every other day, whatever.
And then I had a problem with the escort
as well. Oh my god. Long story, bro. I
was about to smash the windows in. It's
like it can never be normal, can it? You
can never just go out in this country
and it be normal. I'm going to do a
video on this as well. We're going to
talk about that as well. We're not just
talking about dating. But you can't just
go out and things just be normal. I'm
saying it's not a normal country.
It's a [ __ ] country.
I always used to be like [ __ ]
depressed. This country puts me in a bad
mood, bro, sometimes,
you know? It puts you in a bad [ __ ]
mood, don't it? I don't know about you, but
yeah, he didn't do any approaches. He
was scared. Even though I spent £40 on [ __ ] rounds,
he didn't um
he wasn't um on it. So So
he can't complain. I can actually
complain if I got 10 numbers and none of
them's going to meet me, whatever. So,
um, at the end of the day, that's how it is.
>> It's [ __ ] up, is it, bro? Why
I don't know what the problem is. I
don't know if it's because they're rich
or they come from a rich family and they
think they're better than everyone. I
don't know what the problem is. I wish I
would would know what the problem
actually is, but
I don't know, bro. I I generally just think that
I don't know, bro. I don't know what the problem is.
I don't know what the problem is, but
it's not normal.
Yeah, he is a fantasist.
Just like Virgin Boy is a fantasist.
thinking he's got money when he ain't got nothing.
>> Yeah, they're all fantasists.
They sit on YouTube all day every day
cuz they ain't got a life.
>> Yeah, but it's not about that though cuz
I want to actually meet someone. So,
but still [ __ ] up.
It's still [ __ ] up though. Like
whether you had a good night or you
didn't, it's still really [ __ ] up cuz
it tells you all you need to know, is it really?
Then I tried getting an escort and then
she tried scamming me and then I almost
got into a fight and it's just things
that never needed to happen.
Why can't you just go out and it be normal?
You know what I'm saying? Like
Why can't you just go out and it just be
normal for a change?
Maybe one day. Eh,
and at the cinema today, I had problems as well. Yeah,
it's [ __ ] up, man.
Come tomorrow to what? Sidemen Sunday.
Well, I got an escort Jane and I was
like, "Oh, can I um Yeah, I want a blowjob."
So, I gave her £100 cuz I like to
obviously come in her mouth, right? And
she was like, "Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah."
And then while she was sucking my dick,
she was like, "Oh, yeah. You can't come
in my mouth." I was like, "What?
We agreed on we we made we made a deal."
And then she was like, "No, no, no." I
was like, "No, give me half my money
back then." Cuz she'd already sucked my
dick, sucked my balls, sucking her tits
and [ __ ] I was like, "No." And then and
then it's like, "Oh, a girl's got a
different price." I said, "No, they do
not." So I said, "I've been here before
there. I know how it works. I know the
prices. Trust me. I've been doing Escort
for a very long time. A very, very long
time, mate. Probably more than anyone my
age ever has. Not that it's anything to
be proud of, but it is what it is. And
he was trying to say, "Oh, yeah, you
need to leave." I said, "No, I want half
I want half my money back." And I
weren't going to sit there and argue,
right? And I said, "Listen, if you don't
if you don't give it, I'm going to do
your windows in."
So, like, there was people upstairs that
lived above. Um, and they were like,
"Oh, like it's not it's not worth it for
the sake of £100." I was like, "Bro, I'm
going to smash your windows in if you do
not give me half this money back." And
then all of a sudden, I was going around
like kebab shops and that saying, "Oh,
have you got a hammer?" I was going to
do the windows in. Bro, don't take the
piss out of me. It's not about the
money. Just don't take the piss out of
me. I don't care if they're dangerous or
not. You're not taking the piss out of me.
Simple. That's it. I don't give a [ __ ]
if they're dangerous or not. They don't
know me, bro. So, if I d the windows in,
they don't know me. I don't live there.
So, I don't care how dangerous they are,
bro. I don't give a [ __ ] Don't try and
take the piss out of me.
Yeah. Let them have guns, bro. Then they
kill me. Then I die in it, bro. What?
What is it, bro? Like, at the end of the
day, that's it in it.
Well, he didn't. And he gave me half my
money back, so which is what I asked
for. He wouldn't have, bro. I would have
smashed the windows in.
Even if I had to win the cowardly way, I
would have won the cowardly way. So,
they gave half my money back anyway. So,
I saved money in the end.
Well, he obviously didn't because you
come out given half the money back like I demanded
like trying to [ __ ] scam people. So,
that's why I'm saying you can never go
out in this country, Jane, and just
something be normal for one day.
You just can't have anything normal for
one day. You try to work, you deal with
[ __ ] You try and go cinema, I'm
going to tell you what happened today.
Went to do it to do with people. You
can't ever go out and it just be normal.
Like just, oh yeah, it was smooth. It
can never be like that.
You know what I'm saying? There's always
got to be hiccups, whatever you do. Um,
and that's going to be the title of the
video. You can't do anything without
there being hiccups. This is what I'm
trying to say.
So, but yeah, if he would have shoot I
just I just said at first I said like if
you don't get back I'm just going to
call the police and it and then we're
both going to get [ __ ] and I said then
I said oh well I don't know which way to
go. Then I said okay I'm going to do the
windows and and the people upstairs were
getting scared and that in it like they
had nothing to do with it and that and I
was like bro don't take the [ __ ] piss
out of me bro. Then I hurt my foot as
well. I've hurt my feet by the I think I
walk too much.
I don't like how like people think they
can take the piss and it's a shame
because there were nice escorts out
there but they're very they're very hard to find
you know so but there are they are out
there you pay money
and um you know they give you a service
for whatever reason it is but they were
trying to scam me
like someone's gave you £100 they've
we've made a deal then you give them a
[ __ ] Simple. Like it's what the [ __ ]
is all of this coming in your [ __ ]
mouth and [ __ ] It's what the [ __ ] It's
only come. Do you know what I'm saying?
It's just It's always got to be some
dickheadness about it, bro. It's [ __ ]
That's why I enjoy just like my breaking
that, bro. To be fair.
Nothing can be normal.
You know what I'm saying? Like,
well, if you're into [ __ ] the way I
am, you you'd pay it. So I used to just
give this 19year-old £50. She used to
just suck my dick and sw. So £50 a
bargain to be fair. But um yeah,
don't know why they tried scamming me, bro.
>> You're [ __ ] with the wrong person.
And it's not everyone's got their prices
because a walking escort does not charge
£100 for a [ __ ] where you finish yourself.
There's not one woman that does that. So
like, are you going to tell me I'm
wrong? You know, I've been probably I've
been doing these escorts longer than
you've been in the business. So
why don't you go back to LJ's channel,
you little ass licker doggy. You're one
of LJ's little minions. Why don't you go
back to his channel and stop ruining the
vibe on our channel
the vibe on our channel.
So, we're trying to create a [ __ ]
atmosphere on our channel,
you know, going back to your [ __ ] Lord J.
So, yeah, that's it, bro. So, so I've
been doing it since I was 17. So, that's
11 years I've been I've been uh doing
this [ __ ] now longer than you probably
been in the business.
So, that's it. Normally what happens is
they charge you 60 70 for a [ __ ] and
it's extra 30 to come in their mouth.
That's what it is, you know? So I know
how this [ __ ] works.
So I've done it a million times, bro.
Like what the [ __ ] But yeah,
can't even get a date in this country. Hey, Jane.
Yeah, you get all of these women that
get dates with these men, but then they
complain they can't find someone.
Strange, isn't it? But then they
complain about [ __ ] men when they're
the ones that are getting these dates.
You see, I actually made an example to
be fair cuz I said if you go out every
week, you won't even get a date. and
I've done 10 I got 10 numbers. So that's
probably a month's worth of numbers and
I don't have a date.
So I mean that's I mean that tells you
all you you need to know about trying to
date in this country as a man. The fact
that you don't even you don't even have
a date. That's [ __ ] bro. Not
[ __ ] up here,
but that's the way it is.
I'm going to make a noise outside.
Be nice if you could just find a woman
that was a normal AJ.
It's nice if you could just find a woman
that was Oh, my [ __ ] my actual ankles
are hurting me, bro. Ow.
It's my feet. It's my feet and my shins
and my ankles.
painful man. Must have done a lot of walking
and I don't even have a single day.
So yeah, like I said, that's a month's
worth of numbers. That's a month's worth
of trying and not a sausage. Not even a date.
It's funny, man. I need to try and do
this video before I go to sleep. I'm [ __ ] tired.
Do you remember when you wanted to suck
my Willie Jane?
Yeah. You wanted to suck my Why would he
will before, didn't you, Jane? Yeah.
You can't go to work and have a peaceful
day. You can't do anything
in this country. It's just it's just not
a normal country, you know? That's what it is.
Jane wanted to suck my willy the [ __ ]
Didn't you Jane?
Oh, my little nest. Jane.
Oh, I'm so tired. Look how good looking
Peter Billy is compared to N legs.
Look at my skin.
You like my little skin? It's quite
nice, isn't it?
Look at that, bro. Oh, what? Jesus Christ.
Why does my whole [ __ ] leg hurt, man?
But apparently I'm ugly, Jane.
Says the virgin.
I'm the ugly one, apparently. Mate,
look. You can see how nice my skin is. Look.
Look at my skin. I got my skin done
professionally by the barbers. Look, you understand?
Look at that, Stephen Howard. You see
how my skin was a bit [ __ ] See how
nice? Look at Look how Look how clean it
is. See, you still can't even get a
date. It's a [ __ ] madness, bro.
My skin is nice, man.
Jay, let me ask you an honest question, right?
What would you rate The Virgin out of 10?
Be be honest.
You know, you can you we can rate things
and stuff and whatever. What would you
actually rate The Virgin out of 10?
Yep. Always wash my teeth, bro. Goggled
my my um
mouth with salt water.
I've actually got teeth. I'm like virgin boy.
You have to be honest. Tell us like
Oh, my [ __ ] leg, my ankles, man, are
hurting me. That's why I'm in my little bed.
I'm going to sleep next to Scooby-Doo.
I like Scooby.
So, what do you rate um
uh Nons legs?
Look at my cute little face. I'm so cute.
Why do you think USA is you liked me?
because I was cute.
A cute little dumpling. I'm saying
look at my beard. Not one patch on my
Yeah, the virgin is nons legs. Um, Jane,
look. Ghosting. Yeah,
I'm I'm not I'm a decent looking [ __ ] Me
in it, bro. Be honest. I'm a decent
looking bastard, bro. Look. Look. Yeah.
No homo. Yeah. I'm not perfect. I'm no
model. Yeah. I got nice hair.
Nice beard, cute eyes, good skin. Got my
skin done. They talk about my
appearance, bro, but I'm better looking
than them, bro. Oh, man. It hurts. They
talk about me, bro, but I'm better
looking than them. It's [ __ ]
I'm not scared to show my face like
these people are, bro.
It's so weird.
I made loads of new friends.
Yeah, man. I've also made loads of new friends. Nah,
I'm not putting on weight at all. I'm
actually losing weight. I'm not putting
on weight at all at all. I'm going gym soon anyways. So,
I'll be going gym soon anyways. So, I
want I just want to go gym. I want to
build my my body up. So,
um No, I'm not putting on weight.
I walked yesterday ghosting about
I walked on the station to the house
which was about 25 minutes, bro.
in shoes. In [ __ ] shoes cuz the bus
stopped running. Imagine that, bro. A
long walking shoes. Oh, bro. No wonder
my feet are killing me.
They feel like strange, strenuous.
You know what I'm saying?
It was East London.
Strapford where I used to live. Nah, it
was where I used to live. Near where I
used to live. 5 minutes away for from
where I used to live, lad. So,
and I don't give a [ __ ] I would have died.
I would have died yesterday, bro. If I
had to die yesterday, I would have died.
Like, I'm not having someone take the
piss out of me, bro. Like, it's principle.
You know what I'm saying? We already
have to deal with these shitty women in
this country and their stupid [ __ ] that they do.
And then what? We're going to get ripped
off. Like, no, bro. Like, you you you
know what I mean?
Like, we're not I'm not having that, bro. So, that's it.
So, it looks like I won't be back there
for a couple of months.
Uh, she was all right. Yeah,
that's what I'm saying. There's always hiccups.
It can't just be a normal country.
Yeah, I I I've been to a lot of them,
bro. I've done so many escorts. I think
I'm at like 200, you know. I don't I
don't know. I don't know. I don't know
if I don't know
about 200, but I know I've done a lot.
I don't know.
I've done more than any anyone my age.
No, they just stop. Yeah, just stop my
dick and whatever. Yeah. Kiss you. [Music]
Yeah, man. I'm [ __ ] hung over, too.
You like the fade? Cost me a lot of money, bro.
Cost me a lot of Wonga.
But yeah, before I test out the dating
game, cuz it's been a while.
And that's where we're at. Nah,
he just started getting a bit aggy and
that I said no. And they said, "Well,
okay. If you're not going to give the
money back, then I'm just going to do
the windows in."
So that's it.
It's mad, isn't it, bro? It's mad.
That shouldn't have happened, bro. We
made a deal, you know? Like, somebody
could have got really hurt yesterday.
You know what I mean? Ghosting.
And this is all from just going out and
wanting to use a service. Do you
understand? This is what I mean. In this
country, it's like a troll country. It
should have like a troll face as a flag. Yes,
I love [ __ ] I've paid even more
before. I've paid £200 before just for a
[ __ ] and them to swallow it. Yep.
When I used to have the house, I used to
spend a lot of money on escorts.
Yeah, I have, mate.
I paid £250 for a [ __ ] in the in the toilet before.
No, I was screaming outside the house.
I said, "Give the money. Give the money.
Give the money." I said, "Okay, well, if
you're not going to give me the money,
I'm just going to do the [ __ ] I'm
just going to do the windows in." And he
come out. Everyone heard.
So then he come out and then gave half
the money back. So fair enough. Good.
I don't know why it had to come to that.
We made a deal. That was the deal.
There's never been a problem before. You
either do it or you don't do it. And
then we move on. It doesn't ever get to
that point. We We had a deal, you know. So,
no, I went to a kebab shop asking if
they had a hammer cuz I was trying to
look for a brick like to do the windows in.
Um, and I couldn't find one. So, then I
went to the shop
Yeah, but I don't need to record stuff,
bro. For what? For who? For who? And
For what? Who? To these [ __ ] that
what? I'm not scared of people. I don't
need to do that, bro.
Why? Why do I need their validation? I
went live yesterday in the pub cuz it
was funny as [ __ ] I just want to see
what people would say. But I mean, I've
got approach of videos on my other
channel. I uploaded one yesterday. I
don't put it on this channel. I've got a
whole different channel with different
things on it.
So, I don't need to record stuff
to prove I'm not scared of people.
Oh, can I hear that?
So, I couldn't I was looking for like a
brick or a stone, but I couldn't.
Like it's um
I couldn't find a brick or a [ __ ] stone.
I see some guy like you got a hammer,
brother. I'll give you some money if you
give me a hammer.
I was going to do it LT style.
Yeah, that shouldn't have come to that.
I mean, I don't understand what the
problem was. You got given money for service.
The country stinks. It really does stink.
I don't know. I don't go on his channel
anymore. He's a loser.
I let them look the obsessed ones. I let
them um look the obsessed jealous ones.
Nons red star. They're obsessed and
jealous. I just let them do what they
got to do, bro. They're just obsessed,
jealous losers. They ain't got a life,
so I just leave them to it, bro. Cuz at
the end of the day, it shows them to be
the jealous ones. I only replied because
I just said to non legs that you just
copied my holiday because you did.
You're a copycat. Cuz you are a copycat.
You got no mind of your own.
No mind of your own whatsoever. So the
more they do this, the more they showed
them up to be the jealous ones.
So yeah, just let them show themselves
up and show how jealous they are. We
don't need to [ __ ] look on their channel.
They will never stop. Year in year out
they'll do this.
It's [ __ ] it, bro.
They ain't got a life.
You know these people on here ghosting
ain't got a life. Like when I was in the
pub yesterday, you just saw the amount
of people that joined. They ain't got a
life, bro. They just sit on here waiting for content.
You know what I mean?
Cuz you know the thing is um ghosting.
Yeah. Like let me just say this like
there's no reason for them to really dislike me
if you think about it. You know other
than the fact I'm better looking than
them and younger than them. But you know
there's there if you actually think bro
there's not an actual
reason if you think I mean yeah you've
said stuff in the past but they wanted
that reaction they wanted you to react
and then you reacted and what they use
it against you so it's like they don't
really have any real reason to dislike
you. I mean they don't even know you
but yet they want every day stalking you
and harassing you and they don't even
know you. And then when when we say that it's jealousy,
oh, they go on the high [ __ ] "Oh,
we're not jealous. We're not jealous."
But it's like, well, you clearly are
jealous of something cuz
Yeah. Well, that's good to be. That's
all I'm saying, bro. Is it? So,
cuz there's no reason
ghosting because if you see, they only
go for me. They don't go for anyone else.
Do you understand?
So, which is strange.
But anyway, just leave the two. They're losers. Yeah.
It is what it is. Hey, bro. Hey. Hey. Oh,
well, I'm gone, bro. I'll be back
tomorrow, maybe. Yeah,
I'm do this video and yeah, man. In a bit.