[ __ ] me. [Music]
There we go.
You never guess what I've got cooking in
a good old oven. Can't wait.
It's what you need, mate. after the
session that I I had mate. I ice dinner. You know,
I actually feel [ __ ] today. Felt all
right yesterday, but I feel [ __ ] today.
The drinking makes you tired, I guess.
Yep. The drinking makes you tired.
[ __ ] me, bro. It's weird. Sometimes you
feel worse the day after than you
actually do the second day. The day
after the second day.
Yep. You are on YouTube again. And we'll
help you with that. We'll ban you.
You're on YouTube every day. Get the
[ __ ] out of here, [ __ ] This is
my first time on YouTube the whole day.
I've already been off of YouTube for
weeks and you people can't take a day
off of YouTube. So, yeah, don't don't
self-reflect on my channel.
Um, this is not a channel for
self-reflectors. Uh, this is a channel
where people just walk and stuff. And yeah,
we don't have self-reflectors on this
channel, buddy. You can go on LJ's for that.
I mean, I'm chilling. It's Sunday. I'm
[ __ ] hung over as [ __ ] I mean, what
else am I going to be doing? I'm lying
in bed playing GTA. I physically can't do anything.
Tired as [ __ ] bro.
No, I got 10 numbers. None of them
replied back. Like I said, nope. No.
I know it's might sound surprising to
you, but nah, I didn't get [ __ ] all. I
got 10 numbers and they didn't reply,
but didn't follow up with them at some point.
Oh my god, I'm so lagging.
I got a leg of lamb grezy. It cost me £36
and it's uh it's cooking bacon. So,
yeah, why not? I was going to get either
I was going to get beef. No, I wasn't
going to get pork. I was going to get
beef, but then the lamb just looked so
much better. So, I just got the lamb. Doesn't
matter about buddy, mate. What you
fancy, you fancy.
No, I know how to speak to women, mate.
I'm confident. It's them being stuck up
in this country. That's the problem. I
don't need to change the way I speak. I
speak completely fine. I've got You
haven't seen me approach
for a long time. I've got approaches on
my channel. No, my approaches are
completely fine. My texts are completely
fine. It's the fact that they're just stuck up.
Um, that's what it is. And that's why I
agree with you. I went out on Friday,
bro, cuz I hadn't been out for a month.
And it was something to do better than
nothing, you know. So, it is it is what
it is. I'm under no illusion that one
day you're going to go out and it's
going to change. It's never going to
change, but at the same time, you know,
I wanted to go out for a drink.
So, my approach is on fire, bro. Greezy.
I went out Friday. They had on 10
approach to sober. I was using pickup
lines and everything. They just weren't
interested. Just like they never will be
in this country, but I mean I just
wanted to go out. So
yeah, man. I'm just tired. Going to wait
for this roast dinner and probably go
sleep to be honest.
Yep. He's been my friend for a couple of years.
We met in O'Neal's. He's been out on my
birthday. We done New Year's together.
You know, I know he's from another
country, but who cares? You know,
a friend's a friend in it. So, at the
end of the day, bro, why not? Why the [ __ ] not?
Someone better than no one in it. So, yeah.
I don't need to I don't need to change
the way I speak to women. I speak
completely fine, mate. People couldn't
believe what I was doing. They, "Oh, I
wish I could go and speak to someone."
They were saying, "Oh, it annoys me."
They couldn't do it with me. I don't
give a [ __ ] I'll talk to any [ __ ] I
don't care, bro. I don't give a [ __ ]
So, um, no, I don't need to change the
way of anything. It's just they're stuck
up. They're not interested, which we
know this anyways. But grievy, did you
watch my um video
about the hiccups in this country?
Not even talking about women like
hiccups. It's so true, isn't it? I went
to the cinema, I swear to God. Yeah.
Yesterday to watch the new Strangers
film, bro. I had to wait like 15 minutes
for them to change the [ __ ] um drink
machine because it was pissing out water
and the [ __ ] picker mix was [ __ ]
smaller than it was last time I went.
It's like there's always hiccups in this
country. You can't just go out and just
have a normal day. You can't go to work
and have a normal day at day of work.
You know what I'm saying? There's
nothing normal in this country.
So, did you like the copycat one that
you can never do anything in this
country without there being hiccups?
You go on a bus. I went on a bus
uh couple of weeks ago. I was with my
mom and this old guy tried starting. I
told him about himself. Then he shut up
trying to get in people's like business
and [ __ ] or like you might go to work or
you go cinema and the machine's not
working. It's like there's always some
sort of hiccup.
It is it is a depressing place to be
this country. It is. It is [ __ ]
depressing, bro. To be fair, like
um I walked to the supermarket and
walked back. I just got the lamb. It
seemed to be all right, but there's
always some sort of hiccup in this
country. Whatever you do, it really is a
country designed to annoy you and get
under your skin.
Generally, generally is. I definitely
believe that. I'm not even trying when I
say that. I could have missed that film
yesterday, bro, if they took any longer
or like missed the start of it. Um,
where is he? I don't know. Watching but
scared to join.
There's always um hiccups in this
country. So yeah, I'll do my best on
Friday. Try my best. Got 10 numbers. Got
no date for next week. I mean, what can
you say? It's England, isn't it? It's
never going to change.
It's typical England, isn't it? I mean,
what what's there to say about it?
I mean, I I know people dismiss my
struggles, but I don't dismiss my
struggles. So, that's that.
It will never change.
Never. But we expect this in it, lads.
I don't know, man. Natalie G's probably
telling him that he can't join.
How else has he stayed off YouTube this long? So yeah.
Yeah. It's not about the way you speak
to women or stuff. It's the fact that
they're stuck up. Obviously, you didn't
see any of my approaches um
on Friday cuz I didn't record any. I
didn't do any live. But they are proper
proper up their own ass. Um they really
really are. But it's something to do
anyways. You just you just can't
I was speaking to one the f the first
number I got right they were Turkish and
I said I had Turkish in me and I'm like
they're Christian right and I'm atheist
and we was having a conversation and
they were all right but you could just
tell you could just sense the
stuckupness in them like
that Simmons is the worst place for
stuck up people.
I swear to God it's just stuck up
central, mate. I'm telling you. Yeah,
anywhere in London is to be fair, but um yeah,
I think I probably spent about £300 to
be fair last couple of days. But
yeah, it is bad. It is bad.
Should have at least got a date for next
week to be fair. I would have been happy
with one day even if it never went anywhere. But
that's that's how it is in this country, is it?
It would never change. Never.
But I understand like
you know it's about luck in terms of like maybe
you know meeting somebody that you stay
with or whatever that I understand
that's luck and but I mean the fact that
you could just go out right and get all
of them numbers and not get one single
day is messed up. Like complaining or no
complaining that is [ __ ] up. That is
[ __ ] That is really and truly [ __ ]
Like there's no denying that. But
obviously it should be about luck
whether you it shouldn't be luck whether
you get a date or not. You should just
be able to go out and get a [ __ ]
date. [ __ ] especially the way that I
[ __ ] look. Especially the way that I
[ __ ] talk. You should at least be
getting a date that goes nowhere.
Like cuz I I feel like it's it's air.
It's some step forward no matter how
many steps forward it is. So,
I mean it is it is [ __ ] bad to be
honest with you.
Sorry, I just can't stop thinking about
that. That's just insane
to me. Grezy,
I must be missing where this sort of
hope is. It's got to be in some treasure
chest or some [ __ ] cuz I can't find this
hope anywhere, mate. People say that
there is hope and stuff, but I
personally can't see it.
I really really can't see where this
hope is. Grezy, maybe if you could help
me find it or um give me some sort of
answer. I can't find this this hope that
people keep going on about.
I mean, I'm sure you would even agree,
right? If you've went out there looking
your best, doing your best, you should
have at least got a date.
Know what I'm saying, bro? That is
[ __ ] Like, you you have to admit that
is [ __ ] Like, whether you want to
agree or disagree with a lot of things,
I think we can both agree that's messed
up in it. So, I must be missing this
hope somewhere, mate. It must be in
[ __ ] Jack Sparrow's [ __ ] treasure
chest cuz I can't find it. So, anyways,
I got a roast dinner cooking.
I'm not annoyed. I mean, I'm not pissed
off because I know I tried. So, I don't
give a I mean, I'm just saying how
[ __ ] up it is. I'm not even annoyed to be honest.
But this hope that people keep going on
about must be in Jack Sparrow's treasure
chest cuz I can't find it anywhere. I
mean, the fact ghosting that you can go
out and get all of them numbers and not
even get one single date. I mean,
you be the judge, you know? I mean,
like I was saying yesterday, it's not
about having sex or finding a
relationship. It's not about that. It's
about if you done all of them approaches
and you got all of them numbers, you
should at least be getting a date
with the way that you approach with the
way that you look and stuff. Cuz
obviously I spent a lot of money. I
probably spent about 300 pound the past
couple of days.
Now, if I done that every week, every
month, I'd be toast, you know.
That is [ __ ] up, bro.
Really, really is [ __ ] up.
Well, at least I can have a nice lamb
later in it.
I don't know where this hope is, lad.
What do you think, ghosting getting 10
numbers and not getting a date? Uh,
>> I don't know, bro. I ain't spoke to him.
He hasn't come on.
Natalie G's probably banned him from
YouTube. My feet are hurting as well,
Grezy, because I had to walk over a mile
back in shoes. So, my feet are [ __ ] my
[ __ ] ankle and my shin, lad. I mean,
10 numbers are not one single day.
Imagine that, bro.
And I done approaches sober, done them
tipsy, done them drunk, done them everything.
Madness, isn't it?
I didn't even get a reply of any of the
numbers to be fair. Mad.
But one day you'll meet someone
ghosting. Don't you worry about that.
One day you'll find someone.
I think Ant-Man was right. You know,
they're not interested in this country.
I think he is actually right about that
because like how many times do people
use the boyfriend line and you don't
really get a comra out of anyone. I
think he is generally right that they're
not interested in this country.
As much as we take the piss out of it, I
mean, [ __ ] hell. Two people can't be
wrong, bro. Come on. I mean,
I think he is it is
I don't know what I don't know what it
is, bro. It's weird.
I don't know what it is.
Why no one's interested in this country?
I don't get it. [ __ ] up with it.
Damn. So, I don't know when I'll be out again.
Maybe next Saturday cuz my hair will
still be looking good
cuz I remember I got about 12 numbers in
three days and I got 10 numbers in one
day yesterday. So a day before yesterday but
yeah I must be missing where this hope
is cuz there don't seem to be any.
I think I'm just going to book another
holiday when I come back.
put a deposit on another holiday, I
reckon to be honest.
Then you had an escort thing as well. I
mean, it's just
I mean, I'll go out Saturday cuz
obviously I went um
obviously because I um
I've already had my haircut. So fine.
But then after that, I think I'll be
done for another 6 weeks to be fair.
Well, no, actually my I need to go out
my birthday actually. No, no, no. I need
to go out my birthday. My birthday's
soon. So after my birthday, it will probably be
December. I go out again maybe
cuz November I'm going away. So
for two weeks.
So yeah, December, I think maybe
December after that break,
maybe I'll go out every week because
December's very busy.
But it doesn't matter how
busy it is
bye-bye. No simps on my channel. Um,
and to be honest with you,
I I don't agree with that, Grizzly. I
think if you're brave enough to go out
there and approach and do what most
people are afraid of, I think you are
entitled to a date. Definitely. Okay.
And I'll explain it. I don't I don't
agree with that. You can agree, you can
disagree. I I'll explain it because
think about it, right? Yeah.
If you're sat in bed doing nothing,
you're not going to make money, bro.
You're not going to make money. Nah,
they're not interested in this country.
Baz. Um, so like say you you wanted a
good body, like you wanted to build
muscle. You go gym and you build muscle.
So after you put the effort in, you get
muscles, you get a better body. You want
money, you go to work. What happens when
you go to work? You get money. So, if
you're brave enough to go out there and
approach several different women, you
kind of are owed something. Just like if
you was, you know, to work, you'd be
owed money. Just like if you was to um
go to the gym, you'd get a you'd get a
body. Do you understand what I'm saying?
Like, I honestly I'm saying, bro, that
Yeah, you kind of are owed something.
Like the only people that say that are
people that try to excuse their shitty behavior.
Um, you understand ghosting? Because
it's funny how we never
Okay, I'm going to do a video on this.
Actually, do you know what? I'm going to
do a video about this this double
standards cuz I I was actually speaking
to someone else about this um yesterday.
Um, it seems like such an easy claw
attempt to justify people's shitty
behavior and their ignorance. Oh, well,
they don't owe you anything. that's they
think that seems to be their gal jail
free card for acting like a dick when
it's not it's used in the wrong context.
You understand? So yeah,
if you ever had to look again, good luck
to you, mate. Yeah,
cuz I even like a few years ago I used
it used to be easier like you could
actually get like dates off dating apps.
So, I met a couple of people from dating
apps and stuff, but now it's just impossible, bro.
I would say now, yeah, it's
Yeah, bro. Good luck.
If you ever become single again like me,
bro, good luck. You can't even get laid,
let alone a relationship.
What did my experience have my
experience scared you or something?
Yeah, I mean that I just put the truth
out there, bro. I don't need to lie, you
know? Like you get these people on
Reddit that will lie to you saying, "Oh
yeah, go on dating apps, go out and
approach and stuff and you know what I'm saying."
But yeah, if you're willing to put the
effort out there, then yeah, they do owe you something.
Just like if you go to work, you're owed money.
So, well, they obviously didn't work
because the numbers didn't reply back.
So, I'm going to do a video on this
double on the double standards. Um, I
think this needs to be addressed as
well. I was speak like I said I was
speaking to somebody yesterday and
yeah, this needs to be addressed cuz
it's still a big problem um in the
society with the double standards.
Um, and it's and it's more than one thing.
So, yeah, the 10 numbers,
but a lot of them were just same thing.
I have a boyfriend. I'm married. I'm not
interested. Same old [ __ ] just like it
would always be. Same old boring [ __ ]
So yeah, we'll go out next Saturday cuz
we got the haircut and that would that
will be me done until my birthday which
is weeks away. Then after that go to
Thailand and then I won't go out until
mid December I think. So New Year's.
It's all right once you already have
your haircut cuz I mean you can just go
out and drink lad. So,
um, you can just go out and drink,
um, and you're not really losing
anything. Whereas getting your haircut,
oh, it's going to the barbers and
sitting on the chair, it's boring,
having to spend money just to get the
same old [ __ ] Whereas, when you don't
put effort into it, like, okay, I'll
give you an example, right? Say you
don't get your haircut for a week or two
weeks and you go out and you get free
numbers and they don't go anywhere.
You're like, okay, yep, typical. But I
think when you put effort into your
appearance and you actually try and then
you get 10 numbers, then you realize how
impossible it actually is.
Like if if you haven't groomed for a
couple of weeks or a week or and you
just get a few numbers, then it's like,
oh, whatever. I think it's worse when
you actually put effort into your
appearance and you still get the same old [ __ ]
But I don't think so. No.
It's depressing, bro. It is depressing.
But yeah, years ago it was somewhat
possible, but now there is no hope in this country. Sadly,
I should have grabbed [ __ ] by the horns
whilst I could, but
I think Tik Tok has become bigger. Yeah.
Oh my god. So, yeah, they kind of they
do owe you a date.
Um, if you went out sending it, I mean,
they say they're like confident people,
so well, they kind of do owe you
something. You actually put the effort
in. I don't agree with that
um at all, and I don't agree with people saying it.
Well, it is. Well, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. I'll correct you. People have met
people years ago. Some people got lucky
at work. Some people got lucky on a
dating app. There's loads of single
people out there and them other people
have got nothing to do with me. So at
the end of the day, right, just because
other people have met people maybe got
lucky at work or they met years ago,
most people have met people years ago,
that doesn't mean that you're going to meet someone.
Um, so yes, nowadays it is impossible
for a lot of people.
Um, yes, it is impossible for a lot of
people. And to be honest with you, all
of the people that I know are single. Um,
most of the men that I know are single.
The tenants, um, people I've met on
nights out, people have got no
connection. There's more single people.
There's more single men than people in relationships.
I mean, that tells you pretty much all
you need to know. Just because there's
people in relationships
that might have got lucky, that doesn't
mean that it's not going to be
impossible for one person cuz it's just comparing.
So, it's No, it's not to do with Well,
it used to be to do with luck, but it's
not now. It used to be used to be you
could get lucky, but I mean, I got 10
numbers and I didn't even get a date. So,
I mean, there's no point in why I say or
why I show you, you're never going to
understand it. So, I mean, there's
pointlessness even bringing it up. So,
it's not luck now. Now, it's impossible.
It used to be luck. Um, so just because
other people have met someone, it
doesn't mean you're going to meet
someone. So, comparing is ridiculous
because it gets us nowhere. So, I know
I've tried. I know I got 10 numbers. I
know I've not got a date next week. [ __ ]
other people whether they're in a better
position than me or in in a worse
position than me. So,
um it is impossible.
Like some people are just not meant to
meet anyone. It's not unheard of. You
know what I'm saying? Like I've met
[ __ ] virgins that weren't even in
cells. I've met there are people out there.
So, it's like, what the [ __ ]
Just because other people have met
someone and they've had kids, it doesn't
mean you're going to. I mean, you went
out um Friday, you got numbers. You
should have a date next week.
Bro, I I I already have confidence.
What? Why? Why do you think I've not got
confidence? Because I'm stating the truth.
I mean, I don't need to get my
confidence back, lad.
I'm I don't need to get my confidence. I
am confident. I'm just stating the truth.
I mean, it's the way it is. I got 10
numbers and I got no date. That's the
truth. That's not lack of That's not
lack of confidence. That's the truth. I
mean, what don't you like the truth or
something, bro? So, what I'm going to go
to the gym and then as soon as I come
out the gym, I'm going to be like, "Oh,
yeah. The dating game is perfect." It's
not being down. It's speaking the truth.
Just like the person on um the [ __ ]
uh on YouTube called Speak the Truth.
Well, okay, let me repeat myself to you
again cuz you seem to dismiss my
struggles. I don't want to fall out with
you, brother, but I don't know if you're
trolling me or whatever. Right. I have
been at this for 5 years and I'm still single
right now. I don't want to fall out with
you, brother, but you you clearly are
taking a piss now, ain't it? Like, I
could go out another time, brother. I've
not had a date for about 6 months. Yeah.
And I'm sure I've been out more than
five handful of times in them six months.
It's not going to happen in this
country. I don't know how many times.
Um, he must have some coin. No, he
doesn't have coins. No, he doesn't have
any coin. Baz, anyone can buy a new pair
of trainers, bro. I can go out right now
and buy a new pair of trainers. He
doesn't have he doesn't have um coin at
all. He's [ __ ] skinned. Um I've had
dates from approaching before. I mean,
yeah, a million years ago, but that that
doesn't matter. Forget the past, bro.
Let's just forget the past, right? I
went out on Friday. I got 10 numbers.
I've got no date scheduled.
Do you not understand the severity of
that? It's not a little thing. Let's
Okay, let's forget the past like before then, right? Yeah.
I got 10 numbers. I looked my best. I
was confident. I have no date for next
week. I mean, what is there more to say,
bro? Come on.
I mean, you should have at least have a date scheduled.
And then and what about all the other
ones that I approached that didn't give
me their number?
So, I mean, that's just [ __ ] insane,
bro. You know,
it's [ __ ] The dating game's [ __ ]
It really is. But yeah,
but no, it's not about confidence. I'm
not feeling down. It's just
it is what it is. It's never going to change.
Whether you're depressed or you're not,
it's that's the truth. I'm not going to lie,
you know. It will never change with
women. And that's that's it. It's the truth.
That's why I don't really go out
anymore. That's the first time in 6
weeks cuz it will never change. So,
I mean, yeah, true.
But I tried dating apps. I tried
approaching on the street. I tried
approaching in shops. I've approached at
the train station. Um,
I've approached in the bars, in the
pubs, and the clubs. So, I mean
I mean, yeah.
Maybe you're right. Okay. But we're not
just talking about a club. We're not
just talking about a pub. We're talking about every
You know, the dating apps don't work.
The street, they're not interested.
You know what I'm saying? Bye-bye. So, I mean, yeah.
And then the cycle just goes round and
round in circles and never ends. That's
why I don't go out anymore, bro. Try the
library. They're not interested. Listen,
they're not interested in this country.
It doesn't matter whether you go to a
club, whether you go to a pub, whether
you go to a bar, whether you go to a
library, whether you go to a
[ __ ] abortion clinic. They are
not interested in this country. It's
simple, bro. From what from what I've seen,
you know, it's it's insane.
and churched. It's they are not
interested in this country. Oh my god.
It doesn't matter where it is. It could
be a [ __ ] It could be in a [ __ ] hospital.
You know what I'm saying? So,
and these people can try and say that
I'm the problem all I want, but the
thing is I'm not the problem because
they can't even critique anything that I
do. You see, when these people sit there
and try and say that you're the problem,
right? I showed them my approaching
videos and they said, "Okay, well,
critique them. Tell me exactly what is
wrong and they can never do it." So,
they're just saying [ __ ] for the sake of
saying [ __ ] because at the end of the
day, like if you disagree with someone
and someone's done wrong, you would be
able to tell them what they've done
wrong. They can't tell you what you've
done wrong because there's nothing wrong
with what you're doing.
So, they just they're just saying [ __ ]
for the sake of saying [ __ ] Just like
when they tell you that women don't owe
you anything when they do something
shitty to try to justify, you know, to
try to justify their actions.
So that's the thing.
Um, so there's nothing you're doing
wrong because they can't critique
anything that um, you do. And nope, I'm
not pushing above my weight. And there's
no such thing as leagues either.
So, we need to stop talking about this
in a minute as well. It's getting
depressing, bro. It's such a depressing [ __ ] subject.
Jesus Christ. But at the same time, I
don't regret going out cuz I hadn't been
out for like a month. So, I mean, it's all good, you know?
Nope. I tried with fives. Some of them
were fours, fives, eights. No, eights.
Wait, hold on. Most people in England
are not even good-looking. So, most of
them are like four to sevens.
Four. Some of them are sevens. They're
just not interested. Fours, sevens.
I mean, none of them are tens in
England. I mean, maybe the ordered one,
but none of them are tens. They're just
[ __ ] average or
Yeah, they're just it's [ __ ] England,
is it? Like, it's So, basically what
they were saying when I was approaching
them is they didn't really want to talk.
They walked away.
Um, one said they were married, one said
they had a boyfriend. Same old [ __ ] Um,
that was basically the gist of the
street approaching ones. I asked one for
their number and they said no. Um,
mad is it?
Oh, I don't know, bro.
I've been live for 34 minutes. Probably
like 2 hours and a half.
from now. But yeah, bro, it's
depressing. It is. It is [ __ ]
This subject is depressing, lad. Nope.
My mom's making it. I bought it, though.
So, yeah. Um,
yeah, you had a chance before to be with
someone. See, now I can actually like if
you if you turned around right and said
to me a couple of years ago, "It's you."
I'd be like, "Okay, it's me." You know,
you've been on dates um that gave you chances.
Um you know, and you [ __ ] them up for
the reason we already know. So, back
then you could actually say it was me,
but now you can't even say it's me
anymore. Like, you can't even blame me
anymore because like I've actually
tried. And the fact that you can't even
get a date, which is the first step,
a date is the first step, you know, out
of many steps. So, I mean, the fact that
you can't even get a date, it says a
[ __ ] lot, mate. You know, it's not
like you're getting dates and [ __ ]
up. And even then, it would still be
them, but then you'd have some kind of
argument, you know? Say every single
time you went out, right, Grezy? Say you
went out once a week and you got dates,
right? and every single one of them
dates went nowhere. Then at the end of
the day, um, then at the end of the day,
bye-bye nonslegs. Um, then at the end of
the day, you got four dates in a month,
right? And none of them dates went
anywhere. Then obviously you you could
have some kind of argument. That would
be me. But I mean, you can't even say that anymore, you know?
Like, you can't even blame me anymore.
That's that's the that's the mad thing
about it because people love blaming a
man whether it's me or anyone else. They
just love blaming men. They love
sticking up for women. I don't know why
they do it but they do it. So it's like
it's it's irrelevant about other people.
You can you can compare me to married
people, virgin people, people that have
never kissed anyone. I mean you can
compare me to multiple different people
whether they're better or worse than me.
but it's not going to change my reality.
And I think that's the main thing. You
being compared to people is not going to change anything.
So, it's just a waste of time even being
compared to anyone. You put the evidence
out there. You've shown your approaches.
And so, a married man or or a man with
kids is no relevance to me.
That's it. You two people are not
comparable. Some people just stay single
forever. Like there there are people
that, you know, there's women that are
virgins out there. I've come across a
lot of them um lately, you know.
So when they don't have an argument,
they like comparing people to
they like comparing people.
And even though you haven't done
anything wrong and they're not
interested, they have to go on their
high horse and make things up just
because they're not interested. You know
what I'm saying? You know, they have to
make up stuff. Oh, married men or other
people or all of this old bollocks. You
know what I'm saying? Like, it's ridiculous.
Oh, bro, I've already shown more money.
I've already I already destroy these
people every day. Being better looking
than them, having more money than them.
They're already destroyed. Look at how
much time they waste on me all day,
every day. I mean, I done that copycat
video cuz it was funny, but I mean, bro,
they're already destroyed. Think of how
many hours they put in all day, every
day dedicated to [ __ ] with me, bro.
They've all They've been destroyed, bro.
Huh? They have been destroyed for years.
Look how many hours they spend doing
this every day,
you know? Takes dedication, bro, and
time, you know? So, I mean, they've been
destroyed a million times. They would
just pretend they didn't see it like
they always do. Like they pretend they
didn't show get shown thousands then
they run away. Been shown women they run
away and forget it ever happened. No,
they've been destroyed
even though they never admit it.
But yeah, that's the thing, Grezy.
But I mean, I was speaking to this woman
um yesterday in America. She's 38,
right? And I [ __ ] you not, bro.
She's below average looking. Let's put
it that way. She's not the worst, right?
But um she's um she's below average
looking. Put it that way. We don't need
to put a number on it. And her attitude,
you can just tell she's a [ __ ] She's a
single mom. She's almost 40 and she is a [ __ ]
Like just the whole way about her like
thinking she's better than people. Um
you know, her attitude like you can't
explain it. like
um so even when they're 40 they don't
change even when they've got a kid. And
then she's saying, "Oh well, if I go on
a date with someone, I've got to feel
the vibe." I was like, "Listen up here."
Yeah. You're almost 40 years of age.
You're carrying baggage from another man
who you're no longer with. Don't [ __ ]
sit there and try and act like you're in
any position to be picky. I told her
about herself. Like, who are you to
start being picky, brother? way past
your sell by date
and you're carrying another man's
[ __ ] baggage and you think that
you're going to be picky.
Madness, bro. Absolute madness. This
this generation is [ __ ] I swear to
God, bro. I swear down. I could throttle
Laney sometimes. I could literally
throttle Laney sometimes for having me
when she did. I wish she had me in the
[ __ ] 1980s. I could really throttle
her sometimes. you know that
I think it's cruel to have a child to be
honest with you in this day and age
having a boy you have a son right he
gets older can't get laid can't get a
date can't find a wife can't have kids
of his own I think it's cruel to have
kids to be honest even if you're
financially stable but you want to bring
them into a [ __ ] world where it's all
[ __ ] up and we're not even just
talking about dating and women we're
talking about like I've said hiccups
every single time when you go out. It's
cruel. I reckon me to be honest with you.
Bless it. Like at the end of the day,
right, I I see this kid uh some cute
baby yesterday in a buggy and I was
like, "Bless the poor little mage.
He's not going to know what hit him."
Poor innocent Bubba being bought brought
into the [ __ ] world in a westernized
country. Imagine what dating's going to
be like when he's [ __ ] my age. For
[ __ ] sake. Imagine the [ __ ] cost of
living when that poor baby is is going
to be my age.
Cuz it's only going to get worse. You know,
there's a cute baby, you know.
Cute Bubba, bro. Cute Bubba.
Cute baby. So, what you going to do? You
going to try and find someone greasy? Yeah. Yeah, man.
I mean, I tried a lot yesterday and I
couldn't find anyone, bro.
But yeah, like no, I've got a point in
what I'm saying. I had dates years ago.
I had chances years ago, you know. So,
how did I have chances then, but I don't
have any chances now? Because it's
impossible now. That's what I'm saying,
Grezy. It's impossible now. That's it.
So, they love to blame I think it's all
wrong me. They love to blame the men
because other men do it.
like they seem to think that there's
that's the whole point is there's not
someone for everyone. That's the whole
point. The whole point of all of this
comes down to there isn't somebody for
everyone. It's not about other men or
whatever men do. It's the fact that
there's not someone for everyone.
You understand, Grezy? You know, people
believe it, some people believe it, some
people don't believe it. I personally
I mean, I do I believed it then, but I
don't believe it now
cuz obviously I had dates before and stuff. So,
um I'm sure I could have, but now, no,
there isn't someone for everyone. People
base their [ __ ]
They base their standards off a Tik Tok
and therefore [ __ ] stuck up because
of the [ __ ] that they watch. I mean, I I
don't think there is someone for everyone.
I don't know about you, but yeah. Uh,
so what are you going to do to try? You
going to go out approaching or what?
What are you going to do?
See, I I don't know how many times
God is going to tell me this until I get
the hint. Like, how many times are you
going to keep going out and trying until
you get the hint? You understand what
I'm saying, don't you, Grezy? How many
times are you going to keep going out
and trying before you get the hint?
Like things work in strange ways, bro.
Like, you know, when I used to go casino
and I used to win money and you know,
even like the football bets and stuff
recently, I feel like it's God trying to
tell me something again.
You know what I'm saying, bro? Like,
good luck, mate. You know what, Grezy?
Download them apps now. Sunday. No one's
working today. and tell me um how how
you get on with them because personally
I just found them to be fake profiles
and trolls again back in 2015
um it was easier.
It was easier, bro. It was easier. Might
as well. [ __ ] it. Is it? What have you
got to lose?
You got nothing to lose, bro. So
she look there's people on Reddit. Is
being a virgin at 27 a red flag? I'm
currently a 26 year old guy. In a few
months I'll be 27. I'm sure I'm still a
virgin. I've never had a girlfriend. No
religious reasons. Never ask girls out
and they never ask me out. Simple as
that. I'm currently on a weight loss
journey and a mental health improvement.
Don't need won't bother. See
the thing is right
if you didn't try like this guy
then you know you'd understand it but
you've actually tried that's the
difference that's why none of these
people are relatable because they've
never actually tried. If you've never
actually tried, you can't complain. But,
you know, I have tried. That's the thing. [Music]
Some madness, bro.
It is bad, is it?
I just can't wait until this lamb.
I think that's why I tried a lot Friday
cuz I realized I'm not going to be going
out much anymore. I'm getting older so I
really need to um can it,
you know, but
I shouldn't even have to follow up with
any of these numbers. They should have
just had a common decency to reply. Um,
but they don't have no decency
to even reply to someone. I mean, Jesus
Christ. But people think you're going to
get in relationships and [ __ ]
any numbers reply back yet? Nope.
Yeah, bro. I just can't get over Friday.
[ __ ] 10 numbers in not one single
day. That's a madness.
But you'll meet someone one day. I'm
sure of it.
Yeah. One day you'll meet someone, bro.
One day you'll meet someone, buddy.
Sorry, bro. It's just Sorry, man. It's
just depressing as [ __ ] Sorry, bro. I
know. I'm guilt guilty. Guilty, bro.
Guilty. But it's just depressing. Like I
understand there's this guy here that's
saying that he's 27 and he's a virgin. I
understand that you're 27 in few in a
few months time and you're a virgin. But
the difference is these people haven't tried.
They haven't tried anything.
You know what I'm saying? So it's kind of like
I don't know. I need to find someone
that's exactly the same as me to be honest.
It is It is [ __ ] depressing though.
It is depressing, bro.
It really is depressing. Um,
one second, bro.
It's nice having a roast dinner after
drinks, isn't it?
What plans do I have? Well, it's Sunday
uh for the next week. Um, nothing
to be fair. Just chilling. Might go for
some walks. Maybe try to get one of
these numbers to meet me or something.
I'll try to get one of these numbers to meet me. Um, but yeah,
nothing to be fair. I don't I don't
really make plans.
Go for a walk or I don't know.
I need to join the gym soon. So,
I need to leave this country again when
I come back from Thailand. Bro, I really
do need to leave again.
It's already ended, bro. Summer's already ended.
And why am I going to do that, bro? I've
already been all over the country, up
and down the country.
Summer's already ended. It's [ __ ]
winter now. So,
why why am I going to go there?
That doesn't make sense. Why am I going
to go there?
I've already been all over the country.
Why am I going to waste money going there, bro? Crazy bastard. [ __ ]
Wait, one sec.
So, summer ends at the 22nd of September.
the 21st of June to the 22nd of September.
So, Thomas Kession.
But then it says [Music]
>> Oh my [ __ ] leg. [Music]
See, this is what I've been ghosting,
bro. I I'm not jealous of these people.
That's why I leave them alone. They
can't leave me alone. Do you understand?
That's what I'm saying, brother. They
can't leave me alone. I leave them
alone. They can't leave me alone because
they're obsessed with me.
You understand that? But
I just do that copycat video because
it's funny, ain't it? [Music] little copycat.
Yeah, it's funny, man. [Music] All right.
Yeah, man. I can't wait until this lamb
g you. I can't wait. So, yeah. Anyways,
download the apps. Tell me how it goes.
You got nothing to lose.
You got nothing to lose, do you? No,
might as well. Eh,
we're not still in summer. We're in
[ __ ] winter now.
It says the win. Uh, it says the summer
ends on the 22nd of September.
And you really think I'm going to go to
places that you tell me to ghosted? [ __ ]
that. [ __ ] Virgin boy is going to
start going to them places.
You know what I mean? When I go there,
Virgin boy is going to start going
there. Isn't that right, Grezy? Little copycat.
Copycat's going to start going there. [ __ ] off. Copycat.
Yeah, but then the copycat's going to
start going there. You know he stalks me, lad.
He's a little copycat.
[ __ ] hell. [ __ ] copycat.
No, I don't. I know, bro. But I just
don't like people copying me, you know?
Went to Amsterdam just cuz I went to
Amsterdam. That's mad.
I tell you what, mate. My nose ain't
bigger than your fat ugly girlfriend.
Say that much. My nose ain't as big as
your [ __ ] fat ugly girlfriend's belly.
That's for [ __ ] sure, mate. [Music]
Come on, lamb. Peter belly's waiting for you. >> Yeah,
dude. I remember I went bright before
approaching Ghosted. I've not ever been
on a night out in Brighton. So, I was sp
I was speaking to this woman uh this
woman about uh places we had been and stuff
and this convers was the conversation
was all good, but she never replied ever. So, weird.
I've not ever been on a night out in
Brighton, but I've been um
I've not been out there, but I've been
for like days out.
Oh, everyone has more [ __ ] than you,
though. You're still a virgin.
And I don't want that [ __ ] [ __ ] I
don't want Natalie G. For [ __ ] sake. I
could have had that EG before him. I
don't [ __ ] want that slag with
[ __ ] black plats, bro. [ __ ] that.
He's not had more [ __ ] than me, bro.
I've had more [ __ ] than him.
And I've had more [ __ ] than you as
well. You're still a virgin. But either
way, I don't [ __ ] want that G.
You have to be insanely desperate to get
with that. And I had ch I had a chance
to get with her as well. [ __ ] more
[ __ ] than me. What? Because he's been
with two fat ugly women.
Get real, kid. I would not go near any
of them even if you [ __ ] paid me. For [ __ ] sake. >> Yeah.
I would never get rid that energy.
Never. I had a chance to, but I didn't want to.
So, what the [ __ ] You know,
keep [ __ ] stinking.
Nah, that was all [ __ ] Run boy.
He doesn't get more [ __ ] than me, bro.
That's what I used to say to him. Well,
had more he's he hasn't had more [ __ ] than me.
I've been with more women than he [ __ ] has,
mate. I've known him since he was
[ __ ] 25. And since then he he never
ever that I knew of was with anyone but that Kaye [ __ ] yeah
is with K but that's
No one else. He hasn't had more women than me.
Well, that's just Monty though, isn't
it? He's a snake. He would always be a
snake. He's tried snaking me on YouTube
a few times as well. I mean, it's not
surprising. It is Monty. He's a snake. So, I mean,
what do you expect? Remember the Discord
thing when he tried snaking me with the Discord?
He's a snake. So, bro,
I'm so tired. Look at my eyes, bro.
I'm [ __ ] exhausted. Oh, man. My eyes.
Yeah, pretty much.
You know what makes me laugh is that
[ __ ] Chase. He's such bro. Like he
comes on like trying to troll behind the
scenes with non legs, but the little
[ __ ] ain't about nothing.
Like he should have called me out when
he was with non legs in London. I would
have filled them both in. That's why I
[ __ ] I hate that tougher. I've been to
[ __ ] Wales a couple of times and he's
always shut his mouth.
No, I won't. I won't. I won't. He's a
snake. He's a snake. He's a snake, man.
That [ __ ] chase. [ __ ] smashy [ __ ] faces.
I think that Bquest has got back with
Lee because he's blocked me on
everything, deleted all of the messages.
So, I'm assuming that he's got back with
Lee or some [ __ ]
must have got back with Lee. E
was talking like and then I woke up. I
was like, "What the [ __ ] Where have you
gone?" So yeah, he must have got back
with Lee or something.
But yeah, that LJ don't have no coin
just because he buys new trainers.
Anyone could do that. I could go out
right now and buy a new pair of
trainers. I've never been into trainers.
So, I mean,
that doesn't mean someone's got money,
bro. Someone can be on benefits and
[ __ ] buy trainers. [ __ ]
He has to try to convince people that
he's got money, but
he really doesn't. And it's sad. I think
people should just be honest. Like, I
don't have loads and loads and loads and
loads of money, but I have enough money
to do what I want to do. [ __ ] spent
[ __ ] over40 pound on a roast dinner
for today. I don't need to [ __ ] you
know, I just don't know why people don't
just tell the truth.
You got people like Nlegs and [ __ ] L
J thinking they got money when they
really don't. It's just ridiculous.
It's ridiculous why they have to lie,
bro. It's madness.
Just be real with yourself, you know?
I got a feeling I'm going to eat this ro
dinner and [ __ ]
fall asleep to be fair. Yeah,
but that's what I'd always do on a
Sunday. Sunday is a chill day, ain't it?
It's a roast dinner day, a Reddit day.
You know what I mean? Greasy.
It's a roast. Oh, blast back then.
Where should I [Music] What's Yeah.
I'll be back later.