Oh. Oh,
that dinner was delicious. I'm stuffed.
Oh my god, I feel so tired now. [ __ ] hell.
There's some lamb left, Grevy, if you want some.
You and King are invited round.
Got some lovely lamb. Yeah.
[ __ ] hell. I can't believe this
bollocks, bro. Well, one number replied
in the end,
but I mean, it's still [ __ ]
disgusting, bro. [ __ ] one number out
of 10 replied [ __ ] disgusting is in it.
Oh my goodness, bro. It's disgusting.
The dang game is disgusting, bro.
I just got one.
Even though it should be about three or four, but
maybe another one will reply. [ __ ] knows.
Let me see what she looks like. Oh, Joe,
I've got some stuff to tell you, son.
He looks all right.
out yesterday. I got well I went out
Friday and I got 10 numbers
and literally only one replied.
I mean it is funny to be fair. You do
have to laugh about it cuz it's just
unbelievable. I mean, one's literally just replied.
Uh, I'm telling you, mate, this
so-called hope has got to be in Jack
Sparrow's [ __ ] treasure chest
where no one can find because there is
no hope here, Joe. There is no hope, you know.
No. Um, yeah, I just went out Friday,
got in the piss, got 10 numbers, only one replies.
Same old [ __ ] Haven't been gambling cuz
I don't gamble anymore. And yeah,
hope you catch up with my videos.
I still put content out there. Had a
nice roast lamb. Um,
now I feel sleepy. We were talking
about, you know, Virgin Boy being a
copycat and how he copies my holidays.
Literally, he's a copycat. He's a
copycat. He's got no mind of his own.
Um, but yeah,
just we're just talking about that basically
a leads for a couple of years.
I've already been leads once. Yeah,
there's a Victoria there's a there's a
casino there called Victoria Gate. Yep.
Is it Victoria Gate? Yeah.
I mean, the next time I leave London,
like the next time I leave London to go
to another city here will probably be
New Year's Eve,
but that's it really. I'm leaving New
Year's Eve. I'm going somewhere.
Yeah, I'm going somewhere New Year's Eve.
But yeah, what do you think? 10 numbers
and one reply, Joe.
Disgusting, isn't it? I was looking
fresh. I was smelling good.
Tells you all you need to know about the
dating game in this country, doesn't it?
Tells you all you need to know.
Sure. There's something I supposed to say, eh?
I mean, not really. It's like two months after.
So, I mean, um, when I come back, I'm
probably to be honest with you, right?
Doesn't matter if I'm getting numbers.
[ __ ] only one number replied,
so that's disgusting. I was confident as well. Friday,
I done 10 of them sober. The first one I
was [ __ ] myself cuz I hadn't done it
for a month. I had that was my first
time out in a month, by the way. But I
feel like in December, I feel like I
want to go out drinking every week in
December. I like December.
I don't know. I like December. I like I like December,
but it's very busy December. So yeah,
but it doesn't matter about getting
numbers. [ __ ] I can't believe only
one reply. That's [ __ ] insane.
That is [ __ ] bro. There really is no
hope in this country, is there?
Yeah. A woman can just go on a date app
and get a date whenever she wants.
It's mad, isn't it, Joe?
Yes. Uh, Friday was a month's worth of
trying. Basically, 10 numbers. That's
like a month's worth. And I'll be very,
very lucky if I even get one date.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] And then the date
will have to go somewhere.
It's just no chance in this country, is there?
This country annoys me. I don't know
about you, Joe, but it annoys me. I
can't wait till November. I can't wait to leave. Yeah,
>> it's not even about women. It's about
other things as well, which I discussed
on the video. There's always hiccups.
Whenever you try to do something in this
country, there's always some hiccups.
So, it's just a just a country full of
[ __ ] isn't it? So, yeah.
Can't wait to leave me.
really really can't.
But I mean I was always getting numbers.
So I don't know why you're saying at
least you are getting numbers. I was
always getting numbers.
We never went out and never got a number.
Didn't think we'd get 10, but
we somehow did.
It's [ __ ] madness. Oh, I had a
problem with Did you hear about the
escort thing, Joe?
Not 10. The most I've ever got before I
think was about eight or nine and that
was last year.
Yeah, the escort thing was a madness as
well. There's always some sort of
hiccups in this country.
It's just a country just designed to
annoy you. Like, I'm not even I'm not
even trolling you when I'm saying that.
I hate this country. So, at the end of
the night, you know how I always go to
um the escort house. I don't call them
brasses. I hate that word brass. It
sounds so cringe. A brass house. So, I
gave them the £100.
Then, um yeah, was doing whatever. They
were sucking my dick. Then there's like,
"Oh, you can't we we agree that I could
obviously finish cuz that's the whole
point of it." Um and then they was like,
"Oh, uh no, you can't finish." I was
like, "Wait, what do you mean? I just
gave you £100. Normally it's £60 or
maybe £70. So then they said, "Oh yeah,
you can. You can't finish."
And we had already done stuff. I said,
"Okay, well, I want half of my money
back." And they weren't having none of
it at all. The guy come um he's like,
"Oh yeah, you got to go. You got to go."
I said, "Listen, get out of my face."
Yeah. Stop. Stop yelling. Stop trying to
yell like he was trying to intimidate
me. And I was like, "Listen, right? I'm
not going to sit here and start doing
this that and the other. But if you do
not give me half the money back, I'm
going to do your windows in. Simple.
So, at the end of the day, right, I
said, "Listen, give me half the money
back or I'm going to do the windows in.
It's that it's that simple." Um, and
then there was people above. It was like
a flat, b flat. There's, "Oh, there's no
point in the sake of £100." I was like,
"Bro, you're not taking a piss out of
me. It's not about the money. You're not
going to take the piss out of me." I was
trying to look for a brick. I couldn't
find a brick anywhere. Was trying to
look for a stone. Went to a kebab shop.
I was like, "Bro, give me a hammer. I'm
going to do these windows in." Like,
"You're not going to take the piss out
of me." Then he come outside saying, "Oh
yeah, okay. We'll give you half the
money back." Got on the phone to the
boss and they end it. But bro, the
windows was going to go in if he didn't
give me half the money back. Don't take
the piss out of me, bro. Like, we
already have to deal with these [ __ ]
women in this country and their [ __ ]
as it is. we expect to pay for a service
and get the service which what we agreed
on. So that's basically what I'm saying
about there's always hiccups in this
country with anything and everything you
try to do.
I went to the cinema um yesterday.
[ __ ] machine was broken for [ __ ]
15 minutes. I almost [ __ ] missed the
start of the film. Another example, you
tried to pay for a service. There's a
whole palava about it. It's just I hate
this country, bro.
No, I don't seem to get hassled all the
time at all. That was the first time it
ever happened. Um, and it's not me. It's
I've I've seen it happen to other
people, mate. I've seen a guy approach a
woman and this guy tried to get
involved. Everybody would get hassle
if they were doing the things that I was
doing. So simple.
So, you're saying it just like it's me.
I've watched an approach video.
Yeah. Where this guy was approaching a
woman and his stranger tried to get
involved. I was like, "Bro, if that was
if that was going to happen to me, I
would have knocked someone out, bro. I'm
not even joking." Yeah. It's an annoying
country. It's a [ __ ] country, bro. I
hate it. I can't wait to get out of
here. I seriously can't.
And then when you go on a bus, you'll
get with someone, you'll get somebody
that can't mind their own business. Um,
you'll go to work, you can't get
somebody mind their own business. It's
always a palava with something.
You know what I'm saying?
Like I was on a bus a couple of weeks
ago with my mom. Um I was sitting down.
The guy tried getting involved saying,
"Oh, can you give up this seat for a
woman who there was nothing wrong? Um
there was nothing wrong with the woman.
She wasn't old. She wasn't pregnant." I
said, "Why don't why don't you mind your
own business? It's a bit rude you coming
up and asking." And then I and I said
and then he was start and he was
chatting [ __ ] I said, "Get let's get
off the bus then. Come on. Let's get off
the bus and see what you're about. Then
he shut his mouth. It's the same [ __ ]
Like there's I swear to God, bro. Yeah.
There's always a hiccup with something
that you do. I tried to go to the cinema
[ __ ] on like I said um sat uh yeah
Saturday. I went Saturday [ __ ]
machine broke down for 15 [ __ ]
minutes. It was pissing out water.
You know the amount of me I said can you
please like get the Pepsi working
properly cuz the film's about to start.
I want to go in and I almost [ __ ]
missed the start of the film. You know
what the [ __ ] bro? The pick sizes
they've downgraded. Like is can't there
be anything normal in this country ever?
How about you just go out right get 10
numbers and get a date and pay for a
service and just go home? How about just
something like why don't something why
can't it just be normal?
And then the guy, and here's another
thing, right? The guy was trying to say
about how uh you know uh every different
gal has a different price. I was like,
"No, they don't." Every single time,
right, you get a [ __ ] and you get to
finish, it is about 80 to£100.
It's not £100 for a [ __ ] where you
can't finish, brother. It's literally
never been that price. Like, listen to
me, bro. Yeah. Step away from my face.
Yeah. before like it gets bad. Yeah.
Move yourself. Said to him like, "Bro,
I've been doing this for years and I'm
sure you've you've been in this business
for years. I'm not disputing that. But,
brother, I have been doing this for
years and I know how much the things
cost. I've been with a lot of different
escorts. So, it's no, don't try and take the piss."
So, um it's not £100 to get a [ __ ]
without finishing. It's never been that.
It's It's about 70 pound 60 70 pound and
you pay the extra to be able to finish
in the person's mouth. That's how it's
always been as long as I've been doing
it in that exact place. So don't try and
tell me what it is.
And I've never had a problem before. Yeah.
Yeah. But it's No, bro. Because
she was saying it like it it was putting
me off. She was saying, "Oh, yeah. You
can't do it. You can't do it. You can't
do it. You can't do it. But yeah, it
isn't me, Joe. It isn't me. I just gave
you a few examples. I went to the cinema
and the machine broke down. Was that my
fault? So, it's my fault that I went to
the cinema and the machine broke down.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Cuz I broke the
machine, didn't I? Because I went to pay
to see a film, pay for a drink, and
broke the machine myself. Yeah. Yeah. It
was totally me. Yeah. Yeah. Don't tell
anyone, though. when I was sat on the
bus and we got some guy telling me to
give up a seat for a disabled woman
who's not even disabled. Yeah, that was
me, bro. Of course. No, it's people in
this [ __ ] country. And the more life
experiences that you get, the more
problems you'll have, you know? That's
that's what it is. So,
well, Grevy doesn't leave his house, so
no, he wouldn't have these problems cuz
he doesn't even leave his house.
You're asking Greavvesy, has he ever had
problems? Bro, I'm well more traveled than Greavvesy.
Grieves never even hardly left the
village that he lives in. I don't think
he's going to have had much of these
problems, mate. So, yeah.
So, yeah, you can try and blame me all
you want, but I know it's this [ __ ]
country and the [ __ ] in it. I
remember when I used to try working for
Uber as well, you'd get some stupid
little [ __ ] that can start things
they can't finish.
No, it's definitely this [ __ ]
country. And how I know that as well is
because when I used to deal with a lot
of Asian um customers, I never had any
of these problems. It is this [ __ ]
country and the [ __ ] isn't it? It
definitely one million% it is.
Cuz every single Asian person I've dealt
with, I had none of these problems. Not
one of them. Not one single issue. Yeah.
When it's do with these [ __ ] here
and these people trying to scam you,
there's a lot of problems,
you know. So, no, it's definitely the
[ __ ] in this country. Definitely.
And it's the whole um having to wait
around for things um in this country. I
hate having to wait for things, you know, simple.
So the problem is is that um
yeah so anyways I just gave you a new
example the cinema. What was me about that then?
Nah, I got 10 numbers and only one of them replied.
Yeah man, I got 10 numbers and only one
replied. Typical England day. So I went
to the cinema on Saturday and the
machine broke down and it took them 15
minutes to to to to fix it. Was that my fault?
I mean, was that my fault? Well, that I
wanted Pepsi and it was and it was
pissing out water. I mean, how was that
my fault? I went to go to the cinema. I
paid money out of my own pocket to to to
watch a film and the machine broke.
Every single one of them. I mean, how is
that my fault? So
I feel like in this country sometimes
it's just best not even going out and
doing anything. There's always a palava
with it. You get [ __ ] that can't
mind their own business.
It doesn't uh because you shouldn't have
to be waiting 15 minutes for the machine
to work. I was about to miss my [ __ ]
film. Like and every single one it
wasn't like it was one or two of them.
It was every single one of them. Four of
the Pepsi machines were all broken.
Every single one of them. It wasn't two.
It wasn't one. It was every single one of them.
So, what the [ __ ] bro?
So, and I weren't going to have any
other drink but Pepsi. So, it's simple.
But there's always some sort of hiccup
with a lot of things that you do.
No, they had to wait for the sh uh the
syrup to settle or something. So,
well, it is a big deal because you
shouldn't have to be waiting 15 minutes.
You go to the cinema to get your snacks
and and and watch a film. You you
shouldn't have to wait 15 minutes. And
it's not the fact that I had to wait 15
minutes. I had to ask several of members
of staff to go and do it.
So, I mean, at the end of the [ __ ]
day, it's not good enough, bro. No, I'm
not being reasonable. That's [ __ ] ridiculous.
Oh, just some horror movie. So, there's
always hiccups with the in the country. And yeah,
I mean, even though there's never
normally a problem at the escort at the escort house,
there's never there's never normally a
problem. It's just that they don't do
it. So you just have to find some which
is still a problem because if you can't
find somebody that does it then
obviously it becomes a problem but
there's always some sort of like there
there's always a hiccup
like when I watched this black guy
approached a woman
and then this guy tried getting
involved. It was annoying me even
watching it. Like even watching it when
it's not happening to me is annoying
with these [ __ ] in this country. It
is annoying bro. Even when it's not
happening to me.
No, it's not reasonable. It's not
reasonable at all. It's not reasonable
at all. I hate this country. I hate
waiting around for things. I hate the
people in it.
They can't mind their own [ __ ]
business. They like to Do you know what?
I'd respect them if they could actually
start stuff they could finish. Then I'd
actually respect it. But they start
stuff they can't finish. What's the
[ __ ] point? It's just [ __ ]
ridiculous because you ruin your mood,
you ruin everyone else's mood, and then
you be a [ __ ] at the end of it. What's the point?
You know what I'm saying? This there
this country is just full of [ __ ]
It's simple, isn't it? Like,
what else is there to say?
People are in denial if they don't think
that. Very in denial. So,
I hate this country. It [ __ ]
depresses me, bro. It annoys me being in it. So, yeah,
there's so many different things as
well. It's not just women. There's so
many different things. I mean, that
whole escort thing, why not just accept
the £100 and then just let somebody come
in your mouth? Why is it got to be a
thing about it? I don't understand. Like
I I I mean it just to me it just doesn't
make any sense. That's what I mean. It's
a troll country. It's designed to annoy
you and get under your skin. That's what
I'm saying. Because mate, I'm pretty sure
if I was to [ __ ] suck a [ __ ] dick,
which I would never do cuz I'm not
[ __ ] gay. Um I'm pretty sure you
would just let I don't know, someone
finish in your [ __ ] mouth.
I mean, isn't that just a normal thing? So
why not just It just doesn't make any
sense. That's what I mean. It's a
country designed to annoy you and get
under your skin.
That's what I mean. Yeah. But yeah,
it will never change. E England will
England will never change ever. It's a depressing country.
Grezy, we got some um lamb left over for
you and King. If you want to pop round,
we can watch a nice Sidemen Sunday. What
do you think of that? Ah,
one number out of 10. Hey, Jesus Christ.
That is in [ __ ] That's [ __ ] insane,
bro. That really is insane, man. Oh my god.
They're just not interested in this country.
Joe, what's your opinion on the Virgin
um copying my holidays?
going [ __ ] Amsterdam just cuz I went
uh well I am leaving.
Well I am leaving. I mean bro like I
said I didn't go out for a month. Um
so I thought [ __ ] it. I don't even
really I don't go out try I don't go out
and try anymore anything but I I was
just like super bored. So it is the
country is bad.
No, but I will probably end up going
there for good.
How could I do delivery when I don't
even have a delivery account?
Yeah, right. Huh?
I don't know. Some loser and I don't care.
Like I said, we're going to let them
show that they're the obsessed ones by
going on about me all day, every day.
I don't know and I don't care and don't
bring it on my channel.
It's probably that chase though since
you bring it up. That chase is a coward,
man. That chase is such a [ __ ] coward.
Cuz I've been to Wales a few times and
he's shut his mouth every single time
I've been there and he's been to London
with his boyfriend and never once have
they called me out. Yeah, man.
No, I'm I'm Do you know what? After
Thailand, I'm never telling you where
I'm going again,
you know? Because every time I say where
I'm going, we get a virgin that copies
me. Like Amsterdam,
we get a [ __ ] skint virgin that
[ __ ] copies me. So [ __ ] that, bro. No
way. What? So someone can copy my
holidays again? [ __ ] copycat. Little copycat.
[ __ ] what a copycat.
What a copycat. No mind of your own.
Yeah, he's copying.
Joe, it's copying. He's a copycat.
He's a copycat, mate. Have you ever been
to Amsterdam, Joe?
To be fair, I didn't even like it. Me,
I thought it was overpriced, overrated,
it was grimy, it was
I saw rats there. I mean, it's at the
end of the day, like I said on my video,
I don't know if you watch my videos, but
I like the Netherlands. The Dutch people
are nice. The country itself is nice,
but just not Amsterdam.
Yeah. It doesn't matter if he enjoyed
himself or he didn't enjoy himself. He
went because I went,
so it's doesn't matter who enjoyed
himself, who didn't enjoy himself. And
then he's trying to say, "Oh, well, our
experiences are immensely different." It
doesn't matter about our experiences
being different. It's the fact that you
somehow ended up in the same place I ended up. And also,
um, and like like you just said, you're
not into prostitutes and weed. Now, I
can't remember exactly why I went to be
honest, but I know I did go. It was
where I was supposed to go the first
time, but I couldn't because of
restrictions. So, at the end of the day,
uh, he wouldn't have went there. He
would have went to Paris. That's what
I'm saying. He is copying. And don't try
and act like you're the one with money,
and I'm not, mate. I've had more money,
and I have more money than you would
ever have. I've got life experiences
that you [ __ ] well don't.
I just had a [ __ ] I just spent £40 on
a [ __ ] leg of lamb today, you [ __ ]
skint virgin. Something that your mom's
never [ __ ] fed you. Yeah. Yeah. And
it come out of my [ __ ] pocket, you skin bastard.
So yeah, Amsterdam is nice. Don't get
Sorry, not Amsterdam. Netherlands is
nice, bro. Dutch people are really nice,
but it's just Amsterdam is not nice.
Rotterdam's nicer. There's a lot of nice
places in the Netherlands. It it it is a
nice It is a nice country cuz I saw like
other bits of it, but Amsterdam and it
is good, but just not Amsterdam. Simple.
But obviously it's a tourist
um place where people go. So
I went because I'd never been abroad and
I wanted to go abroad. So I went at 23 um
because I never been abroad. So all of
these things that he's doing at 31, I've
already done them
because I'm not skint like him and I
wasn't skint like him. Do you understand?
Yeah, I've heard about Paris. I can't
comment because I've never been, but
yeah, there's nice, trust me,
Netherlands is nice and the people are
always nice. Every single Dutch person
I've met have always been down to earth.
Um, whether they were from Amsterdam or
not, but it's just it's just Amsterdam
is [ __ ] bro.
Um, and I stayed in the hostel because I
wanted to stay in the hostel cuz I
wanted to meet people that were doing
the same thing as me. Don't try and act
like it's cuz I couldn't afford anywhere
else. You skint bastard.
You know what I'm saying? Like, [ __ ]
off, you [ __ ] virgin. Skint virgin.
They ain't done nothing for three
[ __ ] years. Get the [ __ ] out of here.
Oh, that car went flying.
But I've never been to Paris. So,
yeah, I went when I was 23.
20 [ __ ] three. I went
23 years old.
I went twice. I went to two places in a
month. So I went Belgium, then I went to Amsterdam.
And then he copied me. Little copycat.
Because someone's in a relationship
would go to Paris. That's where I was
going to go to Par. I was going to go
Paris with Izzy. When I tried to go to
the Netherlands, they um
they said um oh, you can't uh
you can't because of restrictions. So
then they gave me me a voucher
and then um then I just done Belgium.
Yeah, but why? Most places in Europe are [ __ ] So,
so yeah, I just said like, "Oh, we
should go to Paris." So, you know, you
wouldn't go to No one's saying that you
wouldn't go to Amsterdam ever. We're
saying that you wouldn't go to Amsterdam
your first time abroad.
I mean, you went cuz I went.
Little copycat. Next thing we know,
he'll be going to [ __ ] Thailand, Joe,
because he likes [ __ ] Asian people.
You know what I'm saying?
[ __ ] little copycat.
Tickle him, you know.
[ __ ] madness, bro. Never known
someone to copy someone's holiday. See,
my sister's never been to Amsterdam. I'm
the only one in my family that's ever
been. Even though my sister's been to
loads of countries, but she's never been to Amsterdam
ever. She's never been to the
Netherlands ever. So, you know, what's
the chances, right, that someone's first
holiday has been Amsterdam via the Euro
store like you?
It's a bit dodgy, is it, mate? It's a bit dodge.
So, you know, when I go out in future
and I meet some people, I'm going to ask
them if they ever been to Amsterdam and
was it the first time? Um,
I'd say city. It's got to be city cuz I
don't like the heat.
So, it has to be the city. Yeah,
because I don't really like the heat. My
favorite month is October, December,
March. April, April, March, April,
April, October, December is my favorite months.
So, I don't really like [ __ ]
the heat to be fair, but I don't like it
too cold either. I like it in cuz I like
Guinness. You can't really drink
Guinness in the summer, even though
people do. It's better in the winter.
Um, I thought about Rome. Yeah,
but I mean if I was in a relationship maybe, but
yeah, I thought about Italy, but
I don't know, man.
You'd really have to go with someone to
go there, would it?
Do you think nonslegs would ever have
the balls to go to a different country
by himself like I did?
Nah, I don't think so, mate.
Yeah, I was thinking of the Guinness factory,
actually. Yeah, I was thinking of that. H. Yeah, man.
How much did you spend in leads? Oh, man.
Oh, how much did you spend in leads anyways?
>> Oh, [ __ ] me. Oh [ __ ] I'm 5%. Oh.
I was up in Leeds, but the casino took.
Oh, damn. I don't miss them gambling
days, man. [ __ ] that.
Nah, I don't miss them days.
I don't care anymore. I was going to do
a football bet. I was going to do
Darlington and Meereen on Saturday, but
I never and they [ __ ] both scored as well. [ __ ]
I just don't like gambling anymore to be honest.
I don't know. I just don't think it's
worth the stress.
Just doesn't really seem worth it to me.
Although, one day I do want to I do want
to do um a both teams to score
500 pound both teams to score.
One day I do want to do that. Both teams to score
£500 on a double. Both teams to score.
But [ __ ] that. Yeah, but then they try
to get your money out.
I bet they ask you questions when you're
trying to get your money out, though.
I bet they do when you try and get your
[ __ ] money out though.
What's the problem you've got? It's like
Nottingham. You can walk straight in,
but then it's obviously trying to get
your money out. That's the problem.
I've got this online site called Spin Dog.
I was tempted to have a go the other
day, but I'm not going to cuz it's just fixing it. So,
yeah. But what's the B H
in terms of what? I haven't played on it
yet, but they have a live roulette table,
but I don't know. I'm not getting into
that [ __ ] again, bro. So,
I'm not getting into that [ __ ] again. D.
Maybe I'll go leads New Year's then.
That's the best way to be honest. At
least you know you're going to get your money.
I like the both teams to score, but I
didn't want to risk cuz I wanted to go
out and have fun on Friday. I didn't
want to risk losing money.
So, I didn't want to I was going to do
the both teams to score on the National
North League. There's always loads of
goals, but I just
Uh, I don't really want to be losing
money. I just want to stop the gambling
[ __ ] forever, you know.
So, what you going to try to website Spin Dog?
Yeah, I didn't do a bit to be fair.
It's so mad that you probably have more
chance of winning on the bar roulette.
than online roulette.
It's called Spin Dog. Bye-bye, weirdo. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, [ __ ]
So, what you going to give it a try?
Going to give it a little while.
But the roulette's fixed on it, Joe.
That's why I don't want to go on it
because the roulette's fixed.
It's fixed, isn't it?
Fixed as [ __ ]
Yeah, I could put 400 pound in right now
if I wanted to, but
nah, it's no point.
Yeah, it's a form of entertainment, so they say.
So, secular slot says,
"Fuck that, bro. What are you going to
have a go on it?"
I bet you have a go on it, don't you?
And they charge you fees to deposit and
the minimum withdrawal is 200 and [ __ ] It's just
Yeah. Well, we can't be doing them
anywhere anymore, mate, because we're no
longer rich. So,
and I mean, I wouldn't do it anyways. So,
I wouldn't do them anyways. To be fair,
I stopped ages ago. I stopped like
eight, nine months ago, to be fair. So, yeah.
Nah, mate. I'd rather just save money
and just get out of here like I'm doing.
Yeah, but on what? There's no there's no
sch slots on there.
There's no slots on there, is there?
Oh, you mean like in the Brookies or something?
Imagine putting£500 on a double. both
teams to score. Joe,
lovely £1,800, eh? Jesus Christ. That'd
be nice, isn't it?
That'd be nice.
No, I don't watch your videos.
You will do You will do your balls in
eventually though, matey.
You will do your balls in eventually.
Yeah, you could do that
on like the National Northern League.
They're quite easy. Well, not easy, but
you'll probably get it in eventually.
But on like a normal league, it's too hard.
Imagine that. A 600 pound on a both
double both score, no draw. [ __ ] hell.
That would be a lot of it. Yeah,
that would be a lot, matey. [Music]
But you'll do your balls in, matey.
Eventually, you you will do your balls in.
You know them um Reddit mods, Joe,
you know they they ban people to feel powerful.
You know, they need that power because
they've got no control over anything
else in their life. no life, no money,
don't leave their house. They feel
powerful because they can ban people and
they can't do anything about it.
You know what I mean? Yeah.
Why? Why do you think they're sad?
Where did you win that 2.5K? Bye-bye, weirdo.
But you will do your balls in matey.
Trust me, it's only a matter of time.
You know it. I know it. Is it?
What the [ __ ] man?
What slot are you paying?
What slot are you [ __ ] playing, bro?
What the [ __ ]
Never used to win that to be fair.
That is insane to be honest.
Why are Reddit sad people anyways?
You know what makes me laugh about these
women here? You'll come across a lot of
these women on Reddit, Joe, they're like
27, 28, never kissed anyone, never had
sex, but yet they will go on these dates
with loads of these guys. So you know
when you say about well they choose
other guys and meta t there's this woman
that has that goes on like three four
dates a month and
she's still single.
I mean [ __ ] they're still [ __ ] single bro
because they'd rather no one than have
anyone less than perfect.
That's insane bro. It's actually [ __ ] you know.
Well, that's what the mods do. They try
to they they ban people because they
feel powerful. Is it simple? Yeah. It's crazy.
So they'd rather have no one than have
any anyone less than perfect. So there's
loads of guys that aren't being chosen
to be honest.
How they moan about not being able to
find someone is beyond me though. I
can't even get a date and I got 10
numbers and I don't I'll be lucky if I
even get a date out of any of them
numbers. So there you go. Read and start
what you will.
Yeah. Read and start what you will.
It's [ __ ] up, man.
Yeah. Probably the multiplier on the
roulette to be fair. Yeah.
the four grand.
I think I've got about
£1,500. I think I've got
no I think. Yeah. Spent some money going out. So
yeah, I think it was the four grand. Yeah.
Walked in the casino with 150 on a Wednesday.
come out with 4,000. I didn't even plan
to go out on a Wednesday. My army friend
said, "Oh, let's go out drinking." I
said, "Fuck it. Why not?" And then at
the end of the night, I said, "Do you
want to go casino before we go home?"
He's like, "No, I'd rather just go
home." I said, "All right, I'll message
you tomorrow." And that's how I won that four grand. Yep.
It was good, eh?
Jesus Christ. I couldn't believe it,
man. The fresh 50s.
No, I'm good, thanks. I went to waxies
on Friday, but there was no women there,
so I left.
Yeah, I went to a few places on Friday,
obviously. That's how I got the [ __ ] 10 numbers.
So, um, yeah.
Yes. So, I got about 1,500 left, but I
spent like two something on thingy. So,
yeah. Is what it is, isn't it?
It is what it is. [Music]
I need to build my money up to be
honest. I really need to build my money
up to be honest with you. Without the
whole I was
saying to this guy, uh, I met this guy
on Friday. I said, "Oh, yeah. This is
how much I have left." And [ __ ] This is
how much I have left. And he was like,
"Oh, I have the same amount, but he
works." I was like, "No, you don't.
You're taking a piss." He said, "No, I
do." Before I got paid, I think I had
like 900 pound or something. And he
showed me how much he had till the end
of the month. It was like eight. He said
he just got paid. So he had eight he got 1.9K
and then £800
left out of that. So people that work
have less disposable money than us.
I thought losing the house it would have
been more at I think at the start it was
it was bad cuz obviously you lost a lot
of income but I think I'm just used to
it now to be honest with you. So
it is what it is.
I can make money if I really want to,
but like 1.5k and £100 a week is
is okay for now on it. So,
it is what it is, bro. It is what it is.
Yeah. But by the time they've paid their
rent and [ __ ] they have less than you.
By you, I mean me. So
yeah, like I just have decent money. I
don't have loads and loads of money
anymore, but I have decent money. But it
doesn't matter. As long as you don't
have to stress about money, then it
doesn't really matter, does it? As long
as you don't have to stress, then you're
fine in it. Really?
paid my Xbox as well. So, I'm good, bro.
So, yeah. What is whatever.
What can you do? Oh, but saying that
though, I need to buy a new pair of
[ __ ] jeans. My jeans [ __ ] um
I was in the toilet, Joe, and the
buttons come off. You know, the morning
jeans, the buttons come off. Luckily, I
was wearing a belt so I could like cover
it up cuz I was debating, oh, should I
wear a belt? Should I not wear a belt and um
yeah, I wore a belt. If I didn't, I
would have been [ __ ] So, yeah, that's
another thing I need to replace is them 120 jeans.
Oh, it's always so big, isn't it? So,
no, I don't have it anymore
to be honest. I'll just wear the jeans
how they are to be fair for the time
being. I'll just I'll just wear them how they are. Yeah,
like with about
to be honest.
So, yeah. Yeah, they get more than 1.9K, but they um
a lot of people saying they left with
£500 for the month or 600 or 1,000 or 1,100. So yeah,
it's what it is, bro.
jeans as well. So,
yep. I didn't go out for like a month,
so I was able to save a bit of money. Yeah.
But obviously if this person wants to go
out next week, then I'll be spending money. So yeah,
I'll be spending [ __ ] money. But who
gives a [ __ ] man?
I think as long as you got like
12,300 disposable money and you get
money a week, I feel like you're right, bro.
I mean, look at what Virgin Boy done,
Joe. He He lost out on life for three years
for the sake of 13 grand.
What I'm saying, bro, that's [ __ ] Do
not think that's actually [ __ ] And
then I was thinking, Joe, like, how
about I don't go out for like a month
and then just build my money up and then
go out. I mean, I can go out every week
no matter what. I could go out, but I
wouldn't really be able to save if I was
also doing that.
So then I was like, well, you could save
for like a little bit and then build
your money up and then go out. So like
you could you could also do that as well, but
you understand? So I was also thinking
of that idea as well, just to build up,
but then I was like I was bored on
Friday, so I thought I just go the [ __ ]
just get the [ __ ] out. So yeah,
but look at Virgin Boy. He lost out on
life for [ __ ] 3 years.
Wasn't worth the 13 grand, was it, mate?
Really? It's not worth it. It's not
worth it to lose out on life
or £13,000 for 3 years, is it? That's
like That's saving £4,000.
That's basically £4,000 a year. That's
nothing to save £4,000 a year.
That's not even
£500 a month.
Say normal person on benefits. I don't
go out drinking. Yeah.
Like greasy. You're say you can save
what? £500 a month.
So I'd rather have had the life
experiences I have and not have had that
savings. And I mean it, bro. I generally
generally mean it.
Where am I?
But yeah, I'd rather um
he lived a skint life.
No assets, no designer clothes.
hasn't barely traveled. That's a skint
life. That's not a simple life. It's a skint life.
Um, you know what I'm saying, bro? It's
a skint life.
So, yeah, he lives a skint life.
What do you think of that, Joe? Skint life.
[ __ ] me, bro.
Look at what I've done compared to what
he's done. And I'm 27. I'm not even 28 yet. So,
it's not a competition. It's just
something to, you know, throw in there, bro. [ __ ] Yeah.
So, I get that 100 pound a week. So, it
should be all right. Whatever no
I still feel hung over, mate. Oh [ __ ] Yeah.
[ __ ] hung over ass, man.
So, what are we going to do?
Yeah. Then what's the point of life then?
You know, what's the point of life if
you're not going to die into places or
go places and stuff? Like I know that I
need to adjust my lifestyle now
obviously, but I've already done it all.
The gambling, the drinking, [ __ ]
traveling and [ __ ] So like I'm
I'm okay with it now. At the start it was [ __ ] cuz obviously
it is it is [ __ ] But I mean I just sort
put some money aside and just was
careful with it. And then that's how I
was able to build up again.
That's how I was able to just build my
money up again.
I feel like I'm careful more now with money.
So because of you know how it is. Yeah.
What it is e
you could be like Monty man. [ __ ] 20
to last you [ __ ] two weeks.
to last you two weeks. You know what I mean?
[ __ ] hell. Imagine that.
Madness, it sure [ __ ] them. He want
them burgers to last him.
No, he doesn't.
No, that's all.
Oh man. So, you know, your wins, they
don't trigger me. You see, with some
people, when people gamble, when they
win, it triggers people. It doesn't trigger me.
I don't know why, but it doesn't trigger me, bro.
Maybe because I've done it so many
times. So, who knows? [ __ ] knows. But
doesn't trigger me. No. [Music]
No, it doesn't trigger me, bro.
I do need to do some traveling though.
Definitely. I don't next week. Uh, not
not next week. Next year to be fair, cuz Yeah, man.
We don't want to end up like these old
people that's never been anywhere.
So I want to go to more places as well.
yeah, next year as well after I come
back from thingy.
Wonder did you see what happened to Rice, Joe?
There was an angry mob outside his house again.
Oh, it's funny.
Angry mob outside his house again, bro. Jeez.
Yeah, but I mean there's people that are
[ __ ] Yeah, but there's people that
are my age, bro, that's been to more places.
So, you know,
been there people that's been to a lot
more places than me. Yeah. [Applause]
Did you see what happened to Rise? Did
you see what happened? They done the windows in.
It's [ __ ] madness. Yeah.
Yeah. It's mad, isn't it? I just know
Bonn's watching this right now. He would
love to come on in it.
Bonnie would love to come on. You just knowing it. Yeah. [Laughter]
Yeah. It's funny, isn't it? Oh, [ __ ]
So, you're going to play some online roulette, Joe?
I don't play the roulette anymore, Joe,
cuz every time I play it, it goes on the
left side of zero.
Yeah, it goes on the left side of zero. So,
I kind of packed it in
cuz it always looks for what I ain't got.
It looks for what I haven't got. Yeah. Oh, [ __ ] Nah, bro.
What's the What's a 100 pound going to do?
What's 100 pound going to get you, man?
Come on. Let's be real. You know. Nah.
You If you do it, I'll do it.
Yeah. Yeah. If you do it, I'll do it.
I was on the Baby Guinnesses on Friday.
Baby Guinness. Guinness Joe the [ __ ] lot.
Yeah. The [ __ ] lot, bro.
[ __ ] off, bro. Just chilling.
It's a shot.
You can't do Frankie online on that website.
Let me see. Bend dog.
Where's it gone?
It's called baby goodness, but it tastes
nothing like Guinness. Yeah.
Where's that gone? Spin dog.
I can't find it. Oh, I
Oh, here it is.
Imagine we won four grand again. And
that will get the virgin jealous, won't it, Joe?
You'll get the You'll get the virgin
jealous. The skin virgin. Oh [ __ ]
Here we are.
Let me see if they've got Frankie.
What am I doing? I'm going to bed in a
minute. I'm [ __ ] tired.
Like the good old fishing frenzy days. Hey Joe,
like the good old Sorry, the good old
USA Izzy days.
What is up?
Just like the good old USA days, bud.
[ __ ] I just watched the roulette
table. It just went on five. I need to
stop watching this, bro, cuz I'm going
to end up playing it if I keep watching
it. [ __ ] that. Yeah.
Yeah, I just went on [ __ ] five. You
can't I'm not watching that, bro. I'm
going to end up playing it.
So, yeah. Pointless. I'm good, man. Jesus Christ.
Yeah, five is one of my numbers.
Do you remember the number five Joe?
[ __ ] that man.
You like the number five, don't you, Joe?
I like 5 8 112.
See, I've gone longer than you about gambling.
Yeah. My sister's boyfriend used to like 23.
I can go without gambling longer than
you in it.
Do you remember when I went in Admirals
with £100? I come up with a,000 just on
the roulette. Oh my god, I remember
that. That was a good one. 100£ 100
pound to a,000 on the two pound roulette.
Do you remember it on in the Admirals? Jesus Christ.
Do you remember that one? I went to Admirals. Huh?
Have a little spin, Joe.
Have a little spin.
Have a little spin, matey.
Yeah, I was on my way back home. I used
off at Admirals. Madam of 100, got to
a,000. Took the,000. They gave me a,10 notes. But yeah. Nah.
Well, have a go on the old spin dog.
What on the old spin dog?
Spin dog, you know.
Oh my god. [ __ ] spin dog. [Laughter]
Nah, bro. No, I'm not playing it. [ __ ]
that. No way. Yeah.
Of course you did. Of course she did,
mate. Of course she did. You know,
would have a go. Yeah.
No, I'm not playing that [ __ ]
Cover last week's losses. There you go.
No, I'm all right, bro. I'm just gonna
wait. I'll just save my money. Slower
money. Slower guaranteed money is better than
fast money and risk losing it. So,
[ __ ] that, bro.
No, I'm good. No, no, no, no, no, no,
no. [ __ ] that, bro. [Music]
[ __ ] that. Absolutely [ __ ] that. I
need to build my money up, BT. You know,
next thing you know, I'll be in a
[ __ ] bedit with no [ __ ] bed in it
and no money in it like a certain
person. We know, mate. That's what
you're trying to You're trying to get me
like the skinned virgin in the bedsit,
aren't you? I know what you're trying to
do, mate. It's not going to work. You
want me to lose all my money, don't you?
You want me to end up like the skinned
virgin in the bedsit with no bed and no
money in it. You can get [ __ ] mate.
I gave my barber £50, by the way, Joe,
to get my hair, beard, eyebrows, face mask,
face uh wax,
and sent it doing these approaches. And
I still don't have a date for next week,
I don't think. Tells you all you need to
know about this country. Hey, buddy.
But you're just trying to get me to lose
my money. Yeah. £50 cuz I got the full service.
Yeah, but I got like face mask, face
wax, had stuff done to my skin, got my
eyebrows waxed. So, I mean, yeah, I
don't do it often at all. Maybe twice a year.
So, I thought why not? Let's look Max
made no difference.
not interested in this country, Joe.
Like Ant-Man said, he said, "They're
just not interested in this country."
Yeah, he was trying to get me to lose my
money, mate. I could work and make £500
a week if I wanted to. So,
I don't [ __ ] need to do that [ __ ]
I'd rather slow money than risk money
nowadays, to be honest. Yeah,
I don't know. I don't talk to him
anymore. But he was right about they're
not interested in this country. Obviously,
he's obviously right about that though,
is he? That there's not they're not
interested in this country.
They're just not interested in this
country. Obviously, he's right, isn't he? Duh.
Obviously, he's [ __ ] right though, isn't he? So, yeah.
I don't know what he does but I know
even when I look Ms are not interested
so who knows eh
cunning birds is a pass you can't even
pull in this country you can't even get
a [ __ ] date
I wonder why people on Reddit make it
seem so easy Joe
I don't know why
I think They It's cuz they don't leave
their house or something.
Nothing, man. Nothing's going on at all. [Music]
What should we do?
It is kind of tempting to want to play
roulette to be fair,
but I just don't want to waste the money
on it to be honest with you. So, nah.
How can I do one pound on Frankie when
[ __ ] How can I
when Frankie is not even
on the thing?
Yeah. One of them have Yeah. One out of
the 10 numbers. Yeah. Uh,
no, bro. I need to have loads and loads
of money. I'm going to really start
traveling soon, bro.
I can't afford to be losing any money.
Do you pay off for your holidays, Joe?
I think I'm going to do some work for
like seven days, bro.
I'm going to think I think I'm going to
do like work for seven days.
Just seven days straight. Like just smash it
and then see how much money I make in
them seven days. I think I'm going to do
that, you know, just absolutely some
crackheading hours like and see how much
money I can make in a week. Feel like
I'm going to do that, you know. Defo.
Yeah, I think I am, bro.
Yeah. So, you pay off for stuff, don't
you? You pay off for stuff. You pay off the holidays. Yeah.
Do you reckon I can make 500 pound in a week
working every day or every other day? I
think you could. I think you could. Yeah,
I think so. Yeah.
No, no, no, no.
I bet you I could make more than you in
a month, Joe, if I wanted to.
I bet you I could, mate, if I wanted to.
I bet I can make more than you, lad, in
a month. All my money put together if I
wanted to, matey.
Nah, mate. My legs wouldn't fall off.
You don't know how far I went when I was
doing that delivery job,
bro. You don't know how far I went. It
was [ __ ] You need to be strong to be
able to do it. Not anybody can just do
it. Like, you have to really put your
mind to doing it.
No, it's not easy, bro.
It's fun, though. You get to go to new
areas and [ __ ]
This is fun.
It is funny.
>> Can you imagine you doing that job, Joe?
You wouldn't be able to do it. You're
too fat. You ain't got the stamina.
Imagine Virgin boy trying to do it.
Imagine the skin virgin trying to do it. [ __ ] hell.
Could you imagine the skin virgin trying
to do it? Yeah.
Imagine Virgin boy trying to do it. Jesus Christ. No. No way.
I don't think so.
Virgin boy doing it. Joe
Joe the Skint Virgin doing it.
Imagine a Skint Virgin doing it. Come on.
You want me to play roulette so I can
lose my money and you can laugh at me?
Well, if you delivered food
mixed in with your benefits, you
probably could. With the benefits, you
I reckon you could. Yeah. Defer.
You'd be [ __ ] though. You'd be very tired. So yeah,
I mean I don't even have a delivery
account so I can't even do it. But just
using that as an example
if I ever get my Uber account back
but I can do it anyways.
Good old roulette.
Good old roulette. Eh,
I was on more money than you before
though when I was getting three grand a month. Yeah. Before
I was getting more than you when I had a house. Oh [ __ ] man.
He's an ugly bastard. We know.
What do you mean it wasn't sustainable? Why not?
I feel like I have more money now than
when I had the house. Cuz I feel like
when I had the house, I wasn't careful
with the money. I was always [ __ ]
just spending it and [ __ ] Gambling, drinking, escorts, you know.
Yeah, it was always the scary thing
about it. No, the
the thing about it was Yeah.
was and I still got some money from it
as well. But the thing with it is like
the thing I hated about the house share
is that you never
knew when it was going to end. You never
knew when you was going to get that
letter. Oh, you know what I'm saying?
Um, and the responsibility with it as
well. It was just uh
it's just I could have been [ __ ]
going to be asked with it a lot of the time, man.
But yeah, I'd rather just work
[ __ ] seven days a [ __ ] month, not
have the [ __ ] responsibility. You
know what I mean?
No, I didn't because I had it for three years.
So, I didn't think it was ever going to
happen. The longer it went on, the more
I didn't think it was going to happen.
So, the worst thing was when I was
living there and I thought they could
just come out of nowhere cuz I was
always expecting them to come. But then
after I was like, "Ah,
maybe they lost the case or something."
But I didn't think it was going to end well.
So the matter if it was wrong, if you
find a loot car and you find any way to
make money which which won't end you in
prison, do it. It might not be it might
not be technically legal, but you can't
go to prison for it.
So I mean, if you can find a loophole in
the system to get more money,
anyone's going to do that. Who the [ __ ]
isn't going to do that? Come on, let's
be real. Doesn't matter if it was wrong.
[ __ ] what women do is wrong. What
people do is wrong. No one's perfect. So,
doesn't matter, does it? And you would
do it as well if you could do it.
Yeah, I'm not gambling, bro. Been there,
done that one. A t-shirt. I'd rather
save my money.
So, now if I lost, like it would be hard
trying to get the money back as well. I
just I just don't want to waste money.
been there a t-shirt. Yeah. It doesn't
matter if it was Yeah. You would do it
as well. If you could do it, you would
do it. So there's no point saying that.
Like whether it's wrong or it's not
wrong, you would do it as well if you could. So
you would also do it.
I'm sure anyone would, mate.
Especially since it's one of a [ __ ]
once in a lifetime.
But you couldn't end up in prison over
it. So why wouldn't you do it?
why would you do it for three grand a
month? You know what I'm saying?
But it is nice to not have the
responsibility anymore. To be fair, it is nice.
But it's [ __ ] cuz I lost the house and
the people in the house and the food and
that. That's the [ __ ] thing about it.
Weren't even just the money.
It was It was also that as well. That's
the That was the [ __ ] thing about it.
But it's all right anyways. I don't
care. I'm used to it now. Yeah.
So, you would do it if you could. Of
course you would. Of course you [ __ ]
Nah, mate. Nah. Listen, bro. Even if I
wanted to, I could probably, if I really
wanted to, I could have more money than
most of these people on YouTube in a
month if I really wanted to. But I don't
need to, but I'm just chilling. I've got
enough. So, it is what it is.
It's like Timmy, right? I've got more
money than Timmy. When he asked me to
play the money game, I don't play it.
He's like, "I'll show £200." I was like,
"Nope, not showing you nothing.
I'm not showing money anymore, bro. Done
with that." You know, I've been there,
done it, won a t-shirt.
So, I will never show money ever again,
whether people have it or don't. Never
ever am I showing money ever again, bro. [ __ ] that.
I'll leave people to their self-p
projecting games. Simple. So yeah,
the money's not going to last.
The money's not going to last, bro.
You're going to you're going to have a
big loss at some point. Not that I want
it to happen, but it will happen.
It will happen when you have a you know
where you have a big loss again. Yeah,
you'll have a big loss again, matey. Yeah,
then you'll be crying.
That's what I'm saying. It's not That's
not sustainable. Gambling's not
That's not sustainable, mate. Gambling
cuz you never um
you're never stable with gambling.
That's the thing.
You're never stable with gambling.
So that's why it's just pointless
really. He's just never stable with it, you know.
Yeah. But it will be though. You'll lose
all your money one day.
Don't say it like it can't happen cuz it
will happen one day. You will lose a lot
of [ __ ] money. Yeah. Yeah, man.
So, you're telling me you wouldn't do
the house thing if you could? Joe, don't
be a silly goose. Of course you would. you know,
haven't even heard about it to be fair.
Making myself a nice cup of [ __ ] and
taking a couple of cocoa.
How does that feel, Joe?
I'm surprised you gamble when you have to work.
You know what? Generally, I swear I had
a few different jobs in my life. Yeah.
When I used to gamble crazy. Yeah. Like
when I was younger, as soon as I had to
work for the money, I'd be like, "Nah, I
don't want to like gamble." Cuz
I feel like I worked for the money. It
was so hard to get that money. In fact,
now it's so hard to get money. I don't
want to be out of work. I'd rather like
put it toward another holiday or
something, you know?
It's just I just wouldn't want to. No, I honestly like
if you work, you know, you save money
and [ __ ] and you go on a night out and
you want to go casino with 150. Okay,
that's different, you know, very rarely.
But I mean, you saying like online and [ __ ]
I think if I was ever going to gamble on
anything again. Yeah.
I would say, yeah, but I can afford to
lose it. I mean, I could gamble £300
right now and and I'd lose and lose and
I'd still be okay. Still get £100 a week
extra than what I'm getting. So, I mean,
I I could lose 300 pound technically be
all right, but I wouldn't want to do it. So,
it's not going to affect my life, but
I could lose 150, 300,
but I just don't see the point in it.
To be fair, if I do gamble,
the only thing I would want to gamble,
honestly, is a football.
I want to do Darlington and Kitty Min again
cuz I put 120 on two teams that would
turn back 380. That was a nice win.
And slow as well. Slow was a Slow is a
good one to bet on.
>> Yeah, SL was a good one to bet on. [Music] Um
I feel like Yeah. Like you know that
day, Joe. Yeah. When I went to the
bookies, it was actually my mom's
birthday the Tuesday. I thought, "Let me
do a football bet. We do 160, lost 40 on
the roulette, then put 120 on the
games." But I wish I put the whole 160
on the [ __ ] game now. It would have
been like over 500 pound.
That was the last time I
gambled like that. I think
cuz I went out and I was kind of a bit
low on money.
By low, I think I had like 300 pound
left until like the next week. I was
getting money. It would have been over a
thousand miles. I need to try and recoup.
I need to uh
try and recoup some of the money I spent
back on that Sunday. I spent a lot of
money on that Sunday, bro. So, I would
have been [ __ ]
No, I [ __ ] don't. What the [ __ ] Is
that what you really think?
Who lives in Colchester and Swindon? I
don't know anyone that lives there.
No, I don't, man. I've always been good
with the both teams to score.
See, I put £500 on it, but I can't I'm
not risking£500, bro. I can't I can't risk £500.
I wouldn't want to risk £500.
No, I honestly don't. The slow one. Yeah, but
when are they? No. So, I was going to,
like I said, I was going to do football
on Saturday, but I just didn't want to
lose the money. Huh.
Don't know what women are from
Colchester or Swindon.
Don't know any women that are from there.
Nah, bro. I don't know what you're talking about. No, no,
no. Not at all. Not at all. No,
no. Don't know any woman from Cambridge.
I don't know what you're talking about, matey. No,
but I don't know why you show your
pension because you can't you don't even
have access to your pension.
Name me two cities you've never been to
in England that you want to go.
Mine's Blackpool and Glasgow.
I'm going to go to one of them New
Year's Eve. Or maybe I'll go Leeds New
Year's Eve even though I've already been
to Leeds. No, it's either Leeds or
Glasgow. I think
I'm going to go either Leeds Glasgow or
New Year's Eve.
Saying that though, Liverpool would be
good as well.
So, how many two cities you've never
been to here that you want to go?
It doesn't matter, bro. You I get more
than that. I get more than 1,200 pound a month and
I've got more than that now. So it
doesn't matter does it?
So it doesn't [ __ ] matter, mate. I I
don't I've actually seen your I have
actually seen what you're you're putting
up there, but I don't really understand
your whole point of it. I mean
I don't understand the whole point.
I don't like I don't understand what's
your whole point, you know?
What's up? So, tell me two places you've
never been. Tell me.
Bro, a lot of people on here.
Yeah, but the thing is a lot of people
on here asking though. That's the thing.
Bro, listen. Let me tell you a story. Yeah. bro.
Yeah, it might have been two cities in
England that I've Yeah, in England. Has
to be in England.
Yo, the thing is
a lot of people on here asking,
"I bet you've never been to Sheffield.
I bet you've never been to Brighton and Sheffield."
Oh, Sheffield is class, man.
Sheffield is class. I like Sheffield.
It's one of my favorites, I think. Sheffield. Um,
yeah, I like Sheffield. And
you've never been Brighton or Sheffield?
I know you haven't. H
with your dad at your age.
Okay. You haven't been to Brighton. [Applause]
The only two I've not been to is
Glasgow and Blackport. They're the only
two I've not been. [Music] B boy
scoot in the bed. [ __ ] with [ __ ] no
bed, no money in it. [Music] [Laughter]
Let me see.
What did you say? It was an unbelievable night.
Is this on your channel now? Oh, bless you. very different. Let's see.
Still waiting for the post.
Oh, really? That's nice.
That's nice, bro. [Applause] Okay. Okay.
Okay. You got me.
No, I believed you went to Sheffield,
just not with your dad.
Okay. Okay, you got me.
Yeah, but Joe, I have been all over the
country. You do know that, huh?
You do realize that like I've I have
been all over the country, though. I
mean, everyone knows that. I believe you
went there, but I just didn't think you
went with your dad. Okay. Yeah.
You know what I might do? I was just
thinking about this. Yeah. Before you
post this thing, I'm going to start
gambling on the football again.
What I'm going to do, yeah, is is a
National League playing for a whole month. Here's
what I'm going to do. Yeah,
not this week or next week. I'm going to
start betting on like the both teams to
score and I'm going to try and get one
every week for a month.
That's what I'm going to do. I'm going
to try and get one every week for a month.
That'll be ace, bro. You know, I got I
got I got um I've had a 3-w weekek run
with the both teams to score. You know
that, Joe. Both teams to score. I've had
a I've had a good run on that. Yeah.
Want to start with like 180.
Yeah, that's what I'm going to do. I'm
going to do 180. If it wins next week,
If it loses, take a break. wins again 180.
Do you know when it when it first
started the football right? I got it
twice. I got it two times. I got it two
80 to 280 then 80 to 230. I got it twice. Bro,
I'm going to try and get it every week
for a month. Then
I'll be [ __ ] loaded
and no responsibilities. Yay.
It' be good. Yeah, man.
I can't believe I put 120 on two teams,
Joe. I was kind of [ __ ] myself to be fair
cuz like I know like a lot of people
don't do that. And like the literally it
didn't look like it was going to win.
Then 10 minutes in the second half they
in the second half they just all scored.
I was like thank [ __ ]
Yeah, it was good, man.
I'm going to try it. But yeah, try I
might I'll probably just start with
maybe like 150 or 180.
Try and get it at least three times in a row.
He's [ __ ] rich, man. So, yeah.
What I was thinking of doing, Joe, is
like you could even like put like a
hundred on it and then if it wins, just
lump it all on the next week.
I mean, you could do something like that as well.
Yeah. And it's something about winning a
football bet as well. It's like cuz you
pick the teams.
You actually pick the teams. But the
problem with the football is you're very
like, how do I say it? Like with
football, you're limited. It's just one
bet. Whereas on roulette, right, you
could put £400 and do £70 spins and you
could win thousands. Whereas a football
bet, you're limited to that one bet that
you put on.
That's the only problem with it. But
football is is fair in it. So obviously
it's fair. I've won them. I've lost them. So
the roulette isn't fair.
Yeah, it was 380. I won 380 from 120.
even though it wasn't a lot. I mean,
it's just when I lost the house as well,
so I needed to build some money back up.
Went out the Sunday when I met that
Finnish woman. It was [ __ ] expensive.
So, I'm going to try and win some footballs.
But obviously, I'm not addicted to
gambling, am I?
I'm obviously not addicted to gambling
like you and Timmy. Yeah.
You and Timmy are addicts, fella.
That's what you two are. You're addicted, man.
So yeah, we're going to try and uh
try and win on the football. I think
just for a bit of fun, you know,
and obviously if it loses then we have
to stop. But if it wins and we'll just
keep doing the same bet every week.
150 150 150 150 150. It's simple. Or 180 180 180
and that's it. Yeah.
Ain't the National League supposed to be
playing [ __ ] don't they play Tuesdays anymore?
I only bet bet bet bet bet bet bet bet
bet bet bet bet bet bet bet bet bet bet
bet bet bet on the national league.
The others are too hard to predict.
Do you know what it is though? Yeah.
I've lost so much in the past. Yeah. And
the mood swings it's gave me. I just
don't want to do it anymore.
That's why I stay away from the
roulette. Even when I had a house, I was
doing it like every two months, every 3 months.
I would do it rarely and even then I'd lose. So
I mean do you do you do you think you
would still do it if you won like a h 100red grand?
Do you think if you won like a 100 grand
or a million you'd still do it or nah?
The thing is like I don't want to stress
about [ __ ] money. I don't want to
lose money and have to stress about
money and then have to stress about
[ __ ] women at the same [ __ ] time.
You know what I'm saying? Like that's the thing.
That's why I'm like don't want to do it, you know?
So if you won 400K, you would never gamble again.
You watch the Sidemen, don't you, Joe? I
watch the Sidemen hideand-seek videos.
They gamble, but I don't Well, one of
them gamles, which I don't understand
why they gamble because if you're
[ __ ] a millionaire, why would you
gamble? It don't make no sense. You
wouldn't get no buzz cuz you're a
millionaire. But there are people that
do do it though.
[ __ ] Wayne Rooney used to [ __ ]
gamble in the [ __ ] Manchester casinos. Remember?
I think I just do it cuz they do it, but
you wouldn't get a buzz out of it.
The thing is he if he was a millionaire
you wouldn't though because you'd get
nothing out of it.
It's like playing a game, right? And and
winning fake money. You you get nothing
out of it. There's no buzz. You know,
see me and you, we're not rich. It
doesn't matter who has money, right? It
doesn't matter who has money, more
money, right? But we're not rich. So
when we win, it's like, "Oh, we won money."
Whereas if you're a millionaire, you
don't. You're a [ __ ] millionaire. So
it's like you're not going to get the
same buzz from winning money that you
already have. You understand?
So we're we're [ __ ] That's why. You
know what I'm saying?
We're not millionaires. That's the whole
point of it is we don't know how much
we're going to win.
Yeah. Exactly. Exactly. We do it to win
money. I do it to win money. You know,
when I did used to do it, I done it on I
done it on that Tuesday cuz I needed to
win money cuz I was running a bit low
cuz I spent a lot of money on Sunday. Of
course, you do it for the money. So, if
you're a millionaire, you wouldn't get
anything out of it because you're a millionaire. So,
if you're set for life, you're set for
life in it. So,
of course you do it for the money.
Of course you do it for the money.
Why else would you do it? You know,
so I'm going to do that football thing
and see if I can try and build some money up.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. But
obviously if you was a millionaire, you
wouldn't get that buzz. You wouldn't get
that feeling if you was a millionaire.
Do you know what I'm saying? If you was
a millionaire, money is no problem. So
that's So therefore, you wouldn't
gamble. Do you know what I mean? Yeah.
That's that's exactly what of course
that's the that's the thing.
It's like when I used to go out, right?
I tell you like when I used to go out
if I if I when I used to go out
approaching, right, and I used to deal
with [ __ ] from these [ __ ] women,
right? And at the end of the at the end
of the night, I'd go to the casino,
right? And I'd win money. I'd be like,
"Oh, well, you went out and you won
money. If you didn't go out, you would
have had fun and you wouldn't have won money.
So you would have been indoors, no fun,
and you wouldn't have won money. So I
mean, you won money. So I mean, you
can't complain. And that would just stop
the whole complaining about it because
you want money in it. Get an escort, you
wake up to 50 notes, that's the end of
it. Simple. So So yeah. So yeah,
but yeah, you don't get you wouldn't get
no buzz if you was a millionaire.
You know what? Yeah, I think millionaires Yeah.
they don't enjoy they enjoy life more
than us. But you know the thing is is
that the whole fun about life is in a
way the stress about money. You know
trying to get money to do what you want
that costs that and these things cost a
lot of money. So when you are able to
afford things that cost a lot of money,
it's something to look forward to. It's
something that you've achieved. Whereas
if you're a millionaire and money is no
object, I guess you would just get bored
of it, isn't it? Like imagine that just
being a millionaire. You just get bored
of it, bro. Even though yeah, you'd live
in a mansion and you obviously like but
I mean like there'd never ever be that
stressful money which is the part is a
part of it. You know, I know what I'm
saying, bro. Like, I know this [ __ ]
You know what I mean?
Surprised you've never been to Asperers
Casino, Joe, in Stratford, where I used to live.
There's a casino called Aspers. Big casino.
You know Aspers?
You ever been
in the shopping mall in Westfield? Yeah.
You ever been there or
the only thing you need to be careful of
in London is getting your [ __ ] phone snatched.
Don't believe all the things you hear
about, oh, you're going to get stabbed and nah. Um,
the only thing you need to be careful of
is [ __ ] getting your phone snatched.
Seriously, I think that's the only to be
honest with you, I'd rather get stabbed
than get my [ __ ] phone snatched. To
be honest with you, bro, you don't know
a lot of the [ __ ] you lose on that
phone. Trust me, it ain't good. I think
I probably would rather get stabbed as
long as it wasn't as long as it wasn't brutal.
I think I'd rather get stabbed, bro. I'm
not even joking.
Cuz you don't understand. Like when you
lose your phone, you lose everything on
your phone. Like I remember exactly when
my phone got snatched.
I lost everything on that [ __ ] phone, bro.
Like everything. And I had money coming
in from the casino. I was waiting on
some money from the casino.
Yeah, it is. Yeah, there's an Asper.
There's Naspers in Newcastle as well.
Yeah, I've seen it when I went
Newcastle, but I was waiting money from
the casino. I didn't know if they can
get into my bank. I didn't know if they
can get into Bro, I'd rather have been
stabbed to be honest. I'm not even joking.
It's a big thing losing your phone, bro.
It is a big thing. I couldn't I didn't
do iCloud. I didn't have iCloud. I was
on Samsung. I I didn't back anything up.
Then it was a stress of, oh, I need to
buy a new phone now. What can I get
back? I lost everything on that phone, bro.
So, yeah, I'd rather get stabbed, bro,
than someone steal my phone.
Cuz your phone is your life, bro. Like,
all them contacts you got, it's your life, man.
Why do you think when the police share
come that day, um, when I was living at
the old house, I put my phone in the
garden, they weren't getting that phone,
bro. They was I was not going to let
them get that phone because they weren't
going to give the phone back and then I
would have just lost everything.
So then I need to It was the stress of
getting a new phone. What have I lost?
What can I get back? You know what I'm
saying? It's [ __ ] bro. Trust me, losing
your phone is [ __ ] So yeah,
that's why I put the phone in the garden
that time they come, bro. Even though I
weren't expecting them for me, I just
weren't going to let them take my phone. Simple.
cuz they don't give your phone back.
They've took my devices before and
they've not gave it back. iPad, a phone.
So, I would have never got that phone
back, which is this phone here. Well, obviously
cuz I had money coming from a casino. I
had my bank details on there. I think I
only had about £800, but I was waiting
for money from the casino.
How much were I waiting for? I think I
was waiting for £800.
I won some money in the casino. I
remember I was waiting for money online
and then [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] comes and
[ __ ] snatches my phone up my [ __ ]
hand, bro. I was on Snapchat as well.
That's why I'm always careful now like
with my phone.
It is that bad. It is bad
with roulette. It's bad.
It is bad with roulette. What's it is?
But yeah, it was bad. It was bad.
It was almost as bad as the USA. Is he stress Joe?
Oh, do you remember that little story?
That little towel.
Oh, bless you,
Grezy. There's still some lamb left.
You're more than welcome to come.
>> Yeah, you're more than welcome to come
over for some lamb.
No, come back, Joe. Don't leave me. Oh, cheers.
A lamb sandwich.
I've never heard of that one before.
Do you like my little copycat video, Grezy?
the lamb sandwich. You don't really put
lamb in a sandwich, lad.
That lamb was lovely, though.
See, I've never had a mom that starved
me. I've always had a mom that fed me. Did I?
My mom's never starved me.
It's so weird cuz Greavvesy doesn't
gamble, do you, Grievy? I don't gamble.
Greavvesy don't gamble.
Peter Belly can't get attached anymore
because he's already found his mama.
He's already found his mama.
Jesus Christ, bro.
Where I come out with these things I
shall never touch. Is he found his mama?
That's [ __ ] mad, is it? I wonder
who's been who was behind that account. Griezy.
Do you remember Grievy? Nah. Peter
Belly, you've got to go out. You can't
let these [ __ ] women win.
You remember Grievy? You can't let these
[ __ ] women win.
That is funny, bro.
Let them hunting women win.
Oh, it's funny. Yeah, they're just
egging me on it, Grezy.
Oh, Franklin's in his little car.
[ __ ] lamb cost me 36 [ __ ] quid. Imagine
that Grooy [ __ ]
36 quid there. Right, I'm gone.
Be back tomorrow, maybe.