H. So, why? Hold
on. Why is it showing I'm leftanded? What?
There we go. I don't know what the [ __ ]
bro. I don't know why. Yeah, but it's showing. Oh
[ __ ] It's actually showing the other
side, which is a bit strange.
I think on my front camera looks good. Let's
see. Front camera. Yeah, the front one
looks normal. The other one, but yeah, I thought [ __ ]
it. Go out and give it a whirl. Why not,
mate? I [ __ ]
would. Think to myself, I would. And I
did. So, yeah. I've got the old shorts
on as well, so I'm uh limited to where I
can go, but why the [ __ ] not?
I'm going to send it to but we're just
doing a strip down the street to
see is working in the or in in the but
on the streets better than the
bus should be so
bit I'm not trying to spend more on 40 quid
That's the whole point of
it. They're probably down
to I just really fancy the bell. [Music]
Never have too many numbers. Never have
Mate, it's worth a
while. We're going to down this now.
Yeah, I ate earlier, but I don't think
it was enough to actually fill the stomach,
man. But we'll see. Anyways, you
ready? It's kind of right. It is kind of
at the top. Done. [ __ ] [ __ ] Oh
me. That was almost a full one as well.
Right on to the next one.
[ __ ] No, I had a burger and some hot
wings. I should be all right until later.
Yeah, it's worth a while, man. It's
while. Definitely worth a
[ __ ] Don't there's anyone in the pub.
There's not. No.
Trying to see if there's any ones in the pub. There's
not. So, these are just going to be straight ones.
You know that's 10 pound just going on
this 10 quid just going on this that's a
madness to stick together today to be
Uh hopefully we spend about
4050. Thank you, boss. Thank you.
She looks all right. Kind of.
Um, have a proper look.
No, she's not really that nice. I was
going to do her, but she ain't that nice.
Wow. I've got people looking at me
because of you [ __ ] [ __ ] mate. I
swear down. Yeah, wait a little bit,
mate. Wait a little bit. Trust me, we'll
start getting busy around part five and
I'll just send Oh, send the mate. Trust
me. We can't rely on just you and I'm doing that super
mustache. No, when I do this, bro, when
I look back here and I put my I'm I'm
thinking of sending I'm thinking of
approach the old beard, you know.
Next one, I'm definitely happen to, you
know, I'm definitely happen to
um get some tissue. Yeah,
man. Yes. Hope I spend more than
4050 today in the street and froction
cuz I was [ __ ] bored staying there,
man. There was something I was going to
send, but I just couldn't
bother. Oh, look at Peter Belly looking
handsome with his beard. I style my hair
myself. I think there's one here actually. Yeah, [Music]
boy. Perks are not working, eh? Perks
are not working. Look at this as well,
bro. You just put your feet up like
that. Lovely. Look at that. You can't
What? What more could you ask for?
chilling with your feet up and a nice
Guinness. Like, what more could you
actually ask for in
life? What more like could you actually ask for,
bro? There's nothing more you could
actually ask for in life.
Man, this is the life, man.
eight's got me in the mood for the
[ __ ] Guinnesses to [ __ ]
can go on
about I could I could stay here all day, you
know. I could stay here all [ __ ] day,
bro. I swear down. Just straight up
chilling. Yeah, man. In the shorts, in
trainers, living a life, man. No
working. Just sat over a nice little
Guinness. This is the life, man. Feel
like being on an island, you
know. Someone's left some food there,
but I'm not going to eat
it. He doesn't know what pub I'm in. So,
good luck with that
one. Just don't pissed. Well, he doesn't
know what pub I'm in.
Good with that one, buddy. Yep.
Yeah. Thank you, bro. I got this when I
was in Liverpool.
I got it when I was in Liverpool back a
couple of years ago and first time I've
won it in years. Well, won it a few
times like the past few
weeks. But uh
yeah, nope. And I've got no anxiety
whatsoever. So, keep trying,
buddy. Yeah. This is going to be a
street approaching session today.
No bars, no clubs, just straight on the
street, bro. Straight on the
street. Not done like this for ages. So, yeah. Yeah,
man. Going to be ace, bro. Going to be
[ __ ] hard though. Said I was going to
get three numbers, but [ __ ] who
knows. It's going to just be street.
It's just going to be on the street. cuz
I want to like do a full on street
session. Nah, man. I'm solo today. I'd
rather do it by myself. I might meet my friend on
Saturday. Yeah, I might meet my friend on Saturday, man. Um,
yeah, maybe. I just want to do solo
today. I ain't even got my passport with
me cuz I'm just going to be doing on the
street. Not going into no places, no nothing.
And it will get busy. As long as it
don't stop long as it don't start
[ __ ] raining, we'll be sweet,
man. We'll be sweet. Hopefully I get
Well, we'll get
numbers. How many? I don't know
about Yeah, it's going to be a
madness. Yeah, you're better off doing
it. So, no. If I go out three times a
week, two days, I like to do it solo.
Don't know why this guy's looking at me,
but the [ __ ] Um, two days I like to do
solo and then one day I like to be with someone.
Yeah, because it's fun to just go out with people. I
mean, [ __ ] man. living the
life. No, definitely not. He doesn't
know what pub I'm
in. He doesn't know what pub I'm
in. So, good luck with that one,
man. Yeah, good luck with
that. This is my second one. So the aim
is to spend no more than
about I look nervous. I don't look
nervous one little bit. There's not one
bit of anxiety in me, bro.
Nervous? No, I don't look
nervous. Definitely definitely
not. You might be nervous in your house,
but I'm definitely not
nervous. Not one little bit nervous.
I've been a drinking
[ __ ] Where's my nails? Bye-bye now.
[ __ ] everyone fancies me,
bro. How you doing, man?
Good. You all
right? Just straight up ignore
me. People are very unsocial. Bit weird
awkward. Hopefully we don't get up in the water today. But
yeah, welcome to England. But we have to
make the most of it off, you
know, she just literally just looked at
me like straight. I
swear it's made it awkward.
I know, but they're nasty, isn't
it? That's what people like, bro. It
It's England. It's London. What's
London? They're rude. I'm the only
Londoner. That's not rude. Why people
assume I'm not from here, man? You know
what I'm saying?
Yeah. I've been bothering no for years,
bro. We're going to see some hardcore
street action, bro. What's the time?
424. So, we still got a while to go
before start getting busy on the
streets. Yeah, I'm sending it, bro. And
shorts and everything.
Yeah, got my feet
up. Just tried to start a combo with someone. He
uh he didn't take it very
lightly. This is my second one. I down the first one. Yeah. [Laughter] Yeah. Yep.
So, we're going to stay here for a little
bit now. I'm not showing you around, but
we got too many glasses on this community, unfortunately. But, um,
yeah. So, we're just going to stay here
for a little
bit. Yeah. Too many glasses on this community sadly.
It is a good
bruiser. What I'm probably going to do
is I'm probably going to go live, stay
live for a little
longer. Probably like half hour and then
[ __ ] just start fending it in the
pub. [ __ ] it. Yeah, just start in the
pub and then go out on the
street. Yeah, man. I should do pubs pub
tours around my home city. I'll do a
I'll do a pub craw, but not pubs pubs
I've not been before.
Yeah, pubs I've not been to before
though cuz of um these
grass. People are looking at me. People
Uh try I'll talk to someone in a minute. One sec. [Music]
People are not very social,
bro. But what on my main channel? I
can't put a live stream on my main
channel, bro. You know it's [ __ ] I
can't go live on
it. I need a vape, man. I feel like vaping, man.
Yeah, we will do in a minute,
bro. Everyone's on their phone. Crazy. Everyone's so
untouchable. Oh, bro. Cuz I just down
one before that.
Yeah, it just reminded me about second.
Damn. That's the [ __ ] second one as
well. All right. So, third one. So, this
will be 50 will get us now. Oh, [ __ ] me.
take my [ __ ]
up. Need another gu. I don't really like
them two. I would like, but I don't
really like them
too. But them two over there. They're
worth a while. Them two are definitely
Guinness, man. You good? Can I Guinness,
please? [ __ ] weather's gone [ __ ] again,
bro. Two weeks ago, I was out from 11
till 12:00 at night. 11 um 11:00 in the
morning till 12:00 at night cuz the
weather was so nice. Now it's [ __ ]
[ __ ] bro. Yeah. Hopefully we get a summer. Hopefully.
Last April was cold though. say that,
but last April was
Yeah. Good, buddy.
There we go. The third one out. 15 pound on goodnesses.
Close up my [ __ ] chair.
all that. No, no, I'm not spending more than 50
quid. It's my little spot,
mate. Not all day and all night, bro.
It's been 15 I think it's about 156
pound I've already spent on Guinness.
[ __ ] hell, bro. I need to make money
on YouTube, bro. I'm not [ __ ] rich. I
wish I was [ __ ] rich, bro. I'm not. What's
up? Do I drink? Nah, bro. Not [Music]
really. I don't have the cash on me.
I would be, but I ain't got no cash on me,
bro. I don't I don't carry cash from me
for that exact reason. Because of that,
because of that
reason. I'm not playing Frankie. We're
just getting on the Guinnesses today and
we're sending street approaches. That's
it, bro. That's got to
wait. I'm [ __ ] wavy, bro. [ __ ]
I have to make sure this don't [ __ ]
spit on me,
bro. Oh, face of a nod. Sometimes call
yourself that, man. You're just chilling
here having a Guinness and you're
calling yourself a nod. That's not nice,
man. No good for the old mental
health. No, I'm not going down, bro. [ __ ] that.
How you doing, man? You all right?
I'm trying to like socialize with
people, but they don't really want to
socialize with Peter Belly.
Why don't they want to socialize with
Peter Belly, man? It's crazy. England
just is a lost society, bro. It's actually
England is a uh lost cyber 81. [Music]
Yes. I told Are they for you? Both them drinks,
brother. Are they both? Yeah, they both for you.
Yeah, that's what I'm asking you.
That's not nice, is it, man?
Yeah, it is. And I'm going to keep Yeah,
I'm going to keep it up on the chair as well. Wow. Ah,
that's crazy, man.
I was only short on conversation, man.
Yeah. You're from Scotland? Yeah.
And And you know what? Every time I've
in Scotland, they've been so friendly, man.
Okay. Thanks very much.
Enjoy your drink, man. Okay. Um, crazy. Oops.
yeah, I got completely
put that in the fish and frenzy, but I
don't know what any cast point is to be
fair. How did he come on? Shut up, man.
You're behind your keyboard and you're writing
stuff. I not put my feet up. Well, I
want one. How do I count? What?
No. Okay. 80%.
Um, people outside.
I just toilet, man. One
sec. I need to go piss,
bro. That guy didn't owe me. What the
[ __ ] I said I'll put my feet up where I
want. That's what I said to him. What?
How did he own me, bro? What the [ __ ] I
didn't I couldn't believe his attitude.
Like, bro, I stood where I am. I'm
staying where I am. I'm not moving. I
didn't think I pissed. What do you want
me to do? Start cussing off his mom and
offer him outside? Bro, I said, he's
like, "Oh, you I said, I'll put my feet
where I want." Yeah, it's my country.
You know what I'm saying? The
[ __ ] This will do some of you people
good sometimes. Yeah. Go out, have a cup of
Guinnesses. Even though people are
complete [ __ ] but I mean it's fine,
man. Yeah. How did he own me? What the [ __ ]
I said I put my feet where I want. I do
what I want when I [ __ ] want. And I'm
going back there as well. I told him,
mate, rewind back, bro.
Yeah. Leave it, man. If he wants to be
pissed off, leave him, bro. I don't need
to start fighting people in the middle
of the [ __ ] pub. And this is the same
pub I met
Tam. He's like, "Oh, like I'm put my
feet up because I want to." But I'm
going back to that same spot,
too. One second. I need to piss, bro.
That's another thing about beer. It
makes you have pissed,
brother. Yes, it does,
bro. Oh my god, bro.
See what trouble we can get up to today.
Ladies never get mugged off. Bro, you mad.
Yeah, he's just being a dick, man. Just leave
him. If you come up to me, he will know
what time it
is. I said, I'll put my feet where I
want, mate. I'm putting on the chair. Yeah. So
what? We're going back to that same spot
as well, bro.
And do you know what? I always used to
big up Scottish people for being
friendly as well, but that just No, he's a [ __ ] man.
People better not be on my spot. I don't
know. There we
go. All right. 79%
guys. It is 4:00 now. We'll have a few
more here and then we'll be move on.
Third one 167 on now.
It's going to hit you when you bro and
the wind hits you. It's going to just
you. Then it's going to hit you.
What we saying? 20 on
Frankie. Where's the news? I told you. That's pointless.
It's I think it's in the actual train station.
Yep. No, it's just a weather spoon.
Maybe a sneaky tender. Yeah, it could
do. I'm trying to find out where the
nearest cut point is. I don't know where
the nearest cut point is.
Yeah, he did. But he
ain't but that's why I'm still
here. I don't know where the nearest cast point is.
Um I think it's down the road. Would it
worth it though?
I'm going to put 20 pound in it. I'll
it. I'll put 20 in it,
bro. And that's it. Cuz we're going to
be spending about
£30. Budget a little
bit. All right. I'll end the live and
I'll go back live. The 20 I'll stick in the machine.
20. I'm not doing more than 20 pound.
[ __ ] that. Okay, man. Be right back,
bro. What do you mean let him get away with it,
bro? I told him I'm leaving my feet
there. I'm not moving my feet. Flapping
it in public. How do I flop it in
public? I stayed in the same
place. I said to him, well, I said, I'll
keep I said, I'll put my feet where I
want. What the [ __ ] I told him, I'll
put my feet where I want to put my feet.
That's what I said. Flapping it. I
stayed in the same spot and I'm going
back to the same spot. Yeah, if he come
up to me, he would have known what time
it was, isn't it? He didn't put it on
me. [ __ ] off. Hey, I'll be back live
anyways with a 20 pound and thank you.
Here you go, man. Big up. He didn't put
it on me, bro. He was just a dick. And I
told him about himself. [ __ ] off, man.
If he comes anywhere near me, he will
know what time it is. That's why he left
the pub and I'm not. And I'm coming
back. [ __ ] Scottish prick. Anyways,
be back. One sec. Give me the money out.