Come on, Vid.
Let's be having you.
I need to sort my [ __ ] sleeping
pattern out for real.
Really, really do.
need to be um sort my sleeping pattern out
cuz it is [ __ ]
So, I just had to do a video when I woke
up about how these people here think
that everyone's got the same life as them.
It's strange, man. Expecting some thumbs
up to be fair, but I didn't get any. Why not?
They generally do though think everyone
lives the same life as them. They think
their life goes for everyone else's.
Timmy because he's a virgin. Everyone
else is is a virgin apparently. Even
though I proved I've had sex.
[ __ ] other people being skinn trying
to say that I'm skin. They think
everyone's got the same life as them. It's insane. Oh, Franklin,
you're going to die in a minute if you
crash a car.
I was on Reddit yesterday reading this
thing and it's like these people, they
seriously don't have no life experience, do they?
Proper fantasists. It's a hookup
culture. They say a hookup [ __ ]
culture. Jesus Christ, that's interesting.
Can't even [ __ ] get laid. Can't even
get a [ __ ] kiss, let alone a [ __ ]
relationship. Jesus Christ. These people
are liars on Reddit.
They are [ __ ] liars.
They're definitely taking a piss.
Definitely definitely taking a piss. Oh [ __ ] [Music]
So, we need to change the name of this
community anyways, man. Not a gambling
community. It's a self-p projecting
community. That's what it is.
It's a self-projecting community. It's
not a gambling community. No one even
puts up gambling videos up. No one puts
videos up anymore. So, yeah, it's not a
it's not a gambling community. It's a
talk about yourself community.
That's what it is.
Where people talk about themselves. Yeah. Literally,
cuz they come out with the most specific
random things, which how would they
possibly know this? Again, like I said
on the video, it's because they're
talking about their own lives, their own
existence, their own reality,
skin, ugly, no friends. I mean they are
to be fair they are sat on YouTube from
the time they wake up to the time they
go to bed. Now I'm not sure millionaires
would be doing this you know I'm not
sure millionaires um I never said I'm
leaving and I I can leave whenever I
want to leave. I've already took weeks
off of YouTube.
So it's like I don't need I don't need
to prove anything to you people anymore.
So that's the thing. Um you know it's
just a community Joe. We're going to
change the name of this community. Yeah.
Um it's a self-p projecting community.
It's not a gambling community. It's just
a bunch of losers that talk about
themselves. Don't know if you watched um
my video. Oh yeah, Joe. I won £500 on
roulette by the way. I finally got the money. Yeah.
Yeah. I put 100 on roulette. I got to
like over 500 pound. But to be fair, I
didn't think they were going to give the
money to be honest. I didn't think they
were going to give the money
because I went on the reviews. Yeah,
listen to this. I went on the reviews
and people were saying how they weren't
getting paid, how they've been scammed,
how like that the site owes them money
and [ __ ] where it's not UK regulated.
I'm not going to lie, I was a bit anxious.
I was like, "Oh no, I really kind of
need that 500 pound." You know what I'm
saying? Like obviously obviously it's my
money in it. So,
um, I hit 8112
and, yeah, just took the [ __ ] money,
but I didn't think I was going to get it
to be honest because of the reviews.
This is why you should never read
reviews. I know that now. I learned my lesson.
And the reviews were bad, bro.
Saying how they didn't get paid. And
yeah, it was quite worrying to be honest.
That's why you can never read reviews
whether it's restaurants, whether it's
nightclubs, whether it's casinos because um
but I got the money in the end. I've
never not been paid. Like then I was I
was telling my mom about this as well,
but then you need to think you've never
not been paid. So what's the chances now
you're just not going to get paid? Why
don't you bother online? For what reason?
I mean I tell you oh I tell you what
annoyed me. Yeah about this. So I g So I
gambled. I won. I withdrew. Then a day
later 25 hours later they reversed the
withdrawal. I said what the [ __ ] are you
doing? And then I had to send them a
bank statement and then they after the
bank statement and they just like
processed it. But it's still bad because
the way I see it is, yeah, if they let
you gamble, they should give you your
money. It doesn't matter. Like they let
you on the site, what they should do is
they should if they let you gamble, any
money you you win, you don't need to
verify your details. And then if they
really want you to verify, then then
they can [ __ ] you know, they can
stop you depositing until you verify
yourself. I think that's fair. To be
honest, I don't think they should let
you deposit and then as soon as you win,
want to know this, want to know that,
you know? It's [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
You You let the person deposit, they've
won money, give them the money. Simple. So,
I have to show them a [ __ ] bank
statement as well on my online banking.
It's [ __ ] madness, bro.
But if you was to lose [ __ ] £5,000,
it'd be a Okay. So,
but online's not the only thing. Casinos
are dodgy as well. They'll do anything
to get out of paying someone.
So, it's not just online. It's actual
it's landbased casinos, too. They'll do
anything and everything to try to get
out of paying people.
And they and they can void tickets as
well. To be honest with you, bro, I
don't think I'd ever go to a real life
casino, even if I could, cuz they can
actually void your tickets, which I
didn't even know that until they voided
my [ __ ] money. I was trying to win
back. So, I don't think I would ever go
to um a casino again.
They're dodgy. D I'd say they're more
dodgy than online, to be honest, in
terms of paying people. So
yeah, they just they'll just use any
excuse not to. It's the same with
landbased casinos. The only places you
get paid out fairly is
bookies and [ __ ] arcades. They're the
only place that will pay you out fairly
as quick as you put in. So,
but they do it in real life casinos as
well. I'll never forget that time in
Nottingham when I was with Ant-Man for
£350 [ __ ] pound.
What the [ __ ] bro? They were They was
like, "Oh, you got anything with your
name on it?" No, no. I was like, "What the fuck?" So,
it's not just online, bro. It's also landbased casinos.
And that excuse like, "Oh, yeah. Um, you
said something about the manager's kids.
That's just an excuse. It's an excuse.
It's an excuse. is an excuse, you know. So,
so yeah, it's not just online.
It is not just online, matey. going outside.
Don't ask me why, but I am stay Wednesday. Yeah.
deal with the same [ __ ] on Saturday,
won't we, Joe?
Deal with the same bollocks. I mean, I
really don't want to go out drinking,
but I kind of have to. So, it'd be rude
not to with this haircut, would it?
It'd be rude not to mate. [Music] I'm drinking Yeah, man.
So, I was just on Reddit.
These people make me laugh. All women
want is sex.
That's funny, bro. If only that was
true, eh? If only that was true. Yeah. Jesus Christ.
All women want is sex. Wow.
I was speaking to this guy yesterday.
He's 24. He's never held anyone's hand.
kissed anyone. He's never had sex. And I
said, "Our situation is basically just
it's almost as bad as each other really
because although I might have had stuff,
it's the effort that I put in to get
this shit." You know, like I said, I got
10 numbers on Friday, only one replied
and then they stopped replying. So, I
mean, it's demotivating, isn't it? It
really, really is like demotivating.
and he was saying about um
how like he's had chances to be in
relationships but you know he was too
[ __ ] and I was like oh yeah I've had
the same but you know this was years ago
now the game is actually dead like you
will never ever meet anyone now like
this is why it doesn't even really
bother me anymore I don't really care
because I know
what it is I know I've tried and yeah
and it literally team will never change.
So, I mean, [ __ ] hell.
His is bad because he's almost 24 and
he's never had anything with a woman.
Mine's bad is cuz the amount of effort
that I put in to get what I got. So, yeah.
So, they're both really bad. Really, if
you think about it, I should have a date this week.
Yeah. I should have a [ __ ] date this
week. For all the approaches I [ __ ]
done, all the numbers that I got, I
should have a [ __ ] date. Wow. [Music]
It is a madness, isn't it?
We got some money as well. We could
easily go on a nice lovely date. But nope.
Like I said, that is just demotivating.
The fact that you could potentially get
[ __ ] 10 numbers and not one of them
replies back or one of them replies back
and then stops replying.
It's like that. What motivation would
that possibly give someone to go out and
do it again?
Do you know what I'm saying? What motivation would
that give someone, you know? But like I
said, I'll be out on Saturday cuz So,
I'll be out on Saturday now.
Now, I said I was going to go out the
next week on a Wednesday,
like drink on a Wednesday, but I am just
going to wait until my birthday I think
after Saturday cuz Yeah,
I think I've been out on a Wednesday. I
have been out on a Wednesday twice actually
when that whole USA Izzy thing happened
when I won money at the casino. Yeah, I
think I have actually Wednesday. Yeah.
But yeah, man.
But then people on Reddit don't know
what they're talking about. How women
only want sex. Bro, you you can't even
get a kiss out of someone nowadays, let
alone [ __ ] sex, let alone a [ __ ] relationship.
But I think I've accepted it now anyways
to be honest.
10 numbers only one reply. Jesus [ __ ]
Christ. Should have a [ __ ] date this
Should have a date this week.
I need to follow up with some of them
numbers to be honest.
It's so bad.
It really really is bad. But yeah,
this is [ __ ] disgusting. Yeah. So,
that's where we're at basically.
I won't even get an escort on Saturday
to be honest. Nah, that experience has
put me off, you know.
That experience honestly just put me off, bro.
So, I'll just I would it would just be
going for the drink
to be fair.
Unless Vigy comes back to London or
something, I won't bother. It's just put me off.
Um, but yeah, it will just be the drink on Saturday
and the approach and then that's it. Yep.
I don't want to be spending more than £80.
I do not want to be spending more than £80.
And yeah, obviously I won't get sex cuz
I won't use the escort, but that's fine
by me. I just won't have sex. I think
I'm used to it now. So, it is what it is.
It's like what [ __ ] when [ __ ] tries
to tell people that they can't get laid
when he's the one with somebody with
[ __ ] a black [ __ ] [ __ ] He sounds
like a [ __ ] He sounds like a sexy
frustrated 10year-old, doesn't he? You know,
he really does. Yeah, bro. I hope he
keeps me blocked forever.
Forever and always. I hope he keeps me
blocked, bro. I really do. Cuz I'll
never ever be his friend again.
Little [ __ ] snake.
Know what I'm saying?
Hate that [ __ ] bro. I really do hate that bastard.
My [ __ ] back is hurting, man. Ow.
Oh. back. Oh, [Music]
like I said, I'll be outside. [Music]
Yeah, that's what happens when you sleep
in too long, man. Your [ __ ] back starts hurting.
Sit up straight.
Don't know why Joe come on if he was
just going to leave
that [ __ ] money. Mike needs a slap, don't he?
Little white knicky geeky little nerd.
He never say anything to anyone's face.
Never. It's the same with that [ __ ]
Ricky Billingon. These little white weak
[ __ ] beta males. Yeah. Would never
say anything to anyone's face. But the
keyboard gives them power. Madness. [ __ ] madness. Really is.
I'd love to go and [ __ ] him up, bro. I
swear to God I would. I'm not even
joking. I hate these people on here,
bro. I [ __ ] hate these sick, twisted
people. You really don't understand.
Well, a lot of them anyways.
But we all know how the cookie crumbles, bro.
You go to Birmingham, they don't show up,
you come back, they start their [ __ ]
again. Same thing as when you show them
money. We know this now. We know what
these people do on here. You know, been
[ __ ] doing it [ __ ] years, you
know. It's the same with the money game.
You show them money, they all run away,
wait for you to put the money back in
the bank, and then go, "You skin again."
Same old [ __ ] with these people.
He's a freaky guy, bro. I told him,
"Come to London. I'm out on Saturday
anyway. So, I'll be in access to
anywhere in London to be honest.
Same with that Ricky Mill. Same with
that nons. Have you noticed that they're
all the same? All white, all weak, all
beta males. Give us [ __ ] white people
a bad name, bro. They actually do. They
give us white people a bad name.
Like, you should see this guy in real
life. This money guy, he's about 5 foot
tall, too, bro. He's about 5 foot tall.
He's nothing to look at, bro. He's so
He's some [ __ ] [ __ ] with gorilla
tits. I'm not even joking.
Look, you know what I'm saying, bro?
[ __ ] these people in here are [ __ ] lad.
They ain't got no life. Seriously, bro. Serious.
I got 50 to last me until I get my pip.
Is this guy all right, bro?
Thinks he knows people's lives. cuz
that's his own life. It's just self- projecting, bro.
Same thing as Lord J. It's just self projection.
New Balance trainers, jeans, hoodie,
which cost no more than about £250.
Bro, it's just self projection.
That's all these people do on here. They
think their life goes through everyone else's.
And let's be fair, they call people
skint, but they're sat on YouTube from
the time they wake up to the time they
go to bed obsessing over content.
You know, they ain't got no life. Partly
because they're skint. That's why they
go on about skin cuz they are skint. No,
I'm not joining that [ __ ] [ __ ]
panel. I'm I'm done with these [ __ ]
because I said what I said the other
day. I said, "If I don't retaliate to
these people and they keep going on
about me, obsessing me, stalking me, it
shows them to be the jealous ones and
everything I'm saying about them is
right and everything they're saying
about me is wrong because they keep
doing it." Now, the reason I saw that
Money Mike's comment is because um
the short popped up so I just clicked on
the short and read the comment. But
yeah, I am done with these mongos. These
little self-p projected mongos.
I [ __ ] Well, I am [ __ ] dumb.
Yeah, he's different. Yeah, he's You know,
I only just started talking about that. So,
and ask yourself the question, why they
on YouTube from the time they wake up to
the time they go to bed? It's cuz
they're skin. It's obvious. Put two and
two together. Why do you think they call
people skin every day, bro? Because they are themselves.
I had [ __ ] Timmy calling me a virgin
[ __ ] early hours in the morning. Self projection.
[ __ ] hell. When are these people
going to stop talking about themselves?
You know, it's mad.
These people literally live for YouTube.
Like I go live and talk a bit [ __ ]
Yeah. Cuz it's funny.
But these people literally live for
YouTube from the time they wake up to
the time they go to bed. How mad is that?
Like I said, I'm out Saturday. Yeah, man.
It's all projection here.
you know, [ __ ] the six grand, bro. I
showed Timmy money like back in
I think it was was it February or March?
I can't remember the exact month. But
anyways, I showed him money and when I
showed them money, he ran away. They
want you to show them money so they run
away again. It's [ __ ] stupid.
They just want you to show them money
just so they can run away like they
always do. What's the [ __ ] point?
What's the [ __ ] point? Yeah, tell him
to come on my live.
Tell him to come on my live, bro. He's
not blocked. Tell him to come on my live
and I tell him about himself and here
[ __ ] gorilla tits. Yeah, man.
Just a regular season. Uh,
no, man. My sleeping patterns [ __ ] up.
No, bro. My sleeping pattern is just
[ __ ] To be fair,
I ordered a bagel um the other morning
4:00. It cost me £17.
I know. I was so hungry. But, you know,
I'm out on Saturday though. And then
that's it until my birthday I think.
Cuz I mean it's demotivating isn't it
Joe? You know getting 10 numbers and
only one replying and then you
suggesting to meet up and then they
don't. I mean
I mean people said oh I should have been
annoyed. I mean yeah but I mean I'm used
to it now. Of all people I'm used to
this [ __ ] So what's there to get
annoyed about? It would always be the
same in this country. So I mean that's it.
It would always be the same in this
country. Even though it's like
demotivated and [ __ ] I mean, like I
said, I'm only going out on Saturday
because I've already had my hair done.
So, I I I lose nothing by going out and
spending 8020. What do I lose? Nothing
really. So, but if if I hadn't had my
haircut and that, I'd be done for
another like 6 weeks. Well, I'd be out
on my birthday, but apart from that,
it'd be six weeks. about six weeks me. Yeah,
you know, it is it is [ __ ] up. It is
But like I said, I'm used to it. So,
like I said, it will never change in this country.
But you get these people on Reddit that
say women only want sex. Joe, they're
fantasists. They go on like getting laid
is easy but getting a relationship
isn't. I mean anything is everything is
hard. Relationship, a friendship, you're
not going to get anything no matter what you want.
And they still they're still suggesting
dating apps when them dating apps have been dead
[ __ ] for years. Them dating apps have
been dead for [ __ ] years. And I can
safely say that because I've actually
met people on dating apps. So, I can
actually say that
because the dating apps are dead
because if it was me, that's the
problem. I've met people on dating apps
before, so at least I was able to meet
them. Now, I can't meet them. So,
obviously, it's [ __ ] I don't care
anyways about this, bro. I'm going out
on Saturday. I would have done what I've
had to do for a month and that's it. Simple.
That roulette win was nice. Oh my god. I
wasn't expecting to win 500 pound. I was
expecting to just lose the 100.
So anyways, back to the topic. Why um
why don't you bother with online
when the casinos are just as dodgy?
Them [ __ ] do anything to try to
not pay you out. They do anything and
everything. And don't forget they can
void the ticket. That just put me off,
bro. That just put me right off.
And the Nottingham one as well before
I'd even said that stuff about the
[ __ ] managers kids. It's dodgy. All
of it's dodgy.
Bookies and arcades and maybe like the
pub machines are the only one you you're
going to get paid out fairly.
It is all dodgy.
All of it. It's not just online.
And the thing is with online, they
actually paid me like 20 times before
asking me to verify in golden bet. So
trust me, casinos are just as dodgy as online.
just as dodgy, mate.
I don't know why I gamble to be honest.
I don't even like gambling anymore. I
just thought [ __ ] it.
[ __ ] going out is so expensive now as well.
Jesus Christ. I spend about if I spend
120 150 Saturday, I'll be happy. But it
can't be another four 500 pound weekend
because then I'm not going to be able to
save. It can't be another [ __ ] four or 500
cuz that's what it seems to be.
But I doubt it though.
It's [ __ ] It is expensive. It is
going out nowadays. [ __ ] man.
[ __ ] £400 on [ __ ] what?
To get 10 numbers and not one single date. [ __ ] me. Oh man.
Just getting in a little bed [ __ ] with
no bench, no money in.
I got banned on Reddit, Joe.
They need the power.
Without the power, these mods are nothing.
They're [ __ ] nothing without the power. Oh, Franklin,
what happened here? You been dead.
I'm going to have another burger later.
Not wasting them yummy burgers.
I had to get from the hal butchers
because the mint from the normal
butchers breaks. So
Oh, funny enough, one of the tenants
could have it then, couldn't they? Cuz
it's it's allow it.
So, like I said, I would just meet them
this week. It wasn't for me having my
haircut. I would have just met them and
just got some food with them or something. But
yeah, I'm not wasting this haircut,
mate. It cost me a lot of money, so
Oh, dear me. [ __ ] Franklin,
did you listen to um Virgin Boy thing? I
watched it the other day. I hate to uh
agree with him, but he is right about
the Netherlands. Of course, I I know I'm
right, mate, because I've been to the
Netherlands before you. So, I know
there's nicer places than Amsterdam.
You know, obviously I'm [ __ ] right.
I'm Sam's nowhere near the one of the
nicest place in Netherlands. [ __ ] me.
Nice country, nice people. It's just I'm like so
don't think I have ever met a rude Dutch person.
No, don't think so.
So, we'll see what this Saturday has in
store for us. Eh,
see if we can recover nicely.
Last week was Friday. This week's going
to be Saturday.
How we do next week? But again, I need
to say, buddy,
so hard to be wasting it.
which I could do it if I weren't leaving
the country. I could do it, you know, go
out every week, no problem. But I need
to put money by for like, you know what
I mean? So yeah, basically
Look at these motorways, man.
Them Reddit mods need the power.
I'm going [ __ ] insane, lad.
I'm not going out Friday. I'm going out Saturday.
I went out Friday last week. So, this
week's going to be Saturday. And I was
going to do Wednesday, the week after
that. Just change the days. But I need
to be saving money. I can't afford to be
wasting money [ __ ] drinking in this
[ __ ] country cuz I'm leaving so I
can't be doing that. But yeah,
I mean I think I'm just doing it for the
sake of doing it. I have no hope. There
is no hope. I'm doing it just for the
sake of doing it.
If 10 if you got 10 numbers and only one
reply then you haven't got a single date
this week. It tells you everything you
need to know in this country. So I mean
I've got no hope that
this week is going to be any different
cuz it's always the same.
So and it will always be the same.
Bad is it?
It is bad.
It's [ __ ] depressing, bro. Yeah.
do a football bet Saturday as well.
What do you think's going to happen?
What do you think will happen if I went
to Waxies on Friday? I went to Waxies
last Friday. There was hardly anyone in
there. Just a [ __ ] cockfest. basically.
And then if I stay in that pub, then I
can't go anywhere else.
But I could try there. I could stay
there. But I'd want to try the place I
place that I go.
I mean, I could I don't know.
[ __ ] knows, man. [ __ ] knows.
Don't think I've ever stayed there. It's not very
love to go out bottoms, but they don't
let you in in Traxxy bottoms
to be honest.
I don't know.
I'm going to be wearing trainers this
time in case I have to walk back.
You know, I had to walk back in shoes.
Oh, [ __ ] me up. Um,
maybe I could try there.
I don't know. I might go that area for
my birthday actually. I might go thingy
for my birthday. That area actually to
be fair. That's where they do the bagels in it.
So go to waxes. [Music]
None of them because it's never happened them.
You know, waxes is expensive. Wax is
£780 a pint.
But to be honest with you, you're only
going to be spending like what? £50 there.
If you think about it, £50 80. Yeah.
And we go to the pub as well.
What you want? What you're wanting what
you're wanting to do is
I don't know.
I have wanted to stay in maxis before,
but I always just [ __ ] end up going somewhere else
and it's trying to get into the other
places later. It's hard. So, I don't know.
Oh, he went to my door. He's not about
anything. He came on my door. He He came
on my door, stood behind the gate, and
done nothing. He is not about anything.
And why are you talking about that? I
thought we don't talk about the past.
Isn't that funny? You always You people
always say that you don't talk about the
past, but all you talk about is the past.
We're talking about what I'm doing on Saturday.
We're not talking about someone that
come to London and done absolutely nothing.
See, it's funny how you bring up the
past when it suits yourself, but then
when I tell you about me showing you
people money and you running away, it
doesn't count because it's the past.
That's how you know you're kind of
wasting your time in this bias
community. This is what makes me think
like I can back up what I say. This is
why I think that people are jealous of
me, you know, when I say these things.
Yeah, I I can back up what I'm saying.
Like I really really can. Like I don't
say what I saying and then and then
block people. I back up everything that
I say. You know,
that's what makes me think like you you
part of this is jealousy as well. You
know what I mean?
generally do think that. Generally, [Music]
cuz do you not think it's a bit odd how
I've got so many middle-aged people
obsessed with me?
You don't think that's a bit strange?
And the biasness as well like um I was
saying that virgin boy skin in the bed
suit with absolutely no bed and no money
in it and he says, "Oh well, he show
money." And I was like, "Hold on. When
this [ __ ] sat there calling me a virgin,
even though I've proved I had sex,
why haven't you um backed me up?"
And I've actually proved I had sex. So,
this is what I mean by it's like that's
what pop that's what makes me think it's jealousy. So yeah,
that L is not about nothing.
Not about anything in the slightest. So Saturday. Yeah.
what I'm doing, bro. I don't know what
I'm doing. Well, I think I'm going to be
out all day Saturday, to be fair.
I'm just going to be out all [ __ ] day.
Like, I'm going to be out all day. All day, bro.
Cuz that will be it until my birthday said. Uh,
so it's all right once you've already
had your hair done and stuff, but if you
haven't had your hair done and have to
go barbers and wait around and sit in
the [ __ ] chair for [ __ ] over an
hour, boring as [ __ ] you know?
So, we'll start. Yeah.
But to be fair, I could kind of go to
waxies and and get in at a late time to be honest.
So, we could sort of try that. We could
try and do a little bit of both, but
it's the country bounces that we got a
problem with. That's the thing. So, but
we'll try our best to do both.
cuz we can go there and then go to
waxies, but we can't
but we can't. We can go there and then
go to waxies, but we can't go waxies and
go there. That's going to be the
problem. So, we'll try and do a little
bit of both.
I'll try and do the best I can. But the
thing is, I don't want to like start
going to nightclubs and spending £200
and [ __ ] I can't justify it anymore.
Uh, that's what I used to do when I used
to go traveling. I used to do that.
I used to do that when I went traveling.
When I used to go traveling, I used to
get the haircut the day before because
when when I'd go to different cities and
I'd get my haircut, it would take up
like a lot of the day
cuz I'd have to go to barbers way and
then it would just be like it would take
a lot of the day time of the day. So, I
used to get the my haircut the day before.
So, no, I don't. Yeah, in the future
I'll do that. But my hair's good now. It
was only done last week.
I could still smell the nice barber
smell me for like four days, you know.
It was worth the 50 pound to be fair.
I look smack on [ __ ]
Friday and I don't even have a date this
week, Joe. It's disgusting, isn't it?
It honestly is disgusting, isn't it?
The more you try, the more you lose hope.
Simple, is it?
Yeah, just like this Saturday is not
going to be no different.
But you I'll probably get replies this
time. That was just to be honest with
you, it doesn't really matter whether
they reply or they don't reply. They're
not meeting you. So, I mean, I had one
that replied, but
yeah, it's it's always going to be the
same old here. So,
what's there to do, eh?
There'll be no escorts on Saturday
either because yeah, I don't want to I
just don't want to do that for a very
long time. No thanks.
Not after that.
[ __ ] that, bro. So, yeah.
What makes me laugh, Joe, is how people
think it's going to change. How they
think that like one day you're going to
go out and it's all going to be different.
It's mad, isn't it? They actually think
that one day you're going to go out and
it's not going to happen anymore.
It's funny, bro. It is funny. Yeah, man.
You will never change.
Hey Joe, they're just not interested in this country.
Have you seen how stuck up people look
as well, Joe? Like when you go out,
everyone looks up their own ass. I've
noticed it like when I've been on trains
and stuff, they all look like NPCs.
How do I know uh it won't be different? Um,
how do I know it won't be different? H um
I don't know. How do I know it won't be different?
maybe the fact that I don't know, maybe
last week wasn't any different. Maybe
the past four, five years it's not been
any different. It's always been the same
thing every single time you've gone out.
Maybe that's why. Same as if West Ham
was to lose a game,
you know, five years in a row, they're
kind of going to lose the next time they
go out, the next time they play, not go
out, play. I mean, the fact that it's
been the same for 5 years.
So, I don't think it's all of a sudden
going to change now. It's literally
always going to be the same thing here,
but because I want to go out and drink
anyways. I mean, people probably told me
5 years ago how I couldn't see the
future. And here we are 5 years later
and it's still the same.
It's still the same old [ __ ]
People saying they have boyfriends when
they don't. People giving you their
numbers, leading you on, taking a piss
out of you. It's never none of these
things are never not going to happen.
So, I mean, if some if nothing's changed
in five years, I think that pretty much
dictates your future.
And it's not about just a boyfriend
thing. It's not even just about that.
It's about um the whole even when when
they do reply, it's not just about that.
It's them leading you on, taking a piss.
It's never going to change. Cuz my my
question to you is why hasn't it
already? And I don't think that that can
that can be answered because I'm right
in what I'm saying. If there if it was
going to change, why hasn't it already
changed? Bear in mind, I've tried more
than 99% of people in the world. So, I
think if there was a change that was
going to happen, it would have already
changed by now. But it hasn't.
So, whilst I'm out, I will try because
I'm out and I'm drinking. But like I
said, other than that, I won't be out
until my birthday when I'm going to go
out with my sister on my birthday
and that's it. I mean,
you kind of have to try. You're out
drinking, you know? It's like,
it's like there's nothing else to do.
Even though there is no hope,
there's nothing else to do. I mean,
there is no [ __ ] hope
because you would have found someone by now.
You know, there's not one single
football team in the world that's got
their ass whooped for five years, you know.
So that's the way you got to look at it.
If there was going to be a change, why
hasn't it already changed? And it's not
even just about that. I mean, I put up
with enough [ __ ] with them,
you know, them saying they're going to
meet, they don't meet, you know, just
the [ __ ] that they've been doing for
[ __ ] years, you know? I've already
put up with enough [ __ ] you know? So,
and and another thing to another way to
answer your question as well is that um
I should be on a date this week. There's
no reason why I'm not on a date this
week. I got 10 numbers and about 50
approaches. One replied.
So, I mean that in itself just tells you
how it's not going to change cuz I mean
you haven't even got a date this week.
Not even one date out of [ __ ] 10
numbers and all of them approaches. I
mean, why would you then think the next
time you go out is going to be any different?
It's not It's never going to change.
Things don't just change like that, you know?
I mean, the thing is I should Well, I
mean, I looked my best. I looked maxed.
I had a woman on the train say to me,
she was an not old old but she was maybe
like in her 40s. She said, "Oh, you look
nice." And do you know how rare that is
in London and I went out looks Maxon
smell Maxon couldn't even get a date for
this week. I mean it doesn't it doesn't
give you much hope does it really? Come
on. I mean, here's the thing, Joe. If
you didn't look your best,
um, and then you got maybe, you know,
I don't know, five numbers, then, uh,
maybe. Or, you know, if you looked your
best and you got three numbers, then
well, it's only three people. I mean,
who knows the next time you're going to
go out. But it's the fact that you
looked your best, you done your best,
and you got 10 numbers
that tells me everything I need to know.
you know, like it's it's not one or the
other, it's both. That's the concerning
thing. Um, you look, if you can't even
look your if you can look your best and
get 10 numbers and not even get a date, then
yeah, I don't think there's much hope in
this country. And that was a one-off, by
the way. I've probably not done
something like that in about 8 months.
So, that was it's not it wasn't a normal
Friday. No, I didn't like her, but you
get the point. I looked more than okay.
I smelt more than okay. I got enough
numbers. I don't even have a date. So,
what more am I supposed to do?
It's expensive. I spent, you know, I
paid the barber a lot of money.
Um, expensive after shave, all that
trying and nothing to show for it. I
don't think Saturday is going to be any
different. I really really don't you know
I mean I'm not being picky. All of these
women looked completely different.
You know some of them were fours, some
of them were sixes, some of them were
sevens and they're just not interested
in this. It's like what Ant-Man says. I
think he's got it bang on the money that
they're not interested in this country.
Because if you think about it, right,
two or three different people's
experiences in this country, you know,
and you can't even you can't even get
anyone. So, I think he's bang on the
money. As ridiculous as it sounds, it
does sound hilarious, but every every
woman in the country is the same.
They're all on TikTok. They're all on
Instagram. It's It is true. It generally
generally is true that they aren't
interested in this country. He's right.
He's so right. Cuz I'm talking from my
experiences as well.
They seem very dismissive
before you even finish what you even say. So yeah,
it's mad, isn't it? Even if I got a
date, yeah, this week and it never went
anywhere, I'd be happy with that, you
know? I would have been, okay, well, I
kind of got something back. But I got
literally [ __ ] all
out of them 10 numbers. It's mad.
And then women will be going on multiple
dates a month, but none of these guys
are good enough for them. It's mad,
isn't it? It really, really is mad. I
could throttle lady sometimes, you know.
I could actually strangle her for having
me um in this generation.
I could sometimes just strangle her.
Like you know how Homer strangles Bart.
Should have had me in the 70s, man.
Why the [ __ ] did you have me in this
[ __ ] [ __ ] up? I feel sorry for my um you know
nieces and nephew to be fair. They're
going to be [ __ ] when they're my age.
They're going to be really [ __ ]
Dating, cost a living. Oh, good luck to
them. Hopefully I won't be around to see
it to be honest.
Just like when I saw this little baby on
the bus the other day when I was coming
back from the cinema, I was just like,
"Oh, poor poor little baby. So innocent,
so cute. Bless him. He doesn't know what
what's in store for him in 20 years.
Bless him, you know, cuz they don't, you
know, it's this generation is [ __ ]
dating [ __ ] cost of [ __ ] living
[ __ ] it's just [ __ ] horrendous you know
that's why people leave England for a better life
depression here man
people work they have no money by you
know by the end of the month when they
get paid you can't get laid you can't
get into a relationship. You know what's
what's keeping someone in this country
really? You know,
it's [ __ ] up.
And that's why I think I won the £500. I
think God felt sorry for me.
But I don't know how many times God is
going to do this until you [ __ ] get the hint.
That's what I tell myself. You know, how
many times is God going to do this until
you get the hint,
you know? He's he's even done this with
the football as well.
Cuz that Sunday I went out and met that
[ __ ] Finnish [ __ ] [ __ ] cost me a
load of money as well, you know? So it's
like I don't God is like literally
giving still giving you chances to leave
quicker than you you know you need to. I
generally feel like there is God doing it.
I'm not religious but it is telling you
something because to put cuz I spent about4500
um you know Friday to Sunday and I'm
thinking like he even used to do it with
the [ __ ] casinos as well. It's God
telling you to [ __ ] leave,
you know? That's literally what it it's
telling you, you know? Okay, you spent
money, but we're going to give you your
money back and some more money on top of
it. Now leave.
That's that's what it's literally telling you.
That's a lot of money to spend over a
[ __ ] weekend. £400 considering I
wasn't gambling either. Don't know where
it went to be honest, but
it won't be different this Saturday. How
How much was that? How much was the
pints and leaves by the way?
I bet they weren't £7 [ __ ] 80, were they?
To be fair, if you go to this uh
nightclub from Sunday to Friday, you can
get like bottles and they're like £3
each, which is dirt cheap in London. £3
for a [ __ ] bottle of beer in in a
nightclub in London. That's cheap.
That is [ __ ] cheap. £3 in like that
is cheap, trust me. But in this wax
place, it's £780. So,
well, just generally.
So, so what's the most you want to spend
on a night out? Just drinking them. I
would say if I spend £80, no more,
that's a good night.
I I'm talking about just drinking.
If I spend £80, that's I feel like I
could justify it. Yeah. £80. Okay. Yeah.
But I feel like any more than that
becomes a bit dodge. And I'm talking
just drinking. I'm talking just
drinking. I'm not talking gambling
because that's different.
But I've spent some serious money before just drinking. Yeah.
I remember when I went out with the army
lads, I spent £250.
I spent £2 fucking50 quid, bro. I'm not
even joking. We just went clubs and
[ __ ] Just drinking. I was just drinking as well. So
that's another thing that comes with the
dating is the expense of it.
How I've not gone broke, I shall never
know. How I've not gone broke. Honestly,
how I have not gone broke, God only
knows. To be honest with you,
I think every single time I've gone out, I've gambled.
I've gambled and
I've gambled and [ __ ] um I've just
won sorry I've won money back that I've
spent like when I put that 120 on the
two teams. I won 380 and £100 to the
500. And to be honest, with this casino,
there was no fees when they um they
charged me to deposit, but then when I withdrew,
there was no fees. So,
but honestly, yeah,
landbased casinos are exactly the same.
The only place you get paid out fairly
is bookies and arcades. They're the only
place you get paid out fairly, honestly.
I told you about that time in
Nottingham. Do you remember when I went
to Nottingham with Ant-Man
when I stayed for two days and I got a [ __ ] [ __ ]
Do you remember? Like I wasn't banned at
that point and what they were asking me
to take out £350 was a [ __ ] madness.
I put 200 in, ended up [ __ ] getting
it to 350 after like 40 minutes. And
then they'll say, "Oh, have you got
anything with your name on it?" No, no,
no, no, no. So, it's all dodgy.
It's all [ __ ] dodgy. Trust me. It's
not just online.
[ __ ] asking for a million things for
350 [ __ ] pounds. You know what I'm saying?
But yeah, bookies, you'd always get your money. Um,
that's how it should be. You should get
paid out just as fast as you put in. That's it.
Like I said, don't don't forget they can
actually void your ticket as well, which
is they void my ticket. So that's the
last I went in the casino and I was like £500 in.
So they can actually void your ticket.
So it's just not worth it. You know when
you say about it's not worth the stress
of gambling, do you know what makes the
stress even worse? Well, when people say
it's not worth the stress of gambling,
do you know what? Do you know what the
you know when you was basically saying
about how the gambling stress is not as
bad as some other stress? Well, let me
tell you what stress is. Is not knowing
if you're going to get your money or not.
That's like a big part of the stress.
Not knowing that you if you're going to
get your money or not.
That's like half of the [ __ ] stress.
like with a football bet, you know,
you're going to get paid, but in a
casino or online casino or you just, you
know, you always think, "Okay, this is
going to be the time I don't get paid out." So,
this site is not a UK regulated site,
but they people were saying how they
didn't get paid,
but they paid me. So,
but it's like even
Yeah, but even a hippodrome when I went
hip drone casino in London, they could
they voided my ticket.
So, it's dodgy. So, I still lost money.
So, it's dodgy. It's all dodgy.
All of it is dodgy.
But yeah, at least you know you can go
and spin dog because I've tried it and I
won and they paid me. So
if they didn't pay me, bro, I would have
just went to the bookies and smashed up
with a hammer. Even though the bookies
like it's not them that didn't pay me,
but it's the whole fact of like it's the same industry.
Trust me, if I didn't get that £500,
bro, I would have been going back. I
would have been going and smashing the place up.
[ __ ] that, bro.
That is [ __ ] You know, I would have
smashed the bookies up obviously.
So what? You don't think landbased
casinos are dodgy when it's to do with
[ __ ] paying people out?
They are dodgy as [ __ ]
I might go Nottingham one day again.
But then again, it's trying to get the
money. That's the thing. That's always
going to be the thing cuz it's a walk in
the casino, right? But then it's trying
to get the money.
And if they don't pay me the money, I'm
going to smash the place up. Simple. So,
it's just not worth it.
Well, they voided my ticket. I remember
the last time I went to a casino, they
voided my ticket.
They definitely voided my ticket.
So, the fact that they can do that and
stuff cuz I said stuff about the
manager's kids, it's like it's Yeah,
because I said stuff about the manager's
kids. So, what happened was I went in
and I think I was like four or 500 pound
in, but obviously I was still up. like I
still got the last laugh out of them and
they just wouldn't um
they just voided the ticket. I tried to
give it to this American guy to cash in
and he said it's void. He brought it
back. It was void. They actually voided
the actual ticket.
You know the ticket that you print. So
they can actually void your ticket from
the m from the machine.
It doesn't matter bro. It doesn't
matter. You still want money. They have
to pay you out. end of simple. So, and
it doesn't matter the fact even like the
thing in Nottingham when I tried to get
the £350, they were asking me, "Oh, have
you got anything with your name on it?"
No, no, no. I said, "It's a walking
casino. You let me in." And I wasn't
banned at that time either. So, I'm
thinking, why am I going to show you
something with my name on it when you
let me walk in? I'm not banned. And
what? For £350? Really? I don't know if
you've ever been to that casino in
Nottingham. It's called um
uh I think it's called Alla or
something. I can't remember. It's a priv
I think it's a private casino anyways. But yeah,
I could probably go back into one of them casinos
because I shouldn't have to. I shouldn't
have to do it. for £350.
And I remember No, no, no, no, no, no. I
think I I I remember before. No, I did
get the last laugh last because the last
casino I went to was a casino called Horizons
and they let me in. Right. This is the
last one I went in. Um and cuz they
banned me from all the rest of them. And
um I think I was £400 in and I got it to
£1,200. I was down to my last £60. Not
like money I had but money I put in. I
was down to my last 60 pound. No word of
a lie bro. I got it to 1200 pound. I
think it was 1,100 or 1200 and I literally bro,
oh have you got anything? I said no pay
me now. So they paid me and then when I
tried to go back um face recognition
didn't let me. So in the end I did get
the last half to be fair
because I think that's the last casino I went in
and I hit 11 with my last like 60 pound
and that and yeah
happy days then never got into one again
after that. So I'll never be able to go
to a casino ever again unless I went abroad. So that's it.
Which I don't miss the gambling to be
honest. I mean, you're
you're a [ __ ] addict.
I've seen your [ __ ]
[ __ ] on your channel, Joe. You are
actually an addict, fella.
You an addict, fella. You know, like I
I'm not I would never gamble like that ever again.
I only really do it when I actually need
the extra money. Not need the extra
money, but could do with the extra money.
And that way it just makes more sense me
doing it, you know,
cuz you gamble like [ __ ] mad.
You gamble like every day. I could
gamble right now if I've got the money
to do it, but I just wouldn't want to
lose and then have to try to get the
money back and then have the stress with
women. It's just not worth it. I've
already got enough stresses in my life.
I don't need [ __ ] gambling as another
one, you know? So that's why I just
packed it in.
I do the 10 pound football bet on Saturday. But yeah,
I was thinking of going to Miami next
year, but that's where that [ __ ] is now,
is it? And I actually really just want
to go on holiday. I don't want to like
go and do anything to anyone or start [ __ ]
But that's where they are. So, I mean,
I don't really want to start [ __ ] bro.
I actually just want like a holiday,
another holiday. But they just happen to
be there as well.
And then it makes it will make me look
like a copycat.
Yeah. Well, you're going to um you're
going to lose, bro. You will lose.
So, but but I was actually thinking, you
know, next um next summer,
you know, but
Hi, man. I'm just chilling.
You ever been out drinking on a
Wednesday, Joe? It's a decent day to go out drinking.
Yeah. So that's why I wouldn't because I
wouldn't be able to help myself and I
would just stick it on them. But I don't
want to do that. I'm not going to pay my
own money to get nicked. I actually want
to go and actually go on holiday.
I am leaving. We're talking about next year,
but like so I just have to go somewhere
else cuz if they're still there, I'm not
going there, bro. [ __ ] that. No way.
Saying that though, I'm not really into
beaches. I'm more into like the city
life to be fair.
But you know the thing is Joe, the best
people you meet is midweek. Like I got a
friend in Manchester. He's from around
here, but he lives in Manchester. I met
him Wednesday. I met my army army
friends on Thursdays.
I think Wednesdays and Thursdays are the
best, you know.
Saturdays there's just too many
[ __ ] But I haven't been out for a
while on a Saturday. So I just do it.
But I don't really like the beach life
saying that. I prefer more the city life.
I don't really like the heat. So
I don't like the heat.
I know I'm weird.
It's my birthday this month. Joe, what
you getting me?
Are you going to send me £100? Cuz you
know that I'm poor nowadays.
I'm poor nowadays, bro. You need to give me £100.
So yeah, I'm not really into like the
beach life to be fair cuz like I don't
really like the I don't really like the
heat. Like I said, my favorite month is April, October. Yeah.
I like December as well.
No, give me £100.
You might as well. Don't be selfish. You know,
I don't need professional help just for
stating facts. 10 numbers, Joe, and not
one date this week. Jesus Christ.
It will never change.
Chlory, I'll be out on um Saturday
looking for that change.
pretty much. Yeah.
Like I said, I I'll leave them to make a
fool of themselves
because if they're still doing videos
obsessing over me and stalking over me,
then they're embarrassing themselves and
they're showing them to be the obsessed,
jealous ones, not me. So,
I ain't even got a date this week.
No, bro. I don't go on the channel and I don't care.
I don't care about these low life people. Yeah. So
Joe, do you want to um do you want to do
a bet for Saturday?
I can tell you exactly what's going to
happen. I don't mind betting.
I think on Saturday
I'm going to I want to I want to do p
pro prediction that the people that I
approach are going to say they've got a boyfriend
and I'm going to get three numbers
and out of them three numbers one replies.
Yeah, I think no four numbers and two
replies. Let's have a bet and then they
just don't meet. Yeah, man.
I know these things, bro. I've been
doing this [ __ ] for years.
Years, lad. Yeah. He wants to meet me
then. He can come to London. And if he
wants to meet me.
Yeah. Come to London. I'll meet you on Saturday.
I'm out Saturday, so I can get to anywhere easy.
Didn't you try to pull in leads? Um, Joe.
Oh, I think I'm going to have another
burger soon. Them burgers were delicious. Yummy.
My mommy bought me some ice cream.
Yeah, but you could always have two Ms. Joe.
So, does your MS give you a [ __ ] or nah.
But some people don't do it.
Does your misses give you a [ __ ]
Sorry to sound personal.
N I've actually lost my sex drive to be
honest with you.
I have actually just lost my sex drive.
I think it's because where it's so
impossible in this country. I mean, you
can't really get one. And then the whole
escort thing and stuff. I think I've
just lost my sex drive to be honest.
I just can't be bothered, bro. I'd
rather just I think I'd rather just be
alone. You know, honestly,
if this is the trouble, it's like what
people say. I was reading some stuff on
Reddit yesterday and a lot of the stuff
was true. was like they'd rather be alone
and you know be a bit bored and lonely
than be miserable whilst trying to date.
And I think that is the truth that that
some of the points they made I think
were bang on the money because it's like
when you're trying to date you're just
miserable because of all of the bad
experiences and yeah so what if you
don't have anyone? Oh well, you know it
is what it is. So that's that's what I
think to be honest. Yeah,
the juice ain't worth the squeeze.
But I, like I said, I'll do Saturday cuz
I got nothing better to do. So
no problem spending 60 80 pound. No
problem at all.
But the thing is, you're saying all of
these things, right? But you're
dismissing all of my struggles, which is
what people on Reddit do. Like, you
dismiss the fact that I try to speak to
people, they pretend they've got a
boyfriend. I arrange to meet with
people, they agree, they don't meet.
They reply. They lead people on on
purpose. See what you do, and a lot of
people on Reddit do do it, to be fair,
is you seem to dismiss people's
struggles and just go on to talk about
something completely different. You
know, Reddit is bad at that as well.
Like, I'll show them like screenshots
where people have actually led me on on
purpose and said they're going to meet
and then all of a sudden they can't get
over their ex and all the [ __ ] that
they do. And they seem to dismiss it all.
like dismissing a K in a case in course in court.
So I mean it's you really do dismiss
things. It's like even when you say
about how you can't predict the future.
If you didn't dismiss all of my
experiences, you would be saying that.
So that's what I find a lot of people do
do. They they dismiss your struggles
literally. It is there's no better word
for it. You are dismissing
my struggles. Yeah.
And like I said, it's not just about
people saying they've got boyfriends.
It's about people giving their numbers
and [ __ ] with you. People seem to
dismiss all of them things.
You can't be wrong all of the time. You
can't have been wrong in every single
one of them text messages.
Like, you could be wrong in some of
them, but you can't be wrong in every
single one of them. So, at the end of
the day, it's like you dismiss people's struggles
and then go on to something completely different. No,
I I just want I just want to spread
awareness on how bad the dating game is
in this country.
And the more you try, the more depressed you become,
cuz the more you lose hope. Obviously,
I'll stomach it for Saturday cuz like I
said, I've had my I've got my hair done.
So, yeah. Look, got my hair done and
[ __ ] So, without my t-shirt, so I don't
mind stomaching it. Um, you know, one
more time and that's it. I'll stomach it
and just see what the score is. That's it.
Still got my beard on as well. So
yeah, change my pillowcase every day. So
I'll just stomach it. Yeah.
Been all right. Would have been all
right going on a date this week.
I don't have my hair like before. I do.
I'll show you what I look like the other
day. I do. One second. Hold up.
This was me the other day. Hold on. This
was me on Friday.
I know it's a video on my other channel.
I had to show people that I was dating
and stuff. This was my hair the other
day. I do have my hair like that. It's
just I've not long woke up. And yeah, so
I had the beard done, the hair done,
and yeah, don't even have a date for
this week. I mean, that warrants some
sort of complaining, doesn't it, bro?
That warrants some complaining on
[ __ ] Reddit for a little bit. And to
be honest with you, what makes me gives
me the motivation to try is because it
gives me it gives me a story for Reddit.
I can come back and then over the
weekend say tried. I told you so. I
tried. You know. So yeah, man. It tells
a great story to be honest.
So yeah, I do have my hair like that. I
had my hair like that [ __ ] the other
day. I look sick.
I look [ __ ] ace, man. But never made a difference. [Music] Madness, isn't it?
You might as well go out with [ __ ] all
over your face.
You probably have more chance of [ __ ] pulling.
Yeah. So, yeah, I do have my hair like that.
Just like in that video. I look I look
smacked on Friday. I look sick.
I even had Jane starting to fancy me again. Joe.
Yeah. And that's how my hair was on Friday.
Yeah. But she was just being a [ __ ] She
was being passive aggressive. Do you not
understand the difference? Yeah. My hair
was like that on Saturday. Friday.
Sorry. Why did I say Saturday? It was
like that on Friday.
Yeah. And she was just being a [ __ ] She
was being passive aggressive. Um, I told
her as well that I'd done the Uber
thing, right? And she seemed to look
down on me. I said, I think I said I
made like 90 pound or£100 in a day,
right? And she was like, "Oh, you're
better than working out." I was like,
"Who do you think you are?" Like
firstly, yeah. Do you know how many
people do this Uber thing like they do
it for like um content? Like there's
there's English people that do it in
London as well. They do this Uber thing
for extra money, £50 or they just do it
because they do it. Like, who is she to
be telling you what you should be
looking like and how much money you
should be making?
Like, it's not something that you say to someone,
you know? It's She seemed to think that
that's why I done what I done to her,
cuz she was being a [ __ ] That's why I
stood her up.
Like, that's why I stood the [ __ ] up.
And I was going to rinse her as well. If
she met me um for the steak, I would
have just walked walked out and left her
with a bill cuz she was actually being a
[ __ ] But she was actually being a [ __ ]
though. That's the thing. Um so
I never said it's a job post, but you
know, I made 90. If you make 90 or £100,
you know, who are you to be telling
they're better than than working for
whatever amount? Who are you to be judging people?
You know, it's just not something that
you say and you shouldn't be telling
people that they need to look like this,
they need to look like that. I was fine
how I was that Sunday. There was nothing
wrong with the way that I looked just
cuz I hadn't been to the barber for a
[ __ ] week or two. Oh, [ __ ] well.
You're not so perfect your [ __ ] self.
You know, you could do do with a [ __ ]
boob job, but you don't see me [ __ ]
saying that, do you? And I didn't even
like her. That's the thing.
So, but yeah, I looked my best anyways
on um Friday. You must have missed it.
You must have not been online. I was
live in the pub and stuff and no difference.
So, I don't have any hope that this
Saturday is going to be different
to be fair.
But yeah, I that's why I like stood her
up cuz she was being a [ __ ]
thinking that she's better than people
when she isn't. So yeah,
but let's not talk about it, please.
It's just annoying.
I don't like talking about them experiences.
She was just being a [ __ ]
Okay, I'll show you. Okay, I'll show you
what I look like on thingy. Hold on. So
you can see better.
All of these things are on my other
channel, but these people can't find me.
Sick, bro. One sec.
[ __ ] bro. I would have just done it
to a random person, you know. One
second. And I'm uploading it now so you
can see proper what I was what like
so you can't blame my looks. You can't
um me not approaching or not trying. So
this Friday, that's why it's so [ __ ]
up to be honest cuz there's not really
See, in the past there was there might
have been some reasons,
you know, oh maybe you didn't look your
best, maybe you didn't send it hard
enough, even though I did, but it could
be debatable for a lot of people, but this [ __ ]
Friday was [ __ ] up, bro. I'll send you it now.
You're telling me that I did not look
the business, bro. One second.
You are telling me I did not look Oh my
god. How do I do this?
Oh, [ __ ] sake. Oh, here.
One second. Let me make sure.
One second. Yeah, let me make sure this
is the right thing I'm sending you. I
want to link you to my other channel.
These little mongos on my [ __ ] Hold on.
How my hair was. Anyways, this is what I
look like. Still didn't get any results.
There you go.
I look sick in that video.
Don't know why it's so fuzzy to be
honest, but it is.
So, I mean, if you can't go out looking
like that and pull it, mate, I don't think [ __ ]
you got much chance to be honest with you. Yeah.
You can even see how good my skin was as well. So,
never made a difference. So, that's why
we probably think we're not going to um
find anyone, Joe, is because even when
you look as good as that, you still
can't get anything.
I got face wax done, face mask done,
I got everything. I got the whole thing
from the barbers cuz I thought, "Fuck
it. Why not? and nothing. Um,
well, no, because I've already explained
this. We've already been over this
personality thing. As soon as you try to
speak to somebody, they say they've got a boyfriend.
As soon as you try to speak to someone,
they're not interested. They literally
dismiss you before they even get to know
you. So, it's not your looks, it's not your personality.
It's got to be them being stuck up. It
has to be that. It has to be too many
stuck up [ __ ] in this country. It's
not a personality issue. It takes time
to get to know someone's personality.
And my personality is completely fine.
My personality is completely fine. I've
got so many friends. You know, I've made
so many friends over the years. There's
nothing wrong with my personality. It's
them and their standards. That's what it
is. It's their unrealistic standards.
It it takes time to get to know someone's personality.
And that's that is facts 100%. Because
you try to speak to someone, it's
straight away I've got a boyfriend. It's
straight away I'm not interested.
Straight away before they even get to
know you. Yeah. Literally, it's them.
Defo them. You know, it literally 100%
is. They don't even give people the
chance. You know, I got 10 numbers. I
got one person that replied. Okay, they
replied. Let's go and do something this
week. Didn't reply.
You know, it's people blame people's
other people for the fact that these
women are stuck up in this country,
which is why I'm leaving. That's the
whole point of why I'm leaving
cuz it is them that are the problem.
It definitely definitely is. There's too
many stuck up [ __ ] in this country. That's it.
And the only reason I'm entertaining it
Saturday is because like I said, I've
already had my head on. I'm going to put
it to good use.
And yeah, that's me done till my
birthday. My birthday's on the 27th. So
that's a that's you know be almost 3
weeks away after Saturday. So yeah.
So they just miss people. I mean this is
part part of the whole dismissing. You
know when you said about ever thought it
could be a personality issue, but it
can't be because I've showed my
approaching videos. That's what I'm
saying. You dismiss stuff that you're
shown and then go on to talk about complete nonsense. You know,
it's nothing to do with personality.
None of them even give people a chance.
So, and you've seen this as well. I
mean, I've shown you videos. It's not
like you haven't seen these videos I put
out there where I've approached people
and then they're just stuck up straight.
I mean, they even sound stuck up. You know,
they don't go for personality. You know,
personality is the biggest excuse that
I've I hear. You know, biggest biggest
excuse. It's not personality.
You were born in the wrong generation.
These women are too stuck up. That's
what it is. It's nothing to do with
people's personality. Cuz if it was
personalities, right, you would be go
you I would be on a date this week. I
would be on a date this week and it
would have been [ __ ] up. If it was
generally a personality issue, you would
be on a date every single week and you'd
be [ __ ] every day up if it was personality.
You don't get to know someone's
personality in five or 10 seconds.
and you know all of this stuff as well.
>> You dismiss people's struggles and
resort to making stuff up. That's what
people do on Reddit, you know,
because it's like a they don't even get
to know your personality and b there's
nothing wrong with my personality just
like all of these other people. You
know, it's always such a dumb excuse
personality. It's the lamest excuse I've
ever heard cuz they don't go for personality.
They [ __ ] haven't for [ __ ]
probably [ __ ] decades to be honest.
It's such a lame excuse. It's I feel
like all of these things are always a
cover up for them. Like this whole oh
they don't owe you anything or oh go to
the gym or oh with your personality it's
always a cover up for the fact of what
they really are. stock up [ __ ]
generally generally generally is just like
and you're saying about oh well if
they're like this why do you want them
but I don't I mean I'm going out
Saturday cuz I've got nothing better to
[ __ ] do there's no hope I'm aware
there's no hope but it's either that or
stay in and I'm going to go out so that's it
and it will be exactly the same as it
was last Friday
but just Saturday this time. So yeah,
let's talk about the [ __ ] you know,
expense of it as well.
[ __ ] sick. And to be honest, I could
probably even look better if I went to
the gym to be honest. But it's not it's
not about that stuff, you know? So yeah,
what to wear
on Saturday? I'm not sure,
but it's not personality at all.
But you would think that. I could
understand why you would think that
because if someone's looking good like
the way I'm looking, you would think
that, oh, like, yeah, it's what the [ __ ]
is going on here? Just the same as I
would think. But then obviously that's
what what the approaching videos are there for.
They literally dismiss you before they
even get to know you.
So it's like, what the [ __ ]
Too many stuck up [ __ ] I guess. Yeah.
Do it again on um Saturday and see what the score Oh [ __ ] [Music] Yeah,
I think beer should go back to being
like two pound a pipe, one pound, two
pound a pint.
And that's another thing that makes the
dating thing [ __ ] up is when you can't
justify the money that you've spent.
Like you can justify £200, even 250.
Yeah, if you had a good weekend, yeah,
you can justify that
250. But when you're talking fours and
fives and it's like, bro, you can go on
holiday with £500.
That's the way I just kept seeing it. Sorry.
Oh, it's nice. Yeah.
What does someone do? Okay.
So, yeah, I was looking good like that, man.
So, they can't blame your looks. They
can't blame your hairstyle. They can't
blame the fact that you, you know, that
they can't blame, you know, you not
trying. So really, they're running out
of ideas now, you know.
Um, they can't really blame anything anymore. [Music]
Even that finish one turned out to be a
time waster in the end as well. Yeah.
They all the same. Every single one of them. [Music]
I'm going to try and follow up with some
of these numbers today.
blaming personality. That's a madness.
That is insane. It's just a cover up. [Music]
And you know what? I don't want people
to give me sympathy. I want them to be gobsmacked.
I want them to understand how [ __ ] up
it is and that's it. So, actually to
answer your question, Joe, I actually
don't want people to give me sympathy. I
just want them to be in shock
just like I would be in shock. Like, I
love it. Like, when people are in shock,
that's what I like. I want people to be
in shock. I don't want sympathy. I want
them to be in shock and not believe what
they're actually seeing because it's so unbelievable.
So yeah, then I'll be like, "Okay, well,
my work's done here."
That's actually the whole point of it,
to be honest.
I don't want [ __ ] sympathy from no [ __ ] [ __ ]
you know? But yeah, I want him to be gobbmacked
cuz it is, like I said, it's [ __ ] up, you know. Anyways,
I'm going to go
and I'll be back later. I'm going to do
these burgers, I think. Bro, I'm getting
a bit hungry now. Too much tea time. So, yes.
In a bit.