[ __ ] hell, man.
That Timmy Eldridge is an embarrassment. Really is. Oh. [Music]
going to make myself a burger. I think
in a bit
has some Chinese but still. Yeah.
Oh, I'm not looking forward to tomorrow,
man. Have to go and approach.
[ __ ] that. It's [ __ ] boring. [ __ ] man.
I can't believe
compare his [ __ ] to mine, bro.
You're on a [ __ ] dating app. For [ __ ] sake.
Yeah, you're on a [ __ ] dating app.
You didn't have to spend any [ __ ]
money. I [ __ ] did. You know what I
mean? [ __ ] hell, man. Jesus Christ.
Jesus [ __ ] Christ, man.
No, no, no. The M should still be okay.
Just chilling, man. I didn't go out
today, man. I couldn't be [ __ ] I woke
up and I was like, I can't be bothered.
But definitely tomorrow.
I'm still burnt out from last
I was still burnt out from last Friday
to be fair, man. So, but definitely tomorrow. Definitely. Uh
definitely tomorrow, bro. I'll be out
for a little bit.
Bro, I was so tired. I couldn't be
[ __ ] I was supposed to go to my
sister's today as well and I just stayed
in bed or slept, man. I couldn't Yeah, man.
But yeah, definitely tomorrow we'll send
it and then that's it for 3 weeks. I'm done.
No more wasting money in this country.
[ __ ] that. Absolutely [ __ ] that. Oh man.
Yeah. Send it hard to my
hard hard and then that's it. Finished
until my birthday.
It's a madness, isn't it?
None of them numbers reply back.
This guy I was like, "Oh yeah, got all
the numbers last week. No date for this
week." And this guy was like, "Oh, um,
yeah, I was on Hinge." Ser replies. I
like, "Yeah, he was on a date, but I
actually went out there and wasted money
and wasted time and I actually looked
Max and I still haven't got anything.
So yeah, tomorrow is just purely to be
going out and trying to meet someone.
Not to drink. I am going to be drinking,
but not to drink and have a good time.
I'm literally just trying to meet
someone tomorrow. So that's it and I'm done.
It's [ __ ] ridiculous now, bro.
This generation's [ __ ] is it?
a new video. Maybe
I should do a new video or Yeah.
Why bother? Because I want to make use
of my haircut, bro. Cuz my hair still
looks somewhat fresh. So, I want to once
the hair grows back, I won't be
bothering, bro. But as soon as the hair
grows back, I won't I'll be doing it
like every two months, every 6 weeks.
Trust, I know what I'm doing, bro. It's
just I want to make do of the haircut
before it all goes back. And yeah,
that's it. And then I'll be out on my birthday,
which is over 3 weeks away. So,
yeah. I'm going to book another holiday,
I think. Therefore, definitely, man.
I can't believe how much money I [ __ ]
wasted, bro. That Oh, man.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. I'm
getting my money's worth. Um,
my I mean, it's growing back a little
bit, but it's still sort of fresh. It's
still my beard still like intact and stuff. So,
look, it's not growing back back and it
looks fine. So, I'm just going to Yeah.
Get my money's worth £50 worth and then
that's it, bro.
Until my birthday.
That's disgusting, bro.
Yeah, I'm going to I think I'm going to
do a video on this actually.
No, I'm just going to go to the off license.
Um, and get the beers and off license.
And in the club, the beers are like £3
each. So, I won't be spending more than
£40 tomorrow. Don't you worry about
that. I will not be spending more than £40.
That was a [ __ ] joke. The amount of
money I [ __ ] spent, it doesn't matter
if I won. Doesn't matter. Does not [ __ ] matter.
I'm supposed to be having as much money
as I can, not [ __ ] wasting it. Do you
understand what I'm saying? So,
yeah, you could do that,
bro. I I'll I'll see you tomorrow. Trust
me, I'll be I won't be spending more than4 tomorrow.
Going to get these numbers.
But even like the happy hours, like £3 a
beer, £3 a beer is all right, but you
could just keep doing that.£3 three
pound beer, three pound beer,£3 pound
beer, that's fine.
Um, you know, if the beer's £3, then
it's fine. But trust me, we will be on
it tomorrow, bro. Trust me, 100%. Then
that's me done.
I feel like that winning that £500 was
was telling me something, bro. It was
telling me something, trust me. So, yeah.
We'll see you tomorrow.
Go to your off license. You can get like
free beers for like66.
So yeah, free beers for6
or like a little Oh, just like sneaker
bottle. Yeah, a bottle of rum is like maybe £10
with some coke.
So yeah, we'll spend like4 tomorrow. 30
40 that's fine, but we're not spending
more than that. No way.
Depends, bro. If you do it every month,
you can you can spend a couple hundred
pound, but I done a lot last week. I'm
not wasting that money. You understand,
bro? I'm not wasting that [ __ ] money.
It was hard trying to win that money and
and trying to get the money as well. You
understand? So, I'm not going to waste it.
So, like I said, if I got a date with
somebody, I wouldn't mind spending a
couple hundred pound. Not a problem. But
not just to go out drinking. [ __ ] that.
And obviously again, I'll do on my and
obviously I'll send it again on my birthday. So,
um, and then that's it.
Cuz I'm not going out to enjoy myself
tomorrow. I'm going out to try and beat somebody.
That's why I don't want to be wasting the money,
you know. So, I can either go to the off
license and buy beer,
which is like six pound for a couple
beers, or I can just get the rum,
the small bottle of rum, and then just
mix it. I could do that. Um, not sure.
Yeah, man. It's all right. Once once a
month, if you done it once a month, it's
not bad. You know, spending a couple
hundred pound on a night out once a month. But
you can't justify it other than that,
bro. you know, you just can't justify it.
Never be able to save if you was doing
that every week. So, yeah,
it's never going to change her. So, that's it. [Applause]
Yeah, that's what I'm thinking.
and then buy like a couple of beers or
something. I'll be doing a lot of approaches sober. So, yeah.
Yeah, something like that.
No, I'm not you. Even if you do it every
week, you're not going to meet anyone.
Even if you do it every week, you're
still not going to meet anyone. I mean,
I've lost hope here. That's I don't do
it every week because I've lost hope here
because you're never going to meet
anyone here, you know? I only go out
drinking now because I want to go out drinking.
That's the reason I don't go out every
week because there's no point going out
every week because you're still not
going to meet anyone. Once you've met
one, you've met them all. The only
reason I'm going out tomorrow is cuz the haircut
that cost me a lot of money.
So you could go out every week and you
wouldn't even get a date at the end of
the month. It's a mugs game.
Dating in this country is a complete and
utter mugs game. Think of it. I went out
last week and I got 10 numbers. That is
a month's worth of [ __ ] trying.
That is a [ __ ] month's worth of
trying, bro. I would say I would say
that's about a month's worth.
Yeah, that's about a month's worth right
there. I mean, there you go. And then
when I go out tomorrow, that'll be two
months worth of trying.
And you still can't meet anyone. So,
it's a mugs game. I'm over it now, bro.
I'm get it done tomorrow. Um, then go on
my birthday then. Yeah, I'm booking a
holiday as well next week. of a holiday
when I come back. This is [ __ ]
ridiculous, bro. Really, really ridiculous. So,
yeah, last week I got 10 numbers. That
is about a month's worth of trying. I'm
sure it is. Yeah, definitely is. So, yeah,
you'll never meet anyone
even if you go out every [ __ ] week.
I could go out every week. I just don't
want to waste the money. Waste the time.
Pointless, you know.
Once you've met one, you've met all of them. So,
yeah, that's it.
You could go out, right, every Saturday
and you still wouldn't get a date at the
end of the month.
For real, you still wouldn't.
You still [ __ ] wouldn't.
Once you've met one, you've met him all.
That's the way I say it. See it? Even
when I'm watching other videos.
So, I just go out now when I want to go out.
Uh, you know what I'm saying?
There's absolutely no hope in this
country when it comes to women. So, yeah.
And I'm only going out tomorrow cuz it's
something to do. I ain't got no hope.
No hope whatsoever.
Yeah, but that's a bit different. The
gym is a bit different. All women in
this country are the same. stuck up NPCs
addicted to their phones. So that's not
the same comparison.
So no, it's not like going to the gym
once a month. Not at all. Not in a
million years. Cuz if you went to the
gym in two weeks, you start making progress.
You went out twice a week, you're still
not going to meet a woman. Horrible, horrible
thing to compare. They're completely
different. So we're not talking about
the gym. talking about dating stuck up
women in this country. That's a bit
different than going to the gym. It's a
bit different, mate, than going to the gym.
So, yeah, horrible um
thing to compare it to. So, yeah, you
anyways, like I said, you could go out every Saturday
and you still wouldn't meet a woman.
I've I used to go out two times a week.
I used to go out Thursdays, Saturdays.
Um, and I never met anyone. I never met
anyone. Barely got anyone on the dates?
Says it all. It literally says it all.
Well, do you think that because you go
out more, suddenly it's going to change?
That's got more of a chance of it
changing. That's it. [ __ ] bro. Cuz when
I go out, I make up for the times I
didn't go out. Like I said, you know,
like I said, last week I got 10 numbers.
So, I mean, like I said, that's a month's worth. Yeah. Yeah, man.
forget these messages.
But I'm sure you're just trolling
anyways. You're either trolling or
you're just dismissing my struggles.
And it's so expensive. I can't even
justify it anymore. I'd rather just
leave. Leave again.
I want to go to Miami next year, but I
need to find out that that [ __ ] is not
there anymore cuz I don't want to go
somewhere where that [ __ ] is before I book this.
Do they even ring? No, they're real
numbers. They're definitely real numbers
cuz I WhatsApp them. But yeah, only one
replied and when I said let's meet, they stopped replying.
That tells you all you need to know,
mate. That tells you all you need to [ __ ] know.
It's disgusting. Is it?
It is [ __ ] disgusting.
But I need to find out that [ __ ] is not
there anymore. Cuz if they are, then I'm
going to have to pick somewhere else to go.
I'm not [ __ ] going where that [ __ ] is.
I'm actually trying to go on holiday,
you know what I'm saying? And not [ __ ]
get into confrontations with people,
bro. You know what I mean?
I think it's about 1,500. I think I'll
just book it.
Think. Yeah, man. Defo.
I know, man. Do No, no, no. It's not why
give a number. No, no, no. You need to
stop asking that question, Stephen
Howard. I'm I cuz I'll answer it for
you. You need to stop asking that
question because their answer is always
going to be, "Oh, uh, well, we gave it
just to give it because we felt
uncomfortable and they're going to come
out with all of these excuses." That's
not what the question is. The question
is, why give your number and lead
somebody on if you're not interested?
You know, play play the game, not the
audience. You know what I'm saying,
mate? It's not about giving your number
and not replying. It's about giving your
number and leading somebody on and then
coming out with [ __ ] That's what I
want to know. That's the thing I want to
It's not about them giving their number,
not replying because their excuse is
always going to be, "Oh, well, I gave
the number to uh get away from them."
Okay? So, that's why we don't ask that
question because it's always going to be
that excuse. Why do you give your number, reply,
and then stop replying when someone
says, "Oh, let's go out and meet. Let's
go. Let's go on a date." Why even reply?
Why give your number and why reply? It
just it just doesn't make sense, you
know? and keep replying as well. That's
the thing that doesn't make any sense at all. So
that's why I just can't be bothered with
it anymore, bro. Last week told me
enough, you know, you can be decent
looking, you can smell good, you can
look smack, you can be confident, and
you still won't get [ __ ] all.
And the amount of money I spent on a
[ __ ] weekend. [ __ ] that. I'm not
doing that again, bro. I am not doing that again.
Unless you want to stay in this country
forever and never progress and waste
your money, you keep doing that. But I
won't be doing it.
You know, if you've got no ambitions to
ever want to, you know, leave, then
yeah, just carry on going out every
week, waste, £400,
you know, if you want to do that. But I
won't be doing it.
I'll go out when I want to go out, you know,
and when I go out, I send it. So that's
I haven't had a date since April.
I think it was April the last time I
went on a date. And God knows how many
times I went out since that April.
It is [ __ ] disgusting trying to date
in this country.
There's absolutely no excuse why I don't
have a date this week. No excuse
whatsoever. Got enough numbers. Looks my best. So,
I'll be I'll be wearing that tracksuit
tomorrow, I think. Yeah.
And I I've got put the jeans in a JD
bag, I reckon. Yeah, man. madness.
But yeah, that's what I don't
understand. It's like that. It's like
that Finnish one.
Why give your number
and reply and say you're going to meet
and then come out with some [ __ ]
It's just a waste of everyone's time, you know?
And that cost a lot of money that Sunday
as well. That cost a lot of money too
when I went out that Sunday.
So there'll be no [ __ ]
Yeah, there'll be no um
there'll be none of that, bro. After tomorrow,
you know, you won £500, bro. It's a nice
little win plus your other little wins.
What you wasting money for?
For what, bro? What are you really
wasting money for again? [ __ ] sake, you know?
Don't you know what, right? I feel like
I needed to lose this house to learn
this. Like, I've got money. I'm getting
money next week. Got more than enough
money to do what I want. But I feel like
I needed to lose that house for me to
actually wake up because you know like
in the past I was just wasting money and
wasting money and never never getting
anywhere because you know you're stuck
in that loop. But obviously now you know
it's harder to get money and when you
have money even when you have money
which I have you don't want to be
wasting it you know and you think oh I
can do this with it. I feel like I
needed to learn the hard way like some people
because if you didn't then you'd be continuously
in this circle.
Does that make sense?
So that's why I feel like I like even
that money I didn't even give any of it
back. They paid it into my bank account.
Didn't give any of the money back. Not
giving any of the money back. Just like
the football bets. Like I needed I
needed that to happen, bro. I feel like
I definitely needed to lose that house
because I just would have never stopped
trying here and
it would have just always been the same old [ __ ]
Generally, bro, like I feel like and I I
had to lose that house because I would
have been doing this forever. Seriously.
Um, so it is a good thing it happened in
a way because I would have just stayed
there forever going around in circles.
Doesn't matter, you know, like
it's ridiculous amount of money you
[ __ ] waste on [ __ ] bollocks, you know?
cuz yeah, I would have never have learned. Never.
Just carried on every week. Well, no, I
don't think. No, no, no. Well, to be
fair, I did. I stopped going out every
week. When I don't go out every week,
it's not cuz I can't afford it. It's
because I don't want to go out every
week. Um, even when I had the house, I
still didn't go out every week. Like
towards the end towards like the last n
months, I haven't been going out like
every week. So, but I feel like yeah,
that's the only way I was going to
learn, I think.
But I, you know, get that wake up call
and I'm glad, bro. Really, in a way, I am glad.
And I've got a side hustle as well. I
can make money if I wanted to, but I
don't need to. So yeah,
but like I said, it's okay every month
for every 6 weeks if you want to go out
and have a blowout, you know, that's
completely fine, you know, but not every
[ __ ] week, bro. What the [ __ ]
And I like to go out not worrying about
what I'm spending. But obviously I'm
going to be worrying worrying about what
I'm spending tomorrow. But that's cuz I
have to because I don't want to waste
any money. I don't want to waste more
than I don't want to waste more than 40£40.
So I'm going to have to make do. Simple
because I'm not wasting any more money
than that. It's simple as that. Like I'm
not doing it. So
yeah, just bring a bottle in. I reckon
have a couple of beers.
I think if I get three numbers, even if
I get like three numbers, then that's
it. I'm happy with three numbers.
Then my hair would have going back. So
it comes a point where I'm not dealing
with this [ __ ]
You go [ __ ] holiday with that money.
And I'm probably like the only one Yeah. that like
I'm the only one Yeah. that [ __ ]
would win money and not give it back
because I know how hard money it is to
get money now and I'd rather have
something to do something with that
money. Do you know what I'm saying?
Rather than keeping these [ __ ] clubs
in business and bars in business.
That's it. like
so. Yeah, I don't think I would have
ever learned without the house to go in
to be fair. I would have went out still.
I just don't think I would have had any plans.
So, yeah, it's a good thing happened.
Good thing happened.
Like they say um
one door close, another one opens like that.
>> Yeah. I don't understand why I don't
have a date this week to be fair. That
is cuz it makes you think, well, hold
on. You can go out looking your best.
You can get all of them numbers and you
still can't get anyone that's
interested. What the [ __ ]
It is. It is [ __ ] up, bro.
But it's all right anyways cuz after
tomorrow I won't go out until my
birthday. I'll have a big blow out on my birthday. So yeah.
Damn. So good. [Music] flower.
It actually is, bro. Like, it is just a
big [ __ ] mugs game, isn't it? Dating
in this country.
That's the only way you can like put it.
It's a [ __ ] Mugs game. So yeah.
So you really think that if you went out
every See, this is the whole point of
Stephen Howard where I'm speaking about
like people dismissing my struggles
because they're saying, "Well, you have
to go out every week or your past
doesn't dictate your future." But
they're not forgetting that I've got a
long history with this. So, this is part
of what I mean by how people dismiss my
struggles because they're forgetting all
of the things that you've already done
and you've already tried, you know?
So, that's what I mean by they're
dismissing my struggles cuz we're
talking about I need to go out every
week, bro. I've been out about a million
times drinking. I probably drunk more
than [ __ ] most people my [ __ ] age
and I still haven't found anyone. There
shouldn't even be any need for that talk,
you know, anymore. Like,
you know, go out every week. The past
doesn't dictate the future when it does
because it's the same old [ __ ]
I tell you what, you know, when I before
I tried it on uh Friday, I was actually
going to do a U-turn and go back home.
generally was, bro. Like, I can't be
fat. I can't be fed. Going to the
barbers and [ __ ] And then I just can't
be bothered anymore. It's just the same old [ __ ]
It's just the same old boring [ __ ] Even
then, bro, like I was like, "Oh, I can't
be asked." And I was like, "You might as well." So,
I don't know why these women go out just
to tell everyone they've got boyfriends.
Steven Howard, it's [ __ ] mad. It's so
expensive as well. Like going out
drinking and [ __ ]
and they go out just to tell everyone
they've got boyfriends. It's [ __ ]
mental, bro. It
It's [ __ ] like I don't know. It's
just weird to me cuz I've
It's [ __ ] absolutely insane. Yeah. Yeah, man.
Yeah, man. Yeah, of course they're
lying, bro. Cuz
why the [ __ ] would someone spend so much
money just to go out drinking if you
weren't going to meet anyone?
Like a new friend or a potential
partner. Why would you go out spending
that kind of money? It doesn't make sense.
They don't have boyfriends, bro.
The ones that have boyfriends just like
walk past you or
they sort of like
they don't even entertain you.
Like they're the ones that are
potentially telling the truth. But the
ones that talk and they ain't got boyfriends, bro.
They don't have boyfriends. Just like if
you was in a relationship, you wouldn't
even entertain someone trying to talk to you. Yeah, man.
Nah, bro. I'm my own wing, man. I don't
need anyone with me.
I'll go out by myself.
But I don't understand why people seem
to still think that there's hope in this
country. I mean, I've not had a date
since April and they're still talking
like there's hope.
Like, it's actually mad. Like, they
actually are still trying to tell you
that there's hope. But, I mean, there's
not even been any recent dates. If there
was like recent dates, right, then I'd
be like, "Okay, fair enough." You know,
the the stove is getting warmer, but
there's not been a date since April.
I mean, that's a long [ __ ] time, bro.
Ap was it April? I think the last day I
quote was April.
That is a long ass time, bro. And I've
been out a lot since then. That was
before I lost the house as well. So,
so there's not been any recent dates.
No, there's not been any recent dates.
But they somehow seem to think that one
day you're going to go out and it's all
going to change.
Madness, is it Stephen Howard?
So that's the whole point of yeah them
dismissing your struggles. [Music]
It's mad, bro. It is mad.
Really is. I'm going to do a video, I think.
I've not been on a date since April,
bro. I mean, that says a lot to have not
been on a date since April.
Um, and no, my dates don't [ __ ] up. The
last date I went on, we was holding
hands. Everything was fine. Um,
then I went to kiss and she didn't want to kiss.
I mean, what what more did you want me
to do? What more am I supposed to do?
And then the other one claimed they
didn't feel the vibe within 10 minutes.
What am I supposed to do, bro? Be Superman.
Am I supposed to be a [ __ ] psychic or
something? But that [ __ ] doesn't matter
anyways, bro. That none of that [ __ ]
matters. The fact that you've not had a
date since April says a lot, especially
how much I've tried as well.
But that doesn't matter, bro. Whether
you was a problem, whether you're not a
problem, you have not had a date since
April, regardless of whoever the problem
is. You know, April, that's a long
[ __ ] time, bro.
So, and I've done a lot of approaches since then.
I mean, I'd love to know where these
people that claim it's so easy to get
laid and stuff. I'd love to know. There
must be something I'm missing.
There generally must be something I'm
missing. Some sort of application, some
sort of location I'm missing because
people on the internet seem to say it's
easy to get laid and easy to get dates.
I must be missing something. Must be
I must be missing something, lad.
And the women go on dates to pass time.
I mean, it's it's not about anyone doing
anything wrong. It's women go on dates
to pass time. And bro, it doesn't even
matter about that anyways cuz it's not
like I've got a date every week. I've
got a date every two weeks. Doesn't
matter what how the dates go. I've not
been on a date since April.
So, it doesn't really matter, does it?
It's just pointless conversation. So,
Yeah, that is.
Oh, they just they just make excuses,
bro. They just like they like basically
any kind of struggle you show them, they
just miss it. Like I show them um for
example, I'll show them like screenshots
of people that I've met, right? And
they'll be like, "Oh, yeah, but you're
trying to meet them too fast." I'm
thinking, "Huh?" I mean, I've approached
them in person. What do you want me to
do? speak to somebody for a month before
meeting them. You want me to speak to
somebody for 10 years before meeting
them? And I was like, "Okay, so what
about the ones that didn't reply in the
first place? What about the ones that
led me on? What about the ones that
agreed that agreed to meeting and then
they never met and they never talk about
them ones?" So they just what they do is
they dismiss your struggles. So anything
that you show them, they just dismiss it.
That's basically what I mean by they
dismiss your struggles because I'm
thinking, well, this one was supposed to
meet me. Now they're saying they can't
get over their ex. I'd show them ones
where people didn't even reply.
So, they just literally
nitpick and go for things that suit
themselves. That's what they do. So, honestly.
So yeah, like they just
they just make up stuff and dismiss your struggles basically.
It's just a mugs game, bro. That's all
it is is a Mugs game. You know,
that's all it is. So, yeah.
Yeah. I've not had a date since April. Wow.
No, that wouldn't be funny, bro. That
would give [ __ ] Reddit the perfect
excuse to blame the man. They love doing
it anyways. Blame a man.
But yeah, man.
I'm going to do a video about this actually. Yeah,
but it's like even when Joe says, "Oh,
the past don't dictate the future." He
must be forgetting about the past 5
years I've been trying.
So that's why I'm saying they dismiss your struggles.
That's literally what they do is they
ignore all of the bad experiences that you've had.
I don't even want to try tomorrow. I
don't want to go out tomorrow, bro. But
I'm going to have to. So,
it's depressing. It's [ __ ]
It is tiring, you know. Really is.
What are you talking about?
I just to be honest with you, I hate
talking about it, bro. It's just
depressing to be honest. I don't know. I
don't even know why I bring it up. I
think it's because I'm in such
disbelief, bro. But we'll be changing
the [ __ ] topic from tomorrow, bro.
Don't worry. Cuz it's just depressing.
It really is just so depressing.
It's like talking about death and [ __ ]
It's depressing as [ __ ]
Turn on my TV.
Yeah, you've seen her. The one I was in
a picture with.
They just go on dates to pass time and
make you feel like [ __ ] That's why they do it. Nah,
no, bro. But I'm just going to do a
video talking about this. Anyways, skin
and no money in it.
No better money. [ __ ] you.
I am so tired, man.
I was going to use some more of that
mint, but it might be off now. So,
probably not a good idea to be fair. [Music]
Oh, [ __ ] You like my little dating videos?
Not yet, mate.
That's another thing I need to be doing as well. [Music] Virgin
Is the skin virgin still going on about me? Steven Howard.
Nah, man. I was going Oh, you able to fight me.
>> [ __ ] [ __ ]
I'm going to make myself a hot chocolate.
Monty is such a snake, you know. I would
never be friends with Bobby ever, ever, ever again. You know,
never, bro. you're going to [ __ ] right off.
Um, you know, from now on it's just
going to be about me, me, me, me, me,
me, me, me. I'm going to be selfish with
money cuz that's a lot of also I learn as well.
You know, he is a [ __ ] [ __ ] as well.
Bitching me over a [ __ ] slag, bro.
What the [ __ ] Imagine
that ditching somebody in your [ __ ] slag.
Okay, bad it
is. Is the car
He is a [ __ ] bro.
Get me in the bed and
drive me [ __ ] mad.
You drive me [ __ ] mad, mate. In the
bed with no bed and no money in it. [Music]
Yeah. It doesn't m Yeah. Out of my
money. Yeah. My money that I spent.
The £200 that I [ __ ] spent
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] Yeah.
[ __ ] sake, man.
He's a [ __ ]
[ __ ] Monty is. He's a [ __ ] [ __ ] mate. Oh,
yeah. At least I can take a day off of
YouTube, unlike you. Oh,
you're the one sat on YouTube all day,
every day. Too scared to leave your house.
look closer to home. You can't even take
a day off of YouTube. I've took weeks
off of YouTube, bro. Same can't be said about you. Yeah, man.
Anyways, I'm going to help your YouTube
problem right now.
Bye-bye. See you later.
No, he didn't.
I can't [ __ ] believe I don't have a
[ __ ] date this week.
It's [ __ ] disgusting, isn't it?
I mean, it's like people should really
be saying to you like, you know, you
should just go out because you want to
go out, you should just go out drinking
because you want to go out drinking,
etc. you know, they shouldn't be giving
you any kind of hope that it's going to
change cuz it will never change.
You know, that's that's it. You know, it
will literally never ever change,
but they could still tell you, you know,
you just go out and have fun and stuff.
I just don't know how they think that
all of a sudden it's going to change.
They're very optimistic.
I don't know where they got it from, to
be honest with you, bro. Why are they so optimistic?
Why they seem to think that one day it's
just going to change?
I wish I could be like them, bro. I wish
I could be like them.
They're so optimistic.
But so all the things that's been
happening to me for years is no longer
going to happen.
I've been through [ __ ] hell and back, bro.
And they're still telling you that one
day you're going to meet someone. It's
just It's just lucky I've never wanted
kids in it really.
It's just lucky I've never really wanted
kids. I don't really have a sex drive
much anymore cuz if you obviously if you
wanted children, some people live to
have kids. I can't stand kids and I've
got nieces and nephews and stuff but you
know obviously if I really wanted kids
it could be it could be a problem you know
because there is some people that
generally want kids
you know so it's just lucky I've never
wanted kids to be honest with you and
adopting is not the same even though
people that do adopt
it's a good thing they got people that
do adopt but at the same time like so
you would want your own kid. It's just
lucky I've never wanted kids
cuz I'd be [ __ ] Really [ __ ] you know. So, yeah.
Yeah, he has seen a pair of tits. His own tits.
Yeah, his own tits.
You doing a football bet on Saturday?
I'm not doing a football bet.
I'm all right, bro.
Would you go out every week drinking if
you could? I could go out every week
drinking, but I don't enjoy it when I do
it every week. Uh,
would you do it every week? No.
Would you go out drinking every week?
Me personally, honestly, I like to do it
every two weeks,
but sometimes I take like a long break because
don't know why I take breaks. I've got
the money to go out and stuff, but I just
I don't know. Just a break just
does you good in it. So yeah, man.
Yeah, it's boring. You can't pull. It's expensive.
I mean, the only thing you can really
spend money on nowadays is a holiday.
That's the only real thing you can
have to show for your money as a holiday
really if you think about it.
But I am going somewhere New Year's Eve.
Definitely going somewhere New Year's
Eve. Matey, I have to go somewhere New Year's Eve. Defer
definitely going somewhere New Year's Eve. Yep.
I mean, I like the pubs, though. I like
Do you know what I like? I like a nice Weather Spoons.
I like a nice Weather Spoons in central
London. You can't beat a nice Weather Spoons
on a Thursday. Oh, it's lush.
A nice Weather Spoons on a Thursday. Yeah,
I do like a weather spoons though.
Nice goodness in the weather spoons. Yeah. [Music]
It's nice, isn't it? Central London Weather Spoons.
I like doing approaches in the Weather
Spoons. I've done so many, bro.
It's fun, man. And it's fun.
So yeah, I might meet someone tomorrow,
Steven Howard. You never know.
Could get lucky tomorrow.
Yeah, I think we got more chances of um
pigs flying to be fair.
More chances of pigs flying. Literally,
what makes you say that I'm not going to
meet anyone tomorrow? Why are you being negative? Huh?
Why? Why do you think I'm I'm not going
to meet anyone tomorrow? Why are you being negative?
You never know till you try,
Stephen. I would. You never know till you try.
Every week, Steven Howard.
What if I went out every week for a
month? Do you think then or
What makes you say that?
I hate Reddit, man.
I [ __ ] hate [ __ ] Reddit.
It's full of [ __ ] power hungry mods.
They ain't got no life.
They need power over the internet. It's
[ __ ] sad, bro.
past history in it. Yeah.
What it is? It is your past history which people
seem to dismiss. Yeah,
I just want to get some numbers even if
get three numbers, four numbers. I'm
happy I got my money's worth in the
haircut, you know. So,
I think I lasted three or four weeks
without going out. I done good, didn't
I, Steven Howard?
I done [ __ ] good, man.
When I went out, [ __ ] spent £4500,
[ __ ] won the money back.
So, I'm not going to waste it again, am I? You know,
I'm not going to [ __ ] waste it.
Yeah, that's the reason I'm going out
tomorrow, bro. Only cuz it's something
to do. But for after tomorrow, the next
time will be my birthday and probably
the next time after that will probably be December
cuz I'm going away in November. But even
then, yeah, it probably be just it
probably be mid December to be fair and
New Year's Eve. So,
it is something to do. And yeah,
it's long traveling as well, but it's
better than doing it's better than
nothing for the sake of 30, you know. So, yeah,
December's very very very busy.
Like it's really busy, bro.
Yeah, December's very busy.
December's good for like Weather Spoons, man.
And your band. Bye-bye. Yeah, man. Um,
live for the 10th time today. I didn't
know I've been live 10 times. I thought
it was the second time. Strange. Yeah, man. [Music]
getting buy the bad [ __ ] with no bed in
it. No money in it. No bed.
There's a con. There's 31 [ __ ]
days in October, bro. I'm not sure.
How much money do you think is a good
amount of money to last you for a month? Steven Howard
to last you for a month. Maybe 1,400,500.
Should last a month, is it? Yeah.
No, like just like if you was just going
to go out drinking
every week. Yeah. Spending. Yeah.
Basically, but not on holiday. Just here.
Yeah, maybe 1,500.
I was going to say
£500 for the month. [ __ ] that, bro. Nah.
What? 500 to last you a month. Nah, bro.
My money built up cuz I won some bets. But
if you survive on 500 pound in a month,
I can do that, bro.
Because if you go out once, more than
half of that money is gone. So
yeah, more than half that money is gone.
So, how much of you was going to the pubs then?
Say he was going to the pubs, maybe a thousand. Yeah, mom.
>> Yeah, exactly like me. I have [ __ ]
Here's the thing. Yeah. Here's the
thing, bro. How much money would you
need, though? Like,
if you were
If you're going to the pubs,
how much for a month? Like a thousand.
Yeah, I'm not giving them my money
either, bro. I'd rather just go on
another holiday with it.
Literally, if you went on holiday, then
yeah, it doesn't matter. You can spend
what you want. But yeah, it's true, isn't it? you know.
So, how much money would you need
for a month to last you a,000? Nah, bro.
I'd say like 17,800
even though that's a bit people say it's excessive but
I never really saw it like that you know >> we've
£500 last you for the month so that's
how much you've got in your bank account £500
the [ __ ] that Yeah.
Yeah. So, how much how much money do you
get a month?
Yes. How much So, what do you save? How
much do you save then? So,
so you're like,
so you spend five, so you'll spend 500
and save like 600.
It's so mad. Like this month, bro, I can
spend like £900 and save a,000.
That's cuz I want money from the
football and [ __ ] That's what I'm
saying. Once I've got the money, I don't
want to be wasting it, bro.
Yeah, I could I could spend almost
double that and still have a thousand left.
That's cuz I was just careful and just
one money and that in it. So,
but I wouldn't waste it. That's what I'm
saying. Just cuz I have it to waste
doesn't mean I'm going to waste it.
There you go.
So, you know,
I wouldn't even do two weekends in
London to be fair.
Yeah, I would even do two weekends in London.
I know. It's crazy, isn't it?
Crazy [ __ ] expensive.
We should have more than that, man. We
won a couple of football bets,
didn't we? We won a couple of [ __ ] football bets.
Yeah, I think I'm up over £1,000 cuz we
won we won the football bets.
But I I put that 120 on 1380, didn't I?
You didn't you wasn't in that bet cuz I
didn't tell anyone I'd done it. Then
obviously the 500 [ __ ] that I got to
from 100. So I think I'm up I think it's
got to be over maybe 1,100 pound.
Yeah, I think I'm up about that. Yeah,
to be honest.
Yeah, I lost some, but I'm still up overall.
You should have done the 120 one that I
done to 380.
That was a lovely little win.
after. Oh yeah,
that's good, man. That's good.
Virgin boy ain't got no money.
Virgin boy ain't got no money, mate.
Nah, not Virgin boy, mate. The skin virgin, mate.
Not the skin virgin boy, mate. One second. Yeah, man.
speaking to this woman on Reddit.
See, that's the f that's the worst thing about
Friday, bro. Does that actually look
good as well?
One second, bro.
Yeah, that's the worst thing about
Friday, bro. I look sick on Friday, bro.
I made uh Jane catch feelings again. She
couldn't help it, but she has to put on
a face for Mark. for Arsenal Mark.
You know I know that. You know that,
mate. Come on.
She has to put on the face for him, don't she? [ __ ] madness.
Really, really is. Yeah.
Well, I need to go in a minute. Yeah,
I'm going to do a video. Make sure you watch You watch Oh [ __ ]
Right. Yeah, I'm going to do a video in
a bit and be back tomorrow or