Yo, to get some [ __ ] went to get some
chicken and [ __ ]
Oh, back now.
Back in the old nesticles
back in the oldest.
No, I said earlier that I'm not going
out. I'm done now till my birthday. I
can't be bothered. Waste of time. Waste of money.
Same old [ __ ] So you fought wrong
and stop coming to my channel trying to
troll me cuz I'll just block you again. Yeah.
Simples. You fought wrong cuz I said
earlier that I'm staying. So
yeah, now I'm done after last week I
think. Yeah. Spending all that money,
not having a date this week. [ __ ] that.
Absolutely [ __ ] that.
I'm good. I'd rather stay in and chill.
I went for a long walk, got some food,
come back. Not going out.
We'll never change in this country. So,
no need to go out and waste money, waste
time, waste money, waste effort. No need for it. Yeah.
That's the way I see it. Yeah,
definitely going to play some Black Ops 2 later. Yeah,
I'll be showing you tomorrow as well. I
might go for a walk. Yeah,
last week was so depressing.
It was [ __ ] raining today as well.
Well, November can finally [ __ ] leave. Yay.
No life for anyone in this country.
It's no life for [ __ ] anyone. So, yeah.
Yes. In a good old nestic
good old nest.
[ __ ] tired, man. Yeah.
Don't ever change it, would it? Never. Never. Potter.
Good thing I've got Good thing I've got
the the room, the bed, the TV, the Xbox.
I've got a nice setup.
It's good I've got a nice setup to be fair.
This is the best I guess. Yeah,
there's no hope in this country.
I should have gave up a long ass time ago.
Just chilling, bro. I didn't go out
today. I don't think I'm going to go out
again for a very long time to be honest
with you. after last week just her
numbers and not one date and the money I spent. Yeah.
Yeah, man. I don't think I've been going out for
a long time.
I changed my mind. Yeah.
[ __ ] in it.
England is so [ __ ] Such a depressing country.
Hate it here.
No, I'm not gambling either
cuz I don't need to gamble. I have
enough money. So,
no, there's no point. No ski.
I do that [ __ ] bro. He's chilling.
There's a Northern League playing tomorrow.
Let's do 500 pound. Both teams to score tomorrow.
[ __ ] that, bro. You want to do it
tomorrow?£500. Both teams to score.
Yeah, that's a good league. Loads of
goals. could leave that. Yep.
So an overly is an overly plane tomorrow.
Loads of goals.
Loads of goals on that league, mate. Yeah.
How much you putting on it?
I could put 120 on it, but there's no point.
I don't want to gamble, bro. I'm all
right with the money that I have. What's up?
do 120, bro. Why don't you put 120 on it? Yeah.
You could easily get a four both score
no draw in that league.
So what? You don't do 80 pound anymore? No.
You done with that?
What? Put 120.
What? Oh, you'll put 120 on it. Really?
So, what you're going to put 120? You're
not going to put 120 on the football bet?
What? Will you actually put 120 on a football bet? Yeah. Nah, bro.
Pick Darlington and Kitty Minister.
There's always goals 72 games.
Yeah, I done a 121 return 380. Yay.
I want to try and get a four. Both score no draw.
What do you think of that, Steve? I
would both score no draw fourfold.
So, was Ant-Man right that they're not
interested in this country? Steven Howard,
was he right about that? That they're
not interested in this country?
Yeah, he was right. Hate to say it.
Yeah, I think he's right, man.
What do you think? I think so.
You're not interested in this country?
Yeah, I think he's right. Definitely.
Yeah, but he's right though. Is it?
What do you think, Stephen Howard? I
think he's right. Defo
from my experiences. These experiences.
Yeah, I think he's right though. They're
not interested in this country.
They just aren't interested in this country. Oh man. All right.
They aren't in this country.
Uh I just can't get over.
I just can't get over last week
spending all that money. I told some of
my friends they couldn't believe it.
Don't know who that is.
So yeah, I'm going to book a holiday um
another holiday next week.
Put deposit on another holiday I think. Defo Matey.
So, I didn't spend any money this month
cuz I won. You see? So, money I spent I got back.
Never heard of them.
You reckon if I went out today I would
have pulled Steven Howard? No. Well,
yeah, I won 500 on the roulette. That's
the last time I gambled.
You keep it there, eh?
No point wasting money in this country.
How do you know?
How do you know? Maybe I would.
I'm happy I've got the TV, the Xbox.
I've got some money and [ __ ] so I can
keep myself occupied at home.
Yeah, last month I saved 500. This month
I saved a,000 and obviously I won like
the money I spent. Yeah. And also
the [ __ ] that happened last week as well
with the escort and [ __ ] I'd rather
just like be like, "Nah, I can't be asked.
And then you remember I got kicked out
for [ __ ] talking to people and [ __ ]
I'd rather just save my money.
No one needs that negativity in their life.
I really want to do a [ __ ] both teams
tomorrow, but I don't want to gamble.
I want to put like 120 on it, 140 on it,
and I don't want to really risk that
kind of money.
See, these are all things I've learned from sort of
um the house and stuff when I used to
gamble and gamble and gamble and [ __ ]
like so. Just don't want to make the same mistakes
that I did before, you know. Yeah.
Yeah. You could do 50.
Could do. Yeah.
then the return is not going to be as
much. So what's the point?
Because the return is not going to be as much
30 on like four teams.
Yeah, 50 pound the return is not as
much. We done really good on the
football last month and the month before
we done good on the football. That's why
I've got so much money from the [ __ ]
the wins that just added up.
Yeah, it was just the wins that added
up, was it?
We had a nice one the first start of the
[ __ ] the first match of the season,
bro. [ __ ] 80 to 280. That's when I
went to Birmingham
to see Monty. I don't know why I
bothered, but yeah, I'll never be
friends with that snake ever again. Never. Ever.
That was 280. Then we won the week and
then the week after that we won again. Yeah, mom.
We had some good ones.
That was sick, bro. Nope.
Why are you asking such a stupid question?
Why would I kick a [ __ ]
multi-billionaire out of bed?
Come on, man.
That's silly. Very silly.
We done good, bro.
80 to 280, then 80 to 230.
Imagine we done 120 every week and we
won every week for a month. Jesus.
What's a uh threefold?
Cuz I don't really want to lose £300.
Sorry, £100. Sorry. Threefold.
Can't be bothered, man.
I'm saving money now. I'm leaving soon. So
[ __ ] wasted enough money last week.
He is a snake. I will never be friends
with him ever again. I swear to God.
It is hard unless you do it on the
northern well unless you do it on the
[ __ ] Northern um
unless you do it on the Northern League
or any kind of national league. It is
hard. It's only easy on the [ __ ] National League.
There's loads of goals. Loads of goals.
I had £120 on two and I got 380.
I was buzzing, man.
Yeah, do it. [ __ ] it. Why not give it a
whirl? I would.
I'd give it a whirl.
Yeah, I would. Why not? Really?
You going out? Um, you going out
drinking this week?
I won't be. I'll be chilling tomorrow.
Can't be bothered with the women, the [ __ ]
the expense of it,
the bad experience I had last week. No
thanks. I'd rather just stay in. Yeah.
Uh, I got a nice telly. Got Xbox. Yeah.
He is a snake. Yeah,
he still watches. Don't worry about
that. He still watches.
Oh, really? You go home quite early then?
Yeah. I normally go home around I like
to go home around 11:00,
but I'll start at like 2:00 and then go
home at 11:00. Yeah.
Spent £600 last week. [ __ ] it now. Jesus.
That's the madness.
Don't even know what on mate. Drinking,
haircut, food, [ __ ] bagels. [ __ ] madness, bro.
The most I've ever spent on a night out
was about £700.
So that almost
almost beat it. Yeah. Yeah, mom.
Are you going for some Guinnesses tomorrow? Yeah.
>> Nice, man. Nice.
It's about £780 a goodness. Here £7 [ __ ] 80.
Yeah, I've got no responsibilities. Me,
I'm not a landlord anymore. I'm not in a
relationship. I don't have any kids. So,
I don't have any responsibilities. It's lush. Yeah, nice. Nice.
I love this.
Nah, long story, man.
Not going to get into it. But yeah, no. Yep.
But I won't be going on nights out anymore.
It's too negative. The bad experiences
with women, the escort thing I had last
week, the amount of money you spend,
it's just not worth it.
I'd rather just stay home and take
[ __ ] cocoon more, bro, and just play
some [ __ ] GTA. It's just not worth it. So, yeah.
Yeah, man. I've had baby Guinness a lot.
It's just not worth it anymore. So, yeah.
Yeah, baby. Goodness is good. So yeah,
I put £100 on roulette last uh Sunday
and I won £500.
I'm not getting into gambling, bro. I'm
not interested in gambling.
I don't know why I gambled on Sunday,
but I'm not interested in it, bro.
This is not a gambling channel. I
learned my [ __ ] lesson a long ass time ago.
I should have learned my lesson about
women as well than being all the [ __ ]
same a long time ago, but I never. But yeah,
I should have knew all women were the
same. Gambling's [ __ ] So yeah,
[ __ ] are negative in this country.
That's why I'm leaving.
That's why I'm leaving, bro.
It's depressing, lad.
Yeah, that was the first time in a month
cuz I was bred at 2:00 in the morning.
Yeah, but I'm not interested generally.
I mean, I was really [ __ ] bored, so I
thought, yeah, let me just put 100
pound. But what you're talking about,
I'm guessing that you gamble multiple
times a week. Yeah.
I'm guessing you gamble multiple times a
week. I'm guessing. But
yeah, I'm going Thailand, bro. Thailand in November.
It's too depressing here.
The women, it's it's [ __ ] It's just
depressing. I'm miserable here, bro. Absolutely miserable,
you know. Depressing. Horrible country,
but nothing ever changes.
So, I'm [ __ ] off. Yeah.
What do you mean you can't afford to gamble?
How can you not?
You know, I don't even gamble every week.
So, even if you gamble once a month,
you're still not interested in gambling.
I still wouldn't say that's an interest
in gambling. To be fair, it's not
frequent enough to be interested in it. Yeah, man.
Free children. God help you.
£600 I spent last week.
So, how much do you have left for the month?
I got uh two bills
and it comes to £45.
They're the only two things I have to
pay out for, I think. So,
yeah, about 456.
That's my outgoing for the month. Nope.
don't want children. Never wanted
children. And even if I did want
children, I wouldn't be able to have children.
So luckily, I never wanted children. So,
doesn't matter how it's only £45. It's
Xbox phone bill. Done. Mama. Mama. Oh,
can you smell a bomb? Steven Howard, I
can smell a bomb.
I can smell him. Can you smell him?
Yeah, I can smell a bomb
all the way from here. Can you smell him?
Don't know if I'm the only one, but I
can smell a bomb here.
Yeah, I can definitely smell him. Can
you smell them?
They make it too obvious.
They make it so obvious.
They make it so obvious, bro. Seriously,
you know, you know when it's these
people when they're always trying to
like get you to gamble as well.
Um when you have these people trying to
get you to gamble, right? You know, it's
like one of them like this Joe account
does it as well. Yeah.
Yeah. That's definitely definitely bomb.
Uh, so obvious.
Yeah, that's bomb.
Like I said, you know, when they're
trying to get you to gamble. Yeah.
I'll probably just be in bed all day
tomorrow to be honest.
Depressed as usual.
Shouldn't go out anymore, bro. Drinking.
The more you try, the more you lose
hope. [ __ ] up, is it?
Cuz the more you try, the more you lose hope, you know. Yeah.
What do you think of Timmy Aldridge?
So, how much are you really putting on
the football tomorrow? Yeah.
Do you know that's why Lord Jay calls
people skin? Cuz he is skin.
As Vonnie used to say, they call you
skin cuz they're skin. Put two and two
together for [ __ ] sake. It's so obvious.
I don't know where I look at the teams
because sometimes the Northern League
doesn't show up.
Take all your skin cuz there again. Okay.
Yeah, man. Sorry.
Let's put £500 on two teams. Both teams.
M. Let's do 500 pound on a double team to score.
Why not? You scared?
Imagine you done that and they refuse to pay out.
Yeah. Imagine you done that and they
refused to pay out Steven Howard.
You'd cry, wouldn't you? Yeah.
What would you do if they refuse to pay you out? H
they said they refused to pay you out.
What would you do?
Yeah, but what if they refuse to pay you
out in the bookies? Yeah.
What? What? You'd smash the shop off if
they didn't pay you out? Really?
What if they refuse to pay out? Yeah.
Virgin boy skint in the bed sit with
absolutely no bed and absolutely no
money in it. Yeah.
We need to win a football matey.
Don't we matey?
Can't believe I gambled last Sunday,
bro. I don't want to be getting into
that [ __ ] again. Yeah.
Yeah, I won 500
last Sunday, but I haven't been back since.
Yeah, I don't play it much. just
sometimes once a month, once every
couple of months if that
Yep. It is for mugs.
That's why I don't do it, Dad.
I only done it because I was bored.
And I spent a lot of money last week.
Wanted to try and wanted to try and win some money. Uh don't know
sources. Rose, do you think £1,200 is
enough to last somebody for the month?
Do you think that's enough to last
someone for a month?
I put £100 on the roulette. They charged
me £103. I got it to 570. Took 507. So 40.
Well, I just say it's £500 cuz I only
put £100 in. So say 500 in it. Yep. Yeah.
You like my TV? My TV is sick.
Do you like it?
It's good TV.
You are all the same. They've got the
same attitude, same mannerisms.
You think the Virgin will ever get laid Virgin board. T videos [Music] about my co
I like Timmy Aldidge. you um
I had um three pieces of chicken
I walked and then walked all the way back.
So I'm still able to go out and stuff.
Still depressed over the last week
is enough to make anyone down, you know. Yeah,
>> he's got nice TV.
Some of the tenders that I'll buy Xbox
and TV not for sale. No, mine. Yeah.
Want to buy my [ __ ] TV. Not for sale.
It's not for sale, man. [ __ ] off.
People can't say anything about me anymore. Grevy.
Oh, you ain't got a TV. I've got a TV. I
mean, what can people say,
Grezy? You know what can people really
say, mate? Nothing.
Don't say anything about me, mate.
people. Someone on Reddit said they
don't have the answers as to why I can't
find someone we
said that your approaches seem fine
and stuff. Yeah. He said that you're
decent looking. They don't know what the problem is.
What do you think the problem is, Grezy?
This generation or
did you see my response back to Virgin Boy?
Did you see it?
Right. What I said though, ain't it?
It's not about taking accountability.
I put up videos where I've tried
speaking to a woman normally and they're
not interested straight away.
What accountability am I supposed to
take what? By trying to meet someone or
arranging a date with someone.
But that's society for you, is it?
They're always going to defend women.
That's their life. Grezy,
nothing's going to change there. You know,
they just love just blaming men. I don't
know why they do it, but they do it.
I've had it before, Greavesy, where I've
not even finished my sentence and
someone said they're not interested.
So, what am I supposed to take
accountability for? What? Trying to
speak to someone?
It has happened before. Yes, it has
Is that them or is that me?
You know, it's I mean, I've got [ __ ]
videos where it's happened.
Yeah, I literally have videos where it's happened.
Little telly greasy.
That's why I'll never invite you around
cuz you'll probably nick my telly.
Yeah, you'll probably nick my telly, matey, won't you? Yeah. Mhm.
But self projecting
skint and anxious
that self projections.
You ain't [ __ ] ran away, have you, son?
Yeah, that's self projection.
I mean, I spent £600 last week. Still
got a couple of,000. Nothing skit about me, mate.
Self projection. Like I've said, we
don't all have your life.
This is a problem with people in this
community. They seem to think everyone's
got the same life as them. Anxious skin,
can't leave their house.
Everyone thinks they've got the [ __ ]
same life as them on here. It's [ __ ] madness.
You've never got my uh sublet money
stopped and I've got savings and I have
more money than you would ever have. So
try again. You've never ever got my
subleting money stopped. I can go out
every week if I want to. You don't know
how much I have and anything. So you
never got anyone subleting money
stopped. So you keep trying to convince
yourself that. But that never happened,
mate. You could never get someone sublet
subleting money stopped. And mate, I
will never have as much anxiety as you
people. So stop selfjecting. Not
everyone's got your life, you know, bro.
You want like £300 a month? Allow it. I
can go out whenever I want, however I
want. I have more money than you would ever have.
And yeah, that's it. Simple.
Everything you say is just about your
own life. Give it up, kid. How many
years have you been [ __ ] doing this
now on YouTube? So, yeah.
[ __ ] idiots on here, bro. I swear to
God. Absolute idiots.
Proper proper [ __ ] idiots on here. Jesus Christ.
Yeah. Controls my life. Yeah. Self
projecting again. Like I've said a
million times, we don't all have your life.
We do not all have your life.
Anxiety sat at home all day every day.
That's your life. That's not my life.
Same thing as skin. Skin is your life,
not my life. self projecting.
We don't all have your life
[ __ ] mongos on YouTube from the time
you wake up to the time you go [ __ ]
bed talking about people that you don't
even know. And the fact that you come
out with the most specific random
things. It's It just goes to show you're
just talking about yourselves
cuz you where the [ __ ] does this [ __ ]
even come from? You know what I'm
saying? Where where does it even come from?
Seriously, where does it even come from? What's it?
What's that? What's that? Treble.
You did not get anyone's sublet money
stopped. Mate, if any of you got my
money stopped, one of you would be dead.
I've said this a million times. You
know, it's it's [ __ ] obvious. I would
have at least tried to get one of these
mongos. You've never got anyone's sublet
money stopped. I still have more money
than you. I could go out every week if I
want to. Not a problem at all. You do
not know how much money people have.
So yeah, like I said, let's just try again.
You never got anyone stop letting money
stopped. You would not be able to get
someone's money stopped. I've explained
this about a million times. If I have to
do a video explaining this a million
times to you mongos, I'll do it. [ __ ]
it. I'll do a video.
No. Red Star sent letters. Yeah. I had
that house for 4 years. No. I had that
house for 4 years and the landlord was
trying to get it back for 4 years. It
had nothing to do with you people on
YouTube. Nothing to do with you people
on YouTube at all. Yeah. They were
trying to get it back before people even
knew where I lived. It was nothing to do
with you people. Nothing at all. You are
the one that's in denial.
So, stop talking absolute [ __ ] You
know, they were on that for like 4 years
trying to get a house back. Nothing to
do with Red Star. You've never got any
of my money stocked ever. So, stop
making [ __ ] up
because it would never ever [ __ ]
happen. It would never ever ever ever
happen. You tried to get my benefits.
stopped. Yeah, you tried to get my
benefits stopped and had to answer them
phone calls, but you never got anyone
sublet money stopped.
So, and I've still got more money than
you and I can still go out whenever I
want. So, and I've still got more money
than you would ever have. So, more
money, better looking, go out and like
you, you [ __ ] [ __ ] Get [ __ ]
gone. You think any of you skint little
mongos would get my money stopped? You
little skint spastics on YouTube. You
[ __ ] mongos. You mters. You think any
of you fat, ugly disabled virgins could
ever get my money stopped? You [ __ ]
[ __ ] skin bastards on YouTube that run
away every single time you get show
money. Please, mate. You fat skin ugly
mongos that can't get off of YouTube.
Come on, man. This is funny now, bro.
Seriously, have a word of yourself.
And you gone, [ __ ]
Yeah, man. Had to get rid of this [ __ ]
Steven Howard, listen.
These people never got any of my money stopped.
Not one bit of my money stopped. Bro, if
somebody got any of my money stopped, I
would have killed one of these people.
Believe you me, bro. You already saw
what I done to nonslegs and made the
[ __ ] [ __ ] scared to go out for a
month with the posters and that was like £180
that they tried to get stopped. I had to
do the whole thing again and I literally
made the [ __ ] literally run out of his
virgin area with the posters.
Trust me, if somebody got my money
stopped, I would have killed someone.
And and I'm telling you straight, bro.
Like you're you're making stuff up. You
never got no one's money stopped. And I
got more money than you, which kills you
a million times. I keep saying this.
So yeah, how much money do I have now?
Tell me how much money I've got now more
than you. Simple.
So that's it.
Bro, they're [ __ ] skint.
Yeah. And that was that was [ __ ] £180
as well, bro.
These people on here are proper [ __ ]
disabled in it, man. You got to feel
sorry for them in it. Yeah.
Unusual they stalking. What a sad life
they live, eh?
Stephen Howard, what a sad skint life they live.
And they think I can't go out drinking.
I could literally go out every week.
Literally every week, mate. Twice a week
if I wanted to, but I just don't want to.
Even when I [ __ ] had the house, I
didn't go out every week towards the
last year of it. It's not a financial thing, [ __ ]
You understand? It's because we don't
want to go out and [ __ ] waste our
time or waste our [ __ ] money.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, exactly, bro. And that was over
180, bro. I had to start the whole thing again.
You never ever ever ever ever got my
money stopped because if you got my
money stopped right, why would it take
four years? Think about all the beef.
Yeah. Me and LT had. Yeah. People knew
where I lived. People knew what I was
doing. If you was to have got someone's
money stopped, it would have not took
four years. Just like the benefits
wouldn't have took four years. You
didn't get anyone's money stopped. You
tried to get people's money stopped, but
how would you be able to control a court
case? How would you be able to control a
court case when you've got absolutely no evidence?
You did not stop anyone's money. You
never have and you never [ __ ] will,
you know. And just like the [ __ ] last
time, bro, it's annoying when they say
that because they really did not, bro.
Because one of them would have been dead
if they did. Trust me, they would have.
these [ __ ] ugly skinned mongos. They
would be dead on the ground, bro. If any
of these little mongos got my money
stopped, believe you me, bro. I don't
[ __ ] around with that. You saw what I
done with the posters.
Why don't you do yourself a favor and
get off of YouTube and stop being a
jealous stop being jealous of people
that you don't know every [ __ ] day,
you [ __ ] losers. We don't all have
the same [ __ ] life as you people
have. Skin [ __ ] ugly. Can't get off
of YouTube. They seem to think
everyone's got the same life as them.
The specifics that they come out with,
the randomness that they come out with,
they seem to think everyone lives their
life. Skinned, ugly, can't get off of
YouTube. I, bro, I swear to God, they
think everyone's got the same life as them.
They seem to think everyone has got the
same [ __ ] life as them.
You know what I mean?
It's a [ __ ] madness. Yeah. Rough it.
>> You didn't get any You didn't get any um
person sublet money stopped.
Who do you think's behind that Red Star
account, Steven Howard? I think it's
Chase. Me personally,
you didn't You cannot control a court case.
You cannot take something to court. You
did not get anyone's money [ __ ]
stopped. Trust me, you [ __ ] did not.
So, I don't know why you keep [ __ ] saying that.
Anyone that's had one over on me, I will
tell them that someone's had [ __ ] one
over on me. You've never got anyone stop
letting money stop. You never have and
you never will. Just like you will never
have more money than me. So, you know,
it's that simple.
Yeah, I reckon it's that chase, you know, bro
or Pat Mustard. Whoever it is is a
[ __ ] coward behind that account. I
mean, for [ __ ] sake, how many years
have they been doing this now on
YouTube? [ __ ] lowife skin stalking
little [ __ ] Can't [ __ ] even get off
of YouTube. Like, think about it, bro.
They're s their whole life, bro. Yeah,
think about it. Yeah. Their whole life
is stalking someone that they don't even
know. They don't get paid for it. They
have no money. They got no life. Think
of think of their reality, bro. Just
think of what they look like. Whoever's
behind that account,
some [ __ ] fat loss. [ __ ] Mongol.
Just think about it, bro.
Sat on YouTube [ __ ] some fat virgin.
You just know it's some fat virgin, bro.
Behind that account, skin, no life. You
know, you just know, bro. It 100%. You
just know, man. You know,
he literally stalks my every move. He's
a [ __ ] He's a manta. Trust me, bro. He
He literally stalks my every move cuz he
ain't got a life. All because I'm better
looking than him and I've got more money
than him. What a [ __ ] loser, bro.
Like, he's an absolute [ __ ] loser.
An absolute loser, bro. An alltime
loser. Trust me, bro. Like, you know
what I mean? Like every single move he's
there. He's stalking some fat virgin,
bro, that lives with his mom. I'm
telling you, bro. 100%.
In his 40s. I'm telling you, bro.
Whoever's behind that account. Yeah.
Fat virgin that ain't got no life skin.
You know what I mean?
I don't go out every week because I like
a detox. What the [ __ ] bro?
You know what I'm saying? That's it. Yeah. Yeah,
that country ain't got no life, bro.
Some fat virgin that lives with his mom
in his 40s. I'm telling you, man.
It's nice. But in a way, Stephen Albert,
it's nice to have so many people jealous
of you. It just makes you like, it gives
you a kind of ego, you know.
You know that you're better looking than
these people. You got more money than
them. It's nice, man. It is nice.
ever thought that maybe when people get older
their priorities change. That's why they
don't want to go out drinking every [ __ ] week.
But yeah, bro. I can go out every week
if I want. I've got my hair done. Got a
couple of thousand. Get money weekly.
Could easy go out.
Bro, you didn't stop anyone's money.
Bomb. I've got more money than you. Wins
a bet. I'm I'm skinn, bro. You don't
know how much money I have and you
didn't stop anyone's money. So, keep
embarrassing yourself. I'm not even
going to block you. I'm skinn. I've got
more money than you. I've literally got
thousands. You don't know how much I
have. So, I'm going to let you keep
talking about yourself and keep self
projecting because you don't bother no one.
I've got more money than you would ever
have. So, keep typing. No one cares. You
don't know, bro. I get money every week.
I'm not sat in a bedsit with [ __ ] a 5
in TV like you [ __ ] [ __ ] You're
talking about people that live with
their mom. Mate, you live in a bedsit
with a couple of thousand pounds.
I've got more than you would ever have.
Bro, the day I get to my 40s and I'm sat
in a bedsit alone is the day I kill
myself. Which is why you do all of this
YouTube [ __ ] You're in your 40s. You're
past your sale by date. You got no
money. I'm better looking than you. I'm
younger than you. I got more money than
you. For [ __ ] sake, brother. You're in
your 40s and you got no money.
You can keep convincing yourself that
you got my buddy stopped, mate. I make
money. I've got more money than you. You
can keep talking [ __ ] in your 40s in
your bedset, Mr. Lonely. You need to
play that Mr. Lonely song again, bro.
Cuz that goes for you. In your 40s,
always a loner and a virgin.
No one cares about you, bro. Your
opinion is so irrelevant. You're so
irrelevant that you your opinion doesn't
even matter. You're in your 40s. You've
never traveled nowhere. You've got no
money. Don't even try to come at me,
bro. Someone that's younger than you,
better looking than you. I've got more
money than you as well, bro. You're on
£300 a month, bomb. Let's not talk about
3k a month. You get You get [ __ ] £300
a month. You don't know how much money I have.
I have more money than you.
More money than you. Better looking than
you. So, I don't know why you keep
talking about 3K, bro. I've got over 3K
the past two months. You don't know me.
We're not all in a bed sit in our 40s
like you. And I know every single time I
say that, bro, it gets to you. We're not
all the bomb on 300 pound a month skin
like you in a bedsit. We're not all the
same as you. We don't all have your
life, lad. We don't all have your life.
What did you say? £240 disability
benefits rejection. He's talking about
himself. I bro, I swear to God I'm not
going to block this. He's talking about
his own life. Where the [ __ ] would you
get £240 from? Bomb. We don't all have
your life skinned in a bedit. I don't
know how many times I have to say this
to you, bro. I can pull out jumpers
that's worth more than anything in your
shitty little bedset. arms. That's worth
more than your whole shitty little life.
I don't know why. Where the [ __ ] did you
just get £240 from? That's your life.
He's a self projector, bro.
He's talking about himself. He's talking
about his own disabled life in his 40s.
240 disability benefits.
I'm dead. I'm [ __ ] dead. I've got
more than a year's worth in my bank
account right now.
Projector. The 40-year-old projector
that's never been abroad in his little
bedsit. What a sad loader. To be honest,
bomb, I do feel sorry for you, mate. If
I was as ugly as you and old as you, I
would have killed myself a long time
ago. Sat in a bed sit in his 40s, not
wanted by no one, skint, got no money.
Imagine being you. Imagine being that loser.
That big fat ugly bomb loser like you.
To be honest with you, bro. No, actually
at the end of the day, lad. Yeah,
actually that's that's actually Yeah,
that is actually funny to be honest with
you cuz you actually think you know how
much people have. That's how much you
get. You do not know what money people
get, what money people don't get. You
don't know what people have. You don't
know what people don't have. You are
talking about your [ __ ] self. £240
a [ __ ] month. What the [ __ ] are you
going on about? That's your own life, mister.
Mr. Mcu pretending that he's been to
America when he's never been anywhere.
[ __ ] 80 pound a week. This is
project, bro. This is serious projection.
Uh bomb, you're a serious You're You're
a serious projector, mate. 80 pound a
[ __ ] week. Oh [ __ ] I'm dead wrong.
Oh my god. £240 a month, mate. I've got
more than a year's worth of that just in
my bank account right now. You don't
know anything about anyone, mate.
You didn't get any of my money stopped.
You keep saying that, bro. But but you
never got anyone. You literally got no
one's money stopped. You got no one's
money stopped. I've got more money than
you will ever have. You're the one
that's on £240 a month, not me. You
never got any of my money stopped
because that's why I've got more money
than you. And I can prove I got more
money than you as well. So at the end of
the day, you didn't get anyone's money
stopped. And all of them years me having
that money, getting sex, traveling,
something you could do
alone in his bed [ __ ] with no money.
Bro, that's your life. Your skint life.
That's not my life. We don't all have
the same life as you. Bomb bedsit.
[ __ ] no money. Can't even leave his
[ __ ] shitty bedsuit. We don't all
have your poverty life. I mean, look at
it right now. Yeah. Let's talk about
things we've actually got, bomb. Better
TV than you, better clothes than you,
more money than you, a better bed than
you. Like, come in and talk, bro. At the
end of the day, mate, it doesn't matter
where you go in the world. Yeah, mate.
And my head ain't bigger than yours.
That [ __ ] ugly, bold virgin head that you've got.
That [ __ ] ugly skint baldy head that
you've got, you baldy bastard. You
remember when you were trying to call me
bald with that big fat ugly virgin head
of yours? That big skin ugly bold
northern virgin head of yours and I made
you run away off of YouTube. Guess what,
bro? Do you know the difference is bomb?
No one made me run away from YouTube
because of my [ __ ] head. Nobody made
me run away from YouTube like you did.
No one's made me run away cuz I was so
ugly. We made you run away cuz you know
you're an ugly bastard. As soon as your
head got out there, man, you ran away
cuz you know you're ugly. So everything
that you say, you contradict yourself.
You're on 240 [ __ ] pounds a [ __ ]
month. You just give yourself away
there, kid. You've literally just give
you literally give yourself away there.
Yeah, you've literally gave yourself
away there, kid.
And also, if somebody was to get 80
pound a week, it's actually more than
240 a month, [ __ ] So, get your
maths right. You know, it doesn't kill
me at all. I've got more money than you.
I'm better looking than you. I've got a
better life than you. You don't know how
much money I get. I've got over 3K this
month and last month. Try again. It must
kill you though being on £240 a month.
It must kill you though being on £240 a month.
I've got more money than you would ever
have. And you know when I'm saying that
I'm right as well. So that's it. Bro,
listen. You're on £240 a month. Get out
of here. You fat ugly virgin in his
little shitty bed sit talking about my
TV. My TV's better than yours. I'm
better looking than you. I'm not some
40year-old [ __ ] on benefits like you,
mate. You're in your [ __ ] 40s on
benefits, you skid loser. How the [ __ ]
you trying to talk about me, bro? In
your shitty little beds sit with your
shitty little TV and your shitty head
with your shitty benefit money. Trying
to talk about me, brother. Everyone has
not got the same life as you.
£240 a month self projecting again. I
just told you I've got more. If I've got
200 If I get £240 a month, how have I
how have I got more than a year's worth
in my bank account? That's your own life
you're talking about. That's your own
self-p projecting life. Just like when
you used to say that people was ugly and
you turned out to be ugly and you ran
off of YouTube. That's your own life.
All you're talking about is your own
life. That's why I'm not blocking you
because everything that you say is about
is a self- projection and a
self-reflection of your own life. So,
we're not even blocking you. Keep
talking about your life. Keep talking
about how you're disabled. You don't get
three grand a month. You're on 240 a
month. Keep talking about your life, bro.
I love it. You can keep talking about
your life, fatty head. But you know
what, Bomb though? No, no, no, no, no,
no. I'm not even going to like slay Bomb
that much to be honest. Like he got me
laid. You know that day I went to
Manchester the second time. I got this
[ __ ] fat ugly bastard got me laid
when he was sat there skin in his virgin
shitty little bed suit with a shitty TV.
He got me [ __ ] laid.
But seriously, bomb, you need to sort
that head out cuz that is [ __ ] ugly.
Trying to tell everybody that you get a
haircut every week when you don't even
have any hair. You [ __ ] ugly manta.
You ugly skint manta. [ __ ] hell. You
ugly skint manta. You ain't got a
[ __ ] clue, do you, son?
Was a serial self projector. [ __ ]
£240 a month.
What the [ __ ]
We've he said that I've got £240 a
month. Yeah, I've got more than a year's
worth of that in my bank account right now. [Laughter]
He's a self projector.
He's projecting Grezy. He's a projector.
He's the one that's on that amount of
money. Where the [ __ ] did that come
from? You need to ask yourself this
stuff, Grevy. Yeah.
Where this stuff actually comes from
because I have never been on £240 a month.
You don't know how much money I get. You
don't know how much money I have. Stop self projecting.
Like, it's that simple, isn't it? It's
that [ __ ] simple, bro.
He's a [ __ ] Bro, he's a self projector, man. £240
a [ __ ] month. I spent triple that
last weekend. He's a self projector.
Everything Bomb says is about himself.
Big head. He's got a big head. Skin,
he's skin. Everything he says is about
his own life, bro.
Are you forgetting this guy ran away
when his head got out there? His actual
big fat head got out there. He ran off of YouTube. Yeah, man. Oh [ __ ]
Yeah, these people are self projectors, bro.
Yep. Self projector again. Ain't got a
pot to piss in. Yep. Talking about yourself again.
Self-reflectctors everywhere. Greavvesy.
Yep. You asking for life. Talking about yourself.
Yep. That's you you're talking about.
You asking. Yes, you are.
Yeah, man. Skint. Yeah. Self projector.
Same reason why you don't Same reason
why you don't have a job.
You skint self-reflector.
Exactly the same reason. Same question
to you. Why don't you get a job? Same
question to you. Why don't you get a
job? I sound like Monty now, you know,
cuz Monty used to do this [ __ ]
Oh man. Do you know what it is funny to
be honest? Now it is entertainer because
they talk like they know your life, but
they're only bouncing off their own
lives. £240 a month. [ __ ] me. I didn't
know I get £240 a month. That's news to me, mate.
That's really news to me.
Really? That that I didn't know I got
£240 a month. Jesus Christ.
That is [ __ ]
self projecting, bro.
To the [ __ ] max.
Why don't you get yourself a job?
Why don't you get a job?
Same question to you. Why don't you get a job? Get
>> off of YouTube, you skin bastard. Get
yourself a job.
and stop self projecting.
I might have to do a video and bomb the self projector. Yeah, man.
I get £240 a month. Jesus Christ, if
only these people knew. Eh, if only
these people [ __ ] knew.
Then he says I get 240 a month. But if I
got 80 pound a week, that would be, you know,
320 a month, not 240. So your math is a
bit a bit off to be honest with you,
bum. So which one is it? You know,
these people don't know how much money people have
and they talk like they do. It's quite hilar
isn't it? It's quite hilar self projectors. Mom's
a self projector. Oh,
I'm going to have to do a video on bomb.
It is It is a bit funny. It is a bit
It's the same as Money M. They come out
with the most random specific things. So
it must be their own lives that they're
talking about. You know what I'm saying? [Laughter]
Do you remember when Monty used to do this? Greasy. Yeah.
Do you remember?
£240 a month.
Even though I've got more than a years
of that in my bank account.
Interesting, mate. Isn't it very interesting?
These people are self-relectors,
Grezy. These people are [ __ ] self-p
projectors. They didn't get anyone's
money [ __ ] stopped.
And mate, even if you I mean, if you got
someone's money stopped, one of you
would have been getting killed. A and B,
I would have found another way to make
money, mate. So, I mean, what? It took
you four years to get someone's money
stopped. Oh, Bob, stop lying. Stop
talking [ __ ] mate. You know what I'm saying?
So, what it took you So, it took you
four years to get my money stopped. Oh,
that's that's good that you let somebody
enjoy three grand a month for 4 years.
Really? But for four four years of me
getting that money,
you you finally got it stopped after
four years. I don't think so, mate.
I really really don't think so.
And I've seen you speak about that a few
times as well. £240.
Bro, you are an absolute [ __ ] clown.
Even if I got [ __ ] £1,200 a month
instead of 3k a month, £1,200 a month
instead of 3k, bro, somebody would have
been getting killed. So if I was left
with [ __ ] £300 a [ __ ] month, mate,
somebody would definitely be getting
killed, you know.
That is funny as [ __ ] man. These people
these people self reflectors.
It see how they're [ __ ] self-reflectors, man.
Real real self-reflectors.
Don't know where somebody would come out
with 240 above.
They didn't get anyone's money stopped.
They knew about the court case and then
when it happened, they tried to make it
seem like they're the ones that got the
money stopped when they never. That's
what they That's what they done. They
would never have got my money stopped,
mate. Cuz one of these people would have
been getting [ __ ] killed.
Trust me. I mean, I don't think you
stopped me getting three grand, mate,
and left me with 300 a month, you know?
These people. Hey, Grezy. These people, mate. Honestly.
Yeah. Bomb is just a failure in life. A
complete and utter [ __ ] up.
But in a way it is, like I said, it's
entertaining because they don't actually
know how much money you have. That's the
thing about it is they don't know how
much money you have and they try to talk
like they know how much money you have
when they [ __ ] don't. That's the funny thing.
You know what I'm saying?
I mean, I could go out every week. I
don't know why I don't. I just don't.
It's not affordability, mate. It's not affordability.
I assure you it's not. I mean, I could
go out tomorrow if I really want to, but
I can't be annoyed with it.
There's not actually a real reason why
to be honest. I mean what tomorrow I'd
spend what maybe £100.
Let's just say you get an escort month.
What what would you spend £100? Why
can't I go out and spend £100 every week? Why?
You know, doesn't make a lot of sense.
Of course I could. The [ __ ]
He's a [ __ ] idiot any man that
£240 a [ __ ] month. What the [ __ ]
really really needs to stop believing
this red star.
I'm going to have to do a video about
this, bro, cuz I don't want people
actually believing this [ __ ] and
just punch lies and then I'm going to
bring up the nons thing as well, you know?
So just clearing the air cuz yeah it's
an annoying it's an annoying rumor if
anyone actually believes it you know
it's a madness Yeah.
Yeah, bombers are selfjector. One sec. Right,
I'm going to go [ __ ] here. I'll be right
back. Going to make a cup of [ __ ] and
then come back, bro. Two seconds.
No, I'm back.
>> [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, they've never had my money stop, bro.
Trust me, they never have.
They just make up stuff.
These people on here really need to get
a life, you know?
You know what I'm saying?
Never ever got my money stop. Never.
I don't know why they keep making up the
stories that they have. Yeah, man.
What do you think of it all? Greet uh
Steven Howard, I think it's all [ __ ] weird, me.
I think it's all [ __ ] weird. And I
didn't get [ __ ] three grand from [ __ ] subletting.
I didn't get three grand from subleting.
A lot of it was my benefits.
So, get your facts right, mate.
It's actually like two and a bit, but
still bad. But you didn't get anyone's
money stopped. Trust me, you never Yeah.
Cuz we might get genuine people like
Scoop and genuine people like other
other genuine people. They might
actually believe it.
They might actually genuinely believe
it. You know what I'm saying? And we
don't want that, bro. Because Yeah.
I've actually I actually lost, 1700
pound from the sublet. So, I didn't I
didn't lose three grand, mate. I lost about 1,700,
which is still [ __ ] [ __ ] But, you
know what I'm saying? Like, you don't
know how much money people have. You
don't know how much money people get. I
don't want to go out tomorrow because I
don't want to go out tomorrow.
I could probably spend £80 if I wanted
to. But I'm just sick of the whole [ __ ]
I don't [ __ ] know exactly why. You
know, when I had the house, when I used
to be cooked for, I would go 6 weeks
without going out and I was still
getting the money. But
I mean, and there's a way I can make
money as well if I wanted to, which I'm
not going to get into cuz no one's
business. But still, you know, stop
[ __ ] thinking that everyone's got the
same life as you.
And that's what it is. Steven Howard,
they think everyone's got the same life as them. Oh yeah.
They are projectors.
[ __ ] projectors, mate.
Anyways, why is this red why is this red
star guy so jealous of me, bro? What the
[ __ ] man? So weird.
So obsessed with me. Just is it cuz I'm
better looking than him or something? I
don't know why he's so obsessed with me.
This weirdo, man. Yeah,
I don't know where we got that £240 from.
He's [ __ ] must be talking about his [ __ ] self.
He ain't [ __ ] talking about me, mate.
Not talking about me.
And he said I got £80 a week. So if I
got 80 a week, surely to god that would
be more than
240 a [ __ ]
it would be more than 240 a month. He
doesn't even make sense. He's a [ __ ]
He doesn't know what money I get. He
doesn't know how much money I get.
So yeah, I don't know why he's [ __ ]
I could go out tomorrow if I wanted to.
Well, I don't know. I just can't be
bothered with it
cuz it's always the same [ __ ]
every time you go out in it, Grezy. So [ __ ] yeah.
Would you go out tomorrow if you was messy? No,
I think Greavvesy would if he was me. Wouldn't you?
Would you go out, Grezy,
for a few drinks?
Would you go out for a few drinks, Greavvesy? A,
would you go out tomorrow if you was me? Steven Howard.
Would you go out drinking if you was me? Few drinks. Huh?
you grieve few drinks? Nah,
I don't find this country funny.
There's nothing to laugh at in this
country. I don't find any of it funny.
Being rejected by women, being put in a
bad mood, I don't find any of it funny.
Do you find any of it funny, Grezy? I don't.
I don't find it funny.
Yep. You'll meet someone when you least
expect it. So they say. Yep. Yeah.
What do you think will happen, Steven,
if I do some approaches in the pub tomorrow?
What do you think will happen if I do
some approaches in the pub? Any anyone's
got anyone got any predictions or
anyone got any predictions? Yeah.
Yeah. When you tell me what will happen
if I do some approach in the clubs tomorrow.
Yeah. When you answer me what will
happen if I do and I want you to be
honest. If I go
if I go to the boss tomorrow and do some approaches.
>> No, but what? No, but what would they
say when I approach?
Yeah, but they can't have a boyfriend
though because they're in the clubs.
Yeah, but they're in the bars and clubs,
grievy, so how could I have boyfriends, you know?
What's that subreddit about?
What's it about? Yep.
Oh, come on. Right. I'm just
cup of [ __ ]
Ry lovely cup of [ __ ]
Do you like a cup of cuntsy?
Crazy. Do you be honest? Do you think I
can afford to go out drinking every week?
I'm telling you I [ __ ] can.
I'm telling you I [ __ ] can, mate.
Why don't we tell Why don't we ask
Squeezy what he thinks?
What do you think, Stephen? Now, do you
think I can go out drinking every week?
Pretty sure I can.
What do you think? Really?
Have you seen that where people have
lost their [ __ ]
Steven Howard? Do you think I could
afford to go out drinking every week?
I've read it before where people have
lost their like YouTube income.
Like they're they're getting drastically
a lot less money now because of [ __ ] YouTube.
It's funny, isn't it? Yeah.
I could go out drinking every week if I
wanted, mate. But I don't want to. So
cuz it will never change with women. So
there's no point me going out, you know.
should really go out tomorrow because my
hair's still fresh, but nah, it's too depressing.
It's too depressing, bro.
Yeah, I got some nice clothes.
But no, I'm good, bro.
It's too [ __ ] depressing, man.
It's too depressing in it.
I got Spider-Man mug. See, look. Yeah.
No, I can't go out, bro. It's too depressing.
It's too depressing. Grezy,
why do you find it so funny, Grezy?
It's not funny. It's depressing.
I'm I'm in a bad mood when I'm in this
country. It's [ __ ] depressing.
Ruy thinks it's funny.
Rubs is a nasty [ __ ]
Rubs is a nasty little [ __ ] Yeah,
Grey's is a nasty cat.
Greasy's a nasty little [ __ ]
Aren't you Grezy?
Aren't you Grezy? A nasty [ __ ]
Are you a nasty little [ __ ]
You're a nasty little [ __ ]
Women are bad people in general. Grievy,
never forget that. Yeah.
Never forget that.
Never ever forget that greasy wound or
bad bad bad people in general.
Could you imagine Gregy being a landlord
for four years?
Grievesy could never be a landlord.
Greavves as a landlord.
Greasy, could you do it? Could you be a landlord?
How much money did you save this month? Greavves.
Was it 500?
Uh, was it 500? Bless you.
Oh, bless you.
Was it 500?
Bless you then. Oh, bless
That's so cute.
You were supposed to say 500.
I beat you. I saved a thousand.
I saved a thousand this month.
Yeah, I got lucky in a few things. So you know.
Yeah, that's good, isn't it? I saved a
thousand this month. That's That's good,
isn't it, Groovy?
And don't forget, I had a [ __ ] mad
weekend as well, which was expensive. Yeah.
Yeah. I saved more than you, Grezy. best shot.
Last month I saved
Last month I saved 400. This month I saved 1,000.
Good. Is it Greavves? I done good. Mhm.
How much did you save this month, Steven Howard?
I keep getting these [ __ ] porn ads
keep popping up. Grey, is there any way
to get rid of them?
They're like [ __ ] porn ads.
It's [ __ ] annoying, man.
Yeah. Is there a way to get rid of it? Grezy.
Yeah. You beat Grezy, but I beat you.
You beat Graves and I beat you.
Is it expensive?
What if you delete Chrome and then reinstall it?
Yeah, I'm not going to lie. It's [ __ ]
annoying, bro. And I don't want to get
someone's number and then they pull the
screen down and then they see this porn [ __ ]
Just porn sites. Yeah.
There's definitely a way to get rid of
it, isn't it, Greasy? There's got to be
a way to get rid of it. No.
Grezy. I just I was just calling Captain [ __ ]
but he hasn't picked up. Captain,
that's what we used to call the Jamaican
guy uh that used to come and do the
scrap for us at the house. Captain.
That's what you say. Captain.
I didn't see captain last time I went there. Captain. Captain gunsy.
I can't believe you only saved 350 this
month, you silly goose.
You're such a silly goose.
£1,200 a month is enough for Greavvesy, isn't it?
Is it enough for you, Grezy? Bless you.
It's not enough for Peter Belly.
No, it's all right, man.
Try and save more.
So, what if you wanted to go out
drinking, Grezy? What would you do if
you wanted to go out drinking?
cuz you can't afford to go out drinking.
Can you greasy? You can't afford to go out drinking [Laughter]
Virgin boy skin in the bedroom with no
bed and no money in it. We can smell
your [ __ ] mile off, son. [Laughter]
You think it's all a [ __ ] laugh,
don't you, Greasy?
You think it's all a laugh. What
do you think?
I made you laugh.
My friend says that he has 600 pound
to last him for a month. [ __ ] hell.
Well, I'm going Yeah. See you later, alligator. tomorrow