All [Music]
right, this little [ __ ] [ __ ] has
been [ __ ] texting me. Yeah, [ __ ]
I woke up. I see his [ __ ] messages.
He's a [ __ ] clown, man. And yes, you
do look like [ __ ] Timmy Eldridge. And
I knew you were still watching as well.
I knew he was still watching.
Um, am I going out? Have you got brain
damage? I literally said for the past
three days, I'm not going out. Have you
got brain damage or something? You must
have something wrong with your brain or
something where you don't listen to
things properly. But anyways, yeah, this
is to [ __ ] Monty. I already went to
Birmingham last time. Yeah, it's it's on
you now to come to [ __ ] London for
[ __ ] sake. Why would Why would you
have brain damage? Because I literally
told you already that I'm not going out.
I literally told you that's me done
until my birthday and you're asking me
the same question. So, you must have
brain damage. Nothing changed. I didn't
change my mind. I don't change my mind on things.
So, yeah. Anyways, this [ __ ] was
[ __ ] I was live and I told everyone
on YouTube that was watching me, you
being one of them. So anyways, uh Monty,
you should come to [ __ ] London. You
should come to London, man. I went to
Birmingham last time. You [ __ ] little
[ __ ] You [ __ ] nons
me on [ __ ] Facebook. He ain't about
nothing, mate. I'd rather have no bird
than have the birds that you get. Fat,
ugly [ __ ] slags. You know, [ __ ]
Kaye. Yeah. And [ __ ] Natalie. I've
never been with anything as ugly in my
life. And trust me, I've been with like some
not so good-looking people when I'm
drunk. Like, bro, he's with [ __ ] a
fat ugly slag. I'd rather have nothing
than than be with that, bro. And I've
been had my chance to be with that. And
I didn't [ __ ] want that. You know
what I mean? Yeah. He should come to
[ __ ] London. I'll smash his [ __ ] face in.
Oh, you shout it from LJ. uh get your
facts right. LJ actually stood behind
the gate and didn't want none of it and
had several chances to hit me. I didn't
need to come outside and I also gave him
a second chance. You are the one that
was arguing with [ __ ] Michael and
[ __ ] Timmy for God knows how long.
Even though you all live in the same city
and none of you done nothing. What a
bunch of [ __ ] clowns. None of you
done [ __ ] nothing to each other. Oh yeah.
Hey, why won't he come to London? I'll
meet you. I definitely will meet you if
you come to London.
You know, I'll just go out on a drink
and I'll just meet you at the same time.
But he won't come to London because he's
scared. He's scared. He's [ __ ]
skinned. I'm not [ __ ] wasting my time
and [ __ ] money going to [ __ ]
Birmingham. But [ __ ] what, bro? I already went.
It's your turn to come to London now. You know,
[ __ ] hell, man. [ __ ] pedo.
Yeah. [ __ ] Skint Pedo.
[ __ ] messaging me and [ __ ]
I woke up at 2:30, by the way. I always
wake up the same time, 2:30. It's
really, really bad, man. Really bad.
I know it's bad, to be fair. Messaging
me talking [ __ ] trying to say, "Oh, I
can't get laid and and for me to come to
Birmingham." I said, "Listen, come to
[ __ ] London and I'll slap your
[ __ ] head in." Simple.
I don't need to come to [ __ ]
Oh, no more bomb. Bye-bye self
projector. Anyways, we're talking um about [ __ ]
bomb. Sorry, we're talking about [ __ ]
uh Monty. Stop messaging me telling me I
can't get laid. I would never get with
them [ __ ] ugly women that you get
with. I've never been with anything as
ugly as [ __ ] Kaye and [ __ ] Natalie
G. Never, bro. I swear to God, I've
never been with anything as ugly as that.
Trust me, bro. Trust me. And I've been
with some Yeah. not so good-looking
people when I've been drunk, but still.
Even that [ __ ] transgender looking
thing was better than Natalie G. You
know that thing in the [ __ ] O'Neils?
Even she was [ __ ] better.
You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
I want to ignore these accounts. Anyway,
grievy man. Um, I can go out whenever I
want. I've got a couple of thousand in
my account. I can go out whenever I
want. I can gamble whenever I want.
These people don't know me. They don't
know how much money I've got. So, let
this bomb under these fake accounts. He
self projected. He doesn't know what
money people have. He doesn't know what
money people don't have. And he also
never got any of my money stopped. And
he doesn't know how much money I get a
month either. So yeah, you can keep
guessing and getting it wrong.
Like Griez, I don't want to go out
drinking today cuz I can't be bothered
because it's just the same old [ __ ]
every time you go out. I think that's a
fair point. No, I think like that's
that's a fair reason why I don't want to go out.
Like my haircut expense is already gone.
So all I would be spending is 80 to 150.
I don't want to go out. I don't [ __ ]
want to. You know, it's it's Simple as
that, you know.
I could go out today, I can go to
Birmingham, I could book a hotel, I can
get on the piss
and I still have loads of money. As an
example, I don't want to. Do you understand?
You know what I mean?
Was that not a good enough reason, Grezy?
So yeah, it's just the same old [ __ ]
And the longer you go without going out,
you also enjoy it more.
And I'm discouraged, you know, getting [ __ ]
um 10 numbers or not a date. I'm just
very discouraged by that. So I just
don't want to
make sense. No.
Doesn't that not make sense, Squeezy?
to go out every week if I wanted to.
Every week, but I don't want to. Simple.
So, yes, you do not own me. You do not
get any of my money stopped. And you
also don't know how much money I get. So keep self-projected.
You did not get anyone's money stopped.
And I can also make money whenever I
want to. You've got severe mental health.
Yeah. I couldn't even do a football bet
today anyways. Greasy cuz I woke up at
2:30 and the football um starts at three
and yeah, I was nowhere near a bookie.
So and I wouldn't have done a bet
anyways. I don't think. Let's just hope
the two that I was going to pick didn't both score. So yeah,
think with Natalie G is a W.
He generally generally thinks that being
with Bro, I wouldn't even get with her
if I was [ __ ] 10 Guinnesses down.
Greavesy, are you [ __ ] mad?
She is [ __ ] stinking sand. Kaye is
He's not even been with a [ __ ] decent
looking [ __ ] woman and he's trying to
talk about [ __ ] me. I'd rather have nothing.
wouldn't even [ __ ] get head off the [ __ ] [ __ ] You know,
he's a little soft ass. Monty's a little
soft ass. [ __ ] Same with [ __ ]
Michael Basset. Same with [ __ ] Timmy.
They're all soft asses.
All the soft asses live in [ __ ] Birmingham. Yeah.
All [ __ ] soft asses, mate.
That's what they are. Stuffed bastards.
I didn't bet.
But yeah, I could go out drinking. I
could go out right now. How much? Right.
Let me just
I could go out and spend £400 every week
if I wanted to.
Like, not that I would spend £400 every
week. Not that a night out would come to
that, but I could go out every week and
spend £400 and still have money.
You don't know how much money people
have. You don't know how much money
people get. But it's entertaining though
to like think these people know how much
you have. It is in a way. Yeah. Entertaining
to be fair.
If I wanted to, I could go on a blast
every week, but I don't want to cuz it's
[ __ ] it's the same [ __ ]
and I'm discouraged from the last week as well.
I still wouldn't go out. Even if I won a
bet, I still wouldn't go out. I'm
generally done, bro. You not understand.
You remember when I You remember when I
started betting on the football, right?
You remember when I started betting on
the football and I'd win? I still
wouldn't go out until maybe two weeks
after. Yeah. Even when I won on the
football, I never used to go out. That's
how I knew I was done. I'd go to like
the cinema or something. I wouldn't even
go out. I still wouldn't go out drinking
because it was always the same old in
this country. Like it would always be
the same old. So yeah,
even if I won a football bet, even if I
done a bet today
and when I win, it's like, "Oh, I've got
more money to carry over." Yes.
I still wouldn't go out whether I won a
bet or I didn't win a bet because it's
always just the same old [ __ ] Yeah. I
went out last week, which was the first
time in a month. I go out like once a
month or every 6 weeks.
Yeah. And even then, I was about to do a U-turn.
So, I'm really really done in this
country. I'm putting this money to good
use, bro. For real. I'm not trying. I I
I won't when I go out again, it's
because I generally want to go out
because I'm bored out my head. It would.
It's because that that way I can say,
"Oh, well, I had fun anyways." I'm not
having fun going out every week. It's
not long enough, you know? I wouldn't
have fun going out every week,
man. I could do it every week. I got the
I've got the money to do it every week.
It's only 80 to 150,
but nah. Can't be asked. Can't be
annoyed with it. Boring.
I'd rather just Yeah. Just save the
money, put it to good use. So, yeah,
I went out cuz I wanted to go out and drink,
but that's why I'm not going out today
cuz nothing ever changes. Nothing will
ever change with women. So,
but yeah, bomb never got anyone's money
stopped. I've got money and I can make
money whenever I want. If I needed more
money, you don't know how much people
have. You don't know how much people
don't have. £240 a month.
Jesus [ __ ] Christ.
These people really are serial self projectors.
It's funny. It is funny. Sad but funny, you know. So yeah,
it's nice to go and even when I had the
house, I wasn't going out every week.
I've not been out every week for like a
year. Like yeah, I've not been out. I
take six week breaks,
four, three, you know, they're all
different. I never went out every week
in the past year I had the house.
Maybe a year ago I did, but even when I
had the house, I still wasn't going out
every week. You don't know anything
about anyone or what people have, what
people don't have.
You really, really, really, really,
really, really don't. And people don't
need to prove themselves to you.
So that's it. Yeah,
Like I said, back when I was in the old
house, tenants used to cook for me. Used
to play GTA, went out every 3 weeks maybe.
Or I'd go out. I'd stay in until I feel
like I could no longer stay in. So I'd
stay in. I was like, "Okay, now I really
need to go out." That's it. It was It's
been that way for a year, you know.
Because it just got boring going out.
Um I don't know what else you can really
say. I mean, we can't even say it's a
waste of money cuz we got money. So, I
mean, it wouldn't really affect, you know, but
us. But nah,
after last week, bro, I'm good.
I'm really, really good.
I can't wait to leave.
So, I guess it's not even not really about
the money either really because I can go
out every week if I want to. I can go to
a new city every week if I wanted to.
And I'd still have money. So, what the
[ __ ] Think about people have what
people don't have. They had McDonald's as well.
So yeah, and like I said, I'm going out
on my birthday just cuz it's simply my
birthday. So, and then I think I'll be out.
Then after that it'll be December, then
it'll be then it'll be it'll be in mid
December. Then it'll be New Year's Eve.
I hope them ones [ __ ] didn't score, bro.
I'm going to be very sad if they did.
Yeah. Colchester [ __ ]
Am I going anywhere with my mates? Nope.
I'm going out with my sister on my
birthday cuz we've been talking about
going out for a long time, but we just
didn't get around to doing it.
Then I'm going away, then I'll go out
again. I don't know. December is a time
I'd get tempted to go out in to be fair
cuz December's very busy.
But I'm definitely going away New Year's Eve 100%.
Been saying it for so many years. I'm
going to go out of London one New Year's Eve.
This This time I'm definitely going to
do it. Think I'm going to go Scotland.
I'm going to probably book it soon to be fair.
The trains for New Year's Eve
or book the flights. I could either book
the flights or book the train.
Just my sister.
Yeah, I either
book the flights or book the train.
Which one? Eh,
the train is just easier, isn't it? And cheaper.
Definitely [ __ ] off New Year's Eve. Definitely. Nope.
Yeah, I definitely need to do something
this New Year's.
Yeah, I've took breaks going out when
I've had money, when I've had loads of
money, when I've had [ __ ] Well, I've
never had no money for [ __ ] years.
But still, it's not about It's not about
a money thing.
It's not about anything to do with money.
Don't know last week. Why would I go out
again when last week I got 10 numbers
and I haven't even got a date? It's discouraging.
It's so discouraging.
It's not even worth the time. Yep.
I hope them teams don't score, bro.
I really hope they don't score, man.
all right in a little bed suit with no
bed, no money in it.
You like that, don't you, Sham?
You like that? You little shitty bedset
out of London.
Be honest, mate. You like it, don't you? Come on.
I don't know how Monty was trying to say
to me, "Oh yeah, you go for escorts. You
go for escorts." But he wanted an
escort. When we went back to [ __ ]
where he was staying, he wanted an
escort. I'm just listening to his voice
now. And no, I can understand Kayle's
ugly but not Natalie. Natalie G is ugly
the same as Kaye the same as you. You're
all [ __ ] ugly. What the [ __ ]
and that energy is [ __ ] ugly. What the [ __ ]
And so is Kaye.
They're both ugly, bro. What the [ __ ]
People have seen women that I've pulled
You know what I mean? People have seen
women that I have pulled. Monty, you know,
people have already seen women that I've pulled
and they've all been [ __ ] better than
[ __ ] what Monty's had.
[ __ ] hell, man.
Guys are [ __ ] tall.
[ __ ] even USA. Izzy was better than [ __ ] Natalie.
He was [ __ ] kind of stinking as well. [ __ ] idiot.
No, no, no, no, no.
Don't know what I fancy to eat today.
One of them bathe again.
could be another number, you know.
Well, obviously if it conked up with
[ __ ] that's the problem. Oh, man.
I can make money right now and [ __ ]
wouldn't go out.
This I've got I've got a bone to pick with you, Timmy.
[ __ ] better be Timmy. Hey,
what I told you about Have a mon. Timmy,
>> what matter?
>> That that I was just talking to Monty.
He's a [ __ ] spaz. I said if he's got
>> nons PJ, you know this. Turn down the
teddy, man. I'm on the I'm on the hangs
with Peter. We can play it back afterwards, bro.
>> Yeah, I told I told him I told him it's
time to come to London. I told him it's
his turn to come to London now.
>> Nah, he won't come to London, bro. He's
a grass. He put his own bird in the
[ __ ] nick the nons.
>> Timmy, you do remind me of him, though.
Timmy, you do remind me of him a little bit.
>> Shut up. I don't wear three pound hats
from Primark. My hats cost302 plus the
>> You wearing a little You was wearing a
little You was wearing You was wearing a
little You was wearing a little Lacost
hat, wasn't you, Timmy?
>> Pardon? You was wearing a little
lacrosse hat, wasn't you, Timmy?
>> Yeah, that cost me 38 quid. That one
did. That's not a cheap hat, that one.
>> I know, man. How's the game?
>> Anyway, anyway, PJ, let's get to the
point. You haven't got any money to gamble. >> Mhm.
>> No, I'm I'm skin. Can you give me 20?
>> Yes, you are. Would you like me to
donate you 55 p?
>> I won £500 roulette last week,
>> bro. Be careful of them machines. You
>> No, no, no. It was online. It was
online. No, no, Timmy. It was It was It
was last Sunday. It was last It was last
So, what you done with your £500?
>> I just left it in the bank. Just left it there.
>> Can I have a look?
>> What? If you want,
>> please do. Stop for me. It's just so you
can go and say I'm not skinned. I'm not
>> I've already showed you that I'm not ski,
>> bro. I didn't see the 500 quid. That's
why I'm asking you to show me.
>> You showed I showed you £1,300 before,
>> bro. When was that? I can't remember.
I'm a [ __ ]
>> [ __ ] It was like back in February, March.
>> [ __ ] me. September now, bro.
>> Yeah. How's the gambling been for you? >> Halloween, >> huh?
>> It's Halloween now.
>> How's the gambling been for you?
>> Well, I'll show you PJ right now. I'll
put on my magic camera. Right. It's been
hit and miss. I started the week off with 723
Sterning pounds. Right. We have live
kings and millionaires even though I've
got to go out and buy a lawn mower
because it's just blown up. Right.
Let me get to the wall.
I've still got that left which is about £495
and I've got 1 pound50 in scrap nod in
my pocket. So
>> well to
last you for the month doing okay
>> to last you for the month.
>> No till next Friday.
>> How much do you get next Friday? >> 2.3,000.
>> No you don't.
>> No I do. Honestly, I do, mate. Yeah.
>> How? How?
>> Bro, I'm not on benefits anymore. You
I'm I'm self-employed. I'm doing all
right. We We We've got a new company
called Cleaners on Tours. >> Really?
>> Yeah. We're going to be We're going to
be on telly soon. Right. You still do.
We're going to do one of them TV
programs where we can do your house up
in 60 minutes.
>> I I think me and you should go out New
Year's Eve. PJ, you've got to [ __ ]
say a lot of stories to people before
you and me actually speak.
>> I was thinking we could go to Blackpool
in the West Midlands. Bro,
>> you've got a lot of women to apologize
to because I need to discuss that with
you. What was you Why was you having a
go at that woman, bro? I know you
struggle with But I mean, that was a bit
out of line. That poor girl looks so
[ __ ] lost. It was untrue.
>> It was funny, was it?
>> Funny, Peter. Not funny. It
>> is funny, is it?
>> Be funny. Right. I'm going to show you
an example. Peter. Right. Right. Peter,
right? Look at my face. Smile. Funny.
Not funny. You were asking that woman.
So anyway, right. Um, let's get to the
point. What's your opinion on Lord Egg?
>> I think he's a [ __ ] [ __ ] Naunt.
>> You going to Birmingham and give him a good batting? Huh?
>> Are you going to battle him? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. You know, you know he's in
Birmingham in November. I'm not going.
He [ __ ] cost me 300 quid last time
and he's I said to him to go live,
right? And I was [ __ ] you
>> 300 quid. >> Pardon?
>> Who the [ __ ] Why the [ __ ] did he go
Blackpool? Who goes to Blackpool in the
winter? He's so
>> Yeah. Who goes to Pound Bank for their
[ __ ] lunch on holiday in Blackpool?
>> Yeah, it's cuz he's skin.
>> Is it? But you're skinned, too. No, but
you're also skin.
>> You're broke. PJ, show me a Fiverr. Mhm.
>> Uh, no, man. Can you give me £10?
>> You're that [ __ ] broke. Give me a
PayPal and I'll put it in.
>> No, you can. You can bank transfer me. >> God. >> Huh?
>> Anyway, PJ, before I go, what's gone on
with you and Mongol? What have you fell?
>> Oh, because he keeps messaging me
saying, "Oh, how Natalie G's I said
Natalie G's ugly." That's my opinion. I
think she's ugly. I don't know what your opinion is.
>> That's the to be fair, that's the
funniest thing I've heard Peter say all [ __ ] week.
>> Sorry, man. That That actually is funny.
See, let's let's do the face again, PJ. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Funny. Last one. Not funny. Natalie G
was calling her fat. Extremely funny. >> Yeah.
So basically, do you call her a fat
[ __ ] [ __ ] or a [ __ ]
>> No, I just I just think she's ugly.
>> Did you say that she looks like Did you
call her Shrek? >> No.
>> Why' you call her Shrek? She looks like Shrek.
>> Do you not like her?
>> Do I? [ __ ] She [ __ ] wished a kid to
be stabbed. She's gone out with a bacon
who had a teenage dating app on his
phone. No, she's my best friend. PJ
don't [ __ ] like her. And Lisa, you
see what happened to And Lisa, she's a
mother level. She needs domestic bleach
on her [ __ ] self. She needs to dissolve.
>> That's Let's It's not about salting the
slug. It's about bleaching the what? The garretts.
>> Can you hear me, PJ? >> Hello.
I think your stream's [ __ ] PJ, you
need to reset.
>> I can hear you.
What was that?
What the [ __ ]
Yeah, man. I own [ __ ] Monty earlier.
[ __ ] [ __ ] was [ __ ] messaging me.
Stupid [ __ ] [ __ ]
He's saying how he's getting paid 2.3K
next Friday. Baz,
he's saying that he he has his he's um
he's not on benefits anymore. Oh man.
Yeah, he's a he's skinn he's a virgin.
Yeah, I own [ __ ] Monty earlier, man.
You know what made me laugh? I was on uh
Timmy's live earlier and someone said to
Timmy, "You need to stop gambling. get
off YouTube and get a woman. He told
Timmy to [ __ ] get a woman, mate. If I
can't even get a woman being [ __ ]
decent looking and [ __ ] normal and
having [ __ ] money, I don't think he's
going to get a woman, you know? It's
just like, nah.
Pretty sure that person must have been
[ __ ] trolling him, mate.
Yeah, I know. I know.
I know, man. [ __ ] madness.
No, no, no.
Yep. I met Slug ages ago, man. He's a [ __ ]
He's a proper [ __ ] like [ __ ] bugger. Yeah,
I met that [ __ ] skint through [ __ ] Yeah.
You know, the first thing he said was
that he chased me around the bull ring.
That's what he said. The first rumor he
made up was when we met, um, he chased
me around the boring. That was his first
[ __ ] lie, bro. Yeah.
Madness, isn't it? [ __ ] madness.
That was his first lie. Yeah.
Hey, [ __ ] I didn't go out today
drinking because I didn't want to. I can
afford it, but I just didn't want to.
You understand how it is, right? Going
out here and I have a boyfriend. It's
[ __ ] depressing, bro.
I just didn't want to. Oh, man.
I think they're going to [ __ ] score, man. Oh no.
[ __ ] should have put a bet on it. Now
Darlington needs All it needs is
Darlington to [ __ ] score.
Oh no. Should have put a bet on it.
I hope Darlington doesn't score.
Going to pick them [ __ ] teams as
well. [ __ ] sake.
Stop talking about yourself.
Nah, I won't. To be fair, I've got
enough money. I've got enough money. It
is what it is. But yeah, it won't be
nice if they score
cuz I generally think I could win a
football bet every [ __ ] week, bro.
I reckon I could.
Let's just hope they don't [ __ ] score.
But nah, not really to be fair cuz I
don't want to get into this gambling [ __ ] again.
So yeah, if they score then they score on it.
What can you say? If they score, they [ __ ] score. Yeah.
Yes. I've got plans in Birmingham,
Monty, but I'm not going to waste my
time and money going to [ __ ] Birmingham. Simple.
So that's why I ain't going. Waste of time.
Bet these can't score.
It is what it is. [Music]
They'll probably as well luck.
Uh, not long. Woke up. Just chilling,
playing some GTA.
Yeah, man. I've been asleep most of the
day. My day is always the same. Going to
get some food in a bit.
Told you I wasn't going out today. Not
worth the time, not worth the effort,
not worth the money. No. Uh,
probably very early to be fair. Yeah.
I told you I weren't going to go out drinking today. Absolutely pointless.
And I've got a boyfriend. I'm not
interested. [ __ ] that.
Country is a [ __ ] joke. So yeah,
I didn't do a football bat. I never said
I had a football bat.
I never said that on a football bet.
What the [ __ ]
I said on a football. I think this [ __ ]
the bet I was going to do is going to win. Typical up.
No, no, no, no. Yeah.
There's this bar like going to in
London. It's [ __ ] sick. No heat.
No, no, no.
could have went out to that bar today. It I'm [Music]
Uh, get some food, chill out, and go to sleep.
that's my plans. They're What's yours? Uh, Yeah,
>> I ain't going out. [ __ ] that.
Going out to get rejected. No, I'm good. Thanks.
Going out, wasting money and getting
rejected. [ __ ] that.
Still don't know what I'm going to eat, but yeah,
definitely not definitely not doing that.
If it would have changed, it would have
changed 5 years ago.
I don't think it's going to change. It
would have changed by now when I went up
and down the country approaching six
7,000 women. No, if it was going to
change, it would have already.
Don't dismiss my struggles.
That's one thing I ask you not to do is
dismiss my struggles.
If it was going to change, it would have
changed by now.
I've tried more than
anybody in the world of my age. Spent
money, traveled. If it was going to
change, I'm sure it would have changed by now.
So, do whatever you like, but do not
dismiss my struggles. That's one thing
I'll ask you not to do cuz I find it
quite offensive because it costs a lot
of money, a lot of time I put into this.
So when people dismiss my struggles, it's
I hate it. I find it offensive and why
hasn't it already changed?
Obviously the number one question is why
hasn't it already changed? We've been
trying for 5 years. We spent time. We
spent money. We've met enough women.
Yeah. I put too much in work. I I put
too much work. That's how I know to give
up in this country and I'm leaving. Simple.
So, are you forgetting the fact that I
got 10 numbers last week and didn't get
any dates for this week?
Did you seem to dismiss that?
Did you seem to dismiss that? Last week,
10 numbers, only one replied.
I don't think I'm going to be out again
in a hurry.
It would never change. Never.
If it was going to change, it would have
changed by now. Don't dismiss my struggles. Please.
Giving up is the only way and leaving,
which is what I'm doing in November.
This is a depressing life here.
A [ __ ] depressing life.
It's so depressing. That's why I'm not
going out today,
cuz it will be the same thing as it
always is. Don't dismiss my struggles, please. It's offensive.
Any thoughts on me trying for the past
four years and not getting anywhere? Uh
that keep keeps slipping your mind.
Um I tried for five years and I've got nowhere.
Um any thoughts on that or just dismiss
it like it never happened? Just dismiss
it. Yeah. Yeah.
No thoughts on the past four or five
years trying and getting nowhere,
wasting time and money getting [ __ ]
around. No, no opinions on that or
no. Today will be different. Yeah. Yeah.
Because today will be so much different
to them other four or five years you've tried.
Yeah. Yeah. Right. What's the odds?
That's more than [ __ ] lottery odds.
So one day So we're going to go out
today and we're not going to deal with
all of the [ __ ] that we've been dealing
with for 5 years. No way.
No way is that believable, bro. Come on.
You need to convince me. You need to
really really convince me. You need to
make me buy it. Just pretend you're a
marketer and you're trying to sell
something to me
cuz I'm not buying anything you're
saying. It 100% would have already
changed by now if it was going to change.
I I won't regret Nope. Nope. Nope. I see
this is funny, right? You say this,
right? Most people when they don't try,
they do regret it. But with me, I
already know the result. So, I'd rather
not try. I'd rather not humiliate myself
and have any more bad experiences. I
won't regret it at all because I've
tried enough. I've been trying for
years. So, in in in normal circumstances,
yes, people do regret it. But not me
because I've tried so much. I already
know the result. So, it doesn't bother
me. I mean, I've I've sat next to
someone on a bus, didn't speak to them,
didn't care. Glad I didn't because I
already knew what the result would be if I did.
it will be the same old boring as it
always is. So, I don't regret it. If I
see someone I like and I don't speak to
them, I don't regret it because I don't
I know I will have no more bad experiences,
one less bad experience. It doesn't
bother me. That's the thing where I've
tried so much
and I already know what it is. Don't
bother me. I don't regret. No regrets for me.
There'll be no depression tomorrow. Be lovely. [ __ ] lovely.
So yeah, I I don't regret not trying.
There's been people I've seen a look at
of before and I've liked them and I've
not done it.
No, I'm all right. Thanks. I'm retired.
Been there, done it, worn the t-shirt.
been there, done that, won the t-shirt. So, yeah,
the only way I'm going to try now is if
someone pays me, bro.
Pays me for my time.
I won't be trying again.
[ __ ] last week, 10 [ __ ] numbers,
not even a single day. Disgusting. Absolutely disgusting.
It's more disgusting than a pedophile.
It's more disgusting than a [ __ ] nons.
Could have easily went on a date this
week, spent 2300. Not a problem. We have the money. Uh,
I might order at like 4:00 in the morning.
I really hope Darlington don't score. So yeah,
I'm sure I would have met someone by now
if there was hope in this country. I'm sure. No, no,
I'm sure of it.
I got Oh, you know,
I don't know.
I know I'm good.
We got a lamb coming to be fairly I reckon.
What's the day today? Oh yeah, Saturday
should be like Saturday
in a little bed. No bed, no money in it.
You know my little saying skin in a bed
suit with no bed, no money in it.
I really hope these [ __ ] don't score.
Hey. Yeah. Yeah.
You sound like Rust the mouse.
He is from Jamaica.
Yeah, I do as well to be honest. I'm
just going to get a lamb curry.
I'm just in this habit of saving money.
You know, you ever get them habits where
you just want to save money? I don't know why.
Is this me Oh, Uh,
well, as soon as I've got my haircut,
probably about 80 to 100 pound.
Probably 80 to probably
probably 70 to about 120.
But I'm still not doing it
because I don't want to do it.
So, got the money. Could do it every
week if I wanted to. Yeah.
I'd say about 80 to 120. Yeah. What do you think?
Yeah. I'm sure I could have met the girl
in my dreams all them other four or five
years that I was trying, but I never.
I'm not so sure.
I'm sure if that would have happened,
that would have happened by now.
I'm sure it would have already happened by now.
And I'm sure today would be no different.
than all the other times I've gone out
and tried here. And I've got a boyfriend
getting numbers that mess around with
you. [ __ ] that. I'm not putting up with
that [ __ ] no more.
No, I'm not putting up with that [ __ ] no more.
If I would have met the girl of my
dreams, I'm sure I would be with someone
now. Traveled all over the country, been
out in London a million times, done
thousands of approaches. I'm not so sure
this time would be different.
It's not having an attitude. It's speaking facts.
I tried last week, got 10 numbers, don't
have a date this week.
And um that's not an attitude. That's
being realistic. That's telling the
truth. Like I went out last week,
got 10 numbers, no reply.
Uh one replied, "That's not an attitude.
That actually happened."
That's not an attitude. That's being
real. Just because it's something that
you don't like to hear, um it doesn't
mean it's an attitude. It's not a
defeatist attitude. It's the truth.
I went out last week, spent a [ __ ]
bomb and got nowhere.
That actually happened. That's my attitude. So yeah,
Please don't [ __ ] score.
So yeah, man.
Yeah, I didn't do a bet, bro. [ __ ] I
hope Darlington don't [ __ ] score cuz
that would have been my bet one.
So why are you saying that I've got a
defeist attitude by telling you the
truth? I have tried for the past four or five years
and it's the same old. Not interested. I
have a boyfriend. I'm going to mess you
around. That's not the fetus. That's
reality. That's telling you the truth.
Gonna get a nice curry today. [ __ ]
See, that's not being defeated. That's
telling the truth.
I'm so happy I didn't go out today.
Nah, you don't need to be sorry, man.
Everyone dismisses my struggles cuz it
don't suit them.
You don't need to be sorry. Sorry about what?
Everyone dismisses my struggles cuz it
doesn't suit them.
There's no way you going out today would
be different than any of them four or
five years you've been going out and
still haven't found anyone.
I mean, there's no [ __ ] way today
would be any different. And it never is
any different. Just like when we went
out last week, looks Maxon, that wasn't any different.
So, just like today would be no
different. Just like when we went to
Wales and then we went to Wales again.
It was absolutely no different
and it will never be any different here.
Nah, bro. I'm done with it.
I'm [ __ ] done with it. It's depressing.
If I was going to go out today, I would
have probably went to Wales to be
honest. I would have just got a train to Wales.
To be fair,
I don't even think I'd go out in London.
I just go to Wales or something.
Maybe I could do that now. Just go get a
train to Wales. as you do. Nah, no.
Um, maybe because the fact of what I was
telling you earlier about I've tried a
million times and I'm I still haven't found anyone.
Maybe that's why. Maybe because of why I
sent you earlier that you seem to dismiss
hear the same old [ __ ] I have a
boyfriend. I'm not interested. Takes its
toll on you.
So, I mean, there's every reason why not to go. So little
better not [ __ ] score, mate.
They [ __ ] better not
cuz I was going to put 120 on that.
They [ __ ] better not score, mate. No, no.
Nope. I'm confident.
I can approach sober.
Most people can't approach sober. Nope.
I've got confidence. I've got skills.
I've been doing this for years. Oh, nope.
My confidence is fine.
I got 10 numbers last week.
I can approach with confidence. I can approach sober.
Yep. No com no amount of confidence is
going to change the fact that these
women are stuck up in this country.
As much as I wish it was true, Nope.
And why are you saying more confidence
is needed when I am confident? I can
literally approach sober.
It's not about confidence. They're not
interested in this country. I mean, I
don't know how many approaches I have
exed, you know.
To be honest with you,
nothing wrong with my confidence,
nothing wrong with my approaches.
Not at all.
More confidence is needed. You should
just saw how confident I was [ __ ]
last week. I actually recorded an
approach, but I don't put it on this channel.
H, it's mad, is it? They never blame
women. They always blame the man.
It's [ __ ] madness, bro. This is why I
don't even bother no more.
Why are you telling me that I need more
confidence when I'm already confident
and I can approach anyone sober?
Why are you telling me that I need confidence
when I'm already confident? What the [ __ ]
Yeah, I know. I woke up at 2:30 to be fair. What's up?
These [ __ ] better not fall.
See if Darlington was playing home,
they would score 100%.
These [ __ ] better not [ __ ] score, man.
Sorry to record.
I'm going Thailand, but I'm going to
book another holiday next week.
I think I'm I'm going to go Miami next
summer, you know.
I'm going to book it for next summer. Yeah.
Only if that cunt's not there. If that
cunt's there, then I'm going to pick
somewhere else. I need to make sure
they're not there cuz I I actually want
to go on holiday and not get into like
confrontations with people.
You didn't answer my question. Why are
you saying that I need more confidence
when I'm already confident
and I can approach sober? I mean, confidence.
It doesn't matter about confidence. They
don't care about confidence.
That was just a thing [ __ ] made it up
by a [ __ ] s.
I've got money, designer clothes. I'm
confident. I'm decent looking. It's
still not good enough. So,
time to leave. Simple.
It will never change in this country ever. Right.
I don't think they're going to score.
Hopefully they don't.
I don't even know why I'm watching. Like
I want to bet on it. Yeah.
Yeah, I don't think they're going to
Monty messaging me on [ __ ] Facebook. Steven Howard [ __ ] idiot.
I have a boyfriend. Give it a [ __ ]
rest. Every single time I go on these
[ __ ] approaching videos, I have a
boyfriend. I have a boyfriend. Give it a
[ __ ] rest. Just come out with a
different excuse. It's so boring now.
Like even when it's not happening to me,
it's so [ __ ] boring.
God, it is so boring.
It's so [ __ ] boring, bro. Just come
out with something different, something
new. Just give the guy some constructive
criticism. It's so [ __ ]
boring hearing it. Even when it's not
happening to you, it's so annoying, bro.
They do not have no [ __ ] boyfriend.
The boyfriend do not [ __ ] exist. Just
give the guys some constructive criticism.
Or just be honest, that boyfriend [ __ ]
is so boring. They're [ __ ] MPCs.
They're like them [ __ ]
Star Wars [ __ ] dro them Star Wars
[ __ ] droids, bro.
No, I'm not drinking.
I'm not going out until my birthday.
I don't think they're going to score.
So, we saved oursel £120.
Yep. Get up there, son.
Come on, man. No,
I definitely didn't.
No, I definitely didn't, mate. And you
can [ __ ] off yourself. Reflector. >> Bye-bye.
boyfriend [ __ ] is so boring. Yeah. Heat. [Music]
Yeah. Bonnie was messaging me trying to
talk [ __ ] on Facebook. I said, "Come to
[ __ ] London. I'll slap you up, you little fanny. [Music] Yeah,
could [ __ ] strangle that Monty, you
know? He's the one that [ __ ]
introduced me to the [ __ ] virgin
[ __ ] skinting the bed [ __ ] you know,
[ __ ] bed in it and living in out of
London. [ __ ] hell, mate.
Yeah, man. Yeah, he still wouldn't beat
me, bro. He wouldn't beat me.
Yeah, but he wouldn't beat me, bro.
Trust me, he wouldn't.
He belly, you know. What's up? One second.
Yeah. Hopefully the [ __ ] don't score, eh?
Oh, I'm [ __ ] hungry, lad. No,
no, man. And I woke up at [ __ ]
I woke up at 2:30 [ __ ] [ __ ]
talking [ __ ] [ __ ] mongo's
[ __ ] stinking sading stinking.
Yeah, he going out today
only to get a curry candy.
Yeah, not going out drinking today.
Candy, I can't be bothered with it here.
And I've got a boyfriend. Not interested.
Going out drinking just to come home
with what's porn. Anyways, that's [ __ ] depressing.
I think that's going. Yay.
It's one of them things, isn't it?
Football is very unpredictable. Yeah.
I'm so glad I didn't bet, bro.
It's not over yet.
It's not over to the fat lady [ __ ] sings, mate. Yay.
[ __ ] They better not score, bro. I'll
cry. I'll [ __ ] cry. I'll cry if they
score. I'll cry.
That's what I'll do. [ __ ] cry. Yeah.
I think you've got more chance of
[ __ ] winning on roulette me than football.
What do you think? Yeah.
Little Bad. No money in it.
No bad. No money in it.
I don't think they're going to score. Yay.
Luckily, I didn't put a little bet on it. She can also flash.
Please don't [ __ ] score.
No, I'm all right. Thanks.
Do you reckon I should go to Waxies
today and drink some Guinness?
Steven Howard, do you reckon I should go
to like the pub and drink do some approaches?
But what would happen?
The same. Oh [ __ ]
I have a boyfriend.
I'm not interested.
Am I [ __ ] going to waste my Um, no, not yet. Oh, sorry. flask score.
almost full time. Yay. always little.
Yeah, man. I think we got a lucky escape. Yes,
we got lucky escape. Not bad on that. Yep.
One nil. We got a lucky escape. We got a
Lucky escape, bro. Yes,
we would have been down 120. I'm so glad
I didn't bet on it. Yeah.
Yeah, it's finished, bro. I'm happy we
didn't build on it.
Uh, what did you
Yep. I saved 120, bro.
Imagine we done 50 on a
Six. Both score no draw.
We would have been rich. There was six
games. Both scored no draw.
Yeah, we would have been [ __ ] rich.
We We would have been rich, matey.
[ __ ] hell. Could you imagine [ __ ]
score? No [ __ ] draw. [ __ ] hell. Uh,
do you know what I need to bet on? I
need to bet on slow. I need to bet on
the Southern League, bro. Cuz do you
know the slow game? They always both
score no draw on that one.
Oh, it was. Yeah.
Oh, Jesus Christ. It was [ __ ] What?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven,
eight. Almost eight. Both score
in a [ __ ] row. Oh my [ __ ] god, bro.
That is a madness. Jeez.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
We need to bet on I'm going to bet on
slow next time
cuz they always [ __ ] are both scoring that game.
Yeah, I'm live. Jesus.
Let's do slow next time.
Let's do slow and kitty minister. One
from the south, one from the north.
Do I want to chat? Not really.
Yeah, that's what I was thinking. Yeah.
Yeah. Don would have [ __ ] me up today. Two version
in the bed with no bed and no money in
it. Living in our London.
No bed, no money.
[ __ ] going mad.
But I money and I bet in it.
skin little [ __ ] when I
dude. Oh man. Bur
in the bed.
Why is that skin virgin so obsessed with
me? For [ __ ] sake.
You so obsessed with me.
Never meet somebody with autism.
There you go. Autism.
More of the story.
inversions are obsessed with me. Steven
Howard, he's [ __ ] nuts.
Oh [ __ ] I shouldn't have said where I'm
probably going to go next, to be fair.
He's going to start going there. Steven
Howard. He's He's going to start going there.
cuz he likes to copy my holiday. A little copycat.
Oh, little copycat. We're going to start going there. Little copycat
copies my holidays.
Yeah, man. And he was saying, "Oh,
that's like if I go to Blackpool,
that's like I'm copying him." Well, no,
because there's a big difference. The
only place I've never been to is
Blackpool. And I was actually supposed
to go to Blackpool before
you, but there was a train strike in
Manchester, so I had to stay another um
day in Manchester, and that's the only
place I've never been to. The first
place you went was Amsterdam,
which is where I went because you're a
little copycat. Now, Blackpool would
have been the only place that I have not
been, let alone the first place I would
have been, mate. So, big difference. Little copycat.
You know, you little copycat. Copycat. Yeah.
Um, so yeah, there's a big difference.
You and Amsterdam just cuz I did. [ __ ]
Here we go. [ __ ] Thailand next. We
going [ __ ] Florida next.
Copycat. [ __ ] tickle him. I could I
[ __ ] I [ __ ] tickle you. I [ __ ]
tickle you. [ __ ] tickle you.
[ __ ] tickle. Tickle. [ __ ] tickle, mate. Steven Howard,
I don't think we can be friends with Jo anymore
because there's a big problem.
There's a big problem with these people,
mate, on this community. Do you know
what the problem is?
And I'm getting sick of it. you know,
we can't we can't get along with um
Joe F and a few other people anymore.
Steven Howard, do you know what the
reason for that is? No, because
when I say, oh, you know, nons is a virgin,
you get these people that [ __ ] come
and say, well, he can't be cuz he got a
[ __ ] girlfriend. But yet, when he's
trying to call me a virgin, I've
literally proved I've had sex. I've
literally been in bed with women and no
one backs me up,
you know, and when I've shown like
£6,000 and made people run away and I've
shown money several times, no one backs
me up. So to [ __ ] with all of you, you
know, you want to stick up for a virgin [ __ ] naunt.
They literally pull me up on it say,
"Oh, you can't be a virgin. You got a
[ __ ] girlfriend." Yet I've literally
proved I've had sex, which is more than
someone having a girlfriend. So, it's
just very unfair on here, you know, Steven Howard
because you're a you are a mong. Stop
calling yourself a mong. So, if someone
has been to the same place as you is
copying, you're a proper mong. No wonder
everyone want Bro, you people laugh at
yourselves. That's all you laugh at is
yourselves. I mean, so do you want me to
answer the question?
cuz you ask me a question and I'll answer it.
I mean the first place you went to is Amsterdam
and I I went to Amsterdam. So yeah, I
would say that is copying.
Yeah, that is copying
for somebody to have gone to the to to
Amsterdam where you went the first time
they went abroad.
Yeah. Yeah. That's copying definitely,
mate. There's over 300 different
countries you could have went to, but
you went to Amsterdam the first time you
went abroad. Yeah, that sounds like
copying to me. Bye-bye now. One sec. anything more.
such a badass me.
Even when the Reddit mods b me, I just
keep making new accounts. It's pointless. Um,
I'm going to have a curry, ma'am.
Yeah, I'm going to have a lamb curry, I reckon. Nice bindaloo.
Yeah, I haven't had a curry for some time.
maybe has some ticker with it. Who knows?
I've just got into this routine of
saving money, bro. I'm just addicted to
saving money for a bit.
You know how it is.
My birthday soon. I want a birthday. Can
everybody give me a birthday card with
20 pound in it?
Could you imagine
everyone giving me a card with 20 pound in it?
That would be a [ __ ] lovely site, you know. [Music] That's not more.
I'm not Joe's friend anymore.
You know what? I don't like what you
people do on here.
I know what I don't like what you people
do on here.
I don't like it. Whenever I say that,
you know, virgin boy is a virgin. People
come come on saying, "Oh, um, he can't
be a virgin. He's got a girlfriend." No,
no, no, no, no, no. But when he calls me
a virgin, no one backs me up, even
though I proved I've had sex. You know
what the [ __ ] Why do people do that?
Steven Howard. Oh, when he calls me
skint and I've already beat him at the
money game multiple times and I've had a
better life than him. No one ever backs
me up. Are these people jealous of me or something?
It's weird cuz no one seems to back me
no one seems to back me up.
Oh, boos. I had McDonald's at 4:00 in
the morning. I got three fries. So, I
got two fries, six nuggets, and a chicken mac. [Music] Yeah. Victory sip. Oh.
Virgin boy skin in a bed [ __ ] with
[ __ ] no bed and [ __ ] no money in
it. You know what I'm like, mate.
So why does no one defend me then when
Virgin boy goes for me?
Can someone answer?
I will never be Monty's friend again. He
says that if I go to Birmingham, he's
going to smash me up. Bro, the guy could
never beat me in a fight. I was thinking
of just going there. Yeah. And then for content.
Yeah, but I don't get angry.
Should I just go to Birmingham and smash him up?
Who would your money be on winning the
fight? Be a body. Who would your money be on?
Bro, I could [ __ ] him up very easy.
I'll go there and [ __ ] him really hard. Yeah,
I should go to Birmingham and [ __ ] him hard, bro. It
What do you think, Grezy?
Who do you think would win? M
Peter Bennett would win. Look at me,
bro. Look at Look at this mug. This mug
would definitely win, you know.
Got shot on, by the way.
I would win, mate. Lovely.
Why would anyone um back me up when I
talk about kids? Well, nons legs is a nons.
I mean, he's an actual nons. So, stop
using that kids thing as an excuse
because you like it when people talk
about kids. You love the reaction. So,
stop using that as an excuse. Stop being a narcissist.
Stop being a narcissist. A, you like it
when people react and talk about kids.
That's why you do this in the first
place. And secondly, um, the person that
you're backing up is an actual nons.
Um, so that must mean you people are
nonses. So I mean, he's an actual [ __ ] nons.
You know what I'm saying, mate? An actual pedo.
And you love it when people say stuff
about kids and women and stuff. You love it.
Oh, shut the [ __ ] up. Your mom's
windows. Shut up, man.
Bacon. What the [ __ ] is this bacon word
as well? Jesus Christ.
[ __ ] weirdos, man.
I like Timmy. He makes me laugh. Boom.
Does he make you laugh? [Laughter]
Yeah, Timmy's entertaining, is it?
Yeah, he's funny as [ __ ] Hey, Timmy Aldridge.
It's so weird that I'm the one that
brought Monty on here.
If it wasn't for me, Monty wouldn't have
met Timmy Aldridge. You know that. Yeah,
I'm always getting a picture.
skin in the bed.
I don't bet no money. M
let's get in the bed [ __ ] with no bed in it.
Such a catchy saying, isn't it? Yes.
Franklin Virgin boy skin the bench with
no bed, nobody in it out of London.
He's [ __ ] skink.
He's [ __ ] skinky.
A skint bastard. That's what he is.
Skint [ __ ] with no money.
That's why when Peter Belly shows him
thousands, he runs away cuz he ain't got
nothing. He ain't got [ __ ] all.
Skip boy ain't got nothing.
I don't know why Timmy keeps asking
people to show him money. When when
people show him money, he runs away.
I'm not showing you nothing.
I'm not showing you fat.
I've got two pounds right there on the
side cuz I don't have cash on me and I'm
not showing you nothing. Not fuckle.
How's that one grievy? I'm not showing
you nothing, matey.
Nah, you start showing us something.
How's about that one, Grezy? Yeah.
You should be loving me, bro. I didn't
go out drinking today. Instead, I'd rather
sit and [ __ ] entertain you clowns. Huh?
Entertain you [ __ ]
Rather entertain you than these [ __ ]
women. [ __ ] women that are all the same.
And the thing is when you go out every
week, Greaves, you don't enjoy it
like you do every two to, you know, four
weeks. The longer you go without going
out, the more you enjoy it when you do go out
cuz it's just like a new thing all over.
Not a new thing all over again, but you
know, you understand what I'm saying,
don't you, Greavves?
Don't you, son?
You understand, don't you?
Right. You understand? Right. Yeah. You
understand? Yeah. You understand? Yeah.
You understand? Yeah. You understand?
Yeah. Sorry, I'm just very hyper at the
minute. I've just had some Coca-Cola from McDonald's. So,
yeah. very hyperactive.
I really want you, but I don't think you want me, Grezy.
But I don't think you want me.
I do. I do.
Have you got any siblings? Uh, Gravesy,
have you got any siblings? Huh?
Any brothers, any sisters?
Oh yeah, I remember you saying I've got
two sisters. One I don't talk to. One I do obviously.
Do you remember when I was shouting at
that woman in the park?
She deserved it.
And do you know what? I didn't do it for
no reason. Grezy, I don't start on
people for no reason. I just knew she
was just like going to waste my time and
stuff. See, Greavves, I don't start at
people for no reason. Like that person,
I stood up and made them go to waxies.
Um, that's because they were trying to
take the piss out of me. So, I thought,
"Fuck it." You know,
I didn't like her attitude and what she
was what she was saying and [ __ ] So, I was like,
"The [ __ ] deserved it. I don't people
for no reason.
So I [ __ ] hate women, bro. Really? I
really hate him, man.
They're bad people in general.
They really really are bad
bad people in general.
Uh Mr. G used to say they're nice people
in general. They're [ __ ] bad people
And it's mad how like
Ant-Man says to me how like I'm immature
and stuff. He used to say I'm immature
and maybe that's my problem with women.
And I'm thinking I'm I'm immature. I I
am immature by the way. I am a bit
immature. But compared to them people
that play games and lead people on, they
are the most immaturest people you could
ever. And and the thing is, Grezies,
even when they're 27, 28, 29, they're
still the same. Immature. They never
grow up. They never ever ever grow up.
They're literally all the same. Look at
Jane. She's like what, in her 40s? And
she's still an immature [ __ ] I mean,
I'm not immature compared to them, mate.
Trust me, you know. So, yeah. [Music] Nothing Funny Grezy.
So, I'm going to do a football bet next
week. I'm going to put 20 pound on it.
We're going to do slow kitty minister.
Let's do slow. Let's do slow.
Let's do slow kitty minister.
Slow Kitty Minister and Darlington.
Let's do it. Let's stick 30 pound on it.
How about that one, son? H.
That's a good bet. No.
Let's make it a B score. No draw. He's
got nothing back.
Greezy, can you send me 20 pound for my birthday, please?
Can you set Can you send me 20 for my birthday?
Why not? It's my birthday. Music.
Okay. How about £10 then?
When you come around to see me and King's
a cute little whiffter.
Now, seriously, I'm going to buy my own
Frenchie. I'm going to buy my own one.
Like a dotted one. You know, like a You
know them little dotted ones? The dotted
Frenchies? I'm going to buy my own one.
Yeah, I'm going to buy my own one.
Anyways, my own dog point
when I can.
>> What did you buckle?
>> Really? That was the same thing this
morning as well when I peeled him off. >> Yeah,
we need to do that.
>> That tomorrow. [Music]
>> Yeah, that's what I said.
When can I see King again?
>> When can I see King again?
He's cute, isn't it? Yeah. [Music]
Where's this coming?
This person's blocked me on Instagram. Run.
Anyways, I'll be back later. Yeah.