Oh, little copycat. Little copycat.
I might show you all the [ __ ] TSR
[ __ ] um boom man.
Do you think?
What do you think?
Little copycat. You little copycat.
Oh, yeah. You little copycat. Copycat. Uh
I might show what the channel will call
TS um sub and they'll copy each other.
You got no mind of the [ __ ] home.
Don't know if they'd copy Southern's
holiday though. Not sure about that one. Maybe.
Maybe they would. Who knows? I don't
think we'll ever know to be honest.
This community is very [ __ ] weird, isn't it?
It is a weird community, mate. It is a
really freaky community.
Planning to actually leave it soon
if I'm being honest. Yeah,
cuz it's the same atmosphere.
Same [ __ ] atmosphere every [ __ ] day.
Might get a crab today. I'm not entirely
sure what I fancy. Ta that
obviously Tuesday I'm getting a T-
because it's always Tuesday to
get an event with no money in it. So
could afford a T-Bone. It's fine. It's
not off the cards, you know. So you're
Oh, [ __ ] hell, man.
I need to stop waking up at these silly times.
Really do. I've got bed hair.
I used to be such an early bird.
What happened though? What happened?
Don't think we'll ever know, you know.
[ __ ] had some chicken nuggets yesterday.
[ __ ] early hours in the morning. They
made me feel sick. Yuck.
Disgusting. Got some chips as well. Yeah.
I was thinking of going out every week again
just to get out of that bomb. But that's
what he wants me to do. He wants me to
go out and have these [ __ ] shitty
women that all the [ __ ] same.
And I'm not trying to [ __ ] do that,
you know? That's why he makes up stories
that he's got people's money stopped
when he [ __ ] hasn't, you know.
So, yeah, that's the thing.
That's safe, man.
Yeah, it is.
Hey big fan. [Music]
Oh, what a virgin.
You nasty virgin. Damn.
Smack in the face.
I've got a [ __ ] bone to pick with you, Joseph. Joseph Farah. Joseph Farra.
I've got a bone to pick with you. Joseph Joseph. Joseph Fra.
That's why I'm going to start covering
you now. Why you never stick Why you
never stick up for me?
You know, when people are going for me, Joseph.
Yeah. Story of your life. And you would
only know that if you was on YouTube yourself.
I mean, I'm self-aware. I mean, yeah.
I've got nothing better to do.
You know what? What am I supposed to be doing?
Is there anything else I'm supposed to
be doing or what?
And only you would know that because you
was also on YouTube. So, it's an
oxymoron, mate. You know, it's an
oxymoron. I don't know how many times
you have to go over this. You know,
you people on YouTube every day. You
can't take a day off of it.
You know, this is like therapy to me.
This ain't my life. It's your lives.
Do you know? Oh,
what was I supposed to be doing?
Is there actually a reason? I can't even
use the money as an excuse, can I? Cuz I
got money. So, it's not even about, oh,
I'm not wasting money. I just can't be [ __ ] you know?
Just can't be [ __ ] going out drinking.
So, I just thought I'd talk to you [ __ ] idiots.
Yeah, I won't be going out again until
my birthday, which is everyone knows my birthday. So,
what are you getting me for my birthday?
I want money in a card.
I really want to know what your problem
is, you people here.
Skin again. Oh, self-projecting
comments. We don't entertain them. Um,
but what I want to know is why are you
[ __ ] never back me up, you know? I'm
waiting for Joseph.
Yeah, this is like therapy to me. Yeah.
See, this is Everyone uses YouTube for
like a different thing. Like LJ uses it
to project his life onto people. You use
it to project your life onto people. Um,
calling people what you are, i.e. skin,
i.e. no friends, just talking about
yourselves. Um, and I use it just as
like a therapy session.
I should really see a therapist, right?
Cuz I reckon if I saw a therapist, I
would never come on YouTube again.
Everyone uses it for different reasons.
Most people use it to self project
their life onto others. You know,
Mont is like, "Oh, I know where you
live." So, I messaged him back yesterday
saying, "So, if you know where I live,
what are you going to do about it? You
[ __ ] snake. [ __ ] off, you snaky
cunt." That's adding to um one of my
regrets in life is going to Birmingham
and spending that money. I will never
ever ever be that snake's friend ever
again. I'd rather be Timmy Eldridge's friend.
Yep. I'd rather be Timmy Eldridge's
friend. I will [ __ ] never be that
snake's friend again. [ __ ] that, bro.
He's a [ __ ] snake
going there spending that [ __ ] money
for [ __ ] no reason. [ __ ] that, stupid [ __ ] Yeah,
but yeah, the the self-p projected
comments like Skint again. Yeah, that
that doesn't bother anyone. That's just
you talking about yourselves. That
doesn't bother anyone.
Only you would know who is Skint, which
is yourselves. So yeah,
never skin. I've not been skinting four
years, but you still try to call me skin. Crazy.
Oh, self projector. Eh.
So anyways, we'll wait for Joseph for
that's his new name.
I want to know
why people are fast enough to defend it
to defend this [ __ ] virgin
but they're not [ __ ] you know
you know but not me you know
I mean I'm not moaning there's nothing
to moan about I mean I'm leaving I'm
going in November
I'm leaving this country I'm not moaning mate
not moaning about women because women
are all the same. So there's nothing to
moan about anymore.
I done something about it. I stopped
going out and dealing with it. So yeah,
[ __ ] that. I wasn't going to put that [ __ ] anymore. So yeah,
but you are fine ones to talk about
people repeating themselves. Aren't you?
Cuz you people have been repeating yourselves
since I've been on here.
Your skin, get a job.
You know, we've heard all these things
before these self-p projecting things.
So, you kind of repeat yourselves, too,
don't you? Come on. Now, he's not about it.
I want to know why these people defend,
you know, the Virgin, but they don't defend me. Crazy.
I want to know why they're so fast to go
to his rescue, but no one ever backs me
up. I feel a bit left out.
Strange, isn't it?
Very, very strange people in here, mate. Yeah.
Because I'll say for example, he's a
virgin. And then people say, "Well, you
kind of have a v. You can't be a virgin.
You got a girlfriend."
But yet when they're calling me things,
no one backs me up. So I want to know
why that is. Cuz I've actually proved
I've had sex. I've actually proved I got
more money than him multiple times.
So something's not right here, mate.
Can somebody answer me it, please? Thank you.
Um, I'm all right. Just chilling,
playing some GTA.
Yeah. I said to [ __ ] [ __ ] come to [ __ ] London.
He was like, "Oh, you got beef in uh
Birmingham. You might as well come to
Birmingham." I said, "No, I come to
Birmingham last time. You can come to
London now. It's only an hour and 20
minutes. Stop using excuses."
Uh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. You
can't say that, Eldridge. You can't ask
people to prove stuff and then when they
prove stuff then say, "Oh, why do you
have to prove everything?" You've asked
people to prove stuff. That's why we
prove stuff, son. You know, so whenever
you get proven wrong, so it's like every
time you get proven wrong, you backtrack
what you say.
Bit weird, isn't it, mate?
It's like every time you get proven
wrong, you then say, "Oh, why do you
have to prove yourself?" It doesn't
really wash in the washing machine, mate.
I'm speaking generally. Yeah, but I'm
I mean, I don't prove myself. You know,
people come, I don't do it anymore.
People come on here, they call me skinn,
they don't know how much money I have,
and I don't show them nothing. And they
continuously self-project. I mean, I
don't show anything anymore.
Because obviously self, you know,
self projectors. I don't show them
anything. If they say I'm skinn, I just
say, "Okay, self projecting."
So, I mean, I just ignore it. Is it?
Yeah. Nothing to show as usual. Yeah.
Again, self projected. You've been shown
thousands and thousands multiple times.
I've also shown Timmy money a few months
ago as well. Every single time you
people get shown money, you run away.
And the community is dead as it is. So,
I think I won't show you anything to be
honest. When are you people really going
to stop this self projecting thing? It's
getting really old now. Like, no. Like,
ser on a real though, it's getting boring now.
It's really really really getting
boring. Like, we get it, man. We know
that you're skin. We know that you got
no money. But that's not everyone else.
That's you people that are saying it. We
need to really come out with some
different things now. It's getting insanely boring. Seriously. Seriously, mate.
Um, he beat me. Uh, no. I stopped
showing money about six, seven months
ago when it was clear that nobody was
ever going to show me anything. And FYI,
it took Non's legs two years to beat me
and him having no life experience for
three years. Yeah, I would still say
he's a loser in my book.
Two years to beat me, three years to
save the money despite not living your
best life. Nah, I'd say he's still a
loser to be honest.
I'd say he's I'd say he's still a loser, mate.
Cuz why didn't he show that 13 grand
when I showed that six grand? Because he
was still saving in his bedset cuz he
didn't have it. So yeah,
but bro, listen, £13,000
is nothing compared to life experiences.
You do realize that he's never stayed in
any good hotels, never been to any nice
restaurants, no designer clothes. Why
would you jeopardize your life for 3
years for $13,000?
That's just ridiculous.
That is [ __ ] ridiculous.
Why would anyone do that? That's mad.
[ __ ] absolute [ __ ] madness.
Stayed in good hotels, went to nice
restaurants, traveled, been on some nice
dates, [ __ ] a load of escorts. I would
not trade up for 13 grand. And I'm not
even just saying that.
Um, when did I get laid without paying
for it? Multiple times, which you've
seen, but you ignore. This is what I'm
saying. I'm wasting my time with this
community with these little bongos. They
clearly like nons. So,
you need to ask yourself the same
question, bro. When did you get laid
without paying? I've been laid multiple
times without paying. I've shown it on
YouTube as well.
So, again, you need to ask yourself that question.
You're getting yourself confused with me. Again,
what you people like to do
and I have stayed in good hotels. So
yeah, it's not worth £13,000 is not
worth a year's life experiences.
You really let alone three years. And
I'm not just saying that. And I'm not
just [ __ ] saying that, you know.
Well, everyone's seen the hotels I've stayed in.
I'd rather be sat here with less money
than that and know I've had life
experiences and I can go out whenever I
want and I've got stuff to show for my money.
It's not like he's just I've never
stayed in a holiday in in my life.
Never stayed in a Holiday in. That's one
hotel I've never stayed in. I've also
never stayed in Premier in Nope. Never
stayed in Premier in either.
I've stayed in Plaza Hotel. I've stayed
at the Hilton Hotel,
bro. You've seen the hotels I've stayed
in. What the [ __ ] So, yeah,
I would not trade my year life
experiences at my peak of YouTube for £13,000.
No [ __ ] way.
No [ __ ] way, hoes. [ __ ] Hey,
what's the point in life if you're just
going to be sat in a bed sit for [ __ ] 3 years?
But what's the [ __ ] point? You know,
you have to copy my holidays. Yeah, whatever.
Yeah. Bye-bye, [ __ ]
You people are proper spasticated on
here. Aren't you proper proper spasticated?
So anyways, why do you um not back me up
when I prove things?
That's how you know it's just a waste of
time. This community, they love
nonsense. That's what makes me think
they're jealous of me to be honest with
you. Not that I'm saying there's
anything to be jealous of. I'm I I don't
rate myself in any [ __ ] way. I'm a
normal person. But it's weird how they
would back someone else up, but they
don't back you up.
That's so weird.
I know, man. It seems like jealousy to me.
And you shouldn't be asking me the
question. You should be asking yourself
the question cuz only you know it. I
don't know why you ask me.
Then I ask you the same thing why you do
what you do every day.
You have been shown thousands and
thousands and thousands of pounds
multiple times. I will never show you
money ever, ever, ever, ever, ever again.
I will never show you money ever again.
I don't play your little self-projecting games.
Talking about yourself, I've been with
more women than you will ever be with
women. And who what woman would want a
keyboard warrior on £300 a month like you,
bro? Look at your [ __ ] self, bro.
You're fat and ugly in your 40s sat on
YouTube every day. What woman would want you?
Some fat, ugly guy on YouTube every day
with no money? What woman would want an
ugly bastard like you? Some ugly guy in
his 40s sat on YouTube every [ __ ]
day, no life. That's why you're still a
virgin. So don't come on here
self-reflecting your [ __ ] to me. I'm not
some ugly guy in my 40s with nothing
like you. At least I'm young enough to
change it. Unlike you, [ __ ] Can't get
off of YouTube.
I've had more women than you. You fat
ugly bastard. Don't even try and talk
about women to me. You know, you're the
one that's got nothing. I've got more
money than you will ever have. I've
proven to you people multiple times I've
got more money than you. I'm better
looking than you. I've had more women
than you. multiple multiple times.
Everything that you do on here is self-
projecting your fat, ugly lives onto
people. No one's interested.
No one's interested in you fat, ugly
people that have got nothing. Self-
project away. That's why we do not block
you. You know, I have had more women.
Okay. Where's your woman? Why don't you
come in and show us your money and your
woman? Same [ __ ] with you self
projectors every single time, man.
Okay, let's see your money. Let's see
your woman. Come on.
Let's see your money in your women. Come
on, let's have it. Come on. Let's see
your body. Let's see your face. Let's
see your women. Let's branch out today.
And this is where you always lose. So,
there's just no point coming on here
starting this [ __ ] You people are fat
and ugly. You've never been with a
woman. You can't even show your [ __ ] faces.
sat on YouTube fat, ugly with no money
every day, thinking that everyone's got
the same life as you, bro. We do not
have the same life as you,
you know, and how can I talk about
people going on here? Finally, a normal
question. I mean, I can talk about it
because I've been off of YouTube for two
weeks and you people can't take a day
off of YouTube. I mean, does that answer
your question? I've been off YouTube
weeks, 3 weeks, and every single time
you people on YouTube from the time you
wake up to the time that you go to bed,
that given me a little bit of room to
talk, you know? It gives me a little bit
of room to talk when I've been off of
YouTube for 3 weeks and then I've looked
what's happening in them three weeks
back and you've been on YouTube every
day. I kind of think I've got some room
to talk. No. So, yeah.
But anyways, these self-projecting
comments, they don't bother no one, man.
You people are the ones with nothing.
You are the ones that sit on YouTube
from the time you wake up to the time
you go to bed. No women, no money, no
looks, no youth. You got [ __ ] all.
That's why you do what you do every day,
bro. We laugh at you now, man. We laugh at you.
It's funny to be honest. It is funny.
It's not even worth blocking the comments.
Respectable woman. So, you're definitely
definitely a s. You're definitely a
white knight and you've definitely never
been with a woman. I can tell. I can
tell by the way you're writing stuff.
You generally generally think everyone
has got the same life as you people.
Generally you come out with the most random specific things
on people that you don't even know. So
it's like where the [ __ ] do these things
even come from? And it comes from their
own lives that they are living because it's self-projected.
How long have you people been coming on
here now self projecting your lives? Oh,
this person's skin, this person's got
nothing. And every single time you get
show money, you run away. It's ridiculous.
It's ridiculous, man. You know.
Yeah. And what have you got? YouTube.
YouTube in your 40s.
Yeah. What have you got? A YouTube app
to self project on every day.
That's your life. Your life sounds a lot
worse than mine. And you're also old as
well. So, I mean, I take my life over your life.
I'm better looking than you. I've got
more money than you, better clothes than
you. Got more friends than you.
Everything you people say is about your
own lives. That's why it doesn't bother
no one because it's just self projection.
You people are oldies and you got [ __ ]
all. That's why every single time I say
this stuff, I hit a nerve. You know, you
people are 47 and you got nothing in
life. Self projecting.
It's the same three or four people that
do this. No car, no investments on the
tubes. Bro, listen. Everything that you
say is about yourselves. The only thing
that you've got wrong is your age. The
only thing that you've got wrong is your age.
Everything. You don't know what money
people have. No education. Self projected.
He's talking about himself. Everything
is about his own lives. This is what I'm
saying. This is so entertaining, right?
A bunch of 40 year olds that have got
nothing talking about their own lives.
This is entertaining.
self-p projected their own life sat on
YouTube with no money, no life, no
education. That's literally their own
lives they're talking about and they
prove it to themselves every single day.
The more they come on here and do this,
the more it shows it's them. Their
40-year-old virgin life, their stinky
fat ugly life on YouTube every day. You
are 48 and you've got nothing in your
life. I've got youth. I'm not old like you people.
You know, [ __ ] you're 47 and I've got
more than you. So [ __ ] that says a
lot, bro. Even if I was 28 and I and I
was all of them things, I would still
have more than you. That's the
embarrassing thing about it.
I've got more money than you. I'm better
looking than you. I'm not old like you.
That's where the jealousy comes from,
bro. Listen, any of you people come on
here right now and you join a link and
you show your face, it would show why
you do this every day. fat, ugly, lonely
people that ain't got nothing.
Benefits. You do not know what money
people have. You do not know what money
people don't have. You only know about
your own 40-year-old [ __ ] life on
YouTube year in year out, year in year
out. Cuz I'm pretty sure if you had
anything in your life, you would not be
sat here on here doing this every day.
You people are ugly people in your 40s.
Let's not [ __ ] self-reflect now,
mate. Let's talk about you mters. How
long have you been on here now doing
this? Self-p projecting your skittness,
self-p projecting your ugliness, your
loneliness for years. You've been doing
it for [ __ ] years.
You know, you people are the 40-year-old
ugly, spasticated people that can't get
off of YouTube. Nothing you say bothers
anyone. To be honest with you, I'm just
going to go and get some popcorn in a
bit, bro, and just just watch yourself
reflect your life away cuz it's entertaining.
You only know about your own [ __ ] lives.
You're ugly 40-year-old bitter people
that have nothing in life. And you come
on here and you take your angers out on
other people because you are the ones in
your 40s and you got [ __ ] all in your
life. That's why you do this. That's why
you come on here every day and you do
this. You know what I mean? So anyways,
come in the hangouts and let's show
let's play the money game and let's play
the looks game. And until you do that,
I'm not even going to respond anymore,
bro. You're [ __ ] boring as [ __ ] You
people seriously need to get a life. You
seriously need to get a life. You don't
know anything about anyone.
You only know about your own lives.
Anyways, come in the hangouts, man.
Well, let's play the money game.
Let's play the money games. Let's see
your face, bro. You people are fat, ugly
mun. You ain't got nothing in your
lives, bro. How you trying to talk about
other people? You are in your [ __ ]
40s. You're a bunch of old spastics. And
every time I say that, bro, you know
what I'm saying is the truth.
You know what I'm saying? Nah, nah.
Nah. I've already beat him at the
[ __ ] money game. Beat him at the
better looks game. Beat him at the
better women game. Beat him at the
better life game. I beat him in every
single game possible.
You know you people when are you people
going to get off of YouTube and get a life anyways.
You do not know how much money I have.
You do not know how much money I get.
You do not know what I have and what I don't have.
So keep guessing. You don't know
anything about anyone but your own life.
All of this is just self- projective, you know.
Yeah. Talking about yourself again. No
hope, no prospects, bro. Listen, listen,
listen, listen. Now, this is this is a
big thing, right? When you say about how
when you say about how I've got no hope,
that is you people. You are in your 40s.
You're you're past your sale by day.
Okay, let's just go by what you're
saying, right? And everything that you
say about me is the truth, right? Which
it isn't. It's your own lives. skin,
ugly, no woman, that's all your lives.
But let's just say hypothetically
everything that you're saying about me
was true right now. How old am I and how
old are you? I'm 27.
You people are in your 40s and you got
nothing. No hope, no money, no woman.
And you're all old. You've got no hope.
That's the thing. You fat ugly people.
You mongaloids. You ugly old people.
I've got no hope. I would have hope.
Even if I was [ __ ] homeless with a
pound to my my name, I've got hope
because I'm not old [ __ ] spasticated
people like you. I've got age on my
side. I'm not in my 40s sat there with
no money, no life, no friends like
[ __ ] you people. You know what I'm saying?
You people in your 40s and you have
nothing. That's why you're you're
talking about people being in their 20s better
everything with you people is self
projection. But that thing right there
when you say about no hope that applies
to you people. This is why you do the
whole self projecting on YouTube because
you realize that you are the ones with
no hope. You are the ones that are very
ugly. You are the ones that have got
nothing in your lives. And you realize
that you're too old to change it.
Because if you realize, if you think
right, none of these people are in their
20s because people that are in their 20s
in a bad situation in life can actually
change their life. Whereas these people
are too old. They that's the whole point
point. They've got no hope. So
everything that they say is about their
own lives. They're self-reflecting their
own lives onto me. So that's it. I mean,
I rely on a football bet. No, I don't.
No, I don't. Even when I won a football
bet, I still don't go out.
So, no, I really don't. I won over 500
pound last week. I still didn't go out.
So, you don't know anything, mate. Keep
talking about your own lives. You are
the ones that are in your 40s, sat
online, ugly as [ __ ] ain't got no life,
ain't got no hope. That's why you come
on here self projecting talking about
people that you don't even know. People
that you don't even [ __ ] know. That's
the funny thing. people that you've
never met, people that you don't [ __ ]
know for [ __ ] saying, you know what
I'm [ __ ] saying for Well, you are
projecting because how could a 27y old
have no hope?
You How the [ __ ] could a 27y old, bro?
You people don't work. You people are
sat on your fat ugly asses on benefits
every day of your life. You do not work.
You people are [ __ ] mongos
sat on YouTube, the Mongols. And
anyways, let me finish what I'm saying.
Now, you said about having no hope. Now,
bro, any 27y old has hope. Come on, man.
Even if if a 27y old was a [ __ ] drug
drug addict. Yeah. On the [ __ ]
street, they've got hope. I'm pretty
sure any 27y old can change their life,
mate. You know, it's not old in theory.
And what you mean is you people have got
no hope cuz you're in your 40s and you
have failed everything in life. Again,
self-p projection. It's a self
projection of your own lives. That's why
none of you join the hangouts and show
your faces cuz you're all fat and ugly.
Fat, ugly, no hopers. That's that on
YouTube every day. It's what I'm saying.
It's true. It's the truth. You know,
bro, age on my side, bro. You're in your
40s. You're self projecting,
bro. You're talking about yourselves.
You people are single, skin on benefits.
Everything you're saying is about yourselves.
Sat on YouTube in your 40s, no money,
never been with a at least I've been
with a woman, unlike you ugly people.
Sat on YouTube every day. Been here,
there, everywhere. You [ __ ] fat ugly
self projectors can't even get your ugly
asses off YouTube cuz you're too
disabled. These people honestly
commenting right now. Yeah. Every time
they leave their house, they probably
get bullied for being so ugly. That's
why this is why these people do not
leave their [ __ ] houses for like
because every time they try, they're so
ugly. They probably get bullied. That's
why they come here self-projected
because they're ugly little bully
victims. You can just tell these people
got get bullied every day. They try to
leave their house. Bro, you people are
on benefits. Stop self-reflecting.
You people are the fat ugly people on
benefits. I don't know why you keep self-reflecting.
Everything you say is about your own
lives and I will prove it. If you join
the hangouts, I will prove everything is
about you people.
You know, fat, ugly, skin, lonely
benefits. It's all about you little
mongos. Cuz think about it. How many
years have you been self-projecting? And
how in listen what have you done in four years?
What have you done in four years? Come
on, tell us what you've all done in four
years other than self-reflect every day
on YouTube talking about yourselves,
you know, self projecting. That's all
you people do cuz that's all you have.
You don't know about anyone anyone
else's life. You only know about your own lives.
[ __ ] 40year-old spastics on YouTube
every day. And when I say this, you
don't like it because it's the truth.
I've done more, mate, in a year of my
life than you've done in a [ __ ]
probably two decades of your life, bro.
Like, it's not even funny.
You just you you seem to have this
disability, bro, where you think
everyone's got exactly the same life as yours.
And what do you mean by going out once a
month? I go out every day.
I mean, yeah, I'm going on holiday on no
in November. Do I need to go out every
week? But anyways, you little mongos are
something to laugh at.
[ __ ] ugly little nerds sat on YouTube
every day. Little And you know what I'd
say? I'd say you people are probably
still [ __ ] virgins. That's what makes
me laugh. You're probably still [ __ ] virgins.
Can't join the panel cuz you're too
ugly. You just [ __ ] 40-year-old fat
spasticated nerds. You see someone
younger than you, better looking than
you, and you think, "Oh, let me project
my life onto this person." 48, no job,
no money, no anything. Do you know what
I'm saying, mate?
I feel sorry for you 40year-old
spastics. I generally feel sorry for you
people. I generally do. That's why I'm
not blocking you. Like, I want to I'm
I'm actually giving you a platform cuz I
don't even want to I don't even want to
block you to be fair.
I don't even want to block you [ __ ]
fat ugly mongos. I feel so for you. No
one else will probably give you a platform,
you know? So, I I just let you comment
to be honest. You can keep
self-reflecting cuz that's your life
you're talking about. No one else is, you know.
I don't know how many times you're going
to get embarrassed as well. Losing the
money game. It's just ridiculous.
But no, I'm not going to I'm not going
to block because all you people are
doing is showing yourselves up and
embarrassing yourselves, you know. Let's
see how long you can keep this up for.
So the longest you So you're not going
to come in the hangouts and you're not
going to show your face and you're not
going to talk. Okay?
So the longer you do this, the more it
shows it's about yourselves. Cuz trust
me, if you people, right, had any kind
of life, you wouldn't be on here every
day self projecting. If you had any kind
of life, any kind of money, you wouldn't
be on here doing what you're doing.
So, I just You show yourself up the more
you do this. Really, mate? You know?
Well, let me tell you something, man.
This is going to be my my last words to
you. I bet you your mother is more
ashamed of you than my mom is ashamed of
me. In your 40s, no life, no money, no
friends, can't take a day off of
YouTube. I'm pretty sure your mother is
more ashamed than you, mate. And you got
no hope either. So anyways, we're not
responding to these people anymore.
These little self projectors. We'll let
them embarrass themselves. I'm not even
going to block them.
>> All right.
>> Where's Joseph? I've been waiting for you.
We're not entertaining these little
self-p projectoring nerds.
I think Joseph's too busy [ __ ]
gambling to be honest.
Too busy gambling. Yeah,
Joseph Fur's too busy gambling sadly.
But I think he'll come back to be honest.
But yeah, I mean,
does anyone even [ __ ] put up gambling
videos anymore? I don't I don't see the
point of this community. It's No one
puts up gambling videos. No one [ __ ] There's no
There's nothing really behind this
anymore, is it? just a bunch of people
that failed in life that self- project
every day. There's nothing there's nothing else.
Just people that have got no life that
try to talk about other people's lives
because they've got no life and they've
failed. That's basically what this 90%
of this place is about.
You know, just a bunch of
self-projecting fat, ugly disabled
people that ain't got a life that self-
project. It's a madness, isn't it?
But I can understand why they do it. I
mean, being them, you know, fat, ugly,
you know, we've seen what these people
look like that do this, a lot of these
people, and they're always really,
really fat and ugly.
So, they see somebody that's better
looking than them, bit younger than
them, has a life unlike them, and they
go mad. And then they call you all the
things that they are themselves. That's
that's how this I I know about this
stuff. I know about um psychology and
stuff, you know.
It's [ __ ] m to be honest with you
though. Like these people should be
literally put up in a [ __ ] school of
[ __ ] kids of not what to be like when
you know they're your age.
It's so weird. like they got they've got
no life so they have to obsess over
other people's lives.
It's so weird. Like
they've got no life of their own. So
they have to bounce off other people's
lives. And to be honest with you, right,
let me let me tell you something. I I
have rephrased what I've said before.
It's not about being on YouTube every
day. Like anyone can go on YouTube once
a day, but what these people do, right?
They sit on on YouTube from the time
they wake up to the time they go to bed
hating, self-projecting. They've got
nothing. They've got nobody. These
people really have got nobody. They're
probably full of anxiety. They probably
can't even leave the house or beds
rather unless they take some [ __ ]
prodal [ __ ] pills.
These people really are embarrassing.
Really, really are. I'd hate to be these
people in my 40s.
I think I'd kill myself to be honest
with you if I had to be like these
people sat on YouTube self-p projecting,
you know? I'd kill myself. I think I
would just kill myself to be honest.
These people can't even go out for a
drink. Imagine that. Like not even being
able to go out for a drink. No money,
too much anxiety. [ __ ] hell, these people, man.
They talk like they know people because
they think everyone's got the same life
as them. [ __ ] wow, bro. That's wild.
Really is wild.
I'm [ __ ] younger than these people.
I'm [ __ ] better looking than these
people. I've got [ __ ] Oh my god. It's
a madness. Why don't any of these people
come in the [ __ ] hangouts?
Because they're too ugly. These people
are ugly bastards. If they show their fac
and remember Bomb says it all, mate.
Says it [ __ ] all.
She didn't come back on it, did she,
Gray Cat? Nah.
Like anything that these people try to
say about other people's lives, their
life is way worse, man.
way worse than anyone else they're
trying to talk about. You know,
these people have definitely been
bullied in life. Definitely definitely
definitely been bullied in life.
Mad, isn't it? It's crazy.
It's a proper disabled community, isn't it?
Proper proper disabled community.
Had more women than them, have more
money than them, better looking than
them, younger than them, and they still talk [ __ ]
They still talk [ __ ] [ __ ] That's why
I said anyone who's watching this or
anyone who watches this back, anyone
that's younger than these people, anyone
that's better looking than these people,
they gravitate towards you, you know,
they don't like it the fact that they're
old, they're ugly, they got nothing.
That's why they do all of this stuff.
Genacy comes into it with these people,
you know. That's why they do what they
do every single day on this [ __ ]
website. younger than them, better
looking than them, and they think that
everyone's got the same life as them, you know,
and then the argument is going to be
like, "Oh, well, if you're so
good-looking, why have you not had a
woman?" Yeah, I've been with more women
than them. So, what I'm saying is they
gravitate to anyone that's younger and
better looking than them.
It's like a bottlefly
being um attracted to [ __ ] on a summer's
day. They gravitate towards [ __ ] Have
you ever seen like them green flies?
It's like these people. Anyone that's
better looking than these people, anyone
that's younger than these people, they
don't like it. That's why they go for me
because there's actual like No, no, I'm
not even saying that. I'm not even
blowing smoke at my own ass. I don't
think I'm anything, you know? I I
literally Well, okay, let's talk about
your life then. What have you got? Okay,
let's talk about your life. What have
you people got?
What have you people got, bro? sat on
YouTube in your 40s, ain't got nothing
every day. What What What have you got
in your life? But it is strange how
you've got so many people that don't
know you gravitate towards you.
Seems like jealousy to me, but we won't
get into that because we don't like
using that word.
The things you say about kids. Um well,
there's a problem with what you're
saying. Um you wanted that reaction
about kids. You like people talking
about kids. Um, you wanted that reaction.
You got that reaction and then you're
trying to use it against someone. And
also the people that you defend like
nonslegs are actual nonsers.
Um, you've got caught. Prove it. Prove
it. Come in now and show us your house.
And no, I mean there's people on here
that's actually said stuff about kids.
um people that are actual nonses like
nods legs but you don't go for nods legs
so that's where the jealousy comes into it mate
and you done all of this [ __ ] before the
[ __ ] um women's stuff as well so it's
because I'm better looking than you and
I'm younger than you and I got more
money than you Ronald Pump was right
Pump was definitely right with you
people you're better looking than them
you got more money than them and you got
a better life than them and I've got a
better [ __ ] life than you mate Just
because I'm on a detox, taking a break,
a break from drinking doesn't make it
any less true, mate. You know,
cuz I mean, didn't Rice say stuff about
kids? Didn't Benny say stuff about kids?
I stick by what I say, mate. I stick by
what I say.
Well, I don't get 1,200 pound a month.
You don't know how much money I get. So
Rice has spoke about kids. Nons legs are
a nons. So it's not about people talking
about kids because you like nonses. You love nonses.
I mean you [ __ ] love nonses.
Yeah, you people have Yeah, you people
have got [ __ ] all. Yeah, you're talking
about yourself again. So Rice has spoke
about kids and non legs is an actual non
and has spoke about kids but I don't see
you going for any of these people.
Jealousy is a horrible thing. It really
really is a horrible thing. Let's face
it, right? You can sit there and try and
talk about me and you don't even know
me. But you are the ones that are fat
and ugly. You know that you're fat and
ugly. That's why you can't come and join
and show your faces or anything. You
know, you don't know how much money I
have and you don't know how much money I
get. So, you know, it is funny when you
think, you know, people, you think
everyone's got the same life as you
generally. Like, you generally think
everyone's got the same life as you.
Uh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. That wasn't people from YouTube.
That was a pe That was people from
around the area.
That was people from around the [ __ ] area.
So no, that was people from around the
area. He had been talking about kids.
Same as Belly. And it's not because
people speak about kids. You used to do
the same thing when people speak about women.
You hate the fact that people are better
looking than you and younger than you.
So that's what it is with you people. If
you showed your face, it would prove why
you do what you do every day on YouTube.
It comes to jealousy at the end of the
[ __ ] day for you people. Simple. It
comes to jealousy with you people.
And I'm in my rights to say that as
well. I am actually in my rights to say that
cuz how no one goes for anyone else. And
when you have people dedicated to
[ __ ] with you, I mean, yeah, it kind
of is jealousy to be fair. So you can
say you're not jealous and there's
nothing to be jealous of, but then I'm
putting the link out and I'm getting you
to show your face and you're not doing
it. So it's like I I can prove what
you're jealous of if you come and you
cut your camera on, but you won't do
that. So, you know, arguments go
nowhere, is it? I mean,
so yeah, there's no channels dedicated
to rice. There's no channels dedicated to nonslegs.
Ah, that's Oh, that's the good excuse,
eh? Good old excuse. Why would anyone
want to dox themsel?
Love that excuse. Class, I love that
excuse, mate. That's class. That is
there. That's the That's the excuse Bomb
used to use that he turned out to be fat and ugly.
Strange, eh? Strange. No, there isn't.
There's no channels dedicated to Rice.
There's no channels dedicated to dodge legs.
I didn't know I I get 1,200 power a month.
That's interesting. That's very very
You know, I have a big nose. Um, I don't
have a big nose and I don't look like a
terrorist. Cut your camera on someone.
Listen, listen, bro. Even if I had a big
nose and I look like a terrorist, bro,
you people are fat, white, and ugly with
a peanut head. That's why you don't show
your faces because you're very ugly, you know?
Shite bucket. What the [ __ ] you on about?
I mean, you people are way more uglier
than I'll ever be, so I don't understand
what that uh comment's about. I'm
younger than you. I've got hair unlike
you. I'm better looking than you. And
that's why you don't show your faces.
It's you don't show your faces because
you're butt ugly. Just the same if I was
going to go on a [ __ ] if I was going
to go on a community, right, and I was
to call a bunch of these people ugly and
then I'd say, "Oh, I'll not show my face
cuz there's no point." I would show my
face. You can't have that over on me cuz
you're ugly. That's it. That's said in
the most like normal way, lad. You don't
show your faces cuz you're butt [ __ ]
ugly. It's not because you don't want to
dox yourself. And that's part of why
it's it's part of the reason why you do
what you do every day,
you know. No, it's not about, bro, I'm
saying that you people because you
people are fat and ugly. You're not normal people.
I'm good-looking and I've been with more
women than you and I've been in a
relationship unlike you. Yes. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm good-looking. Yeah. I've been
with more women than you and I've been
in a relationship unlike you. Yeah.
Again, self projecting. None of you
people come and show your faces cuz
you're ugly. It's all jealousy with
these people. I've known it for years.
You people are fat and ugly and you're
talking about people's nose. These
people probably look worse than [ __ ] Timmy Eldridge.
They don't show themselves cuz they're
fat and ugly. They're so ugly. That's
why they do all of this every day, mate.
But yeah, anyways, you're changing the
subject again and you're making stuff
up. If you're not jealous of my looks,
then why don't you come and show your face then?
You know, why are you going to let
someone have that over you? I don't
know, man. I'm going to I'm going to
[ __ ] go. Um,
yeah. And you're in your 40s and you've
never slept with any woman.
And you're in your 40s and you've never
ever been with a woman. So, again,
you're just you're just turning it back
on to me. Whenever we're trying to get
you to show your faces and talk about
you, you're turning it back on to me.
It's because you're fat and ugly. That's
what I'm saying. That's why you do what
you do every day. You're fat, ugly, and
you're jealous of someone younger and
better looking than you. And you can
deny it all you want, but we know the truth. So,
and yeah, I am going to meet up with
Timmy. Yeah, I'd rather meet up with
[ __ ] Timmy than [ __ ] Bongo.
Well, if you go to Birmingham, I'm going
to smash your He's not going to do
nothing, mate. I told the guy to come to
London. He would do it. I should have to
go to Birmingham again. I only went to Birmingham.
And then do you know what he tried
saying? Oh, do you know what this little
[ __ ] tried saying? He tried saying
Yeah. He tried [ __ ] saying,
uh, do you know what he tried saying,
right? He tried telling me that I'm skin.
He tried to say that I'm skin
when he's the one that had 20 to last
him for two weeks. What the [ __ ] Do you
remember when he had nine burgers? Yeah.
To last him for two weeks. Was it nine
burgers? 20 to last him for [ __ ] two
[ __ ] weeks. And he tried to call
other people [ __ ] skin.
Oh my. Jesus. Well, I mean, I'm I mean,
I've been laid more times than you have.
You can't even get laid. You've never
been laid once. That doesn't add up.
Yeah, I'm poor. You don't know how much
money I have. Again, you don't know how
much money I have. You know what doesn't
add up? I tell you what doesn't add up
is you people claim that you're not
jealous of anything. Yet, you can't show
your faces. You never been seen with a
woman. You come on here continuously
every day for years and self project.
That doesn't add up. That's something
that doesn't add up. How you claim that
you got money, you got your life sorted,
yet you're on air every single day projecting
to people that you don't even know
that's half your age. That's what
doesn't add up, mate. That's what
doesn't [ __ ] add up. Look, you're
still on here typing. It goes to show
you got no life,
you know? It just goes to show that you
people have got no life. What you do on
here every day,
you know, some madness.
Fat, ugly people that ain't got a life.
Anyways, I'm going to block you now
anyways cuz you're boring. I want some
genuine people here. Not these little mongos, self projectors.
[ __ ] absolute mongos, bro. So, yeah.
[ __ ] wild, lad. [ __ ] wild.
And then they say about stuff that
people said about kids, but bro, the
thing is they wanted people to talk about kids.
They love and and they wouldn't still
be. It's just they're excused for being
jealous. That's all it is. And bro, I'm
not delusional when I'm saying this
stuff. I generally believe it. I
generally generally generally [ __ ]
believe it. Do I like, bro, do you think
I think any normal person is jealous of
me? No, I [ __ ] do not. But I I
believe these people are. I generally
generally do believe these people are
because these people don't even leave
the house. They don't have no money. the
[ __ ] that they do every single day on
YouTube because someone has apparently
spoke about [ __ ] kids. It's an
excuse. It is a [ __ ] excuse with
these jealous ass ugly people. So So
they're trying to use things people said
about [ __ ] kids. What a madness, bro.
No normal person acts like this really,
mate. They really really don't, you know.
Yeah. They're just [ __ ]
[ __ ] Hell, mom.
No, no, no. [Music]
I think I'll have to go for a drink at some point.
And yeah, there's I don't [ __ ] moan
about the women's [ __ ] anymore.
This is why these breaks are necessary because I mean
there's nothing to moan about.
It's never going to change. What the [ __ ]
What left to be said? We don't moan anymore.
It's never ever going to change. So,
best get used to it. Simple, isn't it?
I mean, it's why I don't go out every
week cuz I'm not going to enjoy myself
going out every [ __ ] week when I
[ __ ] want to
is disgusting, but you know, it is what
it is, man.
Only thing I can do is look, smack and
try. When I when I can be bothered to
try, I'll just look, max, and try.
And I don't give a [ __ ] if I don't get
anything, you know? I won't even be
using I won't even be using escorts anymore.
I won't even be using escorts anymore to be fair.
Not after that experience. [ __ ] that. No way.
I look [ __ ] clean last week, bro.
clean. I think I got the same thing done
when I met USA. Is he face wax and
stuff? It's good for your skin.
Good for your skin, man. Yeah. [Music]
speaking to this Ukrainian woman.
But yeah, they kind of live in a different country.
Don't give a [ __ ] to be honest, man.
I'm going to get my drink in a minute,
man. I got a drink in the fridge and
then we'll go get in a bit.
£1,200 a month is peanuts.
These people, they really are idiots, aren't they?
£1,200 a month.
Let me get this man
right back. One second. It's called
He's a proper
but yeah I Yeah.
Why do you people do what you do every
day on here anyways?
Care about kids. You don't care about [ __ ] children.
You don't care about children at all.
That's a lot of [ __ ] dedication and
stalking for people that just speak like
kids. That's part of narcissism.
I generally think what it is with a lot
of these people on here, man, is that
they sit on [ __ ] line, got no life,
failed at everything in their 40s, got
nothing to live for, see someone better
looking, see someone younger than them,
and they just go for them. That's what I
think it is. It's nothing to do with
what people say or what people don't
say. That's ridiculous, bro. That is
you know. Very ridiculous.
These people don't care about kids,
you know? They would [ __ ] kids' life up
if they [ __ ] had a choice. They don't
care about children. Why do they use
children as an excuse every time?
I hate that, man. Dude,
definitely definitely is definitely
jealousy with these people.
Yeah, it definitely definitely is.
You think a normal person would waste
their [ __ ] life on this every day cuz
someone spoke about kids and they don't
even care about kids? Nah, mate.
Jealousy with these people. They ain't
got a life.
That's all it is, man.
uh sat on YouTube every day.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I could do with a Guinness, man. I swear down.
Longer you go about drinking, the more
you crave it. I swear to God. Yeah.
Should we go out every week to to piss
the bomb off?
Should we go out every week to piss bomb off? Seriously.
we actually mate
to piss the bomb off? Yeah,
[ __ ] I never got any of my money stopped.
Oh, no. No, you didn't. I need to win a
football bet in order to go out
drinking. No, I don't.
I've not been out since I won that £500.
Still not been out.
really mate. Yep.
I'll be back later anyways.