That was a [ __ ] late one to be fair.
Hey, sorry man. I [ __ ] woke up a bit late.
I was on [ __ ] Reddit quite late to be fair. So Yeah,
[ __ ] sign up limit for [ __ ] sake, man. Oh man,
they need that power. Them Reddit mods
Without power, they go [ __ ] bonkers.
They like to ban people because, you know, [ __ ]
there's nothing you can do about it.
They ban you, you know. So
that's why they ban people.
She just sounds stuck up the [ __ ]
watching this guy's approach Yeah.
Vibe or something.
That's so [ __ ] Where's my [ __ ] phone? Bye-bye.
throwing it, man. Yeah, that was so mad
like reading that yesterday. How like
about to talk about that. Um how like
women can literally like get sex
whenever they want without even leaving
the house and then in order for you to just
be able to get a date, just a date that
probably won't even go anywhere, go
through hundreds of pounds and
you still can't even get a date. That's
[ __ ] That is completely [ __ ] I was
just thinking about last week when I was
reading all that [ __ ] you know?
It's really eye opening, isn't it?
I was born in the [ __ ] wrong era,
bro. Swear to God, I was.
I wish I was born in the [ __ ] 80s.
So, you know,
we don't care what you [ __ ] have to say
about why people don't get women. We
don't care about you people self-p
projecting cuz that's all you people do
is self project. I've got videos to back
up what I say. I've got evidence to back
up everything that I say. So, your
little s little self-p projecting
excuses. We're not interested in that. So,
we're not interested in [ __ ] and simps.
[ __ ] hell, man. It really, really is
a mug game. Who knows when I'll be out
again. I probably won't even go out for
my birthday, to be fair, after reading
that. It's depressing as [ __ ]
It is depressing as [ __ ]
I just can't believe how like you can
[ __ ] spend hundreds and not even get
a date. Not even one single date and
then, you know, they can get laid
whenever they want. They can get sex
whenever they want. It's [ __ ] depressing, bro.
I swear to God, it is so depressing. I
can't wait to leave, man. I swear to
God, I can't wait to leave in November. You know,
I was on Reddit until late last night,
bro. I went to bed at probably about 600 7.
It was a late one to be fair.
It's crazy, isn't it?
But it will never change. Never change.
It will never change.
Yeah. Do you like my video?
B to fair. I think I nailed it. Hit the
nail on the head.
I think I pretty much Yeah. hit the nail
on the head there.
That's why I won't be going out this week.
Go through a couple hundred pound, get
nothing. Same boat, same story every
week, you know? It's [ __ ] boring, bro.
Tell you what, I was [ __ ] hungry at
[ __ ] 6:00 7 in the morning. I had
[ __ ] Monty [ __ ] messaging me. I
was going to go for a spoon's breakfast,
but I just didn't bother. So,
it's horrible, bro. It really, really is
horrible living like this. And another
thing is, right, people uh there's more
people going Thailand now on Instagram.
I've actually messaged a couple of um
other people as well and um
they're in Thailand now as well. Not for
the same reason, but they're just in
Thailand for a better life. They just
went there for a better life. Loads of
people are leaving England now.
People don't want to be a [ __ ] slave,
you know, 9 to5,
you know, be a slave for the system, you
know. People don't want to do that.
That's another reason why people go
Thailand. Obviously, you can't get laid
here. You can't meet anyone here. It's
not a normal life for a man or anyone
really, you know, in this country.
It's them that's the problem. It's them.
It's their unrealistic standards that
are the problem. It's them being too
picky that's the problem. But Sims will
never tell you that.
It's a depressed life over here, bro.
Like I I take [ __ ] two cocodable
every day or maybe four codonibles cuz I
don't know they make you high.
No, people go to Thailand for a better life.
People go to Thailand for a better life.
They don't just go for the women. They
go for a better life because they don't
want to be a slave to the system. They
like better weather. People don't go all
go to Thailand because of women.
The only one I know that's done that is
[ __ ] Antman and me. No one else has
done it. They go for different reasons,
not because of women. Cuz this country
is [ __ ] This country is depressing. You know,
being a [ __ ] slave, 9 to5, [ __ ] rent prices,
cost of living, can't get laid, you
know? I can I can go on and on and on.
weather, waiting around for things.
It's a depressing [ __ ] country
and the fact that you can spend hundreds
and not even get a date as well is
[ __ ] disgusting to be honest. That is
vile. Absolutely [ __ ] vile. So,
so people go there for a better life.
They don't tend to go there for women. Cuz
think about it. Most people that work,
they don't even have disposable [ __ ]
money. Most people that work in this
country don't even have disposable money,
you know? They don't even have
disposable money. They work and they've
got [ __ ] off. So, they're like a slave
to the system until they're like 60.
What [ __ ] kind of life is that?
What kind of life is that for anyone?
No, even if you want to forget the [ __ ] women.
I feel sorry for a lot of people, you
know, they say, "Oh, they work, they
work, and then they have no money left
over at the end of the month or very
little money." It's madness, isn't it? I
hate to see anyone living like that. No
wonder people [ __ ] [ __ ] off to Thailand. Could
you imagine one of like my sister or
like any other person I know that works
just [ __ ] spent £600 over a [ __ ]
weekend? They'd be [ __ ] bankrupt.
They would be [ __ ] bankrupt.
And I remember saying before about how
the most I ever spent was £700 and that
was a lot. Obviously, I had more money
then, but I always remember as, "Oh
[ __ ] that was a lot of I spent a lot of
money." And you don't even get anything
out of it. Not even a single day. Yet,
you get these people online trying to
tell you that you're going to meet
someone. It's [ __ ] madness.
It is absolute [ __ ] madness, you know?
So, what I'm saying is I'm not saying it
should be easier for men and harder for
women. That's not my argument. My
argument is that if you are willing to
put the effort in, then you should be
getting something out of it.
You know, that's like with anything. But
the thing is, you don't. That's what my
beef is. That's what my roast pink beef
is. You understand?
We're saying that even when you put the
effort in and you spend the money and
you try your hardest, you still won't
get anywhere. That's the whole point of
it being a mugs game.
Cuz when you compare it to gambling,
gambling's not really a mugs game all
that much if you think about it.
You know, gambling's got me out of a
hole a couple of times when I've needed
money, you know, or when I've won money
to lift the mood up to be honest with you.
So, it's not a mug's game really, is it?
When you compare it to trying to date
women in this country. So,
yeah, man. I'm good. I have to be.
Hope you watch my video.
I couldn't believe that. I generally
cuz you can understand how it looks, can't you?
You know, when a woman can just get laid
whenever she wants, get somebody
whenever she wants, and then when you
put the effort in, you spend the money,
you do what people are afraid of, you
still can't even get a date. I mean, I
don't know what more needs to tell you
you've got no hope in this country. I
don't know how many more experiences
have to tell you that you have no hope
here until you get the hint.
And by you, I mean me. Yeah.
Can't believe that.
Say I [ __ ] say I go out this Saturday
and the same thing happens again and I
spend £300 and I don't get a date
because that's exactly what will happen
again. Well, I don't think it will be
£600, but it might be the region of
£3400 by the time Monday comes around
again, you know, and then what? I don't have anything,
you know, like I don't have any dates.
[ __ ] that, bro. I'm not doing that every
[ __ ] week. Just because I can do it,
it doesn't mean I am going to do it. I
shouldn't have to [ __ ] do it, you know?
So yeah, what we was basically saying to
this guy here is that we're not saying
that it should be easy for men and hard
for women. We're saying that basically
if you're willing to put the effort in
like I've like I have and spend the
money like I have, you should get
something out of it. But you don't.
So it is sick and twist. It is twisted.
It's sick and twisted really if you
think about it.
There you go. Did you watch my video?
We never Bro, people don't just go to
Thailand for women.
I already said that. There's loads of
people moving to Thailand now. And it's
not because of women. There's a black
guy I'm speaking to on Instagram. He's
in Thailand. There's a white guy. He's
in Thailand. Loads of people are [ __ ]
And you know what I I think is mad? Even
when I read up stories, bro. Uh, just
watch my video, Ghost, and come back.
And what's so mad is that like you read
stories, like I was saying about where
people work and they have nothing at the
end of the month. And I feel bad. I
think it's just twisted.
Like even when it's not about myself as
well, like they work and they'll have
like nothing. Literally [ __ ] all.
And it's like you you think like, "What
the actual [ __ ] bro?" You know?
So yeah, just watch my video, Ghost, and
then come back, bro.
We'll tell you what I done over last
week as well. Yeah,
it's that they're unrealist. They've got unrealistic standards. Um,
you know, they they've got unrealistic
standards. That's the problem.
Well, basically, Ghosting, uh, I went
out last week or the week before. I
can't even keep I can't even keep track
of [ __ ] time to be honest with you. I
went out, spent 600 pound over a
weekend, got 10 numbers on not one single day.
And then there's women on Reddit that
just call people round to have sex. They
don't even need to leave the house. They
don't need to put any effort into their
life whatsoever in order to get laid or
find anyone, which is okay. But then the
my problem with ghosting is that even
when you put effort into your life, like
you looks max um you know, you approach,
you do everything that you can do, you
still won't meet anyone. And that's why
it's a mug's game. That's why dating in
this country is an absolute mug's game.
And it's worse than gambling. It's way
You know, we're not talking fucking£12,2
[ __ ] pints anymore. I don't know how
that 600 went, but it went. Looked at my
car. I was like, "Oh, 600's gone.
What the [ __ ] bro?" And then to not
even get a single date. Yeah. I'm not
even trying to after, you know, with
them 10 numbers I got. I don't know,
bro. I'm not uh
I'm not uh I'm not thinking about trying
anytime soon here, bro.
I don't know, man. That kind of put me off.
I said I was going to go to my birthday
with my sister, but I think I kind of I
kind of have to do that cuz it's my
birthday and I made plans, but I don't want to. So,
yep. It's not easy at all.
It's not easy at all. It's impossible.
You can't even get laid. You can't You
can't even get a date. Why are we
talking about getting laid? Can't even
get Can't even get a date. It's not easy
at all, mate. It's not easy at all.
So, you can be good-looking, you can
dress good, you can have money, you can
put the effort in, and you still can't
even get a date. You understand how that
looks, don't you, Ghosting? You
understand how that looks, right?
You understand how it looks? Yeah.
But no, it's not easy. There's nothing
easy about it at all.
Remember, don't dis my struggle. Don't
dismiss my struggles.
Yeah, I'm not looking to that in a hurry again.
But no, nothing's easy about it at all, bro.
Yeah, people are getting into
relationships cuz people might have met through work
or they might have met through a friend
or whatever. I don't I I I can tell you
Ghosten that I went out last week looks
maxim you can ask everyone on YouTube
and I got 10 numbers and I got one reply
and I didn't even get a single date.
I I can tell you that, you know. I could
tell you that for nothing, mate. I
wouldn't even charge you. Why don't you
get a job? Same same question goes to
you. Why don't you get a job?
Instead of coming on YouTube asking
people why they don't have a job, why
don't you have a job? Why are you not at
work right now? Stop self projecting.
Bye-bye now. You get yourself a job. But
yeah, ghosting. That's basically what happened. So yeah,
I look sick as [ __ ] bro. Looks max and everything.
She still can't even get a date. Oh, because
um cuz I don't need a job.
But yeah, like you can understand
ghosting where I'm coming from when you
get 10 numbers going out look smacking
and still no one's interested in this country.
I mean, you'd be [ __ ] to be honest
with you, I weren't even that human. I was
I was kind of I was kind of like, yeah,
this is going to happen cuz I'm so used
to it now. I'm so used to the [ __ ]
in this country with dating and that.
I'm so like used to it.
It's just the same old every time you go
out here. You know what I'm saying? But like um
and then I won £500 on the roulette and
I was like, "Okay, that's God telling me
don't go out in this country again."
There literally are signs God's giving
you, bro. Like, believe it or not, I was
actually able to save money this month,
you know? But it's like God telling me
don't go out and try in this country
ever again. That's literally God has
spoken himself bro that £500. Like generally
that is bad bro. Really really bad.
There definitely is no hope here. Seriously,
thanks for calling me good-looking. It
means a lot, man.
It means a lot. Thank you.
pretty hard. I don't know how you do it.
I I've been doing it for years, matey.
So, it's minor to me.
But yeah, it is. It is [ __ ] It is. It
is. I don't even know what to say about
that, bro. to be honest with you last week.
How you can be good-looking,
dress good, smell good, put the effort
in, and still not even get a date.
Does that tell you that there's no hope
for some people?
Does that not tell you?
So, I feel like I just stay in now
ghosting. I don't even go out like well
go out drinking because the the little
bit of boredom
it outweighs the frustration if I was to
go out and try again. So yeah,
it is bad though man. It is bad.
It will never change either. It's been
the same for years. Will it never
change, will it?
I won't be doing that again, Anari.
But no, you definitely can't get women
easy. Definitely definitely definitely not. So yeah,
hope you're good. Anyways, ghost and lad.
But bad things happen to good people.
This is what you need to know in life
that if you was a [ __ ] or a bully when
you was younger, you'd have a good life.
If you was anything [ __ ]
good in any way like I was, you're going
to have a bad life.
So, I mean,
that's that's just how it is, you know?
And if you notice, like people that have
been [ __ ] in the past, like bullies,
nasty people, they're in relationships,
they've, you know, got married, all
horrible people. And you know, good
people either die young or they just
suffer their whole life. So,
but I feel like God says, "Well, we kind
of feel sorry for you, so we'll let you
win some money."
It's so [ __ ] up, bro. Really, really [ __ ] up.
But yeah, you definitely can't get women
easy. Definitely definitely not bad.
It's going to take a very long time now
for hope to regrow.
To be honest, it's going to take a while.
It's not a pedo country, you [ __ ]
idiot. Don't believe everything you [ __ ] read.
Well, now you just use escorts here. Yeah.
Well, saying that escorts probably not
an option anymore either, but try and
find an escort.
That's the only thing
the only thing you can do here is is
just give up and lose hope like I
already have. And you know, if you're
out drinking again, then you can try
when you're drinking, but you just know
it's just going to be the same old.
But I don't know. I've lost hope for a
very long time again after last week's events.
So yeah, I know the solution is to not stay here.
Well, I'm going there for I'm going
there for a couple of weeks. I'm not living there. So
>> yeah, it's [ __ ] madness. I fancied a
bagel earlier, but I was so hungry.
So [ __ ] hungry, man.
But I didn't
and just routine of saving money again.
So yeah, it's going to take long. It's
going to take a long time for hope to
grow again after that.
Do you like them?
Uh what's the latest? It's just the same old.
Yeah. Um Jamie was um uh messaging me on
Facebook earlier, bro. I told him to
[ __ ] off. Um I said, "If you want to
fight, come to London. I'll smash your face in.
simple. Like, don't stop telling me to
come to Birmingham. I already went to
So, come to London. I'm not going to
Birmingham again. I will never be mates
with that snake again. I will never ever
be mates with that snake again, bro.
Do you know how many people I helped out
in the past?
It's not even a [ __ ] joke.
Him. I've helped my sister out in the
past. I I still talk to one of my
sisters and my mom obviously. Um and
it's like, you know, you really really
need to think about you.
That's another thing we need to start
doing is thinking about yourself and
being selfish. Obviously, my mom, I
don't mind, you know, my mom's good in
that, you know, whatever. She's all
right. But I mean, in terms of like
Monty and like I was thinking about like
even people I've helped before, you need
to really stop being you you you you.
cuz if you don't then these this stuff
is going to keep happening. You know
what I mean?
He's not on the community but he's still
with Natalie. Yeah. And I said to him
like come to London. I'll smash your
face and I'm not going to [ __ ]
Birmingham. Why am I going back to Birmingham?
Smash his [ __ ] face in mate.
So that's what you need to be in life.
You need to be a [ __ ] in terms of like
money. Don't give anyone money. Be
selfish. That's what you need to be
like. Trust me, you do.
The only person I've really got time for is Laney.
I don't really have time for anyone else.
He ruined the night out, bro. As soon as
he said, "Oh, I don't have my ID." I was
like, "Oh, [ __ ] sake." I've had this
with [ __ ] Ant-Man before, you know?
[ __ ] I I've had this with [ __ ]
Ant-Man before as well where we met and
he says he doesn't have his proper ID
and it just ruins the whole night cuz
you know that you need ID to get into
these places. You shouldn't but you do.
So it was kind of [ __ ] from there
almost. Yeah, it was it was a nightmare
but I won't be doing it ever again for anyone.
Yeah. And he's a snake.
He is a [ __ ] snake.
And he introduced me to that Skint
virgin as well in the Outer London bedset. Grezy
[ __ ] he he introduced me to that Skint bastard.
And before you say it, yes. £13,000
to have saved for three years is
absolutely [ __ ] skint.
Yeah, exactly. That's how it is. But and
obviously it's a city. It's Birmingham.
It's a city. So, they're going to ask,
but luckily we got into one place. It
was just a I remember before. Yeah, I
never forget this.
Oh, last time I I met Ant-Man, I lost my
bank card. I think I lost my bank card
or something happened and it [ __ ] the
whole night up. Um, but I think the last
time we went out was No, the last time
we went out was was was fine, but the
one before that I lost my bank card and
obviously I had money in my bank card. Um,
and yeah, it was really, really bad.
And I had to like and I didn't have
online banking as well. Oh, it was
madness. And I think the time before I
met him, he didn't have his like ID, so
we had to use his prison ID. And
obviously, we couldn't get into most
places. So, the only time we really had
a normal night out was um [ __ ] um
the last time, which was a Sunday.
So, anytime I meet someone ever again, I
need to say, "Have you got your ID? Have
you got your bank card?" Cuz it's [ __ ]
So, it's not funny, bro. when you when
you're looking forward to a night out
and you've got money and then some you
got a burden that doesn't have his ID
with you. It's not funny with them. It's
not funny, bro. It's annoying as [ __ ]
cuz you're you're ready to have a good
night out. You know, you're all prepared
and then you got some burden like Monty
saying, "Oh, I don't have my ID." Oh,
[ __ ] sake. You know what I'm saying?
It's horrible. It's not funny. It's it's
it's horrible, bro. And I remember the
feeling as well cuz it's happened a few
times. It's happened with Antman as well
when he was in Sheffield. It happened
when he was in Nottingham.
And then last time when he was in
London, it was me losing my bank card. So yeah.
So that's how it is, bro.
Yeah. Ghost. That's how it is.
I had to call my mom to send me money to
my other I can't remember if I lost it
or it got blocked. I can't remember.
I can't exactly remember. There was a
problem with it, but I think I had to
ring my mom and
Oh, I think I had to ring my mom and
send it to Ant-Man's account.
That's what I think happened. No, no.
Yeah, I had to get my mom to send it to
Ant-Man's [ __ ] account.
Oh, it was some madness. It was not the
last time he was in London. The time before that
[ __ ] madness it was, bro. Every
single [ __ ] time. It's some sort of
burden, you know. But the last time, the
last Sunday was all right. Am I going
out approaching this week? Um,
no. Considering I've told you that about
what happened last week about spending the £600
and getting 10 numbers and not getting a
date. Uh, probably not.
What kind of question is that? Uh, no.
What the [ __ ] I'll just about make it
out to my birthday. Stop dismissing my
struggles. Please. That's one thing I
ask you to do is please do not dismiss my struggles,
you know, about the spending the 600
pound and getting the 10 numbers and
only one reply. And this is real severe
[ __ ] It's not entertaining for me. It's
depressing. I mean, I'm I'm glad it's
entertaining for you, bro. I really am.
But for me, it's depressing. So,
yeah, I know that. No, I do have online
banking just not with that account. When
I used to get the money, when I used to
get the sublet money
um when I used to get the sublet money,
I used to put it in a different account.
So that account didn't have online
banking. So that's the story with it basically.
Yeah. Back at two grand again. I'm back
at two grand again and I'm not looking
to waste any of that money.
with a weekly payment. I'm not I'm not
looking to waste any of that two grand, bro.
So, yeah, it might be entertaining for
you, but it's depressing for me.
[ __ ] depressing for me, bro. Yeah,
I need to save. I still need to build my
money up. I'm nowhere near where I want
to be, bro.
So yeah, I mean I get money weekly as
well. I could go out every week drinking
if I wanted to, but I don't want to.
Waste of time, waste of effort, waste of
money. Simple. So
is that right, Grezy? Seven grand.
Most I've added seven.
Six in cash and some in the bank. Yep.
Uh, do I reckon he's skin? 100% he is skin. Yes.
Purely because he calls people skin
every single day and he's the one sat on YouTube.
Don't go out drinking. Doesn't do
anything with his life. I mean, I'm I've
lost hope in life. So, that I've got an
excuse why I don't do anything. After
last week, I lost hope,
you know, like ever trying anything ever
again because that's how this country
gets you. So, I mean, like that's it.
£200 a lot on trainers. Not really, bro.
My trainers have always cost over £200.
My vapors were 215.
Um, you know, he doesn't have money. He
He likes to try to convince people that
he's got money, but truly he is skint,
bro. like he does not get more than600
700 a month. Don't let him try to fool
you or tell you otherwise. He doesn't
have no money. Trust me. I spent [ __ ]
£600 last week over the weekend and I
don't have loads of money.
He doesn't have money.
He still doesn't even make sense.
I've got property. I own property. Bro,
do you really believe that? Come on. the
guy skint and New Balance trainers are
not 200 pound either. They're like the
cheapest one of the cheapest makes. But yeah,
I've lost hope. That's why I don't go
out. It's not a money issue.
I don't really care to be honest with
you, bro. All I know is if people are
coming on YouTube every single day
calling other people's skin their skin
themselves, bro. That's that's all I
know, bro. I couldn't care less to be fair. But
if someone's coming on YouTube every day
calling other people skint, then it must
apply to themselves.
You know, I've done a lot in the past
two months. I've gone to Birmingham.
I've gone out. You know, there's nothing
skint about me, kid.
Nothing's skin about me, matey.
Listen, Monty, stop sending me voice
notes and come to London so I can smash
your [ __ ] head in. Simple. Like,
don't know how many times I have to say
to this stupid [ __ ] [ __ ] I would
rather have no girlfriend than have
Natalie G. I would rather have no
girlfriend than have [ __ ] Kaye. You
know what I'm saying, bro? I would
rather have [ __ ] nothing
than [ __ ] have what he's been with.
I'd rather have nothing, bro. Like,
they're monties. They're monties.
They're not even a flex. Like, actually
get with someone decent. Yeah. Before
trying to tell anyone else they've got no one.
I can't play it, bro. It's on [ __ ] >> Facebook.
>> Listen, Monty, you are lonely. Anyways,
come to London so I can smash your face
in. So I can smash your black teeth in,
you silly [ __ ] Listen, [ __ ] man, I
told him yesterday, bro, you would [ __ ]
your kids if it wasn't for the fact that
you you are no longer allowed to see
your kids. I'm speaking about his kids
and he still won't come and see me. I
told him I will meet him if he comes to
London, bro. I promise. You come to
London and I will smash your face in. I
will smash your black teeth down your
throat. And he won't come. He won't
come, bro. He's scared. That's what I'm
saying. He's scared. Everyone has to go
to Birmingham. Everyone has to go to
him. [ __ ] off, bro. I'm not going to no Birmingham.
You think I'd rather [ __ ] have no one
than have someone that's [ __ ] shagged
a load of [ __ ] Asians,
you know? [ __ ] got black flaps,
[ __ ] STD [ __ ] riding, bro. I'd
rather have nothing, mate. I'd rather
[ __ ] a [ __ ] flesh.
Yeah, I'd rather [ __ ] a [ __ ]
flashlight, bro. Not even joking.
He thinks that's a [ __ ] flex.
You lost hope cuz your skin flint mud
up. Talking about yourself. Like I said,
bro, people that call other people skin
or skin themselves.
Yeah, man. People that call other people
skin or skin themselves ghosting. It's
similar to what I was saying earlier,
bro. That's why I don't even block the
accounts, lad. Cuz if they're bringing
up skin every day, they must be skin.
But we already know that self projection on here.
The the big thing with this ghosting is
is they seem to think that um
I mean, I call I call skimp. No, it's
not a contradiction. You ask me a
question. said, "No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no. One second." You asked me a
question and I answered it. You said,
"Oh, do you think he's got money?" And I
said, "No, I don't think he has money
because of just because somebody buys
trainers, it doesn't mean that they've
got money." You know what I'm saying? I
could go out and buy a load of GS right
now. It doesn't mean that I've got a
load of money. Doesn't mean I'm [ __ ]
rich. So, no.
I said that he's got no money because
you asked me.
You know these people call people
self projection again. The thing is with
this community go is people on here seem
to think everyone's got the same life as them.
They seem to seriously think everyone
lives the same life as them. Skin, no
friends, virgin, never been with a
woman. They seriously think everyone's
got the same life as them. That's what
it comes to. It's it's it's wild. They
come out with the most random specific
things that applies to their own life.
It's proper [ __ ] up, bro. Like they
think everyone's like them skin. That's
why they come here every day calling
people skin cuz they think everyone has
the same life as them.
And yeah, they call people skin cuz
they're skin. Simple. So it's like
that's what it is. They've been doing it for years.
I mean what's okay what's their excuse
for being on YouTube all day every day
then? Like I've told you I've lost hope.
Can't be asked going out. You know I
gave a valid reason why I'm not going
out anymore. What's the people's reason?
So yeah, bro.
Yeah, man. But that's it. So you asked
me if I think NJ has money and no, he
doesn't have money. You asked me a
question and I answered it, you know.
Well, I've already shown you that I
can't get a woman. So, well, I mean, you
know, um, in that way, I mean, you know
what I'm saying? So, I mean, well, I
still can't find anyone, so I've proven it. So, yeah.
Don't be silly, bro. I'm not
good-looking. I'm a ma.
So, you see, this is a bit funny now
because you're saying that I'm good-looking.
And this is basically what I was saying
before is that these people are jealous
of my looks, but then they're asking me
why am I why would anyone be jealous of
me? See, this is funny cuz I used to say
that they were jealous of my looks.
I'll find someone eventually. I'm sure I
will, bro. Yeah. been hearing that since
I was 14. I'm sure I will. Why didn't I
find anybody when I was traveling around the country
when I approached 7,000 women? Why
didn't I find anyone then? Why didn't I
find anyone last week when I got them 10 numbers?
I mean, that's a valid question, isn't
it? I mean, yeah, you can say that, but
would have I already found someone by
now with all the traveling and the
approaching I done?
I'm pretty sure it would have already
happened. I mean, don't let's not
dismiss my struggles here. I get what
you're saying and you're entitled to
your opinion, sir. You genuinely are.
But I'm pretty sure,
no, I don't look at it that way because
you're not going to meet three billion
women. You're you're not going to meet
1% of that population. So, it doesn't
matter if there's three billion females.
I have gone all over the country. I have approached
time and time and time again and none
are interested. That tells me that
there's no one for me and that would
tell anyone with a brain that there's no
one for them. So I don't look at it that
way at all. I look at it as I went out
last week. I got 10 numbers. Don't even
have a date for the week after which was
last week. I've been up and down the
country various times. I've cold
approached [ __ ] god knows how many
times I've got approaches on my [ __ ]
channel and not one of them are
interested. That's the way I look at it.
I see it very very different to how you
see it and the [ __ ] that I've had to put
up with for years with them as well. I
don't see it as there's three billion.
There could be [ __ ] 10 trillion. It
wouldn't make a difference. So,
so why are you telling me that I'm going
to find someone eventually when you know
that I've traveled up and down the
country approaching? You didn't answer
my question. Why haven't I already found them?
If that was the case, why haven't I
already found someone? Why didn't I find
someone last week? Come on, tell me why
I didn't find someone last week. I got
10 numbers. I've done about 40
approaches. Tell me why I didn't I did
not meet anyone last week. I want to
hear it. I tried enough. I looked my
best. Spent enough money.
It doesn't matter if I'm only 27.
It doesn't matter. You tell me why I
Doesn't matter if I'm only 27. I've
tried more than anyone in the world. If
my age is irrelevant, mate. I could be
20 [ __ ] one. So, you need to tell me
why I did not meet someone last week
when I approached 30 to 40 people and I
got 10 numbers. And I got 10 numbers,
right? Yeah. I got 10 numbers and not
even one of them went on a date with me.
Only one of them replied, somebody from
Malaysia. So, at the end of the day, you
can understand how it doesn't look good, does it?
Uh, here we go with the self projection.
Trying to call me ugly again. Bro,
listen. We've got this guy on here
calling me good-looking. Bro, the only
ugly people are you.
The only ugly people are you. You fat
ugly people on YouTube. Look, we got
this guy out here even calling me
good-looking, bro. The only ugly people
are you. Are you forgetting we've seen
you people and you put your camera on?
You are [ __ ] ugly. That's why you
come on here every single day calling
people ugly because you are [ __ ] ugly
yourselves. Fat and ugly. Listen, I'll
prove it right now. Right. Let me put
the link up and you come and put your
camera on. You are [ __ ] ugly. You
people. how you can try and talk about
anyone else. I'll put a link up right
now and I'll prove it. I'll put a link
up right now. If I'm so ugly, come on.
Come on and show your face.
You can't cuz you're [ __ ] ugly.
That's what it is with you people, bro.
You're fat ugly monsters that can't take
a day off of YouTube. You live for
YouTube cuz that's all you ugly people
have. I'm not talking about you ghost.
I'm talking about some of these. Comment
the link. We'll put our camera on. Come
and put your camera on.
What you mean is you are [ __ ] ugly.
Fat and ugly. Just like Gray Cat. Just
like Bomb. I find it offensive when
these fat ugly little low lives come in
here trying to talk about other people.
These fat ugly low lives. Know what I'm saying, bro?
So, and I only spoke to 10 uh people.
Anyways, back to you ghosting that. So,
you're not going to come in and show
your face? Exactly. Cuz you're ugly. Um,
so to answer your question, uh, Ghosten
Sobo, I actually spoke to about 30 40
women. I mean, I got 10 numbers. And in the past
3, four years, I probably approached
7,000 women. So, I'm pretty sure if I
was going to find someone, I would have
found someone by now.
I'm pretty sure if I was going to You're
not coming on here, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
Lj, you're banned. [ __ ] that. You're not
coming on here, [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, at least I'm not a virgin like you,
Bane. At least I'm not a virgin like
you. You can't even come in and show
your face cuz you're too ugly trying to
come in here and call me [ __ ] ugly.
I'm guessing it's about 7,000.
I'm guessing it's 7,000. I don't [ __ ]
I don't [ __ ] know. I'm guessing.
[ __ ] that. That [ __ ] [ __ ] is not
getting a platform on my channel. He
come [ __ ] right off.
Listen, bro. I don't go on his channel
for a reason. So, I'm not going to let
him on my channel.
Yeah. Um I mean, I've I've slept with
women. I've shown me with women, man.
Something that you've never had. I mean,
I've shown in bed with women. Something
that you've never been with cuz you're
too ugly. You ugly. You You can't even
come in and show your face. How are you
going to sit there, right, with your fat
ugly self, with your ugly face, and try
and talk about me when I'm miles better
looking than you? How are you going to
talk about someone that's better looking
than you? Yeah. When you're the one
that's fat and ugly, too scared to show
your face due to fear and embarrassment
of your ugly looks. This is what I'm
saying with these people here, Ghosting,
is that they're all projectors. This is
what I'm saying. They're all fat.
They're all ugly. They're all skin. This
is why they're on here every day. Think
about it, bro. Listen, they're trying to
take the piss out of somebody for losing
hope. Yeah. Right. But they're sat on
YouTube every day. So, they can't have
money. They can't be good-looking. If
they're sat on here, bro, from the time
they wake up to the time they [ __ ] go
to bed, something's wrong in their life,
bro. Do you understand what I'm saying,
bro? Do you know you see what I'm
saying? Something is seriously wrong in
their life. If they're not ugly and they
and they're not skinn and they're on
here all day, every day, do you not
understand? There's something, bro.
wrong with them. Uh, don't ever lose
hope. I lost hope a [ __ ] long time ago, bro. So, yeah.
I'm just so happy I won that money, bro.
And I don't have to go out and try
again. I'm so happy, bro. So,
yeah. Oh, [ __ ]
That's nasty, bro.
Uh, over the past two months, I think
it's over a thousand to be fair. I'm
thinking I don't think it's just that
roulette win. I think cuz I won on the
football as well. I think it's over a
thousand in the past month and a half to be honest.
So, all of the money I spent I got back.
I mean, do you know the last time I went
out? You know when I went out last week?
You know when I went out? Do you know?
Listen, bro. You know the last time I
went out um other than last week was um
was a month. Yeah, was a month, bro.
I've I have definitely lost hope. I went
out that week cuz I was bored. I was
bored and I just wanted to drink. No, I
generally have lost hope. If I if I did
not lose hope, if I haven't lost hope,
I'd be out every week trying. I've got
the money to do it, it's not a problem,
you know, but I mean, the fact that I'm
not trying every week and I only go out
when I'm really bored. That shows I got no hope.
So, I mean, that I mean, I go out
because I'm [ __ ] bored as [ __ ] You
know, after nice detox, I like to get on
it again. I generally have lost time
because I would be out every week
like I used to or I never well I haven't
been out every week for like a year to
be fair but I mean I would be out every week you know
but I'm not because I know there's no
hope here so that's it. It's just a mugs game.
So the only time I go out and I try
again is when I'm extremely bored and I
can't stay in anymore
and I just kill two birds with one stone
and I just try cuz I'm drunk. So
I mean I didn't get anyone not I didn't
get anyone throughout the summer.
Well nobody was interested in the summer. Ghostim.
I didn't get a a single date in this
summer, did I?
I didn't get a single date this summer.
Not this summer. I didn't.
Nope. I didn't get anything this whole
year. The last day I went on was April
with that Italian time waster.
Nope. Not this summer. I didn't get
anything. I've only been on three dates
this year and they were all in the same month.
It was either March or April.
Um, and since then I've been out loads
and not even a single day. So,
nope. I didn't get [ __ ] all this summer.
Uh, basically, um, we was talking and
stuff. Um, funny you should say this. I
already explained this, but you didn't
see it. Um, we was talking. I said, "Oh,
yeah. I'm going to come to Finland and
and see you soon. you know, I've got the
money. It cost like500 pound, whatever.
Not a problem. And then she turned
around and said, "Oh, I'm actually with
somebody. I'm actually um talking to
somebody I like and I want to see where
it goes. Wish you all the best, though."
And I was like, "Oh, no. Here we go
again." I knew they weren't going to be
no different. You know, when people used
to say, "Oh, like, yeah, she could be
different." Women, there's no women that
are different. They're all the same. Um,
so yeah. And then she didn't block me.
She just left it there and I didn't even
reply to it, to be honest. Same old, same old.
I say that with my puppy eyes, you know.
So, just trolling. They're no different.
None of them are different
with their mind games, the trolling. It
will never ever change. Never.
That's why I booked Thailand because I
wasn't going to deal with this [ __ ]
anymore. I weren't going to go out. I
mean, at least they're honest. Um, I
don't think she's honest, mate. I don't
think she met somebody that quickly. I
don't think she, you know, randomly just
met someone like that and just like them
like that, you know. So, it's just mind
games and [ __ ] when Crunch comes to
Crunch. So, nah, they weren't being
honest at all.
The same women The same reason women
don't like you and you're a virgin.
Same reason why women don't like you and
you're still a virgin.
So yeah, that's why. Trust me, when you
lose hope, you will be free, bro. You
will be free. Once you finally lose that
hope, life gets better. Trust me.
Um I mean, she she said that she would
meet me at first.
I mean, she said the distance was fine
to to begin with. So
she said that she wouldn't mind meeting
me if I went there and I was like maybe
I should actually book some now. Then
her tone changed. So
anyways, I I'll you join the hangouts
and we'll have this discussion. Do you
really want to have this discussion?
Right. I'll put the link up and we can
have this discussion via Streamyard. Yeah.
Um, I wouldn't be traveling all the
time. I'd maybe go three times a year.
But do if it means not having to put up
with this [ __ ] [ __ ] every time I go
out in this country, I would do it. If
it means me not having to [ __ ] deal
with [ __ ] this [ __ ] every time I go
out, then I would do it three times a
year. Yeah, why not?
Why the [ __ ] not? you know, it's only
three hours on a plane. So, if it meant
ending all of this, then yeah.
So, I was thinking long term,
you know, it's not a long it's not
long-term trying in this country cuz
it's never ever going to change here.
So, if I have to leave the country three
or so times a year,
not really, bro. Not really.
But it doesn't matter anyways. So
anyways, are you coming on the
Streamlords or to Are you going to come
on and show your face or you just going
to keep self projecting because the
link's there so you can join and let's
see your face and we'll see what's ugly.
I'll show my face and you show your
face. Exactly. Cuz you're an ugly
bastard. And that's when I'll always
have one over on you people because
you're an ugly bastard. That's why you
people don't show your face. Same as Gay
Cat when Gay Cat used to speak about
Kayle's looks and look what Kay look
what she ended up looking like. You
people are ugly. And I'm saying that
with honesty. You are pure [ __ ] ugly.
Like you don't even see ugly people like that
in public to be fair. And that's why you
call people ugly cuz you're ugly yourselves.
I hope I said that in the clearest
accent possible, mate. But that is why
you do what you part of why you do. Why
do you do what you do every day? Come
and answer us. You know,
why do you people do what you do every single day?
If you're not skin and you're not ugly,
why do you haven't lost hope, have you?
You're not saving up for something, are
you? So why do you people do what you do every day?
I've already had a girlfriend and I've
already had sex. Next question.
So, why have I been seen with women and you haven't?
Why have I been seen with women and you
haven't? Why don't you have a
girlfriend? Same question goes to you,
self projector. See, you people like to
ask a lot of people questions, but you
don't like to answer anyone else's questions.
You know what I'm saying? That's what I
find with these people ghosted.
Why don't you have a girlfriend? Why
have you never been laid? The same
question goes to you. Do you know what?
I'm not dealing with this.
I mean, yeah, I'm frustrated now ghosting. So,
but to be honest, no, really, bro. I
don't really have a sex drive much anymore.
I think it kind of died down and
obviously I don't I can't I don't use
escorts anymore obviously because of um
the problem. So yeah, it's just it
doesn't even really
I don't get sexy frustrated, bro. Like
don't know if you do, but I don't
No, really. [ __ ] that, bro. Oh, no.
Nando's [ __ ] Nando's Coke used to be the best. Wow.
But what I'm saying, Ghost, is when I
went out last week, I I didn't think I
was going to meet the love of my life. I
thought that I was going to at least get
a date. So, if you can get 10 numbers
and you can't even get a date, I don't
think you're going to meet someone. I
mean, a date is the first step to
knowing if you're compatible with
someone or not. So, yeah,
like that's it, bro. Like, I won't ask
him to like get sex or anything, but I
would have thought that at least
somebody cuz I'm decent looking, bro. I
look max and everything, man.
I'll show you what I look like if you want.
Deleted it, bro. But yeah, I looked good
anyways, man. But never made a
difference. Not interested in this country.
They're just not interested in this country.
But yeah, that sucks about the drinks,
man. Cuz I I can't drink Diet Coke.
Yeah, they banned that in um KFC. They
banned it in Subway and the only place
you could get it from is like Burger
King and McDonald's. So when I used to
go KFC, I used to have to get the drink from McDonald's.
Oh, it's a nightmare, bro. When I used
to be in when I used to live in
Stratford, I used to get the McDonald's
Coke and then go next door to KFC to get Yeah. chicken.
That's bad, bro.
I have a Tuesday t-bone tomorrow. Yeah,
I'm doing absolutely nothing.
Just like always. Yep.
taking a piss out of me, Bob, saying
that I'm good-looking. Why are you
taking the piss?
If it wasn't for this social media
thing, women would love me, you know, if
it wasn't for, you know, social media. Um,
you know, if it wasn't for this social media [ __ ]
I would be loved by women just like I
was 3 years ago. But now it's a
different ball game. You can't even get anyone.
No, I'm not good-looking, bro. These
people in here call me ugly.
People in here call me ugly, bro.
So, I must be ugly.
me ugly on here, bro.
So, why would these people call me ugly
if I'm good-looking, Bob? Huh?
So, why do these people call me ugly if
I'm not ugly? Bob.
Nah, I never tried it, bro.
You wish you had the balls to go on approach.
I can do it,
but I'm choosing not to do it because
it's too depressing.
It's way too depressive, bro. One Yeah.
So, what would you rate me out of 10?
I just think, bro. Yeah, there's just like
I don't know. I don't know. I just think
there's like not someone for everyone.
I think maybe that just proves there's
not someone for everyone.
Maybe my experiences,
but I think I would have found someone
if it wasn't for like social media and
simps. I mean nowadays. Yeah. I just feel like
there's just not someone for everyone.
That's what I think personally.
So I would have believed it back in the
day when there was no social media cuz
So yeah, I could go out like every week
from now, bro, and I probably wouldn't
even get laid or anything for maybe like
another two years.
Very, very unlikely.
Bad to think that women can get laid
whenever they want and even if you put
effort in and you have balls, you still
can't get anything.
Wow. That is mad, isn't it?
It's uh it's actually a mint Instagram
account. Yeah. If you got loads of followers,
maybe I'll find someone on Reddit.
There we go. Yeah. Yep.
At least I got the money back that I
spent in it. Bob
thinking how the [ __ ] do I have [ __ ]
two grand? What the [ __ ]
And yeah, it's cuz of like the football
bet wins and stuff. So whenever I went out,
I didn't spend anything because I'd win
the money back.
My teeth are not perfect,
but they're okay. Yeah, it could do with whitening. But
if I didn't win that money,
I would be in some bother, bro. I'm not
going to lie to you. But it's okay now
cuz I've built my money up. But it's
only cuz I won football. I won on
obviously the roulette on the Sunday. So
cuz yeah, I've won over a grand the past
month and a half. So it just adds up to
the money that I had in it. So
put £100 on the route and I also won
that football bet. That was I won £39 on
the football bet.
So obviously see people don't think oh
30 winning [ __ ] £39 is a lot of
money. But you know when it pays for
your dry cleaning which is almost4
you're not paying for anything. you're
just winning money and just just paying for
um your outings and stuff. So, what knows?
Obviously, I lost on football as well,
but I mean I'm still up. So,
yeah, it sucks I'm never going to meet anyone, Bob.
really does suck.
Imagine I was a virgin. Could you
imagine I was actually a virgin? Oh, Jesus Christ.
Imagine I was a virgin, bro. Imagine I
was a virgin starting off now. Damn. I
think I probably would have end up
killing myself. But imagine I was a
virgin and I've just got into the dating game.
Yeah, it's bad enough even when you've
had sex. Like I've had sex. Obviously,
you've seen me without sex, but you
know, it's bad enough even when you have sex.
I wouldn't mind if when you put effort
in, you actually got what you wanted.
And I'm all for that. You know, what's
the problem with that? You know, it's
supposed to be harder for men. But like
I said, it's the whole even if you put
effort into it, even if you try, you
still won't get anywhere.
So then it's like sometimes I feel like
I might as well look like Timmy Eldridge.
170. Jesus. I've only [ __ ] done about
five. Well, including not including
escorts. I think it's about four or five.
And the average woman's body count is
about four or five. So, go figure. What
I've had to do to get them body counts, right?
What I've had to do to um
see three years ago, Bob, I never had
these I never had these problems,
you know, like I was I could kiss, I
could get dates, you know, I even had a
few, but I never really had the problems
that I have now. Now, it's just impossible.
It was still hard, don't get me wrong.
It was still [ __ ] hard.
But yeah, my body count is about four or
five excluding escorts. I'm talking
about people that I've not paid for. So
four or five people and four or five is
a normal woman's body count.
So let's just say that you've got a
sister or whatever that like an average
woman that's not a [ __ ] has slept with
about four or five people and they've
never had to do anything to get them
people except being a woman. It's unfair, bro.
very very very unfair.
And you know, you you're going to get
people that sit there and say, "Oh,
well, why don't you do something about
it? What do you want us to do, bro? We
went out, we tried, we spent money. What
else are we supposed to do, bro? What I
don't know what more you're actually
supposed to [ __ ] do, but
>> will never change, will it?" So, it's
not like we haven't [ __ ] tried a
million times. So, like we have every
right to talk about how [ __ ] up it is.
It should be easier for women, but then
as soon as you put effort into your life
and you try, you should get something.
Why shouldn't you get what women can
get? Why are you Why should you not be
able to get exactly what they get when
they don't even try? You know, why not?
Why can't you?
They can get it without trying, without
leaving the house. So why can't you get
it when you want to actually try? It's
not fair, is it? Think about it like
that. Think about it that way, you know? So
that's how it is, bro.
What's I supposed to do, lad? Yeah.
Look stuck up. Like look at this, bro.
There's this woman on Reddit. Yeah, I'll
show you her. Yeah.
Just look stuck up. Like I don't know if
it's me. Yeah. like it was just me or
whatever. But don't they just [ __ ]
look so stuck up?
I forgot where you live, but bro, you
could just see it in their eyes.
They just look stuck up. That western
look they give you. That westernized
look they get. You know what I mean? Nice. Yeah.
Yeah. They just look stuck up.
I swear to God they just you could just
see the westernity in their eyes like
what Ant-Man says. Like look at my eyes. Yeah,
my eyes are like normal.
Look at my eyes. Yeah, they're like see
how my eyes are like cute.
Their eyes is just like [ __ ] devil,
man. You know?
Yeah, bro. I need to wash off my hair and [ __ ]
See, my beard grows back so quickly. Yeah.
Yeah. Did you watch my video? I don't
think anyone can disagree with that video, man.
I don't know what the solution is. I
don't know what you could actually do. I don't know.
Um, I won't be going out for a very long
time. Well, my birthday, but I might
even try and get out of going out on my
birthday to be honest. I probably I
might just just go to a restaurant or something.
I've got some Stonies. I got a Ralph Ren
top. But yeah, I don't know. I said to
my sister I was going to go out. So, I
feel like I kind of have to go out.
Either way, I'm doing something on my
birthday. Like, I'm not staying in on my
birthday. Like, you can't stay. Well, I say
on my birthday. I mean,
my birthday's on a Monday, but I'm going
to go out on a Saturday. I'm still
probably going to do something. I don't
know what to do on a Monday. I don't know. [Music] Don't know.
What can you do on a [ __ ] Monday?
There's nothing you can really do on a
Monday, is there?
That's why I'm going out the Saturday
because you can't you drinking on a Monday.
You're going out tonight. Oh, casino.
What? You got money to go casino?
Thought you didn't have any money.
Thought you didn't have any money, matey.
Yeah, I used to love going casinos
when I was rich.
Nah, bro. But
I don't gamble really anymore.
Oh, yeah. But I'm not Do you know what?
Funny enough. Yeah. I remember the last
time uh I remember the last time I went out. Yeah.
Uh, no, no. On my birthday, I actually
did gamble last year. I put money on 25
and I won. Yeah, I won money on 25 and I
won. Bro, do you remember? You'll be my
25th. USA is he? So, I put I think I put
£8 on 25 and it hit. But I didn't go
out. I went out the night before because
I was too [ __ ] I couldn't even go
out. I I'm sure I didn't go out. No, cuz
I went out the night before and I was
too hung over. So, I couldn't even go
out again. Yeah, I do remember that.
Yeah, I do remember that. Yeah, I do
remember that cuz last my last Yeah.
Yeah, cuz the last year's birthday was
Sunday and I went out the Saturday.
Yeah, I remember getting [ __ ] wrecked
on the Saturday and then getting a
roasted on a Sunday. I gambled on a
Sunday, won some money and yeah, just um didn't um
just didn't bother going out on the
Sunday cuz I went out on the Saturday. So yeah. Yeah,
you got a grand
Grezy's got a couple of bob
under his um
under his bed,
don't you, Grezy?
Oh, I have to approach every time I go
out. Why am I going to go out and waste
money if I'm not going to approach? Of
course I have to. I mean, going out
generally, no. But I mean, every time I
go out drinking, of course I'm going to approach.
Why wouldn't I?
What? For a month? You got to live of it
for what? A month?
So what? You're not going to be going out drinking?
Yeah, that's what I mean. Like if I got
one of my benefit payments, which is
like £700, I would be [ __ ] If I only
had £700, I wouldn't be able to go out drinking
because one weekend could potentially
ruin it. So I mean, I wouldn't be able
to. So what you would you feel
comfortable going out drinking though
with £1,000 in your account?
I still need to build my money up. I
need to try and recoup some of the losses.
But would you be all right though?
Would you be all right with a grand in your account?
Like is that enough for you or
No, I'm saying if you didn't pre-drink,
would it be enough? Yeah,
I got that 2K. Hopefully that lasts a month.
Two grand should last a month, shouldn't it, Bob?
Well, I get two grand. I have two grand,
but I get like
I get 80 every week as well until my
next payment. So, I'm sure
sure that will that would last two grand.
But I'm still not going to go out. I've
got like gums as well, but I've got some
really nice gums to wear as well that I
got from the dry cleaners. But I'm not
I'm not going out. Simple.
I am not going out. No way.
Why are the [ __ ] Reddit mod so power hungry?
Reddit mod so power hungry. Bob,
they're literally so [ __ ] power hungry.
Have you noticed that? I'm greasy.
They ban people for no reason. Yeah, man.
Aren't you trying to like [ __ ]
Aren't you trying to save money?
Aren't you trying to save money to do anything, Bob?
See, I could go out every week drinking
if I wanted to.
Once you've got your haircut, right,
even if you didn't pre-drink, say you
got your haircut, even if you didn't
pre-drink, you're spending what, £100 a
week, you could easily go out.
Bomb doesn't know anything. He doesn't
know how much money people have and what
they don't have. I could also make money
if I wanted to, but I'm lazy. So,
it's the haircut that's a real expense.
And then once you've got that out of the
way, you're good for a month. So
you could spend and if you pre-drunk,
you could probably spend about 4050.
But even if you didn't pre-drink and you
just drunk like
beers, like it's like£3 a beer. So,
it's just scary every time you go out, isn't it?
I'm just so happy that I have money left, bro.
I'm just so happy, you know?
Nothing to worry about money. [ __ ] that.
still nowhere where I'm still nowhere
near where I need to be, but
just not it's just nice not having to
worry about money.
Hate that feeling, bro.
So, I must be the only person that's
gambled that's not gave the money back.
Huh? Isn't that a thing? Hey, Bob.
Check these [ __ ] power hungry mods.
Well, I'll be back later.