Oh,
[ __ ] hell. Yeah, I said to Monty,
I'll come to Birmingham, but he's
talking about [ __ ] slapping people and [ __ ]
That emotion was spicy. Very spicy. Yeah,
that was very spicy.
What I want to know is why does Reddit
dismiss my struggles?
Um, this is why I don't feel like
there's no point ever talking to anyone
ever again because they just dismiss your struggles.
No, I got a tandoori chicken. I can't
really have any hot stuff at the minute
cuz my tongue feels a bit sensitive.
So, I just got a tandoori chicken. I
feel like there's just no point, is there?
cuz they literally just dismiss your struggles.
Literally what they they do. Why do they
dismiss my struggles?
Is it cuz I'm a man and not a woman? I
don't know why they do that. Why do they
keep dismissing my struggles?
They don't seem to have too much to say
about the matter, you know.
I said I was going to go out today and I didn't bother.
I just want to know why people on Reddit
dismiss my struggles. I'm going to ask
Joe when he comes.
Just been off YouTube. I can't be
bothered with it. I'll be I'll be off it again tomorrow.
I can't be asked for this [ __ ] bro.
It's [ __ ] bollocks.
It doesn't matter what I want cuz I'm
not going to get it. So, there's no
point asking what you want cuz you're
not going to get it.
So, does it really matter what you want?
Because either one you're not going to get.
I want to know why these people keep
dismissing my struggles.
I want to know why people keep
dismissing my struggles. Bro,
I was going to go out on a drink today,
Steven Howard, but then I went against it cuz
I realized how bad my experiences are
and then I don't want to put myself
through anymore [ __ ]
That's how bad it is now, bro. That's
the how bad it's actually got. I don't
even want to go out anymore. Like, in
that way, it's, you know,
I was on Reddit and somebody was trying
to say, "Oh, you're too old for me."
What a 28-year-old's too old for a 23 year old.
Same old, never changes. Boring.
It's so [ __ ] boring. Same old, same
old, same old, you know? Never changes here.
I can't be asked with it anymore, bro.
But like I said, I will be out next week
cuz it's my birthday. So,
I feel like I'll only be drinking now on special occasions.
I think the only reason I used to go out
drinking is to try to meet women. And
now I know it's impossible and it will never change.
I just don't. No, but I did used to like
going out as well, but I don't know why
I don't as much now.
It's got money. I've got money to go
out. Not a problem.
Maybe just cuz I'm older and I feel like
you're not going to meet a woman
anyways. So if you're going to go out,
if you're not going to go out, you're
just going to drink in your house. And I
wouldn't drink in my house. So
it's really really bad.
Yeah, I said to Monty, I'll come
Birmingham. He says, "Oh, I'll slap you
in that." So, it's no point me going there.
I bet it's good today as well.
Birmingham on a Thursday.
Bet Thursdays are decent. Bet you it is.
I mean, it's the second biggest city. So,
so I bet I bet it would be decent.
He said if I go there, he's going to
slap me. So, I can't be [ __ ]
bothered, bro. I'm not going.
And it's so cold outside. I'd rather
just chill indoors.
Just chill indoors, man. It's nice.
It's nice indoors. What do you need to
go out for, man? What do you need to go
out for? Huh?
I love October. My favorite month.
What's your favorite month? So yeah. [Music]
Yeah, it's always going to be the same.
Yeah, I saw it. I saw it.
Michael's like, "Oh, if you want
trouble, come around the corner." I
would have went around the corner. Me?
I don't like that Michael, bro. He's a
little snake. I've seen what he does.
He's not He's not even bad compared to him.
Yeah. On YouTube again. I was off of
YouTube for over a week. You can't take
a day off of YouTube. Go self-rect
somewhere else. Oh, that's another
thing. Um, when I was subscribed to
people, I'd click on the live streams
occasionally and it would be exactly the
same people, which was all of the
evidence I needed to know that these
people ain't got a life on here. Like
Smokey B. Let's see that Smokey B for example, right?
Uh here's another one. He says that he's
got money. He says this, that and the
other that he's got money.
So why is he on YouTube all day every
day typing cuz mate, even if you've got
money, you ain't got anything going on
in your life if you're doing what you're
doing on here every day. It's obvious,
bro. People that have stuff going on in
their life do not spend all day on here.
You understand? It's so [ __ ] obvious.
Look at all of the people that's left
Ant-Man. I barely go on here anymore.
Um, and there's other people as well
that don't go on here, I'm sure. Anyone
that's got stuff going on in their life,
don't go on here.
It's obvious. It's Bro, trust me. And if
that Smokeoky B was here, I tell him the
same thing and I'd let him up because
what I'm saying is 100% the truth, you know,
cuz it's it's obvious, bro. It's so [ __ ] obvious.
Why would you want to be involved with
this toxic, stupid, negative place? I'm
on it now. Yeah, I haven't been on in
over a week. I'm just chilling, bro. But
I'm not going to be live tomorrow. It's
true, though. It is [ __ ] true. It
really, really is true. So,
but that's it, man.
Yeah. I said I was going to go out
today, Joker, but I didn't bother, bro.
I can't be annoyed with it. I can't be
annoyed with it anymore, bro.
Yeah, you might have money. Yeah, you
might have money assets, but you're not
on it all day, every day, are you?
Cuz I haven't seen you for a long time.
And there's a difference. People can
still come on here occasionally.
Now, I'm not saying you can't come on
here occasionally, bro. I could come on
here I could have a life and come on
here two hours, three hours a day.
You know it. There's What I'm trying to
say is these people spend all day every
day on here. Do you not understand? You
can come on here every day for like an
hour and two or two. Yeah.
But bro, what they do on here, it shows
that they don't have anything.
Do you understand?
So, I know you wanted to see some drunk
content today, but
One second, bro.
Yeah, people on Reddit, they really do
dismiss my struggles.
They don't seem to think that these
women are doing what they're doing on
purpose when they literally Oh, it's so
weird. I don't know why they dismiss
people's struggles. I don't know why
they do it.
Um, I don't know why they do it. I'd
love to know why they do it.
Like, I'm not even asked. Like I'm I'm
just curious as to why they dismiss people's struggles.
You know what I mean, bro?
What the [ __ ]
Yeah, Monty's not even that bad compared
to Money Mike. But I would have said to
Money Mike, "Come around the corner
then, little [ __ ] [ __ ] bro." I
would I would I would have said come
around the corner
if I like if it was me because obviously
the history that I've had I would have
said yeah come then
because of the history that I've got
with with him and that but Monty is not
even that bad compared to him.
Monty is just a bit of a snake
but at the same time I think he's just
so dumb he doesn't even realize he's
doing it to be fair.
And I've known money years as well.
But yeah, they they do definitely dismiss my struggles
and they seem to like nit they want to
like nitpick things that you've done but
not address what they've done. It's
proper [ __ ] up. So
women or [ __ ] that
yeah I was going to go out today Steven
for a piss up but can't be asked. I'd
rather just I might as well just save
myself to my birthday.
You get to save money
and I want to get my hair I'm going to
obviously get my haircut on my birthday
as well. So,
I'm not sure. No, I was going to go out,
but I can't be asked now.
No, I'll definitely go on my birthday.
Well, the 25th. My birthday is the 27th, so
might as well just save myself to my
birthday. And it makes more sense.
Just makes a lot more sense that way, ain't it? [Music] Yep.
I'm going to go out Friday. I'm going to
go out next Friday. So maybe the 24th.
There's no point me going out. Oh, [ __ ]
What month do you like better, September or October?
Yeah, I don't
I'm not going out, bro.
We're going out next Friday. I still
don't like Saturdays to be honest. I
still don't like Saturdays.
I wish he he needs to send me 50. I'm
[ __ ] poor, mate.
I'm [ __ ] poor, mate.
But all that hap all that would happen
today jokers is if I went out Yeah. is
all I'm going to get is I have a
boyfriend, I'm not interested.
Um and numbers that just lead your ass on.
You can't even meet somebody that
doesn't play games at 28 years of age.
It's a madness, isn't it? You would have
thought at 28 years of age you'd be able
to play. You'd actually be able to meet
somebody that does not play games. But
that just seems impossible. So
it's always games, mind games.
So it never change. Yeah. So
I won that £500 back that I spent
them three weeks ago and I kind of I
feel like that's God telling me
something, you know, bro.
I feel like that was God [ __ ]
Yeah, that's the problem. Too many
[ __ ] But Friday is still good. The
best is f Wednesday, Thursday, Friday.
I've met some of the best people on
Wednesdays. Yeah, too many [ __ ]
Yeah, too many [ __ ] on them. And
there's too many young people as well.
There's a lot of young people as well
on um Saturday.
So Thursdays are Wednesdays and
Thursdays are the best
really to go out drinking.
Um Tuesdays are [ __ ]
Yeah, Sunday is when I met that finish one.
But Fridays are still good, but just not
Saturdays. Yeah. So, I could go out
tomorrow if I wanted to, but I'd rather
just save myself.
Save myself for next week.
Yeah, I met some good people when I went
out on Wednesday. I remember that time
[ __ ] USA Izzy messaged me, pissed me
off on that Wednesday. It got me on the
drink and I met some people um on Wednesday.
Yeah, Wednesday's all good.
So sad days here
anyone would do.
This woman was trying to say she
wouldn't get with me because I'm not
Muslim and I'm too old for her. Even
though she's 23. Heard it all before,
mate. Heard it all before.
I [ __ ] heard it all before, mate.
Look. Oh, I was going to go like this.
Even though my beard's a bit, but it's
it's not that bad, my beard. I would
have just brushed it obviously.
Oh, [ __ ] I would
I would have just brushed it,
so it's not too bad.
Yeah, I had tandoori chicken.
So, obviously I would have went out
today like this and then got a haircut
for my birthday cuz but nah,
I'd rather just save myself, man.
No, it's not about lying. It's just an
excuse with them.
It will never change with any of these
women, bro. It's what it is, isn't it?
Like, come and see me.
Yeah, I know. It's just another excuse.
Muslim, you're too old for me. Like even
now, you could get with a 23 year old.
Oh, I had this stupid woman on Reddit.
She's like, "Oh, you approached somebody
that was 19." I didn't even realize they
were 19. And so what if they were
[ __ ] 19? She said, "Oh, stay away
from a woman that's 25 and below." I was
like, "Uh, what are you on about? You
could easily get with a 23 year old. You
can easily get with a 24 year old. I
don't need to get with a 25y old.
Why would I get Why does the person need
to be 25 and above?
23 is more than enough. What the [ __ ]
What's wrong with a 23 year old? What's
wrong with a 24 year old? Yeah.
No, it's just an excuse. Cuz remember
that one I was I met before? They was
like, "Oh, um
what did she say?" Um
she was like, "Oh, well yeah, only get
with you if you're Muslim." Then I said,
"Oh, I I can convert to Muslim."
Yeah. You can't even meet somebody that
doesn't play games at 20 [ __ ] 80
years of age. It's bad.
All they do is lead people on. It's like
when I went to Birmingham, right, when I
saw Monty a few months ago, all of them
free numbers led me on.
That's literally all that happens.
>> Yeah, man.
They like my cute little looks. They're
cute, aren't they?
They [ __ ] um all of them free numbers
led me on as well cuz I remember they all replied.
That's all that ever happens. You just
get led on. There's no point. It's just
games and leading on. That's literally
all it ever is. So yeah,
leading on on games,
that Muslim thing is an annoying excuse as well.
That is an annoying excuse. The age is
an annoying excuse. It's just the same
old [ __ ] right?
This will never change it, will it? Yep. So, yeah.
What's the chances that I'm going to go
out and meet somebody that's not all of these things?
Just Just think of it, bro. Just think
of the odds right now. Cuz I've never
done the lottery. Never have. Never will.
Think about it. Nope.
Not at all.
It's got to be like one in what? A
trillion. That you're going to meet a
woman that doesn't pretend she's got a
boyfriend, that doesn't say that she's
not interested, that gives you a number,
and doesn't play games.
Bro, I don't think it's going to happen.
I don't think you're going to meet
someone, bro. Like, all all of the odds
are the odds are severely severely
severely severely severely
severely stacked against you. So, like
it's But it's obvious, isn't it?
So obvious, man.
It's just games. All it is is games and
games and games and games and games with people.
It's mad, isn't it?
I looked smack three weeks ago as well.
Didn't seem to make much difference
regarding the success. So [ __ ] in it, bro.
I was still stalking me. Nah.
Oh, my buddy's not stalking me anymore.
I thought my pal Red Star would be stalking me.
He'll upload some stuff later.
Yeah, he's my stalker. Red Star is my
if you didn't know.
Why? What happened to him? Yeah. Really?
Look at my beard. Why is my beard like that?
[ __ ] hell, bro. So, I get my haircut
like every month now. Yeah, man. [Music] Yeah.
Nah, it's not about it being worse. It's
all It's all good, bro. It's just never
going to change with women. And I'm
under no illusion that it will
because it's [ __ ] so obvious.
Cuz think about this. Look at all of the
times you've tried and it's never
happened. So it's not going to happen
now. And there's been no buildups to
like anything as well. I've not even had
a date in God knows how long. So it's
very very unlikely that you're going to meet someone.
very very very very very unlikely
and I think that is the truth you know
I mean you can say never say never but
you can never say never that you're
going to win the lottery
so you know that's just the way it is that's it
strange yeah it's strange
I think it's cuz I don't look white.
That's what I think it is.
I think it's cuz I don't look fully white.
And obviously I'm not black, so I'm like
in the [ __ ] middle or some [ __ ] So
that's what I think it is.
Cuz it shouldn't be this hard to to to
find someone. You know what I'm saying?
Like when I So it shouldn't be that
hard, but it seems impossible. Sir, Yeah. Heat.
this woman is saying doesn't make any sense. Right?
This is what I'm saying about, you know,
them dismissing your struggles. If we go
back on it, [ __ ] I think with some of
them moving a little too fast.
Now, I showed her where literally one
didn't some didn't reply to the first
message, some agree to me, and where
some just literally disappeared.
So, what am I supposed to do? I don't
understand. Like, that no matter what
you do, you're wrong.
Which is the whole point of like it
being a it being a Mug's game.
So, like it's like they they see what
you show them, right?
and it doesn't suit them.
So, they think, well, let me inspect
this and let me nitpick and blame the
man. It generally generally generally
feels like that because there's there's
messages here where
they've just literally just disappeared
and some of them have actually agreed to
meet. So, it doesn't it doesn't suit
them. My experiences don't suit these people. you know.
No, I'm not going out tonight, bro.
There's no point.
I'm not making myself ill, bro. I'm all
good. I just want to know why people
dismiss my struggles and make up stuff.
No matter what you do, you're wrong. So,
is there a point in even saying anything
anymore? Because no matter what you do,
they're just going to they're just going
to make things up. So, is is there a
point even asking for advice anymore?
Because they're just going to keep
making stuff up. So, there's there's
literally no point
because what they're saying doesn't make
any sense because there's been people
that have agreed to me. There are some
people that have randomly disappeared.
So no matter what they say that it's
always going to that the excuses are
always going to come to an end. Um
and I don't want you to feel sorry for
me or to not I want you to be thrown
back by what you're shown cuz I would be
thrown back by what I'm shown. So
So it's just they never admit they're
wrong. Does that do you know what I
mean? Joker. They never ever admit they're wrong,
you know? And I'm not making myself ill,
bro. I'm completely calm. I'm just
stating facts that they just they just
they just dismiss your struggles.
And she said, "If you get offended, you
can just block me." I was like, "No, I'm
not going to block you. I want you to elaborate.
You know, if you're going to if you're
going to try and state facts, at least elaborate.
There's always going to be excuses with
these people. I need to stop going on
this [ __ ] bro.
Yeah. See, they're dismissing my struggles.
Yeah. See, they just dismiss your
struggles. Well, the ones that didn't
agree to me, I think it's best to leave
them alone out of respect as well. If
they were interested, they would re
recerate. Again, dismiss my struggles.
Don't you think it's better to just
focus on one girl though instead of
going out with multiple?
No thoughts on the ones that were
leading me on the ones that did agree.
See what I'm saying? They just they just
dismiss your struggles. So, anyone to
come on somewhere and ask for advice, it's completely
pointless because all they're going to
do is make stuff up. So, there's that's
literally all they're ever going to do.
They ignore the [ __ ] that they've done.
And she was like, "Oh, I'm not
dismissing it." Well, well, you are
because most of the messages, right? Hold on.
You're definitely dismissing it. Yeah,
he's definitely dismissing my struggles.
She was like the random disappearance,
etc. is a universal thing. Girls go
through it too, unfortunately. Uh, no
they don't. And even if they did,
they've got options.
Yeah, she's definitely definitely
definitely dismissing my struggles.
Definitely definitely. So, we've
established now there's no point even
asking anyone for [ __ ] advice anymore.
And then they say, "But eventually the
right person will reciprocate." It's
been going on for years.
It's been going on for years. So, so
she just basically So, yeah, there's no
point even asking for any advice from
anyone because they're just going to
dismiss everything that you show them. So, pointless.
How about they just they don't
acknowledge any of it. Do you
understand, Joker? They don't
acknowledge any of it. It say
I might have to do a video on this, bro.
And the videos that I put up now, I
think I'm just going to leave up
cuz it's always excuses with these
people. Like, I don't I don't understand
what the [ __ ] bro. Like, you know what I mean?
clearly clearly leading you on. Like
there's no two ways about that, you know.
You know, they're they're clearly
clearly leading you on.
You know, it doesn't matter if women do
it if guys do it to other women. We're
not talking about other women. We're
talking about me and what I'm showing you.
So stick to the subject. We're not
talking about other people. We're
talking about So yeah, they do they
definitely definitely do dismiss my struggles.
They only acknowledge the things that suit themselves, you know.
and like do a video on this.
Why people keep dismissing my struggles.
That's why I don't have a debate anymore
with like my mom or anything because
there's no point because they're just
going to ignore anything that you say.
It's like you're talking to a brick
wall. Anything you say just gets thrown
in the dust bin. So there's no point
even. It's like going to court with no
defense. It's pointless, you know.
Acknowledge it. That's what I want them
to So, I want them to acknowledge it.
So, they just make up stuff. That's all
they do. I was having this argument with
my mom the other day and she was like,
"Oh, you're anti-woman." And I'd explain
like, "I've had bad experiences. I put
myself out there. Every single woman
that you meet is the same. And no matter
how many times I would say it, it
doesn't seem to register in people's
brain. And then what happens is you're
just wasting your time and you're
wasting their time because
they're always just going to
continuously make stuff up and it
becomes tiring after a while. you know,
it becomes really, really, really tiring
because they have it in their world as
women do nothing wrong. They're all
perfect. So, leave them to it. So, if
someone's got their opinion and you've
got your experiences, just leave it, bro. It
just annoying as [ __ ]
Yeah. Still telling me I'm going to meet someone.
Oh, [ __ ] me.
Still telling me I'm going to meet someone.
These people must be delusional. Delusional, bro.
same [ __ ] advice that they seem to
[ __ ] give. Bro, if I do this video,
you best [ __ ]
then they're telling people to work on
themselves. Same old [ __ ] They just say
the same old thing.
I don't understand why they do this, bro.
same argument. I'll be having the same
argument, bro, until I'm [ __ ] until
I'm like 35, 36.
It's just the same [ __ ] argument. I
said this the other day, bro. It's
literally just the same argument.
and she was like, "Oh, trust me. I've
had bad experiences with my with men."
And I was like, "Trust me, you haven't
right. You haven't gone out and got 10
numbers and not got a date. So, stop
talking [ __ ] [ __ ] stick to the
subject and stop trying to change the
subject. This is what I don't understand
with these people.
They seem to dismiss every bad thing
that they do. I'm going I'm going to do
a video talking about this, bro. I feel
like I really really need to do a video
talking about this. You know,
[ __ ] madness, bro. What the [ __ ]
Why do they just miss Peter Belly
struggles? It's so annoying.
And you do dismiss them because you
don't acknowledge them at all.
Like you you do dismiss them because you
don't point anything out. You make up
excuses. Oh, you've tried to meet them
too fast. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Can't you just acknowledge what they do
is [ __ ] up. Like that's that's all
we're asking you to do. Oh yeah.
Yeah, it just goes round and round and
round in circles.
You just go round and round and round
and round in circles because whatever
you say doesn't register in people's
head. No, it's just a fight this boring argument. Oh yeah,
it does go. As soon as you ask for
advice, you just go around in circles because
they just miss everything that you show
them. They don't even acknowledge anything.
They make up excuses that,
you know, you're trying to meet people
too fast when we all know that if you
try to meet them any longer, oh, you
need to meet them faster. It's just no
matter what you do, you're wrong. So, I
don't understand the whole point of it
to be honest. Um
then they say that you're going to meet someone when
when you know it's ridiculous. It's just
so it just goes round and round and
round in circles. Same [ __ ]
goes round and round and round in circles, bro.
You haven't been led on. Oh my god. Shut
the [ __ ] up. It's the same argument
over and over and over and over again. So annoying.
It's annoying as [ __ ]
They just anything you do is like opposites. So
saying doesn't make any sense because
you're saying that you struggled with men.
You can't get a man. No, no, no, no, no,
no. Yeah. The the the the sole reason
for you not getting with me is because
I'm 28 and you're 23. Do you not see the
hypocrit to see in that?
hypotic and that you're saying that
you're struggling and you can't find
someone and that you have been led on
very very rare but you're not going to
get with somebody because they're 5
years older than you.
Make it make [ __ ] sense,
you know? So, there's a big difference. Yeah.
So, see this this is what doesn't make
any sense about it is that they moan
even though that they've got options
when and they then they try to care
compare people they they try to compare
themselves with people that don't have
options and then they think it's the same
So then stop moaning then. Stop moaning
and winging. Simple. Like I don't want
to hear your moaning and [ __ ] winging then.
So that's it.
[ __ ] madness, bro.
So they're they're trying to compare
they're trying to compare your their
experiences to yours when they literally
don't have to try. Okay, let me put this into Yeah,
it's ridiculous, bro.
Trying to say that she only goes with Muslims.
So, you're picky. You've got
insane standards, yet you're moaning. Do
you not see that? Do you not see the
hypocrisy in that?
Do you not understand? Like you're moaning
when you don't have to try and you have
got insane standards.
It's not even comparable in the slightest.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
No, I'm just on Reddit.
Like I said, the more I think about it,
the more it just puts you off trying.
See, like I said, you get to a a certain
point where you lose hope. And that's
where I'm already at, which is why
obviously I didn't go out today. So,
and then she tries to say about how, oh,
women get led on when that's not what
we're talking about. Stick to the
subject. If you're saying you're going
to sit there and [ __ ] give someone advice,
That's what I mean, bro.
That's why I didn't waste my time today.
So like Yeah.
We cuz it's my [ __ ] birthday,
Otherwise, I wouldn't be bothering,
you know. Swear to God.
[ __ ] depressing as [ __ ]
[ __ ] depressing as [ __ ] bro.
It's so boring. This is why I gave up,
Joker, bro. This is why I gave up.
cuz of this [ __ ] I couldn't be
dealing with it no [ __ ] more, bro.
You know what I'm saying?
This is the kind of [ __ ] that's not even
making me want to go out on my birthday.
Just like it didn't even want to because
it's just the same. It is the same thing
over and over and over again. And it
takes a lot for me to get bored, bro.
You understand? in it.
So yeah, trying to compare you
your situation to mine.
[ __ ] off, man. You know what I mean? [Music]
And they've got like unrealistic [ __ ]
standards as Oh, you know that's another thing. [Music]
And then they try to compare their
situation to yours.
That's the most insulting part about it, you know. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm going to do a video on this.
You better [ __ ] watch it. Another
video for edges.
for me [ __ ] advice when you're not in
the same [ __ ] situation as me and
like they don't acknowledge anything
I don't know why these people keep
dismissing my struggles. Maybe I'll
bring it on to this community. Maybe they'll um
maybe they will someone on this
community will be able to understand it
better than me because they do seriously
seem to dismiss this. They they they
pick out what suits themselves.
Um, and then and then they'll be like,
"Oh, well, what do you want?" Joe will
be like, "Oh, what do you want them to
say?" Uh, how about acknowledge it?
You know what I'm saying? How about
actually acknowledge what you're being shown?
So, yeah. But they can't
No, I am. Why am I not writing ahead
because I'm saying that these people
dismiss my struggles? Because they do
dismiss my struggles.
It's the truth. What am I am I lying
that they don't dismiss my struggles?
They 100% dismiss my struggles. 100% they do.
They don't they go on to they make they
they resort to making up stuff. So
they're clearly clearly dismissing my struggles.
So I I And the thing is I know I'm
right. Like I know what I'm saying is
right. Like it might sound delusional to
you, right? Because I'm not I'm not I'm
not right about everything, but I mean I
literally have showed my experiences and
it just continuously keeps getting
dismissed. It keeps being lost in transit.
And I'm going to touch on to the like
how like they say that eventually you're
going to meet someone and then I decided
okay well we'll meet in the middle t. It's
they're dismissing everything that
you're showing them
like time and time and time and time again.
Just the same just the same argument
over and over and over and over and over
again, you know. Yeah.
No. See, this is what I mean. My
experiences just get dismissed.
You're dismissing them right now by
saying, "Oh, I'm physically fine." No,
no, no, no. Any thoughts on the women
leading me on? Nope. That just gets lost
in transit. See, it just This is why
it's just a pointless argument. It's
point It's pointless even getting into a debate.
It's completely pointless even getting
into it cuz you've already lost before
you even started, you know?
So there's just no [ __ ] point even
getting into it.
They're always going to continuously
defend women. They're always
continuously going to dismiss your
struggles and that's that. I don't know
what more there is anyone can say about
this now. You know,
they don't even acknowledge the fact
that it's [ __ ] up, you know.
They seem to think it's normal, you
know, getting 10 numbers
um and not even getting a date. They
seem to think that's normal.
Like when it's there's nothing normal about that,
you know, and you can't compare that to
how you you know,
and then you're moaning about guys
leading you on when I've just said, "Oh,
let's go on a date." But you won't do it
because I'm 5 years older than you.
So, make it make sense. Please stop
mocking the average guy. It's mocking at
this point. All of these women that say
that they're struggling, they're
literally just mocking men that actually
struggle. I'm going to talk about this
all on a video.
I mean, think about it, bro. Really,
really, really think about it.
You've got unrealistic standards to
begin with, and you're trying to compare
yourself to me. No,
doesn't make sense.
So yeah, I'm going to do a video about
this, bro. I'm going to do a video about
this. Do you like my little videos? Yeah,
people like my little dating videos.
And the thing is, I'm not bitter about
it. I'm just saying it how it is.
Like, I I've accepted it, bro. It's
never going to change. But I think it's
just a funny thing to talk about, you know?
I don't know why they seem to dismiss my struggles.
I don't know why it doesn't suit them, you know.
They go on and talk about something
completely different. Oh, you're trying
to meet them too fast
when it doesn't make sense because
there's ones where they haven't even
replied to the first message or they've
agreed to meet and they haven't. So,
and that's that's what it is. They they
don't acknowledge the wrongdoings that they do.
That's the thing. That's the That's what
the problem is.
And then you got Laney trying to say
that all women aren't the same when
well they clearly clearly clearly are
when every single woman that you meet
seems to do exactly the same thing. Lead
your ass on
but they're all different.
So they say they say that they're all
different but every single one you will
come across will do exactly the same thing.
Like but they're not all the same. They
swear by it that they're not all the
same, but in their messages, it shows
that they really are all the same, even
though they just ignore the fact because
it doesn't suit them. So, I don't know,
bro. I don't know.
It's weird. Very weird. Yeah,
they are such liars.
That's what they are. They're liars.
Oh, look. She says that my age is a
problem. Yeah. When you go on her
Reddit, it said he is 28 male and I am a
23 year old female, which you said to
begin with that my age was the problem.
Yet, here you are. Here it says here
that you would not go with somebody cuz
it's a preference. a barefaced [ __ ]
liar just like all of these other
[ __ ] women. So there we go.
Lies, lies, lies, lies, lies, lies, [ __ ] lies.
There we go. You just call out to be a liar.
You [ __ ] liar.
I just caught her to be a barefaced liar. See,
but I bet you'd be called all the names
under the sun. um when uh you know you'd
be called all the names under the sun if
you was to say that trying to use age as
an excuse because people don't fit your
unrealistic standards. [ __ ] it. I'm
going to do a video on this. [ __ ] it.
You know why not? We ain't done a video in ages. Yeah.
Because somebody doesn't look young.
Because somebody has a [ __ ] beard.
Right. And and and also another thing is yeah, you know,
it's madness. It is it is it is [ __ ]
madness. This is, bro. Seriously,
[ __ ] barefaced liar. If you had a
preference, that is very narcissistic.
That is a trait of narcissism. that is
trying to use a it is it it it it
bro it's like it's like traits of narcissism
because it doesn't want to make them
seem like they've got these unrealistic
insane standards. Um
unrealistic standards rather. So that's
why they say, "Oh, you're too old." When
that's [ __ ] weird. So they're
barefaced [ __ ] liars, which is why
they they defend each other because they're liars.
Yeah, there we go.
They're [ __ ] liars. What? because I
don't look [ __ ] young. Because at the
end of the day, we can all agree
objectively that in that video, there's
nothing wrong with me. I'm not ugly in
that looks m. So, you're going to sit
there and try complaining about [ __ ]
men. Get get [ __ ] real, man.
Seriously, get real.
You know, they have got unrealistic,
insane standards, which is why you've
never been in a [ __ ] relationship
since you're [ __ ] moaning and [ __ ]
complaining, bro. Do you know what?
Yeah, this just puts me off even wanting
to go out on my birthday now. I'm not
even going to lie to you, bro. I might
just go for a meal cuz I am not putting
up with this
[ __ ] anymore. I'm not doing it, bro. I'm
not putting up with this [ __ ] the
[ __ ] the lies, the le I am not
prepared to deal with this anymore, you
know. I'm sorry. Like, all jokes aside,
like I'm not moaning, bro. I'm just saying
that in itself.
So, it is it is kind of like it is a
form of narcissism. So yeah.
So yeah, I'm going to I'm going to do a
video addressing this. This needs to be
this needs to be addressed.
And also, it was a video where I was
objectively above average looking as
well. So that's what she's basically
seeing as me. And then you're trying to
use my age as an excuse. And then you're
trying to then so what anyone that does
not fit into your unrealistic standards
is too old for you. Like what the [ __ ]
Like you even got older women doing it
nowadays. Oh, you're too young for me
and they're not even as good-looking as
you. What the [ __ ]
Wouldn't you just say that
you're not my type because you look too
old or something? and you know, but they
don't want to do that because it's a
form of narcissism
because then it it's kind of like it's
making them look bad. So, in their head,
if they can blame age, right, then it's
their way of sort of getting out of it.
It's all narcissism in a way. If you
think about it, bro, it's got to be some
trait of narcissism when it doesn't seem
[ __ ] right. You know what I mean? So,
and I I refuse to and I'll tell the
story as well. I don't mind telling the
story, you know, about the 10 numbers
and whatever and um stuff,
which is basically why I've not been on
YouTube as well. So, you know, it's not
a problem, man. I talk about all of it.
It's just full of lies. And the maddest
thing is is I'm not even ugly. Like this
is this is the maddest thing about it. I
look [ __ ] normal. Like I just look
like a normal person when I go to the
barbers despite what all of these people
on YouTube want to say, want to troll
and stuff. Like I'm I literally
look completely [ __ ] normal. Could we
could we meet in the middle and say
that? I think we can, you know. So
does that not mean you have got some
sort of unrealistic standards?
You know what I'm saying? Clearly, bro.
Shut up. You're full of [ __ ] Shut up.
That's what I said. You've just been
caught out to be a [ __ ] liar. You
know what I'm saying? So that's it, man.
See, you know, the the maddest thing
about this is Yeah. I I could understand
this, right? If you was like fat and
ugly and like you didn't work on
yourself and it was like something you
could change and then people are just
[ __ ] talking [ __ ] But bro, like
I'm not even any of them things. And
then you've got this person saying that
you're too old for them because you're
[ __ ] 5 years older than them.
You know what I'm saying? right?
Yeah, I I can't deal with this, bro. Seriously,
when I if I do this video, are you going
to um uh are you going to actually go on
my video and watch it? Are you going to
watch it? Yeah.
So, I'm I'm turning I've basically just
said to her, not that I'm interested
her, but for argument sake, I'm asking, "So,
who's all the same women?" "Yeah, of
course they're all the same. They do the
same stuff. They say the same stuff."
So, I've said specifically for feedback,
even though I don't even know this
person, "What's the problem with me?
What's the problem with what I look
like?" And she can't answer it
because we know that I'm not ugly.
So, what's the problem with me? Let's
hear it out of curiosity for the lads, you know,
to be honest with you, bro.
Just for the lows. And they can't answer
it. So, what? You've got unrealistic
standards. Oh, and you're also talking
about guys asking you out now. See, I've
never been asked out. So,
the more and more deeper you get into
this, the more and more and more you
just don't want to try anymore.
You know, the worse and worse and worse
it gets because you do know that like
everyone you go out and meet, they're
just going to be the same.
So, it's [ __ ] madness. So yeah,
but yeah, that's that's where we're at.
I could understand. Yeah, if you was
fat, ugly, broke, like all of these
things, then I could actually understand
it a little bit more,
but there's nothing. So,
why wouldn't you want to get with a
28-year-old? I'm still 27 technically,
but it just doesn't make any sense. And
you don't seem to think that you've got unrealistic expectations.
You know, you might want to actually
give your [ __ ] head a wobble.
and saying about how people are Muslim.
Nope, I'm not becoming fat. Not in the
slightest. So then you're and then
you're hearing about these excuses. And
to be honest with you,
we're talking about at least 6 months,
bro, before trying again.
Like really, really. And no, I'm not
becoming fat. We're talking really about
six months, man.
I think about six months. Um,
no, I'm not becoming fat either. So,
and I thought, okay, we'll be fair about this. So, yeah,
I just hate the lies and the [ __ ]
And you know, I've I've I've kind of
accepted the fact that h it's always
going to be this way, ain't it? Yeah, man.
Nope. I'm not getting fat.
Oh, there we go. Then the person blocked me.
So, what was the point of all of that?
Using age as an excuse and any anyone
would think, right, that you're just fat
ugly guy with no hair. Like generally,
bro, the way these women go on, right,
it's it's it's it's [ __ ]
I might even send this video to [ __ ] London Taylor.
Um, you know, you didn't say you prefer
this kind of guy or prefer that kind of
t. You use my age as an excuse when I'm
probably better looking than you are.
Like we're just using this as an example
even though hypothetically this is
probably never going to happen. You understand?
And then you claim I'm I'm stalking your
profile because I went down your profile
and realized that you was just full of [ __ ]
You know it's madness. They have got
unrealistic standards which is part of
the reason why you haven't been in a relationship.
Difference. You are not in a
relationship because you've got
unrealistic standards. Men don't get in
men that haven't been in relationships
is because they can't find anyone. The
ones that haven't. Do you understand? So
it's a madness.
It really really really really is a madness, bro.
They have got unrealistic standards.
Seems that no one will [ __ ] do with these people. It's mad.
already been proven to be a liar just
like they're all liars. So yeah, madness.
You know, you know what I'm saying is
right, is it Steven Howard? You do
realize what I'm saying is right.
Listen, Joker. This woman just said that
she doesn't go for people that are my
age, which is 28. Then I went on her
profile and it says that she was trying
with some guy that was 28. And I
thought, "Oh, I thought you don't go
with people that are." So again, they do
a lot of similar things for people that
are all different apparently. So strange.
No, I am [ __ ] right. I am [ __ ]
right because I called her out being a liar.
So I am [ __ ] right because that's the
age that I am. You said that you don't
go. You said that I'm too old for you.
They do and say exactly the same thing
for people that are all apparently different.
I'm Muslim. I can't. It's the same
thing. Isn't it? What's the chances,
bro? that you meet people that do
exactly the same [ __ ] thing that are
all apparently different.
Come on, bro. Like, everyone is We have
got all our We We can put our opinions
out here. No one gets blocked, you know?
I'm I'm ready, bro. Like, I'm ready for
a whole debate on this. No one's getting
blocked. No one's getting anything. No
one's getting nothing.
What is it with these narcissistic
excuses over and over and over and over
again? Why do they all do and say
exactly the same thing for people that
are not all the same? I just want to
know this, bro.
Like actions. I'm going to do a video on
this. [ __ ] it. I'm going to save my time
and I'm going to do a video on this. And
after I do a video, I'm not going to
talk about it anymore.
And apparently I'm stalking your
profile. What? Cuz I read a I took a
look on your Reddit. That is so very public. So yeah.
And then there's that Muslim excuse.
I've heard that one. It seems they come
out with so many similar excuses. Muslims age
stuff. They do a lot of things that are
they do a lot of see the thing is cuz
with me, right, if somebody was the same
as me, I'd be concerned.
You understand? If I I'm a man, right?
And if somebody was the same as me,
I would be very very very very very concerned.
Do you understand?
I'd be very concerned. Let alone if I
met so many other people that were
exactly the same as me. I'd be very,
very concerned. Do you not find it
strange that these women have got
exactly the same excuses? That every
excuse they come out with is exactly the
same. They do exactly the same stuff for
people that are apparently all
different. Do you not see it as weird?
But apparently they're not all the same.
Do you not think it's weird, bro?
Oh man. So yeah,
it's a madness. So yeah,
it is strange bro. Very strange.
Everyone keep dismissing my [ __ ] struggles.
Everyone just dismisses my struggles.
Is there even a point of me even saying anything? Yeah, man.
Okay. Whatever you say, bro. I'm not
even going to react to that, man. You
can carry on being a white knight all
your life. See where that gets you. I'm not interested.
You could, bro. Calling someone an
insult is the same as calling a woman a
[ __ ] It has no substance.
It really, really, really has no
substance. It's just boring now, bro.
It's like calling a woman a [ __ ] It's
so overused that it's just boring now.
Like, no one even takes it seriously.
We just Well, same [ __ ] bro. It's not even effective.
That's cool, man.
Oh, [ __ ] Yeah, bro. Like, it doesn't
doesn't mean anything you using that word.
I see that word used so many times.
Yeah. An instant murder. Yeah, we've
heard it before, bro. Yeah. You're going
to go around killing people. Yeah, we've
heard it all before.
We've heard it all before, bro.
It's boring now.
White nighting will never get you laid.
Remember that quote of Peter Belly?
It will never get you laid, bro. Trust
me. Don't even So yeah.
No, it's just boring. We've heard it a
million times, bro. We've heard it a
million times. You're an incel. I don't
know. We've heard it before. Try and
call somebody a word that's not so
overused and we might actually be able
to take you seriously.
I can't honestly believe all women are
the same. Um,
I don't know, man. They do a lot of the same stuff.
They say a lot of the same stuff for
people that are all apparently
different. I don't know, man. They do a
lot of the same. They have a lot of
similarities even when they're not even
talking to me. I mean,
I don't know, man. I'd like to not
believe it, but they do a lot of the
same stuff. And I'm not getting into
this debate. There's no point me even
having this debate.
I mean, they say the same stuff, they do
the same stuff, but they're all
apparently different. Makes you wonder, doesn't it?
And I'm not getting into this argument
with you as well because there's no
point getting into an argument with it,
which is what what I'm going to discuss
on the video later. There's no point
even getting into it. No sh
I do a lot of the same stuff to you.
Anyways, moving on. I'm not getting into
this argument anyways. It's boring. I'm
not having debates about this. So,
anyways, moving on. We're not having this conversation.
I'm doing a video um later about this.
Anyways, I might bring up my mom as well
um cuz I think that's interesting. And I
am meeting these people in the middle as
well. I am I am meeting these people in
the middle. So
no. Uh what the [ __ ]
Yeah, that's definitely bomb.
Okay, bro. I'm not going to have this conversation.
I'm not having this argument. So, you're
wasting your time.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Whatever. I'm not
having this conversation with you.
I'm going to do a video later. If you
want to watch the video later, you can
watch it. I'm not getting into any
debates because there's no point when
you're just going to dismiss someone's struggles.
That's all that ever happens. There's
literally no point because whatever
someone shows you, you're just going to
dismiss. There's it's a waste of both of
our time. So, it's ridiculous. So, it's
and for the record, I've been with more
than 40 women, but I'm not going to say
anything about that because it's just a pointless debate.
I feel like with this thing, people just
should just say anything, you know?
Um, yeah, I've been with more than 40 women, bro.
But I want to say what I want to say,
but I'm not going to say it, bro. What's
the point? Two people argue, no one's
going to agree, and it just goes around in circles.
I learned that with [ __ ] Reddit as
well. So what's the [ __ ] point?
So because at the end of the day, let me
I'll just leave you at I'll just leave
you with it with this. The only ones
that can prove that they're different is
them. Not you, not me, not [ __ ] King
the dog. The only ones that can prove
that they're not all the same are them.
And they can't. So, at the end of the
day, it's it's ridiculous what I say,
what you say, because it's down to them
to prove that they're different to me.
Just look like if I was to believe in
God, right? If I was to believe in God,
I would want some sort of evidence,
which is why I've never believed in God.
So if they can't show me they're
different, I'm not going to believe it
and I'd have no reason to believe it.
So that's the way I see it.
let me tell you how bad this is, right?
If I went out today like I was planning
to go out, I could tell you exactly what
would happen. I could bet you two grand
right now cash exactly what would happen.
I could tell you exactly what would
happen. I'd get told I have a boyfriend.
I'm not interested. Um
I I I I'm not interested. I believe in
God. Uh sorry, I'm not interested. I've
got a boyfriend and I'm going to get
numbers that lead me on.
That is literally all that would happen.
And I'd be willing to bet a couple
thousand pound cash on that right now
and make myself
uh if there was a bet market in the
bookies with this, I'd be rich. Put it
that way. Cuz I' I'd know all of these
things. I'm the expert, you know.
So I I understand your point, but my
point is, okay, let me give you an
example. You might have not heard this
earlier. I was supposed to meet somebody
last Saturday. They agreed to meet. They
asked me where they wanted to meet. I
said, "Okay, let's go to Liverpool
Street. Let's meet up." They then went quiet.
So, I mean, yeah, and I'm going to bring
all of this up as well cuz that needs to
also be addressed. So, they said, "Oh,
where do you want to meet Saturday?" I
said, "Oh, we'll meet." And then they come back
uh a day before trying to say that they
can't meet because they're sick.
when we agreed this on the Wednesday, a
few days would have been the Tuesday.
So, it's always going to be mind games
with these women that are apparently
different. Um, and that's it. So, yeah.
conversation that I had with my mom as
well. I know, Bubble. Guess what? Yeah,
I was on Reddit, right? And this woman
said that she can't get in a
relationship. She's never been in a
relationship. I said, "Oh, why don't you
get with me?" Hypothetically, obviously,
it's never going to happen. Don't even
know what she looks like. So,
hypothetically, I was like, "Oh, why
don't you get with me?" "Oh, you're too
old for me." Oh, we've heard that one
before. How many times have you heard
that one? 23, 28. Well, I'm 27 still.
So, let's just say 23, 28. Yeah. Which
is a 5 year age gap. Oh, no, you're too
old for me. Even though there's nothing
wrong with the way that I look, I look
smack in that video where they saw me.
And then there, oh no, I don't get with
anyone that age. And then I was
scrolling through their profile and then
it's like, "Oh yeah, I'm I'm trying with
this guy that's 28." And then I caught
her to be a liar. And then guess what
she done? She called me a stalker. Isn't
that very funny? A stalker. Which cuz
somebody went on something that you
posted so [ __ ] publicly. I'm also I'm
I'm apparently a stalker. Why? Cuz you
got caught to be a liar.
So the more you think about this stuff,
the more you realize, the more you just
don't want to try, you know. And it's
going to be very, very hard for me to
even go out on my birthday to be honest.
Bro, that in itself is like. Yeah. So
I'm a stalker cuz I caught you to be a
liar for something that you posted publicly.
And I said, why don't you say it here
and now? What's wrong with the way why
why would you get with me? What's wrong
with me? You know, let's hear it here
and now. Let's let let's get into it
right here, right now. I'm here, bro.
Come on. What's the problem? Wouldn't
have it just been better if you just
said, "Oh, I don't go with guys that
have got beards."
Instead of making up a [ __ ] to try
to v It's a way of trying to victimize
themselves. You don't understand how
this this narcissism works with these people.
I need to get out of my own head. Did
you just realize? Did you just listen to
what I just said to you?
Did you just listen to what I just said
to you? Again, you seem to dismiss it.
But the title of the video is going to
be why do people keep dismissing my struggles?
Cuz that's that is what this problem is.
It seems to be this this major major
major problem of people keep dismissing
things that they're being shown. And I'm
not sure why they're doing it.
So, you should go you should go with
someone and be like uh you should go
with someone on you you should say like
yeah you don't go with guys that have
got beards or you don't go with guys
that have got you know because I looks
Max there was nothing wrong with the way
that I looked this is a example of
someone's unrealistic standards
you know this is this is right this is
an example same thing with when they say
that we're not going get with you cuz
you're not Muslim. It is the same
[ __ ] thing, bro.
Why do you know what I'm saying?
It's madness treating people like
they're ugly when they when you're
probably better looking than [ __ ]
them. Like, get the [ __ ] real, bro.
You're probably better looking than them.
You know what I'm saying? And then
saying that I am a stalker.
Why? Because I've gone on one of your
posts that you've posted so very publicly
that you wanted the whole world to
[ __ ] see. Do you know what I'm saying?
That's an example of it, bro. That is an
example of it.
Anyways, I'm going to do this video soon. Anyways, So yeah,
I just want to know why at my age I've
not been proven wrong.
Why I've not already been proven wrong
to be honest at my age.
I would just love to know why I have not
been proven wrong.
If they're not all the same, I just
would like to know why I've not been proven wrong.
I would love to know.
I would just love to know why I've not
been proven wrong if all of these women
are apparently not the same. I was
speaking to my mom about this as well.
And then I got called a stalker for
going on what you post publicly.
I just wanted to see if he was lying or
telling the truth. I mean, you've put it
out there on the internet. See, they use
the stalking card when they're caught
out to be a liar.
They do a lot of the same [ __ ] things
for people that are all different,
don't they, Steven Howard? They do a lot
of the same things for people that are apparently different.
That must be
What do That must be insane.
They do a lot of the same stuff.
They [ __ ] do, mate.
They sure like to try to convince people
that they're all the same, don't they?
Age as an excuse, religion, you know,
but they're all different. And I'm not
even talking about the boyfriend [ __ ]
I'm talking about the [ __ ] they do when
they give their numbers. We're not even
just talking about the boyfriend [ __ ]
That's just one That's just one thing.
That's nasty relevant. We're talking
about the [ __ ] they actually do via text
and the lies and the [ __ ]
over and over and over and over and over again. Liars,
which I can understand if he was fat and
broke and [ __ ] you know what I'm
saying, and ugly and [ __ ] and people had
to work on themselves, then I'd actually
[ __ ] understand it.
But yeah, I'll do a video on this anyways.
Yeah. And I was saying to this woman as
well, she was like, "Oh, men ruined the
dating game." And I said, "No, simps and
white knights ruined the dating game."
And she said, "Oh, yeah. I met a Tinder
guy and I got raped and t I said, "Yeah,
but white knights and simps ruined the
dating game, inflating women's egos,
making them feel like they're better
than they actually are.
What the [ __ ] Like,
no. It's it's white knights and simps
that ruin the the dating game, making
women feel like they're better than they
are, which is why they act like [ __ ] You understand?
So, it wasn't women that got raped by
[ __ ] men. What the [ __ ] Yeah,
they're in clubs. They're everywhere, bro.
They're everywhere, man.
She said that she got [ __ ] raped or some [ __ ]
And I said, "Yeah,
but the thing is, you shouldn't have any
sympathy for these women because when
they get chances to meet normal, nice
people, they're not interested. So don't
don't give them sympathy. They they they
don't deserve no sympathy for not being
able to find anyone or meeting people
that hit them because they choose these
kind of people. They go with these kind
of people. You understand?
Like they they they choose these kinds
of people. They want these kind of
people that beat them and cheat on them
and det. We've seen it all before.
You know what I mean, bro? We've seen it
all before, man. So yeah,
I'm in the minority with this problem.
Am I really?
I don't think so. I think I'm not just
scared to say what I think.
No, I never said they chose to get
raped. We're not talking about raped.
We're talking about these women that go
with these men that abuse them and cheat
on them and t
and I'm not in a minority with this
problem. There's loads of people that
are worse than me. They just don't say
anything. Just because you see couples
that I've met years ago or maybe met at
work or they somehow found somebody out
there that was different, that does not
mean that I'm in this minority. People
just don't say anything about it.
And I accepted it as well. To be fair,
I'm not even moaning. It's just about
the Reddit thing. I knew after getting
them 10 numbers and not getting a date
that it's never going to change. So, in
a way, it was a good thing that it
happened. But, it's just this Reddit
thing kind of annoyed me.
And it does annoy me when they try to
mock men as well by saying that they
can't find anyone yet. Any normal nice
person that they come across, they're
not going to be interested in them.
Yeah. She said she got raped, but and
she thinks because of that that's what's
ruined the dating game. Okay, bro. I'm delusional. Whatever.
Yeah, whatever, bro. I'm delusional.
Like I said, I've got my experiences
which don't suit you. So, where's this
where's this conversation going? Where's
this argument going?
I've got approaching videos that are
normal. I've got text messages that are
normal. I had a I had somebody agree to
meet me on Saturday and they asked me
where do they want to meet and I I said
let's meet this place and they didn't
show up. Okay, bro. I'm delusional.
Whatever you think. I'm not I'm not asked.
You know, I'm delusional, bro. Whatever.
You keep you keep telling yourself that.
So, yeah. And that was last I'm sure it
was last Saturday. Yeah, it was last
Saturday. So, it was two weeks after.
Yeah. And I was looking forward to going
out as well.
Um, again, dismissing my struggles. Did
you just hear what I just told? Again,
I'm not having this conversation. We're
not going around the random circles.
I've shown what I about to show. I've
showed my approaching videos. If you
want to keep dismissing all of these
things, then keep dismissing them. I'm
not explaining myself anymore.
I'm not explaining myself anymore. I'm
not getting into this. You keep
dismissing my struggles, that's on you,
bro. I'm not I'm not repeating myself anymore.
I just gave you an example about last
week who was supposed to meet me. So
like I said, bro, you can keep white
nighting all your life. That's on you,
man. We can all live our own lives.
Do I think she was lying about what
being sick? Um,
yes. Just mind games as usual. That's
all they ever do is mind game. All
that's all they ever do is play mind games,
but they're all different apparently.
They all seem to have the same attitude,
use the same excuses, use age as an
excuse, use religion as an excuse. They
all lead people on, but they're all
different. They all do the same thing,
but they're all different. What? Because
they've got different hair color that
somehow makes them different. Interesting.
You know, I was actually going to show
my screenshots on um
on YouTube to show the [ __ ] I've been
dealing with within like the past four
or five months. Um I don't think people
are going to believe their own eyes. I
think they're really going to come.
They're going to be lost with excuses. I mean,
they say that they'll probably still
make excuses for them. So,
about no, maybe she did get raped. We're
not talking. But what I'm saying is they
go for people that that do this that
treat them like [ __ ]
They go for these people that cheat on
them and abuse them and then when and
they're not interested in a normal person.
So it's like
they are mocking the average guy.
You know there's a guy on Reddit. He's
27 and he's a virgin. He was posting
that he's born in 1998 and he's a
virgin. Now, someone like that is
actually struggling. These women are not
struggling. They are mocking the average
guy. They have no problems finding
anyone that wants to date them. Trust
me, they don't. Yeah, they might have to
deal with a few creeps sending them dick
pictures on dating apps and stuff, but
I'm sure they can find somebody if they
really want to. They are mocking the average guy
or any guy that struggles. They
literally are mocking you. That's what they're doing.
And I know this cuz I've made dating
profiles of women,
um, average looking women, and they get
match after match after match after
match after match, but they still come
online and complain. How can they
[ __ ] complain? What the [ __ ] you know? So, yeah, man.
Yeah, I don't need money, bro. I got money.
I got money, bro. One sec.
So yeah, but that's just my 50 cents anyways.
So and he's got P. One sec, M. [ __ ] madness. [Music] Yeah, mom. Yeah, bro.
But yeah, they just miss my struggles 100%.
But yeah, they just miss your struggles. It's weird.
H that coming on too strong excuse. It's
always a [ __ ] excuse, isn't it?
Game. This is one of the reasons why I
feel so happy, bro. That I'm not dating
women anymore, you know? I feel so
happy, you know?
Like, that's why. Why do you think I was
so calm? Cuz I don't date anymore, you
know? I don't try anymore.
Coming on too strong. It's always a [ __ ] excuse.
It's always a [ __ ] excuse with these
people, you know. Yeah.
So yeah, man.
So yeah, I look forward to my video
that's going to be getting uh 10 thumbs
up. So be looking forward to that. Cheers.
Yeah. Give me 10 thumbs up, mate. Thank you. Yeah.
10 and thumbs up, mate. Trust me. Yeah. So, yeah,
these women make up the most madest excuses.
Glad I gave up this dating thing, bro. I
really am so glad. Like, this video is
just a oneoff, by the way.
Ah, [ __ ] me.
Yeah, man. I don't think I will ever try
again, bro. Yeah, I I seriously don't
think I I don't think I'll ever try
again here, to be honest with you.
I feel like I'm at that stage now with
my um tolerance.
I can't tolerate it no more.
Yeah, I don't I I can't see it
happening, bro. I seriously I can't see it happening.
You really can't see it happening, bro. So yeah, liars, bro.
I think I might just go for a meal on my
birthday. My birthday's a Monday.
I just can't
see it happening again, bro. Like trying
having to deal with that [ __ ] again. I'm
too old for you. I'm too young for you.
I'm a Muslim. Which is another thing.
They use religion as an excuse.
And then when you say you'll convert to
Muslim, there's another excuse. So it's
just like 28 years of age and still
playing these dumbass games with people
at 28 years of age.
Oh, it's so funny cuz there was this
woman that I I met a couple of times,
right? And we spent hours with each
other and she said, "Oh, I can't get you
cuz you're Muslim." I said, "Oh, really?
Well, let me convert to Muslim then."
Just as it just just testing the waters here.
And then there's another excuse. Oh,
well, I'm not looking for anyone. So, is
are they never ever will they ever stop
being full of [ __ ] These people
forever ever in their life are you going
to meet someone that's not full of [ __ ]
that doesn't play games? I don't think so. Yeah,
but yeah, they definitely just missed my struggles 100%. Yeah.
So yeah, man.
I'm too intelligent for these people. I
know. Steven Howard, I'm way too
intelligent for these people.
Yeah. And they use excuses like religion
and and [ __ ] like that.
It's mad. Oh, you can't bet you can't
wait for this video. They're just random
ones when I just want to get these
things on my chest, bro.
It's mad. So, it must seem that they
must like these really, really white
guys with no beards or some [ __ ] No man. So yeah.
So look, I'm speaking to her on another
account and she's up for dating and
stuff and hooking up.
But yeah, she said she'd only date me if I'm Muslim.
These people are full of full of [ __ ]
These people are so full of [ __ ]
They're so full of [ __ ]
These women are so full of [ __ ] lad. Oh,
I'm too intelligent for these people,
aren't I, Joker? Yeah. So yeah,
I'm intelligent, aren't I, Steven
Howard? I am [ __ ] well am, bro. I
really, really am. You know,
I'm so like I'm so intelligent. They're
so full of [ __ ]
So full of [ __ ] bro. They're so so so
Women are liars.
Oh, and then she says that she does have
an Instagram, so she's a liar. These
women are liars.
I've already proved them to be liars, bro. [ __ ]
Yeah. [ __ ] liars that you wouldn't
date anyone that's not [ __ ] Muslim.
[ __ ] liar. But you wouldn't get with
a 28-year-old. You're a liar. I [ __ ]
look [ __ ] I look more [ __ ] Muslim
than any [ __ ] [ __ ] else.
You know, to be honest, most people
would think I'm [ __ ] Muslim. [ __ ]
liars. I'm so sick of this [ __ ] you know.
Yeah, about you don't have Instagram.
I'm so done with dealing with that [ __ ] bro. Seriously, madness.
Yeah, I look Muslim. I look people Some
people would think I am Muslim. Some
even though I'm not Muslim.
I can't believe that, bro. That's madness.
These women are such hypocrites, liars.
That's why I don't bother with them anymore.
I don't contradict anything. not [ __ ]
say either, bro.
Say you don't have Instagram. Saying
that you don't date people that are 28
and you only go with people that are
Muslims, even though I look Muslims
because I'm not a white [ __ ] a white
person. That's eight out of 10. And
you're [ __ ] complaining about me.
[ __ ] out of here, man.
It's so depressing, bro. I don't even
like talking about this. I feel like mid
mid combo is just too depressing. I
don't even like talking about this. So so depressing.
That's why I gave up. So yeah. Yep. madness.
I'm going to make a tea soon and do this video.
My sleeping bag is proper [ __ ] bro.
They lie so much to be honest with you, man.
It's [ __ ] weird, isn't it? No. So yeah,
should I bring a lady up in the video as
well? I think I should. Um, yeah.
What should I start as?
I'll say it like um
why did everyone dismiss Peter Belly struggles?
That's what I'm gonna That's what I'm
going to play as. Oh,
or I should say seems there's no point
having a debate if everyone's just going
to dismiss Peter Belly struggles or
something like that.
You're not someone's type. If I'm not
someone's type, they've got unrealistic standards
because obviously I'm not ugly and
obviously I looks back when I put myself
out there. So for you to not be
someone's type which which would then
mean that they have got unrealistic
standards to a degree. You understand
what I'm saying? Because they're saying
about how they go for personality and
ret and all of this [ __ ] Obviously
they say looks they say that they women
don't go for looks but they obviously
clearly do but then that doesn't make
any sense cuz you're good-looking as
well. So they've got unrealistic
standards and it very much is about
something physical if they're not giving
somebody that's conventionally
attractive a chance. So nothing they say makes sense.
Nothing they say seems to make any sense
if you think about it. You know,
because they say they're going for
personality, but even if somebody is
above average looking or average or
whatever, they still wouldn't even give
somebody a chance
because you're not their specific shadow
type that they've got, materialistic
type that's they've got in their head.
So, it doesn't make any sense. You'll
hear all of these excuses, you're too
old for me, you're not Muslim, you're
this, you're that. It's [ __ ] mental, bro. You know my huh?
Yeah, they're [ __ ] liars.
So, um, and I'm going to bring this
woman up as well on Reddit.
I love how they use the stalking card
when they get proven wrong. I just love
it. I completely love it.
Whenever they get proven wrong, they
always use the stalking card.
You know what? Cuz I went on your Reddit
on something that you posted so publicly
on your page.
What the [ __ ]
They're just absolute liars.
No, no, no, no, no, no. All because I
wasn't that person's materialistic shadow type.
Even though I'd say I don't know why I'm
out of 10. What was I in the video?
Seven out of 10, 6.5 out of 10. Good
enough for somebody to get to know
someone's personality if it's if we're
using this as an example, you know. So strange
tells you a lot. Tells me a lot. But yeah,
I think the alternative is to stick to
escorts. I'm guessing now
don't see there's any other
That sucks [ __ ]
See, it's funny. You know, when you get
these little accounts like Ricky Milling
and these little white knights, if only
they knew about how real life worked,
but they they don't. Do you understand,
bro? They don't.
So, that's that in it. So yeah.
Yeah. This is this this calls for a banger video.
So only if these little white knights
would actually know what they're
actually like if they actually step out
their [ __ ] house for once.
Do you know what I'm saying? So it's mad
they're going to be addressed as well. So yeah,
but they say that they don't go for
looks. They literally go for more than
looks when it's to do with physical stuff,
you know? That's what it is. It's like
they go for more than more than looks.
They go for the impossible.
It will simply be as if you're not white
and you ain't got no beard, we're not
going to go for you.
Or if you don't have a beard or if you
have a beard, we're not going to go for
you. You know what I'm saying? Like it's
that's how shallow they are.
So they go for more than than looks. You understand?
And you know that and I know that. So
that's what a lot of these people
probably saw on my WhatsApp. Oh, he's
got a beard. He looks Mediterranean. Not interested.
I mean, think about it, bro. At this point,
that's probably what I saw and then [ __ ]
it, you know?
So, yeah. Madness.
It's [ __ ] bad.
one is someone's type. Well, if everyone
is someone's type, why don't I have a
date out of any of them 10 numbers? So, yeah,
it's so depressing,
you know, talking about this. I even say
like even when I've been on Instagram
chats with people that we need to stop
talking about it. It's too depressing, you know. Yeah.
That's where we're at, bro. It
So, they go for more than just looks
because I think even if someone's
decently [ __ ] attractive, that's
still not good enough for them, you know? Yeah.
And it's weird because they they
nothing wrong with the way that you look.
Do you understand what I'm saying? So,
and then it causes more more more problems.
Nah, not in the oven. It dries uh it
dries out in the oven. It's no good in
And then it's like even like sometimes I
wake up like everyone's got some tight,
but if that was the case, you would be
with someone. So that's the whole point
because they only
address what they want to address.
And then obviously these women are
trying to make you feel some sort of way
when there's nothing wrong with the way
that you look. There won't wrong with
the way that I look. So they go for a
lot more than looks when it comes to phys
to it being physical,
you know. So they say they go for
personality. What once somebody meets
the threshold of their unrealistic, you know?
And that's where we're at in it. So
this personality thing,
they go for personality once you've
already met their unrealistic threshold standards,
which is unfucking realistic. It's
probably like some white [ __ ] boy
with no beard. That's probably what they
go for. It's like some white guy with no
beard. And if anyone else is not that,
then they're not interested. Can figure
this [ __ ] out for themselves, you know?
It's what it is, man.
So, something something's wrong there, bro.
And yeah, I'm not the best version of
myself. No one's the best version of
themsel. But you're good enough now to
date. You know, you shouldn't have to be
dealing with people making up excuses. Um,
well, I'm not a virgin
about, oh, I'm not getting with you cuz
you're too old.
When we go on your post and we see that
you've been with somebody the same age
as me or trying with someone the same
age as me and then accuse me of being a
stalker when I've clicked on it. the [ __ ]
And I'm going to think and I'm going to
ask them as well. When you say your
women aren't the same,
right, you must be talking about their hair color
or maybe their height. Because if you're
talking about them, yes, they are. So,
and I've never been shown any different
despite how many times I've been I put
myself on the line time and time and
time and time again, you know.
No, it's not about it being everything,
bro. But it does need to be addressed
cuz it's a serious problem. So,
it needs to be addressed. So yeah.
And from now
going to delete my videos either.
So when I put videos out there, I'm not
going to delete my videos. So I'm just
going to leave them out there forever.
So that's it.
It's madness, isn't it?
But they don't seem to think these women
are the problem.
And they don't seem to think that
unrealistic standards is the problem.
It's a madness. It really, really is [ __ ] madness. Yeah.
Using religion as an excuse, mad.
Yeah. Some madness. Yeah, mom.
Anyways, I'm going now and I'm going to
make a TN video.
Yeah. Right. I'm going to make a tea and
then um do this video and talk some
[ __ ] [ __ ] about this bollock today.
another thing that you get.
Well, I'll see you
maybe tomorrow or something. I don't know. It's addicting
these videos and [ __ ]