Batman [ __ ] Batman. That's a
reloc [ __ ] leg.
Bob is a [ __ ] legend. I love him. [Music]
Trust me, these [ __ ] coming here,
man. Don't [ __ ] go off me when I'm in
a [ __ ] toilet. You
can again. We're going to
[ __ ] and then we're going to
send a [ __ ] on street as well.
We only got one that's
Bob. He wasn't he
wasn't like a lot of people in England. He was a
legend. Some people come
in it, man. He was a good guy. You see the big
Yes. Yeah. You didn't find my channel,
Bob. You never found my channel,
man. You never found my channel. We'll [Music]
find. Come on, bud.
Yeah. I'm going to send it.
Bro, what the [ __ ] These people left
two drinks over here. They left two
drinks. Oh, no. They drunk it.
Still punching out.
[ __ ] B, I'm after some [ __ ] women,
bro. But no one was in the [ __ ] pub.
What? I just thought I'd talk to this
old old elderly
gentleman. I thought let me just talk to this elderly
gentleman because why not,
mate? Let's go,
buddy. Well, I'm trying to find some
people here. There's no one here, but I
got to stay in here, mate. I got the old
shorts on. Them [ __ ] ain't going to let
me in if I ain't got a
short ain't after me. You little
[ __ ] [ __ ] me,
bro. I'm steaming. I'm waiting for some
people to come, bro. What the
[ __ ] Put your old shorts on. Imagine
that. M. I can't see. There's no one
here. I'm waiting for some people to be
here, bro. But then know where they are.
Well, there's people here, but they're
in there's like a couple. I'm trying to
When I find a woman or a woman with a
friend, I'll do it, bro. Don't worry. Don't worry,
Sab. Bro, that guy didn't own me.
Listen, I put my feet up, bro. I just
said, Listen, my feet up, bro. He didn't
owe no one, bro. He didn't owe no one.
I'm going to stay here and I'll stay
until about 9:30 and I'll keep it moving. Wait, bro.
Just Oh. Uh. Oh, no. That's a guy
actually. So, we can't do that.
What was your uncle, mate? You already
know, bro. Come on. Where these [ __ ]
bro? Where these [ __ ] at, bro? Ste,
bro. Bob's a [ __ ] legend, mate.
Respect the elderly, mate.
Trying to find some women, but there's
no one about.
No. Yeah, cuz it's early, bro. Cuz it's
early. We had to get to scrap before
them bouncer [ __ ] That's what I'm
saying, bro. We had to We had to get to
scrap before them bouncer [ __ ]
Otherwise, it would have been it, mate.
It would have been
it. We had to get to scrap before them bouncer [ __ ]
Yes. Go away. Easy. Need on your old
legs like. Yes, mate. We have to get
some scrap, Gary, before them bouncer
[ __ ] You know what I'm saying, bro?
And them bouncer [ __ ] come, mate. We're
[ __ ] We weren't going to get in.
That's why I had to come in early, bro. mate. Yeah.
Right. When the phone is on 50%, I've
got to love and leave you, man. I got to
[ __ ] love and leave you, bud. Unless
we find someone that will stick with
us. [ __ ] me, man.
Yeah. I know. It's mad, bro. That Yes. What up, bro? This
Why am I wearing shorts? Cuz shorts are
the best, bro.
30 [ __ ] women here, mate. I don't think they're
in my fingers.
Let's get on there, boy. [Music]
Well, they're going to come, bro.
They're going to come. They're going to [ __ ]
come. And when they come, I'm going to
go back live.
I'm wavy, bro. [Music]
I'll do her [ __ ]
night. I'm going to wake up with a
banging hangover tomorrow cuz of
you. I'm going to wake up tomorrow with
a [ __ ] banging hangover,
mate. Mate, that Scottish guy didn't owe
me. Bro, listen. I had my feet, bro.
Listen. Yeah, I had my feet on here,
bro. Listen, bro. No, listen, bro. Mine
had his feet on
here. I had my feet on here, bro.
Mother, I said, listen, I was trying to
talk to him normally like I did, Bob. He
was like, oh, uh, I said, mate, I'll put
my feet where I want. I said I told him
I'll put my feet where I want, mate. Do
you see me back down, bro? My feet was
stiff here, bro. Yeah. [ __ ]
[ __ ] Got his brick. He don't want no
smoke, mate. He's a [ __ ] mate. He's a
[ __ ] [ __ ] If he was about
anything. Yeah, he would have come over.
He was [ __ ] about I swear
[ __ ] was like 50 minutes 50 m
away from me.
Yeah, I ain't scared of no one, bro.
Listen, he is a [ __ ] [ __ ] No, they
won't, mate. Once you're already in,
mate, you're already in [ __ ] in. Once
you're already in, they can't chuck you out.
[ __ ] He's not about nothing, mate.
Let me tell you something now. I'll
shout it out now. I don't care. Listen,
I was trying to be friendly to the guy
like I did Bob. And he's like, "Oh, you
don't see me asking about why your feet
I said, "Hey, my feet are where they
are, mate." And I'm not moving him,
mate. That's what I said to him. Yeah,
boy. I'll [ __ ] kick his ass back to
[ __ ] Scotland, bro. He's a [ __ ] He
knew he can go there with me, man.
been a ticket for no reason.
Over the folded.
Oh, when there's someone
but another guy with no girls in
it. I'm not in O'Neal's mate. You don't
know where I
am. Are you
He's a [ __ ] He's scared, isn't he?
Did he come in my personal space, bro?
Did the guy come in my personal space?
No, cuz he knew. It will get busy in a
bit. Defo, you're trying to [ __ ] tell
me, mate. No, there's no security here.
Listen, the [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah, I
told him. I'll put my feet where I want,
mate. Here, I'll do it again.
Mate, my feet are
here. Look right up, man. What you going
to do? Nothing. You we Scottish bombs to
you. [ __ ] off, man. You Scottish. [ __ ]
Celtic. [ __ ] rangers. [ __ ] you. Kill wear and
[ __ ] [ __ ] the Scottish. They're all
[ __ ] Yo, we bought crack in you. [ __ ]
off, mate. You're a little Scottish
little prick, man. You know, I'm trying
I was trying to be nice to the dude as
well. And he's giving me attitude. Why
don't you [ __ ] back to Scotland, you
cross [ __ ] white blue flag, you [ __ ]
Yeah, he didn't owe me, bro. All Yeah, I
was like, bro, bear in mind, I was
shocked. I was like, this guy doesn't
get rude to me. You're we got
quing. We stole all your women as well,
bro. Yeah, I told him I put my feet
where I [ __ ] want, mate. That's what I told
him. Don't tell me where I can put my
feet. Like, no, bro. [ __ ] back to
Scotland where you come from, you little
kilwar and pipe sucking little [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] They're all a big
talk to Scots, but in reality, they're
not about nothing. Trying to tell me
Glasgow's all this. Oh, Glasgow.
Don't get there. [ __ ] off. [ __ ] going.
Sky prick. And I'll say to their face
when I say no one's there on
me. He was going to try and tell me
where I was going to move my little legs
to my own country. You
mad? That's a violation,
bro. That's a mad violation, bro. You
ain't telling me where I'm putting my
[ __ ] legs, mate.
You are not telling man where he's
putting his [ __ ] leg. You [ __ ] Yeah.
You know what I'm saying? I've had a
[ __ ] day, mate. I will put my feet
wherever I [ __ ] see, mate. You know
what? I'll put my feet where I
want. I asked you or you drink was a
beer and it was a [ __ ] jack. I'll put
my feet where I want. I'll stay where I
want as well. You know, you [ __ ] kill
wear and [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah, he's got I
left, but I'm in a night. Should get
vision a bit. Give it a little while. And to
think in bed today. No, mate. Can't be
lying in bed. We got to give it a little
Well, I would. I [ __ ] would. Steven I
would give it
a I [ __ ] would. You know what I'm
saying would, mate. We got the old
shorts on as
well, bro. This guy was being a dick for
no reason. I've already been to Scotland
two times and none of you [ __ ]
Look, got the
old Look at the old shorts. Ready for
the old approach. Easy on the old
knees. On the old knees, buddy.
Yeah. Look at
that. That hair, man. It's
stick looking like a stick cut, bro.
Like a [ __ ] masters. You look I even
take it off. Look at this. Look at that.
Easy old socks. That bro
slid 100%. We are getting some [ __ ]
We're going to stay in this place until
about 10. Until about
10. Oh, I spotted until about 10:00 and
then after 10 we're going to the about
9:30. Oh no, he's easy by 9:30 and after 9:30 discuss Maybe nothing.
Maybe I'm still I am actually It's not even
funny. Nah, bro. Cuz I'm limited. Got
the old shorts on, is I?
Not even, bro. I got the old shorts on, didn't I? [Music]
Nah, man. Cuz I'm I'm I'm limited to
where I can go, man. And it's happy hour, so
[ __ ] That's right. P
and I find someone
bro maybe. Yeah.
Oh [ __ ] bro. I like gas, bro.
Hope he doesn't stay where I am cuz he's [ __ ] [Music]
retards. Nah, bro. Stop self-relecting. You're already
bored, mate. I need to go to Turkey. My
hairline's fine. You're already bored. Stop
self-reflecting. You're the one who's
already bored. You little self-reflector.
I'm going to send it to him. Watch when
it gets busy.
Mate, you're already bored. Speak for yourself. Little
self-reflector. My hairline's crazy, is
it? No, I think it's all right, man.
You're self-reflecting. You're already bored.
You're already [ __ ] bored. Stop
self-reflecting, mate. You're already
bored. Stop self-relecting, you little self-reflector. [Music]
Listen, it seems of
us did it. Stop
self-reflecting. That's what I say to him.
But me and you are meant to
I'm [ __ ] steaming, bro.
We're going to get some [ __ ] Trust
me, we will get some [ __ ] bro. Mate,
you're already bored. Stop
self-relecting, mate. Not balding. Not
one part of me is balding, mate. Stop self-reflecting. I said,
"Yeah, well, I'm going to send it."
Watch. Swear on when people come. Cuz
when the came out, I just didn't know what.
Yeah. And he's going to [ __ ] diverge.
I'm [ __ ] steaming, bro. [Music]
We're going to get some [ __ ] today, bro. Trust.
Yeah, I will, bro. I will. I will.
Listen, bro. I'm 53%. Yeah. When it goes
on 50%. I'm going to cut the live stream
out and then I'll go back
live. 50% live. What were we? 20 to
6, mate. We're going to be sending it
all night, ain't
we? I'm [ __ ] wavy, bro. Ah,
[ __ ] What's that?
I got [ __ ] as
well. I got a [ __ ] [ __ ] mate. I got
the I got the surv on. Yes, I've got the
[ __ ] But make it confidence.
You already know, mate. You already
know, bro. Watch. When people come in,
you're going to see it. You will see it.
You will say, bro, trust me, you will
that you know what,
mate, mate. I'm
[ __ ] I am [ __ ] It's over. I need
to cut this live stream in a bit and
then just wait here until it gets busy
because if I go out I can't come back in
which is obviously the old school and
we're going to send it
100%. Something the [ __ ] virgin can
never do the orington virgin. Isn't that right Steven
Howard? Isn't that right? Steven Howard
the [ __ ] virgin. Virgin Mary will
[ __ ] die a virgin.
He will. He will [ __ ] die a virgin.
[ __ ] Virgin Mary.
Yeah, they are, mate. They got no life.
They're fat, ugly little mongos. Told
you, mate. They're fat, ugly little
mongos, bro. I'll go out and sing the [ __ ] by
myself, mate. They're all virgins. Why
they on YouTube every day, bro, watching
L J? cuz they ain't got a life, man. Do you understand?
Watch, bro. Watch. Let it get busy. It will pick
up. Sean will die virgin. Steven Howard.
Steven. Steven Howard. Sean will die a
virgin. All my words die one
little. He will [ __ ] die a virgin. He
will never get laid.
Virgin [ __ ] ugly [ __ ] with his
[ __ ] gap teeth.
You will [ __ ] die. Virgin die
one. Let me Okay. What's
it? There we go. It's tapped. It's gone. Oh, there we
go. I'm getting paper.
Bro, what the [ __ ] is going on
here? What I paid one pound for? Go
on. There you go.
I want a
paper. I've already inserted it. What? Try
again on hell.
What the [ __ ] is going on here then?
Excuse me. Excuse me. I just put two
pound on it and it's not coming
on. The [ __ ] is going on, bro?
I just put two pound on it. It put it
said put one pound and I put another
pound on it. He didn't come on.
I just paid like two
times from America. Hey, easy.
Bro, we're going to send these
approaching when these [ __ ] come
up. I ain't trying to
wait. Are you from
milk? How is it for certain credit? I
put [ __ ] two pound on it.
Bro, man just put two pound on it, bro.
How the [ __ ] is it telling man to insert quitting?
How is it telling me to quit? I just put
two quid on it, mate. When the when the
battery gets to 50%, I've got to end it
and then come
back. I need to end
it from America, man. Wonder if she's
from Boston probably.
I want to play some
games. I want to play some games. How
you tell me?
Are you from America? No. Where you
from? Canada. Ah, almost. Al almost.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. With everything going
on. Where you from? Toronto. Ah, nice,
man. So, you have like turkey bacon for
breakfast, right? That's a big That's a
big open, right? Yeah. I should be
working, I think. I don't know. I knew I
knew it was somewhere from there. It
should be hopefully. I just put two pound on
it. So, what brings you to London here? Wow.
What's going on though? It still doesn't explain that
ever. It's still telling me to insert
money. It doesn't make sense. Money.
No, it's still telling me to insert money.
I've just I don't know how to I've never
touched it before if I'm being honest.
How long you been in London for? Three
years now. Three years. I've never seen
you here before. I'm here,
but I come here all the time and I never
see you here. I like I come like every week. Yeah. Um
Oh, there we go. Yeah. Now I need to
figure out how to pay it. Yeah, I think
I think it is. Um, I mean, it's not
telling me to insert any more money.
Yeah, I've used this. Yeah.
Yeah. Think so. Yeah. Yeah. Good.
Good. Get a
lumber. When she comes by,
bro. She can smell it, bro. She can
it. Watch. It's on 50%. When it goes to
49, I got to end it there, bro. I swear
there. What the [ __ ] am I doing,
bro? When she comes back,
bro. Oh, it's me to put more money
in. It's telling me to put more money
in. What? I'm going to get another robot.
No way. More money in. What the [ __ ] I
put two quid in it.
Yeah. How do you from there in Canada?
Sorry, Chad. But I was still with you, [ __ ]
When it gets to 49, I've got to end this
live stream and come back, bro.
One second. What is it? Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, from Canada. Yeah, that reminds me where
uh I'm from Canada,
man. Love it.
[ __ ] pang, bro.
I might get another
still. One second. And she comes
back. Yeah, it's just took money off me.
Two quid. I'm never getting two pound
back. I'm never getting two pound back.
I'll be accepting it.
I've never had a Canadian Izzy before.
Well, I'm going to chat. I'm going to get a
number. One second, bro.
Wait, bro. Wait, wait, wait. Just wait a
little bit. I'm going to come back live.
I'm going to come live, bro. Watch.