Why does my microphone work on that but not that?
Strange, isn't it? That's weird. Yeah.
I was going to do a football bet
earlier, but I just went to another
place in school back
to Could be all
Too depressing to walk that far to be honest.
I was going to do a football bet, but
I didn't bother.
This women [ __ ] sure takes it to you.
when it's been happening for Yes.
sleeping P's [ __ ] as well. Oh, well,
probably cuz I don't got to drink it
anymore to be fair. Yeah.
What a depressing life. Eh,
having to use escorts for the rest of
your life. How depressing is that?
That's how you degrade your way one way.
You you degrade yourself one way or the
[ __ ] other, you know? [ __ ] hell. Stay mode.
I was going to do um a football bet
earlier, but I went to I went to get
some breakfast, but I couldn't be
bothered to walk any further to do the football bet.
So depressed. I can't stop thinking
about my bad experiences with women.
I was thinking of suicide last night,
bro. That's why I went back live.
Every single day I I feel like I'm
closer to it cuz it never changes ever.
It's just bad experiences led on. Bad
experiences led on. Bad experiences led So toxic.
Oh, it is.
Yeah, it's a depressing depressing life.
I pray every day when I go to sleep, I
don't wake up, bro. It's depressing as [ __ ]
It's so depressing.
Only you can explain it. It is. It's
really, really bad.
No, I'm not putting a bet on. I'm
staying in bed. I'm going sleeping a bit. It's depressing
putting a bet on. I'm nowhere near a bookies anyways. And yeah,
you know, I'm depressed. I'm staying in
bed all day.
I'm depressed me. Yeah.
There's no getting over 3 weeks ago,
getting 10 numbers and not a single day.
There's no recover from that.
Yeah, I'll be in bed today. Depressed.
I'm probably I will end up killing
myself soon. Trust me, I will. I will. I
definitely definitely am end going to do
it soon, bro. decided. Yeah.
It's depressing as [ __ ] Really is.
Nah. Don't have the time. Don't have the energy, bro.
I don't have the energy for it, bro. Too old.
But yeah, I'll be killing myself soon anyways.
So that's Yeah, it's too depressing, bro.
it's never changing, bro. Never changing
in this country with these women. You
don't need therapy or counseling. You
need better experiences.
Nope. I've already been on the apps.
Deleted them, bro. Deleted them like two days ago.
I deleted him like two days ago. I'm
sure it was like two days ago. You don't
need therapy. You don't need counseling.
You need better experiences with women.
That's never going to happen. We're
beyond that now. We've gave him chance
after chance after chance after chance
after chance. And um another thing was I
was speaking to this woman earlier on
Reddit and she's so ew. She says, "Oh, I
don't owe you anything to read your
messages." I was like, "Ew." A woman
that says, "I don't owe you anything."
That's so cringe. It's so ew. It's It
gives me the it
like, "You don't owe anyone anything.
You're sat there [ __ ] typing to me,
you know? It's so ew. It will never
change and they'll never change. [ __ ]
boring as [ __ ] So yeah,
hopefully just die my sleep. That'll be nice.
Being lovely, bro. Cuz it's not changing.
Seriously. Seriously, it ain't changing.
[ __ ] up to put on with that [ __ ] all
your life. [ __ ] that. That is depressing
as [ __ ] You don't need therapy. You
don't need counseling. You need better experiences.
I've explained this like millions and
millions and millions of times. And
you're not ever going to get better
experiences with women. They're always
going to prove they're all the same. It
doesn't matter what anybody [ __ ]
says. Me, you, the [ __ ] two dogs. It doesn't matter.
So that's where we're at basically here.
Nope. I've already been on the apps.
They don't work. I don't even get any
matches now. And when I did, they didn't reply.
So no. Been there, done that. Got the t-shirt. No.
Already done that.
I'll be ending my life soon anyways.
It's too depressing. The more and more
you think about it, the more more it's
just too depressing.
It's bad. It really, really is bad.
It's like you was put on earth to be
mocked by women
and laughed at. That's what it generally
generally feels like. If you look at
these experiences, you will see exactly
what I mean.
you will see exactly what I mean.
Well, it is for me when you've had as
many bad experiences as I have and you
have women on Reddit claiming that they
can't find somebody when they can.
They literally can find someone. Any
woman can find someone
and that's it. Stop [ __ ] saying that
you can't find someone when you [ __ ]
can. Any woman can find someone.
The amount of simps and [ __ ] white
knights and [ __ ] I shouldn't have to
use an escort.
I could I could use an escort once a
month. I I should have to use an escort.
I've done enough approaches. I've put
enough effort into it. I've done what
most people are afraid of. So,
I shouldn't have to use an escort. You understand? So
you're degrading yourself more
approaching women than you are using an escort.
Facts. Being led on, took the piss out
of. That's worse than using an escort.
That's degrading yourself more than
using an escort. Yeah.
What do you mean women aren't for me?
I'm not gay. No.
No. I hate them, bro. I hate them.
They're [ __ ] [ __ ]
They are absolute [ __ ]
Really, really, really are.
And how people say they're not the same
is beyond me. You know,
I've also shown you my experiences with
them as well, which people seem to
dismiss. People seem to love dismissing my experiences.
The leading on, the piss taking, it
doesn't seem to suit anyone.
Doesn't seem to
shock anyone what they do. They think
it's nothing when it's [ __ ] bad what
they do, you know? So yeah. Yeah.
But they're not all the same apparently. Bubble.
Both of them.
Well, a white knight would never cop
block me. So, I'm not the one to ask
that question because it would never happen.
It would never happen cuz people have
tried it before and it hasn't worked.
You white knight would never cop block
me cuz I'd smash their [ __ ] teeth
down their throat.
After the last American that tried it
with me, he shot himself. It would never happen.
Yeah. It's such a shame all women are
the same, is it?
It's mad how all women are the same.
It doesn't matter what anyone says, they
prove that they're all the same every
single time you meet one. Leading on
mind game, same mannerisms, same
excuses. I'm surprised people like Nons
would say they're not all the same when
they obviously are all NPCs.
It's so [ __ ] obvious that they're all the same.
They they do they do too much of the
same stuff to be all different. They're
all the [ __ ] same.
Literally, it's mad. They are literally
all the same. Yeah.
But now something has got to give.
We can't be doing this all our [ __ ]
life. We can't be, bro. This is not normal.
I was saying this on the way to get breakfast. Um yeah,
it's not normal, bro. It's not normal.
Whatever the [ __ ] normal is,
these experiences are not normal.
No, that never happened.
But yeah, the more I think about when I
got them 10 numbers in not a single day,
it makes you want to kill yourself. It's
depressing. There's no reason for it.
Literally no reason for it at all.
No one ever got me phone out of a club. No. [ __ ] all
depressing. Is it?
I ain't gambled for a few weeks. Don't
need that stress in my life.
Already have enough [ __ ] with women. Yeah.
It's like you were born to be mocked by
these women. That's what it feels like.
That's what it generally feels like. You know,
they do on purpose as well, which is
another thing that no one acknowledges
that they do their [ __ ] behavior and
they're leading on on purpose. They
literally [ __ ] do. Like I can back up
everything I [ __ ] say
and it's never ending and it will never
end. It's [ __ ] depressing.
Yeah, it's bad. It's bad. Bad. Bad. Bad.
Bad. And it will never change. Yeah, man.
I so [ __ ] sleeping. So [ __ ] up. Yep.
It sucks that the only way out is
suicide, isn't it? Cuz that's like the
last resort to like anything. But I
seriously can't say a way out. Been
trying for years. Been getting bad
experiences for years. Nothing ever
changes. Same old, same old. Boring. You
know, it's depressing as [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] depressing as [ __ ] bro.
I don't even gamble anymore. I got
money. I don't even gamble. >> Yeah.
It's like you were born to be mocked and
have bad experiences. That's what it
feels like generally. What it feels like.
I should need to pay for an escort.
People do use escorts, but I don't I I
should have to use an escort.
I've put the effort in. I've put the
I've looked my best. I've approached. I
don't need I I don't need to use an
escort. Should have or I shouldn't have
to use an escort.
You know what I mean?
That's where we're at basically.
Let's see what Reddit's saying.
without drinking in a [ __ ] long time, bro. Yeah. Heat. No,
no, I had breakfast earlier.
sucks. This life, it
just out of there.
[ __ ] depressing, bro.
What's the thing?
Yeah, I was going to do a football bet.
I was going to do a treble. Five. I draw. Nah.
I'm going to have to use escorts for the
rest of my life. How depressing is that? Yep. Yeah. Yeah,
I can't believe escorts or living in
Thailand or South America is like the
only option. That's [ __ ] bro. Really, really [ __ ]
They ruin people's confidence
and then they tell people to become
confident when they're the kinds that
ruined it in the first place. Yeah.
just don't read it now. Yeah.
Oh man, I'm [ __ ] depressed.
I was thinking of suicide again last night.
I went for some breakfast earlier. I was
going to do a football. I didn't want to
walk that far
to the bookies. M. [Music]
>> Yeah. So depressing this life. Can't
wait for it to end.
Bad experiences with women, being
mocked, being led on. I'm ready to get
out of this life, bro. For real. It's so depressing.
It's a depressing life that never changes.
[ __ ] hell, man.
No, I'm not betting, bro. I'm not
getting out of bed. I'm not going
anywhere. I'm not doing anything. This
is my dayto-day life.
Often getting them 10 numbers and not a
single day. Just
Kill the vibe, bro. Kill the mood.
I went to get some breakfast earlier.
Greavves. Yeah, I done a video for you,
but I haven't uploaded yet. Yeah,
you go to Birmingham, bro. I can barely
make up the [ __ ] road,
let alone [ __ ] Birmingham.
It's too depressing, bro. I'm too depressed.
could barely make up the [ __ ] road. I
walked to King earlier and got some
breakfast and that was it.
Yeah, just the bad experiences with women. Tandy man,
just a summary of like thinking about
all the things I've been through with
these women and [ __ ]
It's mad. It's mad depressing.
Mad mad depressing.
and knowing I'd have to use escorts for
the rest of my life.
That is [ __ ] depressing.
Really, really, really depressing.
I tell people on Reddit and um stuff,
but they just dismiss my struggles.
So, the things really go anywhere
because they just dismiss my struggles.
It doesn't suit them.
Yeah. My bad experiences don't suit them.
same old it. Yep.
I'm not playing a victim. I've gone out.
I've tried. I've put the effort in. I
got 10 numbers and I've been led on. I
had my time wasted, flaked. I got all
the messages. I've got everything to back up
um what I'm saying. I'm not playing the
victim. I'm speaking facts.
People that play the victim have not
tried anything. I have probably more
than anyone in the world. So, you might
want to get your facts right before
accusing somebody of playing the victim.
You might want to get your facts right.
See, what's the day today? Right. Well,
Saturday, of course,
use this as an example. I could go out
today, try and meet women, and I'd have
exactly the same experiences. So, now
it's beyond the point. Well, going out
and trying is not going to help either.
It's going to get you mocked. It's going
to get you more bad experiences. It's
going to get you mocked by women. So,
you have no choice but to stay in bed
because no matter what you do,
the experiences are going to get worse. So,
so yeah, bro. So, yeah, using that as an
example, I could go out today and
exactly the same thing would happen
again. It's toxic. Very, very, very, very toxic. So, yeah. Yep.
I don't feel I can recover from that
three weeks ago, bro.
10 numbers, spent £600, didn't even get
a single date.
That is [ __ ] depressing.
That is depressing. Come on.
Let's Let's agree that is depressing and
it's discouraging and it shows you that
if you would go out again,
I'm the only one that's tried the way I
have who can't get a date. Yes. Yes. I'm
the only one that's tried more than
anyone in the world. Yes, I have. Yes, I
have. I can actually sit there and say
that. So, I got 10 numbers. I look to my
best. There's no reason for me to not
have a date. There's no reason for me to
not be with anyone. And there's no
reason for me to have to use an escort.
There's literally no reason. So, yeah.
So yeah, it's depressing,
but people on Reddit still think you're
going to meet someone.
Very optimistic of them. E,
you know, it's bad. Really, really bad. So,
can't believe giving up is the only solution. It's mad.
You obviously no one's type in this
country. That's been established
as far as this country goes. So you
doing anything here now would just be a
waste of time.
Already been proven. I don't know how
much mos [ __ ] you've got to put up with before
you realize like you've done what you're
about to do. You tried your best. That's
it. There's no trying again here.
Yeah, you had no problem with women.
Good for you. I've had loads of problems with them.
I mean, I can put all of my experiences
on on a video, like the screenshots and
stuff, but it doesn't suit anyone. So,
there's there's literally no point of me
there's no point wasting my time doing
that because it doesn't suit it's not
going to suit anyone.
They don't shoot them. So there's no
point. They'll just dismiss it cuz it
doesn't suit them. So there's no point
really doing that.
Yeah. You know what I say?
And all the people you have met have
shhat on you in the end.
USA is the other people dates have
wasted your time.
Some people just born to be mocked.
That's what it is. That's really really
I never thought suicide would be the
only way out. Seriously. Never thought
that in a million years,
but seems that it is bad.
Really, really, really, really bad.
And I have to give up for my own
well-being as well of how toxic it is.
Now people on Reddit say that I'm going
to meet someone candy man.
Their comments trigger me when they say
to other people, "Oh, you just need to
go out and approach women."
Someone will make a post some random
person and then they will comment
saying, "Oh, you need to go out and put
yourself out there." Yeah. You need to
put yourself out there. You need to
approach women, do you? Yeah.
They're just all [ __ ]
Mom was ignoring you and I kept calling
her and she said, "Oh, no one you can't
get a girlfriend." I said, "You're not
going to rage you're not going to you're
not going to rage bait me.
So, there's no point trying to rage bait
me cuz it's not going to work. Obviously. Yeah.
It's like this little Ricky Milling
little white knight. Little [ __ ]
virgin. He doesn't know anything about
women. When he's trying to say, "Oh,
it's about me talking about, oh, let's
have babies." The guy's a white knight.
He's a [ __ ] joke. He doesn't know anything. So, yeah. Yeah,
it's depressing, isn't it? to know that
there are people out there that's having sex
or someone might be getting pregnant and
you're sat there suffering being mocked
and you can't do anything for your own well-being
cuz obviously you can't go out and try
again beyond that now. It's it it's no,
you can't do that anymore. So,
it's for the best that you don't do it
either. So, you're basically screwed now.
It's really really bad. No, it's not
about them being anything or not. I I
should be getting I should be having
sex. I should have a sex life. There's
no reason why I don't have a sex life. I
shouldn't have to use an escort.
You know, even though going with an
escort is not as degrading as putting up
with this [ __ ]
you know? It's nowhere near as degrading
as that. But you shouldn't have to use an escort.
I don't know why they still think. I
mean, if you think about this right now,
yeah, how many years have I been trying
and it's been the same old [ __ ] [ __ ]
So, the chances are that one day you go
out and try again, you're going to meet
someone. It's like one in a trillion, bro.
It's got to be lottery odds. Cuz if it
was anything less than lottery odds, you
would have already found someone. It's
so obvious. It's so [ __ ] obvious,
bro. Like, it's not been going on for
months. It's been going on for years.
All that will happen is
you go out, you hear, "I've got a
boyfriend. You hear I'm not interested.
You'll get numbers and then you get led
on. There's nothing else that will happen."
There is literally nothing else that will happen.
And if you're extremely or if you're
extremely extremely extremely extremely
extremely lucky, you go on a date with a
woman who wants to make you feel [ __ ]
about yourself. There's nothing else
that will happen.
There's nothing, bro.
There's literally nothing else that will
happen by that.
It's a [ __ ] madness, isn't it, bro?
It's a [ __ ] madness. They'll lead you
on for their own entertainment,
but they're not all the same. Women
aren't all the same. They just say the
same stuff, do the same stuff, play the
same games, lead people on, but they're
not the same.
There's a line there. But they're not
the same. They do a lot of the same
[ __ ] stuff for people that are not
the [ __ ] same. I [ __ ] tell you
that now, mate. I'd be very concerned if
somebody was very similar to me, let
alone the [ __ ] same as me, but would
agree to disagree on that one.
They are all the [ __ ] same. I was
supposed to meet someone last [ __ ] Saturday.
Wasted my time.
Ah, typical that one, isn't it? So yeah,
it's [ __ ] up, is it, man?
Have to use escort forever
for the rest of your life.
Like that's where we're at. Like that's
literally the only thing you can do.
or go South America or live in Asia.
There's there's literally nothing else.
There is literally nothing else you can
do. And that's not even the same. So,
doesn't seem normal, does it? It doesn't
seem normal. It's [ __ ] weird.
I'd rather get an escort than ever try
again, bro. to be fair.
Dealing with their [ __ ]
Dealing with their [ __ ] [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] that, bro.
I'm getting too old to go to clubs now as well.
Yeah, man. I'm too old to know. Yeah.
I need a cola. Yeah,
I'm going to watch some Incel videos, I
think, before I go to sleep.
Even though I can't relate to them being
a virgin. not incel. They don't class
themselves as incelss. But even though I
can't relate as
um obviously I'm not a virgin, but
obviously I'm still struggling now. So,
so I'll go on their videos and
um like a community I can relate to basically. Yeah. Yep. Imagine
I had to like if I if I wanted to try again, right,
I'd have to stop for like 6 months, bro.
Literally, it'd have to be about 6
months to a year. You'd have to get like
an escort every month and you'd have to
try again in like 6 months minimum. Minimum.
And even then, I think I'd say it's 6 to 8 months
before you could even reconsider again.
Bro, it's that bad. Like, so
yeah, it's not good, bro. It's not good.
depressing in it. Yeah, same old Anyway, I'm gone.
You better make it up on the store