[ __ ] it up.
So, there you go. Put some of the
messages up. They're only a small part.
I don't know why my mic doesn't work on
these [ __ ] um apps, man.
I don't know why. What's wrong with it? [ __ ] annoyance.
So there we go. Those are only some of
the messages. So you can see I haven't
typed anything wrong.
Haven't spoke about babies making babies, you know. So I
Wish I could talk over it, but it won't let me.
Does anyone have a solution to this
microwave problem? [ __ ] microphone
problem. You are single forever, Terry.
You're probably still a virgin. I don't
know why you're self projecting, bro. At
least I owe my [ __ ] bro. You're You're
probably still a virgin, Terry. You're
like 4 foot two. You can't afford a new
pair of trainers. Who are you to talk about anyone?
Like, like I said, bro, you're probably
still a [ __ ] virgin for God's sake.
For [ __ ] like, oh, you got kids, bro.
Have you shown anyone on here your kids?
No, you [ __ ] haven't. So shut the
[ __ ] up. A lot of people say [ __ ] on
here. So until you can actually prove
something, shut up, man. You are single.
You're single right now and you can't
even afford a new pair of trainers. So
how are you to talk about me? [ __ ]
hell, man. How are you to talk about [ __ ] me?
Get a [ __ ] grip, S. I know.
No, it's not that uh I don't think no
one has anything. I think you people
don't have anything. That's what I
think. I think you people on YouTube
don't have anything.
I don't think normal people don't have
anything. I think you people don't have
And I've proven it many times as well.
Just like with that smoky bee, I proved
it. And I'm not just talking about
money. I'm not even just talking about that.
I think you people don't know anything
cuz you're sat on YouTube all day every
day typing away and I've seen it myself.
So yeah, that's that's it.
I think you people don't have anything.
Yeah, but Terry, you can't even afford a
new pair of trainers. You're about 5
foot tall. You You can't talk about anyone.
Yeah, of course you do. Well, do you
want to Why don't you come in and show
us your house?
Okay, that's fact. Sh. Do you want to
come in and show us your house?
Okay. Do you want to join Hangouts and
show us your house?
Nice. Can I see it? Can I see your cars?
Can I see your house?
Oh, lovely. I'd love to see that. A four
bed house. That's nice. But can we see it?
Can we see it?
You at work. Exactly.
Cuz you ain't got it. You've got
nothing. You're self projector. You are
the jobless loser.
That's Yeah, you're self projecting,
bro. I know people do I know people do
night shifts, but I it's very unlikely
that that you do night work. So, you're
sat there on YouTube. Terry, you're
still a virgin. That's even more
shocking. Listen, listen, listen,
listen, listen, listen. Right. You
people don't work. You sit on YouTube
every day typing away. I've seen it with
my own eyes. I've seen what you people
do with my own eyes. sat on YouTube
every every day typing away. But Terry,
you're like 48 and you're still a
virgin, so I don't know why you're
talking about other people. What's
shocking is you're [ __ ] a [ __ ]
You're ugly and you can't even afford a
new pair of trainers. That is embarrassing.
And you're single yourself. And that's
why you can't prove it that you're, you
know, you're in a relationship. All right,
here we go.
One sec. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. One second. Second. Maybe not.
Come on then.
Come on then. But Terry, you can't even
afford a new pair of trainers. You're
like 5 foot [ __ ] tall and you're
thing yourself and you're trying to
[ __ ] preach to others. You're trying
to [ __ ] preach to others. Really?
Does anyone know how to fix the [ __ ]
microphone for Samsung? It doesn't work
on any of the apps. I tried to send
voice notes. It doesn't work.
And I've tried every method possible
and it just doesn't work. And I don't
know why it doesn't work.
Yeah, of course it is. Yeah. So, why
can't you afford a new pair of trainers
then? If you've got all of this money,
tell us why you can't afford
um a new pair of trainers H.
Come on, tell me. Why can't you afford a
new pair of trainers then if you've got
all of this money? M
doesn't let me.
>> There you go. You scruffy [ __ ] [ __ ] Not sat.
>> Yeah, that doesn't mean you're at work
because you're sat somewhere.
>> You scruffy little [ __ ]
>> You are a scruffy little bastard. Shut
the [ __ ] up.
>> I'll [ __ ] murder you, you [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Well, come and meet me then. Come
and meet me then, you little weasel.
[ __ ] cut you up, boy.
>> Yeah, come and meet me then, you little weasel.
>> I'll [ __ ] meet you anytime.
>> Yeah, go and meet me anytime. Anytime
you want. Yeah, that's fine. Stop being
a keyboard warrior.
>> Sorry, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Yeah, sorry. What could someone call me
off guard? Yeah. Yeah, I'll make you say sorry, though.
>> You'll never I'll make you say sorry,
you [ __ ] ugly don bastard.
>> Listen, don't leave.
>> What do you want to meet?
>> You limp from limb. You [ __ ] immature
little [ __ ] Shut the [ __ ] up, you ugly
northerner. Sort that ugly northern
accent out, you ugly northerner.
>> You boy.
>> Yeah. Well, meet me there. Well, meet me then.
>> [ __ ] with men, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Okay, meet me then. Meet me there.
[ __ ] little ride around [ __ ]
delivery job. You minimum wage.
>> Yeah, bro. Bro, listen listen. You ugly
and bro, you're someone's [ __ ] You're
at work right now. You're someone's
[ __ ] You got no education. You got no
money. You have to work for someone. Do
you really think if you you would to be
working for someone because you got no
education? I've got money. I don't need
to work. I don't need to be someone's
[ __ ] Listen, I can go out right now
and do something. I don't need to be
someone's [ __ ] cuz I've got the brain. You understand?
>> Because I am down.
>> You have to be someone's [ __ ] because
you got no education. Cuz you got to be someone's [ __ ] >> Yeah.
>> [ __ ] own.
>> You [ __ ] ugly northern bastard. Go
sort your ugly accent out, you ugly
northern [ __ ] Yeah.
And you know what I mean, bro? Listen.
Listen. Why are you at work right now? Come on.
Why are you being someone's [ __ ]
Exactly. Anyone that has to work for someone.
Anyone that has to work for someone,
bro. Ain't got no intelligence, ain't
got ain't got no brain.
We know this.
We [ __ ] well know this. It's obvious.
I done that [ __ ] um Uber thing for a
laugh. Yeah, cuz the weather was nice.
Let you know just I done it just to do
it. I don't need to be someone's [ __ ]
You're sat there right now having to be
someone's [ __ ] And you're bragging to
others. You're bragging to others. Yeah.
Yeah. But I don't need but listen.
Listen. I've got money and I don't need
to work. I don't need to work. Smart
people don't need to [ __ ] work. Do you understand?
Smart people don't need to [ __ ] work.
And that's that that's that.
Yeah. Working. Listen, Terry, you was my
[ __ ] When I went to your area, you was
my [ __ ] You didn't even come out. So,
anyways, if you got all of this money,
why can't you afford a new pair of trainers?
Huh? Why can't you afford a new pair of
trainers? Come on, tell us. Tell us. We
want to know. Come on.
Tell us. Huh?
Also, have you am I the only channel you
go on? Did you see what happened between
Monty and Rice?
Or am I the only channel that you go on
because you love stalking me? Huh? Go on.
Am I the only channel you go on because
you love stalking me?
Tell me. Go on.
Have you been watching other channels? Huh?
I'm going to knock him out.
I'm going to knock him out. I'm going.
So, you didn't see Monty and Rice meet
up and throw hands?
So, you didn't see that? No. I mean,
there's a video of it. How did you not
see it? I'm going to knock him out.
I'll send it to you.
I'm going to knock him out. Yeah. See na na. N. See,
go in the video then. I just linked you a video. Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, that in itself is sad that
you work but you come on here. It's like
Smokey B. He says he's got all this
money yet. I I was off of YouTube for eight days.
Yeah, I was off of YouTube for eight
days, but I came on um live streams
occasionally and it was the same people.
It just shows they've got no life. Even
if they've got like a job, right? Even
if they've got a job and they've got
money, that doesn't mean they've got a
life. That is facts right there. Because
anyone that's got [ __ ] going on doesn't
come on here. They can't take a day off
of YouTube. So at the end of the day,
even if they have a job and you know
they have money, they ain't got a life.
They ain't got a [ __ ] life,
you know. Nah, no, no, no, no. These
people ain't got a life.
These people ain't got a [ __ ] life.
Just click on the video. Can you just
watch it? It's not even long. Just watch it.
I'm going to knock him out.
Well, I'm going to knock him out. Go on.
Making money. I've got money.
I've got money. Terry,
I've got money. Matey,
go and watch the video.
You want me to play it on the TV? [Laughter]
Do you remember me and you had a fight over YouTube? Remember?
Me and you had a fight over you. Oh, how
much money do I have then?
How much money do I have? Hm.
How much money do I have then? Gone. Oh,
if I'm How much money do I have? You
don't know how much I have,
do you? Come on.
I've got more money than the virgin.
There we go.
The skinned version in the bed sit with
no bed and no [ __ ] money in it. [Laughter] Yeah. One sec. [Applause]
13 grand is nothing.
What do you think? 13 grand is worth
sitting in a bedsit for 3 years. No
life, no no life experience, no
restaurants, no designer clothes. You
think 30 grand saving for 3 years is any
kind of money? Are you having a wank?
That's [ __ ] nothing. You crazy bastard,
mate. I used to spend three, four grand
a month. It's absolutely [ __ ] all. Why
are you going on like that's a lot of
money? You think 13 grand to have saved
for 3 years is a lot of money, bro? You
really think that's a lot of money? To
have had no life experiences
for [ __ ] 3 years,
you know? grand as [ __ ] all. Listen,
listen, bro. If he's got all this money,
why has he got no life experiences? Why
didn't he go abroad until he was 30? No
designer clothes. Why is he living like
a poor person if he's got all this
money? It doesn't add up. Because he had
nothing for them three years, you know,
to be able to get that 13 grand. 13
grand. [ __ ] all. If I had to sit in my
bedsit with no bed and no money in it
for three years to get 13 grand, I would
tell you to [ __ ] off. I'm not sitting
like a [ __ ] skin virgin in a bedit
with no bed in it, wasting my life for
the sake of 13 grand. Are you [ __ ]
crazy, mate? I wouldn't even have traded
it for a year of my life experiences.
Terry, how much do you think I spent in a year? How?
Listen, bro. How much money do you think
I used to spend in a year when I used to
go gambling, traveling? Mate, I wouldn't
trade a year for 13 grand, let alone
[ __ ] 3 years
in a [ __ ] stinky shitty bed with no
bed in it for 13 grand.
Like, seriously, mate. Seriously? No.
Hey, did you watch the video bubble?
For some reason, my microphone's not
working on any of the apps.
I don't [ __ ] know why, bro. I really
don't know why.
Like, it don't let me send voice notes.
It doesn't let me It doesn't let me use
microphone on any apps. I've I've
tried searching for solutions. I've tried everything, you know.
Did you watch my video?
I'm going to climb this guy out.
Anyways, did you watch my video?
What did you think of it? Now you tell
me what I done wrong in their messages.
I'm all for it, bro. I'm open. You tell
I know I I I couldn't speak in the um on
the screen recorder. I don't know why
they didn't let me, but it does let me.
So, what did I do wrong? Tell me what I done wrong.
I think they solid combos, mate.
I think they were solid.
Don't know about you.
Did you watch the video?
I never spoke about getting someone
pregnant and having babies. Made up.
Did you watch the video?
Come on, Ricky Mingden. Tell us what
I've done wrong.
Tell me what I've done wrong. I'd love to know.
What did I do wrong? I'm waiting.
Come on. The comments are open.
I think they were good combos.
So, am I lying when I'm saying I've been led on?
No. Go on. Tell me. Did you watch my video?
Tell me what I've done wrong in them combos.
Wait, what have I've done wrong? Nothing.
So, there we go.
There we [ __ ] go. Come on.
Yeah. Tell me. Tell me what I've done wrong. Go on.
Monty man said to me, "Fuck off." I said
I'll do you in
I'll do you in Connor. Yeah.
Anyways, did you watch the video with the messages?
What did I do wrong?
Come on, Baba. What did I do wrong? What's madness?
But they say I'm the problem. I'd love
to know what I done wrong, you know.
He's mad in he'll
meet someone. So they say
I'm not so sure about that bubble.
I'm not so sure all women aren't the same either.
Yeah, I cold approached all them people
by the way. Well, they were all from approaches.
Can you tell me what you think about the
messages? You keep ignoring my question.
Stop ignoring me.
That rice is trying to give me [ __ ]
cheek. I can [ __ ] get Kaye off him
any [ __ ] time.
Why do you think they're crazy? Huh?
Why are they crazy, bro?
Weird, isn't it?
But they say you can meet someone on
Reddit. They say you can just get laid on Reddit.
I'm not so sure. Uh People
on Reddit say you can meet someone,
talk to women in person, but all of
their messages were from approaches. So yeah,
would you say them women led me on on
the messages bubble? Definitely
definitely let me hold it. cover out.
Well, at least Monty's over Natalie now, is it? Yeah.
I've never known someone to lose
everything over YouTube.
I've never known it. But Monty, he's the only one
that can lose everything over YouTube.
You would have thought a normal person
would have just got off of it. I'm sure
the skinned virgin in the bedset would
get off YouTube if he was going to
[ __ ] lose. Well, he doesn't have
anything to lose to be honest. [ __ ]
virgin, but um you know, hypothetically,
if he had something to lose, I'm sure if
he lost it, he'd get off YouTube.
He just won't get off it. Will he just
won't get off YouTube?
No. My mom didn't have to move because
of YouTube. My mom was moving anyways. Try again.
Try again. Nope. He wanted to move anyways. So,
he still won't get off of YouTube. Still
won't get off of YouTube, lad. [Laughter]
You would never get on YouTube. No.
Yeah. And I went to your area and you did nothing.
You don't [ __ ] you little wimp. Yeah. [Laughter]
I went to your area and you didn't show
up cuz you're a [ __ ]
Cuz you're a [ __ ] boy.
You knew you was going to get [ __ ] up.
I can't believe you actually think 13
grand is a lot of money. It's [ __ ]
That is nothing, mate.
That is nothing.
So when I was showing money, I was
[ __ ] living the life. Designer
clothes, gambling. I weren't stuck in a
shitty out of London bedsit with no bed
in it. Do you understand terror? I
weren't sat there in an outer London
shitty bed sit with no bed like I got
money when I don't cuz I've got a poxy
small pocket change of 13 grand which
ain't [ __ ] you know what I'm saying mate
I weren't sat there in a bedroom with a
fat ugly girlfriend with no bed
designer clothes restaurants
I didn't I didn't need to save for 3
years I'd rather [ __ ] live with my
mom than live in a shitty out of London
beds in it with no bed in it.
I'd rather that than live in a [ __ ] council bedsit,
you know. That's worse living in a
council bedsit with no money in it. No
bed, no money in it. [ __ ] that, son. Nah.
>> Nope. I'm not broke at all. Still got
money. You don't know what I have. Ah,
that's what I love. You don't know how
much money I have. That's the funniest
thing about it is you act like you know people's lives,
you know, but you don't.
It doesn't matter. I've still got money.
You don't know how much money I have.
Da da da da da da da da da da. You don't
know how much money I have.
So yeah, but what I'm trying to say is I
was living the life designer clothes. I
wasn't sat in a bedsit.
That's the difference.
Sat a bed sit with no [ __ ] bed, no
money in it.
So yeah, no bed, no money in it.
No, no, no, no, no. You say 13 grand's a
lot, but it wouldn't even last 6 months.
You You think about what you're saying.
You're saying 13 grand is a lot of
money, yet it wouldn't even last 6 months.
If you're the age of like 24, 25, 26, it
would even last.
Uh, it would not last. Um,
you know how much money I went through
in one month before?
Thousands, mate. [ __ ] thousands.
It's not a lot of money. Trust me, it's
not a lifechanging amount of money the
way you people are making it out to me.
No [ __ ] way you you
um well, I showed him money for over a
year and he couldn't show anything.
So that just goes to show he didn't have
it for a year cuz he had to save
you. So you wait, so you think that's an
achievement? Saving 13 grand for 3 years
and having no bed, no life experiences,
didn't go abroad until he was 30. You
You seem to think that's a win. Do you
not understand the meaning of [ __ ]
life is to be lived? He couldn't [ __ ]
go abroad before 30 cuz he couldn't
afford it. That's I'm not I'm not taking
a piss. Like you think I'm taking a
piss. I'm generally not taking a piss.
I'm being honest. He He couldn't afford
it. He just wasn't in he didn't have the finances
to be able to afford it. And that's
absolutely fine. That's absolutely okay
not to be able to afford it. You know,
that's it, mate. That's [ __ ] well it.
So, you try living a life of that money
that you showed and see how quickly it goes.
You know, I could show money cuz I was
getting over three grand a month.
over getting getting over three grand a
month and I was winning money all the
time. So, I could very much show that
money a year later. You won't be able
to. And that's what it is. Show that
money in 6 months time. I think that's a
that's a that's a fair point. Show that
money in 6 months time. Live your life
right for 6 months, whatever it is. Uh
just a good life. Show that money back
in six months and I'll say, "Okay, yeah, you're right."
So yeah, you don't know how much money I
get and you don't know how much money I have. So yeah,
that's beer money for most people.
That's beer money. What the [ __ ] are you
talking about? Beer money.h.
You don't know how much money I have and
you don't know how much money I get. Try
again. But yeah, you come back in 6
months with the same amount of money.
Then I'll be like, "Okay, fair [ __ ]
enough." Okay, so how much money do I
have now then?
How much money do I have now? So what?
You drink £1,200 in beer? I think someone's exaggerating.
I think someone's exaggerating, mate.
What? £1,200 a month for beer? Yeah.
£1,200 a month you spend on beer?
Really? I ain't drunk for like a month
to be fair. I don't really drink
anymore. Can't afford it. Got the money.
Just don't want to. Simple.
Cuz I was going out drinking to talk to
like Well, part of it was approaching
women even though I didn't need to and I
don't bother with them anymore. So,
yeah, of course you do. Yeah, of course
Really? Really? Uh-huh.
Really? So, you spend more than £300
every week going out? Yeah, of course
you do. No, you [ __ ] don't. No, you
No, you do not. Stop talking [ __ ]
What's every weekend?
Someone's telling fibs.
Someone's telling fibbies.
Someone's selling fib. Someone's selling fibbies.
Yeah, that's because you're a [ __ ] cokehead.
Yeah, that's nothing to be proud of
being a cokehead.
If I go out on Saturday or whatever,
I'll probably spend
80 120. But I mean, that's just drinks.
Obviously, I get a haircut. That's
expensive. But probably like doing it
every week, maybe it's like 80 to about
150. That's how much I spend.
What? You actually waste your money on cocaine? Wow. Wow, that's crazy. Very crazy.
You just took your habit out, matey. Yeah.
Nothing to be proud of doing cocaine. No.
Why did you do cocaine?
Why do you do cocaine?
Why don't you sublet? Huh?
Terry, why don't you sublet
Why don't you um sublet
rejected? said, "But I've been with more
women than you."
I've actually been with more women than you, matey.
Yeah, but But would you stop if you
could? You would if you could.
Sure you would if you could. Huh? Yeah, man.
Reddit is [ __ ] addicting. Nah,
you would illegally sublet. I think
you're telling me you wouldn't illegally
sublet even if you could. Wish you would [ __ ]
Yeah, but if you did and you had a
chance to, you wouldn't it?
Yeah, you would if you um
Reddit mods are power hungry.
No, it's not how I lost it. None of
these people made me lose that. No, none
of these people made me lose that. They
were trying to get them the house back
for years, mate. If somebody got my
income stopped, somebody would be
getting killed. That's not how I lost
it. It was nothing to do with these
people. The landlord was trying to get
it back for ages since people since my
mom left. And they say and they say that
they done it to try and get a reaction.
They never got my income stopped because
I would have killed someone if they did.
I told them the story and because they
reported me and it never worked, they
tried to make it seem like they got my
money stopped. No, they did not. No,
Because how long did I'm not going to
get into it anyways, bro? Because it's
they if somebody got my money stopped,
somebody would be getting killed. Like
any normal person would be doing that.
So, they might have sent them letters.
They might have reported, but mate, they
did not get my money stopped. The
landlord was trying to get it back for
years. Literally from the very very
[ __ ] start they were [ __ ] sending
letters and all sorts and they [ __ ]
took it to cool and rare rare. I'm not
getting into it anyways, bro. It's ridiculous.
What the [ __ ] man?
And why is it why is telling the woman
I'm a landlord hilarious when I
literally was a landlord? I wasn't
lying, was I? So,
no. again. They never got my money
stopped again. You're not going to get a
reaction. You keep telling yourself
that, bro. But you never These people
never got my money stopped. They didn't.
They're saying that to try and get a
reaction. It's not going to work. You
know, you never got my money stopped.
Cuz if you got my money stopped, why did
it take three and a half years for you
to get my money stopped? Wouldn't have
it happened a lot sooner than that. You
never got my money stopped. If anyone
got my money stopped, I would have
killed one of these people on here. I
would have killed them. Trust me. And
you can send that to the police. Trust
me, I wouldn't be so calm if somebody
got my money stopped because it never happened.
Believe you me, somebody would have been
getting killed if they if they [ __ ]
with any part of my money. Believe that,
bro. That is that is serious [ __ ] But
it never bothered me because they never
got my money stopped. Simple. That's it.
Anyways, we're not talking about that. Sorry.
So yeah, but anyways, that's I put the
messages out there anyways to show what
they like and what they do. So that's that.
Is that the only thing you took into
that video? Is that the only thing you
got out of that video? Is me saying I'm
a landlord? [ __ ] sake, bro.
Is that the only thing you took out of it? So yeah. Yeah,
that's strange. That's the only thing
you took out of it to be fair.
That's not the only thing that was
[ __ ] shown, bro. Like what the [ __ ]
Is that the only thing?
Yeah, I can swear to God on anyone's
people got my money stopped. Believe it,
don't believe it. That's up to you, bro.
I'm not asked.
Truck me. You saw what I done on to
nonslegs when they tried to get £180 of
my money stopped. I had the [ __ ]
running. I'm not a fighter. I'm running
to the place.
And he stopped going to his area for
like he stopped going he stopped going to um
these events for a whole month and that
was over £180. Sincerely believe me when
I tell you if somebody got my money
stopped they would be getting killed.
believe that, bro, because look what
happened over the benefit stuff.
I said, "Yeah, [ __ ] that. That was the
final straw, bro." I was like, "You
[ __ ] virgin cunt." You [ __ ] made
made you stop going to them events,
didn't I? You weren't so big then, was
you? You [ __ ] ugly virgin [ __ ] You
in the skin bed sit, you know? Oh, bro,
I don't need to say his name. He knows
exactly who I'm talking about. So, I'm
smart. Cuz that's what you people do
when you get your ass a good old
whooping. Listen, this is what you do on
here. When you can't take no more and
you get your ass a good old whooping,
you're so much of a loser that you have
to go to the police. The bullying is so
bad. I'm the fighter. Please. The
bullying was that bad to go to the
police. You [ __ ] virgin punk. Yeah.
You got to [ __ ] with me or you skin
punk. You know what I mean?
I had you going to the police. The
bullying was that bad. You couldn't take
it. You were so much of a loser. You had
to go to the police. You [ __ ] loser.
You got bullied.
You [ __ ] bullied loser. You couldn't
take it. I ran into the place. I'm not a
fighter. I'm autistic. I'm not a
fighter. If anybody was not unbiased,
they would see how the guy didn't win.
But you're all biased. And that was £180.
And I was £180.
>> Yeah. Well, I didn't go running to the
police saying I'm not a fighter. I've got autism.
I mean, we've got somebody on YouTube
that [ __ ] does videos of me every
day. Even though we went to the police
screaming and crying he wasn't a
fighter. Cried to the police that he was
not a fighter.
I don't know how [ __ ] Terry can come
on here. When I went to his area and he
didn't show up, but everyone's got
different rules, don't they, mate? One
rule for one, one rule for another. I
went to Ty's area and he didn't show up.
But again, that doesn't suit you. So,
is that the only thing you took from the
women video? I knew my struggles would
get dismissed, but I mean it's out there
anyways. So, you know,
You know, so that's the only thing you
took out the video.
Come on, Ricky Millin. Where's the baby
talk? You [ __ ] white knight simp hunt
c hunt. You [ __ ] poverty with hull
wanker. Little simp. Where's the baby
talk in any of them [ __ ] messages?
You [ __ ] white knight virgin.
Yeah, I mean he he could he could
comment on it because apparently we talk
about babies and making babies. Now I
might be blind, but I don't see any baby
talking any of them messages. It's just
another white night excuse to stick up
for women, which is the whole point of the video.
It's because I knew none of their
messages can get critiqued. Not any of
them. And that's why I said anyone's
welcome. everyone's as long as you're
not hating and projecting, you can give
an opinion and no one can do it because
there's nothing they can say about the
messages. It's simple, you know. Um, so
that's that's why I don't bother trying
anymore. Got the money, can go out
whenever I want. But nah, enough is enough, mate.
Enough is a [ __ ] enough, you know?
That is that's mad.
After that [ __ ] three weeks ago,
spending that 600 pound and getting 10
numbers and not a date. I was like,
"Nah, that is me done. Done.
That is me done."
I would use a [ __ ] escort every
month, but I just don't want to. And I
don't have really much of a sex drive anymore. So, that's it.
Yeah, I need to give up for like at
least 6 months.
6 to 8 months. I think so. Going to
Thailand next month anyway. So, won't
get any of that [ __ ] there. Simple.
Won't get any of that [ __ ] over there.
But Ricky, I want you to comment. You
[ __ ] hull wanker
living in [ __ ] poverty, mate.
You know, he lives in Hull. So, yeah. That's it.
People need to stop defending women.
There's no messages there that could be
critiqued. And if there is, critique
them. It shows what they're like. It
shows what they're about. So that's it.
But like I said, it will probably get dismissed. But
um yeah, cuz Yeah, it is. Yeah.
Yeah. I won't, bro. I won't. I won't.
I've already been on a plane
without any panic attacks, so Yeah.
So, yeah, we're at it. Pretty much. Yeah, man.
going to do a football bet yesterday,
but I didn't bother.
Yeah, I can't believe it either because
it never happened. You're still using
the word scene. Cringe. Get a new word.
That's so cringe and common. Scenes. It
makes you sound like a [ __ ]
You're still using them cringy words. Scenes.
Bro, stop it. It's cringe as [ __ ] Stop
using words like that, bro. It's cringe scenes.
You need to You need to think of some
new words, bro.
[ __ ] hell. Need to think of some new
words for real.
In your [ __ ] mind, bro. You know.
No, I messaged her um a few months ago
saying, "Let me come and slap you up in
front of your boyfriend." It was back. I
said, "I'll come to you next Thursday."
And I kept off YouTube. The [ __ ] went
silent, bro. She ain't about nothing,
man. Oh, her [ __ ] dad. They know
they'd get [ __ ] up.
They know they will get [ __ ] up, bro.
You ain't about that life. And I said
I'll do it in front of your boyfriend as
well. I'm not going to do it unless your
boyfriend's there because I don't like
white knights to begin with. So yeah.
Yeah. I mean money doesn't ban anyone
because you can't read what they're
saying. He doesn't even realize they're
taking the piss out of him.
Yeah. He doesn't even realize. That's
how dumb he is.
Well, maybe he doesn't read like maybe
he doesn't go in the comments anymore.
He can't read them anyways. So yeah.
I said, "Let me come next week,
Thursday, Friday. I'll slap you up in
front of your boyfriend." I think
it's so toxic.
So [ __ ] toxic, bro. Was it
last night? Thought you don't go on
there much. I thought you don't watch
anyone but me.
You slipped up there, didn't you?
Didn't you, Terry? You slipped up there, son. Yeah.
They started a court case with that house like
it was not when was it? Not last summer.
No, no, no.
Yeah, it was last summer. They started
sticking [ __ ] on the [ __ ] door and that
had nothing to do with Red Star. Red
Star didn't know anything about it.
So trust me, they never got my money stopped, mate.
Because one of these people would have paid
and obviously it wouldn't have been Red
Star. It would have been because
obviously he would never meet me because
he's a coward.
Yeah. The dating scene is uh toxic, bro. Toxic.
Let me see.
Oh, [ __ ] sake.
I need to go soon. Yep.
It was so awkward doing that video
without audio, but it doesn't work.
But you know the Reddit mods, Terry,
they're very power hungry.
You know, you you to sit on a site all
day having to control it, you've got to
be a sad.
You've got to be a sad.
You would even agree there, would it?
Yeah. I had to sit on a [ __ ] diet
all day controlling it. Yeah, it's sad.
They're very very power hungry. These
mods probably 40
probably never kissed a woman, never
been laid probably. And they take their
frustration out on you and they feel
powerful because they can ban you and
you can do nothing about it. Yeah.
Yeah, basically this
sad in a way, huh?
Ricky Milling, where are you? I want you
to critique my messages.
You'd have a hard time doing that, mate.
You'd have a hard time doing that.
They ban people to feel powerful though, Terry.
They go mad. They need that power. [ __ ]
Yeah. No, they do sit on a site all day.
How do you think they ban people?
I mean, no, they are sad.
The mods. So, you're telling me the mods
don't sit on Reddit all day every day? Yeah.
Do you remember USA? Is he
[ __ ] [ __ ] bricks, bro? [ __ ] shack bricks.
Yeah, cuz they're sados. Anyone that
needs to sit on a website controlling
it, it's sad whether they get paid or
they don't get paid.
It's sad. It's [ __ ] sad.
[ __ ] sitting on a site all day
[ __ ] modding it. That is sad. Whether
they don't whether they get paid or not, it's sad, you know.
I think Virgin Boy needs to [ __ ] come
Birmingham with me.
I can't believe he's going to be [ __ ]
I can't believe he's 31 and he's never
had sex. [ __ ] hell.
I don't feel that bad. I can't believe
he's never been laid. Can't believe he's
never had it, Terry. You know,
I can't believe like
he's never going to lose it. Never going
to pop it. Pop that V card. And before
you say he's got a girlfriend, [ __ ] off.
Showing a [ __ ] ugly the wolf a few
times in pictures does not prove you've
had sex. Me, I proved I've had sex.
Everyone Everyone seen my little porno.
Everyone's seen my porno. So,
you know what I mean? Um, Terry,
I've actually proved I've had sex. He
hasn't. He's just shown a [ __ ]
disabled. The wolf.
Yeah, I've already had a girlfriend and
Yeah, he has a girlfriend. Okay, I
proved I've had sex. So, which one's
more believable? Someone that's had that
has a girlfriend or someone that's
proved they've had sex?
I mean, it's it's somebody that's proved
they've had sex
than somebody that's got a girlfriend,
you know, mate. Just because he's got a
disabled girlfriend, it doesn't mean he
sleeps with her. She's disabled. She
wouldn't even need them needs in the relationship.
But you know what looks even more
stupid? When someone's proved to you
they've had sex and you're still telling
them that they're a virgin. you know
that he is a virgin. Even though he
shows an ugly dwarf, he is still a
virgin. There's absolutely no proof that
he has had sex. There is proof that I've
I have proved that I've had sex. I've
shown me in hotel rooms with [ __ ] uh
women multiple times.
I mean, that weren't paid for. He has
never proved you've had sex. And showing
a disabled girl does not prove he's had
sex. I want to see a porno. He can't do
that because he's [ __ ] little tiny
dick don't go up. Terry, trust me. I
know the virgin better than he knows himself.
I know that skin virgin better than he
knows his [ __ ] himself, mate.
He's never had it, mate. He's never had
it. Okay. Do you want me to put a video up?
Well, it does prove it cuz I was lying
in bed next to the women.
You're trying to tell me that skin pun
has had sex cuz he shows a disabled girl
that can't consent a couple of times.
Are you Are you mugging me off? Are you
[ __ ] mugging me off, mate? He's so
obviously a virgin,
bro. I don't want I would rather have no
girlfriend than have that ugly thing.
And I've had a girlfriend before and I'd
rather have no girlfriend than have
that. I don't want that ugly thing. I'd
rather have nothing. That is a disabled
the wolf. That's not a girlfriend. I
don't hate that. Trust me, I wouldn't
get with that if that was the last thing
on earth. I don't target disabled girls.
Believe you me, I don't hate it. He can
keep her. He can keep the dwolf that
doesn't give him sex. I don't want that.
Why would I want to get with a disabled wolf?
that doesn't give me sex and keeps me a
virgin. I'd rather not have anything.
I wouldn't I'd rather have nothing than
a disabled girl that doesn't give me
sex. And that's why I'm still a virgin at 31
being that 31year-old virgin. And you
can tell he's a virgin as well because
how he goes on about my sloppy seconds.
He has not had sex. I swear my dead dad
that that virgin has never had sex and
that's why he used to call me a virgin
in the past because he's the biggest one
himself. So he knows all the telltale
signs because he's the biggest one. He's
the biggest virgin. When I used to meet
him, I used to say, "Oh, I've had sex
with this escort. I've had sex with that
escort." And he wouldn't believe it. And
it's cuz he's never had it. He's still a
virgin. And that's how and that's where
the the nickname come from. Virgin boy
because he obviously is a virgin,
you know, virgin boy. Skin in a bed sit
with no bed and nobody. It's it's it's a
thing. Virgin boy, he will always be a
virgin. It's always proves he has
physically had sex in my eyes. He's
always that skinned virgin in the bedit.
And yes, 13 grand is absolutely skint if
you want to ask me, son. You know. Yeah.
Yeah. Why? Because why not? It's funny.
I don't hate that someone's in a bed sit
with no bed with a disabled girl. Like,
he hates his girlfriend so much that he
clings on to all the other women that
I've been with. He's not even happy with
her. You know, I don't want a [ __ ]
disabled girl that keeps me a virgin.
Why the [ __ ] would I hate that son?
You know, he's a [ __ ] skin [ __ ] with
an ugly disabled girl. I'd rather have nothing.
I would rather have nothing, son.
Virgin boy skin in a bed sit with no
money, no bed in it. Think about it,
bro. I'm younger than him. Got more
money than him. Been with more women
than him. Designed the clothes, better
life than him. So I can sit there and
say, "Skint virgin in the bed. Sit with
no bed in it." cuz it's the truth. He's
a big big virgin,
you know. And you want to talk about
convincing things, mate. You showing
ugly the wolf ain't convincing anyone
that you've had sex. Trust me, son. So yeah,
that's it. Sunshine. Rain of sunshine, mate.
Do you reckon Virgin boy will ever lose
it? Do you reckon he'll ever get laid?
Do you reckon he'll ever lose it? I
don't think his ugly face will allow it, mate,
you know. But look at you, Terry. You're
48 and you're still a virgin and you
can't even afford a new pair of trainers
and you're a [ __ ]
You're a [ __ ] that can't even afford a
new pair of trainers. That's the [ __ ] madness.
That's the [ __ ] madness, mate.
You know, you haven't had more
girlfriends than me. I've been with way
more women than you. More women than
you. More women than the skinned virgin
in a bed sit with no bed, no money in
it. Ricky Milling, where the [ __ ] are
you? Where the [ __ ] are you? You [ __ ]
Ricky Milling, where the [ __ ] are you?
Where's the baby talk? You [ __ ] white
knight [ __ ] You white whole little virgin [ __ ]
Hey, did you see that picture that you
put up trying to flex your skinny ass arms?
You know, you [ __ ] whole white knight
[ __ ] ruining a [ __ ] date game for us, son. You know,
you know, mate. Yeah.
They got a thumbs up already. So, come
on, white knight. Come on. What you got? Go on.
Critique it. Critique it, you [ __ ]
But guess what kills Virgin Boy? That he
would never sleep with the women that
I've slept with. And that kills him. And
there's actual proof that it kills him.
He's jealous of USA Izzy. He's jealous
of normal Izzy. He's jealous of Sig
because he will never be able to get any
of them women ever. And they're not
perfect. They're not. They're just But
when you compare it to who he's with,
um, you know, I've never gone on about
his girlfriend. I would never get with
his girlfriend. She's [ __ ] ugly. Fat and ugly.
He goes on about my sloppy seconds,
though, cuz he's jealous.
Don't know why though. They're not even
that good. But obviously, compared to
compared to Sarah, Terry, anything looks
good, you know? Anything looks [ __ ] good, mate.
You know, anything looks good. But yeah,
the messages. Um, now to be fair, what I
was going to go over the message one by
one by one,
you know, like saying, "Oh, this
happened, that happened, when it
happened, do I think it's right, do I
think it's wrong?"
Um, you know, that kind of stuff. And to
be fair, when you've messaged one and
they've not replied, have they led you
on? No. Have they done anything bad?
Not really. But it goes against what
people say about how they go for
personality and ret and they tried to
cover up the fact that they are very
very shallow. Women are more shallow
than men. I mean that just it it just
But that's But have they led you on that
one? No. So, I would have went, you
know, I've got a lot, bro. A lot of messages.
Way more than that.
There was one, there was one from uh
Italy as well.
Um, and she was just a narcissist as
well. But like, I can't talk over them
because it doesn't let me. I don't know
how to talk to women. Well, my messages say otherwise.
My messages say otherwise. And like I
said, anyone's open to critiquing them.
So, I mean, my messages say otherwise,
buddy. And actions speak louder than words.
I mean, there's pretty good
conversations there. There's women that
have agreed to meet and they've
disappeared. So, anything you say is just [ __ ]
My message would prove it.
My messages prove that it made women
agree to meet me and then they've not
met me. So if I was bad at talking to
women, they wouldn't agree to meet me.
So I'm not having this conversation. My
messages prove what I've what I've
wanted to prove, what I've intended to
prove. So that's it. My messages prove
and and I could even show messages where
they've replied to negativity as well.
They've ignored normal messages and
replied to negativity.
Yeah, I lack experience, bro. I don't
need to listen to you. My messages say it all.
If you didn't know how to speak to
women, why have some of these women
agreed to meet you and then backed out?
Because they were trolling you and
leading you on. It's [ __ ] obvious,
you know? So, no matter what you try and
say, my I've got the evidence to back it up.
Yeah. I come across as a desperate dean.
Well, they agreed to me.
Well, they agreed to me. I mean, some of
them didn't even reply back.
So, I I'd love to see them be critiqued.
Like, the comments are not being disabled. So,
good luck with that one.
You know, I want that Ricky Milling to
comment on it. You said about people
talking about babies, about people
talking about See, I can blame women and
I can back it up. I can back it up with
my messages. I can back it up with my
experiences. I can back it up with my
approaches, what they're like. So, at
the end of the day, where are you, Ricky?
So, that's it.
But my messages prove everything you say
to be wrong about, oh, you talk about
babies and you're the problem and
and all of these excuses that you make
for these women time and time and time
and time again. You're running out of
excuses, white night boy. Do you understand? So,
uh, it proves that it's them.
It proves that it's them. And I've got a
lot of I got a lot more messages, too.
I don't know why my mic ain't working on
these apps, but it's not,
which it was. So, yeah.
So, it shows what they're like. It shows
what these women are like.
And also, the ones that never even
replied to begin with,
it's obvious. It's obvious the problem
is them. So [ __ ] obvious. How many
[ __ ] man does someone need a [ __ ] show?
So come on, bro. Where are you, man?
Critique all of their messages. I can
show you more if you want.
So we know now there's no point even
going out and trying, Terry.
There's no point even going out and trying.
Yeah, I'm immature.
Yeah, they're the ones that lead people
on for their own entertainment. And I'm
the one that's immature.
But I'm the one that's immature, yet
they're the ones that lead people on for
their own entertainment.
I don't think I'm as mature as them,
mate. Immature as them. Yeah. Yeah. I
don't think I'm as immature as them.
I've already given up. Oh [ __ ] bro. I
gave up 3 weeks ago.
I gave up three weeks ago, lad. So
can't be bothered. Yeah, no.
Yeah. Well, I seem to carried on some
good combos there.
I seem to carry on some good combos
there. I'm a good texter.
Yeah. So, come on. Hit me with it, bro.
What's going on?
What's the score, Ricky? All the way
from home. You have so many excuses for these women.
Women. It's not women. We've heard your
[ __ ] I've seen your [ __ ] enough [ __ ]
times. Right. And you know, it's there.
You can you can comment. You're not
going to get blocked. You don't need to
go on the skin virgin's page to [ __ ]
[ __ ] with a bed sit with no money. You
can go on this video and we can have it
out, you know, cuz you like to white
knight women. I don't know why it's
never going to get you laid, but you
still white night them anyways. It
doesn't matter. I just, you know,
but yeah, I need to
see how to fix this mic. I don't know
why it's not working on these apps.
I'm going to do a video to Ricky
Milling. Let me make sure he's um not blocked.
I don't think he is. One second
cuz we have to make it fair, you know,
if we're having people come on our channel.
Yeah. Where who's talking about babies, bro?
What do you think I say about women?
uh is the truth. Going by their messages
unless I'm missing something you know
there was an Italian one that I was going to ever
She was a narcissist.
All women are the [ __ ] same.
All the [ __ ] same.
They're all the [ __ ] same.
All women are the [ __ ] same.
Come on, let's have it out, bro. Come on. Yeah,
they're not all the same, but they all
say the same stuff, have the same excuses,
do the same stuff, have the same
mannerisms, but they're not all the same.
But they're not all the same. H, strange.
So, they say the same stuff, do the same
stuff, play the same games, have the same excuses,
but they're not all the same. H danger.
What's the chance of that? So many
similarities, but they're not the same.
I need to do this video to Ricky
Millington. It doesn't stop here, son. I
want you to tell me what the [ __ ] was
wrong with them messages. You know you
little white knight [ __ ] sticking up
for women. You sad bastard. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come
Um. Yeah. It It just makes them look
like an NPC. And it's not even just me.
It's other guys that go approach them.
They get the same stuff. You're too old.
You're too young. Um, you know, um, same
[ __ ] It's They're literally like NPCs.
They're all the same.
They literally are like all the same.
Uh, no, it's not just me. And again, I
put evidence out there. I've shown my
messages, so that proves everything. And
no, it's not just me, bro. I'm a M. I'm
a million times better looking than you,
you little [ __ ] with shitty trainers.
I'm way How can you call me a B when I'm
better looking than you? You little
weasel. You are Listen, bro. Listen,
listen. You are uglier than me. I don't
know why you keep typing over [ __ ] I'm
a million times better looking than
you'll ever be. I can afford new
trainers. You have nothing on me, bro.
You know what I'm saying?
Well, I've got a bone to pick with you,
Stephen. What the [ __ ] is going on in them messages?
What the [ __ ] is going on in that video,
son? Cuz there was no babies mentioned,
there was no kids mentioned, and they
all [ __ ] strung me on, you know?
Oh, you're boring. Get a timeout.
Steven Howard, what the [ __ ] is going on
in them messages? Huh?
No. Go on. I want to know why the [ __ ]
these women are [ __ ] leading me on.
That's what I want to [ __ ] know. So,
I'm [ __ ] going mad. [ __ ] knows why.
Too much caffeine or some [ __ ] You said
that I talk about babies. You say that I
[ __ ] it up. Well, the messages say
otherwise. What's the [ __ ] problem?
What is the [ __ ] problem with them
[ __ ] messages? The comments are open
to anyone to comment.
What? What? What? What? What is it,
Stephen Howard? So, can I now say that
they're all the [ __ ] same? Can I am I
can I sit there and then and now say
that these women are all the same?
I think I'm in my rights now to say that
they're all the [ __ ] same. If you're
not going to comment and you're not
going to critique my [ __ ]
all right, I'm going to say that they're
all the [ __ ] same.
All these women are the [ __ ] same.
And I'm going to say it with a big fat a
mate after the [ __ ] ep.
Steven Howard, this is [ __ ] madness.
Uh, I was a landlord and they don't know
a liar because I didn't lie,
you know. So, I've got a bone to pick
with that [ __ ] Ricky Millon. You
[ __ ] white knight trying to say that
people talk about [ __ ] babies and
stuff. This is why you're still a whole
virgin. This is why you're still a
virgin stuck in hull and you're never
going to leave it. And I'll [ __ ] say
to your [ __ ] face cap. I've had
enough of going on your sitting all
comments on the skinned virgin in the
shitty bed suit with no you know son.
Right. Yeah. I love you know mate that
I've got more money than you and your
boyfriend and I've got more experience
than you and your gay boyfriend. Right.
That's not the [ __ ] You told me that
I was talking about [ __ ] kids. Having
kids with people that I don't know.
Come on. I want to hear it. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Let's [ __ ] have you. Come on with all
of your excuses.
Running out of excuses now, aren't you?
I've got a lot more messages if you want
to see them.
[ __ ] a lot of you.
You're big enough when you're [ __ ]
commenting on your gay boyfriend's
[ __ ] messages. Bro, listen. £13,000
does nothing. You know what I want? The
better life. I want the better life.
Better looks, better money, better
women, better travel. I don't give a
[ __ ] about 13 grand, lad.
You know, I don't give a [ __ ] about a
shitty 13 grand. I want a better looks
and a better life game. And £13,000
is nothing to not do anything for 3 years,
mate. That is nothing to say for Listen,
bro. I used to go through about £6,000 a
month. £13,000 is nothing to say for 3
years. Do you understand, S?
He also won the shittest life game. He
also won the no bed game with no money
in it. S
all the time. Proper holidays. Okay.
Yeah. I went abroad when I was 23.
He went abroad when he was 31.
And he's woman is disabled. He's got a disabled woman.
That's That wolf is not a [ __ ] woman.
Listen, you northern [ __ ] I know that
where you live up north, you [ __ ]
northerner. All the birds are [ __ ]
ugly. But let me tell you where I'm
from. Most people wouldn't get with that
if you [ __ ] pay them.
That is not a [ __ ] woman. And also I
went abroad eight years before him. But
he's got all this money. You northerners.
You [ __ ] ugly northerners. And bro,
don't try and sit there and say you will
do me in. I will slap the northern out
of you. You silly [ __ ] You silly
[ __ ] Norban [ __ ] Yeah, bro. He goes
on holidays eight years after me. That's
how skint he is. He had to go he had to
copy my holidays eight years after me
because he's a skinned virgin hand with
an A. I mean, think about it. Who the
[ __ ] goes abroad when they're 31? People
that can't afford it. You know, I'm
going a bit [ __ ] mad here. I'm
[ __ ] aware, son. But the day someone
goes abroad when they're 31, it's cuz
they ain't got the money to do it in their 20ies,
sunshine. You understand? And I'd rather
have no woman than have an ugly the wolf
that don't give me sex like him. Which
is why he's still a big virgin. I'm
going to I'm going to throw him. I'm
going to pick him up and I'm going to
throw him. You little virgin.
You know what I'm saying? If he had sex
with someone like that, it would be
classed as rape, mate. So, I'm telling
you, he's a [ __ ] virgin.
Yeah. I don't have money. Okay, mate. I
don't have money. Okay. You know so much
about me, don't you, son? Am I Am I in a
bed sit with no bed, no money in the
mate? Am I able? Okay. Yeah, man.
Well, I need to I've got a bone to pick
with that Ricky, mate. So, what do you
think of the message, Steven Howard?
Now, do you understand where I'm coming
from with these [ __ ] women?
You know what I'm saying? Now, now do
you understand, bro? Now that you [ __ ] understand. You know,
you people don't bully no one. You bully yourselves.
We're going to time these haters out,
man. They're not giving an opinion on
[ __ ] anything here.
So, there you go. You saw the um you saw
the message of Steven Howard.
So, I've got a bone to pick with that
[ __ ] Ricky Milling.
It's It is. Yeah, but you know, they are
definitely the problem. Women are
definitely the problem. You critique any
of them [ __ ] messages, bro. And I'll
be here all day listening to it, but you
can't. So, you make up stuff cuz in your
little head, you think defending women
is going to get you laid.
No, no, no. But seriously, Steven, what
was wrong with the messages? You know
what was wrong with the messages? Nothing.
From what I can see, from what you can see.
We agreed to meet and look, there's a beard.
I've got a bone to pick without [ __ ]
Ricky Millington. And let me let me let
me let me start by saying this. I've got
more money than both of you combined and
I've got more life experience than both
of you [ __ ] combined. So if you want
to sit there and start [ __ ] talking
[ __ ] [ __ ] about what people have and
what don't have, mate, you live in hell.
You're in no place to talk about anyone, son.
Yeah, but it proves that it's them
that's the problem.
That's what I'm saying. It proves that
they are the problem. That's what I'm
saying. That's the whole point. you. No
one can critique them.
So Ricky Milling, please feel free to
comment, son. Please do, mate. Please
do. And I've caught you enough time on
the Virgin Channel skinting the bed suit
with no bed, no money in it. Talking
about people having money, mate. I've
got more money than both of you. I got
more life experience than both of you.
Talking about money, eh? Don't you live
in a hole? You know,
and that video was kind of dedicated to
you because you were making excuses that
people was talking about having babies
with people. Now, I don't see any babies mentioned there,
you know. So, what was the excuse then
with them messages, Rickster? You know, [ __ ] excuses.
I don't know why they make excuses and
just say they're not interested in this
country and they've got unrealistic
standards because it's a front. It's a cover.
You don't understand. It's a front. It's
a cover. They're never going to admit women's wrongdoings.
So they make excuses. Oh, you've got a
bad personality. You're this. Oh, we go for personality.
When they are even more shallow than [ __ ] men,
you know, the difference between getting
with you and not getting with you could
be something as simple as you having a
beard, you having blue eyes and not
green eyes. It could be that [ __ ] pathetic, you know. Yeah.
And that's it, bro.
Little hole wanker.
Did you put a thumbs up on the video?
Cuz someone put a thumbs up on it. It
was sweet, wasn't it? And they were all
women I approached as well.
So now do you kind of understand what
they're actually like?
Yeah, she's not looking to date right
now yet. She was talking to me and
leading me on. But yeah, they all do the
same thing for people that are
apparently so different. I I know I keep
saying it, you know.
No, I'm banning you cuz you repeat yourself. Bye-bye.
You get banned again. You're banned cuz
you're talking [ __ ] You're just
projecting your montiness onto other people. So,
I'm going to have to do a video to Ricky
Milling. You don't have to go in your
little gay skin boyfriend's channel
anymore talking about people that you
don't [ __ ] know.
You know what I mean?
you you know it's right there. It is
literally right there. You can comment
on it. You don't need to go on your
little nons [ __ ] boyfriends
channel trying to talk about buddy when
you don't know what people have. I have
more money than both of you. I've had
[ __ ] more life experience than
[ __ ] both of you. You know that's it.
So this is why I don't go out trying cuz
that's the only thing that's ever going to happen
is you get led on.
So that's it.
But I mean, how many more times, right,
you have to put yourself on the line in
hopes to find someone that's different?
cuz we've been doing it for years. We
have been doing it for [ __ ] years.
You know, how many times does someone
have to keep putting themselves on the
line to be shown that all women are the same?
Like, it's a general question I'm asking
you, um, Steven Howard, how many times
does someone have to keep doing it till
they realize, oh, women are all the
same? I mean, how many [ __ ] times? That's it.
What? For the rest of our life.
But they were the same all along.
They're all the same. All the [ __ ]
See, you remember when Virgin Boy used
to say, "Oh,
they're not all the same. You don't know
all women." That's literally what he
used to say. "I don't know all women,
yet I've met more women than you will
ever meet. I've been with more women
than you will ever have. And I'm [ __ ]
telling you, [ __ ] that they are all
the [ __ ] same because I've been with
more women than you. I've met more women
than you have.
They're not all the same. You don't know all women.
So, you know, he was a white knight from
from um from the getgo, to be honest.
They don't know all women.
Don't know all women.
Is that a good impersonation of him? You
don't know all women. I [ __ ] know
more women than [ __ ] you, [ __ ]
And I've probably um met women than he
has ever met in his life and will ever
meet. Well, more women than he will ever
meet in his life.
>> You don't know all women.
He don't know all women,
>> you know.
Right. I'm going to put that Ricky
Milling Hunt in his place in a bit. You
better check the video out. And you want
to say, "Oh, how can I call him a virgin
because he's a big virgin and I know him
better than he knows he's [ __ ] self
cunt." Me, I prove I've had sex. So, yeah. Tell me,
I'm going to do a video. Come on. Come
on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
You're not going to come on that night.
Nah, you come on.
Oh, bro, they're all women are all the
same. I know all women. This is what he
used to say. This is what this little
[ __ ] used to say, mate. Yeah, I'll do
a Wait. Oh, you can't even see me. He
used to like get his hands. He's like,
"You don't know all women."
[ __ ] know more women than you, [ __ ]
They don't know all women. They don't
know all women. They're not all the
same. They're not all the same.
Don't know what we mean. You don't know.
That's how he talks. He's a [ __ ]
right? Ricky Millington, what's going on, mate?
Cuz I haven't had a reply,
you know. And and and you want to talk
about how how can I say he's a virgin
cuz he is a [ __ ] virgin [ __ ]
And if he if he went near any if he went
anywhere near that disabled girl
sexually, he would be done cuz she's
disabled. Me, I proved about sex. Don't
say that about me, mate. You know what I'm saying?
More trying to tell people that they're
jealous of holidays people have gone on
eight years before then, you know. Oh,
Jesus Christ, Ricky.
Jesus Christ, Rickster. I can show you
more if you want. You know, we can go all day
cuz I can't see any baby talking any of
them messages, mate. So,
people just just are scared to admit
what women are. Unrealistic standards,
[ __ ] They just they they they
Yeah, they just they're just scared to
say what they are.
Do I guess?
Yeah. Will you? That's nice for you.
That's nice for you, mate.
I can't believe he fancied USA, is he?
So, I'm going to do I've got a bone to
pick with Ricky Millington.
He would literally be locked up if he
went anywhere near that disabled girl
sexually, which is how we know he's a
[ __ ] virgin. Got more money than you.
Got more money than him. Stop talking
about people that you don't [ __ ] know.
You know, no one cares about the
letters, Terry. If you put letters up,
no one no one cares. No one's going to
do anything. No one's asked. You're only
trolling yourself because you're wasting
your time and your money. No one cares.
You're only wasting your time and your
money. No one's bothered.
You can do it again. It's been done
about two times. No one cares. You're
more than welcome to do that. And you're
more than welcome to waste your money.
You're only trolling yourself.
That's absolutely fine. If you want to
waste your little one,
you know. No, they didn't care like last
time. I left last time because I was
having an argument with my mother.
That's why I left. I didn't leave
because of the neighbors and the
neighbors never cared the first time.
So, bro, you can, you know,
you can do posters and whatever.
Uh, that's fine. No one cares. You're
just wasting your own money, money, and
time. So, you're trolling yourself really.
So, you're more than welcome to.
I've got a bone to pick you. That's what
I used to say to these people on Reddit.
Why are you telling people to go out and approach women?
Why the [ __ ] are you telling people to
go out and approach women?
That's where Gregy got the saying from.
I've got a bone to pick with you.
You [ __ ] little hole [ __ ] You little
Yorkshire [ __ ] Yeah, with your little
[ __ ] skinny [ __ ] arms. Where the
[ __ ] are you now, [ __ ] You know, Ricky
[ __ ] Milington. [ __ ] got no
[ __ ] life, [ __ ] That's what your
surname should [ __ ] be.
Yeah. Will you really, mate? Yeah.
Terry, no one believes you're going to
do anything, mate. After last time
when I went to your area, you did nothing.
So, Ricky Millington.
Let's get that mixed up. What's going
on, son? What is really going on?
Because this is getting silly now, mate.
I've seen you slag me off right to your
little gay n boyfriend million times,
right? I need to really come to hull and
do you in mate cuz I'll [ __ ] do it.
You're saying that about me being a
problem. Really? Their messages show
that they're the problem even though
it's a hard [ __ ] pill to [ __ ] swallow.
I'm going I'll come to how do you inmate
seeing you talk a lot of [ __ ]
you know, saying I'm jealous of somebody
going on the same holiday as I went on
eight years after me. I mean, for [ __ ]
sake, have a [ __ ] word with yourself, Millington.
I shouldn't even be doing a video to
this Ricky, but I'm going to because
he's doing my [ __ ] nighting.
He's a He's a hull. He's a He's a He's a hull s.
Imagine living in hull and still
happened to White Knight. That is some
next level desperation.
And I'm going to rip this [ __ ] apart.
I'm going to rip him a new [ __ ] bro.
Imagine living in Hull and still happen
to be a white knight.
I mean, what the [ __ ] is is going on
with your life, son?
You know, I mean, cost you to live in
the most deprived place ever and still
have to white knight.
I'm going to completely [ __ ] own this
[ __ ] I'm going to mang him and tag him.
I said, "Come on. I've done that video
dedicated to you, Ricky." Right? cuz
I've caught you slagging me off behind
your boyfriend's back with a [ __ ] disabled girlfriend. You know,
I really really
don't understand you, mate. Be a man. Come on.
You know, you know you're down bad when
you're you're still white nighting in a
place like [ __ ] Hunt. I mean, for
[ __ ] sake, you could give the women
[ __ ] 10 [ __ ] pound and I'm sure
they'd [ __ ] suck you off.
I mean London is very high maintenance
you know it's [ __ ] very westernized
you know where somewhere like [ __ ]
hull you still having to white night
mate got a b you
know and I'm not even [ __ ] joking bro oh look one comment
Oh, fair enough. Fair enough.
Yeah. Here we go. Here we go. Ah, I see
what you mean now. Oh. Oh, you see what
I mean now? After how many years? They
should have told you first they didn't
want to take things further to you in
advance instead of them prolonging it.
And your text are very polite to thank
you. This is somebody that is not a yes
man that does not come on my channel.
[ __ ] a [ __ ] men to [ __ ] that.
And that is like 1% of it, you know? So
before trying to tell people that
they're the [ __ ] problem, mate. Yeah.
All because someone's a [ __ ] man, you
know. It's it's ridiculous.
And your texts are very polite, too.
Exactly. This is the problem.
Yeah. Which is what I've been trying to
say [ __ ] all along. And that is
nowhere near 10% of it, bro. And don't
forget, I've only had this phone for
like uh less than a year now. And that's
barely 10% of it. But I just thought I'd
just show ones that are So, mate, before
telling people that they're the problem,
you know, and this guy doesn't like me,
he goes on L J and he never goes on
mine. That is what you call an unbiased opinion, you know. So,
no, he's not. His name is Tiger Tiger
and he does never go on my channel. He
doesn't agree with anything I say. So, yeah,
he he's not a yes man. He never goes on
my live stream. He never goes on my
channel ever. But I know who he is. So,
trust me, that is a pretty impartial [ __ ] party, you know? Tiger. Tiger.
Yeah, he doesn't go on my channel. He
doesn't know who I am. He doesn't even
like me for [ __ ] sake.
So, you should have listened before I
had to start showing all of these messages.
But whatever, it is what it is. But I
want this Ricky Milling to come on my
[ __ ] channel. You slag me off behind
my back to your little nons boyfriend
[ __ ] a million times, [ __ ] Yeah, cuz
I've seen you. So what?
Oh, you're boring, bro. You're not going
to anyone's mom's. You're not doing
anything. Shut up. What? 4:00 in the
morning, bro. How far do you live away?
Come on, man. So yeah,
and that's the thing. I mean, there was
one in Italy, but
she was trying to say about how she was
going to but she was still a narcissist.
Anyways, I'm gone.