Yo,
[ __ ] it up.
There we go.
I've got a bone to pick with you. Ricky Mills in
you know that saying is it
h what was that all one comment so that
video got one [ __ ] wow
two but one of them is [ __ ] me. So
I've been sleeping all day.
Did you watch the um
video where I show the messages? Bad, isn't it?
Really bad, huh?
I've been asleep all day, mate.
Just woke up.
Sleeping B's fat.
Yeah. That's why I put the messages out
there anyway, so you have a insight what
I've been [ __ ] dealing with with
these [ __ ] Where the [ __ ] is Ricky
Millington? The [ __ ] son of white knight.
[ __ ] got a bone to pick with him.
I [ __ ] left the comments open for
him. So she talks about people talking
about making [ __ ] babies.
So this is probably why we think all
women are the same. Bob Bills,
they're not the same. They're not the
same. You don't know all women. Not the
>> Is that a good impression?
What the [ __ ] same, huh?
Yeah, right. They're all NPCs. [ __ ] that. So yeah,
that's why I gave up.
Does somebody know how to um fix this? I
can't use my microphone on any app. like
it works on video so the microphone
itself is not broken but when I try to
use it on an app WhatsApp
Facebook it doesn't work and I've tried
everything literally everything
to be fair the phone is [ __ ]
I've got a bone to pick me with you.
That's what I say to people on Reddit
when they try and say getting sex is
easy, [ __ ] liars.
But this ain't getting [ __ ] texted
easy on [ __ ] Reddit. Jesus Christ.
Must be something I'm [ __ ] missing.
They are going up with dating.
They are giving up with it. Ra, there's
no point when women are all the same. Pointless. [ __ ] pointless.
They're all the same. Oh
yeah. That's why I gave up, bro. Cuz
they're all the same. They do the same thing.
Yeah. That's why I gave up.
You can see they're leading on on purpose.
Um, just stringing along.
They're not replying to the first message.
It's all toxic, bro.
But people on Reddit say it's easy. Yeah, right. Yeah, man.
So that's what will happen when you go
out and try.
That's all that would ever happen.
Yeah. I mean, I've tried everything.
I mean, bro, you're talking to me,
someone that's done this non-stop for
four or five years.
I mean, did you not not learn anything
from the video?
I mean, did you not did you you saw the
video, right? Did you not learn anything
from the video?
I even had someone agree with me.
somebody that doesn't even like me, that
doesn't even go on my channel.
And it got two thumbs up, but it got
three, but obviously I was one of them. So So
that's what you took. That's what you um
took out of that video.
Yeah, I got two from got three thumbs up. But
um and these were all from cold approaches.
So you understand why we think women are
all the same now.
Well, go and read them all. You should
go and read them all and come back to
me. It took me time to make that video. So yeah.
Joe's gone quiet as well.
Oh, that virgin's mad
[ __ ] longer than that virgin. He's
[ __ ] mad. He is getting in his little
bed [ __ ] with no bed, no money in it.
Um, when am I going next? Out next. I've
literally told you I've given up. So, never.
I've literally told you a million times
I've given up cuz of what happened 3 weeks ago.
Yeah. And I'm not going to change my mind. So,
that was a learning um le uh that was a
learning lesson for me.
So, uh, never.
>> This is [ __ ] that.
But people on Reddit say getting sex is
easy. Lo, they say getting sex is easy.
I said, "Is it?" Then I showed them the
approaches, the dating app to the
Really? Getting sex is easy? Must be new to me. Yeah, right.
So, yeah, I'm never going out again. [ __ ] that. Yeah, man.
No way. [ __ ] that. There's There's no
going back after that, I'm afraid.
And that's and it's like what this um
tiger tiger Ted
It's like what this tiger tiger said. He
said, "Ah, I see what you mean now. They
should have told you first that they
didn't want to take things further to
you in advance instead of them
prolonging it." And your text were very
polite, too. Yeah, exactly. Cuz they
done it on purpose. They didn't all of a
sudden change their mind. They done the
whole thing on purpose.
which is obviously people on Reddit
don't understand that they they seem to think they
they don't do on purpose when they
clearly [ __ ] well do. So
I don't think nothing's going to
convince me to go out again within the final straw.
So yeah, that's where we're at.
Bro, I've tried everything.
You're asking me if I've tried this.
Have I tried that? I've tried everything.
Yes, I have tried that.
I tried that in the video. If you
actually watch the video properly, you
would have seen
that virgin's [ __ ] mad. Virgin's mad.
So yeah, I have tried that. I tried it
in a video.
They just ain't interested in this country.
But people on Reddit say that you'll get laid
to get sex. [ __ ] hell.
All women aren't the same.
They just do the same stuff, say the
same stuff, have the same mannerisms,
but they're not the same. They're not
the [ __ ] same. None of them are the
Women aren't the same.
I mean, who who even says that, man?
Why would someone even say that?
So silly when they obviously are all the same.
They obviously are all the [ __ ] same.
Why do people say that they're not when
they obviously are? It's so obvious that
they're all the same.
Where's this [ __ ] Ricky Millington
bun to pick with him?
He loads on the virgin channel, the non
virgin channel, but it doesn't come on
mine even when I [ __ ] enable the comments. white knight.
[ __ ] white knight, can't you?
We go mad at stuff like that, mate. You
know me. You [ __ ] know me, mate.
They say it's easy to get s on [ __ ] idiots. Virgin can't virgin.
The Virgin can't
bo on Reddit say it's easy to get sex,
but dating apps don't work. And when you
approach women, they pretend they've got
boyfriends. I don't believe them.
They lie on Reddit.
They lie so much on Reddit, Bob. Yeah.
You know they say getting sex isn't easy, Bob.
[ __ ] Is it [ __ ] Is it liar?
Reddit lies so much.
They call it a um they call it a hookup culture.
Now it's hard.
I don't think hard is the word. I think
it's impossible now.
I don't think it's hard. I think it's
other guys do it. Watch out for the other guys.
You can't even have a conversation
nowadays without hearing and I've got a
boyfriend. Yeah. People on [ __ ]
Reddit seem to think that
you can get laid.
I don't understand. [ __ ] liars.
Nah. Even when they're pissed, they're
not interested. There's no such thing as luck
when it comes to this anymore. They're not interested.
Even on a night out, they're not interested.
That's why I gave up.
Lucky on a night out.
Yeah, but only did that. But people on
Reddit say that you can get sex and
stuff. That's mad.
They say you can get lame,
Bob. They say it's easy to get sex.
I must be missing something.
Must be missing something, right?
Yeah, maybe I'm insecure.
Any thoughts on the messages that I
showed you or
cuz now now you're just making up stuff.
Now you're just completely making up
stuff cuz I've never been in my life, man.
I've literally shown you messages, but
you didn't really seem to
you seem to dismiss them. So why would I
be insecure? I've literally put messages up there.
Yeah, I got a message back leading me
on. I'd rather not have a message back.
So, are you just going to dismiss any I
I'd rather not have a response than be
led the [ __ ] on and still be single at
almost 28 years of age. Trust me, a
message back is not a win. Being led on
is not a win. It's even worse.
So, good for other men if they don't get
a reply. That's good for them. I went
out approaching and I've been led on.
Simple. So, I give up. That's my choice. So yeah.
So what if men don't get reply back? I
got led on. I don't want anything to do
with women ever again. They're all the
same. They proved it time and time and
time again. You're not going to change
my mind. So that's it.
They've had plenty of chances to prove
they're all different and they can't. That's
stop racing me.
But people on Reddit say you can get sex
easy. [ __ ] hell. [ __ ] liars
already tried to fat chick.
I know I should do I should be not a
car. I don't want a car, but I should be
I should have a home with someone. Yeah,
my age definitely. I was speaking to
thinking about this. I should have more
in my life at this age. It's like I
didn't try to meet anyone for years.
But not a car cuz I wouldn't drive
anyways. But yeah.
Yeah. But it's never going to happen. It
would have happened by now. So
yeah, 28 is quite old, bro. I should
have more in life. Especially since I
tried so hard.
So you're not going to meet anyone now
until you're probably like 50.
That's why I need to that's why I'm
leaving the country cuz that's the only
thing I can do to have a normal life.
But there ain't a normal life here. I
should have met someone. I tried more
than enough. I put the messages out
there, you know. So,
no, but why why are you talking about that? Huh? One second.
But yeah, that's that's what I've been
dealing with for um
um years with these women. So, and the
ones that uh said straight away they're
not looking to date or whatever, that
they didn't lead you on. Did they do
anything wrong? Not really. No. But it
also contradicts when they say that
women go for personality and this that
and the other when they won't even give
you a type if you're not their physical
type even if you're [ __ ] decent looking.
So that lie still gets spread around
that they go for personality and
appearance isn't appearance is
everything to them. Even if you are good-looking, you know,
even if you're decent looking. So, it is
about um appearance. Even if you look
good, they won't give you a chance. I
don't know why people act like oh
appearance to women. Nothing.
What did you think of the messages, Grezy?
got a bone to pick were you. You went quiet.
So, it was a whole of YouTube versus me
and no one could say a damn thing about
their messages. Knew it. And the only
person that did comment agreed with me.
I mean, yeah, they they they like
personality when you already pass the
unrealistic threshold of their standards.
I wasn't homeless and I'm not getting
into that. I mean, yeah, they like
personality once you've already met
their unrealistic standards. Sure, then
they'll then they'll look for
personality, but if if you're not their
physical type, like maybe you have a
beard, maybe you don't have a beard,
they won't even entertain you. And
that's how shallow women are. And it's a
cover up. See, women, See, men will
admit it. Oh, they go for this, they
like men admit it, but with women, us go
for go for um appearance. No, not us.
We're perfect. We only go for personality.
Really? You go for personality?
Really? When you don't even give
somebody a chance to get to know their personality? Nah.
And their messages prove it.
Some of them should women should have
gave you a chance.
You know, we're in the first message,
but they never. So that whole they go
for personality is you like I said they
go for personality after you meet their unrealistic standards.
But yeah at 28 I should have a home. I
should have um a partner. I should have
all of these things. I'm very aware that
I'm kind of a [ __ ] at 28,
you know. I'm very very very aware. I'm
self-aware me, you know.
Okay. And you're banned. So yeah,
I'm very aware that I have a [ __ ] up, mate. You know,
again, no opinion on the messages.
Just completely dismissed them. Didn't suit you.
didn't. So, you've you've dismissed all
of the messages I've shown what women
have done. Ah, I knew it. I knew it
before I done the video. They just miss
any bad thing women do. So, there's no
point getting into any debate, any kind
of argument. You might as well not even
be a candidate cuz they're always going
to defend the women. It's a waste of everyone's time.
There's no point getting into any kind
of debate, wasting energy, cuz whatever
you show will get dismissed. I showed
messages where women have led me on.
They didn't even give me the chance. And
even though I put it out there, we're
still having some other random conversation. Like, no. So,
that's it. And I've given up with a
dating game anyways. I don't want to hear it.
Simple. So, yeah.
So, yeah, you obviously dismissed
everything I showed, so that's fine.
Doesn't suit them.
My experiences don't suit them. Grezy, I
know you like that little saying, don't you?
And that's why I don't um get like the
urge to go out drinking anymore and
stuff because I should be with someone
now. I should be settled down. It's like
what Bob said. I'm 28 in 8 days.
So, I should be settled down. I should
be with someone. There's no reason why
I'm not with someone.
There's literally no reason. I've tried,
put the effort in, texted normally.
There's no reason. Absolutely no reason. >> So, so yeah.
And I don't use escorts anymore cuz I
don't have a sex drive.
Nah, nothing to be happy about
being rejected and by women all your
life. Nothing to be happy about. That's
why I gave up. I am happy. No, I am
happy. I'm happy I gave up. Like I'm not
depressed. It's just my life is a bit
[ __ ] But I am happy nonetheless. I am
happy. I'm not depressed like or anything. Um,
so I am like I'm all good, but that's
cuz I gave up with dating. If I was
still dating, I' i'd be depressed,
toxic, miserable, cuz that's how it used
to get me when I was dating, approaching
women and stuff.
Like I'm not broke or anything. I got
money, you know, whatever. But my life
should be better at this age. Yeah. So So
it was all right. It was all right at
24, 25, 26. You know, you're still kind
of young. 28, you you should be settled
down with someone, which is why
obviously I don't go out drinking much anymore.
Yeah, I'll touch lucky soon. I'm not so
sure cuz they said that to me 5 years
ago as well. And it's been the same old.
And this is how you know Greavesy that
you'll never meet anyone because you
know people that are saying that you're
going to meet someone where T
and let's just say that they're right
that you're going to meet someone. If
it's not happen in four or five years,
the odds of you suddenly meeting someone
now is got to be like winning the
lottery twice in a row because how many
times you've tried and you put yourself
out there, you're not just going to it's
not just suddenly going to change. It's
like when you play roulette, right? It's
like when you play roulette, bro, you
win sometimes, you lose sometimes, you
win sometimes, you lose sometimes. You
wouldn't lose for five years and then suddenly win.
It's not going to happen. And if it is
going to happen, I mean, like I said,
you've got more chance of winning the lottery.
It's so obvious. You've got more chance
of winning the lottery. You know what
I'm saying, Greedy? Because it's been
going on for years. It's not been going
on for a month, 6 months. 6 months is
nothing. It has been going on for years
with these women. So, it's not going to
just suddenly stop now.
Happy. I'm I'm all good. Like,
yeah, exactly. And that's what the
problem is, Greavves. See, back in the day,
women couldn't be picky because they
couldn't choose men because if they
liked a man, they couldn't approach
them. A woman couldn't approach a man
because they were scared. And obviously,
if the man was scared, which most men
are, they couldn't be picky. So, what
whoever approached them is what they'd
end up with.
Do you understand?
Like it's it's whatever whoever
approaches them, they can't be picky.
They get what they're given unless they
want to go and approach men. But now
with all of these simps and white
knights, you got no chance. You've got
absolutely no chance.
You got no chance now.
It's like my dad. Sorry to say this, but
my dad was quite ugly, but my mom was
good-looking when she was younger. Now
if Tik Tok and Instagram and stuff was
around back then, you know, maybe that
maybe they would have been together.
You understand the point I'm trying to
make? And even like my sister and her
boyfriend, they've been together for like
15 16 years and I was before and and if
and if they didn't meet then, she
probably wouldn't be with him now. You'd
be with someone else. So unless you got
lucky back in the day or you've got
loads of Instagram followers and loads
and loads and loads and loads and loads
and loads of money,
you're [ __ ] You have to go to Asia.
That's it. Or South America. But I still
think that if I was somewhere else but
England, I would have met someone by
now. Like I keep saying, Belgium, maybe
the Netherlands after like a year. Uh,
no. My dad's dead. So,
like I think if you tried as much as you
did in another country, even like
America, I still think I don't know. I
But I reckon if you were someone like
Belgium, you definitely would.
You're just no one's type in this country. That's it.
That's what it is. So, yeah.
And it's mad cuz even when I had loads
and loads of money, I've still got money
now. It still never made a difference. I
was doing better than a lot of people my
age. Still never made a difference. Um,
not really. No, but I reckon if I was in
Belgium, I definitely reckon I would
have met someone definitely by now. And
any anywhere, I don't know about France,
but I think even then, man, I still
think England is the worst [ __ ] even
if it took 6 months to a year, I think
this is the worst country to try and
date. any westernized country is. But I
don't know. I don't know. I don't know.
I could just see me jumping on on a
dating app in a different country and
getting lucky. But not here.
Definitely not here.
No, I wouldn't really want to know.
It's bad this whole social media thing. I know,
but I reckon I would have been someone's
type in Belgium. Definitely.
A lot of Belgians are dark and you get
like a lot of Turkish people there. I
definitely think if I was in another
country, I would have found someone.
But yeah, I'm not saying everything
you're saying is wrong. I should be
settled down. I should be with someone,
you know. I should, you know, but
at least I had the money to [ __ ]
live through my [ __ ] 20s and stuff
and live the life, you know? See, now
it's not even about living the life.
I've got the money. It's not about
money. It's about the whole you should
be settled down now. you know
that's why I don't go out anymore drinking so
should be a lot of things at this age
but I'm not so
also social media is unhealthy because a
lot of people compare themselves to
people which is also unhealthy greasy
like if you go on Instagram and stuff.
You'll compare yourself to people that
only show the best parts of their life,
you know, stuff like that. So, yeah.
Where's Joseph gone?
Get a little bit of [ __ ] with bad no
money in it.
An old one. It's an old tree. So yeah,
sad is it?
Probably will never change, will it?
Well, it will never change, will it?
Like, I don't even know what to do at
this point. But
moving forward, it is scary. Very scary.
Life becomes scary when you get to this age.
It's all right [ __ ] around when
you're 24, 25, you know.
It's very scary, bro. At this age, it's scary.
I was saying this to my mom as well. I
said I should be better at this age, to be honest.
Obviously, it's not entirely my [ __ ]
fault. You know, I try to meet someone
better to t to tech.
You know, I'll never be able to afford
to live by myself in London unless I had
a partner. So, there's no way I'd be
able to afford it
cuz most people don't afford it. They
can't afford it in London. They live
with their parents or they live with
someone else or
I'm just lucky I had the money to enjoy
my 20s. It could have been a lot worse.
And now I don't have the same amount of
money anymore. I still have money. I
still have more than enough money. I
don't get the same amount of money. It's
not a problem because I should be with
someone now anyways.
I should I should have met someone
but I haven't. And now I haven't met
anyone. Why should I have to keep
trying? I'm too I'm 28 years of age,
bro. In [ __ ] 8 days. I should have to
try again. I've tried more than enough. So,
my life is pretty [ __ ] to be honest.
See, if I still had the old house, it
would have been good. I had that room.
I could still keep living like but now I
kind of have to wake up. So
it won't get worse. It will just it will
just stay the same.
I don't miss alcohol. Like I I haven't
drunk for a month. It doesn't bother me alcohol.
It really doesn't bother me.
Like I I only used to really go out
drinking to have fun and try and meet
women, but none are interested. So
I messaged this person on Reddit. They
were like, "Not you again."
And they say, "Oh, get get an escort every month.
I don't need confidence. I can be
confident without alcohol."
And no, it doesn't. I mean, you still
have to [ __ ] you still have to have
the balls to approach even if you're
drunk. Unless you're really [ __ ]
Nah, even even with me, it doesn't
affect me. You know, if I'm in a Weather Spoons drinking,
you know, I'm [ __ ]
I'm in a Weather Spoons drinking. And
I'm still having to [ __ ]
push myself to do it on days where I
don't feel as confident. Doesn't matter, bro.
Going to order a curry. I don't think
I'm going to eat today, to be honest.
You know, nonslex. He likes She Carl.
You can't deny she's attractive.
You're gay. You don't find her
attractive. You're gay.
You don't find her attractive. You're
gay. Oh, must be gay then.
Whole chicken, rice, and a drink.
This woman said to me, "It won't it will
not be easy to be your friend because
when I say things to help, you won't listen."
I get extra hot.
I know. And she's 33, that woman as well.
That woman is 33 as well. So, it just
goes to show the games never stop.
Yeah, it shows the games never stop with these women.
Yeah, she was 3. I'm sure she was 33. Sir,
all women aren't the same. You don't
know all women.
You don't know all women. Yeah.
And they led me on as well. It's not
like any of them were honest. Well,
maybe two or three of them are honest.
They were like, "Oh, I I don't want to
take things further." No, no, no, no,
no. which again is fine. They haven't
done anything wrong, but it still kind
of goes against the whole women go for
personality because none of them were
willing to meet me. Even though when I
looked Max, when I met them, I was
object I was I was objectively above average looking. So
you say that women aren't picky, but
that shows they kind of are. So yeah, man.
Unrealistic standards, isn't it?
It's bad, bro. Very bad.
Yeah, that one was when I met uh
I met [ __ ]
um I met her when I was with Monty.
A couple of them.
when I was with Monty.
So that's what happens whenever you go
out. You just deal with people that play games.
So that's why I can't be bothered anymore.
that's all it will ever be here. So
that's it. Let's go.
I got some bacon. I think I'll just cook
some bacon if I get hungry.
The the the funniest one is they won't
date you cuz you're not Muslim.
Um I shouldn't uh I didn't ask them for
a date straight away.
There was ones where I didn't rush into it.
There was literally ones where I didn't
rush into it and there was also ones
where they didn't reply to the first message.
So I mean I was speaking to some of them
for over a week.
I did say to one I am Muslim and then
she was like oh I'm not looking to date
anyone right now. Same old [ __ ]
Yeah. Then when you say you're Muslim
it's another excuse. Or when you say
you'll become Muslim it's another
excuse. It's just games and excuses.
with these people. So, there's no point
playing them, you know?
It's just always a nar's always an
excuse. There was a message that I was
going to put up and it was this woman
from Italy and she was a proper narcissist.
They just say that they're not looking for anyone.
Yeah, I have. And then they just say
that they're not looking for anyone. So, yeah.
Um, again, I'll repeat myself the third
time. I already have. And then they say
that, "Oh, I'm not looking to date anyone." So, same old
same old here, it um nowadays. Yeah.
Who's that? Hold on. Yeah. All that ever
happens when you go out and you approach
is they either say they're not
interested straight away without even
getting to know you, your personality,
but yet they go for personality and that
looks weird. Um, or they say that they
have a boyfriend
or they ignore you or they give you
their number and then they lead you on.
Literally nothing else ever happens.
That's the only thing that would ever happen here.
So yeah, people need to stop lying about
how women don't go for appearance and
stuff because if you're not their exact
preference, they won't even give you a chance.
They need to stop coping
cuz that's what a lot of these people
do. It's like the whole women don't know
you anything. That's used to cover up
their shitty behavior. They think that
justifies their shitty behavior. Oh,
well, they don't owe you anything. I
mean, really? I mean, it would have took
you less than 10 seconds of your life to
to to explain something and you're
really going to hit people with that
excuse. So, all of these things are just
like a cover up.
Like they go for personality and it's
[ __ ] Absolute [ __ ] Because if
you see in their messages, you can see
why people didn't even give me the chance. But yeah,
it is bad, isn't it?
Like I said, I don't use escorts cuz I
don't really have a sex drive.
It's kind of So, I don't really need them. So,
Yeah. Well, I did used to go swimming.
But yeah, that's all that ever happens.
Why does people on Reddit make excuses
for these women? Oh, maybe they changed their mind.
What? They changed their mind. So they
agreed for to meet you and then they
changed their mind. No,
it's very obvious that it was done on
purpose multiple times. You know, we had
somebody agree to meet then when we were
supposed to meet, oh, I'm going to try
with my ex.
I mean, it's very concerning. Um, you know,
would you agree, Bob Bills, that they
make excuses for women on Reddit?
Definitely make excuses. Definitely. Definitely. Definitely.
Because as a man, you would never agree
to go on a date with someone and change
your mind before you go on a date with
them. That doesn't make no sense.
Like, that literally makes no sense whatsoever.
There's It's all well and you know,
dates not going anywhere,
you know, a date not going anywhere and stuff.
You know, but that's that's when you're
actually on the [ __ ] date. Like, who
would that just does not make no sense?
That makes no sense.
Yeah. But that excuse doesn't cover it,
bubble, though, because they lead me on
via text. So, when when they give their
number, they don't reply, then that's
obviously they're getting rid of you.
They're they're, you know, they're
they're they're lying to get rid of you.
No, sorry. They're But
what I'm saying is is when I've shown
these people the messages on Reddit of
these women leading me on, they make
excuses. Oh, oh, uh, yeah, they changed
their minds, but they didn't. So yeah,
they're making excuses for women all the time.
I had this woman on Reddit. Yeah, she
was reading my messages. I showed her my screenshots, right?
And she was like, "Oh." I said, "You
haven't even read my screenshots." I
said, "I don't owe you by time to read
them." I said, "Who the [ __ ] do you
think you're [ __ ] talking to? Don't
[ __ ] talk to me like that." So any
time where I'm proving a woman to be
wrong and he doesn't suit you, I don't
owe you anything. Cuz it seems like such
a lame excuse to cover up any kind of
wrongdoing that they do.
If you've noticed, that saying always
gets used to cover up women's shitty
actions. It never gets used any other way. Crazy. Oh, so yeah.
me now with some 19year-old in America
which I wouldn't get with them cuz
they're 19 too old for them and they
live in America anyway this
I would never get with a 19y old now
minimum like 23
I think that's an okay age.
No, I would get 19 now.
Boys, get in the bed.
I mean, she'd have to be a [ __ ] 10
out of 10.
She would have to be a [ __ ] 10 out of 10, mate.
For me to get with a [ __ ] 19year-old
again. They'd have to be. And I wouldn't
date them either.
Even if they were hot, I wouldn't date
them. No way. They could look like a
model. I still wouldn't date them.
Yeah. I mean, you can [ __ ] one if
they're 10 out of 10. Literally, if they
were a 10, then maybe. Yeah.
But not not date. No matter what they
look like, I wouldn't date them.
No way. They could look like a model. I
still wouldn't date them.
You have nothing in common with a 19year-old. Nothing.
I got a boat. Where did Ricky Millington go?
>> For my birthday next Monday.
People on Reddit say that it's easy to
get sex bubble, but I don't understand
how because the dating apps don't work
and if you approach in bars and clubs,
they pretend they've got boyfriends.
I showed them my little evidence to show
what I've been going through for years.
I said to one uh earlier, Gre, I've got
a bone to pick with you. Why are you
going on Reddit saying it's easy to get
sex and dates? I got a bone to pick with
you. What are you [ __ ] lying for?
Sex is easy.
Sex is easy. Really? Getting sex is
easy, is it? I don't think getting sex
is easy either, mate. Just my um 14 cents.
I mean, dating apps don't work.
Approaching women, no one's interested.
I don't think getting sex is easy.
I I really really don't think getting
sex is easy, mate.
I just don't think getting sex is easy. No.
I mean, I've only had four or five one night stands
and trust me, it wasn't easy. So,
>> oh yeah, if you use escorts, yeah,
obviously, but we're talking like normally.
Yeah, if you're using escorts, obviously
that's easy. Yeah,
but we're talking about if you weren't using escorts.
Nah, same same hard level,
same same difficult level.
I'd rather have no [ __ ] than have that
[ __ ] disabled thing.
That's what makes me laugh with this
[ __ ] Ricky Millington. He says I'm
jealous. What? Cuz he has sex with a
disabled girl that you couldn't even pay
me to have sex with. That he's been on
holidays that I've been on 8 years before him.
I've literally done them same holidays
when I was 23 and I could do it all over
again if I wanted to.
Sex with a disabled girl. Trust me, I'm
not jealous of that.
I'm really really not jealous of of that
as well. If you see all of these women
um that I've approached, they've never
looked like Sarah. Why would I be
jealous of somebody that copied my
holiday eight years after?
What is this? Is this guy for real?
Like, why would someone be jealous of
somebody that's copied my holiday?
That is weird, bro. What the [ __ ]
And if he has all this money, why did it
take him to 30 to go abroad? Cuz he
simply couldn't afford it. It's simple
as that. Cuz
the only reason right that nonsense has
got a bit of money is because he doesn't
he didn't do anything with his life in
them years. He just sat in his little
bed sit with no bed, no money in it,
right? Saving saving saving saving
saving saving saving. So he missed out
on life experiences more than 3 years
due to saving
which, like I said, I wouldn't do that.
I wouldn't [ __ ] trade my life experiences.
So, well, obviously he has,
but these people here need to stop
lying, you know? It's it's ridiculous.
Yeah, he's not allowed to touch her.
He's definitely not had sex. And Ricky
was like, "Oh, how can he say you've not
had sex? You've got a girlfriend."
I mean, I've actually proved I've had sex.
Thailanders, I've actually proved I've had sex. So,
I mean, is that more proof than someone
having a disabled girlfriend?
I I would have thought.
And I was thinking if I was going to go
out drinking again, I'd go somewhere
else like Bristol.
I don't know.
But I won't be going out drinking again. 12 hours,
you know. That's mad.
Why would somebody be jealous of an ugly
[ __ ] in a bite with no life experiences?
I mean, it's Why would someone be
jealous? I mean, they say that I'm the
one that's jealous. Yeah, the [ __ ] can't
stop going on about me. So actions speak
louder than words. You're saying that
I'm jealous. Yeah. This skinned virgin
goes on about me every day.
That's a way to show that the other
person's jealous, right?
So that proves that they're jealous of
me, you know.
No, it was only a suggestion, bro. I'm
not I'm not going
the West Country. No.
They say you'll meet someone on Reddit bubble.
Now, if you ain't met anyone by now,
you're never going to meet anyone. It's
simple. I remember when I went to I
remember I went to [ __ ]
I remember when I went to uh Cardiff.
You remember that time I went Wales two
times in a week straight. One Friday
then I went the next Friday. You
remember that time? Didn't meet anyone.
Got numbers led beyond. Same old [ __ ]
No, they're not, mate. I've been all
over the country and women are the same everywhere.
I've been all over the country and trust
me, women are the same everywhere.
I went to Wales. I don't know if it was
last year, but I remember I went one
Friday, then I went again.
Nothing happened. I was a bad bastard, bro. Crazy. Nope. Not really.
But they go on like women don't go for
looks and and or specific preference
they have. They seem to think that that
stuff don't matter when it does.
Cuz even if you're good-looking or like
decent looking, they still won't get
with you. They still won't give you a chance.
This is something that this Ricky Mill
[ __ ] weirdo don't know.
Nah, I'm not getting a fat bird.
I mean, USA Izzy was kind of fat and she
had an ego as well.
But no, women are the same everywhere.
Yeah, I'm all right.
That five guys was yummy.
King enjoyed it.
Can't be bothered to eat, man. That's a lot.
I got some bacon, don't I? So, got some
popcorn. I'm good.
Rock and roll don't post anymore, does he? Uh yeah,
Candy man. Did you watch Did you Did you
see the messages?
Hope you enjoyed the video, man. It's
[ __ ] Yeah, you just pile the messages together.
Nope. The reason I didn't meet right is
because if I met them, I would have
ended up staying there drinking and
approaching women and then the same
thing would happen again and again and
again and again and again.
So that's why I didn't that's the truth
why I didn't go. I know what I'm like as well. So
that's why I didn't go to be fair.
I'm going to knock him out. Do you
remember that Grezy? On the same website
you can watch John um Bigs on. I think
it's big stock link. The same website
you can watch Jojo on. Oh, that's
that's madness. That is madness.
Remember when Timmy said that I'm going
to knock him out?
[ __ ] hell. Oh, J
from Star Wars. He's cute, isn't it?
Why is a 17y old coming up on my [ __ ]
If someone's like 16, 17, I don't talk
to them. I just block them.
I bet you virgin boy don't skin [ __ ] in
the bed it
I bet you virgin boy don't
that [ __ ] predator
that skin predator mate
yeah it cost it cost £12 his burger cost
£12 but yeah I didn't buy
five guys is all right you know it
tastes like a proper homemade burger but
it's not as good as DBK. It is
overrated, but it still tastes like a proper burger.
>> Them women were trolling in their messages.
It's always the French ones that um
get myself down. waxes.
Any opinion on the messages that I put up
or I guess they didn't suit you?
>> None of the messages suited you.
There was two there was two people I
liked out of their message that Alina
was the one from Finland
and there was someone else from France,
but I'm not sure I put that person up.
And I was really trying with them and I
actually thought they were going to meet
but all women are the same.
Yeah. Any thoughts on the whole them
leading me on?
Nah. Didn't suit you, does it?
What I have in my my Five Guys burger
was bacon, cheese, and jalapenos.
No, I'm not going to wax.
I ain't going to wax, bro. [ __ ] that.
I'm done in this country.
I'm too old to be doing this [ __ ] now. [ __ ] waxes.
That's when I met that one from Finland
on Sunday. I met her on a Sunday.
Yeah, I met them on um Sunday.
I met Alina in Waxies on a Sunday.
>> It doesn't shoot them, does it? My
experiences don't suit people.
Yeah, I'm not ugly. I can be decent
looking, but I still can't meet anyone,
you know, and I don't care. I hope she
gets capped when she dies.
I hope she gets capped and dies. Her ego
is so big for somebody that looks like
[ __ ] her. I think we can all agree on
that one, mate.
She's like [ __ ] Who the [ __ ] does she
think she is?
She's ruder than a lot of women that are
actually like good-looking.
You know that one from Finland? She's
good-looking and she ain't got an
attitude like her. Americans
are so entitled. They're so entitled.
But I hate Americans.
I really do. They're the worst.
So, how can someone look like that and
have an ego like that?
Oh, it's just my friend.
No women, French women are nice, but
they're just trolls.
I mean that you see the thing is you you
you say about French women but if you
went out right now and you approached a
French woman she would not say she would
not say she has a boyfriend. She
wouldn't be rude. She'd be nice to you.
She would give you her number and then
she would lead your ass on. So
but they would never ever say they have
a boyfriend. Never. Cuz I've met loads
of defense women and they've always done
the same thing. Trolls.
That's all they do is troll. Nothing else.
Yeah. I mean, they are high. Yeah. But
I'm saying that Yeah, they're they're
impossible. I tell you the ones that are
impossible to get. Italian and French.
You're never getting them.
If I could if I could get with anyone,
it would be with a French. But even
Italian, you got no chance.
French and Italian, nah. Never happening
in a million years.
No, I know. I I know they've got high
standards, but I'm saying that they
won't they will troll you rather than
just outright reject you. That's what I'm saying.
So, but yeah, French. Yeah, they're they're impossible.
They're impossible. and Italian.
Like the Italian woman I went on a date
with, he was holding hands, vibing. I
tried to kiss her. She didn't want to
kiss. What the [ __ ] Yeah. There
is worse. Yeah.
Yeah. New Zealand. Yeah. Because it's
it's a westernized country.
It's a westernized country. But do you
reckon if I was in Paris, right, trying
as hard as I did in Paris as I did here,
you reckon I would have found someone by
now? See, I still think I would have found someone.
I don't know why, but I think I would
have just found someone.
Yeah, but it's still the West. They're
still [ __ ] You know what I'm
saying? Like it's it's the same as [ __ ] Australia.
Australia's Australia's bad as well.
Them women just lead you on. Same. Yeah.
Yeah, they're wester they're western
counts. They're westernized. It's the
same as Australia,
but people don't seem to admit that
they've got no their standards are not
high. Their standards are unrealistic.
Cuz when I look smack, I'm I'm good-look
when I look max. I dress good. I smell
good. People don't even give me the
chance to get to know my personality.
So, their standards are not high. Their
standards are unrealistic.
That there's a big difference. Everyone
should have high Well, a lot of people
that look good should have high standards.
No, I haven't.
But their standards are unrealistic. But
people try to make it seem like they
would go with anyone if their
personality is good.
They're very very in denial. Very very
cuz bubble they made a um Tinder profile
of a guy right that looked really good.
A really good-look white guy and he was
saying to these women that he's these
women that he was a child predator
and they had no problem with that. They
was happy to get with him. They were
happy to meet him. Then they put an
average guy on Tinder with a good
personality and no one was interested. Thailand.
So, you understand what I mean? They
they they um they very very much do go for
top tier men lookwise.
So, I don't know why people act like they don't. Yeah,
that's the [ __ ] that's the [ __ ] up
thing about it.
Women are bad people in general.
Yeah. Everyone pulls in [ __ ] Thailand.
Yeah. Even South America. You go South
America, you'll meet someone.
Yeah. But you will never you will never um
you'll never meet anyone. Yeah.
You want to see the breakfast I got the
other day, Grezy?
I'll I'll put a video up.
I put a video up and show Grezy.
No, I'm not really a fan of black women
to be honest.
But would I get with one still? Probably. Yeah.
So that's the difference between me and women.
Well, I'm putting a video up. Yeah. Reeves.
So that's the difference.
a woman. The difference the thing about
women getting with you and not getting
with you could be simply because you
have a beard or you don't have a beard.
That's how shallow they are. That's how
shallow these women are.
But people on [ __ ]
um people on Reddit, nah, women go for personality.
I put the video up. Go on my channel.
Yeah. Hope you liked it.
I'm going to have some popcorn over there.
No, I got it from the breakfast place.
Yeah. And do you want to see do you want
to see what it look like after play after
Here we go.
Not even joking, bro.
I didn't eat the um the uh breakfast
yuins, but yeah, I the best.
That was delicious.
I love piggies.
Yeah, I really But I ate all the piggies
and the sausages. I was the first one there.
Do you like piggies?
It's like No, it's a breakfast Yorkshire pudding.
Yeah, it's a it's a breakfast one.
Imagine me and USA Izzy having some piggies together.
That's cute, isn't it? Uh,
why can't I get attached anymore?
Grievy. Well, no, I I can get attached,
but I couldn't get attached for like two years.
I couldn't get attached for two years.
Why is that?
Two years. I couldn't get attached for
That was weird, is it? Why? [Laughter]
I'm not going to lie. I was eating some
bacon right a couple of weeks ago
and there was the there was a pig on TV
and it was putting me off because pigs
are so ugly and I swore I'd never eat
pork again. And then a couple of days
later I ate pork again cuz I love piggies. Yeah.
Because you already found your mama.
Oh, that's cute, isn't it? Peter belly
stick. Not Peter Belly's mama.
Whoever that account
Peter Bell is mama,
that's a troll account, is it?
So, what happened between non legs and Britney?
Why didn't they get together?
Um, Britney and Nonsy.
No, it's not weird, bro. It's not weird
cuz pork chops have got a nasty color.
It's like gray.
No, no, it's not. It's not weird. I
mean, pork chops look a bit
um disgusting at times, you know.
No, it's not good. Um, Grezy,
so why did non legs get with Britney?
What was the problem there?
So what happened between not the Virgin
and [ __ ] Britney?
He was crying over her, but they never
ever got together.
Wonder what happened there. Why did Why
didn't hit Why didn't the skin virgin
ever get with her?
Skinn Virgin the bad [ __ ] with no bed,
no money in it.
You didn't want him.
Just didn't didn't want to know.
Just wanted him.
Just wanted him, mate. You can't You
can't explain this. Didn't want to know.
Remember, I'll never forget this.
Stop going on about some girl that don't want you. I'm not.
What about when [ __ ] P went to
[ __ ] 80s? I'll never forget that.
Bquest knows the scar.
Bquest knows the scar, mate, doesn't he?
My mama abandoned me. I'm not.
Stop going that some girl that don't
want you. I'm not. You remember that
one, Grezy? He said, "I'm not.
I'm not." No, he's like, "Give like give
your head a wobble. Stop going on about
some girl on you.
I'm not." Don't you remember that, Grezy?
You must have been on the community then.
He was talking about
some girl that he went on a date with.
Then she blocked him.
He met her parents. Then she blocked him.
And then he was going on and on and on
and some account said, "Give your head a
wobble and stop going on about some girl
that don't want you." I'm not.
Stop going on about some girl that don't
want to know.
Some girl that don't want to know.
Don't want to know you.
That dad want to know you.
Dad want to know you.
No, not this one. Britney was Where's Joseph?
I call him Joseph Bara. Joe F. Joseph Barra.
But yeah, NG's really he really does
need to get laid.
Seriously, I couldn't imagine being a
[ __ ] 31y old virgin.
I couldn't imagine it.
I just couldn't imagine making it to
that age and still being a virgin. Come
on, Ricky Millington.
How How can you say that he's a ver how
can he call you a virgin when you've got
a girlfriend? Easy. He's He's a virgin
and he's got a disabled girlfriend. And
if you went anywhere near her, he'd be
locked up. If he touched don't be
touched though in that way he would be
locked up. He's not allowed anywhere near her.
He's not allowed anywhere near her in
that way cuz he'd get locked up cuz
she's vulnerable. That's how he's a [ __ ] virgin
[ __ ] skin merge in the [ __ ] bed.
No bed. No matter.
Yeah, I need to get myself
popcorn from downstairs.
Did you find USA? Izzy rude bubble.
Very rude pun. Hey,
I can see her having a baby soon.
Do you remember that approach that I
done that had [ __ ] nonsense crying?
He was crying, bro.
[ __ ] crime. Do you remember?
He was [ __ ] crying. He was like, "No,
did it [ __ ]
It's cringe." You remember the approach?
Because because he ain't got the looks
to do it. He ain't got the confidence to
do it. Why are you still a big virgin?
Why do you never go on his channel and
call him a a virgin?
But when he calls me a virgin, you don't
back me up. I think you're supposed to
be one of the [ __ ] brothers, but you
don't back me up, mate.
You don't back me up when he when he's
when he's calling me a skin virgin.
Yeah, you're supposed to be one of the [ __ ] rubs. Yeah.
In hotel. I don't know what the [ __ ]
you're talking about. Never stayed at
premiering in my life.
What the [ __ ] are you going on about?
Monty didn't lose everything over
YouTube. Really? Did he Grezy?
There's no way you can lose everything
on the same website you can watch Yoda on.
There's There's no way, mate. There's no way.
Yeah, but Mickey Mouse is on YouTube. [Laughter] though. We
Okay, I'm staying in a Premier Hotel. Okay.
Okay. Yeah, I'm in a Premier Hotel.
You got me, man. Totally
mind. Do you
you do you skin bur? You had some? No.
Nope. I'm not putting the camera on.
So why don't he just get off of YouTube?
If it ruined his life, then shouldn't he
get off of YouTube?
ruined his life.
That's bad, is it?
Probably ruin the [ __ ] skin merger's
life as well in the [ __ ] bench sit
with no money.
You want me to start playing the money
game again, Greasy? Get the 50 notes
out. You don't want to make the skint
jealous though, do we?
Come on, Ricky Billington. Where are you, son?
Where are you, little hull wanker?
Yeah, I'm in a hotel.
Oh, sorry. I hope I didn't want to uh
put the camera on the other bit because
um I'm having a little ear in the sink.
Can you hear that, Graves?
I'm having a little we >> Yeah,
he said it ruined his life. Nah.
Did it actually Did it actually ruin his life? Right.
You should blame the [ __ ] skin virgin.
How can it How can YouTube ruin someone's life?
Did you see the messages, tutorials?
Did you see the messages? No one's [ __ ] interested.
What the [ __ ]
We're all on the same website and you
can watch Dobby on
all on the same website. You can watch
the Sideman on.
I'm going to knock him out.
Excuse me. I'm going to knock him out.
>> That's what Timmy said.
Yeah. I love the the house. He's cute, isn't it?
Do you think USA was kind of rude?
Notorious. I haven't approached for
almost a month now. Haven't been out
drinking. I've given up with it. There's
no point anymore. They're not [ __ ]
interested in this country.
No, they're not interested. It's a
Oh, you had a girlfriend. Lucky you,
bro. I can't find anyone.
No one's interested.
Lucky you, bro.
I can't find no one.
Did you see the messages I put out?
Give him a watch. Mhm. Yeah.
You remember [ __ ] Money M saying, "Do
you want if you want trouble,
come around the corner?"
One second. I'm going to I'm going to
put this on the screen. Yeah. One
second. Two cents.
So, you're saying, right, that Monty man, right? um
basically lost everything on this same
website. You're telling me Timmy
Eldridge is on the same website you can
watch this on? You know,
there's a reason for that group by the
way. I'm not explaining it. So So you're
trying to tell me this is the same website
I got my window smashed in on?
Nah. If you want in trouble, come around the corner. [Laughter] Look, we
are trying to tell me that's the same
website you can lose it all on.
Nah. No. No way.
So why is why is M why is Mickey Mouse
on there then?
So why is Mickey Mouse on there then? H [ __ ] mon
the same website right el was like I'm
going to knock him out. Oh,
Reza, you love King, don't you? I think
you love King out of you. You love King
the most out of everyone on this community.
I'm going to buy my own dog.
I'm going to buy my own puppy. Would
you like to see it when I buy your little puppy? H
I would love to just live in Scotland.
I'd love if I if I honestly right if you
if you really want to know where I'd
want to be in life, right, I'd be living
in Edinburgh with a nice little Mel
Frenchie, nice TV, nice bed. Oh yeah,
that's that's what I' I' I'd want to be
right now, mate.
That's where I'd want to be right now.
All by myself. Honestly, honest to God,
bro. If you said to me, "Where where
would you want to be in life there?"
Honest to God, bro,
I live in Edinburgh with a lovely little Yeah.
King's not allowed piggies. They're not
allowed piggies. You know that, Grezy.
No, they're not allowed piggies.
Grezy King got a little upgrade
cuz he's so used to going to McDonald's
and having a McDonald's burger, but this
time he got a Five Guys one. Bless him.
Yeah. He said, "Thank you for the burger.
Do you remember when I went out
approaching with a dog?
You remember when I approach him with a dog? Mhm. Remember
I used to give that 19y old50 to suck my willie?
I used to give her£50 to suck my willie.
I think that was a good deal to be honest.
What the [ __ ] is £50? You'll be paid
like a £100 to a [ __ ] escort. She
swallowed it one time as well. Grey,
it was funny.
Ah, do you remember that one? Yeah, they
were waiting, weren't they? Well, what
site was that on? The the Paulo video.
It weren't the same website you can
watch Yoda on.
No, look. What is it?
There's no way.
There's no way. This this this site
needs to be monitored. Look.
And and it's the same website you can
watch Harry Potter on when they were all
like [ __ ] nine little kids.
Look at Yoda. Bless him. Yoda died of old age.
If you want If you want trouble, come
around the corner. You saw the video.
You saw the video though, didn't you,
Ruby? If you want trouble, come around the corner. [Laughter]
You saw it though, didn't you, Gres?
I bet you I didn't think if she met me,
she'd be stuck with me for life, did she?
I actually didn't know she was going to
be stuck with me for life. Disagree.
Someone said I'm like Chucky. You can't
get rid of the [ __ ]
Is that true? I'm like, Tucky, you can't
get rid of the [ __ ] bro.
How am I in a hotel? I'm in a [ __ ]
house, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
Eating popcorn. I didn't know. just
looked like a [ __ ] pre.
That's a premier M.
You promised me I'm in a I'm in a Premier M.
You're a [ __ ] [ __ ] Everybody knows
where I am.
Stop talking [ __ ]
Why would I be in a premier in? They
don't even [ __ ] help homeless [ __ ]
people, you [ __ ] [ __ ] Why the [ __ ]
would I be in a [ __ ] Premier in? What idiot?
Never stayed in a Premier in my life.
Go away, Bob.
I agree with you. You're still there.
What's this all about?
Oh, you're a [ __ ]
You're a [ __ ] I want to show you
this. What do you think of this, Grezy?
What do you think of that? Oh, look.
Monty man's live. As soon as I've
clicked [ __ ] Dobby, I've got a notification
for Monty Man. Look, that's Dobby.
if you want trouble, come.
It needs to be monitored.
This website needs to be monitored.
It can't be safe for [ __ ] kids, you know. Mhm.
Oh, Monty man's live. Let's have a little watch.
Right. I'll be back live in a bit. I'm
going to watch Monty.