in the air. Two days now
they're coming again. Yeah.
I rise, man. What's your problem with
me? I don't want to I don't want to fall
out with you, man. Offends to the end.
Hideyho. Haha. I know what your problem
is with me. We're mates.
Me, you, and Kaye are mates. You can all
go out for a nice drink together.
I don't want to fight. I'm a lover, not a fighter. Yeah.
What I'm saying?
Yeah, man. I just I just didn't. Sorry about that.
No, no, link.
I don't want to fight, man. I don't want
to fight somebody on the same website
you can watch Yoda on. That's
ridiculous. [ __ ] that. I'm not doing
You silly goose.
You're nothing but a silly goose.
I'm not fighting, bro. I'm not fighting over YouTube. That's ridiculous.
I could I I reckon I could beat Monty if
I wanted to. I reckon I could. But yeah, pointless.
My fighting days are done.
That doesn't matter. Why are you asking
weird questions for
Yeah, but that Yeah, but that argument
What the [ __ ] going on with my TV?
But the thing is, bro, that's not going
to work cuz obviously you showed up. So,
what the [ __ ] is going on with this TV, bro? Huh?
Hold on. But then you would have turned up.
So the whole that argument doesn't make sense, bro. Just stay.
What the [ __ ] Restart.
No, not me.
There's something wrong with this [ __ ] Xbox. Oh,
Am I going down O'Neal O'Neal tonight?
Um, well, considering after three weeks
a What happened a month ago? No. [ __ ] that.
I'm done. D done.
I just enjoy, you know, the peace and
quiet. I really do. It's so nice.
nothing to do with that [ __ ] It was
It's so toxic.
Oh, what happened a month ago? I tell
you if you want. Um, so
I went out, I got 10 numbers, spent £600
and I only got one reply who said they
were going to meet me, but then they
never and I looked smacked as well. So
after that, I just I just got put off
basically. So anyone [ __ ] would to be fair.
Yeah. A month it was about a month ago
now and then I won the money back and I
was like that's it. I'm not doing this
again. [ __ ] that.
I was like I'm not doing that again.
That was a month ago. It's my birthday next Monday.
And yeah, it's just been nice like not
being with the toxic [ __ ]
the I've got a boyfriend leading on. Oh,
it's so toxic, you know?
So, that's why I'm like uh I'm I'm happy
now to be honest. I feel like I'm on holiday.
When you take a break from this date and
[ __ ] you actually feel like you're on
holiday. It's so nice, you know? So, [Music]
A long [ __ ] break, mate. A long
break. I'm thinking six months minimum
if I that's even if I ever try again to
be honest which I doubt I will.
So cuz that how can you how can you how
can you be motivated after that 10
numbers after looks max m max is not
even a single day. How could you be
motivated after that?
That is just discouraging. Why would you
even try again after that? It's mad. No,
only a little bit. I don't really have
much of a sex drive anymore. There's
escorts I can see, but nah.
So, I don't think I'd ever be trying
again to be fair. I supposed to be going
out on my birthday. Well, this the
Saturday before my birthday, but I don't think so
to be honest.
I'm sure if there was someone out there,
I would have met them in the past. Well,
if there's someone out there, why have I
not met anyone in 5 years?
So, you're saying that there's someone
out there? Well, I've been up and down
the country approaching thousands of
women and I haven't found anyone.
So yeah, there might be someone out
there, but you probably got more chance
of winning the lottery
because for doing something for four or
five years and not meeting anyone, you'd
have to be doing something like the lottery
because I'm sure you would have met
someone in in four or five years. No,
I think I've approached more than 100
women. I've approached more than 5,000
women. So if there was somebody out
there, you would have met them by now.
It's obvious. It's [ __ ] obvious.
You would have already met them,
you know. So
yeah, the dating pool has got piss in it. Yeah. So
if there was someone out there, you you
would be with someone now.
So what's your opinion on that one? If
there was someone out there, I would
have met them. Yeah. Next next month.
Don't forget, I've tried an abnormal
amount as well cuz I had a house for as
long as I did. So, I used to go out multiple times.
So, go back to work or anything. So, I'm
I'm pretty sure I'm pretty confident
there's no one for me cuz I would have
met them by now. 100%.
And every time I go out now, I feel like
I don't get anything out of it.
I just feel like I never get anything
out of it. Like I wake up and I'm not
even excited. I was like, "Oh, so
I just can't justify it anymore." Yeah.
Yeah. And I've had like minor minor
minor successes. But obviously also last
um sorry last month really done it for
me as well.
Was it it must have been September.
Yeah. That that in itself like even if
you haven't been trying for 5 years
looks max getting 10 numbers and not
even getting a date like give the [ __ ]
up literally like that's that's
ridiculous. And I spent £5600 as well. So
I was like, "Okay, you want the money
back?" And then one of the numbers
replied, funny enough, they was like,
"Oh, let me know when you're back in the
area." And I was like, "Okay, well, this
this seems positive."
Even though I knew I was going to get
[ __ ] over in the end, but I was just
trying to like say, "Oh, okay. Yeah,
there's a chance of them meeting." We
scheduled to meet on Saturday and the
day before they said that they were
sick. Never heard from them again. So, um, uh,
well, I went to
I went to get my haircut. I approached
on the street. Then I went to a couple
of pubs, bars,
uh, drunk. I don't know what where the
money went. Drunk. I didn't gamble
either, so that that's that's another
thing. If I gambled, I'd see where it
went. Then I went to an escort. Had a
bad experience with an escort. Yeah. I
approached, got 10 numbers, drunk, got
an escort. Then I think it was from the
from the Friday to the Sunday I spent that
food approaching, drinks, escort. He
[ __ ] me over. So yeah, after then I
kind of got put off of trying again cuz
it's like I looked smacked, I dressed
good, I smelt good, and I got 10 numbers.
I didn't get free numbers.
I didn't get [ __ ]
um I didn't look like [ __ ] So, there's
no real reason why I didn't get a date.
So, there's there's not really any going
back after that to be honest.
And it's it's scary. So, um,
it was just to I went to see this
escort, asked to get a [ __ ] and be
able to finish in their mouth. They
agreed to it, gave them the £100 and
then um they were they done it and then
uh they was like, well, whilst they were
doing it, they were like, "Oh, yeah, you
can't come uh you can't come in my
mouth." I was like, "Huh?" We agreed to
that and I paid that and I said, "Okay,
I want half the money back." So, she was
trying to scam me. Um, and then a guy
come and I told him to get out of my
face. Yeah. And then it was toxic. We
were arguing and he's, "Oh, you have to
go." I said, "I'm going to go, but if
you don't give me the money back, I'm
going to do your windows in." And then,
um, it went on for ages, ages, ages. And
I was going to do the window in. I was
looking for like a brick. Um,
and then he come out in the I just I
just wanted half the money back. I
wanted half the money back. All the
money back. And then in the end, he gave
half the money back. And then since then
I just got put off ever trying in this
country again. So I was like no it's not
worth it. It's not [ __ ] worth it.
It's not worth it.
Um I even have like them say sometimes
oh come come and see me. They were in
the escort house and there's like oh
come and see me and I just get put off.
I said I'm not coming. Ones I've been
with before I just got put off. Like
that that experience just put me off.
It's toxic. So I just don't do anything now really. So yeah,
it was really bad, bro. It was really, really bad.
So I wouldn't feel
comfortable ever walking in there again.
So that's that. Lucky I won the money back.
It's really really lucky I won the money
back but that's not the point if I won
the money back. So
um I won the money back but it's not the
point. It's I could be a millionaire.
That's ridiculous. I can't believe I
spent all that money and I didn't
gamble. That's the thing. If I had
gamble and stayed in a hotel I can see
where the money went. I don't know where
the [ __ ] it went
just on [ __ ] So after that I just
gave up. It's clear you're never going
to meet anyone. I don't know how how
much clearer it has to be. So, I ain't
going there again. And after that, I was
depressed for like two weeks as well.
And then I was like, well, well, it is
what it is now.
So, it's clear it's never going to change.
And I was confident on that uh that
month ago as well didn't make a difference. Nope.
Go self-reflect on another channel. Um
I was I was speaking to my mom
and she was like, "Oh yeah, didn't you
didn't you have one going on a wild
goose chase?" which I need to message my
sister about this um because she brought
it up and I don't think she she knew the
reason. Obviously I don't speak to
anymore cuz I tan but didn't you want to
know the reason? I can tell you the
reason you know it's like yeah I had
them going on a wild goose chase because
they were being passive aggressive and
they were being a [ __ ]
It wasn't a [ __ ] innocent [ __ ]
person. It was somebody that was being a
[ __ ] and trying to be passive aggressive
so that I'll be a [ __ ] back to them.
[ __ ] it. I had enough of that [ __ ] So that's it. Um,
no, that's a load of [ __ ] I'm not
getting into silly argue, silly rumors,
madeup stuff. I don't address madeup
stuff. So I said to my wife, is there
any point of this when you're just going
to dismiss anything I I show you or say?
Is is there any point? If you're just
going to ignore what people say and show you,
then I don't see the point in this.
I had them going on a wild Yeah. And I
said, "What about what they done being
passive aggressive and being a [ __ ]
you know?" So they're lucky I was a wild
goose chase and and they didn't have a
[ __ ] £300 bill.
So consider yourself lucky.
And it's just toxic. It is just toxic.
So that's why I just don't bother anymore.
It's always going to be the same. I know
now as well. And the thing is, these
people are going to make you feel like
you're ugly when you're not ugly.
There's nothing wrong with the way that
I look, but because of their unrealistic
[ __ ] standards, you know, I'm not I'm
not dealing with their [ __ ]
Any thoughts on the me approaching for 5 years
and getting nowhere? Or did that slip your mind?
That's what I'm saying. People just
dismiss my struggles. So, there's no
point me even being in an argument.
There's no point me being a candidate to
anything because people just ignore
everything that you say. Everything that
you say you've been through, it don't
suit them. So there's there's no point
in me being a candidate in this in this
debate. I might as well not be there
because you just dismiss everything.
I said it to my mom as well. I was like
there's no point of I said this to her
earlier. I said there's no point of the
debate because you just dismiss anything
that people show you or what people tell you. Like it's
it's like there's no you need to stop
going around in circles. And the thing
is, yeah, it it might sound easy to you,
oh yeah, go out and try again. Go out
and try again. But this is how we get in
the same cycle.
You need to join the pool industry. You
need to leave the country.
You need to use escorts for the rest of
your life. You need to break the cycle
cuz it ain't good. A cycle is not good.
Cuz let's just say for argument sake I
go out on my birthday.
What do you think is probably going to
happen going from previous experiences
cuz we've got so many of them.
Do you think Right. Okay. It's it's use
this analogy about gambling right if you
gambled right and you started and you
never ever won
you think you would you would do it
again? I don't think you would because
what gets you hooked is the wins.
We've had no dates since April. So, it's
not even like there were little ones
there. Oh, well, this that they're long
gone today getting good experiences in
this country. So, there's there's, you know,
it's like I I lost when I was playing
them machines. I think I lost for like
six months in in a row when I was living
at the other house. That's why I gave up
because you need to break the cycle. If
you don't break the cycle, you're [ __ ]
So that's it. And and and obviously like
I said, it's hard because
um it's so easy, you know.
No, I'm not telling that story again. But yeah,
like I said, Caddy man, if you was
getting um dates and stuff and little
successes, then it'd be a different story, you know.
But yeah, I can't believe these women
actually think they have it bad.
Could you imagine the women actually go
out and approach men and still not get a
date? I'd love to know how they'd feel.
I wonder how they'd feel. Candy,
I love these women that complain they
can't find someone,
you know. I love it. I love it. They
complain they can't find someone when
they can get anyone they want.
They can get anyone they want.
Look at these people that date on
YouTube. Look at these big YouTubers.
Look at the women that they're with.
They're average. They're average people.
If you've seen some of the sidemen
girlfriends, right? They're not even
anything to write home about.
Like it's that bad a normal woman could
probably get with a big YouTuber now.
And an average man couldn't even get a
fat ugly woman.
It's mad, isn't it?
Try central London. Um I've tried
central London for years. They're not interested.
They ain't interested in this country
again. 5 years.
Yeah. Beautiful, sexy woman.
Uh, I bet you I have.
I bet you I have. I I I bet you I
really, really have, mate. I used to go
out approaching every single day.
Trust me, I have. I really, really,
really, really have.
Trust me, I have, mate.
But really, really I've tried
everything. I have approached all day.
Yes, I have. Yes, I have. From the time
I woke up to the time I go to bed. I bet
you there's not a lot of things I ain't
tried. And that's not me being stubborn.
That's me talking the truth.
You know, trust me, I have. They're not
interested in this country.
So, I just call it a day.
And yes, I have. Every time I go out, I
look my best. And still nothing.
I've got a nice after save right there.
Sage. It's what I wore when I last went out. So yeah. Yeah.
sister getting drunk. I ain't drunk for
like a month. Don't miss it to be honest.
So yeah, I have approached all day.
You seem to keep this missing the 5 years.
No, it won't work cuz I've already tried it.
No, it won't work because I've already tried it.
If someone's getting three grand a month
for four years from not working, I think
they've done a lot of [ __ ] If someone's
not had to work in three, four, no, it's
not three years. in four years and they
have all this money. Think of what kind
of [ __ ] they got up to,
you know? Just think of what kind of
[ __ ] that person got up to and realize
how silly what you're saying sounds.
I got up to quite a bit. Quite a bit,
mate. You know,
trust me, it won't work. They're not
interested. you can look your best,
smell your best, and they're still not
interested. I remember when I I was also
going to the gym as well when I was in
the um uh old house and I started
approaching again. Not interested.
I've tried everything. Literally
everything. I've tried more than anyone
in the world.
It would be very hard to find somebody
that tried more than me. So,
if you haven't met anyone at this age,
you're never going to meet anyone. Well, that's it. So, yeah. Don't know.
I'm not liking the odds, bro. I'm not
liking the odds that, you know, the next
time you go out, it's going to be
different. I'm not liking them odds.
I wouldn't put a bet on them odds. So,
why would I Why would I try? I wouldn't
put a bet on them odds. It's got to be
in the millions. It's got to be in the
because again, the argument is always
going to be why haven't you already found someone?
And what can people say to that? They
can't say you didn't look your best.
They can't say that you didn't try your
best. They can't say that you're ugly.
They can't say anything. So,
So that's where we're at. Oh, well
Um, yeah, if it only took one, it would
have happened by now.
Uh, yes, I have tried before telling
them it's my birthday cuz I've been out
on my birthday.
Uh, yes I have. Cuz every birthday I go
out. I've gone out every birthday.
Yeah. Every birthday I've had I've gone
out. So yeah, I have to write that.
Well, you're talking to someone that's
that's tried everything.
Literally like I'm not even being
stubborn. I'm not being I'm not even you
might think I'm being awkward and that
and I'm coming across as like
argumentative, but you're talking to
someone that got three grand for 4 years
for not working. I think I got up to a
lot of [ __ ] you know?
I've tried everything. [Music]
But you ain't But you ain't tried
approaching trying to I've been all over
the country approaching. I've been all
over London approaching. I've been all
over the country. I've been to Scotland.
I've been to Wales.
Yes, I have tried.
I've tried that a million times. I live in London,
so why wouldn't have I tried that? What
the [ __ ] are you? I've tried King's
Cross. Tried everything. They're not
interested in this country.
They told me this a long time ago, so I
[ __ ] wouldn't waste my [ __ ] time.
Yes, I have. I've tried Chinatown. I
used to go to the O'Neals in Chinatown
every week. I used to go um
Thursday and Saturdays. Every week I
used to go drinking in the O'Neal's Chinatown.
I You can't just give up. I think I can
cuz I have. So I can just give up cuz I
Bro, I used to go to Chinatown three
times a week approaching. I used to go
to the O'Neal's Water Street.
>> Oh no. O'Neal was a water street. You
know what I mean?
Yeah. O'Neal's Water Street is in Chinatown.
I tried in the waxies as well. Chinatown.
So yeah, I have tried Chinatown many
times. I've been everywhere. So
So that's it.
And you know the thing is kind of uh you
know what it's not even about this is
how [ __ ] up this is. Yeah. It's not
even about finding um the one. It's
let's talk about how you can't even get
a [ __ ] date man. Do do you understand
what I mean bro? Like hear me out here.
It's not about oh finding the one not
finding the one right. Um, but they're
not uh you if you can't even get a date,
it doesn't look good, does it, bro?
That's That's the thing. Tried um
Romanian and Polish girls. Yes, I have.
Um and they weren't interested either.
I've come across a lot of Polish women,
a lot of Romanian women, obviously being
in London. Yes, I have.
Chinese, I haven't tried Chinese cuz I
don't find them attractive.
But I have tried Romanian. Yes. And I
have tried Polish and I have tried
Albanian as well.
Keep suggesting things that that you
don't think I've tried and I'll tell you
if I've tried it or not. But Chinese I
haven't because I don't find them attractive. So
I'm trying to think if I have.
I think I have. No. No. I think I
technically have, but not many times.
But they weren't interested either.
I think I have actually, but not that
many times. But I I'm sure I have.
Miracle. I think I have maybe a couple
of times. They weren't interested either.
But if you been like a proper Chinese,
born there. No, I haven't. Ones that
were born here. I have. Yeah.
But yeah, I have Romanian.
Nope. I've even offered money
cuz when I was at my wits end, I was
like, "Oh, let me pull out some money,
see if this works." Um, that never worked either
pretty much. I've tried everything but speed dating. So,
I've already tried that. I've already
I've tried that. I've got videos where
Offering money. Yep.
Yeah, I have tried that.
It was more for sex, but I was offering like£3400.
I was like, "Oh [ __ ] that doesn't
work." I thought that was going to work.
Me, I generally thought that would have
worked. I was surprised when that never
worked because obviously the state of
what the country is in and a lot of
people don't have money.
Yes, I have done that. Yes, I have done
I can actually I can actually send you a
video where I've done that. To be honest,
I have done that. Yes, I have.
I was surprised. cuz I think I offered
£400 at one point and nah,
I was surprised cuz most people got
skin. Most people are are broke because
of the state of this country. So I'm
surprised that never worked.
Like obviously like yeah people have got
like morals and stuff but you know you'd
be surprised what people would do for
money. You know people have done it
before you know when when it's something
like that. So I'm I mean
it's like and the thing is they don't
have money as well a lot of these people. So
but yeah I have tried that. Yeah. So met. yeah,
you have to understand, bro. People have
got different lives than you. I very
much have tried everything that I could think of
and it's just the same old.
But how can you find a one if you can't
if you're not even going on dates?
No, it won't work.
I've offered like I pulled out cash like
£400 cash and offered people money for a
[ __ ] and it never worked. They weren't interested. So,
no, it won't work.
I've also offered to take people to like
Burger and Lobster, which is [ __ ]
expensive. It doesn't work.
Trust me, it don't work.
And why would you pay to take somebody
on a date when you're paying for a date?
That doesn't make any sense. You're
paying for the date. It doesn't work.
You can meet somebody and you can
approach and say, "Oh, um, let's go to
the shard. Let's go to the shard."
I've done it. Oh, candy man. I've done
it. Have I tried inside shopping
centers? Yep. Many times. I used to live
by one. Yep. Many, many, many, many
times. I've done it in different cities
as well. Manchester, Newcastle.
I've tried in a coffee shop. I remember
um I approached somebody in a coffee
shop and I start I tried starting a
conversation with them and I said, "Oh,
where?" I said, "Oh, where you from?"
They like, "Just London." I just walked away.
No, you won't. So, yeah, you could
approach someone and offer to take them
to the sh. They still wouldn't go with you.
Cuz I used to offer like expensive dates
and they still weren't interested. So,
and I think the fact that you can't even
get a date, it just shows you're not
going to meet anyone because you don't
even have people willing to give you a
chance. So, it's very very unlikely that
you're just going to suddenly find
someone that's different. Very, very
unlikely, especially with my history.
So, yeah, you've got a bone to pick with
me. What bone?
But no, I've done it, Candy, man. I've
gone out and offered people money on the street sober.
Yeah, that was me. Yeah. Yeah, that was
me. I ruined the [ __ ] didn't I?
Well, it's ruined for me. So,
Yep. Yeah, that was me.
Oh, Franklin's on his little phone. So, yeah.
Um, so yeah, I have offered um
I've approached on the street, shopping
malls, restaurants, train station.
Doesn't really matter where you approach
someone. They're all the same anyways. So,
yeah, they're all the same, so it
doesn't matter where.
I was loving the conversation about this
earlier with Laney that there's no
[ __ ] point you
starting something if you're just going
to dismiss everything someone says and shows you.
You could you end up feeling like the
boy who cried wolf. If you get into an
argument with any of these people, you
feel like I just thought I'd put that
Ricky in his place.
Then I think I'd done a good job of
that. But you know, at the end of the
day, you just end up feeling like the
boy who cried wolf, if you get what I mean. greasy.
It's like being a kid abused 100 years
ago where you you weren't listened to.
You know, years and years ago, like 70
to 100 years ago, if you got abused as a
child, like hit or whatever, you
couldn't go to anyone that you wouldn't
be listened to. Back in the day, you
weren't listened to. So, that's what it
feels like with this.
And I'm not even taking a piss. like it
feels like the boy who cried wolf
and it it it just gets frustrating, you know.
So, it really really does get annoying
cuz it doesn't suit them.
You know, my experiences don't suit them.
Sounds funny, but it's true. Is it? Yeah.
Who the [ __ ] is doing fireworks?
Oh yeah, I have tried that.
Yes, I have tried it.
You're saying you bet I haven't tried,
but we've already established that I've tried everything.
Yes, I have. I've been out with Stone
Island, Fresh Trainers.
Yes, I have. And it still never made a difference. Yep.
It's so sickening to think the things
I've tried. I mean, I remember going to
a mall, right, and spending £1,200
before on garments and I was looking
fresh as, but never made a difference.
Never made an ounce of difference.
Yeah. Smile at them for them to look at
you like you're a [ __ ] weirdo. Yeah. Yeah, man. Oh, yeah.
Yeah. Remember I spent £1,200 on garments?
You remember when I had them 50 nights?
Still didn't really get much.
The mugs game in this country
to me. I could sit and complain for the
rest of my life and no one can tell me
nothing. That's how bad it is.
No one can tell you anything, Grezy.
That's how bad it is.
What can they say? Go and try, you know,
like what can they say? It's not
something that you've already done.
Just need to focus on leaving now. Money and leaving. Bro,
why would I try something like that?
That's ridiculous. I've already offered
people money. I tell you what I have
done. Oh, I tell you what I have done,
which I thought this was going to work
back um when I used to meet people and
they didn't reply. I used to save money
for like a couple of months and have
them in 50s and I'd say, "Look how much
money I've saved." Um and it used to be
a lot of it not going out. And I thought
that would tempt them to want to meet,
but they still weren't interested. So,
I used to do stuff like that. I used to
do similar stuff before, but you know,
I don't know why my mom Yeah, my mom was
trying to My mom brought up, "Oh, did
you have a woman going on a wild goose
chase?" I said, "Yes."
I She was being a [ __ ]
Cuz my sister brought it up. I said I'm
going to reply and I say to her like you
know in the future if you are going to
bring something up like that at least
explain why I actually done it. There
was a reason why I done that cuz she was
being a [ __ ] So
you don't want to know. She don't want
to know you. She don't want to know you.
Reddit bans people.
We Reddit bans people, man. Madness. Anyone
here go on Reddit or no?
Yeah. I just can't justify it anymore.
I can't justify going out trying anymore.
Like I said, I could understand if you
was going on dates and they weren't
going anywhere, then I could I could understand it,
you know? But if you can't even get a
[ __ ] date, then it's like, what the
I'd see that as a W if you was
frequently getting dates. I'm like,
okay, well, women get dates, you get
dates. Fair enough. But if you can't
even get that, then
you know there's there's no going back.
Yes, I have. I've been to Middlesbrough.
Yes, I have, mate.
I've approached in many different cities.
Yep, I have. I've been to Middlesbrough,
been to I've approached Newcastle where
people looked [ __ ] I remember this
woman before. I approached her and she
had like a bruise on her neck where
she'd been strangled. I'll never forget
that. It was [ __ ] wild. Where she'd
obviously been strangled by someone. You
could see the bruise on her [ __ ]
neck. [ __ ] me. I have, mate. I've been
to Leeds. have been been Sheffield.
I have I have mate.
They just aren't interested in this country.
Virgin boy skin in a bed sh and I bet no
money in it. Oh yeah.
You reckon you'll ever lose it? You
reckon you'll ever pop it?
Pop that recard. So yeah,
that's how it is. E.
Hey, did you go on my uh
did you go on my messages? Did you see
the video I put up of my messages? You
did you watch the messages from the women?
I didn't delete any comments. I don't
need to delete comments. I'm a big boy.
You know, I stand my ground.
Did you watch like the messages I put
up? What they've done and that?
Yeah. And you see what they do and you
see what they like. I'm going to send my
mom that video.
Did you see my comment back to Ricky?
Yeah. I don't know why audio is not
working on my phone.
Yeah. [ __ ] any of them. Uh you said you
watched the video
so you would know that I didn't
considering they led me on. So you just
said that you watched the video. Yeah.
None of them are interested.
Just leading me on. Same old [ __ ] I
might send my mom the video. See what
she thinks of that, you know.
Oh, watch the video, bro. Watch the
video. Go over the combos.
Oh, go over it, bro. It's only It's only 6 minutes
and read the comments and what I've
replied back to this Ricky.
Take your time, man. We got all We got all night.
Don't we Rick? You like it when I say that, Rickster?
I just thought I had to reply to that
comment, bro. And and I had great fun
writing it to be honest, you Huh? Fireworks.
>> Don't let these cunning women win.
I let these hunted women win it.
to talk to women with. outside.
[ __ ] sake, man. [Applause] So yeah,
it's not a big p. >> Oh.
>> Oh [ __ ]
Almost saw my Pekka there.
Oh, look at that beard. E,
it's not long enough yet.
Stop it, fireworks.
You're being silly now.
Yeah. And and also read out Ricky's
reply and read my reply.
I love I can't stop reading it out. I'm
addicted to reading it out, you know?
I'm addicted to [ __ ]
reading it out cuz it shows how
intelligent I am. See, people
underestimate me and they think I'm
thick, but I'm not. Don't read it, man.
I don't need to delete comments, mate.
I'm not scared of any comments.
How How could I be when I know the truth,
you know? Come on, bro. I don't need to
delete anything. The only reason I disabled comments
is cuz it was for the spam [ __ ]
stupid self-projected [ __ ] trolls.
But I thought, let me leave leave the
comments open because people think that
I I don't because I'm a coward. You know,
>> I ain't some [ __ ] bad [ __ ] with no
bed, no money in it.
I've got a B to pick with you. Yeah,
I've got a bone to pick with you.
Oh, do you? Uhhuh. Yeah.
Yeah, that's why I gave up, bro. To be honest,
I just saw a summary of what it was like
and I was like, there's no point.
You still there?
The only ones that weren't in the wrong
were the ones that didn't reply.
But it is still a bit um
it's still a bit um what's the word? The
ones that didn't reply. But it is still
a bit um
it's still a bit uh weird.
Because the thing is, these people say
that women go for personality and stuff,
yet if you're not their physical type,
they won't even give you a chance.
I've already approached a fat and ugly
woman when I was in leads.
And to be honest, I wouldn't I wouldn't
do it anymore because I don't like fat
and ugly women. I shouldn't have to get
with a fat ugly woman. There's nothing
wrong with the way that I look. I should
be able to date someone in my league.
No, not even fit. Just somebody that looks normal. So
I should I want to date somebody in my league.
Whether that's five, six, seven. So
So what's your opinion on the messages?
They had the same attitude.
I'll give you uh I'll give you an
example. There's this woman who is on
Instagram. I think she's like 37
and she's fat and ugly and she's
constantly showing her tits on Instagram
and I always like, "Oh, let's meet.
Let's meet. Let's meet." And she will
she won't meet. She'll message me. She
say she says I'm good-look and she will
never meet. She says that she's with
someone even though she isn't. So yeah.
What do you mean how blunt they are? So
and that's that's only like 10% of it.
I've got many many more messages. Um, so
it was just in my best it was in my best
interest to just give up.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. Yeah,
there's been a few of them. That's what
I'm saying. All of these people are
saying that you're acting weird and
you're acting desperate, but it ruined
their argument because
they are saying that they're going to
meet you. They're loving your messages
and then they're backing out.
Yeah, it's been the same for years. It's
always going to be the same here. That's
why I gave up,
you know. Yeah, it will never change ever.
What about the American one that said
that she's got getting back with her ex? Oh, no.
Yeah, it's been a there's been a lot of them, bro.
So, they just lead people on.
The ones that said, "Oh, I'm sorry. I'm
not interested." That's not leading
someone on. But it's a bit strange as to
why they're not interested.
Considering so many people say they go
for personality, but they don't even
want to give you a chance.
It is a bit odd, isn't it?
They're so scared to um offend
That's the right word.
Yeah, but I won't I wouldn't want to do that.
People say that all women aren't the same.
I said to my mom earlier, I said, "Uh,
well, they do a lot of the same stuff.
They act the same way. They do the same
stuff. They say the same stuff. They
have the same mannerisms for people that
are all apparently different.
They do a lot of the same stuff for
people that aren't the same. I'll give
it to them. If they're not all the same,
then they act a lot like one another,
don't they? And I was saying to my mom
as well that if I was um I was saying
that uh if somebody was exactly the same
as me, I'd be very concerned.
And then you hear about people, oh well,
other people in relationships. Then I I
actually look and then you actually see
that more people are not in
relationships. Or maybe it's even,
but most of the people I know aren't in relationships. Friends,
even women I've met, they're not in relationships.
Like there's there is a lot of single
people out there. So
more people are single than aren't
to be honest cuz think of all of these
women that you meet that give you their
number then lead you on. They're
obviously single in it. The ones that
generally don't have boyfriends and
think of how many times they lie about having boyfriends.
More people are single. There's got to
be more people are single. It has to be
because how do you come across so many
single people? Yeah. Obviously, there's
people in relationships, but
there's got to be just as many single people.
I don't know the exact statistics, but
it has to be because of um Yeah,
cuz you meet so many single people
and you meet the occasional person in a
relationship. That's that's that's that.
I swear to God. Cuz
if you look at all of them women on
WhatsApp, they were all single.
They were all single. Strange. So yeah. Yeah.
No, I haven't tried that cuz I don't
want to be with an escort.
There was one escort I like but she was married.
She was [ __ ] married.
But I used to [ __ ] this 19year-old.
like a year like two years ago.
Sometimes I just give her £50 and she'd
give me a [ __ ]
which is a bargain really cuz she would
like swallow and stuff. So it was a
bargain. £50 for a [ __ ] and them to
swallow it. That's a [ __ ] bargain
with an escort you're talking like £200.
So I used to just do that. Yeah.
See, I can never be a normal person that
likes women and sticks up for women
because I've had so many experiences with them.
So this is what you obviously when
you've had so many experiences, you
can't And also, why have you had so many
experiences? You put yourself on the
line many times for these women to prove
they're not all the same.
You went through so much [ __ ] with them,
and they always prove that they're all
the same. So, why are you going to
continuously meet people that are all
the same? They will never change, not
even at the age of 28. So,
um, it was an American in the alleyway.
Yeah, there's some American in the alleyway.
Yeah. She's like, "I really want you,
but I don't think you want me."
A lot of these women I I'll give you a
fun fact. Uh Hugh,
a fun story rather.
I I met this Albadian woman before. We
was kissing. I was touching her. We was
kissing. that was touching her
and then she was like, "Oh, she doesn't
want to meet again. She just wants to be
friends." I said, "Really? Is there
anything I done wrong? Wrong? What did I
do wrong?" And then she was like, "Oh,
we don't understand English. I don't
understand English. So, it's best not to
meet." I was like, "But you already knew
there was a language barrier.
So, there's people that you could
actually kiss and they'd still they'd
still ghost you and stuff.
It's just a Mugs game, isn't it? It's
just a mugs It's just a Mugs game.
That's That's that started it. So,
just all the same, bro. Oh, that's it.
Oh, not the same.
I used to say that to the skin virgin in the bed.
Women are all the same. I used to say,
"You don't know all women. You don't
know all women."
I know more women than you. I've been
with more women than you.
I don't I don't know how people can say
that they're not all the same. I I don't
know how they can say that.
I really don't know how people can say
that all women aren't the same. Nope. No.
The worst one was that USA is he love
bombing, leading on then ghosting and
making up stories.
Typical American, eh?
Typical [ __ ] America [ __ ] king.
Yeah, they're not going to give a [ __ ]
are they? Why are they going to care?
They're not going to give a [ __ ] are they?
People on Reddit tell me that I'll meet someone here.
on Reddit say I'll meet someone new.
They've been saying it for years.
want to know.
I want to know. Yeah, women. Ignore us. Uh
yeah. Well, I'm leaving the country. Yeah. So, yeah,
you got a few options. You either
leave the country,
which is what I'm doing, or you use
escorts every month for like six months
and then consider trying again after 6
months. But you need to stop for like 6
months for your own well-being. Um,
or you could approach every single day,
but I wouldn't recommend that because
then that means No, that's not an option
either because Yeah. So basically that's
the only options that you have.
So you couldn't approach every day cuz
you'd just become depressed. So yeah,
but if you thinking about trying her
again, you'd have to stop for 6 months.
Oh, she just dismisses my struggles.
Bit like most people, they just dismiss your struggles. Yeah.
That's it. I'd explain to her why I like
when I had that [ __ ] going on a wild
goose chase and I'd explain why I done
it cuz she was being a [ __ ] and she was
being passive aggressive and um it
doesn't seem to suit them. So that's why
I don't really talk about it anymore. I
avoid like any kind of argument because
anything you show them or tell them,
they will just ignore it.
So there's no there's not really a point
in it to be honest. And you end up
feeling like the boy who cried wolf.
Pointless. [ __ ] pointless.
Cuz she said to me earlier, "Didn't you
have somebody going on a wild goose
chase?" I said, "Yes, because they were
being a [ __ ]
It wasn't an innocent person
being passive aggressive trying to tell
me how I need to change my hair and try
and tell me how I need to go to the gym
and like when I'm not even fat. Like she
was trying to be passive aggressive to
try to knock someone's confidence down
like and and it wasn't advice, you know,
it was being passive aggressive. So
yeah, I had her going around All's
mother. Yeah, she's a [ __ ] [ __ ] her.
Yeah, that's how I explained why I done it. Obviously,
uh yeah, what can anyone say? There's
nothing anyone can say.
It would never change, would it? So what
what what is there left for anyone to
say, you know? So
that's where we're at, bro. That's where we're at. Yeah. virgin boy
skin with no bed, no money in it.
That's so catchy, isn't it?
So catch you that.
So I assume that's the one my sister was
speaking about. She must have been
speaking about that time.
Yeah, she was being a [ __ ]
Who are you to try and tell someone what
what they should look like, especially
when you first met someone? That's not
something that you say to someone.
But yeah, this is a headache that people don't need.
I can't believe that uh
I can't believe that a cat I can't
um that got 10 thumbs up. just read
through some message and you weak of
desperation loving their messages asking
what they like about you saying you go
their city sending voice notes all after
meeting once you are too full on it's
massively offputting to women that's
partly why you won't they won't meet you
it's the way you're acting also non-stop
asking to meet them when you don't know
them you have no game that's your
problem this is not a dig just facts
did you read my response to him
I'm going to read it again. I love
reading this. I love reading things I wrote out.
I don't know how that I don't know how
that got 10 thumbs up to be honest cuz
the proof is there what they've done. But yeah,
it's like they've completely dismissed
everything that you've shown them and
made up something that suits themsel
cuz I mean there's messages there. Okay. So
he wrote just Okay, let's let's do it
then. So he wrote just read through some
Did you read it?
Well, he wrote, "Just read through some
messages and you weak of desperation.
Loving their messages, asking what they
like about you, saying you'll go their
city, sending voice notes all after
meeting once. You are way too full on
it's massly off-putting to women. That's
partly why they won't meet you. It's the
way you're acting." Also, none non-stop
asking to meet them and you don't know
them. You have no game, PJ. That's your
problem. And this is not a dig, just
facts. Then I replied,
listen to my reply, right? which I don't
think a lot of people read. I said, "I
replied to your message on the video,
but in case you can't be bothered to
watch it, I'll be nice and reply here."
I think that I've I've read in quotation
some messages. Pretty much sums up my
argument. You seem to dismiss the ones
that didn't reply to the first message.
You also just missed ones where they
replied back once. I asked them a
question. I never heard from them ever
again. How about the one who admitted to
having a great time with me with me and
was still up for meeting and then hit me
3 hours before meeting me with I'm sorry
I'm going to give it another go with my
ex. What was the excuse there Ricky? So
yeah, the sum was you picking out a few
that you thought you would write on and
the others you dismissed because it
didn't suit your narrative. Then I put
in quotation mark loving their messages.
I said as I mentioned in my previous
video in brackets in case you haven't
seen it I would strongly advise getting
your eyes tested if you have haven't
already if you haven't so already
because how did you manage to dismiss
the fact they were loving my messages
more than I love theirs. So if going by
your logic loving someone's messages on
WhatsApp is a big problem would that not
make the women who love my messages the
problem also since they are doing the
same. Some even loved my messages and I
never loved theirs. So, by your logic,
it's okay for women to love my messages,
but if I do it back, it justifies them
being toxic and leading me on and it
being a me problem. You never address
the women that loved my my first message
first. Do tell us what you thought about
that. I'm curious.
Then I quoted another thing he said,
asking what they like about you saying
you'll go to a city and sending voice
notes all after meeting once. You are
too full on and that's partly why they
won't meet you. It's the way that you're
acting. quotation mark. I said, now as I
stated previously, this goes back to the
I quote I quote some messages, but to be
honest, it's less than 10%. I said that
to one to maximum. What about the rest
that that you dismissed that involve
none of the things that you're
mentioning? Also, you might want to
retake geography lessons because Finland
is a country, not a city, last time I
checked. So, what I met up with a woman
from Finland. We was talking for a
month. So, I suggested going to see her.
Big deal. question. Why are you not
allowed to send someone voice notes
because you've only met them once? Is
this some kind of new rule you've made
up? Pretty sure people send voice notes
all the time to people they haven't even met. Um
then um he wrote uh in quotation mark
that's partly why they won't meet you
because of how you're acting. I said,
I'm not now I'm not sure if you
remember, but I approached women in
public in public bars, clubs, um in
public bars, clubs, uh public uh one say
so well in public bars clubs. I've never
been one for online dating. So, if I'm
approaching them and they reply and they
agreed to meet me and love my messages
in in brackets the thing you called me
out for, I would have guessed I come I
came across as normal since why give me
their number, reply, love my messages,
then agree to meet me. I'm sure if I was
acting desperate or being off-put and
they wouldn't bother even replying in
the first place. That ruins your whole
argument. um them the other one he
quoted also quote quote from him also
non-stop asking them to meet you when
you don't know them I said to him I
would advise you to learn the concept of
non-stop asking a woman out twice is
hardly non-stop I don't need to know the
ins and out about someone because I
asked them out on a date twice like when
people have a problem it's like when
people have a problem with you trying to
meet a woman after a week of speaking to
her and claiming it's too soon yeah have
no problem of a woman wanting to meet
someone straight away without even
knowing anything about them in brackets
personal experience. Um then in the last
where I quote it was you have no game PJ
and this is not a dig just facts. I said
hm well considering I don't have to rely
on dating apps and can approach women
and get them to reply. I would bet
that's more than what most men can do
including yourself. Am I lying? If not
please do um show me how it's done. I'd
love to learn from the best. Then
uh I wrote also before I finish this I
just wanted to say please learn the
definition of facts. Facts is something
that is set in stone. In fact, let me
put put up a quote from yours a while
back. You're good-looking PJ. Women are
too picky. That's why you can't pull.
Which very much sums of sums up
everything you say as being anything but
facts. You can't play two sides of a
coin. Hold that out. And I never heard
from him ever again.
You know, I don't think a lot of people
read it to be honest, but he got bodied,
mate. You know what? What can you really
say to that? You can say anything you
want. You're not blocked. You know,
the guy got his ass whooped, bro.
I just I I [ __ ] deconstructed
everything he said cuz it's [ __ ]
That's why it's absolute [ __ ]
You know, you can't send a woman a voice
note because you've only met her but
once. Is that is that is that a [ __ ]
um is that uh is that some sort of is
that uh is there a requirement to having
to meet someone? See, what I don't
understand, right, is one woman I met
before, um she wanted to meet me
straight away. Her first message was
like, "Oh, let's meet Tuesday." Yeah.
When I speak to a woman for a week and I
try to meet her, apparently it's too um
apparently it's too it's too it's too full on
even though they can want to meet me straight away. So
I think it's um the fact that I don't
look fully white.
I'll show you me, bro.
I don't mind showing you, man. So
he got he got destroyed though, didn't
he? He actually got destroyed.
He got [ __ ] bodied, bro.
Because what he's saying doesn't make
any sense. He he he would have had a
better argument saying, "Oh, the ones
that didn't reply was because you come
across as bad." Then I wouldn't really
have an argument.
Then I could say, "Uh, well, yeah." So,
if if someone said, "See, I I would know
how to win that argument
because I would I would I would
deconstruct the ones that um that didn't
that didn't reply.
I've got I've got after shave. I've got Sage.
I've got After Shave. Doesn't make a
difference. I've got all I've got the
Sage. I had to buy another one cuz it got stolen."
So if he had said that then he he could
have well there's nothing I could have said
really but he you know he if he was act
if it was the way he was acting why are
they messaging you agreeing to meet you
it doesn't get me [ __ ]
it doesn't get me [ __ ] mate
it doesn't get me anything
stop dismissing my struggle
before I pick you up and throw you, you know.
Yeah. So, that's that.
Why do people seem to dismiss all the
things women do? I'm just c I'm just
curious. Sorry to sound like I'm
repeating, but I just want to know.
It doesn't suit them, does it?
Oh, you can't give me hope.
I'll show you what I look like the last
time I went out approaching.
I don't think you can give me hope, bro.
That was the final straw.
When I last went out approaching, I'll
send you the video.
Yep. Like they just missed where the
women was leading me on. Yeah. Like I I
met um someone from America before and
their first message was
um do you want to meet up on Tuesday?
That was literally their first message.
Do you want to meet up on Tuesday? And I
was like hell yeah. But if I was
speaking to somebody for a week and I
tried meeting them, they would say, "Oh,
you're moving too fast. You're trying to
meet them too fast. So do you understand
the double standards? Do you not
understand what's wrong with that? You know,
so it's okay for a woman
to and that whole don't knowing someone,
you don't need to know someone to send
somebody two voice notes.
The [ __ ] That doesn't make sense.
So if I tried to meet a woman within the
first message of meeting her, I'd get
Simps chasing me down with an axe. I
would get white knights trying to kill
me. But a woman tries to meet you
straight away. That's completely fine.
It's completely fine. It's not weird.
See what I'm saying, bro? It's [ __ ] madness.
I'll show you what I look like when I
last went out.
But how how that how they got thumbs up.
how I can only assume that them 10
thumbs up or a people that don't like me
or b people that don't leave the house
because I I don't understand how they can
how they can agree when I've literally
shown their messages. I don't care if
they agree or disagree, but I I don't
know. And then one one person that
agreed with me got three thumbs up.
Four, if you if you count me, but three
that's not including me. So, it's I feel
sorry for them, bro. Them 10 people,
they they've got a lot to learn to be
honest with you.
They must not speak to women.
Already tried it. I've got Stone
Islands. Doesn't make a difference.
They're not interested.
I can show you some of the stonies I
have. Actually, this is what I look like
when I last went out.
owe you what I have. I need to buy some
new jeans, man. But I still I mean,
look, I can show you what I've got.
That was when I last went out.
I got some trainers. They're not They're
not fresh enough, but
I can show you. I put the badges back on it.
I can show you some stuff I got, bro.
Mind that. These are like expensive gums.
Um, this is my stony.
That's my stony got dry clean. Door look
fresh as [ __ ]
Got these trainers. I think I've worn
them a couple of times. They're still
fresh. Kind of.
They're still kind of fresh.
I'd say they're fresh enough.
I've got two trainers, Harachis and these.
These are my are good ones. Yeah. Hold on.
They still smell box fresh to be honest.
Yeah, they still smell box fresh. Yeah. See,
got a lot of stonies, bro.
I got these jeans, Ammani jeans, but to
be fair, the buttons broke on him,
but you could still rock them. They are
a bit faded, but you could still rock
them. This, this, and this.
I got these jeans,
and I got these jeans.
So, I mean, evil ones you could rock.
Also, real gars. I don't wear fake [ __ ]
I mean, I tell you what happened with
this year. I was in the toilet and the button broke,
which obviously I can still wear a
couple of times. The button broke.
Luckily, I had a belt on,
but I'll still wear him a couple more times.
Yep, they are all real. I wouldn't ever
wear anything fake. I got a few more
stonies. I've got a green one as well.
I used to have a lot of bloody matey. I
still have money, but you know, I used
to have a lot of money. A lot of disposable money.
Got Reese stuff as well. So,
I must be doing something wrong.
Yeah. Well, you saw the messages.
You saw the messages.
It is all fresh. I mean, you saw I mean,
I can show you.
I can show you a couple my approaches if you want.
I could be doing something wrong or
women could just have an in unrealistic standards.
I mean, maybe. I like this. I need to
wear this. This is expensive.
Yeah, I could be doing something wrong
or they could just have unrealistic
standards and you might not be their
type. That's also a possibility.
So, yeah, man. They're my stories.
Yeah. Yeah, it could be do doing
something wrong or you could just be
none of these women's type, which is
probably the most likely to be honest.
It's not about doing something wrong. If
you're not someone's physical type,
they're not interested. I learned that.
I learned that. I also learned that from
Reddit as well. Um,
so it it's very much to do with like physical.
If you're not their exact preference,
they won't get with you. That's and I
learned that. And I think that's what
people don't understand. They seem to
think that it's about personality and no
no. Yeah. After you've already
passed the threshold of of physical. So
yeah, that's it.
Doesn't matter if I fall a few times.
Okay. Okay. Let's let's give you a
summary of my trying. Okay.
You want me I'll give you a summary. So,
I've been out in London about
a million times. No exaggeration. I've
been to Manchester 10 times. I've been
to Liverpool. Always wanted to go back
to Liverpool. Liverpool. Uh Liverpool.
I've been to Liverpool. I've been to
Manchester 10 times. I've been to
Newcastle. I've been to Sheffield two
times. I've been to Leeds. I've been to
Scotland two times. I've been to Wales
three times. I've been to Brighton,
which I've done a I've never been on a
night out in Brighton, but I've done
approaches in Brighton. Been to
Nottingham four times. Been to
Birmingham seven times.
I've been to so many places and
approached so many different women.
Multiple I've done it in Milton Kees as
well since you spoke about shopping
centers. And through all of them years
of trying, I've only had six one night stands.
That is that is disgusting.
I mean, in itself, that is [ __ ]
disgusting. It doesn't it doesn't make
up for all of the bad experiences, you know, hotels. So,
also what's really bad about it is you
didn't get as many dates as you should
have been getting. It's not even about
sex. It's like there's no like when I
went Manchester. Okay, so let me give an
example. Last time I went Manchester, I
should have an option to be able to go
back there and meet someone. Whatever
happens happens. No one knows what will
happen. But that's another thing. It's
not just about sex or or or that. It's
about the fact that you don't have any
options in any of these places, which
you should which you which you should
because when you've gone to these
places, you haven't even got dates.
That's the thing that's [ __ ] up about
it. You should be getting dates regular.
Somebody that looks the way that I do,
that can approach the way I do, should
be getting should be getting dates.
That's the thing. If I had two dates for
them 10 numbers and they didn't go
anywhere, then okay, whatever. I would
have been back on the bandwagon in two
weeks. But somebody with my look should
be getting dates. Somebody with my look
should be getting more. And the fact
that you're not suggests that you're no
one's type in this country. It's got to
be. It's [ __ ] obvious.
Whether it's cuz you've got a beard,
whether it's because you don't look
fully white. That's why I put it down to obviously
appearance. It's got to be. There's
nothing else it can be.
Oh, no. I didn't.
But like every time you go out, you
should get a date cuz women get dates
easily. Like there's this woman, she
gets three dates a month, so you can't
even get a date. So
that's what makes it seem like, you
know, it's impossible cuz if you can't
even get a date, I mean. Yeah.
So it's got to be cuz you don't look
fully white or you got a beard or
there's something there's something not
right there. I know there's not because
Yeah. There's you know
you there's something not right. you
should be getting more success than that.
Which makes me think that it's got to be
their standards. They're unrealistic. It
has to be. There's nothing else it can
You know, people want to pull it down to
personality and stuff, but in my case,
I'm not even ugly, so it's weird.
Yeah, but not re Okay. Okay. Yeah. In
the past, it seems to have gotten harder
now. If it was as easy as it was back
two years ago, I probably wouldn't give
up. But this year, I've had about three
dates in this whole year and they were
all in the same month.
They were all in the same month. Yep.
And I think it was March. Must have been
March or April. I think it was March.
And since then, I haven't had anything
since. So, that tells you all you need to know. Um, yeah.
And they were just time wasters. So
that's starting it.
But this year I've only had three dates.
Nope. I can tell you exactly what happened. Uh
the first one was
um she approached me. It was on a bank
holiday, right, on a Friday
and um she was talk we was talking right and uh
I got I got her number and she's like,
"Oh, I oh let's meet up." And she seemed
right in her messages. No stuckness just
seemed maybe cuz she was from the north.
She seemed like um quite nice, you know.
She approached me um and we went to um
we went to uh so then we met and she was
living in Hartford. She lives in Harper.
So she traveled down to London. Um so we
met up and just talking about interest.
We had similar interest. Had a drink.
Nothing like holding hands. No weirdness
or anything like that. And I said and
this was a Thursday. I said, "Oh yeah,
it was good meeting. when should we meet
again? And then she's like, "Oh, I
didn't really feel the vibe."
I was like, "Huh?" I was thinking in my
head, I was like, "What? What the [ __ ]
What do you mean you don't feel the
vibe? You approached me. You gave me
Max. I acted as normal as I possibly
could." And you're [ __ ] So, you're
you're saying within 30 minutes
again is because you don't feel the
vibe. So, you're giving up at any sign of disappointment
when feedings can change over
give up very quickly. Um, and I thought,
what the [ __ ] do these people
don't understand? And it pissed me off
the whole night. And then I just sent it.
32 as well. She was 32 and she was
average looking. That's what made it even worse.
being pushy, wasn't being weird, none of
that stuff. Didn't hold her hand, didn't
kiss her. We were like,
"Nope, nothing like that as well, cuz I
would have known." Then the other date was
so that doesn't make any sense.
And feelings change over time as well. They
you know, I mean, what five are they
looking for? And before I get on to the
other ones, I was also another
they have unrealistic expectations
before going on the date. Like they're
expecting some roy
expectation. They will sit there and say
they don't feel the vibe. That's another
thing I I I came to realize with these
dates because you can act normal
the vibe or how they don't feel the
connection. So that's why I was like, is
there a point of me even going out with
any of these people?
And then, okay, so the other two ones,
one was from Birmingham
and to be honest with you, she was [ __ ]
right. And yeah, she was from Birmingham
and um she was bad. And then she was
trying to get me to pay for everything
like her drinks and that and I just
walked out. I just ditched her cuz I'm
not going to [ __ ] sit there and pay
for people's [ __ ] drinks and food all
night. And then the other one, this is
the one that pissed me off. There was
this one from uh Italy.
And then we was we was we was drinking,
vibing, holding hands, vaping. And after
3 hours, I went to try and kiss her and
then she moved away. I was like, "What the fuck?"
Like she didn't want to kiss. I thought
that's a bit strange.
you know, we was holding hands, was
getting on, and I thought, "Yeah, after
three hours, you can try and kiss
someone." And then she used that as an
excuse to not meet me again. And I was
like, "Okay, well, there's no point even
going out with anyone anymore then.
There's no point of even going out with anyone anymore.
If someone's just going to [ __ ] go
out to just pass time, there's no point." So
I gave up from there to be honest. But
those were the last three dates
and that was all in one month. And after
that I didn't get anything else.
So you have to go out and approach.
Oh, like she Oh, I just walked out cuz I
she said, "Oh, let's go get some food."
I said, "Okay." And then she wanted me
to pay for it. So then I just walked out.
Yeah. I just walked out. I just ditched her.
She was She said she was skint and she
only had 20 pound. Yeah. She was from
Birmingham. I remember that one.
So, I had three in a month and then
after that it kind of just Yeah, I
didn't get any after that.
So, they've got unrealistic expectations
cuz I know with that Italian one, if I
didn't try to kiss her, she still
wouldn't have met me.
After I tried to kiss her, she just
went. She just left.
She just left, bro. And tried to use
that. And then I said to her, "Oh, um I
did try to like make amends and stuff."
I said, "Oh, um yeah, sorry about uh the
other day and stuff. I just was like a
bit drunk. I just made an excuse." I
said, "Oh, let's go for like a meal."
Cuz I was really wanting to try again
with this person. Um to see if they were
genuine. And then um they were coming
out with, "Oh, no. I think it's best not to."
But to be honest with you,
um and I sent them like a voice. Oh,
let's just go out for like a meal, like
no drinking and stuff because like I
wanted to try a game with this person.
But if they were really using that as an
excuse, the chances are they were going
to play games to begin with. Also, I
knew she was going to be a [ __ ] And do
you know how I knew she was going to be
a [ __ ] Cuz I offered to buy her a
drink. I remember when I was waiting for
her and I had this bad I could always
pick up on vibes and she was like, "Oh,
no, that's not it's not really
necessary." And I was like,
that's a bit dodgy to say something like
that. Um, you you know, people don't
normally respond that way. It come
across as very,
I don't know, it didn't ring right. You
know, like when when someone like say
you offer to buy someone a drink and
they say that's not necessary, it comes
across as very
stuck up as ridiculous as it sounds
because you would just say no or um you
don't have to or um no it's like that to
me doesn't sound right. I don't know
about you that sounds weird. Um
so yeah. And then I sent a voicemail
saying, "Oh, let's just go out for like
a meal." And when I was walking to the
bookies, no drinking, no nothing. And
she just didn't want to. So then she was
using as an excuse. Oh, I'm going back
to Italy. So chances are they were just
wasting my time.
So why even go out with somebody if if
if you're going to waste their time?
Cuz I knew 100% I would have got ghosted. 100%.
They're always full of excuses and a mo
and and any chance they get to victimize
themselves, they will do it.
What's a red flag? What's saying that
that's not necessary? That was dodgy,
bro. Very, very dodgy.
And I And but to be honest with you,
that was the last date I went on and I
knew it was going to be bad because when
you've had so many dates, you just know
what to expect.
You know what to expect. Now,
what's a red flag that that's not necessary?
Why would you say it's a red flag?
Nah, bro. Just type.
You can just type, bro.
Yeah, that was a proper one. And there
was a date before, right?
I was waiting for her in the casino.
and she was like, "Oh, that's not really um"
She said, "That's not uh that's not
really my vibe."
I said, "Huh? I'm the one taking you on
a date and and a ci you can go on a date
to the casino."
Um, and I knew that one was going to be
a bad one as well because of the vibes,
because of how they're acting. Like, oh,
yeah, that's not really necessary. No,
sorry, not necessary. Um, that's not
really uh that's not really my vibe. I
mean, people go on dates to the casino
all the time when there's so many
casinos in London. You just get on with
it and just do it. You don't sit there
and say it's not your vibe.
And I was like, that was like last
November or no the November before that.
And I was like, "Okay, this doesn't seem
good to me." I can pick up on vibes very
quickly from people.
So, how did you know they're not
necessary to buy a drink is cuz it comes
across as like stuck up.
Yeah, she was a weirdo. Yeah. Yeah, she
turned out to be a weirdo. Yeah, she's
American as well.
Another [ __ ] So,
but there was ones before there was one
I went on before, right? Uh this one
from uh Ukraine and she was all right.
Went casino, vibed,
went for drinks.
Um they weren't rude or anything and
then I was expecting to see them again
and they say, "Oh, there's
I didn't feel the connection." I don't
know what connection they're after.
We were talking about like New Year's
resolutions and stuff. I don't know what
they're actually expecting from someone,
which made me think they've got unrealistic expectations,
you know? They just uh
it's either that or they're purposely
[ __ ] with people. So, like, which one is it? Um,
but yeah, that Italian one, that was
dodgy. And the fact that she didn't want
to meet again just because somebody
tried to kiss her, that's that's not
good enough. So what So what would have
happened then? We would have kept
meeting up and never kissed and never done anything.
I don't understand what why you It's
just weird, bro. Um
so yeah, like the I've been on casino
dates before. It's fun. Yeah,
there was one before she was um
she promised me, "Oh, yeah, we were
going to meet and then she said, "Oh,
I'm getting back with my ex."
They do a lot of the same stuff for
people that aren't all the same. Steven
Howard, I have to keep saying that. I
have to I have to keep saying that. I'm
sorry, mate. They do a lot of the same
stuff for people that are different.
I give them that, mate.
They do a lot of the same stuff. A lot
of them are even vegetarians as well.
That's another similarity they have.
So, it seems that they're looking for this.
So, why do you why do you think that was
a red flag saying that it's not
necessary to buy me a drink?
Because it comes across as like stuck up.
it comes across as like stuck up and I
would have actually like carried on
going and seeing her if she if she was
all right cuz she was good-looking as
well. But she just turned out to be a
[ __ ] like all of them. But Italian women are [ __ ]
They're the they're they're pretty
they're a close second to French to be honest.
But to be honest, French don't come up
come across as stuck up as Italian
women, which is strange because French
people are rude. So,
it's always going to be mind games and
[ __ ] with these people. So, it's
better off not like what people say, the
dating pool has got pee in it. So, yeah.
So, yeah. And I weren't going to carry
on dealing with that [ __ ] So, yeah.
No, she didn't.
Yeah, Italian women are really bad.
They're really I've had a lot of bad
experiences with them, bro.
Um, really bad.
Could you imagine going to Rome and
trying to date? Oh, that never in a
million years would you ever find
someone in that country. They're the
worst. Well, no. French are the worst.
They're the second.
Italian women are bad, bad, bad, bad, bad. Yeah. So,
she couldn't eat any and and even if she
didn't want to drink, she she should
have said I remember I spent like £200
that day on a date cuz I was drinking a
lot as well. I was drinking a lot to be
fair. I kind of miss that bar, you know,
that B1. Oh, it's so nice. I love it,
man. The toilet smell nice. The toilet
smell nice as well. The thing is is that
the thing is is that even if they didn't
they didn't want you to buy them a
drink, there's a way of saying it like,
"Oh, um, you don't need to. Um,
it's fine, honestly." And then if you
try to sway them
or like you buy them a drink, they buy
you a drink or something other than
that. That wasn't right, bro.
I was getting bad vibes after them, to be honest.
And then some of them have been normal,
but then they just claim they don't feel
the connection, which I don't know what
they're after. I generally don't
understand what they want from someone,
you know? You go out, you look smack,
you act normal. I I don't know what more
somebody can do. Seriously, I don't.
That's why I gave up with that as well.
And it's always like you're treading on
eggshells not to [ __ ] it up, bro.
Yeah, that Italian one. I would have
waited. I didn't care about the sex
either. I would have carried on meeting
her. I weren't even thinking about sex or anything.
She seemed like I like the way that she
looked and that. And to be fair, on the
date, she was acting all right. But
yeah, I would have like waited I I
wouldn't have cared, bro. You know, I
would have waited a month or whatever. I
wasn't thinking about that, honestly.
like a kiss is nothing, you know?
You know how I like [ __ ] and [ __ ] I
wasn't even thinking about a [ __ ] or
anything like that. I swear to God. So
that's why I said to them, "Oh, let's
just go out for like a meal without no
drinks and stuff." And they said no. So
I mean, what what do you what would you say?
No. But what happens is you buy them
around, they buy you around
if they don't want you buying
everything. That's that's normally how it goes.
But yeah, I don't know. Yeah.
So they must be [ __ ] with people on purpose
and they say, "Well, why would they want
to waste your time and their time?"
Okay. So if they're not trying to waste
their time and my time, why would you
why would you Okay. Okay. Let's go logic
then. So, why would you approach
somebody, give them your number, and
give up at the first sign of disappointment
when you're 32 and you're average
looking? Why would you give up on the
first sign of disappointment?
You know, that's that's that's another
thing. And that's a big thing with
dating is they give up at the first sign of disappointment.
I could have gave up on USA when I first
met her. I didn't really like the way
she looked. You didn't see me giving up. So
strange. It is weird.
It is a mess. Yeah, really is.
I know. She was like a she was like a
four or five. And I was telling to these
black guys. I met these black guys. They
were from London as well. and they like,
"Oh, you can do better than that. Like,
you you're better than that." I said to
them, "I I understand that, bro, but
that's not the problem. The problem is
if you've got
um if you've got these four out of 10,
five out of 10 that are 32, mind you, is
that is old for a woman thinking that
they're better than you, that's [ __ ]
that that doesn't look good, does it? Do
you understand how it doesn't look good at all?"
Like, it's not the I don't like them or
whatever. It's it's the whole thing of
it. And she's 32. She was 32 as well,
which means that is old for a woman.
It's old. Obviously, men can still look
good in their 40s, but that's old. Even
a woman at 28, that's old.
She No, she wasn't that ugly. She was
like a four out of 10, five out of 10.
Her name was Jessica. She weren't that
she weren't fat. No, she was just like
average to slightly below. You weren't
that bad, but still like I'm above
average and I'm younger than her.
What vibe are you wanting? Like I don't understand.
I can show you what she looks like if
Let me get a picture up if I can find her. Um,
where is this [ __ ] woman now?
She wasn't stuck.
Oh, that's going to annoy me now. Where
the [ __ ] is it?
Please. I'm trying to find her. What's that?
It wasn't stuck up or anything.
Please one second. [ __ ] bro.
Yes, they have. I had a one night stand
with a New Zealander before and her
[ __ ] was ranked.
Yes, I have. Where is this [ __ ] woman?
delete a Facebook.
It just stunk.
I'm trying to find this
Can't find a profile.
That is annoying.
Oh, where's that profile gone? I've just
gone on my other one as well. I can't find her.
Let me try. Huh?
Why can't I find her?
That is strange.
Do I have any pictures? I don't think I
do. I can I can Let me see.
That's going to annoy me now.
Where the [ __ ] is it?
I don't think I saved any pictures of her.
That's going to annoy me. That is going
to annoy me. She hasn't blocked me. She
didn't know I knew her Facebook and I
was on my other Facebook as well.
That is annoying. Wait, when was this March?
My birthday is March, isn't it, Greasy?
She didn't block me cuz she didn't know.
She didn't know my profile
and I've got another Facebook as well.
She didn't block me. Let me try and find her.
He couldn't cuz she didn't know my name
and she didn't know my Facebook.
I'm going to I ain't going to stop till
I find this [ __ ]
Virgin boy sking his little bed [ __ ]
with no bed, no money in it. Bear with
me. I'm going to find it. Yeah. Virgin boy.
Oh, do you remember the Frankie days?
I was watching Donald Duck on YouTube. Um,
yesterday, Grezy. Donald Duck. You
remember Donald, don't you? I'm still
looking for this, by the way. Please
bear with me.
That is annoying.
I'm going to find it. Don't worry.
People on Reddit say it's easy to get laid.
They make it seem like it's easy to get
sex. They're idiots.
Who is she?
I remember I met a solicitor before we
went on a date.
Another time waster.
Where is this [ __ ] [ __ ]
No, I'm still looking, bro. Give me a minute.
I don't think I've got any pictures of
her. Let me go on my other
He didn't block me because she doesn't.
I might not save any pictures. One sec.
You go on my other browser.
Got her. Got her. Got her. Got her. Got
her. I've got a picture.
I'd say she's like a four out of 10. And
she was 32.
play about four. Yeah, [Music]
I'm not doing anything wrong.
And I do go on Reddit, but they just
dismiss my struggles. That's her.
She's like a four or five. So, she's 32.
Yeah. But she's not good enough to um
she's not good enough to have the
standards that she has.
I never said she was ugly, but she's not
good enough to have the unrealistic
standards that she has.
Cuz I am a man that's obviously 27, right?
I'm I'm better looking than her. And you
know, I'm [ __ ] you know, but the the
point is is that you've got people like
this that's got unrealistic standards.
Yeah. So that's Yeah. She's like
average, isn't it?
I went to a I went to a nightclub. She
approached me. She like, "Oh, you got
you got a nice beard. you look
attractive t gave me a number. We were
speaking the next day. The next Thursday
we met. You come to London cuz we met in
London. And then we went for a drink.
We went for a drink and um
um we went for a drink and we was
talking about places we've been and
stuff and whatever. And then um I said,
"Oh, like yeah, we'll meet again at some
point, whatever. Good." Then she said
she doesn't feel the vibe.
It's like, "What do you What do you mean
you're not feeling it? What the [ __ ]
That doesn't even make any sense. How
could you not feel something as fast as
that? What within half an hour?" So
again, giving up on the first sign of
disappointment. And at the end of the day, she's
32 and I'm 27. So,
um, no, I wasn't being pushy and I
wasn't being a weirdo either. I
literally explained that. Didn't hold a
hand. Didn't get close to her. No, I
didn't. No, I didn't. I know exactly how
I act on dates.
So, there's no maybe about it. It never happened.
So, we were sat opposite each other the
whole time. Literally, we were we was
sat opposite each other. We was nowhere
near each other. So, so yeah,
that's another thing as well.
Yeah. And I swear to God, I didn't do
anything. Didn't hold a hand. Didn't go
near her. We was opposite each other. It
was just talking about like where we've
been, what we've done. Um, she was
saying that she was from New She said
she's from Newcastle. I said, "Oh, I've
been to Newcastle." It was very just
normal. There was there was there was nothing.
You know what I'm saying? So then that
made me think, well, we've got these
women that are 32 that are average
looking thinking that they're better than you.
So it's it's not looking good, is it?
So, and that's and it wasn't cuz I liked
them cuz I didn't like them like that,
you know. But I mean, it's what I was
trying to explain to these black guys is
that it's it's the whole principle when
you've got somebody that's average
looking that's 32 that thinks they're
better than you. You understand?
No. Then she she wasn't feeling it
and then I told her about herself and
then she blocked me. Yeah. That's what
they do. That, bro, there's women with
kids. Bro, listen. I was speaking to
this woman in America. She is
Oh, I think she's 42. And guess what?
She thinks that [ __ ] don't stink. Yeah.
Yeah. And she's got kids. So, you've
even got women in their 40s with kids
that think they're better than you. I'm
not even joking, bro. She was from
America. Where was she from? Was it Philadelphia?
It might have been Philadelphia or some
New Jersey. No. No. She was from New
Jersey. And I'm thinking, "Oh, okay.
Well, this she's going to be a bit
easier, is it?" Cuz she's older and
she's got kids. Oh, no. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no. They still think
they're better than you. Yeah. It's mad.
I think at this point, the only women
that don't think they're better than you
are [ __ ] 80 year olds.
Yeah. Yeah, she was like a five. She was
like an average. She wasn't that bad,
but she was like an average. So,
yeah. And how can you claim you don't
feel revived that quickly?
That doesn't make any sense. So, they
give up at any first bit of disappointment. So, Disappointment.
No, I'm not doing it. I've done it many times before.
Mm-m. I'm never trying again in this
country ever again.
I'm not doing it.
Too much time, too much effort, too much
money. I'm not doing it.
Yeah, which six is basically average.
Yeah, she's average. But what goes
against her is her age. She's 32. She's
32 and average. No one said she was
ugly. She's 32 and she's average.
You should not be turning someone like
me down. My SMV is higher than hers.
That's the whole point. Yes, she's six,
which is basically average, which is
like the same as me.
No, she wasn't fat at all. But their SMV
goes down as they get older. Ours go get
better as we get older.
No, she wasn't fat at all.
So, I don't know what vibe he was
looking for considering we was we was
opposite each other. No, she wasn't fat at all.
Yes, cuz she wasn't fat.
She weren't fat at all. It was like normal.
No, I don't even think I have her number
anymore. I deleted it.
So, I'm not going out on my birthday. I
went out last birthday. My lot last
birthday I went on. I went out. I've
been out every year on my birthday.
I'm not doing it again. I should have
got a date with them 10 numbers last month.
Um, I can give up cuz I am cuz I'm going
to Thailand next month. So, I can give
up and I will watch me.
Think about it, bro. I have the money. I
have plenty of money to go out. It's not
a problem. I would have been out. I
would have been back out by now.
Trust me, I have no You get to a point
where you think, "Okay, yeah, it's
impossible now. We've done this a
million times." you know, at a couple of
years ago, it'd be like I used to go out
every week, twice a week, and I used to
think, oh yeah, like it's going to be
different this time. It's going to be
different this time. Always. Oh, this is
when I still had hope. So, I'd always
want to like go out and try again, but
now I I know there's no hope here.
There's There's clearly none. There's no like, yeah,
I'd rather sat I'd rather sit home and be bored
bored out my head than go through any of
that again, you know? So,
oh, mate, that virgin is always looking
at women. He hates it when I speak to
new women, don't he? I've noticed that
with the virgin. I went on his channel
earlier before uh um before I went to
sleep. I've noticed that he hates it
when people meet women. He's such a virgin.
Everything suggests that he's a virgin,
but people say that he's not cuz he's
got a girlfriend. [ __ ] hell. Yeah,
bro. He he he he does this. He He's very
jealous of anyone meeting women. And he
doesn't do it for reaction either. He
doesn't do it for reaction because no
one else does it. Oh, yeah. That
virgin's mad. He's been doing it for years.
Yeah, that he he is definitely a virgin.
Definitely definitely a virgin.
I have an eight, you know.
Oh, just some idiot on YouTube, bro.
Just just some idiot on YouTube. But
yeah, the point is there's no hope for
me here. So that's that. Um
I'm not going through that [ __ ] ever again.
Oh, it doesn't matter, bro. It's irrelevant.
Um, I'm not prepared to go through that
[ __ ] with these women ever again.
It's not like you actually meet someone that's serious,
right? It's not like you meet someone that's serious. um
you know that would that would make you
wait a month for sex. I wouldn't mind
that. I don't give a it's not all about
just the sex.
But they even it's like I don't
understand people on Reddit um you they
think getting laid is easy. They say
I'll go on dating apps. Dating apps
don't work. I could do a video on dating
apps if you want showing my dating app
profile. They don't work. probably
because I'm not [ __ ] white.
I don't [ __ ] know.
So, it's like you're you're lowering
your standards. So, me getting with that
32-y old, that's me lowering my
standards and then they still think
they're better than me. Do you not
understand, Hugh? That
um that that these is is you're lowering
your standards. You think you're doing
good by lowering your standards, but
then they end up thinking that they're
better than you, right? That's the weird
thing. Like, you know, USA Izzy, right?
I'll give you an example. That American
that I had the one night stand with.
When I met her, I was like, "Okay, well,
he isn't that good-looking, but
whatever." And I just I just went along
with it. And I thought me lowering my standards
is the right thing. And you're helping
people by doing that. And then it turns
out then they they think that they're
better than you in the end. So you end
up giving feel like you're giving them a
chance and lowering yourself only for
them to then think they're better than
you and [ __ ] you over in the end. It's
madness. That is [ __ ] madness.
You want me to do a video on dating
apps? Okay, I will.
Cuz people keep telling me to go on
dating apps to get sex
when you can't even barely get a match.
And if it is, it's from a fat single mom
with an ego. Just use dating apps, bro. They say, "Yeah,
I can show you a screenshot of my hinge.
Just use dating apps, bro. See, I've
never really been one for dating apps.
A, because you don't know who you're talking to
and that would make that would make you
hate women more,
you know, using dating apps because you
don't know who you're talking to. And
I just don't like dating apps. You know
what I'm saying? Even though I have used them.
Yeah. So they say, you want me to show
my hinge? Okay, one sec.
I'll show you my hinge, bro. I'll show you.
Yeah. And you don't And and also you
can't stand out. The thing with dating
apps is you can't stand out.
So unless you're in a in a place where
the population is about 5,000 people, I
wouldn't even bother with them because
it's like you don't know who you're
talking to. You can't stand out. You
don't know what they look like until you
meet them. I just they've just never
been for me.
But obviously I I still click on it now
and then because it's it doesn't take
any time at all just going on it, does
it? But I don't um I've never been one
for like four of them. Like I stopped
going on it for like a year.
I've stopped going on it for like a
year. Dating out for like a year, bro.
But I'll show you my hinge anyway since
you want to see.
One second, bro.
Hey, man. I'll show you.
2 seconds. But I'm getting up for you. Hold on.
Right. Two seconds. Yeah. Hold on.
I need to screen record it and I'll link you it.
All right. Okay, there you go.
Well, I'll send it to you. Yeah, sex.
I'm going to do a proper video on it at some point. But yeah, All right.
Go on dating apps. They said you'll get
sex. They said I got a bone to pick with
you people on Reddit. [ __ ] lying.
There you go. That's my data profile.
Not a single match to be had. Larger. Yeah.
>> Yep. That's my dating profile.
Not a single match.
Not a single match to be had.
But that's how you get sex.
You have sex on dating apps.
So they say,
"Have you tried the apps?" Yep. Not a sausage. Yeah.
You get bare sex. Really?
Bare sex. You get bare sex, bro.
That's my dating profile.
Can't even get a [ __ ] match. But go
on dating apps. You'll get sex. Try the
Try the apps. They said
makes you wonder, doesn't it?
Yeah. Buy the apps. 18 apps.
So they say.
So they say I got I got a Tinder one as
well. Can't get any bloody matches. Nah.
Anyways, I'm going to delete
the app. any less.
No, he didn't. No, he didn't, bro.
I might um put my dating profile out
there and be like, "Dating apps. Go on
dating apps to get laid, bro.
Go on dating apps to get laid, bro." Yeah.
I need to get some a bit hungry, you
know, but I don't I think everywhere's closed now.
I closed in 20 minutes.
Oh, [ __ ] I haven't even ate, bro, since earlier.
It's fine, man. I won't eat.
Yeah. See, I can't even get a match. Um,
that's my stomach, by the way. Um,
I eat. What should I eat? Let's see. Yep.
Can't even get a match.
Did you see the dating apps?
I look more than okay.
I look more than okay, matey. I look I'd
say I look above average looking.
Oh, I need to eat something, bro.
[ __ ] those. Damn.
want to get five guys again, but
I can't keep buying it, bro. It's expensive.
I need to start saving money as well.
I could get like some chicken wings or
something. I don't know what I'm going
to eat. I probably won't eat, man.
Nope. Not even one match.
And I don't think I'm ugly here.
Well, I think I look pretty [ __ ] normal.
Nope. Not even one match.
But people say you get sex on dating
apps, get laid. So they say, disappointment face.
Yeah, I think I look pretty good. Me,
don't know about you.
I might have to get a McDonald's, bro.
Might have to
get a chicken mac.
What do you want, B? It's the cheapest and yeah,
need to save some money, bro. Really?
They say you get laid on dating apps.
Yep. That's what we're having now.
Yep. It is nice, man. That's what I'm
having right now.
They tell me to go on dating apps on
Reddit here. What do you What do you
think the problem is?
The thing is the fact I don't look fully white or
get some coke. Yeah.
Add four nuggets.
But yeah, they're good pictures as well.
That's what makes me think that it's um
my like the heritage that I look
cuz it's weird. No.
So when people say dating apps are
working for them, I can't relate. I can
never relate to them. When it came to
dating apps, I couldn't relate cuz they
never ever worked for me. Never. So
then you realize that what the [ __ ]
bro? Like you're no one's type in this
country. So you're no one's type in this
country. Why are you going to keep
trying? It's [ __ ] stupid, you know?
There's literally like no point.
That's £12. It's not too bad. Then
medium. I get some extra fries as well. Oh. Okay.
Scing these little bed [ __ ] with no bed,
no money in it.
Can't stop saying that, man. I'm [ __ ]
in the head. found. >> Yeah.
No, I don't I don't compare myself to
other people. And man, used to do that,
but I don't compare myself to strangers.
Waste of time. But yeah, why do people
keep telling me to go on dating apps? Q.
You see, people tell me to go on dating
apps and stuff.
They don't even work.
Yeah, there's fireworks here as well.
So, what do you think of the dating um
what do you think of my dating profile?
What do you think the problem is, Hugh?
Cuz I I think I look normal. I I don't
think I look ugly.
And I never did to be honest with you.
I had this woman on Reddit, right, say
to me, "Oh, I can't get with you cuz
you're too old for She was 23, 28, and
she wouldn't get with me because I'm I'm
not Muslim. Um, and I found out she'd
been with a 28-year-old before. So, I
had to stop the whole like dating thing
for my own mental health,
you know, as as you would, you know,
it's um to cocktick.
Yeah, I paid for Tinder. Uh-huh. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. To be fair, I used to have
offers to meet me on dating apps um
um back years ago, like say 2, three
years ago, they used to work.
Like I have met like I met some crazy
woman, bro. Oh, I'll never forget that.
Then I met someone else that went on
dates and I had someone else come to my
house, but they were like years ago,
bro. But for the most part, they've
always been they don't work. Now they
definitely don't work for me anyways.
So I don't know how people still suggest
them to be honest. But in 2015, yeah,
pretty sure they did work. Oh, mate.
No, I don't look bad in any of the
photos. Just the picture's bad. Um,
so I went to Redden, right? I went to
meet this woman in Redden.
Um, and she
uh went to meet this woman in Reddit uh
in Redden, sorry. And she was [ __ ]
crazy, bro. Crazy. She's like, "Oh,
you're my everything."
And I was trying to like [ __ ] And she
didn't want it. And I waited until like
7:00 in the morning to get out of there.
But the mad thing about it was is that
there was no Ubers cuz obviously it was
in a village. So I couldn't even get an
Uber to the train station. And so what I
had to do cuz there was no signs, I had
to knock on people's door one by one
asking for directions to get the [ __ ]
out of there cuz there's no there's no
um there's no um
there was no signs
cuz it was a village and there was no
Ubers cuz it was a village.
So Oh, it was mad. It was some place called Sandhurst.
Oh, mate. I remember that day. Went all
the way to find. She still wouldn't [ __ ] either. Yeah.
She was crazy.
But she wouldn't [ __ ] either.
So, I just left.
There's a place called Sandhurst. It was
a nice little village.
And I got the [ __ ] out of there. Do you
remember that one Steven Howard? Yeah.
This a madness. Madness, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. I don't think I'm ever going to
meet anyone. Hugh.
I don't think I'm going to meet anyone.
I mean, I look pretty normal, don't I?
From like the videos and stuff.
What do you think?
It wasn't funny. It was [ __ ] weird.
But now like dating apps now.
What do you think you What do you think
the problem is?
Yeah, I look like normal to above average looking. So,
it's depressing, isn't it?
People on Reddit tell you that you're
still going to meet someone.
Yeah, that's what it is. That's I mean
these ugly people, right? And this is
what I tried to say to Adman when he
says, "Oh, there's ugly people that get
women." I mean, yeah, there's ugly
people that get women, but I think
that's because they might have met
through work or they got lucky in a
different circumstance or they met years
ago. Like, it's not now. It's not people
in my situation where it's happening now.
Cuz the thing is, right, let me tell you
something cute. These people um are
saying about like how women are um
how women are the problem and stuff.
saying how women are not the problem
but um how um
what I was going to say
[ __ ] brain freeze I'm saying about how these women
I forgot what I saying now
um what was it. Um,
oh yeah. Oh, how people in relationships
I had brain freeze there. They say about
how there's millions of people in
relationships. But let me tell you
something, Q. Most of the people that I
know are single. The men, the women I
come across, they're single.
You know what I mean? No, they don't
care. They just tell you to go on dating
apps and they don't work. So yeah, they
don't they they um
they um do you know what some guy said
in the Netherlands? He said in 2025 try
to date as a normal guy. He said have fun mate.
That's what he said.
Um so there's more pe they talk about
millions of people in in relationship
but they don't um talk about all of the
people that are single. They never talk
about them people. And there are a lot
of single people
cuz most of the people I know are
[ __ ] single. Some people I know are
in relationships. Yeah. But majority of
the people I know are single. So
yeah. So there's no point if I'm I'm not
no one's type. So there's no point me
going out and humiliating myself when
I'm obviously no one's type.
I don't care, bro. I don't care what
anyone says about me. I don't give a [ __ ]
But what but the thing is, Hugh, I feel
like in this in this day and age, they
always try to cover up women's shitty
behavior. Like when a normal guy can't
find a woman, he's got to have a bad
personality. He's got to have a bad
personality. when I've done dating I've
done experiments you where I've put up
um pictures of like a white guy with
blue eyes on a dating profile and I've
got matches same person they were
willing to talk to me meet me so all of
this that they go for personality is
secondary and it's [ __ ] it's
[ __ ] bro cuz if that was the case I
would have been I would have been on a
date with with one of them 10 numbers
it is a very physical physical thing And
you don't even have to be ugly either.
But they think us go for appearance. No,
we don't. We don't care about what a man
looks like. It's not like we reject
somebody for having a [ __ ] beard or
we reject somebody for having no beard.
Us. Nah, we don't. We don't go for
appearance. Men do, but we don't. When
that generally can't be true when
somebody can look smack and be above
average looking and still have to deal
with all of these excuses.
They go on like it's not
Oh yeah, Timmy. I know him, bro. Yeah.
So they they always
like we always hear Hugh that a woman
doesn't owe you anything, but we never
hear a man don't owe you anything.
You know what I mean?
You know that whole um women don't owe
you anything. Let me Do you want me to
give you a few double standards?
you. If you say you don't eat [ __ ]
[ __ ] dick. That's completely fine. Um,
if a woman does shitty behavior, oh, she
doesn't owe you anything. If a man does
it, he's a bastard. He's a [ __ ]
bastard, mate. If you try to meet a
woman within a week of meeting her,
you're moving too fast. Yet, if you're a
woman and you try to meet a guy within
the first message, that's completely
fine. That's completely okay.
You know, I can I can go on and on and
on and on and on about these double
standards. I find them very interesting
to be honest.
I find it to be fair. I do find it interesting, you know.
But they do have a physical type.
And what what's annoying with it you is
it's not like you're fat and ugly.
There's no reason for it. If he was fat,
ugly, smelly, broke, then I could
understand, you know, why why it's
happening, but there's no reason for it.
But if you can't figure it out, then
just stop in it. That That's the thing.
Just stop it.
Just stop it. If you look If you look
like Timmy Eldridge, you you'd understand.
If you look like Timmy Eldridge, it
could be maybe cuz you're not 6 foot.
There's there's different reasons.
There's there's various different reasons.
There's various different reasons, bro.
No, I was just talking about some double standards. Yeah.
At Fruit Mad World, he's a [ __ ] So,
so I don't agree with this guy that
says, "Why don't people just admit it's
looks when it comes to women?" Because
it's not just about that. It's about if
you're not their exact preference
physically, they still won't go with
you. Cuz I could make myself
good-looking if I looked Max and that
still wouldn't be enough. So, it's not
just that. It's it's about height. And
it's all physical. It's very well
physical. There's no doubt about that. It's physical,
you know. There's no two ways about
that. It is definitely physical. Um, but it's
it's not just that.
That's even that's not good enough.
Oh, just somebody that I went on a date
with. Another time waster.
Yeah. She was 32, Candy. and we went on
a date and she didn't feel the vibe.
Crazy, isn't it? Somebody that's 32,
that's average looking, somebody with a
lower SMV than you is turning you down
when you're the one lowering your standards.
Huh? Cuz we're talking about dates that
went on. This was back in March.
So, even them, they've got unrealistic
expectations. See the thing is right
if you go you know Thailand right you
might not be able to get every woman you
want like you might not be able to get
like a 19 20 21 22 year old where you
get a 28y old you get a 30y old that
wants relationships like you can get 30
year old women that want relationships
you can't get that here even if a woman
is 30 40 she would still think she's
better than you even if she's got
Like it's the only woman you could
probably get with here is probably an
80y old. That's not even an
exaggeration. That's how unrealistic
their standards are.
Yeah. I mean, I lowered my standards.
And that USA Izzy, she was she was a lot
of people say she's ugly. And even
though she was in her 20s, she was a
[ __ ] I don't know where her ego come
from with somebody that looks like that.
But, you know, that's that's what we're
dealing with cuz it's like the rudest
women are the most ugliest ones as well.
Whereas that 32-year-old weren't ugly.
She was just average. But, you know,
it's it's fine. I was I was low in my standards.
SMV basically means got more like
how I explain it. just like more
potential, like more um higher quality,
you're more um you got more um
you you're worth more than them
basically. That's what it basically
means. Whereas theirs goes down as they
get older, yours goes up.
Yeah, mate. I told you there's a woman
Oh [ __ ] my McDonald's is here. There's
a woman on Instagram. She lives in
Cuden. She is fat and ugly and she's
like 40 and she still says, "Oh, I can't
get with you. I'm with someone." Even
though she's not. And she shows her tips
on [ __ ] all over Instagram. Like she
shows her bra and I'm sure she's got a
kid and she's skinned as well. Yeah.
Yeah. I'll show you her. Yeah. Okay. One
sec. One second.
One second, buddy. We got this back. Oh, you good. Thank you.
Chinese people are so [ __ ] polite,
aren't they? They really are.
That's what SMB means. And obviously
there's there I'll show you
when you're standing. Yeah. They're the
ones that think they're better than you,
but you're lowering your standards.
Like even USA is I was better than her
in every way. Better looking,
right? And even though she might have
went to university and whatever, I was I
was getting over three grand a month not working. as well. Where's
Where's the SC version? Oh, they stop
the [ __ ] they stop the [ __ ] monopoly.
I've tried approaching Albian girls.
If I have
if I have
and like I said that woman that I
approached who I was kissing and
touching their boobs,
she was Albanian.
She was Albanian. And
she there was a language barrier. She
she barely spoke English. We was
kissing, punching. Um,
and she used an excuse not to meet me
again because we couldn't understand
each other even though she knew the
language barrier. But Albanian women,
nah, they're still not interested.
I have come across um Anyways, I'll show
you the [ __ ] one from Instagram. Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] you up little
Steven. Do you think that's weird?
Why Steven Howard? Do you think that's weird?
There you go.
Do you think that's weird? Got some nuggets, too.
You know why I come off YouTube for a
bit? Cuz every time I go at the virgin,
when I go at the virgin saying that
you're a virgin and your skin, people
say, "Oh, how can he be a virgin? He's
got a girlfriend. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. When people try and call me a
virgin, no one talks about the one night
stands I've had. No one No one talks
about the [ __ ] porno. You know, you know,
no one talks about the [ __ ] porno.
You know what I mean?
No one ever backs me up. Stephen Howard,
you don't think that's weird.
You don't think that's weird. No one
backs me up. H
That's why I come off YouTube.
That's why I come off YouTube cuz no one
backs me up.
Well, I'm shoing these chips in my mouth.
I destroyed with it with my reply back.
Them chips are nice. Yeah,
you still here.
Oh, that is lovely. Bluff your puppet
real didn't ask me. Do you think it's
weird that they back the virgin up but
they never back me up? Even people on
this channel will back him up but
they'll never back me up. People that
are supposed to be the brothers. Huh?
They never back me up, but they back him
up. Do you not find that strange?
Oh, he's got a girlfriend now.
But they don't [ __ ] say anything
about all the women that I have had sex
with. No one mentions that.
People are supposed to be the pubs.
Do you not think it's strange, Steven Howard?
You don't find that strange, huh?
How no one ever defends me. They they
defend that virgin.
They defend that stupid version in the bed.
Oh, answer me, Stephen.
You don't think it's James?
Roasting's done it, Joe's done it, and
they're supposed to be the brothers.
And you got Ricky Millington saying
about how how can how can you be how can
you be a virgin when you've got a
girlfriend? How can I be a virgin when
I've literally proved I've slept with women?
Huh? That's more proof than somebody
having a girlfriend. I would say I would
very much say that's that's all you can
prove at this point.
No, they never say anything about when I
call him a skinned virgin.
Oh, that's why I come off YouTube for
eight days, bro. Because they're all biased. Yeah.
You're [ __ ] biased. Yeah.
If he had sex with Sarah,
he would be locked up. he would be
These people in this community, they love nons.
They love nons
because they say about things that I've
said, but they're the ones that stick up
for and LT's done it as well.
LT has done it as well. Oh, how can he
be a virgin if he's got a girlfriend?
How can I be a virgin if I've slept with
women and I put it on videos? How can I
be a virgin? That's the real question.
So, do these people just love nonses or something?
Who is a proper nons? What the [ __ ]
I might do a video about this.
And I've also shown more money than the
virgin multiple times.
And he he he has shown and I've shown
more money than the Virgin multiple times.
No one ever brings up when I showed
[ __ ] £6,000 and the [ __ ] [ __ ]
couldn't even pull out [ __ ] £800. Do you remember?
To be fair, Greavves hasn't done
anything. He hasn't he hasn't picked any
sides, which is good. But Ghost's done
it. Ricky's done it. Joe's done it. Yeah,
it's weird, isn't it?
Shag has done it as well.
Shag has done it as well, even though he
claims he hates nons. Huh?
Cuz I've never seen any of these people
back up me when they're going for me.
Yeah, he's an actual nons regardless of
what I've said.
That's what I find very very sus. You know,
very very weird. Very very good.
But yeah, he he's very jealous of people
meeting new women. Very very jealous. Very jealous.
I mean, that tells me he's still a
virgin. That tells me he's never had it.
The more he does this and gets worked up
at people meeting new women, it just
shows he's never had it. It just proves
it. It prove my point even more. Mar, you know,
I might give him a guide to how to lose
your virginity, run him through it,
football bet, then maybe he can finally
get an aid, you know.
No, not girlfriend. That's a [ __ ] disabled.
They never pop it.
But them 10 thumbs up that um like
Ricky's comment, I feel bad for them
cuz the thing is right,
do I know everything? No. Am I always
right? No. But when it comes to dating a
woman, I think I would know more than most people.
So, how we got 10 thumbs up is I feel
sorry for these people. I feel bad for
them if they generally think that women
go for personality. And I I feel bad for
them. I do feel bad. And if they ever
try, they'll learn the hard way as well.
I feel bad for them. You know what it
is? Is where they don't go out and they
don't speak to women. They don't know
what they're like.
You know what I'm saying? They they they
don't know what women are like. Yeah.
I've got about two grand now. I think
a minute. They [ __ ] they don't speak
to women. So they don't know what women
are like. So they have this m they have
this opinion of they don't know any of
them. You know what I'm saying? Cuz when
I used to meet the skin virgin, I just
used to say, "Oh, all women are the
same." And he says, "You don't know all
women. They're not all the same." That's
what he used to say. And I used to say,
"I know more [ __ ] women than you.
I know more women than [ __ ] you,
mate. I used I used to say this like a
million times. I know more than you."
And then back then, right, I was
immature. I didn't really have much uh
life experience obviously cuz I was 17
18 I didn't know much so I just said it
28-year-old me with more life experience
than he would ever have all women are
the same so I must have knew
from like um I must have knew right that
from the start I must have knew that
they were all the same
I don't know how I knew cuz I didn't
have any experience but I used to just
say they were all the same and that was about
They're all the same. Women are all the
They always They never fail to disappoint.
You can have a skin virgin in a bed
tell you to his blue in the face. Oh,
women aren't the same. You don't know
all women. Yeah. Every time you go out,
they will never fail to disappoint.
It's obvious they are. I got to a point
where this is obviously all the same.
They are all the same, bro.
Yeah. Ricky Bugginson.
They do the same stuff at the same way,
but they're not all the same. [ __ ] bastard.
The [ __ ] virgin bassad. Mhm. [Music]
Did you see my reply to it? I [ __ ]
ruined it, mate.
I ruined that guy, bro. I ruined him. You got
I'm so bad. Mama,
I can't believe Ricky Billington got
ruined. That paragraph that I said
completely ruined him.
He got [ __ ] ruined, mate. I just had a McDonald's.
Did you see my video on my dating
profile? Candy man.
Oh, that was a yummy macke.
I'm full up now. Oh,
that's what I always get after the night
out. I just order a McDonald's
with like some onion and cheese and Oh, it's nice.
Ain't drunk in ages. Don't miss it.
Don't miss it at all. No. A bad boy.
I can smell you a mile off.
in his little bed suit with no bed. No
money in it. Virgin boy.
Oh, it must have been talking about me,
mate. That virgin's obsessed with my
Yeah, he's very Do you know all of this
stuff that he does, Candy Man? All it
does is show how insecure he is.
Have you not realized that?
He's obsessed with me. Do you know what
it is? Right. I'll tell you what it is.
I was live earlier. It's the fact that
he knows that you're better looking than
him. you can go out and approach women
and he can't and he's too ugly and he he
he can't process it in his brain then
that's why he has all of these outbursts
trying to say how you're ugly and this
and that and mate if by the off chance
I'm ugly which I'm not. I mean have you
seen your own face? I'm not going to
keep going around and around in circles
but like you get what I'm saying. Like
he has a little ego. He's very very insecure
about the way he looks. He's in an
unhappy relationship because if he
wasn't, he wouldn't be on YouTube doing this.
You get me? It takes uh dedication to
come on YouTube every day trying to [ __ ]
with someone. He's an insecure virgin.
I've told I've been telling you this for ages.
I don't know why people keep saying that
he's got a girlfriend and that proves
he's had sex. I mean, I've actually
proved I've had sex, but we won't get
into that anyways. But it's because he
knows that you're better looking than
him. And think about it, bro. You you
know them messages with them women, even
though they didn't meet me and whatever,
I mean, you went out and you approached
them. Something that this skinned virgin
could never ever do.
That skinned virgin could never ever
ever do that. And I was also going to
say to Ricky, but I didn't bother by
saying, "You talk about having no game,
but I've never had to resort to disabled
women. I've never had to go on five
dating apps, pay for every single one of
them, and resort to disabled women like
your good friend. I was going to write
that in the end, but um I thought, yeah,
we might as well just not let's stick to
the subject cuz I wanted to stick to the
subject. I've tried in Scotland. I've
been to Scotland.
Yeah, I've been to Scotland twice. So,
he hates the fact that you can go out
and meet women.
You don't get that vibe, Candy.
He hates the fact that anyone can go out
and meet women cuz he's an ugly bastard
himself. That's got anxiety. That's what
it is, bro. It is that.
Yes, I have. And I' and I've been to Scotland
twice and I've been to Wales. Um,
uh, yes, I have. I've got an approach of
me approaching on the train. Yeah.
But yeah, this guy is jealous of anyone
that um can meet women because he's
stuck with um
obviously ugly Sarah and he hates the
fact that you could go out and just go
out and meet someone cuz he's an ugly
bastard skinned with no teeth. And
that's not me reacting, that's me
telling you what he is. So if I'm
reacting is you reacting to me by doing videos. So,
uh, how do I get on? Same old.
It was the same.
No, I do it all night. I do it all
Yeah, I've tried Scotland. Uh, I've been
to Scotland twice, but the first time I
didn't do any approaches to be fair. But
yeah, I have been to Scotland. I've been
to Edinburgh. It was the same there.
I have I have done that and it doesn't work.
Doesn't work at all.
Yeah, I have been to Scotland. I've been
most places. But
I I'll give you a fun fact, right?
There was this one time I um I
approached all day.
All [ __ ] day. I literally started off
in Stratford. I went to central London.
Then I moved to Shepherd's Bush. Then I
ended up in Maiden Head. I was
approaching all [ __ ] day.
And by the end of it, I just got drunk
and just got depressed.
Yeah, I remember that day. It was
[ __ ] I didn't get any numbers. I
don't know what happened. I can't
remember exactly what happened, but I
didn't get anything out of it. I know that much. So, yeah.
Yeah, it was uh
I can't remember what happened, but it
was it was obviously wasn't good.
And I went to the Maiden Head Weather Spoons. Yeah.
So, I know about this [ __ ] bro. In this
country, I know about this [ __ ] and
these women and whatnot. I know what happens.
Don't know. She probably thought she was too good.
She was being a [ __ ] So, yeah. [Music]
I'm not doing anything wrong. Uh where
the [ __ ] is God?
Yeah. So that's it, bro. Some people
just cursed. But I don't know why people
are telling me to go on dating apps, bro.
That's another thing. They tell me to go
on dating apps, but dating apps don't
even work. So, I'm not sure why they
tell you to go on them.
They only work for like gay people,
women, or really, really, really good-looking men. Strange.
And then they make it seem like you can
get sex easy,
bro. I probably won't have sex again until [ __ ]
probably the rest of my life, to be honest. So
my friend said that they're just they're
just not interested in this country
here. I think he was right.
Yeah, they ain't interested in this country. Pretty much. Yeah.
I think so as well.
I can't believe that 32y old. It's a
madness, isn't it? Cuz at that age, they
should be looking to like settle down with someone,
you know? You would have thought like,
yeah, they're they're looking to like
settle down with someone.
I don't need sunbeds, bro. I used to tan
in the summer.
I used to tan in the summer. I tan.
I was tan this summer as well when I was
doing Uber. I was tanned as [ __ ] I
don't go red. I tan.
I tan in the summer when I was approaching.
Yep. A fire go out approaching. I spray
loads of after shave. Still not interested. Yep.
I feel better now. I have no hope
though. I used to go mad when I thought
there was still hope. Having hope is the
worst thing because you feel like you
still got a chance and you and you and
you're under pressure to try and, you
know, try and meet women and stuff when
you know there's no one for you. Like
deep down like
you kind of know there's no one for you,
but your mind's telling you, "No, go out
and try again. Go out and try again. Go
out and try again." And to be fair, I
used to take like six weeks breaks
um before like trying again. Yeah. I
used to stop for like 6 weeks and then try again.
But that was cuz I was just like bored
with it. But there's nothing that's
going to talk me into going out again
after that 500,600
10 numbers and not a day. That was the
end. I think
that was honestly the end.
Really? Yeah. That's [ __ ] insane,
bro. What the [ __ ] So yeah,
and like I said, I don't care about sex
anymore either. So yeah.
Nope. I don't gamble anymore.
I don't gamble, bro. I don't gamble.
No, I don't know what it went on.
I have no idea what it went on.
Maybe it was
£400 and then 100 when I put money on
the roulette. But either way, it was
hundreds. I know I'd spent hundreds by
the time the Monday come round.
I knew it was hundreds. I knew it was So,
it was hundreds, but hundreds. That's
why I got put off. I put £100 on the roulette.
One over 500 pound. Took it. Bam. Ain't
been back since. [ __ ] it. Yeah, man.
10 numbers and no date. And then when
that woman two weeks ago said, "Oh,
yeah. Let's meet. It should be okay." I
was thinking, "Okay, well, we got
somebody that wants to meet. We got some
money. Let's go out.
And then they [ __ ] me over. So I'm done.
I'm [ __ ] done. That was the last
straw. Get [ __ ]
They're just not interested. I tell you
the worst place is Liverpool Street.
Liverpool Street is the worst.
Is the worst. They're so stuck up there.
Oh my god.
If Stuckup had a place, it was it would
be Liverpool Street.
[ __ ] hell, bro. That place. I like it
cuz the restaurants and stuff.
Why you keep saying there's so many
birds? None of them are interested.
Does it matter whether there's birds or not?
Because no, not interested. So why does
it why why does it matter?
Have I tried Victoria? Why do you seem
to think one place that you go, they're
all of a sudden going to be interested?
I don't understand the logic, bro.
They're not interested. It doesn't
matter whether it's Stratford, Victoria, um, East Ham,
[ __ ] Australia. They're not interested.
Well, I already have given up.
I have to give up. I had to I had no
choice but to give up on my own wellbeing.
No, I should have gave up a long time ago.
Why do you think there's going to be one
place where they're suddenly? They're not interested.
You should have learned something from their messages.
It's like you're not going to find someone.
You know, you've had enough bad
experiences to last me a lifetime. You
don't need to keep going. You don't need
to keep trying. You've already proved your point.
They ain't interested in this country.
So, it's like what's more left to do?
it doesn't matter, bro. I got the money back.
So, call it a day here. Yeah.
But people on Reddit say you'll meet
People on Reddit say you'll meet someone.
They say it will happen. You
M they say go on dating apps.
He's um he's a
am I insecure? Um no. No.
But towards the end I started getting
it. Yeah. Cuz of like how they'd make
excuses. Oh, you're too old, you're
this, you're that. And then um that
you're this and that. And then um
you know you you couldn't meet any um
and obviously they'd make excuses and
stuff. So towards the end yeah after years
but I never really thought about it to be honest.
So I just thought I look normal.
Yep. They can literally go on dating
apps and get somebody around their
house. And you know what makes me laugh
is when these women complain they can't find someone.
They complain that they can't find
someone when we all know they can. They
say, "I've never been in a relationship.
I can't find someone." When they
literally can get anyone they want,
which I mentioned this before, it needs
to be illegal for them to write stuff
like that. That should be illegal for a
woman to even complain about men because
they can literally get anyone they want.
So, I'm sick of it when they um sit
there and act like they can't find someone.
Yep. I've tried all of the dating apps.
Uh should be illegal, isn't it? There's
women that say
that's what made me dep That's that's
what made me depressed when I was
reading on Reddit where they can get
somebody to the house to [ __ ] them
straight away and they get they can't go
so long without sex yet you have no
choice if you wanted sex to go without
cuz you can go out and get 10 numbers
and not even get a date.
But I try not to think about that cuz
that's that is depressing. Especially
with like the history that I've got with
them, you know? It's like you try, you
can't even get a date. They can just get
sex relationships whenever they want. No
matter how bad they are. It's bad, bro.
It is bad.
And I wouldn't mind it if you if you
actually got something out of the effort
that you put in, then it wouldn't be
bad. But that's why I gave up. So, made sense. >> Yeah.
Now, Hugh, what I don't understand about
um Ricky's comment is he said that me
loving their messages was part of the problem.
But didn't they love my messages?
H strange. How he got 11 thumbs up is
beyond me. But it's just I guess it's
just people that don't like me that
don't know about women
because I don't know how they can
argue with what they're shown. It's
delusional. That's why I say there's no point
there's no point um getting into any
kind of arguments or any kind of debates
with with any of these people in the
near future. That was a one-off because
like they for example Hugh right I'll
give you a perfect example.
I have gone up to women before and I've
approached them and they've said
straight away not interested like
straight away before I've even finished
my sentence. All of these people online
will say that women go for personality.
You see how the two contradict itself
and even though say you show these videos
um they will still make excuses. So
there's no point in like getting into
any kind of debate
or any kind of conflict about it because
whatever they shown what they're shown
to do wrong they would defend them
anyways. So there's no point. That's why
like you know the 11 thumbs up, it
doesn't bother me because I know I'm
right. I know from my own experiences
what I'm seeing as right.
So if 11 people want to lie, that's
fine. Them 11 people must have never
they must have not saw the video. They
must have not they must have not clicked
on the video because you can't click on
that video and tell me that I'm wrong.
There's no way you can. There's no way
you can if you tried. Sorry. So, yeah,
that's it, bro. So, I just put it down
to 11 people didn't see the video cuz
they seem to ignore everything that
they're shown. I I don't know why they
do it, but they do.
They you can literally approach someone
and they'll say they're not interested
straight away. Literally, that's what
they'll say. But they go for personality
and all of these things and whoever come
out with that idea, I don't [ __ ]
know. But yeah. So yeah,
strange, isn't it?
Don't know what more videos to make to be honest. Nope.
They're just old men that
cuz I was thinking of showing Ricky um
approaches where I've approached them
and they've said straight away they
ain't got a boy, they've got a boyfriend
and they're not interested. But why
would I waste my time? Because they're
just going to dismiss it anyways.
So they dismiss anything wrong that they
do. So there's no what is the [ __ ]
point of it all, you know?
waste of everyone's time really.
They're always going to defend women.
They're never going to stop defending
them. So, there's no point, bro. There
really, really is no point.
So, that's it.
I'm convinced a woman could rape
someone. Well, rape someone. A woman can
rape someone. I re I think a woman could
kill a baby and then people would still
make excuses. They'd blame the baby. I
swear to God, bro.
I generally feel like that, bro.
I generally feel that way.
They'd say the baby had a bad personality. Let's
say the baby to serve the
One second, bro.
One second, lad.
Where's that message?
Oh yeah, that's where we're at.
This woman's a snake. She's put her
Okay, look at that skinned virgin.
Oh, [ __ ] hell. He's [ __ ] mad. That
virgin, isn't he?
So, yeah. This woman, she's put her
[ __ ] thing back to where people can
message her. She's such a snake.
I'm so glad I gave up. Seriously, I'm so
glad I gave up, bro.
Yeah, that [ __ ] that skint version is mad.
That the skin virgin
the other one. Yeah.
He's a full-on virgin, ain't he?
That virgin's mad.
What a life, eh? What a life. What a No.
Yeah, I've already booked it, bro. Yeah.
This woman Yeah. that said she wouldn't
get with me because I'm 28 and she's 23.
And then when I gave her [ __ ] on another
one, she she made it where people could
stop messaging her. Now she's put it
back. So I'm going to message her in a
bit saying, "You little snake rat liar."
Yeah, man. I've already booked it anyways. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
I feel like I'm free, bro.
I feel like I am actually free.
Once you've lost that hope, it's like a
weight like lifted off your shoulder.
It generally feels like you know you're
free, bro. You know
why do people say on Reddit, "Yeah, go
on dating apps to get sex." You They say
getting sex is easy. They're idiots. Yeah.
Yeah. They use it as an excuse. Oh,
you're too old. You're too old for me.
I remember the last time I tried, I was
sending it, bro. Proper sending it. Nothing.
The last time I went out a month ago, I
was sending it. A bro
not interested. So I'm leaving. That's it.
I hate that when they use age as an excuse.
You're too old for me.
You're not a Muslim.
Excuse. I I was I was meeting this here.
I tell you another one, right? I was
meeting this woman, right?
Um and we spent hours together.
One moment this, bro. You spent hours.
Did we meet again?
No, I don't think we did. No, I'll tell
you what happened.
Um we was with each other for like
hours. We went like down um Hide Park.
She was Muslim by the way. And um then I
was talking about oh yeah. She oh she
just wants friends. I said oh what what
you wouldn't want to date and stuff.
She's like oh I can't date you cuz
you're not Muslim.
And when I was speaking to her again I
was like okay I can convert to Muslim.
Then it's like oh I'm not looking for
anyone now right now. I'm not looking
I'm not looking for dating. So, it's
always an excuse with these people.
That's why I don't bother with it
anymore. I don't bother with the
[ __ ] cuz it's always bollocks stupid excuses
that can [ __ ] up your mental health as well.
That Muslim thing isn't. I actually
thought it was legit at first people saying that,
but it's just an excuse.
Trust me, you're best off just leaving.
Like unless if you're someone like me,
you're best off just leaving what I'm
doing cuz you're never going to meet anyone
and you're just going to keep getting
treated like [ __ ] and having to and and
you're just going to have to keep going
going through these games and stuff.
There's there's it's it's not a life
here, bro. You know. No, she was just normal.
Maybe seven. Well, no, maybe six or But yeah,
then I said, "Oh, what if I convert to
Muslim?" And then it's, "Oh, well, I'm
not looking to date anyone anyways."
So, it's not the fact because I'm not
Muslim then, is it? You know, so it's
just excuses and I can't be asked with it.
They've made it categorically
clear that, you know, you're not their
type in this country. So, move on. Done. yeah,
that's it. Well, I just said that to her
to see what she'd say.
I weren't actually going to. I just
wanted to see what she would say
because they they've got so many excuses.
Yeah, I know. I just said it to see what she'd say.
but still, bro, like
I just said that
it's always games with these uh people. So,
yes, she's put her thing back to where
you can message her. He's a little rat.
He's a rat.
It's not having a It's not It's not But
it's very important to discuss my experiences.
No, I'm not talking about that again.
I just want to know why people don't
know the truth. Why people say women go
for personality? Why aren't people honest?
You know, I don't understand why people lie.
And also maybe one day I just want sex
candy. Doubt it though. I don't have
much of a sex drive anymore.
But that probably come with the fact
that I know it's impossible.
So I can't crave something that's
impossible to get. So well, unless you
use an escort.
No, I'm not telling that story. So,
I'm not talking about it, bro. [ __ ]
that. It's weird.
What do you think of the excuses here?
What do you think of the excuses, Q?
You're not Muslim. You're too old. I'm
too young for you. You're too old for me.
Why do they lie so much?
>> No, I'm not talking about it. I can't be asked
much getting in that [ __ ] bed [ __ ]
with all [ __ ] bed. All [ __ ] money in it. Steward
when I money. Mhm. So yeah,
why don't you candy man? Why don't you
ask women why sex is so important for
them? Why they can't live without sex?
I bet you wouldn't ask a woman that, would you? No.
Could that be double standards?
Could that be double standards as well?
I don't know what the problem is.
Well, okay. So, what if I need sex then?
Candy. What if I want to get sex?
Yeah, but it is the same though because
there's women that want relationships.
There's women that complain that they
can't get a get a man
and they must have been trying to look
for a man to get a man.
So, if I wanted to be funny with you, I
could say, "Well, if being in a
relationship is not important, why why
do you see people in relationships? They
must have been seeking for it. They must
have wanted it. So then I could say
exactly I could say the same thing. You
know if if if I wanted to be awkward and
difficult I could say well you say get
in a relationship's not possible but
what about if you do see when you do see
the people in relationships they must
have been seeking out for it to get it.
So it must have mattered to them as well. No.
If you think about it. So
could you imagine grievy on Tinder? So
okay. So what would I do if I wanted to
get sex then? Candy man.
You didn't even see my dating app video,
did you? I done a video. I done a dating
app video. You didn't even see it, did you?
I'm not sure. I assumed he did.
He got put into a coma,
so I assume he died.
I assume he did. I assume he died. Yeah.
I candy man. Why do people keep telling
me to go on dating apps on Reddit, but
they don't work? Candyman.
Candyman. These people on Reddit keep
telling me to go on dating apps to get
sex, but it doesn't work.
Tandy man, we can't even get a bloody match. [ __ ] sake.
They say you need to go on dating app
for easy sex.
[ __ ] they lie so much on Reddit,
don't they? I That's why I can't deal
with Reddit. I can't deal with them
because of the lies.
I don't know
to see what they would say.
I don't know how Ricky got 11 thumbs up
though. He He is completely wrong. But
again, simps are simps and they're
always going to defend women. So, obviously,
pretty much. Yeah.
So Candy man, do you think I'm ever
going to meet someone here?
If I decide if I decided to keep trying,
I might as well start doing the lottery.
Isn't it? I might as well start doing
the [ __ ] lottery at this point.
Nah, you never beat sub. Mhm.
I know. I need to stop moing about it.
Just let it happen. Nothing happens.
You never meet anyone. Uh
I mean it is stupid to go and ask for
advice cuz I know all there is to know
about this. I know what these women are
like. I know what they do. I know
they're time wasters.
So there isn't really much anyone can say.
They're not all the same.
You don't know all women.
They are literally all the [ __ ] same.
For [ __ ] sake, every single one of
them all every single last one of them
are the same. They're not all the same.
That's what nons used to say.
I've already done it in Chinatown.
They said they had boyfriends.
Yeah, I've tried there.
It's mad that I'm never going to ever
have sex again, is it, Candy Man?
It's mad, isn't it? Wasting your youth,
wasting your potential, can't get sex.
It's mad, isn't it?
I don't really like to think about it.
It's too depressing. But
tried it. Tried plenty of fish. Tried Boo. Yeah, please. Yeah.
Yeah. My my my response to Ricky
Millington, I completely [ __ ] destroyed him.
But the thing is, people are always
going to defend women. This is what you
need to understand.
Currently, man, they're always going to
defend women. Even if women are wrong.
So there's no point into getting any
into any kind of debate, any kind of
conflict cuz they just dismiss your
struggles. Cuz I don't understand how 11
people can thumbs up a comment on where
I've put messages out there.
And why it doesn't bother me is because
I I know the truth.
I know. And as long as you know, then that's it.
cuz they completely dismiss everything
that they're shown.
Do you know what I'm saying? So there's
no there's no it's I don't even take it
personal. Yeah, just white knights.
Unless somebody could actually give me a
debate or an argument, then I was like,
"Oh yeah, it's just white knights, isn't
it?" It's like, yeah, people always
going to defend women and blame you. I
don't even take it personal anymore,
bro. like it's just
they would always they're never going to
stop defending women. So, it's whatever.
That's why I diseng
I completely shattered him, bro.
I completely shattered that Ricky in it.
Yeah. But yeah, they're always going to
they're always going to defend women
cuz they've got no experience with
women. So that's why they always will defend them.
Bless them. If anything, I feel sorry
for them, bro. I don't I don't take any
dicks personal cuz like I said, they
don't know the truth. And it's sad that
these people are older than me and they
don't know the truth. I know the truth.
I know they're like, "Yo, that's why I
don't bother with them.
That's why I don't bother with them, bro.
Well, I'll be back in a bit. Yeah.