[Music]
Oh, why does lot of [ __ ] come up? [Laughter]
I was just watching the Star Wars.
What do you mean?
I p it. Oh,
[ __ ] Lilo and [ __ ] Stitch.
Lo and Stitch popped up.
[ __ ] hell, man. Yo, I'm coming off
this community for a bit um after today. Yeah, man.
Don't know when I'll be back.
It's [ __ ] shitty community, ain't it?
It's a shitty community.
Who does that sound like? Hey
There's this guy on Reddit. I messaged
him. He says, "Oh," he says that he's approaching.
He's 30. Yeah. He says he is in England.
I said, "Show him some of my approaching videos." Yeah. Mhm.
Just straight up chilling. N.
Should I go out Saturday?
He thinks no.
me thinks no,
but I don't know.
This was my birthday on Monday. [ __ ] hell.
Getting an old [ __ ] aren't I?
Why is life got to be so hard?
Dating, just [ __ ] like that. Why has it
got to be so [ __ ] difficult?
really don't uh
really don't know
what it This nice teddy. [Music]
I'm not going back and forth with that um
skin little low life insecure virgin by
the way. That was just a oneoff
community post. Wrote it. Not even worth talking about.
I done a community post because they're
not even worth even talking about, you know.
I'm surprised no one's telling this guy
to go to Thailand to be honest with you.
He's asking for advice, but
you read stuff like this.
You already mentioned all the ways to
meet women. You're just too scared to
talk to them, it seems. change the post
from how to meet women to how to get
past approach anxiety. This is the
actual problem you're having.
>> Oh, he's in for a long shock, isn't he?
Then when he finally gets past that
anxiety and realize even approaching doesn't work,
he's probably See, I'm way ahead of
these people. Even this guy, Even though
this guy is 38,
like that's what why you don't take
advice from people online,
cuz they they they sell you a dream.
They lie to you.
So this guy's obviously scared to
approach and obviously he's thinking
that once he approaches he's going to
find someone is what I used to think as
well. You know it's madness
but Antman said a lot he speaks sense
he's like who cares what they think you
know if they want to sit there and be
virgins and defend women all their life
then that's on them in it.
He said, "Who cares? Life's too short."
I think he's [ __ ] right, to be honest.
Yeah, he is right. Definitely, he is.
Surely to God, these people ain't got
any life experience because they would know that,
you know, approaching women in 2025.
Really? Come on.
Come on now.
Why do you even waste your time unless
you're a [ __ ] virgin
trying to get laid or
I don't know.
Yeah, I messaged a guy, showed him some
of my videos.
That must be really [ __ ] though, is
it? When you think that like dating apps
don't work and approaching doesn't work.
It is [ __ ] is it? It is [ __ ]
Really, really, really, really is [ __ ]
You know, I could see that escort in
Manchester that keeps messaging me. But
if I go Manchester, then I will be
approaching because obviously it's
Manchester and it why the [ __ ] not? But
I would be won't be doing it here
cuz it's a change of scenery. I haven't
been for ages.
So obviously a change of scenery. I
wouldn't mind doing it again. Even
though I know I'm not going to go all
that way. I'm not going to go all that
way just to come back. Nope.
Anyways, like I said, I'm not going back
and forth with that virgin. I wrote what
I had to write and that's it.
Yeah. I'll leave him to make himself
look insecure and obsessed. So, yeah. Nope.
Don't know who you're talking about.
Uh, I'm not even going to answer that.
That's a stupid question. I mean, I put
approaching videos up there
and I put messages up there, so that
pretty much contradicts everything you
said. So that's an answer to that. I
mean, like I said, it's like what it's
like what Adam was saying. If you want
to keep defending women and and be a
virgin all your life, that's that's on
you, bro. I don't really mind. I've put
approaches up there. You clearly will
dismiss everything that you're shown.
That's on you, bro. It's not my problem.
I'm not here to convince you to believe
me or to not believe me. I don't care.
You dismiss black and white evidence.
So that's that's you, bro. That's not my
problem. You know,
people like you, there's no hope.
There's no telling people like you.
Obviously, at the very start, even with
some of the messages, people can have
their opinion. People can say stuff, but
when they're actually shown, when you've
gone up to a woman and they've said
they're not interested straight away and
you're still defending them, then
there's nothing anyone can say to you, bro.
There's really really nothing anybody
can say that that will ever change your
mind. There's nothing somebody uh can
show you that will change your mind. So,
um you will just keep dismissing it and
going back to what you think. So that's
fine, bro. You know, it doesn't bother
me. It doesn't get me angry. I'm not I'm
not here. I mean, I've wasted enough
time that I didn't have to to show you
what they're like. I've already wasted
enough time, which I shouldn't have had
to have even done. And you're still
you're still um dismissing it. So,
that's on you, bro. I don't really care
what you think.
You still think women go for personality in 2025?
That's from you, bro. You know,
I mean, there's other things I could do
and show, but I'm not wasting my time.
I've ch enough. So, yeah. Keep defending
women, bro. See how that gets you all your life
cuz you're not even you're not even being impartial.
You're just completely defending them.
Even though I've shown you approaching
videos and I've shown you dating apps
and you're still telling me I'm wrong.
Good luck to you.
Oh, [ __ ] run out of sugar, man. Jesus
Christ. I can't have another cup of tea.
That personality thing is so cop. It's
so boring now. That excuse. I mean,
[ __ ] I've been hearing it for years.
They've got unrealistic expectations.
They've got unrealistic standards. If
you are not their type physically,
they're not even going to give you a
chance. Even if you are goodlook,
I mean, I don't know how many times it
has to be shown to you or said to you
until you [ __ ] realize it. It's It's
[ __ ] up. It's really, really, really
That's what makes me think that you
ain't got no experiences with women.
There's no way someone saying that
saying that could possibly have, you know,
it's madness. It's [ __ ] Why Why is
there like that though? Why is there so
many white knights?
It's [ __ ] weird.
Like you could show them all the
evidence in the world,
black and white evidence, and they'd be
like, "Nope." They'd still be They'd
still be shaking their head. They'd be
like, "No." They'd be shaking their head
like a dog. What the actual [ __ ]
I mean, there's videos where you've
tried to speak to women and they've said
they're not interested straight away.
I mean, I'm pretty I'm pretty sure them
videos that I put up yesterday, two of
them said that exact same thing,
but you said that they're going for personality.
He knows Hugh knows the score.
Hugh knows the score, buddy.
I mean, why do you think Okay, listen to
this, right? Why do you think I don't
try anymore? I've got money. I've got
more than enough money to go out and
try. So, I'm not contradicting myself.
I'm very much
I'm meaning what I'm saying.
I'm meaning what I'm saying. To be
honest, I might go out Saturday cuz
well, we I planned it with my sister for
ages. But even then, like any excuse not
to, I I'll jump at it to be honest cuz
yeah, I know I know what they're like.
I'm not contradicting myself. So yeah,
it's so toxic. Very very very very
I feel so much better now. I've gave up.
So much better. Really, really, really, really do.
You know, I always found me to be my
happiest when I gave up to be honest. So yeah, [Music]
people can argue with them approaching
videos. I should never know.
You do you, man.
You do you. Um,
I give up. But Hugh seems like a legend
to be honest.
Don't mind me a piper. I don't drink anymore. So
Don't drink me.
I really hope this guy messages me. Yeah,
back. He messaging me back.
He needs to. But at the same time, I
don't want to discourage him.
So, I feel like if I show my videos to
him, it is discouraging him.
This is what people on Reddit never tell
you and they will never tell you that if
you even try to speak to a woman, she's
going to say that she's not interested
straight away. Well, there's it's a few
things that happens.
It's it's three it's it's like three
things that happens. They either say
they're not interested before getting to
know your personality
or they say they've got a boyfriend or
they give you their number and they lead
you on. The end.
A galaxy far far away. That's literally
nothing else ever [ __ ] happens.
Nothing else ever happens.
Nothing at all. Just that. So yeah, madness.
How long do you reckon it takes to get
to know someone's personality?
That goes that goes with the whole thing of
them saying about personality. It's a
cover up for their unrealistic
standards. Just like I don't any I don't
owe you anything. These things are all coverups.
And if you don't believe me, right, go
and act like a woman and moan about men
and see if anyone's blaming your personality. You know,
personality is the biggest biggest
busiest biggest biggest excuse.
I've got some solid approaches on my
channel where people didn't even give me
the chance. So, I'd like to see you talk
your way out of that one.
And don't say because you done it on the
street cuz I also done in the pub and
bars as well. And days don't work. So,
that's why I put the date that video up on there.
That's the only way you would kind of
stand out is by approaching someone.
What else? What else you supposed to do?
Go on a site where you get no matches. [ __ ] that. Yeah, that's it.
It's having a homey day today. And it
crazy how people use that personality excuse when
I've literally got friends. I've made
friends all over the country. I've got
friends all over the I've got so all
over the country. Strange that. Very very strange.
Even though I've proved what happens
when you approach them,
they still deny it. Badness. [ __ ] madness.
Doesn't suit them, does it?
It's bad, isn't it? Really bad to be in 2025.
That's what Hugh was saying. Yes. I
said, "Yeah, the 14 people that thumbs
up, they definitely didn't see the video."
No, there's no way they saw the video.
Cuz if they saw the video, they would
have known what they done. So,
they will never stop defending women.
Never. They'll do it to their blue in
the face. They'll do it all their life
and still be virgins. Let them crack on,
mate. Let them crack on. madness.
Yeah, I'm not um going to be trying to
convince people anymore or anything. I
don't care what people think.
So, that's that.
And how somebody could write a comment
like that even though I've shown
approaching videos is [ __ ] mental, you know?
So mad. And they still defend women.
Got to be autism in it. It's got to be autism.
Has to be at this point. It's got to be autism, bro.
What else could it be? why people would
continuously defend the women even
though they're shown otherwise. Maybe
I'll look it up, you know, before I go
to sleep. I think it's got to be autism
me. And a lot of people have got autism
nowadays as well, but I mean it's it it is mad.
Got to be autism. I think they're
autistic to be honest. I'm not even
using that as an insult, bro.
It's mad [ __ ] mental
and people still defend them. Wowza. Wow.
Of course he's contradict. Of course he contradicts himself.
I feel sorry for them that they think
it's a personality. I really do.
I really feel sorry for these people, man.
Just give up with the whole dating
thing. It ain't worth it.
There we go.
Out of them 10 numbers. Only one of them
blocked me. The others just didn't reply.
Madness, isn't it? Madness. Gladness.
I could also No, I'm not putting up anything anymore.
I'm actually I actually woke up with a
[ __ ] I put up I woke up with a [ __ ] migraine.
Yeah, I woke up a [ __ ] migraine, bro.
Probably from all of this YouTube [ __ ]
to be honest.
I'm not showing anything.
I'm not showing anything to um
any anyone anymore. Yeah. Heat.
Yeah, they should Yeah.
Women always have options and they'll
never pick me. So I don't see a reason
to try anymore. It doesn't matter what I
do. If at any point in the last 26 years
I have a reason to think of why. Maybe
in my opinion but I just work in gym
until I die alone. really much.
One person's 26,
but it's for the best anyways, you know.
It's not even give up. For some, man, it never started.
the juice is not worth the squeeze. I'm
going to message this person as well. Reason.
It just doesn't seem worth it. It's not
It's really, really not worth it.
It's better off being alone. Really, the
only thing you that's good is sex. You
You can just [ __ ] pay for sex. It
isn't worth it at all. It's toxic as well. [Music] in boy and run.
[ __ ] dog barking, man.
Some women are evil and are out for
ruining us. Sometimes we might wonder
why try finding love or
is it worth taking the or is worth
taking the risk to be heartbroken again. That's true.
Yeah, this comment is is is is good as well.
No, not at all. I don't blame many of
them for giving up when it's a when it's
such a success pool
these days when you see what some have
to put up
to put up. It's a wonder they didn't
give up a long time ago.
That's very true.
I should have gave up a long time ago to be honest.
Long [ __ ] time ago. Yeah. Oh,
generally speaking, no. They usually go
through a lot of failure before making
that decision. Personally, I went on
several apps and approached dozens of
women in real life with only one date to
show for it. Actually, just wanted to
talk about our late spousees.
I was never harassed or mistreated
during all of those rejections, but
after 6 months or so, I walked away from
trying to stay altogether. Surprisingly,
after a few months, I reload them one up
and was contacted almost immediately by
my loud girlfriend over a year.
But this is someone that
you only get one day though. H.B.
Do some men give up on dating?
Generally, yes. However, many men give
up after failing countless times. I have
no idea what the ratio is, but I'll take
a wild guess. Perhaps 10% of men who
gave up dating did it too early. The
remaining 90% gave up after years or
decades of failure.
Well, it's not even that really.
It's more the fact that you could look
smart, get 10 numbers, and not even get a date.
I mean, that's like it's depends what's
happening over the years.
You know what I'm saying? It depends
like how far you're getting in that.
You know what I mean? Like
if you went out every week and you was
getting two dates a month, then you know
it' be worth it, you know, cuz you'd
think that like there's hope or whatever.
It just it depends what's happening
whilst you're trying, you know.
That was enough to just [ __ ] this, you
know. I'm going to put up with this [ __ ] anymore. So
that's why I um that's why I gave up.
I'm 28 and I've given up hope someone
coming on just to make a damn fool of
myself again. These people are pretty
similar to me. They gave up to be honest.
I feel that way and I'm 28 next [ __ ]
week. I'm [ __ ] not going out again.
[ __ ] that. No way, bro. Worth it.
Not worth it at all. I'm 45.
Never had a date across hundreds of
rejections. I get told I tried harder.
Too little success makes all the
difference. 45 and never had a date
across hundreds of reject. You never had a date.
See, these people are worse than me.
This is what I This is my opinion as
well. Yes, I gave up because I had
literally zero success. I don't see a
point trying when it's never going to
work. Every guy was talking to 20 guys
getting bombarded with attention from 50
guys. So, they care about
they don't care or trying to unless
you're perfect or good at lying.
But some of these are good. Yeah.
Yeah. It isn't worth the effort. It really isn't.
I think it's really easy for women to
underestimate and downplay how difficult
dating is for men because it's something
they've never personally experience and
it's so far from what they do experience.
That's truth. Yeah. Cuz
for you, in order for you to get a date,
you would literally have to physically
go out and keep speaking to people to
even maybe get a date. It's so hard. I
don't know how people go on like it's so
easy. It's [ __ ] It really is bad.
I wouldn't say easy, but it's really
getting a ton of rejection. I stopped
dating because the women I wanted that
they didn't want to date me and the one
she didn't want to date me. I had to see
dating them. And my preference, they
have theirs. cuz it just didn't line up.
That's also another thing is you can
like people that don't like you and you
can not like people that like you
mad, is it? It is mad.
But like I said, I wouldn't mind. I
wouldn't mind if it worked. I wouldn't
mind if when you go out and approach it
would actually work.
That's that's my whole that's my whole
problem with it. It's not that it's
harder for men. It's that even if you
put effort in,
you still won't even get a date. That's
that's my argument cuz it's not supposed
to be easier for men.
Obviously, it never has been even before
social media. But it's more that you can
put the effort in and still get nothing.
That's what put me off, you know? So, so yeah,
just not just doesn't seem worth it.
I just want to keep going around in
circles with my life, you know, when I
could have been doing other things. So,
it's just like there's no
That's my point. That's my point.
Yeah, I gave up approaching women after
I realized how unhinged some of them can
be and I just let them approach me. I
think if I were to become single, I'd
stay that way.
I've given up because I don't stand a
chance of a dating pool. Yeah,
it's [ __ ] up, isn't it? It is [ __ ] up.
Yeah, it doesn't matter. But it's not
like decades of
trying. It's like if I if I got 10
numbers right and I got two dates,
then I'd be like, "Okay, maybe this is
worth keep doing."
or you got a kiss on a date or just
something. It don't even need to be sex.
And they'd be like, "Okay, well, we'll
keep doing this." But
yeah, 10 dates looks max 10 numbers
looks maxed and not a date. Get a [ __ ] Simple. Yeah. What the
What's weird though is when I went to
leads, I got more I got more matches on
the dating apps in leads
than I did here.
Do I do remember that? I do remember that.
Definitely remember that actually
where it leads you.
What would make you consider the
difference between giving up and
realizing it's not worth your time?
Go away, you troll.
No. Uh, I don't mind it, but I prefer two.
Yeah, good one. Go away, you troll.
Yes, it was you.
Yeah, some people give up too soon, some
people don't. It just depends. I I was
right in giving up.
Probably just going to sleep.
I woke up. I had a migraine.
Woke up, had a migraine.
And yeah, going to go to sleep soon. Had
a migraine. I had to go back to sleep. I
woke up at 5. So yeah.
No, I won't, mate. I won't. But my
sister still wants to go out on s I
think my sister might want to go out on
Saturday, but I don't think I will.
No, I won't, mate. No, I won't.
I'll be in Thailand next month.
No, [ __ ] that.
I would need to stop for 6 months, bro,
before even thinking about it again.
Literally 6 months. It' have to be 6
months. Well, now a month. Yeah. No,
I won't be back out before Christmas, bro. Trust me,
I've done this [ __ ] so many times, I'm
fed up with it. I don't even get the
urge to even want to do it again anymore. So,
you fed up with it all. You get to that point like,
I don't give a [ __ ] about sex anymore
either. So yeah, there's nothing a woman
can give me.
A woman can't really give you anything
but sex. She can't give you anything
that you can't give yourself. Think about it. You go
cuz you wouldn't be in a relationship
with someone if you could have sex with
them, would you? Now
you get it.
Yeah, I'm on Reddit reading this. It's true.
Like I said, if you're going out and
getting dates and you're getting stuff,
then you know, carry on. Continue.
You know, so be it. You know, don't give
up. You might not get what you want
straight away, but if you're going out
and you got 10 numbers, you didn't even
get a date or a kiss, then just give the
[ __ ] up. Simple. Like, it's madness.
Only thing is I did want to go out on
October. I did want to go out in
October, which we're October now.
22nd of October. So,
Yeah, this is this is true as well. Not
going to lie, peace peace is underrated
when it comes down to unlimited sex
versus mental health. Mental health
always wins. Facts. Facts.
Definitely 100% mate. 100%. Cuz even if
you was to get sex, right, it wouldn't
be worth dealing with all of that toxic
[ __ ] just to get sex.
Yeah, exactly. You you realize that as
well. Whenever you stop, you feel better.
Just having peace.
Peace is so nice. Peace, you know,
all of that [ __ ] It's nice. It really,
really is nice.
Yeah, it is lovely, you know, just
peace. It is. It really, really is. I
don't miss them at all. I don't miss
talking to them. I don't mean miss
dealing with them.
They're all the same. Anyways,
back a few years ago, I had hope and I
was horny all the time. Now I don't have
hope. I'm not as horny. So,
why do you think I don't pay for
escorts? Why do you think I don't use
escorts? I've got the money. I can do
it. Don't worry, you know. Yeah,
it's nice in the winter
just giving up. It's nice. Yeah, the me
Yeah, it's very true about that.
Your mental health is so good.
That's why I say 6 months.
Like I said, if I went Manchester to see
the escort, I'd try Manchester. I would
try in a different environment. Yeah,
probably would to be honest, but
I'm drinking there anyways. So, I would
I would approach
not sober, but I would do it like drinking
a different environment or a different
country, but not London like that. Oh yeah. So
someone approaches me.
To be honest with you, I'd probably just
tell them I'm not interested
to be honest.
Unless they were really really really
really good looking.
I know it's [ __ ] now. It probably probably won't
probably. Yeah, to be honest,
I don't give a [ __ ] about women, bro.
Soon as I won that money back from that
roulette, I was like, never again.
[ __ ] that [ __ ]
But I don't think anyone's had it
nowhere near as bad as me. Don't know
how that guy done hundreds of approaches
and didn't get a date. That is crazy,
though. But it is possible. It is. It is
possible though, isn't it? Cuz I haven't
had a date since April. So,
I know it's mad, isn't it? It's mad. It is mad.
You literally have to go out. You
literally have to approach a woman and
still not even get a date.
Crazy, isn't it? It is mad when you
think about it. It is
but um I don't understand virgin boy
saying that he's never been rejected because
he says oh the women that I've been with
I've broken up with them. No you
haven't. Men don't break up with women.
Women break up with men.
Correct me if I'm wrong. So, no, they
broke up with you. Even though less than
a month, you have been rejected.
You also been rejected by Britney.
You literally have been rejected.
Men are not the ones that break up with
women. Women break up with men.
Oh, it's a mutual decision. Am I lying? So,
for somebody that's not been in a
relationship, it's funny how I know this
stuff, isn't it? You have been [ __ ]
rejected, you [ __ ] idiot. You've not
been on a date with a woman that you've
liked that's not liked you back. Yet, you're
single at the time.
You have been rejected, but your fragile
ego won't allow you to admit that. See,
me, I'm an ass. I say I've been
rejected, but I've been with more women
than he has.
More women than he would ever be with.
What? Why is he Why what's so hard in
admitting you've been rejected?
That is like what most people have to go
through when they're trying to date.
And even women have been rejected. Even
as well, believe it or not.
But him? Nah, he's never been rejected. He hasn't. 31,
but he's never been rejected. Must be
the only person on earth that's never been rejected.
I can't help but talk about that, bro,
cuz that is insane.
You're the You must be the only 31y old
that's never been rejected.
The only time, the only way you've not
been rejected is if you never tried or
you've been in a relationship all your life.
Or you've been in a relationship. [Applause]
All your life.
But that's the only way you would never been rejected.
I've been on some bad dates,
but yeah, he's chatting [ __ ] He has been rejected.
Definitely has been rejected.
Cuz how can you be 31 and never been
rejected? What the [ __ ] H
That is insane, lad.
What the [ __ ]
Why don't you just admit you've been rejected?
Well, I've been rejected. Huh?
It would never happen. But why is he
saying that he's never been rejected?
I've been rejected. You've been
rejected. You have been rejected. Cuz
women don't women women don't um women.
Uh it used to when I was younger. It did. No. [Music] Um um
uh when I was younger it didn't, but
towards the end I was like, I'm not
putting up with this [ __ ] anymore. and
I'd already had enough experiences and stuff. Um, it's like
I was just, it's not about getting
rejected, it's about being led on.
That's the thing that I can't stand. I
don't give a [ __ ] if you approach
someone in a club and they say I have a
boyfriend cuz you know eventually you're
going to get numbers in it. So, it's
just a whole leading on.
He could never approach, bro, ever in
his life. He doesn't have the balls.
He doesn't have the balls, bro.
That's why he goes on about USA, is he?
Cuz he's jealous.
I am staying positive. I'm leaving.
I'm very positive. I'm leaving, bro. I can't wait. I'm leaving. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm I'm leaving, bro. I'm all
good, man. I've done what I've had to do.
been going out two been going for two
years and only got three dates.
I'm reading some of these comments.
As a 27year-old, young me had hoped to
be married by now. Maybe a kid on the
way. Young me would be disappointed.
Current me has given up on dating. It's
too much of a hassle. Too many women are
too much. Online dating is trash. And in
person is a great since I don't want to
be called a creep for flirting with the
girl I thought was cute while I was out
shopping. After going on countless first
and even second dates, I just can't seem
to meet any woman that I find an
interest in or boring or any
of things as a man. It's just not worth
it to me anymore. So, I just stopped
trying to worry about it. I found myself
happy. Then when I was then when I was
trying to date, I still hope I meet
someone organically, but I'm not holding
my breath as of now my hopes and dreams
of marriage and a family are gone.
That's sad, isn't it? If somebody
actually wants a kid, is it?
That must be worse when you actually
want children as well. I've never wanted
children, so you know, it it's
never bothered me, but obviously
you could see how that would be. Um, yeah.
This is true as well. It's not just men
though. Women go to gay boss
specifically to avoid being approached by guys.
Yeah. It's not Yeah. And I chose to give
up because I tried more than anyone in
the world. So I chose to give up.
Yeah, I've not even attempted to enter
the dating scene and I'm 31 and it just
doesn't seem worth it. I do want to be a
father someday, so I don't know what to do. Nope.
Cuz women can get sex whenever they want. Uh,
okay. So, this guy right here says, "I
think men give up on dating because they
trick themselves that it is too hard,
but it really is not."
That's got to be a troll in it. 100%.
Why would you even write a comment like that?
I would have messaged that person
showing them my approaches,
but I think he's a [ __ ] that is just
stupid to even write that. I mean,
everyone knows dating is hard. No one's
saying it's impossible, but I'm pretty
sure it's hard for [ __ ] most people. Not.
You can't get it.
What makes women worth the effort?
Exactly. I'm doing great without them.
Let's see some effort from a woman and
I'll think about it.
Yeah. The only thing they can give you
is sex. Really, there's nothing else.
Unless you want children, there's
nothing else they can really give you in it.
So nice giving up. It feels so nice. Peaceful. Very peaceful.
It is good to be honest.
But why is the virgin saying he's never
been rejected when he has? Is his
fragile ego that
you've not been rejected?
How is that possible?
How is it possible to be 31 dating and
never been rejected?
That doesn't make any sense.
You have been rejected, mate.
I've never gotten anywhere, so what's
the point? I'm not a gambler. I lose
money. I lose money once or twice and
give it up. Same with dating or even
talking to women to be honest.
Everyone was like, "No, I I think they
give up too late." Yeah.
Like I said, I wouldn't mind going out
every week and getting free numbers,
getting two dates a month. Then I'd be
like then it'd be
But you think about it, it ain't worth
it really, is it? You go out, you spend
money, you try, you drink, you get hung
over the next day.
It truly isn't worth it, is it?
Yeah, I'm going to sleep anyway. See you.