Oh, [ __ ] hell. [ __ ] up me.
[ __ ] hell, man.
Yeah, bro. [ __ ] sleeping patterns all
over the place, boss.
Sorry about that, man.
Did you like my community post? I saw it
got four thumbs up, but they're
obviously for genuine people. You
understand? That's the difference.
There's genuine people on my channel, mate. We know
to me, but she's not that good looking.
She's like a four out of 10.
She just messaged me from Reddit, but
she lives in [ __ ] Ireland. I'm not
going to [ __ ] Ireland, bro. [ __ ] that.
So, these people that speak to me,
they sit there and say, "Oh, you're
cute." and stuff. And that's what USA
Izzy used to say to me as well. Oh,
you're cute and that. That's why she got
with me. So, I'm not I'm not um
sure why it's so hard
cuz they say exactly the same thing. So,
they can't all be lying.
So, it's like you should just be able to
go out there and just meet someone, but
you can't. It's It's disgusting to be
honest, bro. Really is disgusting.
Jesus Christ, man.
Why are these Reddit mods so power
hungry? Candy man,
they're so bloody power hungry.
I don't know, bro. They're so power hungry. Candyman
so bloody power hungry. You know, they
must have been bullied in school. It
feel powerful cuz they can ban people. Ah,
I still feel like I need to go out for birthday, bro.
He got defeated though, didn't he, bro?
He got owned.
Was what was what I'm saying wrong?
what I was saying wrong or
know from Ricky since the approaches
have gone up. Starting to really get
worried now. You said it was how we were
acting. That's why I put some of my approaches up.
It's a hookup culture.
You will never get women. You will never
get a woman with looks like that.
With my looks, bro, you're not going to
make me insecure projecting your
ugliness onto me. You're wasting your
time. You really really are wasting your
No point self- projecting, bro. You're
not going to make me uh
you're not going to make me insecure, bro.
No one has ever made me insecure, really.
Not even people of this community. So
you're wasting your time talking about
my looks. It's in one ear out the other,
mate. I couldn't care less.
Honestly, couldn't care less, mate. I
put my camera on.
You know what I'm saying?
Doesn't matter if you're moaning whether
you can get a girlfriend or not. You
can't be uglier than me and and and talk
about my looks. Doesn't make sense, mate. Yeah. One sec.
Uh, stop it, bro. Stop it. I'm not
answering your stupid self-p projecting
questions. Stop it.
Go away. Your little self-p projecting comments. Yeah.
Let me stop talking about my looks, you
weirdos. Oh my god. [ __ ] hell.
Stop talking about my [ __ ] looks. It's weird.
And I say I'm a bit more than average.
But I'm not talking about my looks.
[ __ ] weird. Oh,
I look like I don't wash. Oh. Uh. Jesus Christ.
Why has everyone got a
Why has everyone um got a love life and
I don't? Good question, bro. It's not
like loads and loads and loads and loads
of people are single, is it? It's not
like 80% of people I know are [ __ ]
single, bro. What do you mean go for
six? I've gone for sixes. I've gone for fives.
Why are you telling me to go for sixes, bro?
A lot of them numbers were sixes. They
were fives. Some of them were fives and
sixes. Why are you Why are you saying to
go for sixes, bro? They've all got
unrealistic standards. It doesn't matter
what they look like.
It doesn't matter if they're [ __ ] 10
or they were [ __ ] five. What the
Listen to me, bro. You can make an average
um you don't have to. You can make an average um
you can make um an average profile of a
woman and she'll get loads and loads and
loads and loads and loads and loads of likes.
If the woman's average, she's got
unrealistic standards as well.
Anyway, you're boring now, bro.
I wish these people would know that
they're not making me insecure every
time they talk about my looks.
Like, they're just hurting themselves
because they're never going to make me
insecure. I don't know how many times I
have to say it.
weird, isn't it, man? Oh, wow.
Yeah, I don't care. Like I said, I'm not
going back and forth.
That's nice for him. I'm not going back
and forth. I'm not a low life.
So, I'm not a low life virgin that's
insecure. So, I'm not going to go back
and forth with someone that's never
going to meet. Like, think about it.
You're that age. You're still doing this
and you're never ever going to meet
anyone. You're unhappy. You're insecure.
When I watched that live stream, bro,
all he was doing is projecting. Unlike
the Ricky Millington one, he was just
like talking [ __ ] but he wasn't
projecting. Whereas this guy is actually
projecting because he's he's calling
people insecure, right? Yet he's the one
sat on YouTube calling me ugly every day
when everybody would agree, even people
that don't like me, that I'm better
looking than him. Whether I'm ugly,
whether I'm good-looking, whether I'm
average, everybody would agree that I'm
better looking at him. No.
So, he's the one that's insecure. He's
the one with a fragile ego. Which is why
I got four thumbs up cuz what I said was [ __ ] right.
Um, and yeah, also because
he says candy, man, that he's never been
rejected and every single woman that
he's been with has he's broke up with
them. But that can't be true because
it's the women that break up with a man.
So, you've never gone on a date with
somebody that you like that haven't
liked you back. He is his ego is so
fragile that he won't even admit that
he's been rejected. It's insane, bro. It
really, really, really, really is insane.
It really, really, really, really is
insane, lad. And he still talks about
USA, is he? It's insane, bro. No one
else brings it up.
No one else brings it up, bro. And the
thing is, Monty's like, "Oh, if you if
you stop responding to if you come off,
people would go for him." People
wouldn't go for him. The only people
that would go for him is Shagger and
Harry. They're the only people.
No one would go for him. No one goes for
him at all except Shagger and Harry.
Yeah, Candy. They're the only ones that are
USA. Izzy thought I was cute.
And so many of these other women say
that I'm cute as well.
So, but he says I'm ugly every day. You see, insecure.
Think about it, bro. For people to do
this, maybe you don't have brain
capacity, but for someone to do this
every day, bro, they're not happy with their life. It's insane.
I'm not going back and forth with a
keyboard war, bro.
[ __ ] ridiculous. I just thought I'd
write that and set the record straight.
Mhm. And another thing is he if he went
out approaching, he would never even get
a phone number. So he's trying to make
fun out of me for going out approaching
and getting rejected. Yet he's the one
that would go out and never even be able
to get a number. Never be able to ever
ever ever get a date. And yet he's
making fun out of me. How does that make sense?
Oh [ __ ] man. I need to start changing
my diet, bro. I feel like I'm dying, man.
It's like what Ant-Man said. He's like,
"Oh, why are you trying to convince
[ __ ] your experiences? Like maybe
they're content, you know, defending
women and being virgins all their life.
Like leave them to it." And he was like,
"Oh, even if they did agree with you,
nothing's going to change, is it?"
like what would actually change. And
he's right. He is actually right. You know,
it doesn't matter what anyone thinks,
does it? Yeah. But listen, bro, you can
call him all these things, right? But
listen, he got off of YouTube and he
made a life for himself. Think about it.
He went off he he come off of YouTube
and he made a life for himself.
You know, you can't you can't take that
away from him. And I I'd say that to
anybody, you know, whether I speak to
them or not. Like you you come off of
this community, you never come back and
you made a life for himself in another
country, bro. You have to give credit
where credit's due.
Seriously, you do, bro. You really,
really do. Yeah.
Look good when I look smack. Is it?
Yeah. I look good when I look Max, matey.
And you don't know why you know last
time I tried candy man I looks maxed I
got my face waxed um
you know got a face mask got a lot mate
the absolute lot.
So, you can see why I'm discouraged, but
might go out with my sister. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't want to go out,
but it is my birthday, so I'm thinking,
you know, well, my birthday is the
Monday. I think I'm going out Saturday.
Maybe I'll just go for a meal on my
birthday. I don't know. I just have no desire.
Once you've lost hope, you've lost hope.
So it's kind of like there's no desire of of you know
you get what I mean. Nah, bro.
Oh, USA. Izzy found me cute.
That's nice, isn't it?
I don't know what I am, but everyone
would agree that I'm better looking than that [ __ ]
Everybody would agree.
No one would even deny it because
they're just [ __ ] they'd be lying to themselves.
He's the one that's insecure with a
fragile ego, bro. Not me. Not me at all. At all.
I had fish and chips before I fell asleep.
someone on Reddit that's 17, I don't
message them. I don't if they're 18, I
don't message them at all. So, when you
got this [ __ ] right, saying, "Oh, it's
this isn't certain um states in America.
Not certain states in America.
What a [ __ ] nons, bro.
Why is there so many women nowadays that
have never been in a relationship? Andy,
God, I've never had.
Why is there so many women that say they
haven't been in a relationship?
I love that Clint's um
I love that Clint's comment. He's a
[ __ ] idiot. The rest is dead yet. Um
uh they're still nurseries,
but the thing is you don't even see
pregnant women that much anymore, you know?
I'm sure there was more pregnant women
before [ __ ] social media than there
is now. He's an absolute idiot. When
these people sit there and say there's
millions of people in relationships,
there's also [ __ ] got to be millions
of people that aren't in relationships
cuz most people are single
for different reasons. And like I said,
I don't know the statistics, but most of
the people I know are single, even
people I met in real life.
Like I said, there's a couple of people
that I know in relationships. Yeah,
obviously. But most are single.
Most are definitely single.
She don't want to know. She just don't
want to know you.
Steven, do you think I was right for
giving up this dating thing? Yeah, pretty much.
Oh, I Okay. Okay. Let me do I'll give up until December.
I think that's fair. I think that's very very fair
cuz December is a good a good mug to go out.
That's the best I could do for you, man.
I think like December
is is very busy.
So, there'll be loads and loads of people out.
It's so bad. I don't want to go out on my birthday.
I'll go for a meal. Like, I'll do
something obviously, but I just don't
want to [ __ ] He said, "Yeah, it's the
same old [ __ ] every time." But I said to
my sister, "We'll go out, but we kind of
fell out, but she still wants to go."
But I mean, I'd rather just have a meal,
bro, and just chill on my birthday, man.
I really can't be annoyed with it all.
It is always the same [ __ ] It is. But I
think in December, bro,
you might just um
might just have more of a chance. Maybe.
Well, that's the best I can do. But
until December, I'm not trying, you know.
I said 6 months, but basically if you if
you don't do it to December, after
December, there'd be no point going out
now until um
there'd be no point going out until um
March. So once December once you're in
the new year, there'd be no point going out.
Well, when I go when I go out again, I
go out again. I'm just going to have to
try to stay with somebody as long as possible
before getting their number. That's the only
thing I I I can do, bro. There's nothing
else I'd be able to do. You know, like
stay with them for like as long as I
possibly can, even if they're with someone. Yeah, know
just I just can't find the desire or the
motive to want to
like I said if I go Manchester and see
that think And
then then I would try Manchester 1
million% I would try Manchester 100%.
On [ __ ] 100%. You might as well in
it. But [ __ ] London, bro.
Like I said, if I was in Belgium, I'd be
out now. If I was in Newcastle, I'd be out.
Newcastle, even Scotland, maybe. But
Maybe I should go to Edinburgh on Saturday.
Yeah. What do you think?
No, I've been to Scotland before.
I remember when I went to Scotland. Oh, [ __ ] hell.
I was a [ __ ] mad [ __ ] weren't I?
[ __ ] mad c.
I've got a new match.
[ __ ] stinking son.
But yeah, he still calls me ugly,
but everyone would tell you that I'm
better looking than him.
Crazy, isn't it?
Did you read my community post, Steven
Howard? Was he one of the one that liked it?
You want me to read it out if you
haven't already? I don't mind reading it
out. Do you know what? At this point, I
should be a [ __ ] author.
Obviously, the punctuation is off point,
but I don't know on purpose because he's
not even worth,
you know, the extra second to get the punctuation right,
except from the quotation marks. Did you read it?
Yeah. What was it right? Was anything I said wrong?
>> I don't think so, bro. True though, isn't it?
Nope. I don't gamble, bro. Rarely. I rarely gamble.
Must not maybe like 10 minutes.
It's true what I'm writing though.
Everything I've said is the truth about him.
He's so scared to admit he's been
rejected. Why? I don't get it.
I seriously don't understand.
I've been rejected, but I haven't.
But not in that way. Well, you most
definitely have been rejected if you've
gone on dates. Shod to god you've not
liked every single date you've been on.
So there's not How has he not been rejected?
He's got such a fragile. It must be part
of his autism, isn't it? He must be part
of his [ __ ] autism. Must be part of
his autism, bro.
He's never going to pop it. He's never
going to lose it. He's never ever ever
going to lose it, mate.
He's doing more [ __ ] live streams
about me as well. He's never going to
lose his virginity, bro.
It's not about grammar. I don't need
grammar, bro. You're not worth spending
the time [ __ ]
No. I met this weirdo years ago when I
was about 17.
And he's been obsessed with me ever
since. He will not leave me alone. This [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, I've shown money multiple multiple
multiple multiple times and I can go to
the bank and get some 50 notes out if
you want, but I'm not going to.
You can self project all you want.
You know what we should do, right? You
know, cuz you know when people shows
money, you know when people show money,
right? When you know when people show money, bro,
it's not about how much they can show.
It's if they can show it. Uh,
nah, 13 grand is not a lot of money.
It's really really not a lot of money,
mate. It's nowhere near as as much as
people are making it out. It really
really isn't. £13,000
for not living life for 3 years is worth
it. Not to be, mate. got to be and it's
not about how much you have, it's how if
you can still show it after a certain
time. You know, somebody can show
[ __ ] 10 grand and then the month, you
know, next month they can't show it
again. It depends how much money you get
as well and all the money you have.
That's that's the thing, you know? So,
if you can't show that same amount of
money in 3 months, then
what's the point? You know what I mean? for £13,000.
Think of it. I've got a couple of,000.
I've got maybe £3,000. But guess what? I
wouldn't want £13,000 if it meant taking
my life experiences back.
Yeah, I might have like 3,000, but I'm I wouldn't,
you know, I wouldn't um
I wouldn't I wouldn't exchange for 13
cuz you have
life is is about life experiences.
Yeah. Well, you're silly then, aren't you?
You're silly, bro. I don't gamble
anymore cuz of um Well, like I said, I
do rarely. It's cuz of um the whole um
mood swings and it's just not worth it.
I might do a football I I do want to do
a like 160 football bet on Saturday
though. I want to try and win a football
bet, bro. Every week. I need to build
some more money up just cuz I just need
to, you know, I might do slow and Kitty
Minister. It should win again. They've
won every game in a [ __ ] month. So
hopefully I remember that time when I
went out that Sunday and I met um finish Izzy.
I had like 200 pound left, bro, until
the next week. I had to try and [ __ ]
win some money.
Lucky I won that football bet in it.
But that was then I've got money. I can
go out. I have got money. The reason I
don't go out trying is not because of
lack of funds. I've got the money.
Definitely definitely definitely have
the money. But not worth it. Look.
What did you Did you lose?
Oh, did you lose?
So, you liked my community post.
I'm too intelligent for these people.
Yeah, this woman's about to come to
Ireland and see me, but she's a bit
stinking so or
Yeah. What do you think about women
sausage rolls? They are [ __ ] aren't
they? They are [ __ ] [ __ ]
They are [ __ ] [ __ ] in it.
I don't understand how people don't see
how [ __ ] up it is. Sausage rolls like
10 numbers looks maxing not even a date
even though someone agreed to meet you.
I don't think people acknowledge like
how [ __ ] up that is.
That is [ __ ] up, bro. Is it?
Oh, this woman says she lives in Scotland.
H maybe I could go to Scotland. Oh, it's
Scotland she lives.
So, I could go to Scotland and then just
get on a drink.
But my birthday is a Monday.
[ __ ] Scotland's a threat, don't it?
She's a bit stinking though. That's the thing.
I don't think it's worth going to Scotland for.
[ __ ] Scotland there.
When you going to lose it?
Yeah. When are you going to pop it? Well,
I can. I mean, that's not even being
picky. If I didn't get with her, that's
not being picky. That's not being picky.
That's just not getting with somebody
that's absolutely stinking. I'm not
I'm decent looking when I go out. I
think there is a bit of difference.
What does she say? She says,
"If you come up for your birthday, I buy
all your drinks on Monday and we can
have an all nighter and watch the sunrise." H.
What do I know about that?
Maybe if you give me a [ __ ] we'll consider.
Oh, my birthday is Monday. It's such a
[ __ ] day. If my birthday was Sunday, you
could still go out drinking, you know,
cuz people would be out Sunday. But on
you, you can't.
Yeah, you can stay with me for a week
and see how it goes. [Music]
Don't know if I believe you.
I'm 28 on Monday.
Remember that Steven Howard? Women are
bad people in general.
Yeah, they are bad people in general proper.
They're proper bad people in general.
USA Izzy's birthday is April. How cute is that?
Nah, she was a [ __ ]
She was a nasty [ __ ]
She caused a lot of problems that [ __ ]
for me, you know.
I need to try and win like 30 grand. Bro,
if I put 500 pound on roulette, there's
a chance I could win 30 grand.
I need I would want to win like 20 30 grand, bro.
I need to win like Yeah. 20 30k.
Remember that time I went casino and I
won four grand? Oh
[ __ ] man. That was mad. Imagine I won
like 20, 30 grand I had in cash. Oh
mate, I'd be laughing. [ __ ] laughing.
Oh, sickening is it?
I know. My friends won 17 grand.
What I would do with 20 grand, bro? Jeez.
Nonsense has got [ __ ] all.
He's got [ __ ] all. Why does everyone
keep going on that like 13 grand is a
lot of money when it isn't?
It's not a lot of money for no life experiences.
You don't understand. Listen, bro. Okay,
listen. Listen. I'll say it to you. I might
I might not have 13 grand, bro. I've got
more life experiences than he will ever
have. Like I said on my post, which is
better than than the 13 grand. What are
you going to do with it, bro? You know, so yeah.
No, how about you get to six grand and
play down to five and then run.
That's what I should have done. That I
went to the casino and I got to four
grand. I should have gambled to 3k and
then took it but really kept going for it.
I missed some times, bro.
Yeah, I should have just played it down
to three cuz what would have I that was
the day I was push America as well.
Madness. [ __ ] madness.
I'd love to win that 18 grand, bro, in cash.
Yeah, I went in with 150 and I hit 11
with a multiplier
165x and I had like 23 pound on it. Oh m
badness. It was a Wednesday as well.
I should have played it down to like
three grand, but as soon as I got to
four grand, I couldn't believe it. I was
in disbelief cuz I was drunk.
I was like, "What the [ __ ] madness.
I couldn't believe it, bro. Oh, I was
like, "What the fuck?" So, you're drunk,
you're just gambling, you expect to win
a couple hundred.
Well, I should have played it to three
grand, but I was like, "I'll just get
out of it." Four grand in it. [ __ ] it.
They gave me the money and wallets as
well. Absolute [ __ ] I'm surprised
people Someone didn't try to rob me.
Yeah, I got a couple of grand Mr. B, but
I wish I had like 18.
The most I've ever had is I think eight.
Yeah, the most I've ever had is about eight grand.
Yeah, that's the most I've ever had.
How much How much cash is nice,
Mr. B? What amount of cash is nice?
Yeah, it was nice, bro. I think the most
I had in cash was like 5.7.
Most of them were in like 50s.
Peter B used to have a lot of [ __ ] money, mate.
Not so much nowadays,
but it's just normal. See, I just have
like a normal amount of money. But yeah,
I'll never be skinn or anything. But
you think you could win £20,000 online though?
Do you think you could like win 20 grand online? Yeah.
That's the thing. If you're on benefits,
right, they give you your money when you
gamble. They give you money in cash. So
the benefit people would never know
because they give it in cash.
So they always give it I don't know what
the most they can give you in cash is
probably like 20 grand but yeah they
give you it in Yeah,
I don't know, bro.
Wish I was rich, matey. Yeah, virgin boy.
I don't know. He's never going to meet anyone.
Yeah, about that. about that
which is okay is it 2K is okay I guess
got some garments as well but the
problem is if I need to buy garments or
something this is what the problem is
going to be but I I won't need you for a long And
you know what I'm saying?
I got money cuz like whenever I I'd go
out, I'd win money from the football. So
I never spend like my own money if that makes sense.
So yeah, I'd never spend.
I've already got gums.
I've already got gums. You've seen it.
You've seen my gums.
[ __ ] long time cuz I don't go out anymore.
Well, I don't go out anymore. So,
yeah, cuz I don't go out.
Um because stab on it. Yeah, it doesn't really go. So yeah,
should last a while, it
got garments, bro. I've got a new pair
of trainers. They still look fresh.
I might wear this if I go out on my
birthday. I might wear this.
I might wear this. [ __ ] me, bro.
Look, Mr. B. Dude, this is dry clean, bro.
I might wear this.
Might wear that.
Might wear this.
They still look fresh in it. I've only
worn them a couple times.
They're still like box fresh.
But you'd have to wear something over
the [ __ ] jumper in it. [Music]
They're my garments. But still look
fresh in it. Going bored. Imagine that.
[ __ ] that, bro.
Yeah, they still smell like brand new.
So, I've got I've got a lot of garments,
don't I, Mr. B?
I got a lot of garments, bro.
Still, it's my favorite one.
Wrong trainers. I didn't know there was
right and wrong trainers.
But yeah, but the thing is now these
Ammoni jeans are like 200 pound now and
I wouldn't pay 200 pound. Even when I
had more money back in the day, I
wouldn't pay £200.
Know what I mean?
But I don't know.
Oh, [ __ ] sake, man.
My jeans are like I need to buy some new
jeans at some point, which is going to be expensive.
It's [ __ ] in it.
So, yeah, still got a few garments to wear.
I ain't no skin version of a [ __ ]
bed. No money in it.
What do you think, Mr. B?
No, no [ __ ] money in it.
Yeah, the button broke on the [ __ ] jeans.
So yeah, them stone islands will last forever.
You never need to buy I never need to
buy another stone island dumper again
to be honest. Once you buy them, they
last forever. But obviously the trainers you will
Yeah, the trainers you will obviously
see I like the Levi tops. You know the
plain Levi tops. It's like a pack of two
for 23. All you got to do is wear white white t-shirt
with Ammani jeans and trainers and then
Bob's your uncle.
Yeah, them Bob's your [ __ ] uncle, Too much.
You you think if you won 20k online on
roulette, do you reckon they'd actually pay you?
You think they would actually pay you 20 grand?
Yeah, that's the best. Um,
you imagine they didn't pay you.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Yeah, you get them white Levi T-shirts
and a nice pair of Ammani jeans.
And Bob's your uncle. Yeah, man.
It's so expensive clothes, isn't it? so expensive.
Back in the day when I had loads and
loads of money, I could do it. But I'll
just buy like I like All Saints as well.
Yeah, I like All Saints.
A lot of my t-shirts are All Saints.
I don't know, bro. Virgin [Music]
no money in it. Yep. One name.
You just don't want to know you.
Just don't want to know you, mate. USA
is he liked my um Stone Island.
Yeah, I remember when I went to the
shopping mall and I I spent
[ __ ] 12 I spent £1,100 on just garments, bro. Madness was mad.
got the summer gear and stuff. Yeah,
it doesn't even seem that much, isn't
it? 1100 pound to get all of that.
Too bad, I guess.
Yeah, I just get the plain Levi t-shirts
and the morning jeans and pair of
trainers. You're good to go in it.
You're good to go, man.
Yeah, he's skinny. He
lo J. He's like, "Oh, I don't even think
he has £500. Why wouldn't I have £500?"
I need to win a football bet every week though, bro. Seriously,
put 180 on it and win every week. Reloaded.
Yeah, you reloaded.
We all good, bro. Yep.
You like my little stone islands. Yeah.
Why are Reddit mods such so power hungry? Copy.
I've realized that they're so bloody power hungry
and I'm sick of it.
These mods are so [ __ ] power hungry.
You know what I mean by that? that they
need to feel in control.
That's what they ban people to feel powerful. Yeah.
He don't want to know.
He don't want to know you.
GBY. She don't want to know you.
No, no, no.
He don't want to know you.
Yeah, I gave up with the whole dating thing, Gobby.
It was getting [ __ ] toxic, lad.
Yeah, this [ __ ] is obsessed, bro. Very
obsessed. I'm on the [ __ ]
Yeah, the pond's up at all. You got [ __ ] ruined.
But it doesn't matter how right you are
about this [ __ ] People, most people
will still act as if they disagree.
You know what I mean? even out there
But you can toss and go, can you?
Where can you get this casual sex?
Because dating apps don't work.
And when you approach women, they
pretend they got boyfriends. So, I'd
love to know.
Must be something I'm missing. Really?
I must be missing something.
>> I'd love to know where you get this casual sex. Yeah.
Oh, you don't believe it's right to be
He's so triggered. I'm actually watching
the live stream. I'm not going to reply
back to it. I'm not replying back to it,
but he's so triggered.
Well, lucky you, bro. I can't get
anyone, man. No one's bloody interested.
Dating apps don't work.
Lucky you, man. Lucky you. [ __ ] jealous.
I'm jealous, man.
[ __ ] you, bro.
And you don't know more women than me.
You've not been with more women than me.
And you ain't got more life experience
than me as well.
No, you don't know more women than me. Yeah.
Where do you find these people? Gobby,
did you did you watch some of my
approaching videos and my videos on
dating apps? I can't get a bloody match.
Gobby, people keep telling me to go on
these bloody dating apps, but they don't work. Sure.
I'm not sure why.
They tell me to go on the apps. got be.
They tell me to approach in person
and then they all say they got bloody boyfriends. Yeah.
It doesn't matter if somebody said that
they're going to um
it doesn't matter if I've said about
other people's kids in retaliation.
You're trying to justify how it's okay
to get with a 16year-old.
Doesn't matter what I've said about
people's kids in retaliation.
No. Doesn't doesn't at all. So what
so what do you want to do? You I don't
understand this the whole point of all
of this, bro.
You just want to be a keyboard warrior
for the rest rest of your low life. I
don't get it. you know,
recent one. It was over a year ago.
Wouldn't wouldn't class that as recent.
Wouldn't class that as recent.
Saving baby grows does not make somebody an aunt. Yeah.
And that casino manager thing was over a
year ago. I don't know. Over a year ago
was recent. This country is so low IQ.
It's It's actually scary, bro. It is actually scary.
We don't know anything again.
And stop talking about mommy. You live
in a council bedsit. I don't know how
many times you have to keep going over
this time and time and time again. You
live in a council bedsit. You are not independent.
Stop talking about people living with
their mummy. You are not independent.
Your living circumstances is [ __ ]
They're proper proper low IQ as well.
Like you live in a cancel bed [ __ ] Stop
telling people who they live with, who
they don't live with. For [ __ ] sake.
You've never worked a day in your life
and you're trying to talk about [ __ ]
people being independent. He's a He's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, they all bro.
>> Yeah, you're not a ladies man. You're a
[ __ ] virgin. So, at least at least
you uh you said that.
Yeah. You're not a ladies man. You're a virgin.
Why Why is it with you and people's
mummy? Like he he he's so but hurt that
his mom abused him and starved him. Do
you think this is where like the the the
insecurities come from?
I've stated it like a million times. I
would rather live with my mom than live
in a bedsit with no bed in it and no
money in it. I've literally stated it
like a million times. I've been like the low IQ.
You live in a cancel bed that you don't
[ __ ] own. You don't even live in a house.
Like do these people do their brains not
work properly or something? Got got to
be something bro that I'm you know
[ __ ] missing here. You know
what is it with you and people's money?
Like why are you so ass with who people
live with and who people don't live
with? You live in a bedsit.
I I don't understand, bro. Like, are you
trying to take some?
No. I I I don't need to work on my
grammar and my punctuation. Um because I
He's not even worth the extra second to
get the grammar and punctuation right.
So, no, I done that on purpose. It's
He's not worth the extra few seconds.
and we're not at school,
so I don't need to work on anything at
all. I done that on purpose. Um, I'm
more educated than he would ever be. I'm
more intelligent than he'd ever be,
which is why my four thumbs up is genuine.
Why is this guy so obsessed with where
who people live with when he lives in a
bedset? I mean, I don't understand what
the whole argument is. You're pathetic.
You've never worked a day in your life,
right? You don't own your house. You
don't have a bed. You've been on
benefits all your life and you've never
worked. And you're trying to talk about
who people live with because the council
gave you a bed sit.
I mean, it's it's it's not a W. I don't
know why you keep saying it like it is a W.
You live in a cancelled bedsit. I'd
rather live with my mom. I don't know
how many times I've said, bro, I've said
this about a million times, right? You
are not independent.
Stop trying to take the mole high ground
for, you know, because you live in a
bedit with a [ __ ] disabled [ __ ] that
can't talk. For [ __ ] sake, it is
generally a [ __ ] madness,
you know. Am I in a relationship? No,
I'm [ __ ] single. So, what what do you
want me to do? pay [ __ ] two, three
grand a month for rent.
Somewhere I I won't stay half the time.
I I don't understand this skint virgin's
logic. He needs to live in the real
world. But obviously getting hand out
your whole life, that's that's that's
not easy, you know. But I don't need to
work on my grandma punctuation at all.
You've read what you've read and that's that.
You just want to go round and round in
circles. Again, insecure. Me, not simple. Like
you want to go round and round in
circles all your life because you're an
insecure little virgin yourself. It's
[ __ ] obvious, bro. [ __ ] going
round in circles all your life on
YouTube. It's [ __ ] pathetic, you know?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. It's not
because it's good or not good. He was
obsessed with this [ __ ] for like two [ __ ] years.
Yeah. Well, it got four thumbs up, so it
must have been right.
Yeah. Well, he got [ __ ] shattered
completely. Grammar, no grammar. He got
owned. Simple as that. So yeah,
he got owned as simple as that.
No, you literally compare it to the
Britney situation. You think that just
because you've been rejected by Britney,
every single woman that I have met, I've
not slept with.
Yeah. Oh, bro, this guy,
he stalks me every day.
I know. I know I'm doing something
right, bro. I've said this a million
times, but these people are too low IQ.
They don't understand that. They waste
every second of every day of their life harassing you,
you know, and then and I've said it in
the past, they've got to be jealous of
something, but then they sit there and
then they say that they're not jealous.
Oh, what's there to be jealous of?
What's there to be jealous of? Yet, they
will continuously stalk you. They will
continuously make videos about you.
They'll continuously go live about you,
but they're not jealous of anything.
Their logic. So why would somebody even bother, you know,
it's because they're insecure, jealous
people with no life? Unless I'm missing
something. What the [ __ ]
It's obvious. It's so obvious. Insecure little virgin.
That's what he is. Nothing I said in
that community post was was wrong.
You know, I hit you. I hit the nail on
the head. That's why you're triggered.
I know you better than you know your virgin self. What's up?
Well, you're talking about grammar and punctuation.
There's no full stop in anything that you've wrote.
H, that's strange. You're probably older than me.
You're talking about grammar and punctuation.
You're not doing correct grammar and punctuation.
H, strange. Well, people definitely read
it and people definitely liked it.
Yeah, this it doesn't matter if it's a
live chat. You're still not using
[ __ ] grammar. You're still not using punctuation.
Yeah. Oh, grammar punctuation. Where's
yours? Where's yours? You [ __ ]
[ __ ] Where's your grammar and punctuation?
You [ __ ] little [ __ ] man. Go [ __ ]
off to Virgin Boy channel. You [ __ ]
[ __ ] Oh, talking about grammar and
punctuation. Oh, grammar and
punctuation, bro. There's no, it's not
worth the extra couple of seconds for
some little skint virgin that ain't got no life, you know. Okay.
still going on about a [ __ ] This
guy, bro, he's definitely a virgin, bro.
I'm telling you, he's a virgin. The way
he convinces himself that people's a
virgin like him. Oh, bro, is it [ __ ]
punctuation? Why the [ __ ] did it get
thumbs up then?
You know, it got thumbs up because I'm
[ __ ] right. That's why
he's so I should have brought up the
escort story as well.
Why don't you believe that someone's had
sex with an escort? That's another good
question. Is it because you're a virgin
and you've never had sex with an escort
or anyone? Well, not an escort, anyone.
That's just like a normal thing to
believe, isn't it?
Having sex with an escort, not having
sex with an escort. It's not
unbelievable, really, is it? Is it strange?
>> Yeah, he's definitely a virgin.
Definitely definitely a virgin.
These people on here really, really need
to get a life. Have you seen that Clint account?
Have you seen that Clint account, Steven Howard?
I said to him, "Oh, yeah. I'm all of
these things that you can't take a day
off of YouTube." And he said, "How do
you know I can't take a day off
YouTube?" Because I've seen you, mate.
That's what I'm doing now. Um, Gobby,
listen, bro. Um, that's what I'm doing
now. If I ever want sex, I'll just use
an escort. But I don't really have a
high sex drive anymore because the way I
see it is is is gobby is that it's not
worth humiliating yourself and dealing
with their games just to be with
someone. It's not worth it. Like going
out looking your best just to just to be
in with a chance of getting a date and
getting somewhere. It's not worth it.
Like if I ever get like a, you know,
horny again, like prop horny, I'll just
get I'll just get an escort.
Yeah, 100%, bro. 1 million%. Because
it's just not worth it. The whole dating
thing is just not worth it.
And there's nothing a woman can really
offer you any other than sex if you
think about it. If you really really
think about it, I was thinking about
this earlier. What can they give you
other than sex that you can't give your
[ __ ] self? They'll drain your money.
They'll give you a headache. Madness.
No, virgin boy. They don't with they
don't want sex with you, which is why
you're still a virgin. And why you
resort And why are you [ __ ]
um why you resort to disabled? Again,
nobody wants sex with you. That's why
you're still a virgin. I've had sex with
plenty of people. Again, self-protecting insecurities again.
>> No, they want it, but they don't want it
with you. That's why you target disabled.
Look at how triggered he is as well.
Have you actually listened to this live stream back?
No, they don't want it with you. That's
why you're still a virgin at 31. Never
had sex. Continuously talking about
people's sex life to make yourself feel
better about you being a virgin. And and
and I'm right. No one can tell me I'm
wrong. Not anyone can tell me my
community post is wrong. They can only
say that there's no grammar in it. No,
they don't want sex with you. That's why
you resort to disabled disabled girls
that can't talk. Simple.
You [ __ ] virgin. I can say it like
[ __ ] terrible, you know.
No, no, no, no, no. You didn't have
relationships that didn't go the way you
wanted. It got You got rejected. I
already brought one [ __ ] person up
that you didn't mention. You got
rejected. You do not get into a
relationship with these women and you
broke up with them. Women break up with
men. Men don't break up with women.
How the [ __ ] would I would I know that
if I don't have these experiences?
You know what I'm saying? Women break up
with men. You got rejected.
Just like that law run. Yes, you did.
You got rejected.
Why are you so scared to say that you've been rejected?
No, I'm watching a live stream back,
bro. I'm watching a bit of the live
stream back. No one's typing.
You You're the one that's a [ __ ]
intel. You're the one that [ __ ]
targets [ __ ] disabled girls. You
[ __ ] low life. You're the one that
has to target disabled women cuz you're
that much of a [ __ ] incel. I'm pretty
sure that's what [ __ ] an incel would [ __ ] do.
We still haven't heard about this. Lara,
you did not be in relationships and you
broke up with all of them women. No
chance. Women are the ones that break up
with people. Men are really the ones
that break up with people going by what
I've seen. And I know this stuff anyways.
Trust me, it's the it's the women that
break up with people, not some skint
little virgin in a bed sit with no teeth.
Am I lying?
You didn't break up with no one. You got
rejected. Shut up. Shut the [ __ ] up. You
have been rejected just like everybody
else. You are not any different at 31.
You are not any different than all of
these other people that's been rejected.
You can't think of somebody that's been
that's rejected you outright. Okay, as I
explained, numbum nuts, dates where you
like people that don't like you back. [ __ ]
Lara that broke up with you.
I mean, you have been rejected. And the
only reason you've not been rejected
more than me is because you ain't got
the balls to go out and meet normal
women, which is why you target disabled.
Yeah, you might have not been rejected
more than me, but I've been with more
women than you have. And no one could
even [ __ ] disagree with that.
You know, I've never known someone so
scared of admitting to being rejected.
I've never known it in my life. That's
that's what I mean. The fragile insecure
ego. This is This is what I mean, bro.
Calling someone an incel that's been
with more women than you, that's had
more sex than you. Just because I don't
lick women's asses, it doesn't make
someone an incel because I don't say,
"Oh, yeah, women are perfect. They go
for personality." Just because I don't
lie, that doesn't mean someone's a
[ __ ] incel. And you'd actually be
more closer to misogynist than an incel.
So, get your facts right. I mean, just
because I don't do that, it doesn't mean
I'm I I'm an incel, what the [ __ ]
How can an incel been with more women
than [ __ ] you? Make it make sense,
you know? It's [ __ ] madness.
Okay. Okay. So, you Okay. So, you've
met, right? You've met so many women
from dating apps and none of them have
ended it with you.
None of none no one's ended it with a 31year-old virgin.
Sounds hard to believe, don't it, Gobby?
It sounds very very hard to believe that
nobody finished it with him and he
finished it with everyone else.
No, shut up. You rejected little virgin.
You've been rejected. Shut up. Shut the [ __ ] up.
I don't think I'd want a virgin as a
teacher. You're You're a teacher of
dating apps. I don't think I'd want a
virgin teaching me about dating apps.
Thank you very much. Cringe.
So your his logic is that anyone that's
not a s or white knight is an incel. Yet
that person that same person has been
with more women than them, but they're
an incel because they don't lick women's
asses. Must be must be referring to
yourself. Must be mate.
This guy is an absolute [ __ ] [ __ ]
He, you know, talk about low IQ. He
didn't even process any of the things
that I wrote. [ __ ] hell. Yeah.
Because you've never spoke to women in
real life, you [ __ ] [ __ ] That's why
you've never been rejected [ __ ] you
know, face to face. It's because you
don't have the balls to approach, which
is why you target disabled. [ __ ] hell.
So yeah, if you if you if you
if you've been dumped then yeah, you
basically have been rejected. It's it's
a form of rejection. And it's not just
about being dumped as well. You've also
gone on dates where I'm sure you've
liked somebody that's not liked you back.
So I'm sure that's also happened as
well. It must have have happened, you know. No, mate.
Yeah, but it can't have been every
single [ __ ] date.
That's madness, bro.
Yeah, but we're not just talking about breakups.
And it's you haven't met a woman
physically cuz you're too socially awkward.
That's why you're too socially awkward.
That's why you you you can't even
function in normal environments.
So, yes, you haven't been rejected
physically because you're too socially
awkward to go into a normal environment
to being a [ __ ] normal environment.
Like, oh my god, what an absolute
[ __ ] idiot. Where are some of these people, bro?
She didn't want to know you cuz you were
scared and you were jobless. I'm not
lying. Thanks for saying that. I wasn't
lying. I knew I wasn't lying, mate.
It's cuz you had no money and you had no
job. You know, at least you admitted it.
Okay. Well, there must have been dates where
there must there must have been dates
where you got rejected, mate. You know,
there's no way, you know, it's not happened.
You skid virgin. [Music]
Oh man, your stimps on your channel need
to get a life as well as you. You really
really need to get a life. How How many
more years are you going to keep doing
this on YouTube?
Yeah, I'm I'm proud to talk about a
19year-old that's 19, not 16. Somebody
that's not that that doesn't go to
school. Yeah. Big difference between 16
and and 19. Yeah. Nah. Yeah. There's a
big difference. Big big [ __ ]
Did you get with a 17y old when you was
22 and pretending that you had sex with her
and you didn't do anything with her at
all? I thought we didn't even make any sense.
Where is Ricky? He's disappeared. This [ __ ]
[ __ ] community, bro.
He wanted to go to C and chase something
that didn't want him.
Yeah. What's wrong with go what's wrong
with a 19y old when you're 26?
I mean they say you're an adult at 18.
There's a bit of a difference.
You lied about sleeping with a 17y old
when you was 22.
You met a 17-year-old and pretended that
you [ __ ] her and you never you [ __ ]
nothing. You never [ __ ] nothing in
your whole virgin life. So I don't know
why you you tell [ __ ] stories.
You have never [ __ ] anything and you
never will [ __ ] anything. You skimp bastard.
again talking about my nose. Even though
everyone agrees I'm better looking than him.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
He's You know what? He He's never going
to get laid. This [ __ ] is never ever
going to get laid, bro. I'm telling you.
He's gonna die a virgin.
Like, I'm not even joking. Steven
Howard, he is going to [ __ ] die a virgin.
This is what I look like, bro.
Nothing wrong with the way that I look. Look. I'm handsome.
Nothing wrong with the way I look at all, mate.
Do a god of barbers at some point, but
it keeps me warm in this cold weather, you know.
But um yeah,
hate the cold weather, bro. Really do.
Really do. Do you? Yes.
Let me listen to some more of this [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Projected. Do you will you ever
stop projecting your virginity onto people?
Will you ever stop? I don't think you'll ever stop.
It takes a certain [ __ ] gobby to want
to sit on the internet and argue with
someone all day every day for years but
never meet them. It takes a certain
certain low IQ person to do that. Would you agree?
Yes, I've listen. You've been in a
relationship with a disabled girl.
That's worse than never having a
relationship. I don't know why this guy
seems to think that he's better than
people when he's not. He says that
people live with his mom. He lives in a
bed sit with no bed. Ain't got no money.
He says that people have never been in a
relationship. The only people that he's
been in a relationship with is a disabled girl.
Why does this guy seem to think Why does
somebody that's never ever worked with
no teeth seem to think that they're
better than someone? I don't understand.
Really, really don't.
Why do you care whether I've been in a
relationship or not? I don't understand.
Look at your own life. You need to go to
the [ __ ] dentist and sort your
[ __ ] ugly, toothless mouth out. I
don't know why you so obsessed with me
and what I do. You know,
this community is full of retards, bro.
I'm literally coming off this [ __ ] soon.
It's so weird, isn't it?
No. Yeah. I I know about her existence
because you wouldn't stop going on about
her every single time I [ __ ] met you.
All you would do is go on about Britney
time and time and time and time again.
[ __ ] sick of [ __ ] hearing it, you know?
[ __ ] chasing something that don't
want you. It's [ __ ] madness. He would
lally sit there and chase something that
never wanted him. Steven Howard, it was
mad. She don't want you.
She don't want you. She never did want
you. Never. [ __ ] hell. Anyways,
no more videos
videos. No more replying.
No, no, mate. No, no, no, no. She's
younger than me, mate. No, no, no, no.
[ __ ] this this this is shitty community,
is it, Steven Howard?
It's such a shitty community, bro. I'm
coming off this [ __ ] bro, for a little
bit. It's a shitty community, ain't it?
You're never going to get laid.
still going on about USA. Is he still
convincing himself that I've not had
slept I've not had sex with her?
He is so jealous, isn't he? I've never
never I've never ever, bro, ever come
across someone so jealous of someone in
my life. And it and it and it validates
my point even more that he's a virgin.
It invalidates my point even more that
he's a virgin and what I'm saying is the
truth. Because bro, why does someone
care if someone's had sex with someone
or not? It's all to make himself feel
better that he's a virgin. And that's
why he does this whole
shouting and stuff. It's mad.
It is. It is actually mad. It's why he's
going live shouting and all of this
[ __ ] bro. It's madness.
It's all because he's never had sex.
That's what it is. So, what what was the
excuse for the escort one then?
What's the Okay, what was the excuse for
the escort one then? Not believing
someone's had sex with an escort. Again,
it all ties down to you and Britney
situation because you're a virgin. It's obvious.
No, you messaged somebody. No, you
messaged somebody coming from a place of
sympathy knowing that you was going to
get the answers that you want. Again,
out of your fragile little ego. Knowing
that I had problems with somebody
speaking [ __ ] knowing that they were
going to talk [ __ ] about me. So again,
not a you and Britney situation. I have
to keep saying this a million times.
Again, not a you and Britney situation.
You knew. No, no, no. What you done was
you knew I had problems with someone.
You messaged them sending them stuff
that I said knowing that knowing damn
well that they were going to talk [ __ ] about me,
which is why they come up with a story
that they've kicked me out of somewhere.
You knew you was going to get the
answers that you wanted because you're
an opportunist and you knew I had
problems with the person. And then
you've messaged them coming from a place
of sympathy just like you do with every
other woman because you're a virgin and
you've never had sex yourself because
your dick don't work properly. So that's
what you done knowing damn well that
they were never ever going to tell the
truth and then somehow oh yeah Britney
situation like it's been explained
multiple multiple multiple times but it
doesn't seem to get through to your
thick go in your fixed skull.
I'm saying Stephen Howard, it is
actually a [ __ ] madness.
You knowing damn well that they were
going to talk [ __ ] and especially that
you you've come from a place of sympathy
again, not a you and Britney situation.
I have to keep repeating it. You compare
the same thing as you being rejected to
Britney. He he he literally compares he
literally write this is what this little
skimp virgin does. He will literally
write say you meet someone right and um
you know they've met you once and you
had a bad time with them. He will
literally do anything to make sure that
you've not had sex with someone because
he's still a virgin. And he's been doing
it for he's been doing it for years.
That's he's been literally doing it for
years. his whole life is validating
himself that everyone's a virgin like
him. And because I've met him like
multiple times, I know this stuff, bro.
Again, you're stuck in the past cuz
you're a virgin. You're you're you're
stuck convincing yourself stuff cuz
you're a virgin. [ __ ] you do it.
You've done it for years. You've
literally been doing it for years. And
you also knew that they had a boyfriend
as well, so you knew damn well they were
going to lie about me. And oh that's he
hasn't sex with her because one person
because because he's met with somebody
one time and they've lied about him. Oh,
I get my little adrenaline rush now. I
get I get the what's it called? I get
the dopamine. That's what he does. He
does this little dopamine thing cuz he's
a [ __ ] virgin.
That's why. And he knew that the person
and he knew that the person was going to
talk [ __ ] about me as well. Just like
most women would talk [ __ ] about
somebody that they met once. He knew
that he was going to get the answers
that he wanted and he come from a place
of sympathy and he made sure as well to
tell the person that I've spoke [ __ ]
about them before messaging them. So
again, that's not a you and Britney situation.
It's not the you that can only get
disabled women situation
obsessed continuously talking about some [ __ ]
idiot from [ __ ] years ago, which is
not the first person that I've been
with. And it and it wasn't the last
person that I've been with. So you you
you cling on to things that you're
jealous of to try to get a dopamine rush.
I know all of this stuff, bro. It's so obvious.
It's so [ __ ] obvious.
What What did you want someone to say? I
don't understand what what what you
wanted them to say.
He's so obsessed and it shows that he's
a virgin and he's not in a happy relationship.
Sat on YouTube, go around in circles
every day, never meeting anyone, just
being a keyboard warrior. grow up and
stop thinking that you can keep taking a
more high ground in people's [ __ ]
living circumstances as well, you know.
Okay, I'm going to do I'm going to do
one more video back to this [ __ ] and
then I am done. Right, I am going to do
one more video back to this [ __ ]
and that is honestly I swear to God in
my mom's life I'm not doing any I'm not
doing any more after this about your
little community post but then you go on
to say that you've read the other uh no
you message somebody coming from a place
of sympathy knewing I had problems with
that person to validate your to try to
validate the fact that you're still a
virgin so you can get that say that
dopamine rush you do it with every
single woman you virgin even people even
people right that you know
it it it's it's crazy. It really really
really really is [ __ ] crazy. It shows
that he's a virgin. How the how these
people can still back this [ __ ] up is is
is mad. Trying to say that he's not a
virgin because he's got girlfriends.
It's [ __ ] It is actually insane, bro.
You knew that I had a problem with
someone, right? And you come from a
place of sympathy, knowing that you was
going to get the answers that you
wanted, knewing damn well without that.
And yes, girls do lie. Girls also lie
about getting raped. Virgin boy. And if
you had if you if you had actually I
mean people do lie about getting raped
even though that is like a more like
severe accusation. It's more rarer. It
does happen. It [ __ ] well does happen
mate. I mean you read about it. So no
you knew that you was going to get the
answer that you wanted. You knew that
the person had a boyfriend and you knew
that you was going to get the answer
that you wanted. Again not the you and Britney situation,
you know. So that's not part of my
little community post. Again, get a
life. Stop coming on YouTube convincing
yourself people ain't slept with people
every day cuz you ain't slept with nothing
or because you ain't slept with a woman.
It's so obvious now. If if every if if
if there was to be any doubt in my mind
that I was lying, bro, he proves it now.
The way he talks about sex, it proves
he's never had it. And I'm going to
bring up the I'm going to bring up the
escort situation as well. I'm going to
bring up the escort. The very first
story that I told how everyone else can
believe it, but him, the virgin, nope.
They show ID. They show ID. It's like
every It's like he gets a dopamine rush.
It's a bit situation
and then he rubs his hands. It's like a
It's like a dopamine rush. It's the same
like rush that you get from gambling.
It's the same um rush that you get from gambling.
Literally, it is the same rush that you
get from gambling. Honestly is.
And no, you message somebody coming from
a place of sympathy
knowing that you was going to get the
answer that you wanted. That's that's
what wasn't it? Because you didn't you
didn't message all the other women that
you knew that was going to shut you
down. But to be honest, you would still
deny it because if someone's not a
virgin like you, you're not happy. You
will literally spend all your life
trying to get somebody to say they're
not slept with me cuz you're a virgin.
And and that is the truth. Nobody can
even deny that, bro. Like many people
are not on it now because they're not
awake. But it's so obvious. It's so [ __ ] obvious
that he is a virgin. Girlfriend, no
girlfriend. It's obvious. You show yourself up.
It's like he needs that He needs that
dopamine rush. He He He He needs that
dopamine rush, mate. If he doesn't have
that dopamine rush, he ain't happy.
It's like he gets a little It's a me situation.
Oh, it literally is that, bro. It
literally is that convincing. And And
even if I [ __ ] hadn't, why are you
still going on about it? you know, since
with since [ __ ] that and now, right?
Since since uh now, I'm not I'm not even
going to do a video.
Yeah, since now. Right. Since uh
don't do a video or do a community post.
I'm going to respond one more time. One
more time to this gun.
cuz I [ __ ] I forgot the escort thing as
well. So yeah, like I said, that's it.
And it's not going to be a [ __ ] hour
long. You're [ __ ] obsessed.
Again, no one in your chat can say that
um no one on your chat um can say that
that you're better looking than me. Like
no, they won't even lie, bro. You could
you could ask everybody on your chat and
they won't even lie.
Like the fact that you still go on about
it, it shows that you are a virgin. It
shows what you are. Same thing with the
escort thing. Everyone has to be a
virgin like you or you're not happy. You
don't get no dopamine rush and that's
what you are. You're a [ __ ] virgin. I
don't care about some disabled girl that
you can't go near sexually. I don't give
a [ __ ] You've been talking about that
for [ __ ] years. I'm telling you what
the [ __ ] you are. Obsessed virgin. It's the truth. Anyways, um
I'm going to respond to this. So, yeah.
What's today? Thursday, isn't it? Good. Yeah, man.