Some people in here really need a [ __ ] life.
Still stalking me.
I wonder who that is.
messaging people's [ __ ] sisters on
Instagram. It's sad as [ __ ]
Sad sad [ __ ]
That Instagram account's been doing that for years.
Sad as [ __ ]
Lonely people that ain't got a life on it. So obvious [ __ ] Yeah, this account
message my sister on Instagram. Sad bastard. Sad. Sad.
These people have anything better to do
with their life?
It's [ __ ] so sad, bro. So sad.
There it is. Yeah.
I'm tired, boss.
Yeah, this account keeps uh messaging my
sister on Instagram.
That bastard. It's the same one that was
stalking me for them years.
You really You really need to question
who's behind this account. It's so sad.
It's really [ __ ] sad.
But how desperate they are to rage bait,
you know, the rage baiting. You can just
tell they've got nothing in their life, these people.
It's so sad.
Got nothing better to do than to [ __ ]
rage bait. What the [ __ ] Like,
why are you [ __ ]
whoever that is trying to rage bait.
We're not talking about that virgin. So
when you're bringing that [ __ ] up,
you're talking to yourself cuz you're
not talking to me.
Yeah, I'm not mentioning that weirdo. So
that's on you if you want to keep
bringing bringing him up. Yeah.
No, it isn't. No, it isn't. I don't know
who it is, but whoever it is, it needs
to they need to get a life.
Whoever is doing it needs to get a
[ __ ] life. That's all I know. Yeah,
you people should get a life in it. Could be.
And I know why they're doing it as well
cuz they think my sister's not going to
come out with me on my birthday. It's
not going to work. He knows about this
community. This some idiot on Instagram
messaging my sister Um
yeah, just some idiot messaging my
sister. That same account that was
stalking me for years, sending a
paragraph trying to rage bait. What a
sad bastard, whoever that is.
I'm still going out for my birthday, so
you're not going to stop that? That's
why I think they've done it. Nope. No
link for you. If you got anything to
say, bro, you can come to London. I'm
not going around in circles with you.
I'm not going around in circles with you, boss.
Well, I'm going out on a Saturday. My
birthday is a Monday, but I'm going for
some food on Monday.
She will go out with me.
But that account is sad.
that person that they've been doing it
for years on Instagram. It's the same profile
and they're proper proper trying to rage
bait as well.
Nope. No catchups. I'm not going around
in circles with you. If you got anything
to say, you can come to London. I was in
your city. You didn't do nothing. End
of. But I ain't going around in circles
of you. Anyways, and you can see how
hard they're trying to rage bait.
If you know what that means. Yo,
it's [ __ ] mental, bro. Really, really is Yeah. Yep. So, yep. Literally,
I had someone message me. Um,
I think it was yesterday before I went to sleep.
This woman from she lives in Scotland,
but she's Canadian. She got my number.
She's [ __ ] stinking, son.
She's like, "Oh, come Scotland. I'm
never coming. I'll never go in Scotland
again. [ __ ] that. She
She's [ __ ] She's [ __ ] stinking, son.
Yeah, she's [ __ ] stinking, son.
Yeah, I do. She's stinking. One second.
show you. Uh even though she's probably
better looking than your Mrs. to be fair.
There we go. Oh, remote.
Why does it not let me?
There we go.
So yeah, she [ __ ] stinking.
Absolutely stinking, Sam.
So I won't go there. He's [ __ ] stinking, son.
No, thank you. Yep.
I don't think so. Yeah.
Nah, I'm all right single, bro. I'm
good. I'm all right. I'm all right single, mate. Really am.
Really am. I'm okay single. Uh,
a woman offers me nothing but sex. I
don't have a high sex drive anymore. So,
I'm good, bro. I'm good. Oh, man.
them tic tacs made me fart. I can't stop farting.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, man. Yeah.
No, obviously not. She's from Reddit. Yeah,
she's from Reddit, mate. The only reason
I'm going out on Saturday cuz it's my uh
two days before my birthday and that
will be it I think.
That's the only reason I'm going or not. Yeah. No. Anyone will do.
Do you remember Joe? It seems anyone will do.
No, it isn't. No.
Well, I've got money to lose,
time to lose by going all the way to [ __ ] Scotland.
[ __ ] that poor game of soldiers. I
[ __ ] ain't going to Scotland ever again. anyone more. Nah.
Ricky's gone quiet, hasn't he, Joe?
Since I put the approaching videos up,
Ricky Millington's gone quiet.
He's gone really quiet, ain't he? Huh?
He's gone awfully quiet.
Starting to get worried
to be honest.
[ __ ] hell, man.
I can't stop laughing at Monty. There
was a comment that I read. I'll read it
out. Yeah, they wrote it to Monty. Yeah. Right. So,
he wrote, "I have one woman and she is
my world. She has been there for me when
I being down to my lowest point in life.
I cannot ask for a better woman. I love
her very much and she is the only one
who I need in my life. She is my everything.
And then the the someone replied,
"Monty, if you're talking about that,
she has moved on from you, mate. Woke up
and smelled the coffee, body, I was
dead. I don't know why that made me laugh. [Laughter]
You know, if I didn't bring body on this community,
he would still have everything in it, Joe. [Laughter]
He would still have everything, wouldn't he?
If I didn't bring him on here, that's
[ __ ] madness, bro. [Laughter]
Oh, that was bad. Yeah,
it's mad why I couldn't move on from
people before because um I could get
better and I did get better.
That's the thing. I I I could get better
and I did get better.
So mine was different than his.
But I don't know, man. Haven't
heard from him. He said it's the way
that I act around women. So, I showed a
couple of approaching videos and
showed where they said they weren't
interested straight away and see what
Ricky thought of that.
I feel really tired, boss.
I'm tired, Joe. Boss,
I'm getting old now. I don't feel like
how I was when I was 25. I'm tired, boss.
really tired of it.
Like I said, I got Saturday all the madness. No,
I don't even use escorts anymore, Joe. I
don't need to, bro. I don't really care
about sex that much.
You get to a certain point where you
just realize it's not worth it trying to
date women. And I was on Reddit. Yeah. Reading
like reasons that people gave up and a
lot of it hit home.
There were some decent subreddits.
I'll read you some of what people said.
I could relate to like a few of the
things they were saying as well.
This person was like, I recognize that
they were never going to work for me
without spending large amount of time. I
have absolutely no desire for her cuz I
don't want to make it obvious how
wealthy I am. Once I left all the apps,
I immediately became so much happier. It
was like I was letting go of something
that simply wasn't meant to be.
That's how I feel. But like obviously with um approaching
so that is true.
This guy ced this guy was 38 yet and
he's like oh
how do I meet women? How do I meet
women? And this guy replied back saying
many of these replies will be people
from the US that don't understand the
date and dynamics are different here.
I'm similar age to you also from UK
people saying you cold you can cold
protest but it's highly difficult here
due to how low trust stranger in society
talking to strangers isn't part of British culture.
Bubble was the answer to me that go
where you you are treated best and are
more and are most attracted to the women
but you still need to learn to cold
approach women that unavoidably wherever you go.
So this guy was like but this doesn't
make sense because he's like yeah I
think this is when I went to USA it was
super easy to chit chat with strangers
everyone was so receptive and open and
you really could start nice chat asking
whoever in the UK or stand office but
it's not true because America's
westernized as well but then the other
guy that replied said so what what are
you going to do mate Poland is only a
Ryan airflight away just saying I don't
know why he's telling him to go Poland though
because that's it's not going to work in Poland. either.
>> Yeah, travel. But the only place that
works is Asia and South America.
I mean, that's weird to say to to
someone go to Poland. Poland's hard.
Hard to get Polish women. Any women are
hard to get that aren't like I've never
been with a Polish.
There's Polish women here.
They are hard.
The hardest is French and Italian.
You got no chance with them.
We have Polish women here. London, for [ __ ] sake.
But it's still a good reply though. He's
telling him to leave, which is good
because I've met many Polish women. Listen,
I'm 28 and have given up hope. If
someone comes along my way, that's
amazing, but I'm done going out there
just to make a damn fool of myself
again. That made me laugh.
And this person said, "How many how many
of you actually approach a woman you you
don't know to ask her out or even for
her contact information? [ __ ] even just
to talk. Well, uh, funny you say that
probably thousands of times,
but there were some good ones.
There were some good replies
like the juice the the the juice aren't
the juice isn't worth the squeeze
and stuff like that
and like it's a lot of time and effort
and money for something that's not um guaranteed.
There were some good replies to be fair
for people that gave up. I could relate
to some of them.
See, mine is I just don't I have nothing
left to prove, though. I've got nothing
left to prove here.
I've been there, done it, won two, so I
tried. It ain't worth it. Um,
yeah, it's just not worth it, is it? Yeah, man.
Yeah, this here's one as well. Haven't
given up yet, but I'm very close. I just
got timed that inconsistency.
You talk to someone who might have
potential. They disappear. You schedule
a date, they end up saying they can't
make it and disappear. That's the most frustrating part.
Yeah, that's the bit I had problems with as well. Yeah.
In general, dating is a waste of time.
It is really. Uh,
so do you like Reddit then? Um, yeah. Somebody replies
A lot of people said they didn't because
they were broke. So money is a lot of a problem with
a lot of people.
I went to the cafe this morning.
So had some piggies. Yeah.
Yeah. And they lie as well.
They're lies as well, Joe. Like a lot of
the things they say they lie about. Yeah, it's true.
Oh, here's one. Oh, man.
life's all about women when you're like
24, 25, 26, but not as you get older. I
couldn't I really couldn't give a [ __ ]
I just said to my mom that like, yeah,
when I go out with my sister, I am
probably going to go and speak to people
cuz why am I going to go out drinking if
I'm not even going to speak to someone?
You know what I mean?
Like, yeah, you can enjoy yourself, go
out drinking and stuff, probably spend a
couple hundred pound, but you got to you
might as well try and speak to someone
in it when you're out drinking
since it's cost so much [ __ ] money, you know? Um
yeah, I've got some pork chop today.
Yeah, I had four slices of bacon, two
sausages, egg, and toast. my fat. I'm
right though, Joe. It um the the Reddit
mod sad, isn't it? Anyone you said that
anyone that has to control the site is
sad, isn't it? Some don't.
Some don't give up fast enough.
A lot of people gave up the same.
Someone said, "I got sick of I got sick
and tired of either drama or heartbreak." Yeah,
this is dating is expensive. If you
spend a lot of money and have low odds,
it's dumb to spend the time and effort and money.
It is true.
Yeah. They ban people. Why?
Well, the one that I showed you in uh
did you see Virgin's boys live stream?
He's still going about is he in [ __ ]
USA? Is he [ __ ] [ __ ] obsessed? I was
watching it yesterday. It's so obsessed.
It doesn't even annoy anyone. It's just
weird. Very very very weird how someone
can be 31, right, and convince
themselves that people ain't had sex
with people to feel better about
themselves. It's quite sad really, isn't
it? You think
a about it?
Why does he care who I've had sex with
or not? It's so weird.
Creepy, isn't it? Like this person on
[ __ ] Instagram is creepy.
At some point you have to save your
heart. It's not an easy decision, but it
can save your whole life. That's true as well.
What? You think I'm going to go all the
way to Scotland for her? [ __ ] that.
If my sister didn't uh agree, I was just
I know who can who can [ __ ] take
someone serious who lied for 10 years
about living in [ __ ] Japan.
Yeah. Like how can anyone take someone
like that seriously
in it? How can you take someone like
that seriously? If my sister wasn't
going to meet me, I probably I probably
would have I probably would have went to
Wales on Saturday to be honest.
Yeah, I probably would have went um Wales.
Do you believe me, Joe?
Yeah, I ain't been Wales for ages, though.
Yeah, that guy.
Why would you believe me? I went to
Wales one Friday, then the next week I
went again. I done it twice.
Uh I can't remember. Was it last year?
Uh about 3 hours?
I done it one Friday,
then I went the next Friday.
Yeah, I did.
Yes, I [ __ ] did. Last year I did it.
Sure was last year.
Didn't even plan. I just went.
No, it isn't. Scotland's [ __ ] far. Scotland's far.
Where would you just go? Where would you
just go? Paddington and then the train's
like an hour and 40. So all in all about
yeah 2 hours and 40 minutes 3 hours
still long enough but no Scotland's far.
That's why I never went back.
That's why I never ever went back. Well,
I've been there twice but I didn't go
back after the second time, you know.
Yeah, it's 5 hours on the train. I've
I've got a train back from there before.
Yeah, but then I've still got to go to
the airport and that. It's just pointless.
I'd rather just jump on the train cuz
even if you fly, it still takes all day
anyways cuz you got to get to the
airport. You got to go earlier. You got
to get through security. You might as
well just jump on the train.
If you go if you if you get a plane
there, it's more
it's more [ __ ] about
cuz I've been I've been there on a plane before.
Now I got a train back. I've got a train
back twice from there.
When I when I was in Newcastle, I went
to Edinburgh. I got a train back from
Edinburgh. Then obviously when I went
the second time, it's [ __ ] long it
was getting back. I remember I fell
asleep and I woke up in Newcastle. I was
like, "Yep, nowhere near home yet." Yeah. No.
Could anyone go like Gatwick and then go
through security? Get it early. It's just
The train is easier. And then from the
airport, you've got to get a tram into
the city center. Anyways,
if you get the train, you just go King's
Cross. Step on, step up.
Remember when I got a plane there, Joe?
I think it was October, wasn't it?
was a little clover.
Yeah, but that's
Yeah, but where in London is that?
It's 4 hours and 40 minutes on the train
and it takes me like 40 minutes to get
to the No. Yeah, it takes like 40
minutes to get to the train station,
which is over 5 hours.
It's [ __ ] long, man.
It's It's 5 hours and a bit more. Yeah,
but I've still got I've still got to go
to King's Cross,
which is like 40 minutes. So,
yeah, it would be about 5 hours.
Yeah, Edinburgh is good for drinking.
I've been to Edinburgh.
Have you been to Edinburgh drinking?
cheap as well. Yeah.
But like I said, Joe, imagine doing that
every week though. Say you went
Edinburgh Friday, Saturday, then Glasggo
Friday, Saturday, Leadeds, Friday,
Saturday, and you kept doing it. Imagine that.
Imagine you done it every week until you
done all the cities. It will take you a
long time, in it.
Yeah, it would take you a long time. Yeah.
Yeah. See, I've been to Edinburgh, but
I've never been to Glasgow.
You haven't been to Birmingham? I bet
you haven't been to Birmingham or not again. Nah.
I've been there like seven times.
No exaggeration. I've been there about
seven times. You've not been to
Nottingham, have you?
You're too old to go there. Just like
I'm too old to go there. Most of the
people is it's like [ __ ] there's a
club called Rock City. I used to go
there. It was all right when I was 24. 24 25.
Too old to go there now. There's like a
Weather Spoons the city center.
So yeah, I have probably been to more
cities than you
if you think about it.
Yeah, if you think about it, mate. Nah,
I have an I80.
Well, maybe the same then.
Maybe the same. I haven't been to
Plymouth though. I haven't been to
Plymouth or anywhere like that. Plymouth. Um, no.
I've never been that like um way the country.
Been to most places though.
Just up Blackpool in Glasgow.
Have you ever been on a night out in
Manchester like the city center? Joseph for
you. Have you ever been like
out in the city center?
Yeah. I used to go like every year
and stay in the um the Ibis in Portland.
Yeah. Do you know the Ibis?
I been Manchester for ages, man.
When was the last time when I uh
the last time was lost? Yeah,
it was before the uh rail card expired, I think.
Yeah. Still didn't get [ __ ] all.
I've never got anything. only that one
time and then the other time I other
times I didn't and I also done Friday
sat I also done Friday Saturday as well
one time there Manchester's good
places did you go clubs did you
Yeah. Have you ever been to Hull?
I might go to Hull on a night out and call um
call Ricky Willington out. That's where he lives
if he actually does live there.
No, I've never been to Holl. Never been there.
Bet you I'd pull there though.
Bet you I [ __ ] would.
[ __ ] deprived there.
I like a weather spoons.
You should go to Waxies. Where should
that uh woman up? Waxies a pub. It's a
pub and it's not just younger people.
It's a nice pub.
Yeah, it's called Waxies. is Irish. Go there.
I go there. Um,
yeah, I met some woman there that was
37. She started sending me nudes. I was
speaking to her on WhatsApp.
Was she 37? Maybe 32, 34. I don't know.
But she was sending me nudes. really wears.
>> That's what's hard to find. Yeah, when
you go to nightclubs, even I'm too old
for nightclubs. So, you got to go like
I like a nice Weather Spoons in central London.
Well, there's good
You should come to London.
We're going for a drink, Joe. Sif. Huh?
So when you went to hole, did you you
got a drink in there? Why not?
I might put um£300 on a both teams to
score on Saturday. Joseph, Kitty,
Minister, and Slow.
Nah, not 300 pound. I do need to do it
again at some point, but I don't want to lose. Maybe 120.
I remember when I put 120 on two teams,
it would turn back 380.
It was a lovely win, mate. Lovely win.
Lovely [ __ ] win, mate.
100 pound on three teams. Yeah, but
I only bet the the Northern League and
the South League loads of goals.
Yeah, that day I went out that Sunday, I
spent some money, bro. And I needed to
[ __ ] win some money back. That's why
I on the football bet and it won. When I
met that Finnish woman,
she [ __ ] me over as well.
100 pound on three teams. You reckon? Nah.
How about £500 on a on a both score? No. Georgia.
Oh, that'd be lovely if it came in, isn't it?
That'd be lovely.
Yeah. Know that would be lovely. I've
had it before when I've done a double uh
both teams to score and they both scored
no draw and I was like, "Fuck, I wish I
had both score no draw on it."
What £100? What for any bet?
What for like any bet?
What about if you done 500? Yeah. 100
pound on like a both score no draw. Yeah.
Maybe I just do £100 on a both score no draw. Double like £700.
What? So you wouldn't put any more on the football?
Yeah, 160 is too much, isn't it? Yeah,
160 is too much.
I remember when I wanted both teams to score last um
one week and then a week after. I think
I've won him three times in a row before.
Yeah, I think one six is too much on a [ __ ]
football in it.
Yeah. Just Yeah. 100 pound. Both score
no draw. That's like 700 return in it.
Slow always both score no draws.
Have you noticed that with SL?
What about 150?
I need to win like 40k, bro. I wish I
could just win like 40 grand.
I wish that time when I went casino, I
won four grand. I wish I won 40 grand. I
wish it was like a 500x.
Uh, how nice would that be?
How nice would that be? 40 grand. Well,
40 or 50 grand
cuz it last me for a very long time. Is it?
I'd be comfortable for a very very very
long time. Imagine just having like 40
grand in cash.
[ __ ] me, bro.
>> They probably give it to you in cash as
well, is it? 40 grand.
>> Yeah, when I won that four grand that
time, I should have played it down to
three grand. See if I could win more,
but I was just happy with the four grand in it.
It's 150 to four grand.
That was bad, is it? Do you remember that?
That was madness, bro.
Nice little 11, eh?
I think they'd give you 40 grand in
cash. Is it?
Would they actually give you in cash? Yep. Yeah, exactly.
I think they would give you 40k in cash.
No, someone I knew he won 17 grand from 140.
Yeah, he won 17.
But he put seven of it back.
Yeah, [ __ ] bad gambler, man.
But I think if you won like 30 grand
online, they wouldn't pay you in it.
I don't think they'd pay you. Do you
believe they pay big amounts online,
Joseph? I don't think they do. No,
I believe these streamers matey.
Do you think Nah,
they probably just shut the site down to
be honest with your [ __ ] money.
You should try that Spin Dog though.
It's a good site, Spin Dog.
I was thinking of playing roulette
yesterday to be fair, but I didn't.
Don't know why. I was getting like a little urge,
but obviously I'm not going to
cuz if I ever play roulette again, it
would just be all my money. It's all or nothing. Simple.
You know what I'm saying? I'll just
stick 500 5600 on it and just try and hit big.
There'll be no 100 pound, 200 pound. No,
I want to hit big.
You know what I'm saying, Joseph? Yeah.
You know what I mean? To try and win as
much as I can. That's what I would do.
Or if you won like 20 30 grand and they
didn't pay you out
or they might pay you out then [ __ ]
shut your account or something.
So, how much was £100 on three? Both
team seems to score pay
maybe 400 maybe. Yeah, but
you say that, but they will do anything
out of getting um they will do anything
to get out of paying people. Look at
that time I went to Nottingham
and they were asking me for stuff to to
take out 350 when I was 200 in. So
you say they've got non issues paying
out but huh they will do anything to try
and get out of paying people even small amounts
but I disagree with that I went nigg
they were trying to get me uh yeah
they're trying to get out paying
tactics they use online they try to get
out of paying so they do they Yeah. So, yeah.
So, what's the most they pay in cash in
casinos? Like 50 grand.
Well, it's not about complying. Why do I
need to show you anything with my name
on it to take out £350?
I don't need to comply. It's £350.
is less than £500.
What I used to do when I was banned, I
used to just go to like I used to just
put the tickets in the machine. As long
as it was like £480, they'd pay it. If
it was over that, then you'd have to
like show them something. For £500,
you'd have to show them something. But
for like £470, you didn't. It was so
weird. I don't know why, but so I just
kept going back and back and back.
kind of miss the casinos, you know,
right land based ones.
I used to love winning in the 50s and
then just [ __ ] go and drink it in it. But
yeah, it was good.
I'm pretty sure I'm banned.
Pretty sure. Yeah.
Yeah. Pretty sure, mate.
Considering they don't even let me in face recognition.
Let's get it.
But to be honest, I probably wouldn't
even bother anyways, you know.
Yeah. But what if it to do with pay me out dojo?
What if I win 30 grand? Then what?
Yeah, I know. I've seen seven neighbors go there. Yeah, but
what about if I want to What about to do
with paying me out? Yeah.
Yeah. Then I'll be [ __ ]
Yeah. And then if they find out I'm bad,
I'm [ __ ] it. Yeah.
Yeah. But then I'll be [ __ ] in it. No.
I I'm pretty sure I am banned. I
wouldn't go to any casino now unless it was abroad.
I wouldn't bother unless I unless I'm in
like Yeah. Unless I'm abroad, I wouldn't
bother. Wouldn't bother.
Remember I went to the Belgium casino.
It was so weird.
So weird that casino.
Do you remember when I went to the
Belgium casino? Jo.
Yeah, there's loads of casinos in Balta.
>> I'd love to win like a four both scar,
but what's the chances of that? Pretty
slim, isn't it?
can happen though it
just need to do like correct score for
two games then I'll be then I'll be loaded
just pick two nil nil games and you've
already you're already winning to start with
think about it
correct score yeah that's that's big money that
That is big money.
Even two of them.
Yeah. The biggest I've got was 75 to1.
That was six teams to win and I won when
I was 19. I didn't even know about
football. I just picked six teams. I
wish I had more on it, Joe. I wish I had
more on it. E,
you want to see my little face? Look at
what t-shirt I'm wearing.
Oh, look at me. Joseph,
I'll get my haircut
in a couple of days. One second.
I'm having a little pain. Shut up,
Mr. Nos. I haven't done anything. What?
Yeah, I had to do a wash. My boxes were
smelling really belly joke. I hadn't
showered for like 3 days and my boxes
were smelling rank. No.
What would make you say that?
W It's cold, bro. It's [ __ ] freezing.
Cold as [ __ ] man. Like cold. No. Oh, [ __ ] Nah.
Nah, that's all. Yeah.
I don't know what to do with life, bro.
It's horrible when you get to this age,
you know? You don't know what to do with your life. Yep. Got it. [Music]
What do you do like in your life, mate?
What do you do?
Oh, it's cold.
It's too cold, man. Yeah,
I walked I don't know. I had a long walk
today, Joseph Bar.
Women are boring, ain't it, Joe?
They're [ __ ] boring.
women quite boring. Jo
need to get a dog.
Yeah, I'll be smarting myself up on
Saturday just to get rejected again.
I'm going to wear the blazer. I'm going
to wear my Rit the Bear um trousers
cuz they'll keep me warm.
But yeah, I'll be getting rejected like
a [ __ ] on Saturday. I'm looking
forward to it, boss.
Yeah, I'm looking forward to it, Joe.
Yeah, looks accent and getting told
about [ __ ] make boyfriends.
Why? Why I don't understand is why they
leave people on
when they they give their number and
then they lead people on. This is what I
don't That's the bit I don't get.
How people defend them
when they do [ __ ] like that.
It's just ridiculous, isn't it? We're
supposed to be
[ __ ] adults here.
You know what I mean? Joseph, for real
to be adult [ __ ] you know?
They lead people on Joe
for their own sick entertainment.
Uh, it's going to be Valentine's
before you know it, Joe. Horrible day.
day Valentine's is.
It's a day to poke fun out of the people
that ain't wanted by nobody.
Let's make fun out of the people that
ain't wanted by nobody.
Isn't that right, Joe? Yeah.
Let's make fun out of the people that
ain't wanteded by nobody. Yeah.
What do you think of that?
Yeah. Yeah. I remember when I went to
leads, I got more matches on the dating
apps in Leeds.
I tell you, I went to Leeds cuz there
was this black guy. He always said, "You
should go to Leeds. You'll pull in
Leads." I went to Leeds. I never pulled.
Never [ __ ] pulled.
They said I poor leads,
but I didn't.
Where you going?
Where you going, Joseph? Anyways, I'm gone. Yeah.