[ __ ] hell, man.
What the [ __ ]
The person is such a [ __ ] ignored
to a lovely um birthday card with 20
pound in it. That's fun.
Oh, the skin virgin ain't even got 20
pound out. Lizzy
nice to wake up to 20
and should be getting 50 as well.
Yeah, should be getting 50, bro.
So that's 70.
Nah, bro. There's no point going on his [ __ ] stream.
Why? What's happened?
Oh, you going to cook some piggies in a minute.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro.
Oh, yeah. I'm going tomorrow. Yeah, to
meet him. I want to [ __ ] him up.
I'm not going on his live stream though.
I'm on here, bro. Can't deal with that.
I can't deal with him.
Well, you only lost 20.
I want a birthday card, Grezy.
Yeah, I want a birthday card. I I went
to the cafe this morning, Grezy. I had some piggies.
I had four piggy. Well, I had four
bacons, two sausages, egg, and some toast. music.
You know, I haven't gambled in ages.
I haven't gambled for like a month. Yeah.
How are you going to lose it? How you
going to lose it? How are you going to pop it?
I need to go to the barbers.
Oh, I need to get a trim, man. Look, I'm
more furry. Look, we look like a little teddy bear.
Yeah. Got my clothes ready for um Saturday.
Should be good.
Yeah. I don't bother responding to the skit version
cuz waste of my time. Yeah. And I'm not
the obsessed one.
I agree with you. I was watching some
Harry Potter before I went to sleep.
Yeah, I was watching some Harry Potter
and it just reminded me of Monty cuz
Monty's on here and he had a fight
with Rice on the same website. I don't
know. It just made me laugh.
Same website you can watch Harry Potter on.
Um just going for some drinks
and then yeah approaching and then that
would be me done. I think probably going
out cuz it's round about on my birthday
You just virgin.
You're a [ __ ] skin virgin, can't you?
Groovy loves me, is in it.
You love me, don't you, Greasy?
Yeah, you did.
Yeah, that person messaging my sister
needs to get a life.
That account's been on it for years now.
You can only imagine how bad their life
is when they're that desperate to try to
[ __ ] rage bait. Isn't it greasy?
It's so sad.
I'm coming off here soon anyways. This community
I'll be off here soon.
This a weirdo community, man.
Every time I keep making a Reddit
account, they just keep logging me out. Grezy,
they need that power, don't they,
Grezy? Them mods need that power because
without that power, they'll go [ __ ]
mad, isn't it? It's all about a power trip
for them. Unlike, you know, Instagram
and YouTube, they don't just ban people, you know.
I'm going to him.
Really? What was he saying?
Let me see.
What was he saying?
I call me a weirdo. Okay.
So, he's just another Ricky Millington.
Nothing new there.
I mean, I mean, think about like this.
Ricky Millington said two years ago that I'm good-looking and um
I'm good-looking and it's the women that are picky.
Then a year and a half later he was
saying that it's not the women, it's me.
So I said which one is it? Is it the
women or is it me? I mean what's changed
in a year and a half? Still haven't
heard from him since I put the
approaching videos up. I still haven't
heard from him. So I don't think we'll
ever know. Boozy.
I don't think we'll ever know if it's me
or the women to be honest. I think it's
the women personally, but you know,
I don't think we'll ever know
cuz he hasn't come back.
He called me a weird uh What's so
I can't I can't find it. But
yeah, it's weird if he has called me a
weirdo. And if someone's got something
to say, they can just say on this
channel, they're not going to get banned, you know.
Why am I a weirdo, man?
I mean, everyone's got their own
opinion. I don't understand why you get
these virgins that sit there and defend
women all day. But if they're happy to
do that, they're happy to do that. They
might be content being virgins and women
not liking them and them having not a
bad word to say about women. That's on
them, bro. Is it? Everyone Everyone has
different lives, don't they?
But I'm coming off this um community soon anyways.
Still simply there. Uh well yeah.
Yep. I'm coming off more than a day.
Something that you can't do.
>> Yeah. Something that you can't do. You
can't come off YouTube, can you, Bubble?
Not even for one day. Not even for one
day. You can't come off of YouTube, can you?
You can't come on YouTube for one bloody
day. Why can't you go off of YouTube for
one bloody day? I got some piggies.
I leave every week. Well, I was off of
YouTube for 9 days. How could I How
could I leave every week?
Yeah, like I said, I'll be out Saturday.
So, I'll be out getting rejected.
The Reddit mods,
they fear different opinions.
They go mad over different opinions. Yeah.
They go mad over people having different opinions.
They buy them to feel powerful.
If you they can ban you grieving and you
can do nothing about it. Nothing.
I'm not saying
but that account messaging there is so
is really really pathetic.
Really really really pathetic. Needs to
get a life.
That's what a lot of people need to do.
Get a life to be honest.
Sat on [ __ ] YouTube all day sad with
their life. Wooding other people that
they don't know. badness,
mate. I can I can meet up with a friend
on Saturday. I've got friends.
Unlike you, LJ, I've got friends.
The reason why I go out a lot by myself
is because I prefer to go out by myself. So, yeah,
I'm going to head out early, but
because I don't want to. Why can't you
take a day off of YouTube?
Why can't you take a day off of YouTube?
You didn't answer my question
to not be able to get get off YouTube
for one day.
I haven't had Peppies in ages. They have
a Peppies in Liverpool Street. It's nice.
Yeah, Pepes is nice.
Yeah, but if you had a life, you
wouldn't like it. But if you had a life,
you wouldn't like it, though. Cuz it's a shitty community
full of like shitty people, bro. If you
had a life, you wouldn't be on here every day.
I want a [ __ ] peppers now.
I just get a whole chicken me. But I
bought some food, so I might as well
just eat the food that I bought. You
know what I mean? I might as well eat
the pork chops cuz they're not going to
be any good.
You got to get off your YouTube. Not
even for one day. You're like [ __ ]
Clint. Not even one day can you get off of YouTube.
Not even one day. Nope.
Monty's not going to beat me, bro. He'll
get smashed up. It's not going to be
like a [ __ ] rice um
thing. He will get [ __ ] up.
Yeah. Did you see Joe's post? Oh,
I can't get one date. I've had more
dates than you've ever had. I've been
with more women than you ever have.
So, you can't get off your YouTube
because you all you have. Anyways, life
experiences don't have to cost a lot of
money and don't have to involve
expensive travel or women. Just look
through this system and count how many
life experiences you have ticked off. I
would suggest most people can tick off
over 15. I suspect you will struggle to
pick off more than three.
Maybe it will sink in soon that there's
more to life than relentlessly pursuing
women and money. to know this list isn't
to troll make fun or anything like that.
Life it's to the point our facts and out
to point out facts and to make you
realize what life experience actually is.
Camping holiday I've never done that.
Caravan holiday I have done that. M
seven nights abroad in the sun. Well
that that costs money. That does
visiting a museum. Done that. Visiting a
zoo. Done that.
Visiting a cathedral, I haven't done
that. The mountain, haven't done that.
Bungee jump, skydive, also cost money.
Um, experience cable car ride, no.
Explore a cave. Nope.
Traveled on a cruise line? No. Rode a
boat? Yes, I have rode a boat. Drove a car?
Nope. Rode a motorbike? Nope. I'd never
ride a motorbike. Read a bike. Read a
book in this in No. Give money or time
to a charity.
Completed a words? No.
Completed a D school puzzle? No. Played
poor nuke against French? Yes, I have
done that. Played a game of darts? Yes,
I have done that. Participated in pub quiz.
No. Own a pet? I have done that. Attend
a life concert? Nope. Attend a live
sporting event? Yes, I have. I mean, if
you cast WWE as a sporting event, I'm
sure it is.
It comes under sport, but no. Play a musical instrument.
No. Write a song. No. Invited and attend
a wedding. Nope.
Wallpaper room. Watch a film at an IMAX.
No. But other than that, meet a famous person.
I've met a few famous people. Well, it
depends what you mean by famous.
Start a business.
I've done five of them things.
But I don't like the sun. No, I get what
you're saying, but if if you wanted to
go to a place, right, like America or
something, it is going to be about money
cuz it costs money. So,
all right, Greg. I was watching Harry
Potter. I was telling you this and it's
when they were kids and they were saying
what they were all sat at the table
saying what they're going to do with
their first paycheck and it reminded me
how dangerous this site is. Why is
little Harry Potter on YouTube when I'm
[ __ ] meeting Monty tomorrow for a fight?
Shouldn't this [ __ ] get monitored?
They always sat down saying what they're
going to do with their first little paycheck.
So innocent, isn't it, YouTube? It's so innocent. Yeah.
What are you going to do with your first
paycheck? Um, I'm going to save it.
That's what they said. Yeah.
Rey, why is little Harry on YouTube? Huh?
I'm getting sent down, mate. Do you
remember who said I'm getting sent down? Oh,
Virgin Boy is going to be so jealous
Saturday. I'm going to I'm going to
dress up nice again.
I'm going to dress up lovely again. He
can't do that cuz his skin
I'm going to be getting the full service
of the barbers.
My hair. Oh my god.
Jesus. Imagine going out like this.
Greasy. I'd look a [ __ ] Wouldn't I
look like the skint virgin?
Like a skint virgin, mate.
So why am I a weirdo here?
I don't know why these people do this
two face [ __ ] Grievy,
I really don't. Yes, sir.
Oh man, that Jane is so boring. That
Jane is so [ __ ] boring. It really,
really is. I don't know how anyone still acknowledges her.
Isn't she so boring? [ __ ] hell.
She's [ __ ] boring, man.
Almost as boring as the [ __ ] skinned
version in a [ __ ] red with no bed in
it, no money in it.
I don't know. I fancy five guys, man.
Yeah, I found five guys.
Well, they're probably closed now.
What time does five guys closed? They've
got to be closed soon know.
How much is it? One sec.
Did get some birthday money, did I? So,
£25 for a [ __ ] meal, bro. For a
burger mill, it's £25. It's ridiculous.
I ain't paying that. That's ridiculous, bro.
I'm not paying it.
Even though I got 20 pound in a card, I
just I'm just not paying that, bro. I
want a burger. I do want a Five Guys
burger, but it's a bit ridiculous, isn't
it? What do you think, Greezy? Should I
pay it? Should I not pay it?
A lot about it, isn't there?
It's a lot of money, bro.
What do you think, Greezy? Should I?
Should I not?
What do you think, Greeny? Should I buy
it? Should I not?
No, it's too expensive, is it? £25.
Well, just want to order something.
Maybe I'll get a coffee again.
No. Fancy five, guys. I can get Burger
King, but Burger King might come cold.
Why is it telling me to log in through
my I'll just get it. [ __ ] it.
I got 20 in the card. I'm getting £50. I
have money. It's just like obviously I
need to save as well.
Nope. I'll never be like you people.
Fancy of five guys. King is coming over.
Um no. So I'm going to get some I'm
going to make some homemade burgers for us.
until he gets confirmation that I'm a
virgin like him.
No, 20 is not all I have. It's what I
got given in a birthday card. Listen properly. Anyways,
virgin boy. He's not going to be happy
until he gets confirmation I'm a virgin
like him, is he?
Everyone's got to be a virgin like him.
Oh, she ain't happy, mate. Is he
There you go. I ordered it. Ordered it.
I have more than £400.
There we go. Ordered it. I put Why not,
mate? Why not?
No. He Why you calling me a weirdo?
Huh? Why are you calling me a weirdo, boss?
Can't wait until Saturday.
I'm going to get wrecked.
I'm going to wear my little Rit the Bear trousers. Bezy,
why am I a weirdo? You
tell me. Why am I a weirdo?
You silly goose.
He's not going to be happy until
He's got confirmation that I'm a virgin like him.
Is he Steven Howard?
Yeah, but Monty, they're not the only
virgins. The people that asked you
about, you know, Natalie, they're not
the only ones that are virgins. Look at
Virgin Boy by
He's a virgin.
He's literally never had it.
Never had it. Never will.
I'm mad at it, Steven. I can't wait for
this five guys. Greasy
since I got given £20
and I'm getting another £50. Why not? H
Why not? In it, Greasy.
Yeah, I only I got bacon, cheese, and
fresh onions. That's all I have on mine.
Sometimes I have jalapenos.
I might have some Dave's Chicken on Saturday. Yeah,
I haven't had Guinness in a long time. Greavves.
Why you asking if I've got £400? I've
got more than £400.
So, I do a football bet for Saturday. Um, Grezy H.
What do you think?
What do you think, Ramsy? H
next month, bro.
Next month. Yeah.
Sick of these bloody women in this country.
Yeah, I was watching Emma Watson um earlier now.
I don't think she's as good as people
make out that she is, but she's got a
really nice voice.
I like her voice, but she's nowhere near
as attractive as people make out she is.
I mean, she has low body, so
she's not anywhere as Do you know what
um people say about Emma watching? Oh,
he looks really, really good. I mean,
yeah, she looks good, but she doesn't
look as good as people are making out.
It's the same thing with Cheryl Cole.
You don't find her attractive. Homo [ __ ] gay.
It's all It's all a trend. And they all
fade fade eventually. They just copy each other.
I mean, yeah, but she's got no body or anything.
What do you think, Grezy?
Yeah, I got 20 pound of this card and
I'm getting £50. So,
fresh start next week. Well, yeah, it's
my birthday in it. So, [ __ ] it. Yeah, man.
Gotten into Five Guys lately.
I think Five Guys is lush.
Do you think Five Guys is lush?
You never had a Five Guys.
All you have to do is go to a bowl and
pick up Five Guys. Get it? You You You
get it? No, I'm only joking. Five Guys
is overrated. Gourmet Burger Kitchen is
better than Five Guys, but Five Guys
does taste like a proper burger, which
is what a burger should taste like. It's
just overpriced and overrated.
Yeah, it's overpriced and overrated,
but it does taste like a proper burger.
So, it still tastes good.
There's nothing worse than going to a
burger place and it tasted like plastic.
Like I said, King's coming later, um,
Reeves, so I might do a little burger video
for you, starring me and King.
He's coming later. So,
yeah, you can [ __ ] off. I'm not joining.
He'll be getting battered tomorrow.
Well, it's not going to be like um
[ __ ] him and R. He's going to get
battered. I want to know why Hugh's
calling me a weirdo. I want to know why
Hugh's calling me a weirdo.
Why am I a weirdo?
What have I done?
What have I done, mate? What have I
[ __ ] done? Huh?
Yeah, he's going to get battered. He's
not going to beat me, bro. He's not
going to beat me. He really, really isn't.
I beat Timmy and Tiger just by myself.
The rice didn't slip. I actually slipped
in that mattress. I actually slipped.
Like Tiger was so weak that even the
punches that he gave, right? He didn't
even bruise me once. Yeah.
Yeah. I could go out with friends if I
wanted to on Saturday, but me and my
sister's been planning for a very very
very very very long time
go out drinking together. So, and
someone else is coming along as well.
And I said, "Don't mind me if I go off
speaking to other people."
That's the only bad thing is they're
going to see me talk. But I don't give a
[ __ ] YOLO. Is it me?
I don't give a [ __ ] mate. Yeah.
Yeah. And after I don't know, man. Maybe
I'll go out the week after cuz I would
have had my haircut in it.
So I'll be look maxing again.
See if we get anything this time.
Hopefully we don't spend £600 this time. [ __ ] sake.
I don't give a [ __ ] how much I spent to
be honest. I mean, it's my birthday, so
Why are you calling me a weirdo? Hugh?
No, I want to know why you're calling me
a weirdo. Dad.
Nope. That [ __ ] stops as you get older.
That's why I don't mind getting this
five guys. I don't give a [ __ ] But
like I said, I got 20 pound in a card. But
it's nice when you win money on your
birthday. I won money last year. Do you
remember when I was betting the number
25 Grezy and I kept winning?
Yeah. [ __ ] it was mad cuz I went out
the Saturday. My birthday was a Sunday.
I should go out on a Sunday but I was
just too [ __ ]
Yeah. Betting the number 25.
We all know why. You know 25th. You'll
be my 25th. Yeah. Why are you calling me
a weirdo anyways?
Yeah. Why am I a weirdo, lad?
And I'm going to go to Dave. Like I
said, I'm going to go to Dave's Chicken as well.
Probably spend a good couple hundred pound.
Yeah, I was just betting the number 25
cuz you'll be my 25th, you know.
>> Nah, I don't believe that. But why are
you calling me a weirdo, Hugh, man?
That's not nice. You don't be a Ricky Millington.
What's the point of being too faced on
the internet, man? You know,
I don't even care if you have said that.
I'm not even going to start. I don't
care, bro. You want to be two-faced?
That's your life in it.
Yeah, I do remember that time. I didn't
have money on it though.
Yeah, I didn't have money on it though, did I?
I might go to leads. Go to Victoria Gate
Casino in Leeds. Uh,
no, I didn't
never got up to 3.3K online. Not
not me. It must be someone else.
No, it wasn't 2.3K. I've never won 2.3K online.
The most I've ever got to online is like £1,500.
Come on, five guys. You still there,
Grezy? I'm still waiting.
I can't wait for this yummy burger. Yeah.
Can I show you the video I was talking about? Um,
I'm going to send you here
if someone's going to get
someone's going to get seriously hurt
tomorrow. And this is the same website.
See, look, that's the same website.
Look, I just sent you it. Imagine
that being a kid. Yeah. And getting a
paycheck up like a [ __ ] million
pound. Imagine that. Could you imagine that, Grezy?
Could you imagine that? Of a million
pound of that age.
I want to know why you're calling me a weirdo. Yeah,
weirdo, lad. I don't need to go in his
live stream. I'll see him tomorrow.
That's all you need to know.
And she's a [ __ ] kid, you [ __ ] nons.
Yeah, but that's Yeah, but what I'm
trying to say, Grevy, that's the same
website, is it not? It's YouTube, though.
You're finding a kid. A babe. Oh, you're a nons. Yeah,
that was a trend though. That Emma
Watson was a trend
because she's got no body. Do you understand?
She's got no body.
So why do so many people like her that
way? She has like no her body's not decent
cuz they're little copycats.
It's just like Virgin Boy that talks
about Sher Cole. The little copycat. Copycat.
He said that she's attractive. He's
copying. He's copying.
He's a little copycat.
Isn't that right, Grezy? He's a little copycat.
Little copycat. You like that little
video of the cat, didn't you? We copy
him. [ __ ] copy him.
[ __ ] copy him. They all cop They all
copy each other.
I mean, she's got a nice voice and you
could fall asleep to her voice.
I mean, we would bang her, but she's
nowhere near as good as what people make
out. Just looks like a dual [ __ ] You
know what I mean?
I already told you
No, she's not bangable in that video.
She's a [ __ ] child, you nuts.
This guy's a [ __ ] pedophile.
What? A [ __ ] 11year-old kid is bangable.
What? She 10. Yeah, 101. Why are you
saying a 10-year-old's bangable? You [ __ ] pedo.
Yeah, but you said she was hot in that
video. In that video, she's a kid. Keep
her away from [ __ ] nonss.
Yeah, keep her away from [ __ ] aunt
legs, mate. Isn't that right, Guzy?
Keep her [ __ ] away from eggs.
She says she doesn't mind meeting for
food and a couple of drinks.
No, I want to go out on a big night out.
I don't want to.
No, no, no, no, no. So, I want to go out properly properly.
That's the thing.
It's my birthday. Bring your little mate, too,
James. I said bring your little mate,
too. Isn't that funny?
I don't want food.
And a [ __ ] couple of drinks, man.
What the [ __ ] I want to be out all night.
You know why I normally go out by
myself, Grezy, is because I don't like
waiting for people. I don't like just I
just like going out and just
you know what I'm saying?
I could get somebody to meet me easily, but
I like waiting around for people.
But I want something that's going to
stay with me all night. And if you're
not going to do that, then
I can probably find someone that will
meet me. Yeah.
The only advantage it has is you're able
to get into more places
so she can stay out with me.
And what can I say?
They have to they'll have to let you in. So,
any any any job, mate. Any job. Any job,
mate. Any job. It's 3 minutes away.
Grezy, I'm looking forward to my tasty burger. Yeah.
I understand you're a bit older now, but
the thing is um
I can't go to Scotland, mate. I can't go
to Scotland. I could go to Scotland, but
it's just [ __ ] long, isn't it?
I don't know, man. I don't know what I'm
doing. I don't want to meet you if
you're only going to stay out with me
for the drinks. I want to be out at
least until like 11:00.
Not till the early hours, but like 11.
Should be here now. waves.
I'm coming, mate.
Is there not anywhere nice you can you
want to eat? Um,
like the steak place,
right? Boss 92. Yeah. >> 92.
But the safe place
Well, I'm going to have to call her in a
minute to see what the [ __ ] we're doing.
You reckon Virgin Boy will meet me?
We can try and get him late.
Oh, the coke is nice and cold. Normally, it's wool.
I'm going to show you. Yeah, that's good.
But the chips ain't called M.
What do you want to do? I don't get what
you want. I'm going to have to call you
in a bit because I need to see what
we're doing now.
24 to 25. I bought a 5,000 of it.
Virgin boy can't do that.
Virgin boy don't have that. Hey, Virgin
boy can't do that.
She was like, "I'll probably stop by the
pub. You can drive me." Oh, yeah. I'm
going to go all the way to Scotland to
join somebody in the pub, aren't I?
>> Yeah. I'm going to go all the way to the [ __ ]
Is there not anywhere nice we can go to
eat like the steak place? Yeah, but I
want to go out drinking as well.
That's the thing.
I want to go out drinking m Really?
If someone told you that they had sexual
arrest, you'd believe it, would you?
I was listening to Virgin Boy and it's
not just about you were saying Izzy.
It's not about
Izzy. You've done this with every woman.
You've done it with escorts. The first
time I told you I had sex with an
escort, you was like, "No, no, no." They
asked for ID. No, no, no.
He He won't be happy until everyone's a
virgin like him in his own head.
Everyone has to be a virgin like this.
He's [ __ ] wild. [ __ ] wild, son.
Why wouldn't you believe
he does not like the fact of anyone having sex?
Cuz he's a virgin. It's so obvious,
isn't it? Not easy or you say easy is
you done it with loads of people.
Oh, cuz you're a virgin. You're a big one. Not bad. >> Yeah,
there's nothing wrong with that. over there. M. Yummy. Amazing. That's lovely.
Well, I hate my sister onions.
I mean like a thing nowadays. Yeah. Now, baby
version of the [ __ ] bed.
My mom's going
to be honest. The chips aren't that bad
music. The worst the worst um chips are off.
They're the worst chips. Yeah. Fancy.
Oh, the chips aren't that bad. They're like big.
I mean, boozy. They're big.
The best chips there is if you go to a steakhouse.
If you go to a proper expensive
steakhouse, they're the best chips
you're going to get.
These chips aren't that bad though.
They're just like mid.
The worst chips is [ __ ] KFC.
The chips are r.
You remember when I used to go and get a
bucket from KFC?
Just a little bucket.
How about we get the ship the virgin? [ __ ] loser.
What a loser.
Well, I'm getting [ __ ] for my birthday. So,
I said to the poop over YouTube cuz you
got the ass weapon.
You [ __ ] loser.
I'm being a [ __ ] So, my sister's going
to take me for some food. My mom's also
taking me for some food.
They're trying to make me big and fat.
I'm already eating a burger.
They're trying to make me big on fat. Oh god. Stop. Stop.
I finished it.
I like the Five Guys milkshake.
I like the peanut butter one. Yeah. Being fat and girlfriend.
So, who's the money off for the fight? Me or
me or um
me or Monty?
Oh, I love banana milkshake. My mom
likes the chocolate one from McDonald's.
I like the banana one. And five, I like
the peanut butter one. Yeah.
Yeah. The peanut butter one's nice.
I'm fine, guys.
Why do you think I win?
I'm a bit confident. Why me?
I think the virgin will come with me and
to me that's a triple threat match. He
might even lose his virginity.
I'm soft, mama. Unst, mama. Unstuck.
When I come back, I'm just going to call my Huh?
I can't stop laughing. They put the
video up on the great guys channel of um
Timmy Aldren's Mike and um
uh Timmy Grezy and they said if you want
to do it dirty we'll go around the
corner. No, just caught me on YouTube.
This can't be.
They put the video back up,
Grezy. They put the video back up.
I'll send you it. I'll send you it. Now,
this can't be right. This can't be
right. Cuz I was watching Harry Potter on this
literally earlier. Like I said, there's
no way this is the same website. It can't be.
This can't be. Go on this [ __ ] website.
Look, there's no way.
I'm going to knock him out. I'm going to
Oh, we're going to knock him out.
Yeah, Monty Monty did go by himself to be fair. That is brave. Yeah.
Do you want trouble or not?
Did you watch it? I'm going to knock him out.
Did you hear that bit crazy?
I'm going to knock him out.
I'm going to watch him. Yeah.
You'll never lose it.
Do you reckon you'll ever lose your V card?
I know a certain person won't.
He doesn't want the link, does he?
>> Oh, he wants to link you. Okay. All
right then. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. I heard
him now. Sorry. I didn't know. Two sec.
I'm [ __ ] knocking virgins out, mate. Yeah.
If you want trouble, we'll go around the corner.
I think that's fake Monty man in it.
Yeah, I think that's fake. Monty, man,
cuz I can't put the I can't hide my
screen anymore. I don't know why, but it
doesn't let me.
Is that you, Monty, that's trying to
join that one? Because I can't hide my
screen, so I don't want anyone p bombing.
Okay. Is it him? Yeah.
Put Put your camera on if it's you. Okay.
No, that's not him.
Show your face if it's you.
Yeah. Show your face if it's you. See,
it's not him. Look,
Monty. Is it you? Okay, okay, okay, okay.
>> You [ __ ] idiot.
>> I can't
I can't hide a screen in it. So, I don't
want you pawn bombing.
>> You're getting your head smashed in tomorrow, PJ.
>> I'm going to knock you out. >> Yeah.
>> No, PJ, you really are getting your ass
smashed in tomorrow.
>> I'm going to knock you out.
>> No, no, no. I swear I'm dead on Lord and
Prim. Yeah, watch your head getting the
fog knocked off your face, you little clown. Yeah.
>> Yeah. We'll see, won't we?
>> No, no. This ain't going to be a rise
fight, you little clown.
>> It's not going to be a rise fight
because I'm going to knock you
>> listen. I'm going to go for the first
first [ __ ] swing. The first swing
bounce back dodge around you. Go bang
again. Watch you going nice, lad. You're going nice.
>> We'll see.
>> Watch me dance circles around you, PJ.
Watch me dance around you like a little
fairy. You are
>> Yeah, we'll see. Yeah,
>> I'm I'm gonna put up a better fight than
Rice. You watch.
>> You're a fairy. You're a [ __ ] fairy.
Better fight. You run up. You run up.
>> I'm And I'm going to wear my little
smart shoes as well. I'm going to wear
my smart shoes and my little Rupet the
Bear trousers. And I'm still going to >> Yeah.
>> Oh, yeah. Okay. Okay.
>> Yeah. I'm going to wear my Rit the Bear
trousers and my smart shoes.
>> I'll still beat you,
>> PJ. You can't even beat yourself. Every
single person you ran off from in a
fight in this community.
>> I beat Timmy. I beat Tiger.
>> Oh my god. Come on. Come on. Come on.
>> Oh my days. Wow. Big you. Big you.
>> Was that Monty? Was that guy that was
One second. Was that guy in your um that
come on your chat talking [ __ ] about me
or was that [ __ ]
>> What you on about?
>> You know that guy you were speaking to?
>> Yeah. So why don't you come over to my
channel and ask him?
I'm asking you cuz I'm not going to
watch your live stream back, am I? I'm
just asking you, did he or not? Simple.
>> I'm not saying [ __ ] if he was or wasn't.
I'm not a snake. If he was, I wasn't.
>> Okay, he was then. So that's it. I'll
show you what I'll be wear. Okay, this
is what I'll be wearing tomorrow. Yeah,
>> he's a [ __ ] freak.
>> I'll show you. Yeah, >> freak.
>> signing up for his funeral tomorrow, boys.
I can't let me what what he has actually
done to my kids. The worst thing
anyone's ever done. And PJ is getting
his head caved into my
>> Right. This is what I'll be wearing.
>> Watch. Two down. Two down. They're going
to get ruined. They're going to get [ __ ] up.
>> My little shoes.
>> Oh, sad.
>> Sad pathetic trousers. >> Yeah.
>> Sad pathetic lad.
>> No, they're not. They're lovely. They
keep me warm in the
>> You're sad. You're you're sad. You're
pathetic. You're you you're only in
Birmingham because we think you're going
on a night out in in Birmingham.
>> I am going on a night out
>> in Birmingham. Yeah. You're going to get
knocked the [ __ ] out for the night out.
Even starts for you, PJ. You're not
going to get
>> That's a load of bollocks.
>> You're not going to get in the club soon
as you got off that train. It's over for you. >> Nah,
>> it's over. Yeah, it's over for you.
He's He's I swear to God as soon as you
>> PJ soon as you go off that train lad
it's over completely.
>> We'll see about that, won't we?
>> Yeah, we will do. We will do.
>> I'm not going to be as easy to beat as Rice.
>> You're going to be pieces peace easy to beat.
>> Nah. Nah.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> You can even beat Timmy Aldridge.
>> Oh my god. TBL just has got a [ __ ]
disabilities. I weren't fighting Timmy,
man. Not a chance. He got He got a punch
and that's it. His game. It was over.
That's it. I felt sorry for Timmy. Tim
did he pull on the floor?
>> No, he didn't go on the floor. No, he didn't.
>> Why not?
>> Why not? Cuz I tapped him. I didn't
really [ __ ] punch him. I give him a tap.
>> That's all.
That's what he said to you though. I'm
going to knock him out. He said he was
pissed off. He was angry. He's got every
right to be got twattied obviously.
>> I'm going to beat you tomorrow on the
same website you can watch Harry Potter
then you'll never come back on this community.
>> Yeah, about that. I think you ped off
watching young kids and putting a link
up of Harry Potter.
>> How How do you work that one out?
>> Cuz they're [ __ ] young kids.
>> Yeah. Do you know when I put it up?
Yeah. Do you know what this guy said? He
said that he said he said the girl's
hot. I said she's 10. You pedo?
>> Yeah, I think you all pedos in this
community to be honest with you.
>> I'm not a pedo.
>> PJ, you're putting [ __ ] young kids up
there like how you put when you were
children. That's [ __ ] weird.
>> So what?
>> So what? That's weird. And then you sit
there and watch cartoons. Probably
Teletubbies. I don't [ __ ] know.
>> Teletubbies. I watch Spongebob Mickey Mouse.
>> We'll let you go then. We'll let you go.
>> Yeah, but I watch on YouTube.
>> Yeah, but I watch on YouTube on it.
>> So, what's coming then, PJ? So, we can
get arranged. It's
>> 3 p.m.
>> 3:00 p.m. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> Are you sure it's not 2:00? No.
>> Nah. 3 p.m.
>> No, I'm sure it's 2:00. Can you get off?
>> I'm going to I'm going to try and bring
legs with me cuz I want to bat both of you.
>> I'm sure you're trying to bring legs for
back up on Do you fancy him by the way?
Do you got a crush on Sha Long Legs?
>> No. He He has a question for me. Have
you seen his live stream?
>> No, no, no. I'm sure I'm sure you would
[ __ ] stick your dick right up.
>> He's the one that goes on about me.
>> Look on his channel. Go on his channel.
>> You go on about each other. You talk
>> No, he goes on about me and I respond to
him. Listen, listen, listen. You're one
of these. You crosses your eyes, your
shy long legs in your head and you just start masturbating. >> No,
>> you're just one of them. Yeah.
>> I I just find it mad how someone could
be 31 and still a virgin.
>> Yeah, I can. I I find it mad that
someone's 28 and still a virgin.
>> But that's not possible though cuz I put a pool.
>> That is possible because look at you.
You can't even pull a woman.
>> You can't You're the one has to cry over hope.
>> Oh, but you're not. is like, "Oh, this
is getting [ __ ] up tomorrow."
>> She is a hoe.
>> He is getting battered tomorrow.
>> Greensby. Keep out for Ginsburg.
>> What's his name? >> Greensby. >> Grimsby,
actually. All right, PJ.
>> Yeah. I'm going to beat you up with my
teddy bear t-shirt.
PJ, you're a pedophile, man. You got
teddy bears on your t-shirt, you nuts.
>> It's actually a brand.
>> Just brush my teeth.
>> You need to brush your teeth. You got black teeth.
>> Oh, I do. PJ, I brush my teeth every day, lad.
>> This woman said if I go to Glad
you try and kiss me, PJ. >> Huh?
Why did you try and kiss me?
>> Stop talking [ __ ]
>> I'm not talking [ __ ] You was at my
house and you stop making up stories.
>> I'm not making up stories. Everybody
seen you pulling me in.
>> Yeah. Okay.
>> Everybody seen you pulling me in.
>> PG. I'm better looking than you.
>> Okay. I'm in a relationship. No, I'm not
>> I am in a relationship.
>> You got split up by Natalie.
>> Me and Natalie are back together. >> Where?
>> He's a big PJ.
>> What? What?
>> I don't need to get off YouTube. Why
don't you get off YouTube, PG? I'm not running off.
>> You're not allowed on YouTube.
>> I am allowed on YouTube. I know.
>> So why did you ask me for a [ __ ] for
a [ __ ] PJ? Why? Why did you give me head?
>> Why did you want to give me a [ __ ]
>> It did happen in in the in the house in
71 in the bedroom.
>> I just had a Five Guys candy, man.
>> A lovely Five Guys.
>> PJ. PJ, why did you send me a video as
well of yourself getting a [ __ ]
>> Cuz it was hot. >> What?
>> It was lovely.
>> No, it went lovely. And why have you got
such a small
>> And why have you Why have you got such a small dick?
>> I got a bigger dick than you.
>> I doubt that very much. PJ, have you not
seen my picture? Have you not seen my
>> The burger place can be.
>> I don't think he's seen my picture, has he?
I don't. No, I don't want to see your
[ __ ] little dick. Thank you.
>> Okay, PJ.
>> No, listen. Okay, PJ.
>> He had it, didn't it?
>> PJ gay. Yeah. Yeah, he is gay. He's gay.
>> She's She's never um never gave you a
[ __ ] Why is that?
>> Oh, PJ, listen.
I've had a [ __ ] blow job off now.
They're not going to give me a [ __ ] You [ __ ]
>> He's never gave me a [ __ ]
>> You're weird. You're a weirdo, PJ.
You've never had a
>> getting into this argument with him,
man. This is just getting sexual. What?
Why is every argument turning sexual
with you, PJ?
>> One second. Hold on.
Brush my teeth. You need to brush your
>> No. Well, why does every argument turn
sexual with you?
>> I think you and non need to get laid.
>> See what I mean? You got non in your mind again.
>> You know, why do you not say anything
live about me for 3 hours?
>> Cuz you and Sean masturbate over each
other. You talk about each other daily.
>> It's like you got I met him through you.
>> It's like you got this love relationship
going on with you and Sean. I don't know what the
>> he didn't make no Sean for me.
>> Yeah, I [ __ ] did.
>> Did you? [ __ ] Sean can even vouch for
that himself and he doesn't even like me. >> Yeah,
even he can even fit.
PJ, why did you want bum sex with me as well? >> Huh?
>> Why did you want bum sex with me as well?
>> Uh, fine.
>> No, no, no.
>> Why you making up stories?
>> I'm not making up stories. I had to
That's why you had to get get you out of
the house quick time, man. >> Making
stories. You know I'm not making stories
PJ me then you wanted to make you or you
wanted to b me or something
>> make up stories
>> I don't need to make up stories you know it's true
to lose their virginity first on sex
>> obviously me you [ __ ] but go on Pierre
>> why did you why did you want to bum me
>> stop making up floors
>> I'm not Baking up stories.
>> Yes. Yes. PJ is David UK.
>> Is it?
>> Why you going to let David UK up?
>> Yeah. One second. Is it? Are you sure?
>> Yes. Yes. What's happening, lads?
>> Just chilling. How are you?
>> Yeah, not too bad. Not too bad.
>> So, um, Dave, who do you think's going
to win the fight tomorrow? Me and Mont.
>> Well, where are you meeting? Are you
actually going to meet for a fight?
>> Well, so you're going to Birmingham
tomorrow on the train to meet Monty for a fight.
>> Yeah. Well, I'm going to go on a night
out as well.
>> Well, in all fairness, uh, judging by
Mongo's last performance, I I'm going to
have to give him the upper hand.
Okay. And what if I win?
>> Well, if you win, then I'll I'll give
you credit. I'll be like, "Yeah, fair
play. You kick Mongo's ass." I'll be lush.
>> The only reason I joined Hold on. Uh, >> yeah.
>> Did you lean in for a kiss with mommy?
>> No, that's a made up story.
>> It did. It did.
>> Story. Okay. Throw your kids then.
>> He wanted to b me as well.
>> Exactly. You can't throw his kids life.
He's a liar, man. I'm not lying about
[ __ ] You know what happens?
>> I'm such a liar, man. Why are you lying about
>> Why are you gay? Yeah.
>> I don't know why he's
>> [ __ ] off, man. You wanted to give me a
bl Yeah. You wanted to kiss me in the pub. Yeah.
>> Oh my god. You wanted to give me a kiss
in the whole thing. You wanted
>> the thing here that gets me PJ is I
>> That doesn't sound like something Monty
would be lying about.
>> I'm not lying PJ. You're not
>> Doesn't sound like you're That's why I
had to join us cuz if if Monty's saying
you've leaned in for a kiss with him on
a night out like I do kind of >> lying.
I'm not lying.
The video's up there anyways, so you
don't have to lie about it.
So why so why did so why did you want to
kiss me anyway, PJ?
>> So what did you do when uh PJ leaned in
for this kiss?
>> Push him where?
>> Why are you making up gay stuff? That's
not true, buddy. That's what makes me
think you're gay to even make up stuff like that.
>> Okay, tell him to swear in these kids
life. It happened then. He's gone. [ __ ]
>> I swear on my [ __ ] kids, man. It happened.
>> It happened. I just
>> The video's there, PJ. The video's
cruising. You pulled me in through the
case. Yeah. We went back to my place cuz
I felt nothing by that. Yeah. And then
you was asking me to give me a blow job
and I said, "Fuck off."
>> You know, when he was asking you to give
him blow, was this after the kiss? When
>> we went back, you asked if we could get
an escort and I said I didn't have
enough money cuz I bought the wrong bank card.
>> No, you wanted to give me You wanted to
give me a
If that's true then, if that's true, why
when I come back you was talking to me
normally then? If I wanted to give you a
[ __ ] and I tried to kiss you, I'm
pretty sure you wouldn't be talking to
me normally. You're a liar. Why do you
lie about stupid gay stuff?
>> I'm not lying. It actually
>> So why did you ask me to spin
your kids life?
>> PJ, you're just abandoned.
>> Exactly. Cuz you're a liar.
>> Yeah, you can't throw in your kids life
cuz you're lying.
I'm not lying.
>> You know what happened? You know what
happened? I said he was upstairs in my
bedroom. I was sat on the bed. You sat on that.
>> You can't You can't swear his kids life,
baby, cuz he's lying.
>> In all fairness, PJ, he doesn't really
have any kids to lives to swear on.
>> I've got more kids than what you got, David.
>> Look, it's not a competition on who has
the most kids. I've got more kids than
you, David. What the [ __ ]
I'm not trying to hear I'm not trying to
be here and have more kids than people.
>> What the [ __ ]
>> That doesn't even make sense. It
>> doesn't make sense.
>> Why David? That doesn't make sense, does it?
>> It doesn't. It doesn't.
>> Well, we're meeting anyway.
>> We're meeting anyway.
>> We are meeting. Yeah.
>> Right. So, tomorrow you're obviously
>> either meeting for a fight or for some sex.
>> It's only one of two outcomes.
>> Like, I don't know who's who's going to
>> who's going to move in for a kiss or
who's going to throw the first punch. I
guess that's what it depends on.
>> I'm going to be throwing the first punch either way.
>> Yeah, but what if you catch the first
kiss instead? What if PJ kisses you
before you can punch him?
No, definitely not going to be falling
in love either. Well, you can [ __ ] in
love with him and he kisses you.
>> But what if he's a really good kisser
and you do fall in love with him?
>> He's got a small dick. Well, we Well, go for
a two second [ __ ] Not worth it.
>> [ __ ] hell. done.
>> I pulled more than you, Barry. I pulled
more than you.
>> Barry, one second. One second. Yeah. One
>> Yeah. See you tomorrow.
>> See you tomorrow. Yeah. Barry, can I ask
you something? You said this is why PJ
can't pull because he's so childish. Um,
it's embarrassing. Um, did you not watch
the approaching videos
that you Why do people seem to dismiss
things that you put up?
Um, did you watch the approaching videos?
Cuz you said that I was childish and I
assume that you you watch my videos.
No, no, no, no, no. You said this is why
PJ can't pull because he's so childish. It's embarrassing,
right? Did you watch the approaching
videos that weren't childish that were
completely normal? I rest my case. Like
I said, everyone's got different lives.
I'm not here to convince you anything.
If you want to be a virgin all your life
and stick up for women and live in
fantasy land, that's your life. I don't
tell people how to live their life. You
know, some some people are, you know, um
some people are um just that way
inclined, you know, they don't have
women. Women don't like them. They're
virgin. And they'll still stick up for
women. Some people are content with that
life. I'm not telling people how to live
their life, but I wouldn't like to live
that life personally, but you know,
cuz this is what I always say that I
have no reason to lie. I've been with
loads of women. I've had sex and I don't
agree with what they do. I don't agree
with it and I will never ever stick up for them.
So, but these people seem to, which I'd
say a lot of these people have had less
women than me. Not all of them, a lot of them.
So, you're dismissing my struggles
again. Good luck to you, bro. That's all
I can say is good luck to you.
See where defending women gets you all
your life. Sticking up for women.
[ __ ] madness. Absolute madness.
And then we got someone calling me an
incel. Yeah, I've had more women than
they have. So, how does that make sense?
You'd actually call me a misogynist. I'm
actually more closer to a misogynist
than an incel cuz I've had more [ __ ]
women than that skint virgin will ever
have. But yeah, he calls me an incel.
What can you do, bro? One of them things.
come to Scotland.
It's your birthday, so we can go extra
hard. I'll get us a hotel room.
That's very tempting.
But the thing is Yeah.
Yeah. I'm the problem, lad. Well, my
approaching videos say otherwise.
My approaching video my approaching uh
my approaching videos say otherwise. Sorry.
But I just wanted to go with Joe's uh channel, right? Uh
you you harassing a woman that called
you out. Your approaching video show you
I mean my approaching video show me say
one say a sentence to someone
and they say they're not interested straight away.
That's what some of them approach videos show.
But that's what I was This guy was like,
"PJ, women are so picky." Also, PJ, this
woman who messaged me is stinking. My
lad, you're going to be single to your
50 at this rate. I mean, there's a big
difference between somebody not getting
with somebody because they're [ __ ]
stinking and then women not getting with
somebody that's average looking.
I mean, there's a big difference.
There's a big big big big difference
there. So, again, you don't have a valid point
because there's a difference between
that's that's not being picky. If you do
not get with somebody that's stinking,
that's having standards. They have unrealistic standards.
You know, you could call me picky if,
for example, I didn't want to get with
somebody that's average looking, then I
would be picky. Then I would be
completely picky. Or if somebody was
blonde, you know, there's a big big big big difference,
you know, between being picky and then,
you know, just having some sort of
standard. So, yeah, big difference. Yeah, madness. Madness.
But like I said, you can continue
sticking up for women all your life. See
where that gets you. It's your life.
this guy said I gave up on dating. Yeah.
I mean, I could go to Scotland and do some approaches,
but then obviously I can't approach
in front of them. That's the problem.
This woman wants to um meet me in
Scotland. She's a bit stinking though,
Jay Willow. But that's not me being
picky. That's the difference. That
comment's wrong. That's not me being
picky. Me being picky is if I didn't
want to get with somebody that's blonde
and not brunette. There's a fine line
between not getting with somebody that's
a bit stinking and cuz I'm not stinking.
I'm I'm normal looking. I think
everybody could agree that I'm normal
looking. So if I looks max and I dress
my best and smell my best and a woman
doesn't give me a chance, that is picky.
That is unrealistic standards.
Do you not understand?
If I was fat, ugly, wasn't groomed, then
it wouldn't be picky.
You understand? There's a there's a
difference there. There's a big
difference between unrealistic standards
and you know someone being p and then
you know what I mean and someone just
not wanting to get with someone that's like that.
So it's not the same as women. Do you
understand Jay Willow? It's not the same
as women. So if I go out when I go out
Saturday um my birthday is Monday. I'm
going out Saturday and I go out and
obviously I'm going to look my best. I'm
going to go to the barbers. If I don't
get a date out of any of them numbers,
yes, them women are picky. They've got unrealistic standards.
Big difference between me not getting
with a fat person. There's a big difference.
So, no, there's a big big big big difference there. Big difference.
These women literally have unrealistic expectations.
I haven't heard from Ricky Jay Willow.
And do I care? Jay Willow, not really.
But people need to stop saying that
it's, you know, personality and [ __ ]
like this when my videos prove that's not true.
It proves it ain't true.
That's But I don't care anymore, bro.
You know what I'm saying? Um, but
I don't care anymore, bro. Really don't
These people are going to look back in
years, Jay Willow,
and they see they would have seen it got
them nowhere defending women.
It's mad. I don't know why they do it.
Obviously, it's their life. They can do
what they want, but [ __ ] really is.
And you can't say that they don't like
my looks, Sho, because objectively I'm average.
So objectively I'm average. So
objectively you're not ugly. No one can
say that you're ugly. Really? They they can't.
Just like if a woman was like
objectively above average looking.
I'm below average. I'm definitely
definitely not below average
and no one cares what you think. I'm
definitely definitely definitely not
below average and nobody would tell me
that apart from people on comm community
on this community that's below average themsel.
So I'm definitely definitely definitely
100% not below average. Not just a
hater. I don't expect somebody to say
that I'm good-looking. I don't want
people to say that I'm good-looking. But
if you're trying to say that I'm not at
least average, you're a hater because
there's no way I'm below average looking.
You're probably below No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no. It's not the truth,
though. Yeah, but it's not the truth
because you're trying to say that I'm
below average, brother. I'm not below average looking.
You're below average looking. I'm not
saying that I'm [ __ ] good-looking,
but I'm average looking. And for you to
say I'm not I'm not even average
looking. Well, not even average. No,
that's projecting. That is you
projecting. I don't want you to say that
I'm good-look, but I'm telling you're
trying to tell me I'm below average,
below normal looking. No, that's yourself.
That is literally yourself.
You must be looking at yourself, bro.
Okay, come on. Come on right now and show yourself.
Right. Come on. Come on here right now
and show show the way that you look.
Come on here and show the way that you look.
I'm below average looking. This isn't
This isn't even me gone to the barbers
yet. No, I don't think I'm below average
looking, mate. I think I look completely
fine. Well, I'm actually hairy at the
minute. I need to go to the barbers.
Yeah, I need to go to the barbers, bro.
Jeez, but below average. Really?
Nah, bro. That's you projecting.
That's That is That is projecting 100.
That 100% is projecting.
Do I look like a three, four out of 10? Really? Really, bro?
And you're and and and you're saying
that's the truth? Really, bro?
This is me. Oh, I don't want to put my
channel out there. Really, bro?
This is literally me, bro, when I've
groomed and you're telling me I'm below average.
This is me when I've looked maxed.
Really, bro? Below average looking. Really?
Really, bro? This is what I'll be
looking like Saturday again.
Yeah, I'm about four. Really, bro?
Really? I don't think so, man. Self projecting. Oh,
that is defo self projecting, bro. Cuz
the thing is, right, we've seen what a
lot of you people look like when you've
put your cameras on.
When you've put your cameras on, right,
we've seen what you people look like.
a lot of you people that's been talking
[ __ ] about people's looks over the years,
you know? We've seen a lot of you people
and then it came to make sense why you
talk about other people's looks, you know.
It's because you people are ugly
yourselves and that's what it is.
You put people down because you are the
ones that are fat and ugly. It's the
truth though. It's not even me being
like but her. It is true. Look at Bomb.
Look at Pat Mustard. Look at uh Graycat,
you know. Look at there. There's been
other people as well. And every single
one that's been talking about that's
been talking [ __ ] about people's looks
for years were all fat and ugly.
Am I lying? There's been a few people.
So, the fact that you're saying that I'm
not even average looking, that is
insane. That That is projecting.
That is projecting. Considering I'm
probably the best looking on this
community as well.
That is insane, bro.
Below average. Really?
Yeah. That's self projecting.
That is really really self projecting, bro.
I'm a four way.
I'm not the best looking guy in this
community. Well, why don't you come on
and show your face?
But all we we all know, right, that this
is self projecting. Even Dave UK, I'm
better looking than him when I try. So,
who's better looking than me on this community?
I mean, you people can't even show your
faces. That's why you try to put other
people down about their looks. It's cuz
you people are fat and ugly. It's the
truth. You're fat and ugly yourselves.
Um, and then that's why you try to talk
[ __ ] about the way other people look.
So, it's just self projecting,
you know? That's all it is. It is self projecting
because I'm better looking than all of
you people on here. That's why you will
not show your faces. When you've been
asked multiple times to show your face,
you will not show your face cuz you are
below average looking, you know.
That's what it is. Use or below average looking yourselves.
And it's a waste of time, bro. Cuz
you're never going to make me feel bad
about my looks.
So there's no point
there's no point trying.
You know, we all know that what you
people look like. Fat, ugly.
You know, and I'm better looking than
Davy UK as well, and I've got better
teeth than him as well. So, who who's
better looking than me on this
community, bro? Who? Monty's not. Virgin
boy is not. You're not. That's why you
can't show your face. Dave UK definitely isn't.
So, who's better looking than me on this
community? L J isn't madness.
community, bro? Cuz Dave is not better
looking than me. Virgin boy is not look
better looking than me. Monty's not
better looking than me. Lodger is not
Shag is not better looking than me. Who's better?
LJ is not better looking than me. You
must have [ __ ] in your eyes. Nope. Lj is
definitely not better looking than me.
So yeah, you can say someone's average looking
or they're nothing special. But for you
to say that someone's below, yeah, that
is you being a hater. That is you self
projecting to the maximum.
Nope. Seaside Mark's not better looking
than me at all. And he's old. L's not
better looking than me. He's bald, fat,
ginger, and he's got four eyes.
And nope, seaside Mark's not better
looking than me either.
No one on this community is better
looking than me, even if they're the
same as me. So again,
you being a self, that's you self projecting. So yeah.
Yeah, that is definitely self projecting.
I could look like Brad Pitt and you'd
still be [ __ ] hating. Jesus Christ. Oh yeah,
Mark isn't better looking than me. And
LJ isn't better looking than me either.
Loj is [ __ ] ugly. Yeah.
below average looking. That's hilarious, bro.
But then you look at what you people
look like and then we'll realize why
you're saying that
cuz you're trying to bring other people
down to your level.
Ugly, fat, no life. Like you think I
don't realize that this is this is a low life community.
It is a low life community. I'm coming
off here soon anyways.
So, and I really really am. Yep.
Yeah, I'm definitely not above average looking.
But the thing is, you're probably uglier than me.
So again, you're not above average
looking. That's why you're trying to
bring me down.
Bro, all of this looks is you just
projecting your insecurities onto me.
And I'm not in I don't even know why I'm
having this conversation. I don't really
give a [ __ ] We all know that anyone
that's talking [ __ ] about my looks, I'm
better looking than them. So that just
dro that just makes the whole thing just sound silly. So
this is all ugly people trying to bring
you down, bro. It's the same with this
[ __ ] And it's not even just about
looks. It's could be with anything as well.
You tell people they've got no money.
They've shown you money multiple times.
I don't show money anymore because it's
just a waste of time, you know.
Yeah. You get 10 out of 10 birds again.
Fantasy world. Fantasy world. What about
all the women I have been with that I
kiss, slept with? What about all the
dates I did get?
I mean, yeah, I think I can't get a date
now because these women have got
unrealistic standards. Nothing to do
with me being ugly.
So, doesn't matter where they're now. It
doesn't matter where they are now.
You didn't bring them up, did you? No. Oh, [ __ ]
Who cares? Who cares? I'm stuck.
What's up, bro?
What size trainers are you? I'm I used
to be 10, but I think I'm nine and a half now. turn.
Yeah. You need to get a job. You need to
What do you think of my approaches,
Candy Man? Ever since I've put them up, [ __ ] um
ever since I put them up, Ricky
Millington's gone quiet.
Can't believe Sausage Roll says that I'm
below average looking. I'm not below
average looking, you little projector.
Yeah, he's gone quiet since I put them
approaches up. Sandy,
you said that it was how I was acting.
So, okay, let me put some approaching
videos up. And then he's he's gone
quiet. You think he's okay? I hope he
hasn't been murdered or anything.
He's gone quiet since I put them
approaching videos up.
Candy, what do you reckon is going to
happen when I go out Saturday
approaching on the drink?
Do you reckon I'm going to pull?
What do you think's going to happen?
This is my birthday Monday, so
I thought give it a little whirl. What
do you think?
What do you think's going to happen?
No, I'm meeting him tomorrow. I'm not
meeting him um Saturday. I'm not going
to hear I've got a boyfriend, am I?
Did you like the approaching videos?
Did you like the approaching videos that
I put up? Ricky Millington's gone quiet.
He said it was how I was acting and stuff.
I was acting normal in them approaches,
but they said they weren't interested. Candy H.
Makes you wonder, doesn't it?
Makes you wonder what's the hope in
actually finding someone. Hey, Candy. H.
What do you think the problem is, Candy?
Dating apps don't work for me. I try to
speak to someone and they pretend they got boyfriends.
And I think I look fairly normal and I
act fairly normal in these approaches.
What do you think?
It seems a bit strange, doesn't it?
Because people on Reddit say I'm going
to meet someone and stuff,
but then when I try to speak to someone,
they say they have a boyfriend,
so I'm not so sure. What do you think?
No, they've all got bloody boyfriends.
Mr. B, did you watch my approaching
videos? They're not bloody interested. H
What do you think?
They're just not interested in this country.
I need to get I'm coming off anyways.
Where did it make sense?