money. Yo,
Monty, why are you talking about your
mom would [ __ ] make you go out and
fight? Yeah, if that was you. You
couldn't even beat Timmy Eldridge, you
weak little man. Shut the [ __ ] up.
Yeah, you couldn't even beat Timmy
Eldridge. You weakling. I beat [ __ ]
Timmy and Tiger. You know
about your [ __ ]
mom would have made you fight. You can't
fight. You're a weakling. The only
person you've ever [ __ ] beat was [ __ ] Rice.
Yeah. A [ __ ] [ __ ] You couldn't
even beat Timmy Eldridge.
Stop talking [ __ ] right? You could have
easily come to London yesterday, but you
didn't. So, shut up.
I seen that Hugh guy talking [ __ ] about
me, but I really don't give a [ __ ] to be honest.
I mean, it's nothing new, is it? Snakes
on this community.
It's not the first time and it won't be
the last time. Tom, let's let's be real here. Yeah.
And he was he was chatting [ __ ] to Monty as well.
Yeah. Didn't bother at all. I told him
he can come to London. I'm not wasting
my time and money anymore.
He he could have easily come to London.
I'm not doing this go round and round in
circles. I said clearly if somebody
gives me £500, I will go. Simple. Make
it worth my time. If not, I'm not doing
it. Simple. You could even beat Timmy
[ __ ] Eldridge. You let Mike get in
your face and you done absolutely
nothing to [ __ ] about it. So why
don't you stop going on like you're
[ __ ] hard cuz you're not.
I said if someone gives me500 pound I'll go. Yeah. Simple. [Music]
Stop bro. Nah, bro. Could be bothered.
Monty is a [ __ ] Monty is a [ __ ]
because I said for him to come to London
and he wouldn't do it. Monty is a [ __ ]
He's a proper [ __ ]
Okay. He is a [ __ ]
Proper proper [ __ ]
I said to one of you, if you give me 500 pound,
other than that, I'm I'm not going.
So, yeah. And I see that Hugh talk [ __ ]
about me as well. Just another keyboard warrior snake.
Nothing new there, is there?
I cannot show and start calling them
out. Well, I can cuz I am and I just
did. So, I can do what I want. So, yeah.
Do you know what I might do, Mr. B? I
might play the money game again with
these people. See who can beat me. You
know what I mean, Mr. B? I might play it
again and see who can beat me. I was
thinking about it. I just woke up. I
made myself a tea, bro. And I was like,
"Yeah, let's start it like I want to
give it a little bit more time." You
know what I'm saying? Because the thing
is, Mr. B, you got to think about it
like this, bro. Yeah. It's not what you
show, it's how long you can show it for.
Think about it, Mr. Be. Am I lying? Am I
not lying? I mean, you've you've shown
the same amount of money, right,
for the longest time possible. It was
always the same amount of money, was it
not? You always had that because that
was what you could show. Cuz that's like
just money you had. So, you're not going
to you're not going to dip into it, are
you, Mr. B? Do you understand?
You see, it's how much you can show,
you know, in in three months time
and that's that, you know, cuz let's
just say, for example, you won 20 grand.
You're not going to have 20 grand in 3
months, are you?
You know, I think that's that's the big
thing with it. Yeah.
That's it, bro.
Let's see if Virgin Boy can show that
[ __ ] 14 grand when I show money
again. Let's see if that if he can still
show that same 14 grand. I'll be like,
"Okay, fair." But you're not going to be
able to, are you? Cuz that's your dad's
money that you had to suck his dick for.
For three years. You had to suck his
dick for three years to be able to um
show that money. And you're not going to
be able to show it again.
Do you understand me? Listen to me.
You been getting any new gums lately? I
need to get some new jeans, bro. £135.
Then I'll probably buy some new trainers.
Oh, it's [ __ ] expensive, is it, bro? GS
has to be done though. E,
[ __ ] hell. Has to be done.
If they're not Ammani jeans, I'm not
wearing them. So, that's that's just me, is it?
Oh, that's another thing he used to be
very obsessed with. Um, if somebody wore
brands cuz he couldn't afford it. He'd
be very, very obsessed with people wearing logos.
Very, very obsessed. He didn't like
people wearing things he couldn't afford himself.
That was weird.
Yeah. Let's see if he can show that 14
grand. When I show money again, I'll get
some 50s out the bank. Let's see if he
can um Let's see if he can show that
same 14 grand.
Yeah, man. No, I know. I know, bro. I'm
just saying, is it? But don't It's not
about how much you It's how much you get
and and what you already have, you know?
It's what you already um
It's what you already have and stuff and
I don't have loads and loads of money. I
have enough money, but I don't I mean I
don't [ __ ] I don't buy clothes
anymore to be honest. I really really
don't. Them days are done. I've still
got my Stone Islands and stuff, but if I
am to buy new clothes again, it has to
be a money jeans. I know my size. They
last for like it's a good investment.
They last for two two and a half years.
I had my them them jeans was £110 and
they last me two and a half years. So I
think they were good investment.
Two and a half years is a [ __ ] good investment, mate.
And trust me, I wore Primark jeans
before. When I went when I was back at
the old house, I didn't have a lot of
money um cuz I was starting off. I wore
these Primark gray jeans. Well, all my
clothes was at my mom's and I wasn't
speaking to my mom. So, I wore like
Primark jeans and then they ripped. So,
110 135 they're worth the investment, you know.
They are definitely worth the investment.
So, I can't wait to go out today, man.
I'm going to send it like mad.
Yeah. Let's see if he can show that
money. Okay, that's cool, bro. Let's see
if you can show the money when I show
money again. Then if you can still show
the same amount of money,
then I'll rate that in it. But if you
can go on holiday and you can show the
same amount of money, then yeah, okay,
that's that's pretty good. If you have
exactly the same amount of money, but if
you can't, then you know,
so like I said, it depends what you
have. See me, I showed 5.7 grand, had
more life experiences than him, was
going out every day, had designer
clothes, was getting three grand a
month. So, at the end of the day, it
it all depends on what you get and what
you already have. Yeah. So,
no, no, no, no, no, no. When I showed
5.7 grand, none of you people showed me
11 grand in all of that year. No, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. You
changed the rules. One second. I showed
5.7 grand and none of you was able to
double it for over [ __ ] a year. So, no.
Right. This woman is like I think she's
trying to [ __ ] with me. This woman, bro, one second.
She's saying that going to
she says meet me in Glasgow tomorrow.
Going to book the Rison Blue
and check in is 3:00. I'll meet you at
the cocktail bar after I'll take you to
St. Jude's after dark.
Nah, this is [ __ ]
There's no way, bro. woman.
Uh there's no way a woman is going to
meet you that fast, bro. I've been
speaking to her for a couple of days.
I don't think this woman, bro, I can't I
can't trust this. I ain't I'm not going
all the way to [ __ ] Glasgow.
There's There's no way. There's no way,
bro. Even though she's thinking what
you're just going to meet me cuz
basically, right, her friend
basically her friend, right? I'm fairly
confident that she's not genuine, but
she could be genuine. So, if she is
genuine, we're [ __ ] Basically,
not really [ __ ] but you know, but
because her friend said, "Oh, I don't
like the things that you've been saying
online." And then she blocked me and all
of a sudden she blocked me. Surely her
friend would have told her about me.
There's no way this woman is just going
to meet me in less than a week.
like I I'm not stupid, you know? I might
be a lot of things, but I'm not stupid.
But that would But even say, for
example, you you did go all the way to
Scotland, then she didn't meet you. I
mean, you could just go on a night out
anyways. So, it wouldn't really But it
is Scotland's far. So, but like I mean,
I've had it before when I went to
Nottingham. This woman was supposed to
meet me. She never I just went on a
night out. So,
but um and she says she's booked this hotel.
I don't think so, bro.
I really, really, really don't think so.
Especially from Canada.
I don't think this [ __ ]
woman is is legit, Mr. Lee. Cuz no one
just would just meet you like that, you know.
There's no way. Absolutely no way.
See, if I was like a bit younger, I
would have went to Scotland tomorrow.
I'm not [ __ ] doing that [ __ ] I've
already been all over the country. I
don't and I know this [ __ ] has tr
there. And then she's going to be like,
"Ah, I made you go there and I'm not there.
But then if she's not trolling then [ __ ]
people going to say, "Oh, I waste your
time and stuff." You know,
let me ask her to prove she's booked it. One second.
But I still won't be going anyways
tomorrow because I'm meeting my sister
and I've got stuff to do tomorrow.
Well, Mr. B, I got a nice football bet here.
I've got a both score no draw. Swindon
versus Colchester and Knox County versus Cambridge.
Got a nice one, bro.
Got a nice Yeah, I put 50 on the
roulette yesterday. got it to 150 on the global roulette.
So, and I put I had 20 pound in the
card, so I just put on a football bet.
See, what I was originally going to do,
I was going to put 150 on two teams on
the Northern League and the South
League, but I um what happened was um
the them leagues weren't playing. And
then when I got the 50 to 150, I
thought, well, I might as well just take
it and then just do a smaller football bet.
Don't mind me playing next week. So, I'm
going to get wrecked tomorrow, bro.
Already got my haircut,
so got my nice clothes. I'm going to get
wrecked tomorrow, bro. I'm going to send
it [ __ ] hard. Like I said, it'll
probably be my last time. It'll probably
be my last time going out, to be fair.
So, make the most of it.
Nice steakhouse today.
I can't wait, bro.
My sister's taking me for some food. Woo!
Can't wait, bro. I really can't wait. I
never had someone take me for a steak
before. It was always [ __ ] me taking them.
I can't wait. Yeah, I've got my Rit the bear.
Hey, we don't need your negativity in
our chat, mate.
You know. Yeah, but I'm going out cuz
it's like a birthday thing, isn't it?
So, it's my birthday in a couple of days.
I won some money. So, I won some money
the past couple of months. So, I've got
nothing to lose. That's what I said to
Adman. And I said, I've got nothing to
lose. I planned going out with my sister
and I've got nothing to lose. So, you know,
if like I said, if it wasn't for my
birthday and do you know the thing is
it's so mad is that you don't know how
much money I gave the barber yesterday,
bro. It's so expensive. Like just
grooming, grooming, drinking. It's It is
generally, bro, a [ __ ] mug's game.
Like I said, if I was a virgin, like non
legs, then I would do it every day, you know?
Yeah, it's not going to work. But I'm
going out anyways.
Yeah, I know, bro. But I'm going out
anyways cuz I plan to go out with my
sister. So, I've got nothing to lose by
going out. I've saved some money as
well. I've won a bit of money. It's
added up, but I've got nothing to lose. So,
What? Yeah. I've said to her, can you
prove you booked the hotel?
So, what you want me to go all the way
to Glasgow in hopes this woman's going
to meet me? Bro, I'm not stupid. I
wasn't born yesterday.
I've got a bad feeling about this.
I'm not stupid, bro. I don't think a
woman's just going to meet me in less
than a week,
you know? Yeah. Okay. She might be a bit
stinking, but it just the whole thing
doesn't add up because her friend
stopped talking to me because of the
things I was saying online. Then all of
a sudden, she's messaged me. She's got
an Irish number, but now she says that
she lives in Scotland. I'm not stupid, bro.
So, I'll go with my gut feeling. But
like I said, even if I went to Scotland,
you know, even if I went to Scotland,
you know, I could still go on a night
out there anyways, but I wouldn't be
going to Scotland.
Yeah, it does. 100%. 100%, bro. Because
her friend stopped talking to me because
of things that I was saying like about
women and stuff, right? So then she's
messaging me saying, "Oh, stop it. It's
took a long time
um to like get in touch with you and
stuff." But nah, it doesn't seem right. It's dodgy.
It's dodge cuz how have you I'm not
stupid, bro. Really? Really not. How
have you moved from [ __ ] Ireland to
Scotland? If if it's true, you can show
me that you've booked the hotel.
So there's no way, bro. No woman is just
going to meet you like that.
Unless you're in [ __ ] Thailand,
put it that way. So
there'll probably be a case where you go
there, but then it's stupid because if
you did go there and then they didn't
show up, then you would just have fun anyways,
wouldn't you not? And you So you started
off in Ireland.
I just I just don't believe it. I don't
I don't know, but I've got a funny
feeling about it.
Obviously, if she can show the proof of
the booking, then
if she um
I don't need to take the risk. I'm busy tomorrow.
I'm busy tomorrow, bro.
If I wasn't,
then maybe I would go.
I'd probably go to Glasgow and Edinburgh
and then just stay there for two days
because then I'd have nothing to lose. So,
but I'm busy tomorrow. I've got plans.
So, um yeah, I can't [ __ ]
go, you know,
she's gone quiet.
She's gone as quiet as Ricky Millington. Yep.
I can't even go on Reddit anymore. Every
time I try and make an account, they
just log me out.
They need that power, Candy, man.
Without that power, the mods are nothing.
But the people that tried to say women don't have
it easy when it comes to dating are just
[ __ ] idiots to be honest. Of course
they have it easy.
Of course they have it [ __ ] easy.
Unless you approach, you're never going
to get a date.
I mean, just think of that, bro.
And also another thing that someone said
made a lot of sense. They were like,
"Listen, right, if you if you put if you
put if you put time, listen, listen. If
you say for example, you go on a date,
right, with someone and then you pay
money, like say you pay for the date and
stuff and you've worked so hard getting
this date, this is also a good point. If
the person doesn't meet you again,
you've basically lost all of that [ __ ]
that you've put into it, they lose
nothing." That's also a very, very good
point. Like say for example, right?
Okay, I'll give you an example. Say I
went out approaching, right? And I was
texting a person for a week. You know, I
approached them, I had to ri them up, I
had to text them, I had to spend money
on the date. I lose all of that if it
doesn't go anywhere. They lose nothing. So
like there's no
I'm saying they that that was also
that's a very good point.
That is a very very very very very good point. So yeah,
and also that the excuse that oh they
only find men that would have sex with
them is [ __ ]
because they would have more chance of
finding a partner if they have more
options than somebody that doesn't have any options. So
you know what I mean, bro?
100% though. 100%.
She's gone quiet after I've asked her to um
show to booking. Yes.
But like I said, if I was if I was the
31y old virgin, then yeah, like I said,
I would approach.
This doesn't seem worth it, does it? Money,
time, effort just to get a date.
It's not worth it, man. Bang. Bang.
Why would I Because what what would I
have to lose?
Because obviously if I get sex and I can
go and try in Scotland, what have I got
to lose? Nothing.
Spending a couple of hundred pound, I've
got nothing to lose, do I? So
that's the way I see it.
But yeah, she's gone quiet since I've
asked her to show the booking.
What do you think of it? AQ bins. It's a
bit dodgy in it. Come on. It's a bit dodgy, mate.
No, it's my birthday on the 27th
because they're not interested in
London. It doesn't matter what they look like.
So, look, I'm going to go out tomorrow.
I'm going to go for this meal. I'm going
to go drinking with my sister. Then
obviously when they leave then I'm just
going to be out all night and you will
see how bad the dating game is. I've
looked smacked. I'm groomed. I've got my
nice clothes to wear tomorrow. My Rupit
the Bear trousers,
my blazer and stuff. So you're going to
see a nice after shave and also you're
going to see
how [ __ ] hard it is to just even get a date.
So yeah, I don't know why that H was
talking [ __ ] about me on Monty's
making stuff up.
Hey, stop making excuses for women,
candy man. Me now, the white knights and
simps, they don't bother me. I don't
care about them
cuz everyone has a different life, you
know? It's like I was saying to you
uh yesterday, if people just sit
and defend women and make excuses for
them all their life, let them let them
crack on. They might be happy with that.
They might be happy with being virgins
and sticking up for women, you know?
That's that's them. It's like Ricky
Millington. He was talking [ __ ] about
me. I showed him a couple of approaches
that proved my point
and he went quiet.
I don't give a [ __ ] what people think,
bro. Who cares what people think? Even
Even if people agree with me. It's not
going to change anything, is it?
Ricky Millington got shown black and
white evidence and he's still shaking
his head like, "Nah, nah." Like, bro, come on.
Let them let them defend women all their life, bro.
See where that gets them, you know? Who cares? Oh, yeah.
Probably. Yeah. So, you think it's
definitely a setup, Candy, man?
100%. Well, I don't understand why you
would just message me someone just to
[ __ ] with them, though.
There's no way. You're just You've just
booked a hotel for us and there's just
no way, bro. There's no way.
Um, so yeah.
It is a setup in it, bro.
It's got to be
Well, I don't just approach women during
the day. I approach women in bars and
clubs on the street.
I mean, I don't know how people say
dating apps work when you can't even get
a date from these dating apps, but
that's another thing, isn't it? If I
didn't approach, I'd be a virgin. I'd be
like nons if I didn't approach.
See, these simps are really stupid. you
know, these white knights and and these
simps because if they stop doing what
they do, then these women wouldn't think
they're better than people and then pe,
you know, more people would actually get
in relationships and actually get laid. But because
they um because they um like white
knight and simp, that's what makes them
think they're better than they are.
So, it's actually the simps problems and
the white and and simps problems and the white knights, but
also it is social media as well because
it gives scared men a platform to have a voice
because they they wouldn't speak to a
woman in real life. They're [ __ ] scared.
They're [ __ ] scared of women. But
online, they can say what they like, you know,
and they make them think they're better
than they actually are.
So, it's it's really the white knights,
simps. You get them in clubs, too. You
get white knights in clubs as well. It's
not just online.
Right. She showed me that she's booked it.
She has booked. It says she has booked it.
Booking.com. Thanks, Amelia.
No, no, no, no. Disagreeing with my
approach. No, no, no, no, no, no. People
can agree with my approaches, cannot
agree with them, but it shows that women
don't go for personality. It shows that
everything people are saying is [ __ ]
when people put up messages and the
women have clearly led me on. If you're
ignoring black and white evidence, then
you're a white knight. simple is there's
there's no two ways about it.
So these people that are saying, "Oh,
uh, yeah, it's not women, it's not
women." Well, I've put up approaches
where I've tried speaking to people and
they've said they're not interested
straight away. There's various different
messages I put up. So yeah, the fact
that you still you're defending them
constantly, you kind of are a white
knight because what could get more than
black and white evidence? Nothing.
There's women that clearly led me on in
their messages. So that that is a white night
cuz you have disagreed with everything.
So it's like there's there's no way they
could have been right every single time.
Even if I was wrong in sometimes. So
yeah, my No, no, no. The reason I put
them approaches back up is because Ricky
was saying it's about how I'm acting
around the women. So, I I showed them
ones where I would not even be able to
finish my sentence and they would say
they're not interested.
Uh, there's nothing wrong with that, but
it proves they don't go for personality.
It proves they don't give you the
chance, you know, that's that's what it
is. It's not about uh, you know, whether
they've got stuff going on in their life
or not. It proves that they don't give
you a chance. They don't have to, but it
proves it. Like that's instead of making
excuses for them, you should say
something like that. I've heard and and
also Candyman, they do make excuses for
them. Like you know that woman that
said, "Oh, she was going to meet me."
Then 3 hours before, oh, I'm getting
with I'm going back with my ex. They'll
make excuses for them like, "Oh, they've
changed their mind." They haven't
changed their mind. They done it on
purpose. It's obvious. They leave people
on. They're not babies. They know what they're doing. So,
but again, there's no point of this
conversation because whatever you're
shown, you're going to you're still
going to disagree. So, there's there's
no point of the the conversation.
People can show you black and white
evidence and you'd still shake your head
like a dog and not believe it. So,
there's there's no point in the whole thing. Anyways,
back to this. Thanks, Amelia. Your
booking in Glasgow is confirmed.
Bro, I've put approaches up that you've
clearly dismissed. So, there's no point
in this conversation.
You dismiss any evidence people show
you. So, is there a point in this conversation?
You've shown black and day black and
white evidence. Sorry, night and day.
Black and white evidence of women
leading me on and you still shake your
head. Bro, there's nothing anyone else
can show you. If you don't want to
believe it, that's on you.
So that's that's it. I've shown you
messages. You didn't believe it. I
showed you approaches. You didn't
believe it. Oh well, bro. That's your
problem, not mine. Thanks, Ailia. Your
booking is in Glasgow is confirmed. The
Rison Blue Hotel is expecting you on
25th. Your payment will be handled by,
hold on, will be handled by
Rison Blue. The payment section below
has more details. You can cancel for
free until the 25th.
Nah, I still don't trust this, bro.
I just don't I I just see it as dodgy,
bro. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
know. I think it's dodge.
I think it's dodgy.
Well, how else am I supposed to think
someone's trying to meet me?
Uh, one second. One second. One second.
One, bro. Listen, I'm not having this
conversation with you. You know, stop
making excuses for them. No one puts a
gun to their head and makes them give
their numbers and lead people on. Once
you give somebody your number and you're
still leading someone on, there's no
excuse for that. So, no. If you give
your number and you, bro, there's no
point in this conversation cuz you're
always going to defend them. So, I don't
know why we're still having this conversation.
Giving you a number and isn't leading
you on. Uh, did you go on the messages
that I put up?
Okay, you might have not seen the video
where I put messages up. They haven't
given your number and they haven't led
me on. Right, you might need to go back
on the video because there were clearly
more than three of them women leading me
on. Am I lying, Candyman?
And the only reason I'm not [ __ ] go,
well, I'm busy tomorrow. I want to meet
this woman. Is because I still don't
trust it. You spoke to me for less than
a week. What I was supposed to think
that you're you're just going to meet me
just like that. Like, nah.
And also, they have led me on. If you
have actually gone on the messages,
which you dismissed, you would see where
they've led me on. So,
but you're going to dismiss everything
you're showing anyways cuz Yeah.
She said, "Does this work for you? I can
change it if need be."
What do you think about this whole
thing, Candy? Man,
so a woman speaking to you, agreeing to
meet you, still wanting to meet you on
the day, and then 3 hours before saying,
"Oh, actually, I'm going to try with my
ex." That's not leading you on, though.
that that's not doing it on purpose. Are
women that have literally agreed to meet
you and suddenly backed out. That's
that's not leading someone on. No. No.
Yeah. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And And
you're right about them ones. Yes. Yes.
Yes. Yes. Yes. You're right about them
ones. The ones that didn't reply didn't
lead me on. They didn't. No. I I I agree
with you. The ones that didn't reply,
there could be reasons for that. They
might have just gave their number to get
away from you or they were drunk. Yes, I
agree with you. So, you think I'm always
right, but I'm not. Yes. The ones that
gave their number and didn't reply. Yes.
Yes. Yes. But there was ones that did
reply and there was ones that did lead
me on. Again, ones that you seem to
dismiss because they didn't suit your
narrative, which were the last ones. The
ones that you're talking about are ones
right at the end, mate. The one about
all the other ones where they're clearly
leading you on, you know, that is
leading you on. And I assure you, I'm
very, very grown up. Um, and that
doesn't make a difference whether I'm
grown up or not grown up. They were
clearly leading me on. I don't know why
we're still having this conversation.
Like, I don't care. What the [ __ ]
They're old numbers. Jesus. No, I'm out
today, Jay Willow.
I'm out today.
I got my haircut yesterday because I
wanted to get out the way cuz of um
you know, Saturday like it might took
like 2 hours to get my haircut by the
time I wait and get my haircut. So, I
thought whilst I was near the place
yesterday, I just get it done.
And I got my football bet.
There isn't many where they replied.
There isn't many when when where they
replied yes there is most of them
yes anyways there's no point trying to
trying to change your mind you you argue
with black and white evidence that's
your problem you know I don't know what
you want anyone to say
because most of them definitely
definitely didn't ignore me because when
I was with Monty and I got three numbers
they literally all replied so yeah there
was a lot of them that ignored of me,
but there was a lot of them that replied
back and led me on. It's I don't know
how you could argue with the fact that
they led me on.
It's It's It seems It's like It doesn't
suit you, does it? Like, do you know
what I mean?
Yeah. And you all And what about the
ones that agreed to meet me and then suddenly disappeared?
What about the ones that write wrote a
nice message and then bro I don't even
know why I'm wasting my time on this.
You're just going to continuously keep
defending them and I don't care about
it. It's your problem.
It is literally your problem. Man, do
you know what I was going to put up? I
was going to put up Yeah. where they
only reply to negativity, but why would
I do that? That's a waste of my time.
You just miss anything that you're shown anyways.
any evidence that you're shown of any
bad that they do, you dismiss it and
shake your head. So, I don't give a
[ __ ] bro. I really don't care.
Well, yeah. And what what I showed you
was women leading me on.
Yeah. I I showed you women leading me
on. Yeah. Yeah. 80% of them women was
leading me on. Yeah. That's what I
showed you. I can tell I can tell you
every conversation in their messages.
But anyways, I don't care, bro. You
think what you want to think.
I don't care. You argue with black and
white evidence. That's on you, bro.
Right. Listen, Jay Willow. Right. Right.
Right. Right. Right. Right. Okay. So,
one second, bro. Alls I say is women owe
you absolutely nothing. Women don't men
don't owe women nothing either. Right.
Jay Willow. Men don't owe women anything
either. Now again, you're using that in
the in the incorrect um term, right?
When a woman does something shitty,
saying that they don't owe you anything,
don't justify it. It's like the most
pathetic way to justify a shitty thing
that they do that, oh, they don't owe
you anything. Oh, they can lead you on
because they don't owe you anything.
They can ghost because they don't owe
you anything. Bro, it doesn't wash. It's
used in the wrong context. And again,
we've never ever heard a man doesn't owe
a woman anything. So,
at the end of the day, bro, like it's
just because you can't justify them
doing something shitty by saying that
they don't owe you anything.
It doesn't wash.
It's boring. Now, come up with a new
argument. It's very, very boring. You
know, use it in the wrong use it in the right context.
Right? But we're not talking about men.
And we're talking about women, so stick
to the subject, right? Men don't owe
them anything. But they seem to think
that men owe them [ __ ] money and
[ __ ] [ __ ] like that, you know?
So again, I've shown you clear as day
proof that they've led me on and we're
still we're still in an argument. I
don't understand what the [ __ ] So
no, it's not my narrative. You're trying
to sit there and say women don't owe you
anything even though they've led me on
and you're trying to justify it by
saying oh they don't owe you anything.
What's that got to do with a woman do
leading you on? You know what the [ __ ]
Stop trying to get out of it by saying
men do the same thing.
Well, they do have a vendetta against
me. Bro, listen. I'm not having this
conversation. You ignore everything
you're shown. That's your problem. It's
not my problem. What is the whole point
of this conversation? People show you
that what they do and you still argue with it.
So there's no point of the whole
conversation. Why are we going back and
forth? You've shown you've seen where
they've led me on and you you shake your
head like a dog. That's your problem,
bro. I'm not here to convince you
anything. I know what they've done. I've
shown you what they've done. Believe it,
don't believe it. I'm not asked. I'm
generally generally not asked. But that
whole women don't owe you anything is
such a lame attempt to justify any
shitty thing that they do. Literally any
shitty thing that they do. Any shitty
thing that they do. Oh, they don't owe
you anything. Oh, they don't owe you
What the [ __ ] And I also explained
right that um
Yeah, but it's not about whether it's
not about whether both sexes do it.
Yeah, but that's not the point. The point is,
stop trying to justify their shitty
actions by saying, "Oh, they don't owe
you anything. Oh, they don't owe you
anything." Because it's it's lame. It's
boring. You know, and why is it always
Okay, let me ask you. Let me ask you
this question, J. Why is it only used
when a woman does something shitty? Let
me Okay, let's let's talk about both
sexes. Okay. Okay. You want to talk
about both sexes, then? Okay. Let's talk
about both sexes. So why is it then
every time a woman does something
shitty, somebody jumps on the bandwagon
and says, "Oh, women don't owe you
anything. Women don't owe you anything."
But then when a man does it, we never
hear about a man not owing anyone
anything. You want to talk about both
sexes? Yeah. Okay, fine.
Go on. Why? Okay. Why is it that when a
woman does something shitty, she doesn't
owe you anything? But when a man does
it, oh, he's a dick.
He's He's the problem, not you. Come on,
let's talk about both sexes
since she wanted to clearly bring it up.
Why is it that when a man doesn't want
to go down on a woman, he's gay, but
when a woman doesn't want to go down on
a man, she just her preference.
Why is it that a woman can try to meet
you within a f in the first message?
Yes, personal experience. Tries to meet
you straight away without even getting
to know anything about you. USA is he
right? Okay. Gone, gone, gone, gone.
Right. But then if you want to try to
meet a woman within a week, oh, you're
meeting her too fast. Oh, you're meeting
her too fast. You don't know her. Answer
these questions. Okay? You want to talk
about both sexes? Let's let's talk about
it. Come on. So
yeah, but now now you're okay. Now
you're changing the subject now. Now
you're now you're now you're twisting
things, right? You said that we're
talking about both sexes. So can you
answer me it then? You know,
you know what I mean?
Can you um can you answer that?
Why are we never told that a man doesn't
know you anything? Why can't Why can a
woman try and meet a man straight away,
but a man can't try and meet a woman straight away? Huh?
Go on. No. See, you can't answer me. So,
you can't answer me. You can't answer me
at all. So,
no. I don't care about them sending the
food flu. a few flirty texts. I'm saying
that they're leading people on.
And I'm I'm not biased, Dave. Willow.
I'm not biased. I don't give a [ __ ]
I've had women. I've had sex. I have no
reason to lie. Excuse me. Hiccups. I've
got no reason to be biased. I I told you
my my honest opinion on that video would
be if I was watching it. Did you not
hear what I said? I would have said
that. Yeah, there's numbers that didn't
reply. Right? Maybe they didn't really
want to give you their number. Maybe
they were drunk. Whatever. They didn't
reply. That's that. That's not a
problem. But I would have said that
there's people that obviously led you
on. There's no denying that. There's
literally no denying that they led you
on. A lot of them people via them texts
and they done it on purpose. Yes. That's
an unbiased opinion if I watch that video.
So, and I'm not a virgin. You know what
I'm saying? I have no reason to um
to sit there and and say [ __ ] I don't
I don't believe, you know? So,
I'm not a virgin. I don't need to hate
on people for no reason. For what, bro?
I just don't understand how you can
blatantly defend everything that they
do. I I don't get it, bro.
Is it autism? Like honestly, Jam,
obviously I know you're not a virgin. I
know you probably have kids or whatever.
I wouldn't say you're a virgin, but are
you sure you ain't got some kind of autism, bro?
Cuz it isn't. It isn't normal. It really ain't normal.
No, it's not about letting it go. That's
not Oh my god. Nobody cares. It was
showing you what I've been through with
these [ __ ] for [ __ ] years.
They've they've blatantly led me on on
purpose. Why are you denying that?
And you still haven't answered the
double the double standards thing,
you know? It's madness. You trying to
say that they haven't led me on is
mental, bro. Is mental cuz they have and
they done it on purpose. And the thing
is what you don't understand Jay Willow,
let me tell you something, my man is,
you know, when you go out and you get
these numbers, the amount of effort that
you have to put in, the amount of money
you have to spend, the the amount of
[ __ ] that you have to go through, they
don't have to go through any of that
[ __ ] when someone goes them.
Do you understand?
Yeah. She showed I thought it was a bit
dodge and I asked her to show the
booking and then she showed the booking.
Your booking in Glasgow is confirmed.
The payment will be handled. So, she has
to pay when she's there. But
I can't go tomorrow. Even if I wanted to
go tomorrow cuz I've I've got plans.
I still think it's dodgy though, mate. I
still think it's dodge because
I don't know why somebody would want to
meet you that quickly.
Yeah, it's a bit dodge that in it.
Oh, [ __ ] man.
So, yeah. And also they don't have to um
they don't have to like go out and spend
money. You know when I when I met that
um that Finnish woman, right?
You know how much I spent?
I spent hundreds, bro. And then to get
numbers that you know, you're in every
right to be pissed off. You've got every
right to be pissed off, you know, to be
honest. the effort, the money that goes
into it just to get led on. I think I'm
very much in my rights to be pissed off.
And that's the thing. You say that this
is um a thing, right? 90 99% of men
would just move on after being ignored,
but just can't let go. Actually, they
wouldn't. If you had to put the time and
money that I put in, actually, you would
kind of be pissed off.
And how do I know this? Cuz I've got life experience.
Why do you think I didn't go out for
over a month since the last time?
I was just like, nah, [ __ ] that. 10
numbers, all that money, all that time,
all that effort, and not a single day.
[ __ ] that, bro. That's why I was so put
off of, you know, going out out again.
So, you know, I think you underestimate
you actually have to put effort into
this [ __ ] You have to put money into
this [ __ ] They don't have to do any of that stuff.
What What What's your opinion on it,
Slim Cognito? Again, you can agree with
me, you can disagree with me. I'm not really asked,
you know? I'm not going to block
somebody that agrees or disagrees, but I
just don't understand how these women
how these people can sit there and deny
the fact that
these women have led me on in their messages
and they try to justify it with they
don't owe you anything. I just it it's
it's [ __ ] mad.
So yeah, if you put the time, effort,
and money into it, then you would be
pissed off. It's not like women. They
don't have to put effort into anything.
They can just jump on a dating app and
get simps. Message them. They don't have
to put no effort. They don't need to
make the first move. They don't need to take risks.
It's very disgusting if you think about
it. That's why it's best to not think
about it. You know, it's best not to
think about how the dating game is
rigged against men because it's like
it's really just better off just not
thinking about it
because it's it is it is [ __ ] It is
I don't agree with any of it and I'm not
a virgin and I've been with women. I
have no reason to defend them when
they're wrong. So yeah,
but the thing is No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no. So yes, it's always
been easier for them, but at least when
you actually put effort into it, you
used to get something out of it back in
the day. You know, women didn't have
unrealistic standards like they do now.
And you know, at the end of the day,
back in the day, women could only get
with men that approached them. They
couldn't afford to be picky.
Yeah. And even though, Slim, I show
these people that they've led me on and
stuff, they still deny it. I show them
black and white evidence and they still deny it.
So, and they just make excuses for them,
saying, "Oh, they changed their mind."
No, no, no. But yeah, it was but they
could they could only get they could
only get who approached them before
social media cuz at least when you
actually spoke to a woman, you would
actually get something. You'd actually
get given a chance. Now you can
approach, you can spend money, you can
look your best, and you still won't get
fuckle. Just like tomorrow, I'll get
[ __ ] I won't get no date for next week.
I will not get nothing.
Just like the last time I went out, I got nothing.
So for you to sit there and say, "Oh, I
shouldn't be [ __ ] pissed off because
someone's led me on and ghosted me."
Well, yeah, I should. I spent a lot of
money the last time I went out. So,
it's always been easy for them, but
now it's just [ __ ] impossible to even
try and get find someone cuz now they've
got unrealistic standards. So
yeah, I find just put it this way, Slim,
if I was gay, do you think people would
be making this amount these amount of
excuses for men? You know,
do you really think they'd be making
these amount excuses for men that men
don't owe me anything and men like they
would literally be chasing men with an
axe? But because it's a woman, so I
think that tells you it's very genderbased,
you know, that's the thing. So that's,
you know, I I listed a bunch of double
standards to Jay Willow and he couldn't
answer them. He wanted to talk about men.
And I said, "Okay, well," I gave him
some examples and then he didn't answer after that. So yeah.
So yeah, man.
And then what if you wanted kids, which
I've never wanted kids, you'd have to
keep repeating this process
after that getting the 10 numbers and
not a date. And one replied, I was
depressed for like two weeks.
So why why wouldn't you be pissed off?
You've put effort in. You've put money
in. You've got somebody that's agreed to
meet you. Agreed to meet you. But oh,
that's okay cuz they don't owe you anything. Madness. mad.
You know, it's it is [ __ ] up.
I generally think a woman could murder
someone and they'd get away with it.
Well, they do get Well, they do get
lesser sentences than men when they murder someone.
Did you know that? They actually do. Yeah. So,
you want to see her? This is her.
She's booked a hotel. So yeah,
so that's the thing, you know,
you are telling people they shouldn't be
depressed after that, spending that
money, putting effort in. Yeah,
but they shouldn't be pissed off. Why
shouldn't you be pissed off? You have
every right to be pissed off, you know?
There's a few times if I didn't win
money back, I would have been [ __ ] So yeah,
but women, they can just go on dating
apps and pick any man they want and
still claim they can't find anyone.
Yeah, it's madness, isn't it?
Life as a woman life as a woman is easy.
You don't have to approach. You don't
have to do anything. You just get the
men come to you.
How mad is that?
And like I said, if you get a date with
someone and it don't go anywhere, you've
lost everything. They lose nothing.
You've lost the time, the effort, the
money, the making the first move. You
lose everything. They don't lose anything.
That's also good. um
um analogy to be fair.
It's like you have you have to you have
to um take risks
that could like [ __ ] up your self-esteem
and mental health. That's bad. Mad.
Yeah. But it isn't though because before
social media, if you approached a woman,
you would find someone. there'd be no
problems though. It's like you put the
effort in but then you'd get something.
Now you can put time, money, effort in
and you still won't get anything. That's
what the problem is. I don't think the
problem is that it's harder. I think the
problem is that even when you put money,
effort, and time in, you still won't get anything.
That's the whole that's the whole thing
about it. That's the [ __ ] up thing So,
but yeah, before social media, of
course, it was still easier for them.
But if no one approached them, they'd be [ __ ] So,
how would I know what, bro? Because I
was around in 2009. Because there was
Well, it's common sense. There was no
social media, so women couldn't be picky.
They'd only have to pick men that
approached them, unless they approached,
which they wouldn't be able to.
So, I mean, it's it's common sense. No,
what the [ __ ] It's common sense. I
mean, it's even changed in the past 3 years. So,
but yeah, as a man, you have to put
money in, time, look your best, risk
getting [ __ ] over,
you know, it's madness. It is. It is
really really bad.
That's why it's a it's a mugs game.
That's why you should just stick to
escorts or leave the country cuz it's
just a mugs game.
So complete and a mugs game. Yeah. But
it wasn't Facebook that was a problem
though. But it Yeah. But Facebook I only
heard about Facebook in 2009.
Everyone here started hearing about it
in like 2009. Even though it was made in
2004, people didn't know about it back in 2004.
I didn't People I know they didn't know
about it until 2008, 2009.
And it wasn't It's not Facebook that's
the problem. It's Instagram,
it's the dating apps, and now it's Tik
Tok. If you eliminated all of them
things, you wouldn't have half these
problems. Even if they even if they left Facebook, um
you took them apps away, you would
notice the difference.
You would notice a big difference.
Facebook isn't isn't the problem.
You know, it'd be a lot harder for
people to find people and, you know, and
and inbox them and stuff. It It's a lot
It would have been a lot harder.
I had chance to have sex when I was 16,
bro. No, not 16, 15.
Yeah, I've had I had chances to have sex
then when I was younger. But I was just too nervous.
And Facebook was around then.
But who knows, bro? Maybe.
Cuz think about it, right? This is the
way I see it. If there was none of this
social media [ __ ] you go and you speak
to a woman and
it will feel like she would have to
choose you because who else is she going
to choose? No simps. She won't be able
to approach men because she'd be scared.
So you that's the way I see it. Maybe
I'm wrong. Maybe maybe it isn't like
that. But all I know is it's disgusting
nowadays. Very very disgusting. Cuz
these women moan that they can't find
somebody to be in a relationship with.
They can get sex whenever they want. Yet
a normal guy won't even be able to get a
date. You can put all of this effort,
all of this time, all this money in and
still won't even be able to get a date.
And there's been a few times, right, um,
recently where I was like, let me go out
and try. And I just keep thinking about
what happened like a month ago and I was
like, nah, [ __ ] that. And I just end up sleeping
because it's demotivating.
It is demotivating. It's It's [ __ ] up. You know,
it should be a crime for women to
complain about men. They they are in no
position to moan that they can't find someone.
It infuriates me, you know, when this
woman's 28 and she says, "Oh, I'm a
virgin. I can't find anyone. It
infuriates me. It should be a crime, you
know, [ __ ] moaning about [ __ ] men.
We've all seen [ __ ] women's Tinder
profiles and [ __ ] [ __ ] off, man.
Well, that's how it is, isn't it? It's
like, okay, let me let me put it this
way, right? I can't speak to a woman
unless I go out approaching. I can't
text a woman. I can't. Okay, this is
Okay, [ __ ] the dating [ __ ] It's so bad
that you wouldn't even be able to talk
to a woman unless you approach her. Yes,
but they've got unrealistic standards.
Yes, that's the difference. They've got
unrealistic standards. Then they wonder
why they can't find someone
because what? How is none of these men
that you're meeting good enough for you?
There's they've got unrealistic
standards. There's a big difference
between standards, high standards and unrealistic standards.
They would reject somebody for having
blue eyes and not green. That's how
pathetic they are.
They'd reject somebody for having a
beard and not having a beard. That is
that is [ __ ] pathetic.
I think we can all agree on that is [ __ ] pathetic.
So that's what it is.
Standards. I'll give you I'll give you
an example of standards, right? So,
someone having standards, right? A re
realistic standards is okay.
Somebody that looks after themsel,
somebody that has money, has hobbies, um
that looks after their body. Um that's
what you call um realistic
standards, high standards or like a good
job. That is very very realistic.
They they would reject somebody for,
like I said, having blue eyes and not green.
Yeah. Well, then stop moaning that you
can't find someone then. Stop moaning
and winging that you can't find someone.
And everyone's allowed preferences, but
excluding yourself to that preference
and then you wonder why you can't find
someone. Stop moaning then. Stop moaning
and complaining. You can't find someone. So,
I mean, and you're trying to justify
them excluding themselves to that
preference, but apparently women go for personality.
It all contradicts itself. It literally
It really, really does. Oh, women women
go for personality, but if if you've got
blue eyes and you don't have green, then
I'm not giving you a chance. But get
over it because it's their preference.
Well, that's probably why you won't find
anyone ever. Will it?
No, no, no, no, no. Again, you're
twisting things. Twisting things again
to suit your narrative. Um, me not
liking a a fat woman would be a bit
different than me rejecting a woman for
being blonde and not br and not and not
being brunette. Blonde and not brunette.
There's a big difference to somebody
that doesn't look after themsel and
doesn't work themselves than somebody
having a different hair color or a
different eye color,
right? There's a big big difference and
that is twisting things what you're
doing right there
because fat women has got nothing to do
with a man having [ __ ] a different
eye color, you know? So again, you're
you're you're twisting things to suit yourself.
is very very very manipulative. You know,
it's like me, right? I'm I'm into Okay,
let me give you my preference, right?
That's like It's like me. Yeah, but why
are we Why are you talking about fat
women? That's not the same thing. Why
Why are you talking about a fat woman?
That is nowhere near the same thing. I'm
not fat. I'm not ugly. I just look
normal. I smell good. So when people sit
there and say, "Oh, well, what if a fat
woman approaches you on the street?" But
what they really mean is, "What would
you do if an average woman approached
you on the street?" That's what the real
question would be. Cuz a lot of people
like to twist things to what suits themselves.
No, it's not the same thing because a
woman being fat is a woman not looking after herself.
Somebody having a different eye color is
something that they can't help. That's
that's an example. No, it's not the same
thing. No, it's not the same thing at
all. No, it's completely not the same thing.
It isn't the same thing at all. No, it's
not. Cuz that's like me, right? Like in
brunettes with green eyes. And anyone
that's not brunette with green eyes, I
wouldn't go near.
I've been with blondes with blue eyes. So,
but then again, so it's so it's not
about personality then. about their
preference. Thank you. So, I see this
[ __ ] for what it is. I don't need to
white night. I don't need to lie. I see
it for what it is. It's that's it, you know.
So, so it's not about personality then.
So, we're getting somewhere. Thank you.
I don't I think people just need to stop
being honest, man.
Really? Well, that's [ __ ] ridiculous. But again,
if that is the case, I'm pretty sure
people admit that. With women, they
won't admit it. People won't admit it.
They'll be like, "Oh, it's about
personality. It's about personality.
It's about personality." When it isn't
about personality, the first thing they
go for is the way someone looks and then
probably like clout or something. They
they will never admit it's something
that somebody can't change.
And other people won't admit it as well.
They they'll be like, "Oh yeah, they go
for personality. They do."
But it's [ __ ] It is absolute
bollocks. They're more shallow than men.
I would say them they are actually more
shallow than men. 100%.
Yeah. But women women are more
definitely more picky than men. 100%.
1 million% women are more picky than men. So
that's that in it.
But either way, eh, disgusting. Absolutely disgusting.
But I've never known men to only like
fat women, to be honest.
I've never ever known that in my life.
That seems ridiculous. But anyways, like
but they admit stuff when it comes to Meno.
Yeah, exactly. And that's what it is.
It's not about someone's personality.
It's not about any of that stuff. I I
know it's because they've got more options,
which is my whole argument, you know.
And like I said, if I don't go out and
and approach a woman, I won't even get
to talk to a woman that is real via
text. Like it's it's [ __ ] madness. It
is actually madness to be honest. So
yeah, but like people need to admit that
though. It's not even like people admit
it. They always sugarcoat it. Like nah,
women don't owe you anything. A woman, a
woman goes goes for looks. Nah, not a
woman. She goes for personality.
They always do things to sugarcoat it
when it comes to a woman. And I don't know why.
Like, just say they're both as bad as
each other. I don't understand. But they always
make up excuses for women. I don't know
why they do it.
A woman lead you on. Ah, she just
changed her mind. a [ __ ] man does it,
mate. The strangers are coming for him
with a [ __ ] axe,
you know. It's It's ridiculous. It
really, really is.
The whole women don't know you anything
is is ridiculous. That is that is such a
lame attempt to cover up their shitty
actions. It's mad
cuz it's only used in that context. It's
never used any other way. It's madness.
So, but how people think I mean they
done this thing, right? Uh let me tell
you what you think of this.
They done this thing, right?
All right. where
there was this male model, well, I think
he was like a model, like good-looking
guy on Tinder, and he and he come across
as a child predator, and women still
wanted to go with him. Women still
wanted to go for him, even though he
said that he beats women and he's a
child predator. And then the average guy
didn't get any attention. That was
normal. I think that pretty much sums up the argument
pretty much. I think that tells you all
you need. And that's not [ __ ]
either. That's not [ __ ] It's very,
very, very much a physical thing. Even
if somebody is decent looking, that's
not even enough. So, I don't know why
people need to sugarcoat and lie.
It's it's ridiculous. It really really is.
They they they lie and say, "Oh, it's
about personality." When it's not. It's
really really not. It is. When you go on
dates, maybe when when you get the date, maybe. Yeah.
They just don't want to admit they're
shallow like them.
You know what I mean? Yeah.
But like I said, they exclude yourself
to that preference and it's a physical
thing which is something that they won't admit.
I'm not ranting about it, bro. You are
the ones that brought it up.
There's nothing to There's nothing more
to say. They're [ __ ] They lead people
on. It will never change.
So, like I said, when I go out tomorrow,
I hope it doesn't bother me. I don't
think it will bother me cuz I don't
think much will be able to bother me
after what happened last month.
I should be okay.
I should be all right, bro. So, yeah.
Yeah, I should be all right.
But it's all right, bro. Like I said,
I'm going Thailand next month anyway, so
it's all good. It's all good in the hood. Yeah,
I was I kept myself occupied yesterday.
It kind of helped. Got my phone mic
fixed, got my haircut, went to the
bookies. I walked there and walked back.
It's good to stay occupied, you know.
It's a It's a good thing. You don't want
to think about how you don't want to
think about this dating thing
and how it's rigged against men. You
really don't want to think about it,
bro. Because that's when you're [ __ ]
The moment you think about it,
right, the more you think about it, the
more like it will you're [ __ ] basically.
So, it's not it's not a good thing to
think about. Really really isn't.
Don't ever try and just don't think
about it. You know what I mean? It's you
don't want to massage yourself in it.
Let's see how you will deal with rejection.
And again, it wasn't rejection. It was
women leading me on. Again, something
that you dismissed. And also, what
you're saying is is is is right, Candy
Man. What's the point of coming online
ranting about it? But we didn't just
rant about it. We actually showed
evidence what they done. but you still
dismiss it. So there is no point
because no matter what you you're shown,
you would just defend them anyways. So
there's got to be a point where we
should agree to disagree, right?
So we we need to agree to disagree at
some point because it's whatever you're shown,
you're just going to keep defending
them. So we're just wasting our time,
you know. I blame women for leading on.
Yeah. Again, I don't see the point of
this conversation. You're always going
to continuously keep defending them.
You've established this. We've
established this. You've shown black and
white evidence of what they've done and
you're still defending them. We're
wasting our time,
right? How about women should stop
leading people on and stop being [ __ ] No. So,
so, okay, we're got we're going round
and round in circles.
We need to agree to disagree at some
point. I've shown you black and white
evidence and you're still defending
them. End the story. Let's agree to
disagree. If if if people can't show you
black and white evidence to change your
mind, then there's no hope for you.
There's generally no hope for you. And
if you want to live your life like that,
live your life like that. I don't care.
I live my life. You live your life. Like
I said at the start before you made me
get into this [ __ ] again. If you want to
keep defending women all your life and
licking their asses and not getting
women and be a virgin, that's your life.
I'm not telling you how to live your
life. You can do whatever you want to do.
People can do whatever the [ __ ] they
want to do. That's your life. You keep
defending them. You keep thinking they
don't do anything wrong. That's on you,
bro. I'm not here to change your mind.
I done a video showing messages. You
don't want to believe it. Good for you,
man. There's no more conversation to
have, is there? You know, so
yeah, again, I've showed you women
leading me on and doing more than ignore
me. And again, you dismissed it. You
dismiss things that don't suit yourself.
Yeah. That's just you will never get a
woman to call you. Yep. That's self
projecting. But we're not talking about
again. You're dismissing things. Okay.
Okay. Let me give you let me give you uh
an analogy here. Yeah. Give you a little
thing here about people dismissing
things that don't suit themselves. Okay.
So, let's just start with what Ricky
said. Yeah. When he commented and that
them 14 thumbs up, they didn't bother me
because them 14 people didn't watch the
video. Right. Let's let's see let's see
what he said. Right. He said that it was
offputting that I I loved their messages
but they loved my messages. He said that
I was asking them to me. I didn't ask
all of them to me. He was saying that I
sent them voice notes. I didn't send
them all voice notes. So you dismiss
things that don't suit you and then you
and then you pick things that you think
you're going to win the argument with
because not every single one of them
conversations got brought up. He he used
me loving their messages loving their
messages as an excuse even though they
loved my messages. You you can't reason
with these people literally. Okay.
So, you don't think So, you don't think
texting somebody and agreeing to meet
them and then not meeting them is is
leading leading you on.
You don't you don't you really don't
think that's leading people on? What is
it then if it's not leading people on?
So, someone saying that they're going to
meet you, agreeing to meet you, and said
the same day they're going to meet you,
and they don't beat you. That's
That's not leading someone on.
That's not leading someone on. What else
could it possibly be if it's not leading someone on?
Right. That's not leading someone on.
Uhhuh. So if that's not leading somebody
on, what is it then? So you say that I
block people, but I don't.
You can't. You can't reason with these white knights.
You really really can't. And I'm not
even calling you simps. I'm calling you
white knights cuz that's what it is.
It's actually white knighting.
Again, you're all you're doing is making
excuses for them. That's literally all
you're doing. What if this they change
their mind? No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no. I feel sorry for you people.
I really, really do feel sorry for you
people. I really, really, really, really do.
It's so bad. I I just don't understand
how people can be shown black and white
evidence and they still argue with it.
That's like going to court. Yeah.
it being on CCTV that you killed someone
and you'll be like, "Well,
not really." And then the judge is like,
"Well, we can see you've stabbed
somebody in the heart and they're dead
and and they're dead." And you'll be like, "Nah,
not really. That's literally what you're
doing. That is literally literally what you're doing."
Yeah, I'm the problem. Like I said, you
keep dismissing my struggles, bro, and
you keep telling yourself that.
You know, you literally dismiss anything
that you're shown. It's mad.
You can't reason with white knights. And
that and that's literally what you are.
You're white knights,
you know? There's no there's no getting
through to white knights. It's just like
what Ant-Man said. They're always going
to keep defending women. Let them be
virgins. Let them live their life. You
know, let them they're happy with that.
You know, maybe it's the way that these
people are brought up. You're never
going to get through to a white knight.
So, there's no point. I don't give a
[ __ ] about this anymore. You keep defending women.
And I don't know what what do you get
out of it as well, you know?
Yeah. It's not healthy. It's not
healthy. I am going to Thailand.
Yeah. Well, like I said, I put my
approaches up there. You dismissed. I am
not talking about this anymore. Anyways,
I've shown my approaches. I've shown my
messages. I've shown my evidence which
puts your which puts your argument to shame.
Anyways, we're not going on about this
now. That's that the reason I put the
videos up was for a reason. So, I'm not
here to justify or try to change your
mind. You keep defending women, bro, all
your life and see where that gets you.
That's your life, not mine.
You do what you got to do.
I know it's not the be all and end all.
I literally don't care about women, but
this guy keeps bringing it up.
So, but like I said, you keep defending
women, defending, you know, arguing
against things that you're shown,
whatever. That's on you. Live your life,
man. You live your life. I'll live my
You know, it is it is scary though how
many white knights there are to be fair.
Really, really, really. You're saying
about it's my approach, yet I've
approached women normally and then
they're not interested and they lead me
on. But yeah, I need to take a hard good
look at myself.
Maybe I'll do a video on this. There's
there's no getting through to white knights.
You can show them every proof in the world
and they would still say, "Nah, mate.
Never happened." They'll shake their
head like a dog. This madness.
I really, really feel sorry for them.
Generally, generally do. It's madness.
Bro, even if you paid for it, you still
wouldn't get it because you're too ugly.
Even if you you can't get it for free or
if you paid because you're so ugly that
even if you tried to pay, they still
wouldn't get with you.
That's even worse. You can't get it for
free and even if you paid, they still
wouldn't give you it. That's how bad it
is for you.
And you're blocked.
I'm going to I'm going to do a video
like I want to know what what you could
possibly do to get through to these white knights.
They don't believe what people tell
them. They don't believe what people
show them. I mean, what could possibly
get through to these white knights? How
could you possibly get through to them?
I don't think we'll ever know, to be honest.
I've put your argument to [ __ ] time and
time and time and time again. I've
literally destroyed your argument. You know,
you're not right. My videos show that
My videos show that you're not right.
So, my videos say otherwise. My
experiences say otherwise.
I mean, there's literally videos out
there where I've tried to speak to
somebody and they've not even gave me a
chance. Again, [ __ ] up your argument.
Every every time your argument gets
[ __ ] up, you still sit there and think you're right.
Even though there's video evidence where
your argument is ruined, you still think
that you're right, you know.
Yeah. And it and it shows No, no. It
shows that women don't go for
personality. It shows women lead people
on in black and white. That's what it
shows. It shows what you're saying is
completely completely wrong.
So yeah, Jay Willow, I might do a video
for Jay Willow to be honest.
There's like no getting through to these white knights.
There's literally no getting through to
them. It's insane. Black and white
evidence and you still nod your head
like a dog.
Yeah. Most of you No, most of you people
in here are married.
Exactly. It gets Exactly. It get It
takes time to get to know someone's
personality and they don't even give you
a chance to begin with. So therefore,
they don't go for personality then.
Exactly. My whole argument. Thank you.
That's what I just said.
Bro, it's not unhealthy. I don't care
about it. You are the ones that keep
bringing it up. I don't give a [ __ ]
about these women. You're the one that
keeps bringing it up.
Yeah. Good for Rice if he has someone.
You don't have anyone. You don't have
Yeah. You don't have anyone and you
don't have no money either.
Rice has someone but you don't. Yeah. Self projecting.
Yeah. I I I feel sorry, bro, for
cuz the mad this is the madest thing
about it, right?
You know, well, I'm better looking than you.
Well, I'm better looking than you, lad.
I'm better looking than you, matey.
Anyways, we're not talking about this.
This is boring.
Do you know the I do you know the irony?
Yeah. Before I end this is that I will
go out tomorrow and I will get more than
these white knights.
That's that's the [ __ ] up thing about it.
But Billy, why do you not have anyone?
You know, you said Rice has someone, but
why don't you have anyone?
Why don't you have anyone? You little self projector.
This is what I mean with you old people
in here, bro.
Yeah. You go home to a woman every
night, mate. Your hand don't count.
Why do I moan? Because I'm not scared to
say what I think. I don't defend women
for the sake of it. I'm not a loser. I
will not sit there and defend them. Even
if I got women every single day, I'm not
a white knight. I'm not going to sit
there and stick up for women for the
sake of it. I'm not a loser. That's what
losers do. And tomorrow, I bet you any
money that I will get more than what all
of these people that are looking women's
asses have for the past 10 years.
But they will still sit there and defend
women. And most of these people are virgins. you know.
Anyways, we're banning these little
mongos now. We want normal people in the [ __ ] chat.
[ __ ] up. Really, really [ __ ] up.
Really, really [ __ ] up, bro.
Yeah, went quiet, didn't he?
I feel sorry.
All these people.
Yeah, she doesn't she doesn't exist. So
that's going to be hard
because do you know what I do you know
what I find mad right is you people
right one sec
you got money you got a life but yet
you're sat on the internet all day every
day you can't take a day off of YouTube
that's what I find funny Huh? Yeah.
But it is mad.
One. Okay. One.
One second. One second. Yeah. Bye-bye.
Yeah, we need to stop talking about this anyways.
We need to stop talking about it, brother. [ __ ] madness.
They're still [ __ ] You know what I mean?
They're [ __ ] dead, man.
Do you want to drink or do you want to
do it bad?
Candy man. Which one do you want to Do
you want to drink or do you want to do it badness?
Monty is a [ __ ] weak little [ __ ]
Why didn't you give me that £500? I
would have went and splashed his face
in. I said if you give me £500, I would have [ __ ]
I would have [ __ ] um done it.
I did say that like if you give me £500.
I did actually say that, didn't I? You
say you've all got money on here
cuz that's the only time obviously if
you come to London that's different obviously like
but I don't know why somebody wouldn't
want to donate that.
Didn't they donate money to he didn't go?
Monty is not strong. He's a little [ __ ]
If money was going to do something, why
didn't he do something when he met me?
Like after the drinking and stuff, he
could have easily done something. He
didn't do nothing. He's not about it.
Not about it at all. So yeah.
But yeah, at least if I got 500 pound,
I'd be like, "Well, I got £500 for it."
[ __ ] going to meet somebody if I'm
not getting money, am I? Madness, bro.
Why any Okay. Why? Okay. Okay. Okay. But
why can't he come to London?
Okay. Moving on now. Why can't he come to London? Huh?
Like serious question. Why can't he come to London?
I'm asking a serious question. It's like
that Hugh. Yeah, I've seen him talk [ __ ]
about me, bro. I don't care, bro.
It's nothing new now that people are
snakes in this community. I don't give a
[ __ ] You know, these people are not
worth my [ __ ] time. But why can't
Monty come to London?
He doesn't live in a tent. He lives in a
house. And he gets benefits, doesn't he?
He gets money. No.
I might make myself a steak in a minute.
A nice steak. Yeah.
Yeah. That Hugh was stirring up [ __ ] He
was lying. trying to say that I said
about taking out money for an escort. That's [ __ ]
Is there anyone that's normal on here
that's not a snake?
Except from [ __ ] Charlie. Is there
anyone normal that don't talk [ __ ]
behind people's back?
[ __ ] sake. We got Ricky Millington two
years ago saying how it's not the women.
Women are too picky.
And I'm I look like this and then and
then all of a sudden now it's me that's
the problem. So which one is it? Is it
me or the women? Heads or tails? Heads
or tails? Which side are you, mate?
Then he says, I get women, mate. I said,
firstly, I'm not your [ __ ] mate. And
secondly, you don't get women. The fact
that you happen to white night, it shows
that you don't get women.
It's always the people that don't get
women that do that. I've had women.
Many, many women. I've never ever
defended them cuz I would never defend
them. They're [ __ ]
But I don't know. Is there anyone on
here that's just like not two-faced? Huh?
I don't really understand to be honest.
We'll cross that bridge when when we
come to it.
Then uh we'll cross that bridge when we
come to it, won't we? But it's never
going to happen.
Let's be real here. It's never going to
happen, is it?
I still smell barbarous, man. I got a nice trim.
Tomorrow is going to be sick.
Yes, it is, man. Yeah,
I can't wait for Thailand next month.
It's going to be sick.
Yeah. But then I think it's strange if
someone's got a woman
and they still defend women.
It's like nonslegs trying to say, "Oh,
I've never been rejected. You [ __ ]
well have been rejected.
You [ __ ] virgin [ __ ] Britney
rejected you." And also, it's the women
that break up with the men. It's not the
men that break up with the women. But
he's broke up with every single
relationship he's been in. Strange when
it's the women that break up with the men.
I've never Obviously, it probably
obviously happens. I'm I'm sure it does
happen. But every single time I've known
somebody get finished, it's always been the woman.
How do I know these things? But not him.
Nah. He's the only 31year-old in the
world that's never been rejected.
He's the only one. The only 31year-old
in the world that's never been rejected.
Mad, isn't it? He has been rejected.
He's been rejected by Britney,
another woman. Well,
what do you want? You clown.
>> Well, you get rejected every day. You muppet.
>> Yeah, you have to get with ugly Natalie.
>> Natalie's ugly as you.
>> Looking better than you will ever get
PJ. Nah, she's stinking, son.
>> You can't even get a bed.
>> How much money do you have?
>> I'm asking you for a reason.
>> Are you asking me for a reason? Money
means [ __ ] to me. Either way, PJ
>> I'm asking you for a reason. How much you have?
>> Oh my god. PJ, listen. I don't give a
[ __ ] I'm asking you for a reason.
>> [ __ ] about I don't give a [ __ ] about
money. What the [ __ ]
>> I'm asking you so you can come to London.
>> See you later. See you laterondon.
>> So you can ask me how much money I've
got. Yeah. To see if you can come to London.
>> See if you can come to London. The man's
a [ __ ] [ __ ]
>> Come to London.
>> The man's a [ __ ] See that PG?
>> See, look. She's a [ __ ] He's a [ __ ]
>> Yeah, [ __ ] You were supposed to come
>> to London. Can you come to London?
>> You were supposed to come, you know, cuz
you were supposed to come here. That
would have deal.
>> Yeah, but can you come to London?
>> Boosting about it. Boosting about it and
all that. Like you're going to come here
and do this and do that to me. Prove it.
Be a manager. You come to London.
PJ, be a man. Be a man.
>> Yeah, you you be a man. Come to London.
>> Just be a man. I don't need to move.
>> You're not going to do anything. I don't
need to move.
>> You had your chance last time to do nothing.
>> PGA. PGA. I don't need him anything.
>> I You apologize back then. But listen,
you've done it again. You bring my kids
up again, didn't you? So, don't really
matter. You can bring them up on you.
You still arranged to come here for me.
So, I keep that word to you. You
threaten to come.
>> Yeah, this guy's a [ __ ] weasel.
>> Why? Why can't you come to London? Rice
went to Birmingham. I've come to
Birmingham. Why does everyone have to go to you? >> Why? >> Yeah.
>> See you later. >> Huh?
>> Oh, by the way, that was talking [ __ ] I
didn't say that. Um, I withd you money
for an escort. That guy's talking a load of [ __ ]
And um when he's on your panel again,
I'm going to join your panel because I
don't think he'll be coming on here again.
That's 10. That normally happens when
someone talks [ __ ] behind your back cuz
he was talking a load of wank cuz I was
watching the live stream back.
No one's [ __ ] No one tried to kiss
you either. You liar. Making up gay
jokes. Trying to say that I asked you
for a [ __ ] [ __ ] made up [ __ ]
I asked you for a [ __ ] That's funny
as [ __ ] Made up gay [ __ ] man.
>> Yeah, I'm sticking to that deal. What
you said, PJ? You were supposed to come
to Birmingham today. You [ __ ] and make
some excuse on me coming to Birming I mean London.
>> Okay, but can you come to London?
>> Yeah, PJ not going to London.
>> I know. He's such a bullshitter. He's a
bullshitter. He make He can't even swear
in his kid's life cuz he's bullshitting.
Listen, I don't need to swirl my kids
eyes for a little kiss to kiss me in a club.
>> [ __ ] hell.
>> You know what I mean? Wanted to kiss me
in a club. Did you
>> I wanted to kiss you in a club. Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
>> You try to keep licking my face with
your tongue out.
>> Yeah, of course I did. Yeah.
>> Proper proper.
You wanted to put You even wanted to
lick me all clean and everything. There it comes.
>> Yeah. Really?
>> Yeah. Yeah, you keep telling yourself that.
>> Anywhere, PJ. When are you coming in Birmingham?
>> When are you coming to London?
>> I don't need to.
>> Yeah. Well, then shut up then.
>> PJ, you don't need to shut up. Say
you're going places where you're scared of going.
>> Yeah, [ __ ] is a weak launch. Yeah, he is.
>> You are weak nons are
you got the weakest nons on your panel.
You got the weirdos over on your side,
man. Who [ __ ] harass women just like
yourself, PJ? What? How do I harass women?
>> Come on. How dare women
shag nothing. You [ __ ] I would rather
>> I'd rather shag nothing than shag that
[ __ ] ugly Natalie G. And I'll say it
to your face as well.
>> You couldn't even beat Money Mike and
[ __ ] Timmy. You could even beat
Timmy. Imagine that. You could even beat
>> I felt sorry for Timmy. I think Timmy
can buy you to be honest. PJ. Well, he
he hasn't battered me.
>> I think he I think he can b you.
>> [ __ ] can't even speak without spitting.
>> I just want a drink of milk,
>> Monty. Man, you're a spaz.
>> No, not a bigger spaz than you. So why
you on pit PJ?
>> Yeah, but Barry, you don't have nothing.
You're still a virgin like most
why you on PJ
every day? You ain't got a life. Most of
you are virgins, mate. You're talking about
>> You sit there. You sit alone and talk about women.
>> Virgins that can't get up on YouTube.
>> Oh, sadly.
Why can't you come to London? Just
answer me why you can't come to London. >> Why?
>> My legs can't hit me that far.
>> I would smash your face and Oh my god.
>> I will smash you. Why can't you dick?
>> You couldn't even be [ __ ] Mike went
in your face and you done nothing. He
said if you want trouble I'm going for Mike.
>> You've done nothing. You done nothing.
>> It weren't what we're going for.
>> Yeah, it doesn't matter.
>> What we're going for?
>> You were chim. Why are you still a virgin?
>> Let's talk about you, the virgin on YouTube.
>> What? [ __ ] what [ __ ] can do. Why are
you still a virgin that has no one?
>> Stop self-reflecting your [ __ ] onto me.
>> PJ, you are the biggest virgin.
>> Why are you still a virgin that can't
get off of YouTube?
>> Stop putting it back. You know, I've
proved these people can't get off of
YouTube time and time again. I've proven about virgin,
>> you know.
>> Yeah. Monty goes for threes out of 10.
Why can't you get anyone Barry? Why are
you still a virgin that can't get off of
YouTube? Let's talk about you. Oh, you're married.
>> Another one that's married. Isn't it so
funny, right, that all of you people
here claim that you're [ __ ] married,
but you're sat on YouTube from the time
you wake up to the time you go to bed,
but you're all married. Get the [ __ ] out
of here. I'm married to your PJ married
to your right hand.
>> PJ, don't don't don't you stress out
because you can't get a woman all the time,
>> mate. I'd rather have no woman than have
ugly Natalie with black flaps.
>> That's all done.
>> Barry being you can't get married to
your right hand.
>> It's not possible. You can't get married
to your right hand, bro. Ask [ __ ] why
he undressed a drunk girl in a hotel.
You can't get married to your right
[ __ ] hand, bro.
Yeah. Why did you undress a drunk girl
in a hotel room?
>> Oh, undress is some lie. Yeah, PJ is
some liable body making up on your side. Yeah.
>> So why why would they make it up?
>> Obviously causing unress. No [ __ ]
man. Help somebody get
>> you can't listen. You
>> Why do they talk about [ __ ] on your
side, PJ? Why do they talk about pedo [ __ ]
>> on your channel? Why do they talk about
pedo [ __ ] up on your channel?
>> They do on your channel as well.
>> Did they [ __ ] my channel's normal? My
channel is actually [ __ ] normal.
>> Normal. Them get kicked. You talk about
Lord of all kids. They get kicked off.
>> They get kicked off. I heard that Hugh
said that he was getting a ten of weed
cuz he was skinned.
>> Tens of weed cuz I'm skinn.
>> No, he said cuz he's skinned. That's
funny, is it?
PJ, this only why you got money is
because you get paid what? Every two weeks.
>> Nope. You don't know how much money. You
get paid every two weeks. Every two
>> Yes. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You do.
>> You get paid every two [ __ ] weeks.
You [ __ ] idiot. And you sit like you
got all this and you got all that, man.
You get paid every two [ __ ] week. You clown.
>> No, I don't. Yeah, you [ __ ] do. You
>> Yeah, you [ __ ] do. Then you're
frauding your house, renting a room out
and all that.
>> I don't even do that anymore. I don't
even do that anymore,
>> man. Yeah. Yeah, I know. Cuz you live at
your mom's house now, you [ __ ]
>> Yeah. So why you talking about renting
rooms when I don't even do that?
>> Yeah, but you do live at your mom's
house, don't you?
>> Why does it matter where I live?
>> Yeah, but you live at your mom's old you
your mom's address in it. But why does
it matter where I live?
>> It does matter, don't it, Pia?
>> But why do you care where I live?
>> Yeah, but you live at your mom's, don't you? >> No.
>> Oh. Oh, no. No, no. I forgot it. It's your sisters.
>> You live with nonslegs cuz she's your
sisters. I forgot. You live with your sister.
>> You live with Nons.
>> How did that pass my memory? >> Nons.
>> Oh, no way. Nons is your mate.
>> Yeah, but why are you living at your sister's pier?
>> Why is nons your mate? >> H
>> Why you living at Why you living at your
sisters? Come on.
>> Cuz it's fun.
>> What you living at sisters? Yeah.
>> Yeah. Why are you not living with your sister?
>> I don't need I don't live with any of my
really is. Why?
>> Because I'm a full grown [ __ ] bloke.
>> This woman wants to meet me tomorrow in
Scotland, but I'm not going Monty.
>> Oh, okay. Okay. So, is she you turning
down with me now? Cuz they'll turn you down. Yeah.
>> No. Do you want to see what she looks like?
>> No. She likes a dude with a wig on.
>> Yeah, that's what she looks like. So, I
can't meet her.
But she looks better than Natalie to be fair.
>> Well, meet you thinks she's better than
Natalie. No, cuz I don't want none of it.
Marty, this community ruined you, didn't it,
>> PJ? This the community's got you class
in [ __ ] London.
>> This community ruined you though, right?
>> Yeah, it's ruined me. But I'm still here.
>> You know, you'll never learn, will you?
You'll never get off YouTube. Get
knocked out, peeps. He's going to get
knocked out. And this is why you won't
come Birmingham YouTube.
>> Why can't you come to Birmingham, PJ?
>> Come to London.
>> You're a [ __ ] bag. That's why PJ, you
will always be a [ __ ] bag.
>> Come to London.
>> What was it all yesterday, people? What
was it yesterday? He's coming to smash
my face. When he gets off this train,
he's going to do that. He's going to do
this. He's going to [ __ ] do that.
That's what he said he's going to do.
They woke up next morning and and just
noticed he took a [ __ ] in his pants. >> Monty,
I'm making myself a lovely steak.
>> Yeah, you make yourself a steak.
>> A lovely steak then. Monty,
>> did you
do you eat steak every single day? You [ __ ] idiot. >> What?
>> You eat steak every day. >> So,
>> yeah. [ __ ] steak head. >> Yeah,
>> it's only what you [ __ ] can cook, you
prick. Easy [ __ ] food.
>> No, I can I can cook better than you.
>> Can you [ __ ] I can't cook. >> Huh?
>> I can cook.
>> You Yeah, but you only eat hello things.
>> Allow me.
Don't get me started on kebabs. PJ, do
not get me started on my kebabs now. PJ,
>> get this B [ __ ] to say birth certificate. Why?
Get these bastards into [ __ ] nons.
Come on, PJ. Say nons. >> What?
>> Say birth certificate.
>> PJ say your mom's a hoe.
>> No, your mom's a hoe. Leslie's a hoe.
>> PJ, why does your mom look like more of
a man than you?
>> I know.
>> She actually does, man. There's no li to
[ __ ] wicked wick.
>> How do you feel that Bryce is going to
be your kid's new daddy?
>> That's Bryce will never be going near my kid.
>> You sure about that?
>> Yeah, I'm sure about that.
>> Nah, I think he will be.
>> I think he won't be. Not when he's in my
mom's care. It's not allowed name
children. Kay, right? PJ. They said,
"Yeah, Kaye is not allowed nowhere near
the children. Rice is allowed nowhere
near the children. They're both banned
from seeing the kids. Even though Rice
has never seen my kids,
Kay is banned from seeing Lord and P."
And Rice is banned from seeing Well,
he's always been banned.
>> He's always been banned.
>> I can't believe you introduced me to that kid. >> PJ,
you're away. I should have smashed you
up out of the [ __ ] court station. I
should have smashed you up on a night
out. I don't know why I didn't.
>> I literally can't believe you introduced
me to that skin virgin though. You're mad.
>> Oh, PG. Listen, I've never introduced
you to Sean. I got you into a community.
Yeah, but I never got you to meet Sean
or Sean never.
>> That was someone else.
You were talking to before I even knew
you were talking to yourself
for that one.
>> Look, just prepare my steak.
>> You can't you can't afford a steak in it.
>> This guy's [ __ ] run, man.
>> Why you
PJ? Is this why your [ __ ] brother and
dad killed himself? How your brain works? >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. No [ __ ] wonder. Your peex
almost sent him. You're a prick. >> Yeah.
>> Didn't your brother kill himself or did
he get battered by a load of Pakis?
>> No, he's still alive. He's still up and going.
>> He got battered by a load of Pakis.
>> Why you being racist for PJ?
>> I'm not. I'm just saying.
>> Yeah, but you're being P. But you're
just being racist, right? But >> no,
>> yeah, but didn't didn't your brother
kill himself with alpha boys then?
>> That's not really killing himself, is it?
>> Just come to London so I can smash you
in, you skinny little [ __ ]
>> You wouldn't beat me. You wouldn't beat
me at all.
>> Yeah, because I'm not coming to London.
you and that [ __ ] skin virgin nonsense.
>> He's only offering me out to go to
London because he knows I'm not going to
go to London. That's what it is. This is
why he's telling me to go to London.
Have you not noticed that? Yeah. He
meets everybody else in this community,
but he will not meet me.
>> Funny thing.
>> I look this is serious [ __ ] I'm going
to smash his face.
>> I look smash.
>> No one can stop this one. children.
>> No one can stop, please.
>> Was your mom a crackhead?
>> Mom was not a crackhead,
>> was she?
>> Was she [ __ ] crackhead?
>> She's never been a crackhead, you prick.
>> Well, these people are saying that she
cracked. She crackhead.
No [ __ ] that [ __ ]
all the crack.
>> I can't believe you introduced me to
that skin virgin. You need to get slapped up.
>> PJ, you shag Sean up the ass. You talk about
>> introduced me to that skin [ __ ] [ __ ] virgin.
>> PJ, you shag shing up the ass.
>> Why did you introduce me to him?
Why do you shag him up the ass, PJ? Why
do you sit there and talk about a man
who you don't know?
>> Every day you go on about him.
>> No, no. Every day you go on about him like
>> he goes on about me.
>> No, no, you you you've got you got a crush dedicated.
>> You literally [ __ ] would go down on
Sean's [ __ ] knob and suck him right
off. He would you would give him a no
off. I swear to God. >> No,
>> I swear to God. You you b Sean Sean and
all legs right over. You're talking about
>> seriously. Why did you introduce me to
that version of that?
>> Yo, put one in the chat. He [ __ ] PJ
would [ __ ] go down on
>> So why does he have a channel dedicated to me?
>> My time.
>> I see you later. My attention's not on
you anyways. I see you later. Yeah. >> Okay.
It can't even come to [ __ ] Birmingham.
>> I'm just cutting up some mushrooms.
Making myself some steak and mushrooms.
Lovely little meal. >> Yeah.
The skin one in the bed.
Why just [ __ ]
uh leg still go about um USA Izzy? I
might give him her number. I think he's
in love with her.
He might finally pop it that big card.
What do you think? He keep he always
goes on about [ __ ] USA is he
does he want her or something? If he
wants her, I can give him her number.
I don't mind, you know. He seems very
very obsessed, Candyman.
Yeah, he seems to be very very obsessed
with this USA, is he?
You never know. He might lose his virginity.
What do you think?
He might actually pop it.
Pop that meard. [ __ ] that B play. [Music]
One sec. I'll let you in now. >> Yo,
>> why are you going on about a woman who
don't want you? Who's never wanted you?
>> You was the one going on about Natalie.
>> Going on going on about you.
>> How about that? Does she know? I'm with
>> I'm with her.
>> Yeah, she'll break up with you again.
>> So, she does. She does. You know,
at least I can remove this time. Yeah.
Yeah. But at least I got at least even
crying over a woman. But at least I got
>> What have you got? You can have a what
what have you got? She got
>> What have you got, PJ? What What have you got?
>> I don't want a three out of 10 with black.
>> What have you got? What have you got?
>> What girlfriend have you got?
>> I I don't want a three out of 10. PJ.
PJ, every time you go downtown, every
woman says, "You look at that big nose." >> Yeah.
>> Look at that big nose. Yeah.
>> At least he's looking [ __ ] like you.
>> Yeah. These this [ __ ] [ __ ]
can pull birds.
>> But you can't pull birds cuz if you
could pull more birds than you, man.
Look in the I'm not being funny. Look at
the nightclub. Come on, man. You were
getting jealous cuz some woman would
strike him a bald head and another man's bald head.
>> You wouldn't be quite,
>> would you? Come on. I love Natalie. And
Natalie is my angel.
>> Yeah, but she don't want you.
>> Oh, she does want me though. That's a
PJ. She really
>> She don't want you like [ __ ] Britney
never wanted [ __ ] nonsakes.
>> I'm leaving. I'm leaving. That's the
thing. Why you self-reflected on [ __ ]
You can't get PJ. That's a woman.
>> I want that [ __ ] ugly [ __ ] I could
have had her before.
>> You don't want no woman. You don't want
no woman, do you? Cuz you can't get a woman. You know
>> why can't you get a woman, please? Yeah.
I feel sorry.
>> I got a woman.
>> Yeah. Right.
>> Yeah. Right. It's a woman with
>> a fat me [ __ ]
>> Okay. So, I got a woman in it. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So, so every time when you
go down town to pull you, how many nos
do you get?
>> Not as many as you.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You [ __ ] do. You
get them all the time.
If you could get women, if you could get
women, you wouldn't be crying over >> Natalie.
Listen, listen. I love hang
on these. You're the one who goes on
these things. Listen,
>> the only two women go and can't even put
on dating apps.
>> The only two women you was masal.
Just saying that all player
>> PJ can't get a woman on no dating apps.
PJ can't get no woman in the real world.
>> You can only get the monsters.
>> PJ is just going to be alone for the
rest of his life.
>> And be with a three out of 10 with black flaps
>> singing [ __ ] lonely. Singing lonely.
>> I don't want I don't want to slag. I
don't want a packy shagger with [ __ ]
black flaps. I'd rather have no one.
>> Why you being racist, PJ? Why you being racist?
>> There you go.
>> Mercist for
>> Do you think you have arrested on charges?
>> You're getting money Mike sloppy
seconds. Imagine that.
>> I'm not getting these vloppy seconds.
Money m's got a small dick.
>> Yeah, you got sloppy seconds.
>> Money m got a small dick. But at least
I'm getting at least I'm getting a funny.
>> Yeah, black. Oh, these have got So, all
these have got a hold to go.
>> Didn't you say you was getting tested?
>> These You know what?
I keep all the bacteria I got off. >> Yeah.
>> I think you and legs needs to get laid.
>> What is it? I get laid more times than
you PJ to be honest. To be honest. Come on.
And if you adding on the prostitutes,
dead 100% don't count out.
>> I can't believe you was crying
overnight. That's pathetic.
>> Oh, it's called love, PJ. When you feel it,
>> PJ will never feel love. PJ, you're the
man who who kicks up woman who don't want him.
>> That's [ __ ]
>> That's pathetic.
>> That's pathetic. It is, isn't it? Ain't
it? Is it pathetic of you crying over a
woman who don't want you?
>> You cry over every single woman what
don't want you.
>> No, that's human.
>> No, no. That's 100% you putting all the
taxes up on that [ __ ] You don't want
me showing everyone that women were
[ __ ] cuz they are [ __ ] So what?
>> No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Women just
see you for who you are.
>> Okay, whatever.
Yeah. And that's just the M.
>> You are the M. Have you seen yourself?
>> And that's the M of all the M. You're
the biggest on YouTube.
>> You are the biggest M on here.
>> You look like you've got cancer.
>> Talk about me.
>> Listen, women love my ball head. You
look like you've got [ __ ] poor PJ
women. W women actually love my crying.
You said that you was going to kill
yourself over slag.
>> Over slag. You said you were going to kill yourself.
>> Listen, I'll do anything finale.
>> He said he was kill himself over mad.
>> Yeah, but PJ I got feelings for Natalie.
That's the thing. Feelings.
>> Mad. You're going to kill yourself over slap.
>> Oh, PJ. PJ I got feelings for that's the
difference. feelings. You would never
have feelings to a woman over a slack.
>> He only repeats now.
>> Over a [ __ ] slag.
>> I'm not even repeating myself off of
this P. You don't understand actual
love. This guy, you've never been in a relationship.
>> Over a slide. You
>> know what I mean?
Feeling poor woman.
>> But he gets all these women inside when
it pops inside.
>> But he gets all these women. You've
never felt that.
>> Well, he gets all these women
>> and and this is why PJ is so angry.
>> You can't be in love with somebody that
you've only known for a couple of
months. He wasn't with
>> I haven't known her for a couple of
months or have not exactly like that is
it. I've known her on YouTube for what years
and then what we meet in person and then
what we go out together for 6 months.
You know six months been going out for
six months. PJ
>> Monty can't cook, can it?
>> I I can cook. Of course I can.
>> You can't.
>> Of course. Of course you can cook.
>> Monty can't cook.
>> Of course I can cook.
>> I can cook.
>> Yes, I can. Have you ever seen me cook PJ?
>> But I didn't f to kill myself. Exactly.
You've never seen me cook, so I do can
cook or not.
>> You know, I didn't say I was going to
kill my [ __ ] self, did I? >> PJ.
>> No, wrong with that. Like I lost myself
and I thought lose myself.
>> You said you was you made you said you
was going to kill yourself to make
everyone feel sorry for you. That's pathetic.
>> PJ, I would depressed. Depression.
>> No, you wasn't. You just wanted attention.
>> Depression. That weren't attention.
>> You just wanted attention.
>> That was not no attention whatsoever.
>> I do not want no one's paying us all
attention on this community.
>> You're just you're just attention seeking.
>> How am I attention seeking without you know
Natalie's on YouTube, you know, she watches, you know.
>> I'm trying to cook you [ __ ] at the same time.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Why? Why? Why you on paper plan?
>> I'm trying to [ __ ] talk. I'm trying
>> Yeah. Yeah. But why don't no woman want
Okay, then if I'm a [ __ ] Yeah. and
and this bastic can get laid. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Listen, you say about you sound
like a 10y old.
>> You know, you know when you say, you
know, when you're saying um about
getting laid, you sound like a 10y old.
You know that.
>> Led PG.
>> Yeah. You sound like a 10-y old. You're
talking about getting sex. Your first
ever girlfriend then PJ. Yeah, because
you never had a girlfriend.
>> PJ, you're a 10year-old. You go out club
approaching. That's [ __ ] 2010.
>> You know what I mean? Who who goes out
cold approaching daily on daily shopping?
>> Yo, would you people press one? Yeah. If
you would call the post a woman doing a
shopping. Yeah. Or would you call a pro
woman in a club?
>> In a club.
>> Crying. Crying over.
>> Not out doing a daily thing.
>> So, which one would you
>> Which ones would you do? Going to
approach some woman in town doing a
daily shopping or out in a nightclub.
Where would you?
>> Right. easier because people are doing
they've all going adults.
>> They're doing a daily [ __ ] things.
>> They're doing a daily things. They're
doing a daily shopping, doing whatever,
getting to work, doing things, and then
then they just got a m there pulling
them up, asking them.
>> You are. You are m
>> You know what I mean? That's how I see it.
>> You are [ __ ] M.
>> You are random women. He's [ __ ] got
his bully. You are a ming
pulling them and don't even want no
bother with you.
>> You are a man.
>> [ __ ] even AC didn't even want you,
man. She even wanted that M.
>> You are a M.
>> Yeah, but why didn't AC want you P?
>> You are a Manta. Yeah.
>> Yeah, but why didn't AC even want you?
>> No one wants you.
What? Listen, can I ask you a question?
Why are all the women you've been with but ugly? >> Huh?
>> There's only been one ugly one, and that's Kayley.
>> No, Natalie's ugly as well.
>> Natalie's not ugly at all.
>> Yes, she is.
>> Is she [ __ ] ugly?
>> She is [ __ ] stinking, son.
I think all the bets you trying pull in
the one in the pub would look like a
more of a dude than that one.
>> You stinking son.
>> Listen Terry, stop talking about people
not meeting people. When I went to your
area, you didn't show up. Stop
forgetting. Yeah. Listen, Terry. Even
though I said last time I was going to
come to your area, Fair enough. But
remember the last time I come to your
area, you didn't show up.
>> I went to your area. You didn't show up.
But you like
Monty never done that. The thing is
Monty never done that. You done that.
>> [ __ ] pants. You remember you come to ter
and you didn't show up. You are the [ __ ] pants.
>> Shitty pants. Remember that time
>> you said you coming to me. You said you
called me out to come to your area and I
went to your area. You didn't come out
cuz you was on bail. Or was it? You on probation.
>> You are shitty pants. It's on someone else.
>> You wouldn't wait for me here, you little [ __ ]
>> I said it's on someone else. So PJ,
>> so why can't you come to Birmingham
then? You you're shouting everybody out online.
>> No, no, no. You're shouting everybody
out online. The fact you're going to
these areas and this and that and then
you're turning up to these areas. >> Okay,
>> Terry, why didn't you come out the last
time I went to your area? If you keep
ignoring the question, I'm going to
block you. Why didn't you come out the
last time I come to your area? Tell
everybody why you didn't come out.
>> It's a weasel. PJ your weasel.
>> Tell everybody why you didn't come out.
Don't be ignoring. Why did you let me
come to your area? You didn't come out.
And this is why I don't waste my time
with you clowns. Cuz you do this all the
time. You tell people to come and you
don't show up.
>> This is why I don't waste my time.
>> Because of people like him.
>> I don't waste my time.
So when you come in Birmingham, please
get this [ __ ] open.
When you come in Birmingham, PJ, you threaten me.
>> Why did you not come?
>> Changing subjects to someone else. PJ,
are you [ __ ] dead? >> Anyways,
>> are you deaf?
>> Are you deaf, PJ? Bye-bye.
See you later.
Let me finish my cooking. Sorry, bro.
Yeah. And this is exactly why I don't
waste my time meeting any people.
Not wasting time cuz you don't show up
and then you pretend it never happened.
Big part reason why I waste my time. The
fact when I went to Terry's area, didn't
show up. No one said anything about it.
Mark Samson, one of these other people,
you know, it's just the same [ __ ]
>> I will never ever meet anyone there ever
again. Unless somebody comes to me or
like I said, they give me that money.
I'll never waste my time or buy a [ __ ]
out of there, bro.
Get him off me. Get him off me. Yet you
told me to come to your area. I went to
your area. You didn't show up. No one
said anything. Exactly my point.
That is exactly
exactly my point.
My food's ready now. Anyways,
that is exactly my point.
You know, exactly my [ __ ] point.
How come somebody that looks like he's
got [ __ ] pants to try and talk about
[ __ ] with me, bro? We'll
be taking an egg and mushrooms.
What bloody is it?
I'll show you that.
We lost it a bit. It like
There you go. [Music]
Yeah, of course I did.
I put butter on it. Butter, salt, lemon.
I was going to put black peppers on it,
but I didn't. Yeah.
should be ready. Lovely egg.
You're lovely there. Ready now.
It's a bastard trying to [ __ ]
cut it off. Oh, that one's all right.
Golden egg next to it.
Look at that.
That is lovely. To be fair, I don't
think the virgin good though.
I don't think the skin virgin good. Yeah.
I don't think any block this money.
There's a lot of people that can go. I can't.
Look at that. That's lovely, mate.
Yes. Egg. This all I used to eat when I
used to go. Mhm.
I'll wait for my football back later.
skin in his little bed with no bed. No money.
They just actually [ __ ] just aim. This
Sorry about that, bro.
That was yummy.
That was delicious.
Oh, that was
that was yummy, bro. Very [ __ ] yummy.
Still got a good cooking me then, don't I? Unlike Virgin,
Monty's a [ __ ] idiot, man.
He's a [ __ ]
You still there, Frosty? I don't
understand how this [ __ ] tried to
say uh that I'm obsessed with this [ __ ]
when he's literally the one that's got a
channel stalking me every day.
What the [ __ ]
These people need to get a life, bro. On here.
I'll be off here soon anyways, bro. In a
couple of days, I'll be off my boyfriend
after my after my birthday.
Um, Monty in it. Oh, nonslegs. He says
that I go on about nonslegs. No,
nonslegs goes on about me. Nons is
obsessed with me. Nons has got a channel
dedicated to me. Him and these little
simps will not leave me alone.
You know, it's I am not obsessed with them.
They are obsessed with me. They will not
leave me alone. They've been doing this
for years and years and years and years
and years and years and years and years
and years online stalking me every single day.
won't leave me alone. Uh,
repeating this is another reason why I'm
coming off this [ __ ] as well. It's full
of [ __ ] low lives.
Yeah, let's be so real about this now.
Do you know what I was thinking, Frosty?
Like, how long is this actually going to
go on for?
This whole weirdness, this stalkness,
how like it's like they don't stop,
Frosty. Like they never ever ever ever
stopped, did they? These people on here,
if you think about it,
it's not self projecting. It's
repeating. It's [ __ ] boring, bro. Is it
really, really is?
I don't need to go to Birmingham.
As predicted, the skin bought a job is
too scared. That's you. You're scared to
meet me when I went to your area three
times and you didn't show up. This is
why I don't bother with these people.
This is why I don't waste my time
meeting anyone on here because it's
they're all a biased audience. You know,
they will never ever ever stop these
people. I should have took advice a long
ass time ago
with these jealous people on here.
They say they're not jealous, but then
they're sat on YouTube every day doing
what they do from the time they wake up
to the time they go to bed. Who knows? E,
but it's not cuz I'm skinn. Show that 14
grand now. Show that for Show that
£14,000 again. You ain't got none, you
[ __ ] skin little bedsit ridden [ __ ]
you know, unhappy, insecure, unhappy
relationship. That's the only vibe I get
from this nonsex. You go on this
nonsex's channel, Frosty Crack. He's an insecure,
unhappy individual with a fragile ego.
That's why my four thumbs up was genuine
because it's right, you know. Yep.
Yeah. Exactly, bro. Exactly.
Yeah, I bet. It's not cuz I'm skinned
though. You are skin. Go and show that
14 grand right now. Show that 14 grand
again. And you can't cuz you don't have
it cuz you are skinned.
You little self projector.
Is that right, Frosty?
Still going about my sloppy seconds. Sad bastard.
I don't know if you've ever gone on this
um nonflex channel
trying to get people to meet people when
you're in your little shitty council
beds owned by the council. Never going
to meet anyone. And you're trying to get
other people to meet other people. You
skinned little bastard.
Yeah. You're going to sit there in your
little council, shitty little bedsuit,
owned by the council with no bed in it,
which is worse than living with your
mommy and try to tell me about not meeting people.
Uh, it's called um
I link. It's called King of the Money
Game, but you're not the king of the
money game cuz you can't show 14 grand
now cuz you ain't got it. Simple. So,
shut the [ __ ] up.
Yeah, he's a [ __ ] weirdo. Like, bro,
literally all these channel is Yeah,
I'll tell you what it is in a nutshell.
It's basically just convincing himself
that I've not had sex with women and
that I'm a virgin like him.
That's like the whole point of his
channel and he never stops. And it shows
that he's insecure. And it shows that
he's a virgin. Because for people to
have time to do this all day, every day,
bro, they're not having sex, they're not
in a happy relationship. Okay, bro. One sec.
Yeah. Where is it? Hold on.
You just type wrong in media.
W R O N G U N Media.
This little skin [ __ ] calling me skin.
I've got more money than you, but I'll
happily play the money game with you.
Do not Don't make me go to the bank
again and destroy you. You little [ __ ]
You ain't got no money. Show the money
right now. Show 14 grand right now on a new video.
Please get real, kid. You couldn't even
show £800. The last time you couldn't
put up that whole video. You were
struggling to show £800. You skimp mess.
You skimp [ __ ] mess.
Yeah, you should be able to find it.
Sat on YouTube every day convincing
yourself and trying to convince other
people that I'm a virgin like you.
Sad bastard. Oh, cuz you've never had
sex. You skint virgin [ __ ]
Yeah, he's skint, bro. Show 14 grand now.
Yeah, no spaces. Yeah.
Yeah. Show him for show show £14,000
right now. You skin little bastard in
you shitty little bedset. Go and show
the same amount of money now, you skin [ __ ]
I'll happily beat you at the money game,
you skin bastard. Stop.
being sat there
in your sk little shitty bedset owned by
the council and you don't own your house
at 31 trying to tell me who I should be [ __ ] meeting
[ __ ] £800 you skin [ __ ] now anyways
show that 40
just say the date we're showing the when
you're showing the money as well you
know show the date when you're showing
the money as
But you can't do that because you
haven't got any money. You're skinned.
You know, that's it.
Trying to stir up a fight. How many
fights is your virgin skin ass stirred
up yet you're happy to hide in your
pants bedsit being [ __ ] scared to
[ __ ] go to events for a month? But
people don't like to address that, do
they? Trying to get me to meet people.
You're trying to get me to meet people.
Didn't you try this with me and the neighbor?
You [ __ ] skint ratfaced ugly virgin
You know that's what I find mad. Bro,
you are skint. The skintest out there.
You've not been to a nice restaurant
ever in your life. You didn't go abroad
until you was 30. You got no clothes.
You got no bed. You don't own a house.
And you're talking about people being
skimped. Everything screams skint about
you. Nothing screams skint about me,
matey. Not one thing. Not [ __ ] one
thing, mate. You know that's the difference.
You are skinned.
You are skint. The skint is [ __ ] going.
Stop thinking that you got money. Elvis
Presley might have had money, mate, but you don't.
Everything is skint about you and
there's nothing. Show it now.
If you want to keep going on about this
£14,000, show it now.
Show the money now. You don't even have £1,000 now.
You know, struggling. He was struggling,
bro. I swear to God. I showed this [ __ ]
5.7 grand and the [ __ ] was struggling, lad.
He was struggling.
He was really struggling. He was like,
he was sucking his dad's dick, right, to
try to get [ __ ]
more money and he he couldn't show
£1,000. I swear to God, bro, like you
dig up a [ __ ] video from ages ago, do
you show £14,000 now then? If you've got
all of this money, big man, come on. I
don't mind playing the money game. I
don't mind going to the bank tomorrow
before I go out. Not a problem. And I'm
not going to have any excuses that you do, mate. You know,
don't try to get other people to meet
people when you will never meet anyone.
You know, you're more than happy to sit
there in your shitty camps or bedsit
with no bed in it talking about other
people's [ __ ] living circumstances.
You know, it's a madness. It's a [ __ ] madness, bro.
You are the biggest coward on YouTube.
I know he's obsessed with me. Yeah, bro.
He's obsessed. This virgin is obsessed.
His life is convincing himself that I'm
a virgin like him. That's literally his
life. He's He's He's insecure with a fragile ego.
He's He's got no life as well.
Insecure with a fragile ego and got no life.
Yeah, man. You can you can go on it.
It's he's been doing it for years.
Oh, the irony. But then he claims that
he's not jealous. Oh, the irony of
wasting every second of every day on
someone, but you're not jealous. Oh, the irony.
Logic not even once. But he's not
jealous, remember? Because there's
nothing to be jealous of. He just spends
all day every day stalking me on
YouTube, obsessing over me. But he's not
jealous. Oh, what the irony. if you even
know what that uh means.
Stop trying to [ __ ] host fights.
Stop trying to [ __ ] host fights, you
[ __ ] skint virgin.
Stop trying to [ __ ] host fights when
you're the one that ran to the police
because you couldn't go to areas for
[ __ ] a month.
Well, I can because do do you know how
much money I have? Okay. Okay. I I I can
slack people off because I've got more
money than this [ __ ]
and I'm more than willing to prove it.
So, how much money do I have right now?
Acubans, you don't know me. You don't
know how much money I have. This is
exactly what I mean. You people need to
stop talking about people that you don't
know that you [ __ ] don't know. This
is your problem in this community. You
seem to think that everybody has got the
same life as you. This is what I mean
with these these people in this
community. They seem to think everyone's
got their life.
Don't know where they get that [ __ ]
idea from, but yeah. They seem to think
everyone's got the same life as them. You know,
you know what I'm saying? You seem to
think everyone's got the same life as
you. That's your problems on here.
Trying to get me to to meet people when
you're the one hiding in your shitty
council beds. running to the police
claiming that you're not a fighter. But
at the end of the day, people forget
about that. Just like when people forget
I went to Terry's area and he didn't
show up. And that's why I don't waste my
time on meeting these people on this
community cuz it's the same old [ __ ]
And a wise person learned from their mistakes.
It's not even as bad. See, this is what
I mean. The guy's a low life. He's more
than happy to go round and round in
circles every day arguing, never
stopping, never meeting anyone because
he ain't got a life. He's still a
virgin. And he can show his disabled
girlfriend all he wants. It doesn't mean
a damn thing because we all know that if
he went anywhere near her, right, in any
kind of sexual way, he would be locked up
cuz she can't consent. She's a [ __ ] spaz
obsessed. I would have thought somebody
would have stopped by now, you know. Tradal stopped this [ __ ]
you know. Yeah. Again, how much money do
I have right now? Since you know so much
about my life. How much money do I have?
Since you seem to know so much about my
life. Let's hear it. Come on. You know,
I mean, for [ __ ] sake, half of you
people on here are on benefits. You're
sat on YouTube every day. I've seen it
with my own eyes from the time you wake
up to the time you go to bed. But you
all got jobs. You've all got a life.
Make it make sense. Don't let your
[ __ ] YouTube [ __ ] um
activity [ __ ] give you away.
trying to get me to [ __ ] meet Monty. The [ __ ]
Maybe I do have a good side hustle. You
don't know me. Stop talking about people
that you don't know. We don't all have
your life. A good side hustle. Who says
I don't have a good side hustle? You
don't know me. This is my whole point
with you people. This is your mistakes.
You think everyone has your life,
benefits, skin. This is this is exactly
what I'm talking about, right? We don't
all live like you. I'm I'm trying to get
this through to your head as much as I
possibly can. You're talking about a
side hustle. How do you know I don't
have a side hustle? You don't know my
life. You don't know how much money I
have. You don't know me, kid. So, I
don't know why you keep talking,
bouncing off your own life, thinking
that everyone's got your life.
And I'm not slagging him off for being
on benefits. I'm slagging him off
because he's [ __ ] skinned. That's the
difference. Nothing to do with benefits.
What the [ __ ] I'm saying he's skinned
because he's skinned. Benefits or no benefits.
Again, this is your problem. You seem to
think everyone's got the same lives as
you people. This is what I mean. This is
your problem. I'm telling you what your problem is.
You care so much about other people's
lives, right, rather than your own
because you ain't got a life. It's
obvious. It's [ __ ] obvious.
You know, you're obsessed with other people.
You know, when I said that he's skint
because he's skint, not because he's on
benefits. And he is skint. He is
properly skint. No one that's got money
lives in a council [ __ ] house owned
by the council. No bed, no travel
history, no designer clothes. Nobody
with money lives that life.
Nobody with money lives the skin life in
every aspect. Trust me, it does not
happen. It literally does not happen.
If you don't like designer clothes, you
would have traveled. If you didn't want
to travel, you would have assets. You
know, you would have done some things.
I'd rather live with my mom than live in
a in a council bedset. I've said it a
million times. It's not an insult. So,
you are absolutely living the [ __ ]
skin life. You know,
no life experience, no designer clothes,
no travel history, no nice restaurants.
You live like a skint person for someone
that that apparently has all this money.
You [ __ ] skint bastard. And this is
why I don't waste my time meeting anyone
on here because it's just the same [ __ ]
with you people. Just like it would
always be the same [ __ ]
Yeah. Well, it's been uh
it's been 12 years and he's still there. Yeah.
It's been 12 years. You know, you want
to talk about other people's life. Then
I never said my life's perfect. You are 31.
You have no teeth. You have no money.
You have no house of your own. You have
got no life experiences. And you're
trying to talk about [ __ ] me. Someone
that's younger than you. The irony. Eh, mad.
[ __ ] absolute madness. You know.
Yeah, it takes a long time, but it
doesn't take 12 years.
It doesn't take 12 years. So, yeah,
you're talking about a side hustle.
Maybe I do have a side hustle. You don't
know. You don't know me. You don't know
how much money I have. This is what I mean
with you people on here. You bounce off
your own lives. You think everyone's got
the same life as you. Skin, no money.
That's what you generally generally
think everyone's got the same life as
you. Cuz the things that you you guess
is so random.
Oh, someone's got £300 in their name.
Where the [ __ ] would that come from? Or
this, that, and the other. Because
obviously you're going by your own lives
and you think that everyone lives the
same life as you. That's what it is. Yeah.
And what are you saying? That you work?
You You don't know. You do not know what
I have and what I don't have. And you
know what? Even if you people did work,
which is highly unlikely, 90% of you
don't work, you ain't got a life. You
ain't got a life cuz you're on here
every day. From the time you wake up to
time you go to bed, you ain't got a
life. It's obvious. I've proven that many times. So yeah, simple.
I could be a drug dealer. How do you
know? Again, you don't know me.
You don't know how much I have. You
don't know how much I don't have. That's
what I'm saying. You seem to be very
obsessed with other people's lives.
This is the thing on here as well.
You know, you obsess over other people's lives.
You know, it's not like you come on here
and say, "Oh, let me let me watch some
content." No, you have to obsess over
other people's lives or compare your
lives to other people's.
It's like the insecure virgin with a fragile ego
sat online every day convincing people
that they're a virgin like him. I've
explained the USA Izzy situation
multiple times. I've explained the Izzy
situation multiple times and you're
still adamant even though nobody cares
about them that I haven't slept with
them. Okay. What about the escort story
then? Okay. What about the escort story?
The first the first one. You didn't
believe that either because it's it's a
pattern with you. You will not be happy
until somebody is a virgin like you.
This is I I I'm very right about what I
say about people. You've done this with
like multiple [ __ ] people. Unless
somebody is a virgin like you, you won't
be happy. You will not be happy until
someone says, "I'm a virgin like
nonslegs." That's literally you, bro.
Like, think about the first time I met
this [ __ ] I said, "Oh yeah, bang the
desk." Didn't believe it. Didn't believe
it. Found every single reason in the
book to not believe it because he is
still a virgin. You've been doing it for
[ __ ] years, mate.
Absolute [ __ ] years.
It's [ __ ] It's been the same [ __ ] for years. there.
>> Right. Let me join Monty's Hangouts
actually. One second, please.
What's the [ __ ] point?
What's the point of it, bro? What is the
actual point? You know,
no one's arguing. Yeah, you're talking
[ __ ] behind my back. I've called you out
on what you're saying, bro. Yeah. And
you're saying nothing. So what's the
point of it, bro? What are you, a [ __ ] 10-year-old? You know,
trying to talk about people being
mentally [ __ ] No, no, no. Like, oh,
just stop it. And then when somebody
comes up on the Hangouts, you've got
nothing to say. It's embarrassing. Madness.
Yeah, but didn't you Oh, this this is
what I mean with this community is
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
I can't be bo with this [ __ ] bro.
Monty, come to London for a beer. We can
go to his mom's. Oh my god. You're not
going to go to anyone's [ __ ] moms.
Shut the [ __ ] up. This This whole
community needs to [ __ ] grow up. Seriously, bro.
seriously need to grow up on this
community. These people do.
It's mad. Honestly mad. You know,
they need to [ __ ] grow up on this
community, bro. Seriously. I'm mad. [Laughter]
[ __ ] hell, Bro,
yeah, I need to go to bed soon as well
to be fair, even though not woke up. Yeah.
What is that?
some more. Anyways,
Yeah, I can't even go on Reddit at all
at all now.
They just log me out as soon as I try to
go on it.
It's just strange how they're able to do that. [Music]
Now the top kind of smells like [ __ ] um
what's it called? Um
yeah, they they block people acu.
They fear different opinions.
They fear different opinions. The mods
go mad over it.
The mods are just people that have been
bullied that are still angry about it
because no other site just bans people but Reddit.
They need to be in control. Do you not
understand? It's a control thing.
And if they're not in control at all
times, they're going mad. It's all about
being in control cuz they don't have a
life outside of Reddit. You see? So,
it never used to be that. It used to be
they let you on it and then a couple of
hours they ban you. So, yeah.
mad at it.
They fear different opinions.
Nah, not at all.
And then the mod will like message me
saying, "Oh, PJ, are you still being an
insult?" And then I always reply, "Oh,
are you still being a sad little virgin
mod that ain't got a life outside of
Reddit?" And then uh because that is
pretty sad, isn't it? to to sit on a
website and mod it all day.
Having to mod a site all day,
that is [ __ ] sad. Yeah.
That's why whenever I speak to someone
on Reddit, I try to get their Instagram.
Yeah. I try to get the Insta cuz uh
Mad. So, I've got to get another device
to be able to go on Reddit now.
But you shouldn't go on Reddit because
it's addicting because you'll go on like
dating advice, right? And someone will
like talk about something and then
you'll disagree with it and then you
want to and I'd get the urge to like
message them and show them my
experiences and stuff. So, that's why
it's like it's just addicting. Red is
Yeah, it is addicting to be fair. Yep. Oh man.
I'm not getting numbers.
I'll probably get like four tomorrow. Five. Yeah. But
what if I don't post anything?
What if I don't post anything?
Yeah, Reddit is addicting though. Definitely is.
But I'm going to wear my smart clothes tomorrow anyways.
Yeah. A lot of people get banned on
Reddit though. A lot of people get banned.
The the mods fear different opinions, don't they?
Yeah, they do.
Have you done a football bot tomorrow?
I hope mine comes in right no draw.
Hopefully it does. Eh,
but I think one will draw to be honest. [Music]
Nah, Reddit is full of keyboard warriors.
They are full of keyboard warriors cuz
no other site bans you. Not YouTube, not
Instagram, not Facebook. It's only
Reddit. It's only Reddit that bans
people like that
because they have to feel in control
because they can ban you. You can't do
anything about it. It's all a power
thing. Whether you want to admit it or
not, it is a power thing.
It's all about being in control.
you know, that's what it is. So, yeah.
And the mods are creepy little keyboard warriors. They're creeps.
Yeah, the mods ad. Yeah, they've got no
life. They're little cryb babies.
They're little cryb babies. It's a
website designed to piss you off.
Yeah, it's a website designed to piss you off.
I'm going to brush my teeth in a minute
cuz I've drunk some coke. So, yeah.
Yeah. [ __ ] losers. It's a loser job.
Yeah. Ban me. Ban someone that's got different opinions.
Sados. Imagine sitting on a [ __ ]
website all day modding it.
You couldn't pay me any amount of money
to do that. That is sad as [ __ ]
That is sad.
You couldn't pay me any money to do
that. That is sad as [ __ ]
Yeah, that is sad. Very sad. [Music] What? What about to sleep? Big
stuff to do tomorrow.
Stop ahead tomorrow as well. Oh, one second. [Music]
What needs to do more often?
What version needs to do more often?
Anyone [ __ ] teeth? Yep. Oh,
you know what, Acuben? You're going to
get to um you're going to get to um
90, right? And you're going to realize
that defending women never got you
anywhere in life. And you're never
getting that time back.
Never getting that time back, mate. Never.
Never ever ever ever ever mad. [ __ ] madness.
Feel bad for you, man. I really do.
has to be said. E, you never.
Yeah, I should get some numbers tomorrow.
Well, I definitely will get numbers.
I ain't approached for ages. It might
feel a bit weird the first one.
Time for some more bad experiences
tomorrow. Ain't it aubans?
Some more bad experiences with women. Yeah, tomorrow.
Want to do a few approaches before I
meet my sister. So, I'll be going there
a bit more early.
We're going a bit earlier.
If you get one
I'll never get. Pretty sure I've been
with more women than you have. Pretty
sure I've been on more dates than you have. No.
I think I've been with more women than
you have, bro. Not to sound immature, I
think I've had sex more times than you
have with people that weren't escorts.
More of a chance than you. And I've also
been with more women than you, as
immature as that sounds. But you don't
see me defending them and licking their asses.
I've had more women than you. But let me
tell you something. Defending women is
never going to make women like you. I
know I'll never get through to these
white you you know you white knights but
yeah of course you do. Yeah. How's core
money but you on this community. Strange
house call money.
But you said I'd be tasting something I
would never get that I will never get.
But I've been with more women than you have.
Way more than you would ever have.
money, car, and a house, but you've
ended up on here. Mad, it is strange.
You wouldn't be on a community like this
from the time you wake up to the time
you go to bed. Cuz when I was when I was
off of YouTube for nine days, whenever
somebody was live, I'd click on it for
like a minute maximum and I'd see who
was on there and it would be the same
people. And I'm thinking, hold on. If
these people have got all of this money
and this fantastic life, why are they on
here every day from the time they wake
up to the time they go?
That seems odd, isn't it? Why they'd
waste their time and life on here? I'm
coming off this community soon. I really
really am coming off here soon.
[ __ ] all idiots on here.
So why are you saying I'm chasing
something I will never get when I've
been with more women than you have? Can
you explain that one? You know,
been with more women
than you would ever get.
That's not even me just saying that.
That's me being real. 100%.
Yeah, my football bet and
my haircut yesterday.
So, I don't do any of them things today.
No, you haven't been with more women
than me. Nowhere near more women than
me. No, you have not.
No, you have not been with more women
than me. No way. No. No. No. No. No. No.
No way. Even excluded escorts. No. No.
No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No.
No. No. Not a [ __ ] chance in a not a
chance in a million years. If you had
really been with that many women, you
wouldn't be resorting to white knighting.
You wouldn't resort to white knighting?
Uh, yes, I have had a girlfriend and
I've also had plenty of chances to be in
relationships. Again, same old
girlfriend argument and you're going to
get the same old answer. You say the
same thing and you're going to get the
same old answer. So, I don't know why
you keep bringing it up. I have had a
girlfriend and I've also had m and I've
also had multiple chances to be in
relationships. A girlfriend is an
individual. It is not all women. This is
what I've had to explain to nonslegs a
few times. A girlfriend is an individual
person. So if you have had a girlfriend,
that does not mean you know more more
about women than me. That is an individual.
Which is why my community post got four
thumbs up cuz they're four legit people,
not [ __ ] 12 simps. You understand?
Yeah. Cuz I just say it.
So, also having a girlfriend is an
individual person. I didn't if you know
that. That's an individual. That's not
like like nonsex. Uh trying to say, "Oh,
he I didn't know more women than him
then and I do than I do now." I said, "I
knew more women than you then and I
absolutely know more women now, even
though I'm younger than you." Yes, I
have. Yes, I do. And yes, I have been
with more women than you. An individual
woman is not all women. You know,
just because you've been in a in a
relationship, that doesn't mean you know
more. I've been traveling the country up
and down for years, mate. I've met many,
many, many, many women, and they're all
the same. They are generally all the
You having one girlfriend does not change that.
And I don't know why you think it would change that. So
that's not even really a life
experience. Being in a relationship is not exactly
a life experience really.
So it's funny when you get these people
that have had a girlfriend. They seem to think
you know it's it it's not a necessity.
Acubins and again I repeat myself. Yes,
I have had one and it's not a necessity.
Having a girlfriend is not a necessity.
Why would that be crazy? It's not a
necessity. It's barely a life experience.
Why do you care if I had a girlfriend or
at 28? Again, obsessed with other
people's lives. It's not a necessity.
So, why would it be crazy if I've never
had a girlfriend at 28? Let's just say
for argue argument sake, I've never had
a girlfriend at 28. I've been with more
women than you. And having a girlfriend
is not a necessity.
It's not having one over on someone.
Especially when I've said about a
million times, I've been in chances to
be in relationships multiple multiple
times. You know, I've said that and you
somehow seem to think that's having one
over on someone. It's not a life experience
like at all.
So madness. [ __ ] madness.
Why would it be crazy?
What I find crazy is you people are
middle age and you can't get off of
YouTube. You sit on YouTube from the
time you wake up to the time you go to
bed and you want to talk about not
having a girlfriend at 28. Look at your
own lives before judging other people.
Yeah. It's not making me feel better. I
know better because it is the truth. I
have been with more women than you.
That's why you feel the need to white
knight. It doesn't make me feel better.
I don't need to make myself feel better.
I know the truth. I have been with more
women than you have. More than you, more
than non legs, more than J. Yes, I
[ __ ] well have. What do you think
I've got up? What do you think I got up
to in four years of being on three grand
a month for not working? What do you
think I was I was getting up to? You
clearly don't get women because if you
got women, you wouldn't white night.
It's [ __ ] obvious. The only people
that white knight are men that never
been with women or can't get women. Simple.
They're the only people that do it. So,
and even if I proved I had a girlfriend,
you'd say I didn't have a girlfriend.
You know, you're obsessed with other
people's lives. This is what I was
telling you about earlier.
You know what I mean? You're obsessed
with other people's lives. Look at your own lives.
Sat on YouTube in your 40s, can't get
off, and you want to talk about not
having a girlfriend. Look at your own lives.
Sat on YouTube lonely. Probably most of
you are virgins, even though you don't
want to admit it, but that's another thing.
Yeah, of course you do, man. You got all
of these things, but you can't get off
of YouTube. Yeah, man. Very believable.
And just because you have a girlfriend,
it doesn't mean you know more about
women than me. Which is why I got four
thumbs up. Having a girlfriend is an
individual person. Cuz let's face it,
you'd still find reasons to hate. I
could be a millionaire. I could be a
relationship. You'd still find a reason
to hate. This is why I'm coming off
here. Cuz you're all idiots. You're all
[ __ ] idiots on here, you know?
All you're all [ __ ] idiots. You
really are idiots. And only idiots stay
on this place. Really, that's what it is. You know,
no, I just don't lick women's asses cuz
I'm not a white knight. I'm not a white
knight like you defending women cuz I'm
not a loser.
I don't defend women cuz I'm not a
loser. You know what I'm saying? Yeah.
Nope. I've been off of YouTube
for days. You people can't take a day
off of YouTube. I think that's more of a
problem than somebody not having a
girlfriend at 28, even though I have had
one. Than people that can't get off of
YouTube has saved their life. It's all
they have. Literally, if this app if
this app closed down tomorrow, you'd be [ __ ]
You would actually be [ __ ] because
it's all you have. Literally all you
have is YouTube. Like that. That isn't
me even like chatting [ __ ] That is me
being for real. Without this app and
self projecting and obsessing, you'd
have [ __ ] all. Literally. That's the
truth. It is. It is the truth. You know,
I'm not a loser. I don't need to defend
women. Only losers do that. You know,
defending women for the sake of it. No,
no, no, no. This is all you people have.
I listen. Okay. I can take a day off of
YouTube. You can't.
I can take a day off of YouTube. You
people can't. That's been proven. So,
that argument is [ __ ] because I've
taken weeks off of YouTube, days off of
YouTube. You can't take a day. It's all
you people have.
It's all you people have.
No, that's you people. That's already been proven.
Also, another thing is when people come
off of YouTube
for like a week, you start wondering why
haven't they commented? Why haven't they
gone live? You start typing. You start
wondering this [ __ ] But again, this
points to the fact that you think
everyone's got the same life as you
people. You think something would have
happened to them because they can take a
day off of YouTube and you people can't.
It all it all stems from self projecting
with you people, you know.
Yeah, you're fantasist. You don't make
no money. You ain't got no car. You
ain't got no house. You're a fantasist.
A lot of you on here are fantasists.
My life is is not as bad as you your
lives, mate. You people don't even leave the house,
mate. My life is not not as bad as yours,
mate. I don't want to be like you people
when I'm in my 30s and 40s, you know?
Like you people here have got the worst
life. Trust me. Like you can't leave
your house. You ain't got no money. You
ain't got no friends and all of these.
And bear in mind when I'm saying these
things to you. Bear in mind, I have
proved all of these things. You don't
need to know how much I make a month.
It's none of your business. And it's
none of your business how much money I
have either. Again, focus on your own
[ __ ] life, which is what you're
referring to. No, no, no. You, you
people have really, really got [ __ ] lives.
Most of you probably can't even leave
the house due to anxiety.
You sit on here every day
self-projecting because you ain't got no life.
Nothing but YouTube. And it's and it's
and and that's the truth. That is
literally the truth. Without YouTube and
bouncing off other people's lives,
you know, you're insecure people that
ain't got a life. That's what you are.
Depressed, insecure people that ain't
got a life. Yeah.
And that's it.
You've never been laid. [ __ ] a
girlfriend. You've never even had sex.
I'd say [ __ ] half of these people on
here were [ __ ] virgins. If not most,
to be honest with you.
Most of these people on here are probably virgins.
Sad low lives. Yeah,
that's what you people are. Sad low lives.
That's the truth.
Yeah, man. You're Bro, yeah. You'd
rather rob than claim benefits coming
from someone that's on benefits. You're
probably on benefits yourself. Self
projecting. That's what you people do.
I'm coming off this community soon.
You're all idiots. You're all [ __ ]
idiots. You're an idiot. Hugh's an
idiot. You're all idiots, you know.
But make sure you remember me when
you're on your deathbed, right? And you
and and and you think to yourself, all
of that time you wasted defending women
and none of them like you. And think of
how much of a waste of time it was.
And and just think of me when you do that.
How many women you defended and they
still don't like you and they're still
not going to give you sex. [ __ ] mad. Yeah.
Yeah. Okay, I will. Why can't you? Why
can't you just show me your car now? Why
can't you show me your car now? You know,
I don't know why you care if someone's
on benefits or not.
Again, are you insecure about your own life?
I don't know why you care what people
claim, what people don't claim.
It seems like you're very insecure about
your own life. That's the vibe you're giving off.
I don't give a [ __ ] who's on benefits,
who works, who's got more than me, less
than me. You seem to be very obsessed.
It's It's almost as if you're insecure
and you need to compare yourself to feel better.
It's [ __ ] quite sad, to be honest with you.
It really, really is quite sad.
Why do you care if someone's on benefits
or not on benefits?
Why are you comparing yourself to
someone on benefits, though? I don't understand.
I don't understand that. Really, really
you're insecure about your own life.
It's obvious. And half of you want
benefits yourselves. Even though you
don't want to admit it, there's no way
you can be on here the amount of times
you are if you working.
>> Yeah, I generally think you people need
to get a life.
Uh you're you're paying for people
benefits. Uh I doubt you I doubt you are
paying for a specific person's benefit.
I I don't think you really really are. I
don't think you really really really are
paying for a specific person's benefit.
I really really don't think you are,
mate. I really don't think you are. And
okay, what about the what about paying
for the royal family? What about paying
for police officers that half of them are nons?
You don't mention that.
It goes on Nazi police officers. It goes
some of it goes to the royal family.
You've got no problem with that. You got
no problem with that, mate.
Mate, your little small income that you
get from working does not pay a specific
person's benefits. It all goes into a
fund. You are paying less than 0.000000001 person.
Your tax goes to [ __ ] Nazi police
officers, the royal [ __ ] family. Yeah,
but you got no problems paying for
these, do you? No. No. No. I don't call
the police. I hate the police. No, wrong
channel. I hate the police.
I was actually arguing with um a woman
the other day on a police documentary
where this they were um trying to um
these two officers were trying to get
this black guy down and they were
struggling. And she was like, "Oh, why
didn't people help?" I said I would
watch it. I hate police. They're pigs. I
[ __ ] hate pigs. So, no, I wouldn't
call them. No. No, I wouldn't, mate.
Even when my phone got stolen. So,
anyways, why have you got no problems
paying for the royal family and pigs?
You got no problem with that. But no,
you seem to think you're better than
people on benefits because 0.00001%
of your money goes onto that
But yeah, you think you're so much, you
know, cuz we don't see we don't see
people like the side men moaning about
paying for people on benefits or any
kind of celebrity. It's only the broke
people that work that's got a problem
with it. It's only the broke people that
work. We don't see rich people or secure
people moaning about paying for people on benefits.
No one. Not even people in real life,
but you people on YouTube that are on
benefits yourselves have a big problem with it.
You know why is that?
Tell me why that is. Huh? Madness. [ __ ] madness. [Music]
Virgin boy skin in your little bed sit
with no bed, no money in it. Now, I'm
glad you've come here, right? Because
you was talking about uh uh people being
uh skintot, whatever. And you was
telling me uh that I needed to meet
Monty cuz I said I was going to meet
Monty. Now, what did you do when I was
in your area three times?
You ran to the police screaming you
weren't a fighter. Don't you dare sit in
your council beds sit with no bed in it
and try and tell me to start meeting
people, son. Cuz I take [ __ ] offense
to that, mate.
I take [ __ ] offense to that. Don't
sit there in your skint caps out of
London beds trying to [ __ ] get me to
[ __ ] meet people when you couldn't
even come out when I was in your shitty
little virgin area. Cuz that I've got a
problem with. That I've got a [ __ ]
problem with, mate. I'm the same man
that had you stop going to Leighton
Stone for about a month. Remember that? No teeth.
Do you remember that? No teeth.
No. No mate, you don't, do you? Cuz you
got selective memory.
No. Oh, do you remember nons reported me
to the police? This is exactly why I'm
coming off this community. I'm going to
leave you low lives um to it in a couple
of days after my birthday and [ __ ] I
won't be back on here to be honest.
Uh only this community has got the um
capability to give people brain damage.
Little lowife little weirdos.
Uh I reported him because the solicitor
and the police was telling me to report
him. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's not selected
by me. The police and the court was
telling me to do it, so I took their advice.
So yeah, I was doing it to save my own ass.
Anyways, you didn't mention what about
the police that you pay for. What about
the royal family?
>> No, my neighbor didn't stop anything.
The only reason I've not done anything
to my neighbor is because the sake my
mom lives here. Get your facts right. I
left this house before I had a problem
with the neighbor. No one ever ran me
out of my area, mate. Nobody ever ran me
out of my area, right? My mom kicked me
out before any of that stuff even
happened. So, stop talking [ __ ]
Nobody has ever run me out of my area
like I ran you out of yours even though
I'm not your neighbor. No. No. No. Not at all.
Not at all. At all. at all. So stop
talking [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah. The only one
that got run out of [ __ ] their their
area is you.
You know that little skint virgin out of London
living with no Betty cuz you can't
afford a bed. And anyways, show me that
14 grand now. Show me that 14k now. Not
from [ __ ] 10 years ago, mate.
You know. No, no, no, no, no. You went
running to the police.
screaming how you weren't a fighter. So
whatever you want to say, right?
Whatever you want to say, mate, it's
it's stupid cuz you went to the police
screaming that you earn a fighter. You
can come online and act at the big [ __ ]
You can do that all you want. Anyone can
do that. But you went to the police
running, screaming for mercy.
Do you know what I mean? Show me that 14
grand. Show me that 14 grand now. I'll
let you up. Show me that 14 grand now,
mate. We all know your [ __ ] skin,
right? When I showed you that £5.7
grand, you couldn't even [ __ ] show £800.
You was like sucking your dad's dick to
try and get money cuz your skin you like.
And even then, you still couldn't even
show £800. You [ __ ] skin bastard
trying to call me skin on your shitty
little virgin channel. I've got more
money than you will ever have. I've got
better clothes than you would ever have.
More life. I've got a bed and more money
than you would ever have. Don't you
[ __ ] dare sit there on on your,000 a
month. Don't sit there on your,000 a
month [ __ ] money trying to tell me.
Yeah. Okay. Do do a video do a video
right now showing it. Do a video right
now talking showing it. Go on. Go on. Go
and do it on your channel cuz we know
what you're like trying to get police
involved and [ __ ] Go do it on your
channel right now and talk. We'll wait for you
and and then try to and then you're
trying to say Hold on. You're trying to
say that I got expelled from school or
something. Bro, you stopped going to
college because people thought you were
gay and then you kept saying Sherlock
Cole's hot. Sher Cole is attractive.
Sherlock Cole's hot. He doesn't win and
you don't win either, you little [ __ ]
virgin. Yeah. He doesn't win and you
don't win. Somebody that's 31 in a bed
sit with no bed with no money doesn't
win anything. And anyone off this
community knows that.
He has never won anything. The only
thing he's won is me making him go to the police.
The only thing he wins is running to the
police screaming that he's not a
fighter. That's the only win he's ever
had. getting run out of his area by
[ __ ] me. That virgin [ __ ] has never run anything.
13. Bro, listen. 13,000 is nothing. It's
no amount of money. Anyways, show the
money now. Go on vid. Do a video right
now talking and showing the money.
Quiet over it. I didn't cry over it. 30
grand is nothing. Why would I cry over 13 grand?
Do you remember when you were saying
Chevro car was attractive to fit in? You
didn't want to feel left out. I've got
my mo my microphone fixed, by the way,
so I can screen record.
Saying it to fit in. You didn't want to
feel left out, you little copycat. And
then you're copying my [ __ ] holiday
and all of that. You know what I'm
saying? Copying my holiday, little copycat.
You said she's attractive to fit in. You
wanted to fit in, Lea.
You literally wanted to fit in with the
crowd. You didn't want to feel left out
cuz of what people in the college were
saying about you.
Do you remember you can't even spell her
name right, you [ __ ] You didn't want
to feel left out. She's [ __ ] ugly and
I've had more women than you and I've
never had to resort to disabled. And
also your your whole channel is
basically convincing yourself that I'm a
virgin like you. You don't believe I've
had sex with anybody. What? Why? Why
didn't you believe the escort story?
Why didn't you believe the escort story?
I mean, that's a pretty believable
thing. It's because you're a virgin and
you've never had it. And you're never
going to be happy until I admit I'm a
virgin like you. But I'm not going to do
it. You're not going to bully me into
admitting that I'm a virgin like you and
you can do community post and you can do
this and you can do that but face facts.
I'm not a virgin like you and I've had
one night stands and I've never had to
resort to disabled like you.
Not everyone has your life. I'm not a
virgin like you. I promise I don't ever
be a virgin like you.
You know you know. Yeah,
bro. I'm on Bell. Yeah. And I'm still
talking [ __ ] about him. I'm still
talking [ __ ] about him. And And he's not
going to do anything about it. I've got
him doing videos and community posts to
me every day. I've already won. I'm
living in his head. I'm living in his
head. He goes on about me every single
day. Even when I'm not on YouTube,
he's going on about me. I've won him.
I've won you. And there's nothing you
can do about it. I've won you. Won him.
I live in your head rent free. Rent free.
I'm living in your head rent free. Bell
won Nobel. I'm the winner. All of this
time that you've wasted on me over the
years and I've not even wasted 10% as
much. I'm living in your head just like
I'm living in your head. Acubans sad
bastard keyboard warrior with no life on
benefits trying to talk about other
people when you want benefits yourself.
You skin bastard.
You know, simple.
Bro, listen. You ran to the police
because you got bullied. That's not
winning. Anybody on this community would
say the same thing. You ran to the
police cuz you got bullied. That's not a
W. Only virgins like Acubans would think
that you've won. Only little sad,
spasticated people like him think that's
a win. Everybody in the real world knows
that you did not win. You ran to the
police harassing them, screaming and
crying that you're not a fighter. Nobody
would think that you've won but these
spastics. That's not a win. You know,
that's exactly what a loser would do.
Which is funny because you use the word
loser a lot. You are the biggest loser
going. You got owned so badly on
YouTube. So badly you couldn't take no
more. you was that much of a loser that
you had to run to the police again. Not
a win. Only spastics like Acubans would
think that you've won. I have literally
went to your area. I've made you scared
to come out. I made you stop going to
events and you've done nothing.
You've done absolutely nothing about it.
You think anyone cares about you going
to the [ __ ] police?
Nobody cares. Nobody gives a [ __ ]
Acubins, that's not going to happen.
You've got too much anxiety. You can't
leave your house. Spastics like you
can't leave the house.
Acubans, spasticated people like you
can't leave the house with without a
appropriate adult. So, I don't think
you're going to be going to any court
case. You little spasticated low life on
YouTube, which is what you people are.
Which is exactly why I'm coming off
shortly after my birthday cuz you all
spasticated low lives and that's what
you are. That's literally what you are.
We can see your common virgin boy.
Skin in the bed sit with no bed, no
money in it.
A few turn up. Yeah. Okay, bro. Life
laughs at you every single day. Skin on
YouTube, no money. That's why every time
I say this stuff to you, you know I'm
right. Skin sat on YouTube pretending
you work when we all know that you
people on YouTube from the time you wake
up to the time you go to bed.
You know, simple. Because you're sad
little lowife spasticated bastards,
which is why a lot of people even don't
come back. Bro, life has laughed at you.
You're on benefits pretending that
you're not. Like you literally think
that you've got this life that you don't
have a partner, a car. You've got [ __ ]
all. We've seen your YouTube activity. I
don't know how many times people have to
keep proving it to you. You're sad,
spasticated, depressed losers. That's
what you are, bro. And I'll do that 8
day thing again if you want. This time I
will screen record it. My mic's working
out. I had to get it fixed. Sad,
spasticated people that have achieved
nothing in life. And guess what? People
like you acubans, let me tell you
something. You're too old now. You got
no hope. There's no going back. You're
not 27. You're not 28. You're not 29.
You can't change it now. You're [ __ ]
Sad little middleage [ __ ] losers.
[ __ ] [ __ ] That's what you are in
this community. You're [ __ ] mongos.
Yeah. It's the truth that I spirit about
you and you know it as well.
[ __ ] fat ugly people. They ain't got a life.
Get off of YouTube for a day. Come on.
Nah, you can't do Can't do that. I'm 28
and never had a girlfriend. I'm 28 and I
have had a girlfriend. Try again. You're
in your 40s and you've never had sex.
Pathetic. And I love when I say stuff
about you. You know that I'm right.
That's why you get triggered. You can
keep saying I've not had a girlfriend
all you want, but I have. And having a
girlfriend is not a necessity. It's not a necessity,
bro. You're like 48 and you've never had
sex again. You're laughing at yourself.
Everything you do, you bounce off of
your own life like this. Yeah. You're on
benefits. You got no life. You can't
leave your house. But you hate other
people that are apparently on benefits.
Huh? Yet you're on benefits yourself.
You can't leave your house. You got no
money yourself. You're virgins. But then
you bounce off of other people's lives.
Like I generally think, yeah, you living
in this fairy tale land, you seem to
think that that's you having a better
life than someone.
Yeah, you've got kids. You keep telling
yourself that. You keep telling yourself
that you got kids. I don't think you've
got kids. Listen, I could go on a on a
community right now and pretend that
I've got these things. It doesn't make
it any true. You're a 48-year-old
virgin. This is why you people do what
you do on here. It's because you've got
nothing. People that have got kids,
people that have got a life, don't do
this. You're sad, spasticated losers.
Stop talking and start showing what
you've got. Right? I don't want to see
your [ __ ] kids. Show us your house
and show us your car. Go on. Instead of
sat there talking about a 28-year-old
that's got a better life than you, cuz
you like Cuz a lot of you people on
here. Yeah. You like to sit here and
talk about people's ages. Bro, a
28-year-old has got a better life than a
40-year-old [ __ ] loser that ain't got
a life. And that's why every time I say
this [ __ ] about you, you've got nothing
else. You've got nothing to say back,
bro. You've got nothing in life. You're
middle-aged. You're a loser. You come on
YouTube every day to feel special about
your imaginary life cuz you've got
nothing. You've got [ __ ] all. You've
been on here for almost 4 hours with me chatting.
You ain't got no kids. You ain't got no
life. Stop talking [ __ ]
Do you know what I'm saying?
Another thing, nonslegs, please don't go
to Thailand next cuz I'm going next
month. Please don't start going Thailand
cuz I know you like to copy my holidays
and you said, "Oh, why am I going to
copy some big nose holiday? some [ __ ]
rat looking [ __ ] with no teeth [ __ ]
copying every single holiday that I go
on. Every time I go on LA, we got some
[ __ ] skin skinny lanky rat copying my holidays.
Every time I go on, we got this skin
ugly bastard rat face with no teeth,
right? [ __ ] copy my ways. Don't you
go Thailand next. Don't you [ __ ] go
Thailand next. I'm telling you. I'm
going to stop telling people where I'm going.
I'm going to stop telling people where
I'm going. Yeah. Before trying to talk
about a 28-year-old, look at your own
[ __ ] virgin life sat on YouTube white
nighting women. You've probably never
even had sex, you [ __ ] loser.
Uh mate, I' mate, I have had a
girlfriend and she never had disabilities.
And my girlfriend never had disabilities
like yours. And all of the women that I
can talk, all of the women that I've
been with can talk.
You having a disabled girlfriend does
not mean you know more women than me.
That's an individual person. And yes, I
can leave the country anytime I want.
Yes, I can. And I have done. Yes, I
have. I've got my passport. I haven't
had to surrender my passport. So, stop
making up stories. Yes, I can. And I already did.
You know, your girlfriend's [ __ ]
disabled, you [ __ ] [ __ ] You're
you're sat there calling me a [ __ ]
incel when you have to [ __ ] target
disabled girls cuz you can't get nothing
normal. You're so socially awkward that
you can't even go to normal events.
That's why you target the disabled.
Typical incel. Isn't it funny how you're
trying to call me an incel? I've been
with more women than you. I've had more
sex than you. I've never had to target
disabled like you in my life. Only an
incel has to target disabled women
because they can't get anything. You are
the little [ __ ] incel. You [ __ ]
skint [ __ ] And let me tell you
something, right? If I was 10 Guinnesses
[ __ ] down, I still would never resort
to something disabled like that. This is
where all of this comes from. You've got
fragile ego. You have got a fragile ego,
right? That's what you've never had sex.
You're still a virgin, right?
Yeah. Acubins, you're a middle-aged
loser. [ __ ] a 28-year-old. Look at your
40-year-old virgin self that can't get
off of YouTube. [ __ ] the 28-year-old
that's got hope. [ __ ] look at a
40year-old that can't get off of
YouTube. The virgin.
You don't like it when I speak facts
about you, do you? You know, bro, you
haven't had sex. You can't have sex with
a disabled girl. You're not going to
convince me, right, that you've had sex
with a disabled girl? It ain't
happening. You've And also another thing
is you want to talk about [ __ ] You
want to talk about you you Okay, show us
this 50k car then. Show us this 50k car.
You want to talk about Right. Hold on.
What was it? You you made me a about I
said that you didn't have sex with Aisha
booty because I was jealous. Huh? No,
because you said that you [ __ ] someone
on a park bench. No, you did not have
sex with somebody on a park bench.
You've never had sex in your life. You
lanky virgin [ __ ] You from the time I
met you to now, you've never stuck your
dick in anything. And you certainly did
not stick your dick in a disabled woman.
You've never had sex in your [ __ ] life.
In your life. It's okay to be a virgin.
There's nothing wrong with being a virgin.
There is nothing wrong with not having
it. Being a 31year-old virgin, there's
nothing wrong with that. You're not
going to convince me that you had sex
with a disabled girl. It's not possible.
The police would get involved. The
police would literally get involved.
The police would literally get involved,
mate. You can't have sex with a disabled
girl. It never happened.
It never ever ever happened.
Yeah, it never happened, mate.
50k coin assets. Is that in your dreams, mate?
To get rejected by escorts. Again, I've
already told you I've been with more
women than you. Isn't it? Every time I
tell you something, you ignore it
because you know it's the truth. You
You people are fat and ugly sat there on
YouTube ain't got no life talking about
a 28-year-old that's better looking than
you, that's got more money than you,
that's been with more women than you,
but yet you're laughing at me. This is
the This is the badest thing is you're
laughing at a 28-year-old that's got
more in life than you. Cuz I'm not sat
on YouTube like a low life every day.
Can't get off it. And you've already
proven what you are.
You know, sad middleage [ __ ] losers.
And you know it's the truth.
Sloppy seconds. You've never stuck your
dick in her. There's no sloppy seconds
to be had. There's no sloppy seconds to
be had. You've never had sex with her.
You're a typical virgin. Why? How can I
get your sloppy seconds when you didn't
have sex with her in the first place?
You literally did not have sex with her
in the first place. There's no sloppy
seconds to be had. Virgin boy.
Virgin boy. There's no sloppy seconds to
be had. You've never had sex.
You've literally never had sex. You've
made up the sex stories. Not me. You
even lied before saying that you got a
[ __ ] by [ __ ] what's her name?
Hannah Hannah Nolles. No, you did not.
You've never had sex.
You have literally never had sex in your
[ __ ] life. I have proved I've had
sex. I put a porno out there.
You know what I'm saying? You've never
had sex. You're not convincing me, mate. You know.
Yeah. I don't want to contact I don't
want to [ __ ] contact them. What the
[ __ ] And they're not your sloppy
seconds either. You've never had sex
with them. You're still a virgin. Virgin
what? Skinting his little bed sick with
no bed, no money in it.
No. No, mate. You've never had sex.
Never. Ever. Ever. That's why you
convince yourself that I've never had
sex with Izzy, Morgan, the escorts. It's
not one or two people. You've done it
with multiple people.
And I'm not and and the Morgan thing,
I've explained it a million times over
and over and over again, and you still
you still don't listen because you
compare it to a you and Britney situation,
your first [ __ ]
Um, I have had a girlfriend
uh and she wasn't disabled.
Yeah. And do you know what's even more
crazy? Someone in their 40s talking
about a 28-year-old.
Yeah. I have a I have had a girlfriend.
I've been with more money than both of
you losers combined. I've had more women
than both of you losers combined. That's
crazy. And my girlfriend wasn't
disabled. I've never been with a
disabled girl. And yes. Yes. I've had
one girlfriend and I'm saying that
you're a virgin and he's a virgin. I'm
calling you both virgins. Yes, I am. Cuz
you are. You're a virgin and he's a
[ __ ] virgin. And you can't prove
otherwise. Just shut the [ __ ] up. You
are a virgin and so is and so is he a
virgin. Just like you acubans sat on
benefits. No woman, no life, no money
say that you drive a car when you've got
assets only in your virgin dreams.
Because again, if you had all of these
things, you wouldn't be on a community
like this. There's no way you're going
to justify how you've got a car, you've
got money, but you're on YouTube. You
ain't even going to try justify it.
You've got [ __ ] all and you've got no
hope as well. See the difference between
me and you, Accuban, say we was in the
same position. Yeah. Say we're exactly
the same two people. Let's just say me
and you are the same two people, right?
You're in your 40s. I'm 28. And you know
I'm right about you. That's why you're
saying these things because you know I'm
right about you. Every time I I I pull
the trigger on you virgins, you go mad
because I'm so right about you people on
here. I'm right about you people. You
don't have a girlfriend. You don't have
kids. You're on benefits. That's why
you're false laughing because you know
I'm right about you. Every time I say
stuff about you people that's right,
you're laughing because you know it's
the truth and that's why you're covering
it up. See Reddit, why can't I get a
girlfriend? Woo! Pull the trigger. I'm
right about you. This is how I know I'm
right about you. I'm right about you 40y
old virgins. I'm right about you.
Simple. I am right about you people.
Anyways, back to the Morgan thing,
right? Anyways, uh, okay, Virgin Boy,
you messaged somebody that I met once
knowing that you was going to get the
answers that you wanted because I was
[ __ ] with them. Yeah, they were
[ __ ] with me. Then I [ __ ] with
them. And you knew that you was going to
get the answers that you wanted. Again,
not a you and Britney situation.
Not a you and Britney situation.
You know, not a you and Britney
situation. Oh my [ __ ] god. He only
has his sister to go up. Self
projecting. I've shown me with friends
multiple times. Anyways, let me put the
link up for you to show what you've got.
Anyways, Acuans, right? Let me put a
link up. You can show us what you've got.
Right. Show us your car. Show us your
assets that you don't have. You 40 old
virgin. Come on. Right. Come on. Show us
all of your assets. Show us your car.
Come on. Show us everything that you've
got. Come on. Show us that you've got
all this money that you're not on
benefits. Let's laugh together. Come on,
you little [ __ ] Come on.
Right. And I've explained the Morgan
situation about a million times, but you
want people to keep explaining it to
you. Show us that. Show us your friend.
Show us your money. Show us your woman,
loser. Come on. Come on. Show us your
ugly face. Show us why you on YouTube
every day. Come on, you ugly bastard.
Let's laugh together. Come on. Come on.
The link is up there. Come on.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. I'm not going to be going live in
the morning. I'm busy tomorrow. Come on.
Show us what you ain't got. Show us your
little fairy tale world that you ain't
got. Show us your makebelieve woman,
your no money, your no kids, just you in
a bedit in your 40s with nobody. Come
on. Why? Why did does it need to be the
morning? Can you just show us your house
and show us your car? Come on. Come on.
You [ __ ] mter. You [ __ ] ugly [ __ ]
You ain't got nothing. Don't come on my
channel. You [ __ ] ugly [ __ ] on
benefits with nothing to show trying to
talk about me. You ugly ugly [ __ ]
You've been on here for 4 hours now.
You've got the link. You can't come on
due to your anxiety, you little [ __ ]
So don't [ __ ] come on here trying to
tell people who wins. You [ __ ] ugly
[ __ ] You ugly bastard who can't join my
live stream. Yeah. No, I'm not I'm not
tearing. I'm not No tears at all, bro.
You [ __ ] ugly benefit [ __ ] [ __ ]
And what you going to do? You're not
going to join. You can't say nothing to
me. You [ __ ] ugly manta. It only
takes certain muners to sit on this
community all day every day not having a
life. It only takes you months. You ugly
people. Yeah. Well, you don't live in
London. You can't afford to live in
Go on. Yeah. You You don't live in
London, you [ __ ] ugly ma. Shut the
[ __ ] up. You can't afford to live in
London, you [ __ ] spaz. No one in my
city sits behind a keyboard and bees a
[ __ ] like you. No one bees a
montaspastic like you. You don't live in
no London. Join the hangouts now. Join
the hangouts now. Come on. Come on. Show
everyone your ugly face. Let's have a
laugh. Show everybody that ugly virgin
benefit face. Come on. You s little bastard.
You want me
right? So, are you joining or not? Bro,
you're you're not going to anyone's
mom's. Shut up. You're a keyboard
warrior. You're not going anywhere.
You're not going anywhere. Shut up.
Oh my god. You're not going anywhere.
You sad little [ __ ] on benefits in your
40s. You're not going anywhere, mate.
You're not showing your ugly face.
You're not meeting anyone for a fight.
Oh, you're boring.
You're boring, kid.
You don't live in London.
You do not live at Bro, listen. You're
not meeting anyone. Stop trying to get
out of it.
[ __ ] 31 years of age and only can get
disabled girls. What a loser. A [ __ ]
living in a [ __ ] bed [ __ ] with no bed
and no money in it. What a [ __ ]
loser. But then he thinks he can talk about me.
He thinks he can talk about my living circumstances and
me not being in a relationship yet only
targets disabled girls, lives somewhere
that's owned by the council but wants to
talk about me. [Music]
Mad, isn't it?
Practice what you preach, mate.
Okay, then do that. Okay, do that all
you want. You you don't scare anyone
because we've we've heard all of this
before. Oh, I'm coming here. [Music]
Yes, but you've not had sex. But you've
never ever had sex. I'm coming off this
community after my birthday. Anyways,
you people are [ __ ] idiots. You are
absolute [ __ ] mongos on this community.
Absolute [ __ ] mongos.
You're not [ __ ] going anywhere, you
[ __ ] na virgin [ __ ] Like, is there
[ __ ] any point in this [ __ ] anymore?
I don't understand it, bro.
Yeah, because you can't [ __ ] her. You
never have [ __ ] her. You've never
You've never [ __ ] her. You're not
allowed to. She's disabled.
You've not been anywhere near that
disabled girl. Your [ __ ] incel. [ __ ]
sat there calling me an insult when I've
been with more women than you and
they've never been disabled and you're
calling me the inel self projecting.
That is self [ __ ] projecting. That is,
you know. No, I don't want to see
kisses. I want to see actual sex.
I want to see actual sex. Kissing
doesn't mean anything. I want to see actual sex.
something that you you can't do because she's disabled.
You [ __ ] incel [ __ ] Trying to call
me an incel and you can only get
disabled girls, you [ __ ] pratt, you know. Yeah.
Sad little bastards. Sad little self
projectors. I'm coming off this [ __ ]
after my birthday anyways.
>> Okay. Hey, can we see some sex?
All right. I want I want to see sex.
Okay. Can I see some sex, please?
That's right. You can't cuz you got a
broken willie. You're not allowed to
have sex with her.
And anyways, back to the Morgan thing.
You knew you was going to get the answer
that you wanted.
You literally knew that you was going to
get the answer that you wanted, but you
got a little dopamine rush. Oh, it's a
me and Britney situation.
Oh, it's a me and Britney situation.
That's That's what you tell yourself
that it's a you and Britney. You knew
you was going to get the answer that you wanted.
You literally knew you cuz cuz I was
[ __ ] with them because of what they
done. You You literally knew you was
going to get the answer that you wanted.
You You literally knew you did.
You knew you did, mate. You knew you did.
Little [ __ ] fragile ego. Little virgin.
Virgin with a fragile ego. I mean, your
dick doesn't even work properly. I've
seen the X-ray. Do you remember when you
show the X-ray of your dick that was broken?
Do you remember?
You knew damn well that USA was going to
lie about me.
You knew damn well that you weren't
going to get the truth. You made sure of
it. And somehow that's that's you
winning. Somehow that's you winning
because you kn you you knew you was
going to get the answer that you wanted.
You messaged somebody randomly out the
blue asking about sex
and um I mean you you you knew, mate. You know
you you you knew. I don't care what I
don't care what people believe. I don't
care. It's like when I say that you're a
virgin. I don't care about people. I'm
telling you you're a [ __ ] virgin. I
don't care about other people. I'm
telling you what you are cuz I know you
better than you know your [ __ ] self.
So I know you better than you know your [ __ ] self.
You know when you used to talk about
things being socially acceptable. I
don't give a [ __ ] what's socially
acceptable or not. You you diagnose
autistic little [ __ ] I don't care. I
don't give a [ __ ] what's socially
acceptable or not. You autistic little [ __ ]
You know, I don't give a [ __ ] what's
socially acceptable. Your dad [ __ ]
nons up. Your mom's not socially acceptable.
But it's okay because certain states of America
18 and above. 18 and above. It's 18 and
above. It's literally 18 and above.
It's literally 18, mate. I have I've had
a relationship, but it wasn't with a
disabled girl like yours.
I've had a relationship, but she wasn't
disabled like your girlfriend, and she
could actually talk unlike your girlfriend.
You know, I don't date disabled girls.
That's not you winning. I don't know why
you seem to think you dating a disabled
girl somehow means that you're winning.
I don't get it. I really don't get it.
You know, it's [ __ ] insane. It
really, really is. You know, you know,
you [ __ ] [ __ ]
When you gonna lose it, when you gonna pop it.
Nope. Never said that, mate. Never said
that. You need to get laid, you little
incel. You're the [ __ ] incel. Only
[ __ ] going for disabled girls. You
can't call me an incel. I've been with
more women than you have. And I've never
had to target disabled girls like you.
I've never had to target disabled girls
like you. If anyone's an incel, you're a [ __ ] incel.
Think of how many [ __ ] women that you
[ __ ] stalk that I've been with. No,
you're definitely the [ __ ] incel,
mate. Not me. You're definitely
definitely the incel.
You are definitely definitely definitely
definitely the incel, mate. Not someone
that's had more women than you.
Someone that's had more women than you
can't be an incel, mate.
Where's this little spaz gone as well? I
thought he was joining.
[ __ ] mongos. your [ __ ] mongos on here.
All little low life [ __ ] self
projectors ain't got a life.
So when are you people actually going to
get a life? When are you going to get
laid as well? Virgin boy, when are you
going to finally get laid and get off of
YouTube? When you finally going to have
sex for the first time? It'll do you
good. It'll [ __ ] do you good, mate.
You know, when are you gonna finally get
laid and stop convincing people that you
know they're a virgin like you? It'll do
you good? Because trust me, I I can tell
you when you finally lose it, when you
finally finally have sex for the first
time, I can I can tell you, it feels good.
It actually feels good. You need to get
sex. You need to get laid. Trust me, you
you'll love it. You'll [ __ ] love it, mate.
You'll [ __ ] love it. Trust me.
Finally lose it, mate.
When you finally [ __ ] lose it,
did I? When you finally finally pop it.
You finally finally pop it.
Yeah. I can't. By the way, do you want
USA? Is he? By the way, I've got a
number if you want to. Cuz you still
seem to be the one that's obsessed with
her, not me.
You You are the one that seems to be
obsessed with this person that I don't
care about. I mean, I can give you a
number if you want. She might not get
with you cuz you're a skin virgin, but I
mean, you never know. You can get into I
mean, I can give you the number if you
want. I think I've got it. Maybe they've
changed their um number. I'll give you
the number if you want.
You should try it since you're the one
that's so obsessed. Monset,
why don't WhatsApp come up anymore?
I've got the number if you want.
Did you do you want the number?
I've got the number if you want. You
know, you could try since you're so
obsessed with this [ __ ]
Right. What is her name?
Okay. So, it's plus one 774
922 3886 cuz you seem to be very very
very obsessed with this USA is he and
and it's very concerning.
It's very very concerning mate. She
might be the one to take your virginity.
That's if she doesn't does doesn't
doesn't give you something. Oh, sorry.
Oh, that's if she doesn't give you
something first, you know, like um
some sort of STD,
you know. You don't know really. You
know, don't know what people could be
bringing into the country.
Oh, look. You can see my face. I wasn't
expecting that. I've got a beard. You
can't go to bed cuz you're not big,
strong, and Turkish like me.
Say, I've got a cut and stuff. No, it
doesn't matter if you've got a
girlfriend. You You seem to be obsessed
with this USA, is he? You give you a
give you a number if you want.
You know, you can try it. You know,
people don't have to lie about having
sex with people like you do. I've been I
was I had more women in that year than
you had in your whole life. Why do I
need to [ __ ] lie about having sex
with someone? You [ __ ] loser. I'm not
like you, mate.
I'm not like [ __ ] you. You're
obsessed with USA is he knew and damn
well he was going to get the answer that
you wanted as well. You knew you was
going to get the answer that you wanted.
You knew it. You knew you was going to
get the answer that you wanted.
You knew you was going to get the answer
that you wanted.
You're very, very [ __ ] insecure, mate. You know,
I can tell some mad stories about you.
I can tell some mad stories about you, mate. You know,
that you'd probably never told anyone before. You know,
you didn't tell people about your dad's cocaine addiction.
You know, you and you and his cocaine addiction.
Why didn't you tell [ __ ] YouTube
about that? You didn't tell anyone about
when he went to [ __ ] um Norway and
married that woman,
you know, and took on her child. There's
a lot of dark your your family's got a
dark dark past. You know,
your family's got a very, very, very dark past. Yeah.
Yeah. Very, very dark past. Yep.
I know all about your dad.
I know all about your dad, mate. He has
a terrible gambling addiction.
Yeah. He was a brick layer. Uh, you said
that he was scared of flying, but he
went to Germany and his birthday is the
1st of September, which is a day before
my mom's birthday. I remember that. Yep.
I remember that. Um, his name was Mick.
Then he started going off the rails with
uh with the cocaine and obviously that
was a big problem.
And obviously uh
That was a big problem. Yeah, he's his
birthday is the the 1st of September.
Yeah, I remember that. I remember everyone's birthday.
Yeah. Lived in cry then. [Laughter]
Yeah, I remember these things. I
remember these things. Yeah. Your dad
went to Germany. You told me your dad
went to Germany, but he didn't like
flying and stuff. You said that one time
he went on a plane, he actually [ __ ] himself.
Yeah. You said he actually [ __ ] his pants.
I remember that.
Yeah. See, I remember these things. So,
nothing I say is lies.
Nothing I say is lies at all. No.
And when your And when your dad went to
uh your dad lived in Gernzi as well for 5 years.
Yeah. Your dad lived in Gernzi.
Do you remember when your dad lived in Gernzi?
Yeah. You told me some wild stories.
Yeah. I can tell you exactly what
happened when we met. The first time we
met was in Victoria and this undercover [ __ ] police
stopped me and his name was Steve. And
I'm thinking just can't [ __ ] stop me.
Weird. And we shook hands. I think it
was about 6:00 p.m. we met. I remember I
was using my mom's freedom pass.
Yeah, I remember that. That was that was
the first time we met and we took pictures. Yeah,
we took pictures. I remember by like
Travalga Square, London Bridge as well.
We took some pictures. Yeah. And I
remember Dean [ __ ] calling me when I
got back. Yeah, I remember that. Yeah.
And that's when you was telling me all
about your dad
about his dark dark past.
Yes, we did go to London Bridge.
We did go to London Bridge, you
[ __ ] Yes, we did. Do you not remember?
Yeah, but same [ __ ] Westminister,
London Bridge. It's the same [ __ ]
London Bridge. The London Eyes of London
Bridge. That's what I mean. And that's
when you was telling me about your your
dad being a filthy naunt.
That's when you was telling me about your dad.
You you told me a lot of things, mate.
You tell me a lot of things. He was
addicted to roulette. Yeah.
You said he had Parkinson's as well.
You've ordered a Uber. Yeah, of course
you have, mate. This is Terry. This
account by the way, people.
Hello, Terry. Low life. Yeah, this is
Terry by the way people.
You've ordered a Uber. Is that supposed
to scare me or something?
Yeah. You said he was into kids.
No, you said he was addicted to roulette.
No, you you said he was you said he was
addicted to roulette, mate.
In the next 10 minutes, I will end a
live again. No, I won't end the live
again because you don't scare me. Your
little games are boring.
Your games are very, very boring, Terry.
You've been doing it for a very long time now.
Yeah. I remember when you you were
trying to chat up that woman in the
Eminem uh shop and then she rejected you.
She rejected you. Do you remember? That
was the first time we met. Yeah. and she
she rejected you.
Do you remember? And that's absolutely fine.
You know the the member of the staff.
She reject Do you remember? She she rejected you.
She probably saw the acne in your face
or something. I don't know. I don't know
the exact story.
And she she rejected you, didn't she?
She didn't want to know, you know.
She didn't want to know you. You know,
she just didn't want to know.
You know, you ain't got the balls to do cold approach.
I'm going to go live tomorrow and
approach some women. I'm going to wind you up.
I'm going to wind you up tomorrow, mate.
Got some nice smart clothes to wear.
Robert the bear trousers,
turtleneck top, nice blazer. Yeah,
I'm going to I'm going to wind you up.
I'm going to wind you up, mate. You
should meet me tomorrow for some Guinnesses.
Why don't you meet me tomorrow? You can
have some beer by the good old times.
you. When you meet me,
slash your [ __ ] head, mate.
Meet me for a little some little beers and stuff,
but the good old times.
Um, I'm not telling you the exact place,
but I'll be in Tottenham Court Road if
you want to meet.
You bring your girlfriend, too, mate.
I'll give you both a [ __ ] item.
I'll give you both a [ __ ] good item. Yeah,
that's what I'm going to do.
I love you. I love the [ __ ] all of
No, I mean Tottenham Court Road.
No, I mean Tottenham Court Road, mate.
That's what I mean, mate. No. I'm going
Totten Court Road.
That's where I'm going. Oh, look. You
can see my little face.
Yeah. Technical Court Road.
Technical Road, mate.
No. No. No. No. No. Go back. NL
job, mate. Get up. K.
Get a job, mate. Get a [ __ ] job. Get
a [ __ ] job. Get a [ __ ] job. Get a
I've got a football bet on for tomorrow.
I can I can I can do football bets
because I've got I got a job. Yeah, I
got I got me. I got you a job. I got
you. I got You ain't got a [ __ ] job,
mate. I've got a [ __ ] job. You ain't
Yeah, yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Yeah. But guess what? I'll always have
more money than you, Terry. And I can I
can afford a new pair of trainers, unlike you. Sad [ __ ] Yeah.
So, you you beating me tomorrow, virgin boy.
We can go to the O'Neals if you want,
even though I'm banned. But I'll sneak
in. We'll have to get there a bit early
though. But I'll sneak in. Yeah,
we're going to get you laid. We're going
to we're going to get you to finally
lose your virginity, mate.
Once and for all. You know,
Terry, terrible trainers.
Terry's a trap. Terry's a trap.
trying to say to LT, "You're not the one.
You're not the [ __ ] one.
Have a word with yourself, you silly cunt."
I just got to bed soon. I've got to be
up in a [ __ ] couple of hours. Got a long day.
We can't all sit online like you, Terry.
21st of February 1995. H
Does that ring a bell, mate? Does that
Does that ring a bell?
Does that Does that ring a bell to you, mate?
21st of February 1995.
Does that Does that ring a bell, mate?
No, mate. No, no, no.
That's not what I'm talking about, mate. No.
I go to a few different Weather Spoons
to chop the ladies, you know. Yeah.
I met USA Izzy outside the Eminem shop.
She offered me her number. Do you
remember when I put that video up there?
Had you [ __ ] raging in it, son?
You had you [ __ ] raging? Do you remember?
Do you [ __ ] remember?
21st of February, 1995.
I don't know, mate. I don't know what
that could possibly be.
But I'm not sure.
You know what is it? Can you tell me
what that is? 21st of February, 1995. H
What is it?
Come on, tell me. What is it?
It's your birth. It's your date of
It's your date of birth, mate. Isn't it? Yeah.
My birthday in two days. Yeah.
I can't wait.
Can't wait, mate. Can't wait. Yeah. So,
what do you want to do, mate?
No one can be more of among the new terrible trainers.
Can't afford new pair of trainers. Got
run out your area by me. I don't know
how you can still talk [ __ ] when I've
literally come to your area and you
didn't show up.
You little [ __ ] And you didn't even
beat me the first time as well.
No, no, no mate. No m Yeah.
No, no, no.
Virgin boy has never been to Manchester.
Virgin boy has never been to Scotland.
Virgin boy has never been to Wales. I've
been to more places than Virgin Boy. Yeah.
Yeah. Terry, I came to your area and you
didn't show up. No, no, no.
You have to admit, n you're scared of
flying, aren't you?
Yeah. I mean, I'm pretty sure I pulled in Manchester. not
scared of flying in it. Nonsense.
Just admit it. You're scared of flying,
aren't you? That's why you took the Euro store.
No, mate. No. No. You You've never been
to Manchester now, mate. Have you? No.
That's why That's why you took the Euro
store, isn't it? Cuz you got a fear of flying.
You're scared of flying, aren't you, mate?
mate? Cuz why would you take the Euro
store? You don't even live in London.
Why would you go to King's Cross when
you don't live in London, mate? No, no, no.
Why are you scared of flying on sakes?
Why are you scared of flying, mate?
Why Why are you scared of flying, mate? Mhm.
You went all the way to King's Cross
from Kent. That's a bit fishy.
That's a bit fishy, mate. Uh, actually,
no. When I went to when I took the Euro store,
I was living in Strapford
all by myself. So try again, mate.
You're not closer to King's Cross to me, mate. No, mate.
No. So why do you get an airplane?
You're scared of planes.
You scared of big big scary planes.
Big scary planes, isn't it?
Is it the big scary planes?
Mun's legs. Bit scary, aren't they?
Bit bit terrifying,
aren't they, mate? You bit bit worried.
Bit bit worried, mate. You know,
about going on a plane.
You're a bit concerned.
You're a bit,
you know, you're a bit uh bit worried
about it, you know.
Tell us. Tell us. Oh, you a bit worried, bit scared,
bit bit terrified,
bit bit cautious,
bit bit frightened, you know, huh? Nah,
you copied me. You're a copycat.
[ __ ] off. You're a copycat. That's what you are.
Yeah, you're a copycat. You you you went
there cuz I went there. Yeah. No, mate.
How did you find the Euro Star? Quite scary.
Was it quite a scary experience?
Was it quite a terrifying experience for you?
Bit bit scary. Bit uh
bit. You know what?
You know a bit scary. Bit scary for you. Yeah.
Bit bit scary, mate.
Bit bit terrifying for you. Bit scary.
It terrifying. Yeah.
Doesn't matter if it's a train.
You never met you again, did she?
Kenji never met you again, did he? I
wonder why. What happened there? We'd
all love to know.
We'd all love to know, mate.
We'd all love to know.
Yeah, I don't care.
But guess what?
So, you're scared of dogs.
I've got a dog downstairs right now.
You would dare come to this household, mate.
I've actually been on a plane, unlike
you. But you're scared of dogs.
Literally terrified of him.
You can't go anywhere near a dog.
You're scared of dogs.
Scared of dogs, mate.
You're fired of [ __ ] dogs. King, come
up here now.
Come here now, King. This [ __ ]
scared of dogs.
You scared? You scared of dogs, mate?
You're scared of dogs, mate. No, you're
scared of dogs. You're scared of bridges
as well. Yeah. You're scared of heights.
You You're scared of heights, mate.
Scared of heights, mate. Scared of heights.
got a better TV than you as well.
I makes you jealous.
No, mate. You scared of dogs, mate.
Look. Got got better TV than you, mate.
Do you remember when you couldn't look
down Westfield? You can look down.
>> You're scared.
So what? You what? You're never ever
going to what? So you're never going to
go on a plane ever?
So you you're never going to go on a plane? Uh never. Jesus Christ.
Okay. Well, tomorrow we can meet up. We
can either go for a drink or do you want
to do it bad? It's up to you. We can
either go for a drink or we can do or do
you want to do it bad
or do you want to do it bad?
Yeah. Yeah. But you can't go on a plane
though cuz you're scared.
You're not You're scared to go on I've
been on a plane. You've never been on a plane?
Nah. You've never been on one.
Bless you. So, we can go for a drink
tomorrow or we can do it bad. It's up to you. Huh?
Yeah. But you even said before that
people copy each other with the chevel
thing. You said that people You said
that there is people that copy each
other. Didn't you say that?
You said, "Oh yeah, people copy each
other." So yeah,
it's never it's never going to come,
mate. I've already been on the plane.
I've got a video of me on the plane, you know.
Yeah, I've got a video of me on a plane, mate. So,
and it's quite a terrifying experience.
So, I don't think you'll be going on one
anytime soon. But you even said that
people say that chevar was attractive to fit in.
No, you No, you said that people copy
each other, but you said that you're not copying.
Yeah. I literally can go on a TSR form
right now and people calling each other
gay because they don't find cheerful car
attractive. It's It was a trend. It was
It hasn't changed. You said that they
copy each other, but you said that you wasn't copying.
You said when you say it, you're not
copying, but they copy. Yeah, you're a
little copycat. You said that if you
don't find her attractive, you're gay. That's copying.
No, that is copying that. That is
definitely definitely copying
because you'll see other people have
said the same thing to other people
because it is literally copying.
Yes, it is copying
people that don't have no mind of their own.
No, I never never change any story. No.
No. Yeah. You said that shovel car was
um attractive. Fit in it.
You said it to fit in.
Yeah. You said it to fit in.
You wanted to fit in
to fit in. No, it hasn't changed. It
hasn't changed at all.
That bastard hoover. I got to go to
sleep soon. ready for my big day today.
Yeah. You said No, no, no. You said that
you you said that you find her
attractive, but you said that there
other people that say she's attractive
say to fit in.
You said people at school do copy each
other, but you said that you're not copying them.
So, you're trying to make out that
you're not like them. So,
Yeah, you're a little copycat.
You're a little copycat cuz you've never
said any of the women that I've been
with, if you don't find them attractive,
you're gay. Only Sher Co. It's got to be
the name, isn't it? It's got to be the
name. It's literally the name.
It's the name.
It's literally the name, isn't it, mate?
Nothing else. Just the name. Bless you
then. Bless you. You know,
it's just a name, mate.
If you don't find her attractive, you're gay.
Little copycat. Well, I think she's
[ __ ] ugly and I've had more women
than you. Does that make me gay?
So be it, mate. Yeah.
You say that people that don't lick
[ __ ] is gay.
You say that people that don't go down
on a woman is gay.
You think that's gay if you don't go
down on a woman?
You You You think that's gay, mate?
Well, Sig had a [ __ ] smelly vagina,
so I didn't go down on her cuz her fanny stunk.
Stunk like [ __ ]
So, you know, they're going to go down
on that. You know, you said that if you
don't go down on a woman.
Yeah. That's gay.
How is that gay? How is that [ __ ]
Nah, mate. Nah.
Yeah, but I've had sex with more women
than you, mate. Doesn't matter about body counts. Also,
also another thing is um
why did you say if you don't go down the
woman you're gay?
Why did you say that?
Why the [ __ ] did you say that, mate?
If you don't go down on a woman that you're gay,
why did you say that? That's ridiculous.
Because you wouldn't call a woman that
doesn't suck dick a lesbian. Double
standards. Thought I'd throw out a
double standard for you right there, mate.
But do you call women that don't suck
dick a lesbian?
Just Just throwing that out there.
Okay. So, what about women that don't suck dick?
Are they lesbians?
Does that mean they're lesbians? Because
there's women that don't like to give
[ __ ] There's women out there. So
that must mean they're lesbian by your
logic then, right?
Or is it different because it's a woman?
Just just throw that out there.
Curious to see what your answer would be
on that one. So if you don't if you
don't want to eat out a woman, you're
gay. But if a woman doesn't want to suck
dick, she's uh see she she's uh she's
she's not a lesbian.
Oh, interesting. Double standards, huh?
Exactly. Cuz you got cuz cuz I'm right.
What I'm saying is right. That's why you
call me an incel.
Why don't Why don't There's women that
don't like to suck dick.
I think Morgan wanted me to eat her out.
I'm not going to eat out your [ __ ] skank [ __ ] That's disgusting.
I've only done that once and I'm never
doing it again. It's [ __ ] vile. [ __ ] that.
I'm not [ __ ] eating a [ __ ] woman out
ever again. That's [ __ ] vile.
When I was with Sig, I was like, "Suck
my toodger." She's like, "I'll suck your
todd if you go down on me." I said, "I'm
not eating you out."
I'm not eating you out. No way. So, I
just won't have the [ __ ] Simple. [ __ ] that. No way. Nah, mate. Oh.
Look at that.
That little face. Hello, mate. You're right.
No, she didn't.
Because I didn't want to eat her out.
So, we just ended up [ __ ]
Yeah. We just ended up having a little [ __ ]
cuz I wasn't going to eat her out. She
said, "If you eat me out," I said, "I'm
not doing that." So
yeah, [ __ ] that. I wasn't going to eat
her out, so
no [ __ ] way.
No, no, mate. No, mate.
How many times do you jerk off to USA?
Is it? You seem to be obsessed with that [ __ ]
How? You seem to be really obsessed with
that [ __ ] in it. I was talking to USA
is his friend for about 5 hours
uh a couple of months ago. Yeah.
Yeah. He was on the phone for like 5 hours, mate.
She suffers from anxiety and
she's been abused by Charles apparently. You know,
no, I've not shown you any
conversations, mate. You don't need to
see any combos. You keep wanting to
convince yourself we ain't had sex. I'm
not I'm not here to convince you
otherwise, mate. I don't give a [ __ ]
what you think. You know,
she [ __ ] shot her pants. She did,
mate. Shut her [ __ ] pants.
[ __ ] horrible old [ __ ]
You horrible old [ __ ] [Laughter] Yeah.
Yeah, I do remember. Yeah. And he got caught out. What?
What are you talking about, you [ __ ] idiot?
What are you talking about? No,
not at all.
Oh, another thing I remember. You said
you used to like um when you was a kid,
Thomas the Tank Engine,
you know, Thomas the Tank Engine.
>> Yeah. I used to like that you used to
you like Thomas the Tank Engine
when you was a kid
when you was a child. You know,
if Morgan ever comes back here, mate,
this is what I'm going to do. Going to
[ __ ] It's back in their face, mate.
But this look,
couple of blows
and then that's it, mate.
That's your lot. That is literally your lot, mate.
All right. Punch in the face.
Then you'll be you'll be [ __ ] then, won't you?
Won't you, mate? Won't you? Yeah.
Yeah. You said that you used to um love
Thomas's Tank Engine.
Then you said that you used to wank off
to Spongebob Squarepants.
As you got a bit older,
you um started masturbating to um Spongebob Squarepants.
Now, don't know why, but that's what you
started coming out with. Um bit weird,
bit sus, but I was like,
you said that you started masturbating to Spongebob. [Laughter]
That's what you Spongebob is not. What
do you mean Spongebob is very childish?
Spongebob is cool.
I like Spongebob.
And you used to say you told me that uh
uh you didn't like The Inbetweeners. You
said you watched it, but you didn't like
it because it's not like reality.
You said that it's too far-fetched.
That's why you didn't like the in between inbetweeners.
Yeah. You said that's why you didn't
like the inbetweeners because it's too um
oh [ __ ] farfetched and not it's not reality.
Yeah, that's what you said.
you said that about um
the inbetweeners that it's just so off
reality that you don't you didn't like it.
Do you remember? I mean, it is it isn't
it's a TV show. It's not supposed to be real, mate.
It's not supposed to be real. You know,
in between us.
It's not supposed to be real. A second.
It's a TV show.
What do you
What do you expect from a TV show, mate?
Not supposed to be real, you know?
It's not supposed to be real, is it? You [ __ ] clown, you know. Yeah.
Yeah. I used to like WWE
back in 2009, 2010,
but now it's all [ __ ] I think the only
wrestlers that's the only wrestler
that's still on there now is CM Punk, you know.
Yeah, CM Punk.
I do remember WWF, mate.
I remember WWF. Yeah,
but then it kind of died. Nah.
Yeah. The only wrestlers there that was
like CM Punk. Yeah.
You never went to see WWE live cuz you
couldn't afford it.
Remember when we spoke about WWE before,
but obviously you couldn't afford to go,
so you never saw it live. I saw it live.
I saw it live a couple of times, mate. I
saw Smackdown and Raw.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I went when I was 12.
I saw Smackdown and Raw. Yeah.
Yeah, I saw Smackdown and Raw. No,
no, mate. No, no, man.
I like John Cena, but he's old now.
His [ __ ] body's all like it's getting bit um
loose and saggy, you know? Yeah, I used
to like John Cena, but yeah,
they're all old now, so N
never seen WW no.
You spelled Finley wrong.
spelled Finlay wrong. No, no,
you spelled Finley wrong, mate. It's fin,
So anyways, would you would would you
shag USA Izzy
if you weren't with the the the the
disabled girl you with now? Would would
you shag her?
Would Would you [ __ ] her, mate?
Nah. Never been to mate. Nah. No. No.
No. No. No.
Would you? Would you, mate?
I remember that time like you tried to
get in somewhere
and the guy was like ID
ID and he was like he was just saying
that to show off.
Do you remember? Cuz you said you'd been
there before and he he he was asking you for ID.
You got IDed a few times, didn't you?
Little bit of ID, mate. No, no, nothing
wrong with that. Bit of ID. We need We
need to see a bit of your ID, mate. You
said that he was showing off or something. Yeah, you um yeah.
Nah, mate. Nah, nah. No, we're not
talking about when you was with me. we
was talking about another time.
No. And also, you can't go into a casino
without ID. They scan everyone's ID. Any
club that you go into central London,
you can't go in without ID unless it's
like a pub. But yeah, you used to have
an ego thing about that as well. Uh, you
can't get into certain places without
them scanning your ID. I mean, yeah, pubs maybe.
But you you wouldn't be able to go.
Okay. Say, for example, you wanted to go
into O'Neal's, right? You're not getting
in without ID, mate, because they
actually scan your ID,
no matter who the [ __ ] you are
in central London anyway. So maybe not
anywhere else, but central London they
do. Yeah, you told me that. I remember
Yeah, he was asking you for ID to show
off in it. But there's nothing wrong
with a bit of ID.
Nothing wrong with a bit of
identification, mate. You maybe maybe
you look young, you know.
Okay. You walk into you walk into O'Neal's, right?
You walk into O'Neal's
Chinatown without showing ID and I'll
give you two grand.
That's That's a good offer, mate. I'll
give you £2,000. 2K bet,2,000 bet.
Yeah. Go to O'Neil's
and uh Yeah. about 10:00 at night. 10:00
at night and say you ain't got your ID,
mate. Yeah. I'll give you £2,000£50 notes.
Yeah. Go on. Yeah. 10:00 at night. Yeah.
cuz we need bit. Not like it has to be
10:00 at night though.
It has to be 10.
Bit of ID, mate. Bit of ID. Nothing
wrong with a bit of ID.
Nothing wrong with a bit of identification.
Nothing wrong with a bit identification.
There's nothing wrong with that at all.
There's nothing wrong with a bit of ID.
Bit of ID. There's nothing wrong with a
bit of ID, is there? Bit of ID, mate.
Bit of ID. I got a passport. I got more
passport stamps than you.
Yeah, I've got more passport stamps than you, mate.
More passport stamps. Yeah, mate.
Oh, [ __ ] hell.
Yeah. Yeah. Bit of ID, mate. Bit of ID.
Bit of ID, please. Bit of ID. Bit of ID,
mate. Bit of ID. Bit of mate. Bit of ID.
Bit of mate. Bit of ID. Bit of ID. Bit
of ID. Bit of ID, mate. Bit of bit of
ID. Bit of ID. Bit of ID, mate. Bit of
Yeah, nothing wrong with a bit of ID, mate.
It's cuz you look young. Cuz obviously
you don't have a beard like me because
you can't grow one.
Yeah, it's fine. There's nothing wrong
with a bit of ID though, is there?
There's nothing wrong with with being IDed.
I don't see the problem with it,
you know, being IDed.
Everyone's got one, you know.
Oh yeah, definitely look younger than
me, mate. Definitely, mate. Yeah, mate.
Look, I got a lovely little beard. Look,
I went to the barbers yesterday. Do you like it?
I got I got it done.
Doesn't matter if you're older than me.
You look younger than me, mate.
You're older, but you look younger.
Yeah. I mean, there's people that look
younger than you, but they're like 3
years older than you.
I mean, I literally know people that
look younger than you, but they're three
years older than you, mate.
So anyways, would you shag USA is he
if he wasn't with the disabled girl?
Would you would you if you wasn't with
the disabled girl? Would you would would
you [ __ ] her?
No. Would would you would you would you [ __ ] her
if you didn't have a disabled girl?
Would you would you give her one? Would
you [ __ ] her up the ass?
Would you Would you give her one, mate?
Would you [ __ ] her?
Would you [ __ ] her, mate?
What you do, mate?
No, no. If you did have a girlfriend.
No, no, no. If you did have a girlfriend.
No, but we're saying if you didn't have
a girlfriend, then what?
No, we're talking about if you didn't.
No, we mean if you did have a girlfriend,
then then would you do it?
You always like Britney, but
you earn her a cuppper. And that's fine.
You know, we're not always
We're not always people's cup of tea.
Yeah, but if you didn't So, if you
didn't have a girlfriend, you would. So,
what Okay, what if your girlfriend said
we can have a freom? Me, you, and USA,
Izzy, then would you
see Britney, you you earn her a cup of
tea and there's there's nothing wrong
with that, you know. You see, with my
mom, she she has no um sugars in her cup
of tea. I've got two I have two sugars in mine.
No, but you might split up one day.
Yeah, but what what if you split up one day?
What what if what if what if what if
what if you split up?
So when you finally have sex with her,
say you you you do get to have sex with
her eventually, your your girlfriend. So
what will happen if you get her
pregnant? Will you keep the bubba?
Would you keep the bubin?
Would you keep the baby? No, mate. mate. Would
would you keep the baby
when when you finally have sex? Will you
keep it? Will you keep the bubba or no?
Yeah. Let's just
I don't know how these people There's
these people they've been together for
years, right? And the person never gets
pregnant. Yeah. Somebody will be with
somebody for eight months and then the
person gets pregnant. I guess it's all
random, isn't it? You know.
Yeah. Cuz you when you might have when
you have sex with her like for the first
time, you never know what could happen,
mate. You need to be careful.
My friend had a problem like you. Well,
I say my my friend uh the tenant. E's
dick didn't work properly and he wanted
me to go to the hospital with him and
toot him. He said, "Oh, can you come and
support me and stuff?" Obviously, I
didn't go in the room with him. So,
maybe you've got that problem with your
with your dick,
you know? Maybe um
maybe you've got that problem with your dick. [Laughter]
What? You was dating months before you
slept together. Why is that?
Me? I need to I need to have sex within
within the first time I'm meeting them.
You know, it's like when I met USA, I
didn't think we was going to do anything
until she started coming on to me. It
was quite aggressive.
It was quite strange.
It was quite odd. You know,
why would why would you date somebody
for months before you slept with them,
mate? Cuz I remember you telling me
before, I do actually remember this. You
said that if you was dating someone, you
wouldn't wait more than a month before
they [ __ ] they had sex with you.
Yeah. You said you wouldn't wait longer
than a month. That's crazy.
Yeah. You actually said longer than a
month then you wouldn't, mate. Good job.
Yeah. Well, I Yeah, it was it was years
ago to be fair, mate. It was years ago
to be fair. Yeah.
Yeah, you used to you used to tell me
that you used to watch KSI.
I remember you told me you used to watch
KSI and that
Yeah, you used to tell me you used to
watch KSI on YouTube and stuff, the FIFA videos.
You said you used to like FIFA. Yeah.
You don't know who KSI is? [ __ ] off.
The big YouTuber, the the the the black guy.
Yeah. You used to watch FIFA. Um used to play FIFA.
You said you used to play FIFA. Yeah.
You've never heard of KSI? Yeah, you have. Um,
no. I don't know if he's been in WWE.
Logan Paul and KSI.
You don't know who they are.
How the [ __ ] do you not know who KSI is?
What the [ __ ]
The one that made the prime drinks.
The one that made the [ __ ] prime drinks.
Yeah. Well, basically they had a boxing match together.
Wow. You actually don't know who that
is. That is surprise. The one that made
the prime drinks. You know, the prime juices.
Yeah, they made prime. Him and Logan
Paul made the prime drinks. That's crazy.
So, what? You don't know the Sidemen or
anyone like that?
You don't You don't watch big YouTubers? No,
maybe you've just not seen them about
Yeah, I don't know how you don't know
KSI, but never mind.
You've been living under a rock, mate, ain't you?
even you and Oh, and you used to tell me
that you used to like Harry Potter as well.
Yeah, you used to like Harry Potter.
Yeah. You used to like Harry Potter, didn't you? No.
No. You you told me that you used to
like Harry Potter.
I tell you something, right? Since we
were speaking about Cheryl Cole, that
Emma Watson, that's another um trend.
Well, people never used to say she was
gay. You were gay if you didn't like her. But
they would they would say that, "Oh, I
wish I could get with her. I really like
her." Which again, there's nothing wrong
with her, but again, overrated.
She's another overrated one.
Oh my god. You don't know who Emma
Watson is? What the [ __ ] The one from Harry Potter.
You don't know who she is. She's [ __ ]
famous as [ __ ] She's been on other
things. Basically, somebody from She was
one of the ones from Harry Potter.
One of the one of three of the main characters.
Yeah. Well, anyways, people used to say
she was um
they overrated her basically
proper like overrated her.
It's just a trend. Like I said to you,
all of these things are trends. Yeah,
don't get me wrong, there's nothing
wrong with the way she looks. She's
she's not ugly. She's got a nice voice,
but she's not as as good as people are
saying she is.
Like then like physically they're
talking about physically, you know. So
you don't think she's attractive now?
Yeah, she's like
slightly above average. Yeah,
but she's got no bums. She's got no
boobs. What the [ __ ]
again. She's good, but people are over
overhyping her up.
Do you know what I'm saying?
I think she looks all right. Yeah,
but she hasn't got much of a body. She's very skinny, you know. Yeah.
It's not It's not just women they done it with.
Yeah, her face is slightly above average.
average, but she's got no ass and boobs. Yeah,
her face is slightly above average. So what?
But people over [ __ ] hyper
because um I don't know why they do
people. I don't know why people do it.
It's not just women they do it with.
They do it with men as well.
They don't you remember they done it
with [ __ ] Mosy's name?
Harry Styles. I don't know if you know
who that is.
Yeah. They done it with Harry Styles as well.
Yes. But what I'm saying is Okay. But
what I'm saying is if it was a normal
person on the street and she wasn't
famous, nobody would care.
same as Harry Styles.
Harry Styles is a somebody in One
Direction, the one of the One Direction um people
be saying that if she wasn't famous.
Oh my god. How the [ __ ] do you not know
One Direction? What the [ __ ]
How do you not know these things, man?
Have you been living under a [ __ ]
rock? The the the band on X Factor that become worldwide from England.
Oh my god. There's no way you can be this stupid. [ __ ]
how how can you be this stupid? My god.
Yeah, but they were famous. They were
very, very famous.
They become like worldwide.
You You've never heard of them.
Cheryl car is a baby by one of the One
Direction members. You You've never
heard of them?
That shocks me how you've not heard of
them or [ __ ] KSI. That is insane
because they're very famous. They're
famous as Justin Bieber.
Okay. How Okay. Okay. So, have you heard of Eminem?
You must have heard of Eminem.
It wouldn't surprise me if you haven't
to be honest. [ __ ] hell. Have you
heard of Eminem?
must know who that is. No.
Yeah, obviously I was going to say
Taylor Swift, but obviously everyone
knows who she is.
Yeah. Well, they were basically very
very famous that group anyways from the
X Factor. So, like really famous back in
like 2011 2012.
You've been living under a rock, ain't you, mate,
for many, many years. So, you don't know
these things. So, right. Okay. So, what
YouTubers do you watch? Do you watch any YouTubers?
They're like, "Okay, so what YouTube
channels do you watch off of this community?
is you don't watch anything off this
community, you know, like No.
Jesus Christ. You're [ __ ]
You're very behind, didn't you, mate? Very behind, you know.
You are quite behind a you
said what do you watch off of this
community like big YouTubers you I'm so
surpris I'm surprised you you didn't
know who KSI was
Jesus Jesus [ __ ] Christ,
you really are a silly cat.
I mean, YouTube in general.
Yeah, not this community. There's
nothing on this community
but a bunch of pedos. [Laughter]
You should meet Timmy Aldridge.
You should meet up with Timmy. You
should meet up with Timmy Aldridge. [Laughter]
Yeah. Why don't you meet up with Timmy? Timmy Aldridge.
You should you should you should go to
barbecue and meet with Timmy Aldridge.
Why don't you meet Timmy Aldridge? Yeah.
Yeah. You should meet Timmy Aldridge.
I think you two would get on.
I'm going to knock him out.
But I do actually need to go to sleep
soon because Yeah, I need to do some
stuff today. Jokes aside. Yeah.
Yeah. So, why don't you meet Timmy Eldridge then?
You like Timmy Eldridge, huh?
You should meet Timmy Eldridge.
No, no. Why don't you meet Timmy Aldridge?
Might as well. [ __ ] it.
All right. See you later, honey.
See See you later, honey chops.
Timmy doesn't like me.
Me and Timmy hate each other. Yeah.
So you can meet Timmy Aldridge.
So why don't you go for Monty Man
anyways? You go for me, but you never go
for Monty Man. That's strange. H
That's very strange. Let's
go for Monty.
Anyways, I'm gone. See you later.