Yeah.
[ __ ] hungry again.
I'm green again. [ __ ] yeah. Don't
Cook up some piggies.
Yes, I am. Are you going to get live
today? You still on YouTube?
I'll be coming off uh this [ __ ] after my
birthday anyways. I'm not going to be on
my birthday, but um get mad. It's time
for a new change, you know.
You really think up today I'm going to
I'm going to win and pull. So today I'll put today
but I order them other million times.
You can't take a day off YouTube.
N it's the same atmosphere on here. Same
come. Same [ __ ] atmosphere.
Just cooking some piggies.
I'm cooking some piggies.
[ __ ] starving. I am
[cough and clears throat]
You can't take off YouTube.
You can't take one one day off of it.
That's all you've got.
That's all we have.
>> Are we going to do the shade with the bread though? [ __ ] slow.
You're on here every day.
One second. How do I do the bed with the sheets?
You could microwave it, I guess.
Well, you can't even take a day off of YouTube.
I think the bread and butter will be all right. >> Yeah, [clears throat]
>> you can't even take it down.
Don't [ __ ] talk about me, lad. Yeah, being piggies.
There we go. Yep.
Got all sage.
So, I deleted the dating apps and I'm
never ever ever ever
going on them ever again.
life from now. Yeah.
Never going to work, are they?
Yeah. Today is going to be different.
Not like I'm not It's not like I've done
this a million times before, is it? Nah.
Today all days is going to be today.
What's the chance today? What's the [ __ ] chances?
You probably got more chances of a 50
both no draw coming in.
I mean, it is going to be the same old
[ __ ] today, but we both so >> Yep.
Why do we do this? Perfect.
Perfect [ __ ] head. Love me.
Do that. Okay.
My god, do that.
You can't take it out of YouTube. It's
all you bloody got. You little one cup
coming online every day creating the same atmosphere.
You're talking about yourself.
This is another reason I come up here.
Coming on here, right? Hello. [snorts]
Coming on here. Seeing a bunch of people
talking about their [ __ ] selves.
You people coming on here talking about
your [ __ ] selves.
One second. Let me do this bacon food. Mate,
need to concentrate. You can't
cook fast. One sec.
That's coming up.
You concentrate here. I'm making some breakfast. Please.
I love piggies.
Who doesn't love piggies? Is it
What's that smell that
is [ __ ] red?
You got more chances of bet winning then.
If we got more chance of the bet winning
than actually putting that way. What should bread?
I'm addicted to saying that. I need to
stop saying that.
>> It's true. But yeah. This [ __ ]
Why is it like a bottom spit? Strange.
How are you going to lose it?
When are you going to lose it? [laughter]
That's my money. myself.
Bacon should be ready.
Over one more time.
If it gets over one last time.
Yeah, there's something wrong with that.
Why don't Why are the [ __ ] spreading?
Doesn't make no sense.
Look at that.
That's what you call a lovely lovely egg.
You can't even split the bottle. Wow.
I was just thinking like wasn't there
yesterday. It's just the same people say
about this bill,
>> you know,
the same people there. Yeah.
Look at these.
Oh, wait. M
>> [clears throat]
>> Yeah, it's the same atmosphere.
That's how it
really want crisp it, you know.
Crisp up. Nice.
Last couple come.
>> [clears throat]
>> You take your day off. That's all you have.
Yeah. If you come on here projection
every day, what would you have?
You [ __ ] off.
This is quite a lush.
This is lush.
Oh, pick this.
Don't know. You know what?
I'm not sure.
You not working today? That what you what people welcome.
Yes, I have. So inside
people are sometimes nothing
went down like a tree.
That one yummy.
I like this.
Yeah. Dups work. Didn't you know, man?
That's what they say on Reddit. Yeah,
also works like obviously
I get like 100 of matches. Yeah.
Oh, I found a way to get back on Reddit bubble.
The [ __ ] mods are such quiet babies.
Ban anyone that's got a different
opinion than them. [ __ ] losers.
Oh, that was lovely.
That was [ __ ] lovely, son. [sighs]
They're always bloody bad to me as soon
as I make an account.
The bloody mods fear different opinions.
It kills them. That's why they need
power because without that power bubble
they're they're [ __ ] nothing. I tell
you [ __ ] nothing. They are [ __ ]
nothing. Without that power
[ __ ] all about that little bit of power.
That's what they get out of bed for. You
know they can ban people
and you can't do nothing about it. [ __ ] losers.
supposed to be meeting that woman today
in Scotland, but I ain't [ __ ] doing that. No.
[ __ ] that, lad.
Oh, them piggies went down like a treat. [sighs]
Yeah, piggies and lies.
Now I have my copper hunt. Who?
There we go. Lovely cup of [ __ ] [clears throat] Lovely.
Lovely cup of K.
>> [clears throat]
>> So, I could go out now and start
approaching, but it's too early. Way too So yeah,
this got me reestablished. Oh, really?
[clears throat and cough] Really, man? Mm- Yeah. >> [snorts] [clears throat]
>> What's up?
That virgin boy [clears throat] TV died. Well, oh [ __ ]
I might as well not go back to sleep to
be honest then. Nope.
Maybe I could
do I don't know.
Them [ __ ] Reddit mods need that power.
Nothing nothing without it.
Nothing. Bloody nothing.
How do I know you're on here every day?
Because when I was off of here and I
clicked on people's live streams, I saw
you type away.
Just admit it. You can't live without
YouTube. You can't take a day off of
YouTube. I'm coming off in a couple of
days. I am actually coming off cuz it's
the same atmosphere. You're 28. You
never had a girlfriend. You're skin. We
hear the same old [ __ ] So yeah,
I'm not doing this. Yeah.
Just self projecting [ __ ]
So yeah, you can't get off of YouTube, lad. No.
I'll be on here for a little bit. Then
I'll try and get a couple of hours sleep.
Get ready to go out. And Jeff live five.
Who's virgin boy?
Oh, not in London. It won't be, mate.
London's always busy.
And I don't live in a town. I live in the city. So, no.
London's always Oh, [ __ ] I can't turn.
[ __ ] Uh, London's always busy. It could
be raining and it will still be busy. I
don't live in the town. I live in a city. So,
get get your facts right. [sighs]
Yeah. Yes, they will in London.
In London, they will.
In London, they will, matey. Always
people out in London, matey.
It could be a Monday and raining and
they'd still be out matey.
So, we'll see how many numbers we can get today.
It's going to be interesting, isn't it?
No, you don't.
No, you don't. Well, then if you if you
if you're more central than me, then you
would know if you go central London,
there's always going to be people out. [snorts] [laughter]
Well, then you know there's always going
to be people out then, right? Yeah. Simple.
I think it's mad that the only way you
can get a date or laid is by
approaching. It's mad, isn't it?
Do not think that's mad.
That is proper mad, isn't it? That's
mad. Yeah. No, it'll be more than tourists.
I've been laid from approaching. But I
mean, that's your only hope. I mean, you
know what I mean? No, you don't. But I
mean, it's your only hope.
Yeah. And you've never had sex?
Yeah. But you've never had sex, so
you're you're you're losing by a long shot.
You've never even had sex.
Yeah. The same will happen today. Who
cares? I'm going for a nice meal. I'm
going for some drinks whilst you're
going to be sat at home on YouTube. No life.
Yeah. Sad with your life? That's fine,
bro. I don't mind.
Yeah, that's fine. The same thing can
happen. I got money to burn. I don't
give a [ __ ]
No one cares.
That's absolutely fine. The beat's being
used on YouTube.
Ain't got a life in it. So
yeah, you do need to have a day off
YouTube talking about yourself.
Why is it with you people in here
talking about yourselves, man? Seriously,
what is it with you little virgins on
here, man? Seriously, I think I I do
actually think most of you are virgins as well.
I generally think most of you on here
are actually virgins.
Like, honestly, I'm not even tapping,
bro. That's what um yeah,
do you know?
No, I don't need to concentrate on
myself. You're my light. I'm talking
about you people.
I'm talking about you people. I would
say most of you are actually virgins.
Yeah, definitely. Most of you are
virgins in this community. It's so obvious.
You ain't got no life but coming on
YouTube trolling. Pathetic really at your age.
It's really pathetic at your age. And
you people have been doing it for years
as well. When are you going to grow up
and get off of YouTube? I'll tell you
when I'm going to be doing it.
In a couple of days. When are you going
to grow up and get off of YouTube, you people? H
When are you going to get off of YouTube?
I'll be sending it today like a [ __ ] bro. Yeah. D
You people really need to get off of
YouTube and get a life. Seriously.
Seriously, dude, man.
Need to get over YouTube and get alive.
Might have a nice Finderoo tomorrow. Uh, well,
I haven't gone out drinking for a month.
Today will be the first time for a
month. Yeah, that sit that [ __ ] sitting
on YouTube being a low life. [ __ ] I'd
rather go out drinking every week than
[ __ ] be sat on YouTube having no life.
So, and we're not just talking about
going out drinking. There's loads of
things you can do that don't cost a lot
of money, but nope. You'd rather sit on
YouTube all day and pretend you've got a
life. Mad, is it?
No, we're not just talking about going out drinking. So
yeah, I think most of you are virgins. Defer 100%.
I do think most of you are virgins on it. Yeah,
little virgins. You can't get off of YouTube. Yeah,
sad. And you are older than me as well. Imagine that.
My mom's got more of a life than you and
she's 6 [ __ ] five.
How mad is that? My actual mother's got
more of a life and she's 65.
Uh, I'm going to a steakhouse today. I
don't know why you're talking about shitty Nandos.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm going to a steakhouse
that's expensive. I don't know why
you're talking about Nando again. Must
be self-p projecting.
And also Nando is not shitty. And again,
I'd rather go out and have a Nando and
sit on YouTube like Yulo lives all day.
And I am actually going to a steakhouse.
Get it right. Thank you. Yeah.
What are you talking about Nando?
I didn't know I was going Nando. I
thought I was going to a steakhouse.
And Nando is not shitty either. Nando is expensive.
Stop hating. This is what I mean with
you people. You like to bring hate.
That's another thing you do on this
community. You bring hate and negativity.
All cuz it's how you feel about
yourselves. Depressed on YouTube every
day. Yeah. I've noticed it with views.
Yeah. Why do you even write a comment like that? [ __ ] idiot.
Nope. I never said Nandos.
This is what I mean with you little weirdos.
This is what I mean with you weirdos on
here. You chat [ __ ] and make stuff up.
Go and get a life. I'll say that to nons
legs as well. Go get a life. You're in
desperate need of one.
Let's get a [ __ ] life. Mhm. Yeah.
Why are you talking about Nando,
bro? Why are you talking about Nando
anyways? Who said Nando?
And also, what's wrong with going to Nando?
That's [ __ ] mad. Yeah, madness.
That's what I mean. You're all idiots on here.
All [ __ ] idiots. And the Gordon
Ramsay restaurant is not even expensive.
You really are idiots.
It's the same atmosphere here
on this community. Yeah.
What if Monty's awake? No.
No, you haven't eaten eaten in more
places than I have, mate. No, you haven't.
>> Have you ever had lobster?
You haven't had more places. You
wouldn't take a date to Nando, bro.
Taking a first date to Nando is too
much. Nando is too good for them. This
guy's definitely a white knight. This
guy's definitely a s.
Wait, you would never take a date to
Nando. Like like a like a first date.
You would never take a first date to
Nando. This guy's definitely a s.
This guy is definitely a s. A f You
would never take a first date to to Nando.
Really? Yeah. You're s 100% s.
I can understand [ __ ] McDonald's and
[ __ ] KFC or some [ __ ] or Weather
Spoons, but Nandos.
Yeah, you're definitely a s.
Defo. Defo. Defo a s.
Yeah, you're definitely a s, man.
Yeah, you haven't ate at more
restaurants than me, bro. I've had a
I've ate at a lot of restaurants.
No, I ate at a lot of restaurants. Good
luck with that, bro.
Good luck with that. I've had steak.
I've had Thai. I've had Chinese. I've had lobster.
I've had a tadium. Good luck with that,
bro. I don't think you have.
I really don't think you have.
[snorts] Doesn't matter if you have to
have your hands on it. No, it doesn't matter.
You are a simp lad. You said you
wouldn't take a first You said you
wouldn't take a date to Nando
when a woman I don't cry. I just tell
people what they're like. They're [ __ ]
They're [ __ ] I'm not a s at all.
How can I be a s when I'm talking [ __ ] about them?
I'm literally talking [ __ ] about them.
How could I be a s?
That doesn't make sense. Yeah. Okay. Whatever.
You're all idiots on here.
You really are idiots on here. You're mad.
How would you know, bubble? You've never
been on a date.
You've never been on a date.
You sad little virgin. Get off of YouTube.
Get off of YouTube and get a life. I
think that's the last thing I want to
say to these people when I come off
here. Get a life. Get off YouTube. >> Yeah.
Get off of YouTube. Stop [ __ ]
commenting on creating the same Mongol
atmosphere every day. Same comment, same
atmosphere, same [ __ ] people. See you
next year. That's what I'm going to say. Yeah,
but how can I be a s when I've spoke
[ __ ] about women? Yeah. Madness.
You need to get alive, lad.
You bounce off of other people's lives.
It's the same as Terry.
Yeah. Cuz you ain't got one of your own.
Ah [sighs and gasps] yeah. Yeah.
No, you It's not free time. You people
are on it from the time you wake up to
the time you go to bed.
No. No way.
It's more than free time. It's way more
No, mate. No,
I haven't rat face with no teeth.
I'm Wobbly Hooter and you're the rat
face with no teeth. We've got little
nicknames for each other.
If I don't eat if I don't stop scoffing
bacon down my throat, I'm going to
become fat like your girlfriend, mate.
Um because, bro, listen, I've seen you
people on here from the time you wake up
to the time you go to bed. You've got no lives.
I know. Trust me. Peter B knows. Yeah.
So, yeah. Says a lot about you, eh?
When you come on here trying to talk
about [ __ ] other people, you know,
when I was off for 9 [clears throat]
days, I was sub to people and I clicked on it. Yep. Mhm.
Yep. Again, having someone on the bell
running to the police screaming you're
not a fighter is not a win. Only these
mongos on here would see it as a win.
No, that but that's not a win.
But that's not that's not a win though.
Only these spastics would see that as a
win. Anyone else would see that as a
loser. A coward loser. Yeah,
that's not a win. That's not a win at all, mate.
You literally ran to the police because
you got owned so badly on YouTube, you
couldn't take no more. That's not a win.
That's not a win. That's what losers do.
I can't take no more. That's literally
what losers do. That's not a win. That's
not a win at all.
That's what a [ __ ] That's what losers
do. You can't take it. You get bullied on YouTube.
I could imagine being so much of a loser
that had nothing left in me that had to
go run into the police. I could never
imagine being that much of a loser. And
trust me, I've I've had loads in my
life, bro. But I can never imagine going
back and forth with someone on YouTube
and being so much of a [ __ ] loser
that I've got nothing left in me. Not
even an ounce of fight left in me. I'm
so much of a loser. I've been beaten so
badly I've had to go to the police.
What a [ __ ] loser. And I literally
mean that when I say that. That's not a
win. That's literally not a win. That's
what a coward would do.
So yeah, I don't know why you seem to
think that's a win, you loser. It just
means you couldn't take me and you have
to go run into the police.
Yeah. Anyways, you're bad now. >> [snorts] >> Yep. Never happened.
This is what I mean with you mongos.
This is why I'm coming off of it.
You're all [ __ ] mongos. You need to
get a life. Desperate need of a life.
That's why I'm coming off this [ __ ]
Monty can stay on here.
Monty can stay on here, but I won't be. Yeah.
Yeah. again. You can't take a day off of YouTube. So yeah,
you can't take one day off of YouTube.
Imagine that. Not one day. Mad.
No, no, no, no. Joseph Farra.
Yeah, you keep telling yourself that.
Yeah, you keep telling yourself that, Mike. buddy.
That's another thing. Why are you people
always trying to compare your lives on
here as well?
It's such a weirdo community. It's the same atmosphere. Literally is.
It's the same [ __ ] atmosphere.
It's the same atmosphere every day. Yeah.
You even need to get a life.
That's what you need. Yeah.
Need to get alive. Get off of YouTube.
We need to get off YouTube.
Get off a YouTuber.
Get a life and get over YouTube.
You people are just fat ugly monk. Fat
ugly mongos ain't got a life in it. Yeah.
It's like that Hugh. Yeah. He was trying
to talk [ __ ] about me, but he was so skint.
He had to buy like a very small amount
of weed cuz he couldn't afford a big
amount. And he's trying to talk [ __ ] about me.
Oh, the irony. The [ __ ] irony. E,
someone's skin trying to talk about me. Huh?
Anyways, I'm blocking you people now. [snorts] yeah. Bye-bye. Mongos atmosphere.
I want to change the [ __ ] chat
around, you know. Mhm. >> [snorts] [laughter]