Yeah, just checking to see if it's the
same people on the YouTuber.
On the YouTuber,
the same people every day.
I'm not going to lie. I'm matey.
Just checking. Just making friends,
guys. I don't want to see anyone on my
bloody live chat,
you know. I don't want to see anyone on
my bloody live chat
cuz I'm the one that's got no life and
all of these people do.
It's sarcasm if you you haven't guessed that.
You can go. Yeah.
on a football bet for Saturday. Yeah,
I just went to uh
you know, good old Spoonies. No,
I I don't really come on here much
anymore to be honest.
No, bro. Oh, [ __ ] It was my birthday yesterday.
I was supposed to go out with my sister
on Saturday, but I didn't bother. I was
too tired. My sleeping pattern's [ __ ] So, yeah,
I'll be out on uh Friday, though. Definitely.
Yeah, I just went to my sister's order.
She ordered some food. My mom's still
yet to take me for a meal. Definitely
being out Friday though cuz I bought
some jeans that were 200 pound. My jeans
[ __ ] it. I had to buy a new pair.
200 [ __ ] quid.
It cost me uh it was my birthday
yesterday. I just went to my sisters,
had ordered some food, chilled out and yeah,
I was supposed to go out Saturday but
again my sleeping pan was [ __ ] So
I'll definitely be out Friday 100%. I'll
be out Friday,
but I ordered some I ordered some jeans,
Joe. 200 [ __ ] pound they cost me.
No, I just got um Well, my sister bought
me food, like I said.
Um she gave me
£20. My mom gave me 50. My mom's taking
me for a meal.
My other sister wished me happy
birthday. Didn't reply. We don't talk. But yeah,
just making friends, Joe. Just making friends.
No, it's not stupid. And I tell you why
it's not stupid. Because they last for 3
years. It's a good investment. It's a
very good investment.
Trust me, it's a good investment, bro.
They last for years.
Yeah, you could have got a [ __ ] phone for that.
Yeah, a [ __ ] phone.
No, bro. They're normally they were 110,
120, but they've gone up. Trust me,
they're worth it. They last for years.
See, when I when I wear a certain pair
of jeans, I stick to them. I don't go
for any less. I don't go for any more
cuz I know the sizes. I know how they
feel. Um, so
they're worth it in my opinion. But it
doesn't matter about like jumpers and
hoodies and stuff. That doesn't matter.
Once you have a nice pair of trainers,
nice pair of jeans, it doesn't matter
what you wear above the waist.
In my opinion, I'll never buy Stone
Island ever again. I've got the money. I
just I just wouldn't, you know?
So, maybe go to like All Saints or
something. Nice All Saints t-shirt,
lush with black jeans. Can't go wrong,
mate. Can you? The football bet. Uh, I
done one Saturday. You got [ __ ] 20
pound the week before that I won. I've
been winning them when I have been doing
them. I done one I done one um
when I went out earlier. I'll show you
if you want. Yeah, man.
Yeah. 200 you get. It's a [ __ ] phone.
Like you know when we was talking about
phones, right? I'll struggle with um
getting any phone out that's not a fold.
I don't think I'd be able to get a a
phone that's not a phone, but I have to
because I can't afford it. So, and by
that I mean I'm not going to pay 178
pound for a [ __ ] phone.
So, can never justify that unless I was
a multi-millionaire. So, yeah.
Just when you when you've had a phone
for so long, you know, but it is what it
is, it how it is.
Never justify that amount of money, bro.
I could never maybe if I won like 40 50
grand or something. But anyways, see look.
Don't know if you can see that football
bet, but the treble both score no draw.
Yeah, it's for Saturday because I was
there anyways. I went Weather Spoon, so
I thought [ __ ] it, I'm going out on Friday.
So, I thought yeah, just do it now. It
going out Friday, getting on the drink.
It's been a long time. I think it's been
six weeks. Yeah, six weeks.
That man's like, "Oh, like you going?" I
said, he thought I went out last week
cuz I was supposed to. I was like, "No,
I haven't been out for 6 weeks." And I
actually just want to drink. I actually
just want to go out and do something
because I've been out for ages.
Yeah, I haven't been out for six weeks,
Ghosten. I'm sure it's 6 weeks. It's got
to be five or six weeks now cuz of the
whole getting 10 numbers and not getting a date.
That was very offputting, bro. That was
that was depressing. That was
depressing, bro. I swear to God. But I I
know it's not going to change here, but
I'm just going to go out for a drink anyways.
You don't need to wish me luck, bro.
It's not going to change. I'm going out
cuz I want to go out and have a drink.
You don't need to wish me luck. It's
never going to change.
It's never ever going to change. Yeah.
It's pro. It's not a problem, bro. It's
I I know that now. I've realized it now.
So, it is what it is, isn't it? So,
I just want to go and have a drink, you
know. So, I know I'm not going to meet anyone. So,
it doesn't matter how many people are
dressed up. There could be a million
women dressed up. They're not interested
in this country. I thought you would
have uh learned something from my um thing. Yeah.
I was speaking to this woman, right?
And I was speaking to her on Instagram.
I messaged her and I was like, "I can't
stand a man that defends women. It
drives me [ __ ] mad. It does. I don't
know what it is." and we was talking and
stuff and then she's like, "Oh yeah, but
a guy defended me before cuz some guy
was beating me up." I said, "Well,
that's a bit different though, isn't
it?" That's like that in that case it's
different. But I mean I I can't stand
these white knights. There was this guy.
Yeah. He was white knighting this
[ __ ] woman, bro. And he slapped the
guy. I said, "I'd like to see you try
and [ __ ] slap me, big man. He's a
[ __ ] He's a big [ __ ] as well, but I I
wouldn't care." And you know, oh, you
disrespected women. I I said, I would
have [ __ ] disrespected these [ __ ]
mom. You know, I hate men that defend
women to look good. I I can't think of
anything worse, bro. I seriously can't.
It that annoys me, bro. That really does
annoy me. But obviously, if it's a
circumstance where someone punched a
random person and that's different. I
said to her, "Your your circumstance is
basically different. If someone's like really like
hurting you, then it's a bit different.
Can't stand men that offend women. I
can't think of anything worse.
Yo, I seriously can't think of anything worse.
I said, I'd like to see you try and slap
me, big man.
And he he would beat me as well cuz he's
a big [ __ ] But I wouldn't I wouldn't
have that, bro. I wouldn't have that. [ __ ] that.
My be was good. I went around my sisters
and yeah, it was fun.
Yeah, it was good, man.
I was supposed to go out on Saturday, so
my sister went out with her friend and
she told me I was like, "Oh, I missed
it." There was some good stuff that
happened, but they they stay stayed
locally, whereas I always go central
London, but I was like, "Oh, man. I
missed all the fun." Damn.
Well, I got my super was too [ __ ] I
couldn't go out. So,
like I said, I'd be out Friday,
bought some 200lb jeans.
See, and man was like, "Oh, don't you
get like bored staying in?" Cuz I've
stayed in for like six weeks. I was
like, to be honest with you, no. To be
honest with you, no. I just watch like
GTA San Andreas clips and it really
doesn't get boring.
If it was like if the weather wasn't so
[ __ ] then maybe. But no, I really don't get bored
because it's always the same in this
country. So when you go out and you have
to deal with that load of [ __ ]
having a break from it feels good. You
don't get bored of it at all. You You
really really don't. You just chill,
watch some GJ San Andreas. It was GJ's
San Andreas birthday on the 26th.
It's 21 years old, Grezy. Don't know if
you noticed that, but yeah, 21 years old.
But to be honest with you, I was I'm not
going to lie to you. I was thinking of
like starting madness on this website, bro.
Like just calling every [ __ ] out.
Calling every bastard out, bro. Like I
swear I thought, "Fuck it." Yo, it like
go to Terry, smash him up. Yeah, just
like doing a madness, I think. Why not?
Bit of fun, isn't it?
Oh, why is Monty saying about the Oh,
why don't the five great great guys meet
me? Why don't they meet me? But he knows
where one of them lives. Scotland.
So, would have he just went to like
Glasgow and went live? Strange.
Yeah. Strange, isn't it?
You just go to [ __ ] Glasgow, would
you? [ __ ] go live and call the ton out
then that's it. Say it's far but he's
saying he wants to meet them though. So oh
I used to travel by myself all the time. So yeah.
So like you don't wear any designer clothes, Joe?
I didn't buy a new pair of trainers
because I've already got a new pair and
it's just jeans you have to like pay
more money for if you want them to feel
good and that. Um,
well, it doesn't work cuz all the people
that defend women are still virgins and
they have had less women than me. So, it
kind of doesn't.
Maybe she felt sorry for him. I Oh, she
could have got with him out. She could
have got back with him out of pity. Yeah.
Yeah. I used to go to Next. I used to
get boxes from Next. Um, yeah, they do
nice suits as well, but yeah,
as you get older, you you you don't
really care about brands as much, I
guess, in it. But I still like to have nice jeans.
I can't wear cheap jeans.
But it doesn't matter about that kind of
[ __ ] anyways. So
as you get older,
it doesn't really matter
cuz the only good thing you can really
do with with your money is go on
holiday. That's really like if you want
to know the money now. What could you do
other than go on holiday? You've got a
phone, you got a TV, whatever. There's
nothing else you really
can do if you out a lot of stuff in it
at um a certain age and stuff, but it it
it how do I explain it? It is worth
spending a bit more like okay, give the
example. Say a t-shirt in Primark's £4.
If you bought a t-shirt that's like 10,
15, 20 pound, it's better quality, you
know, obvious, but we're talking that's
hardly anymore, but we're talking like
big brands, you know. Who gives a [ __ ] about that?
But again, you still need a nice pair of
trainers. As long as you got a nice pair
of trainers, you're laughing. You don't
need anything else. Done.
Nothing else. You don't need anything That's it.
And the money dries up as well for a lot
of people. So, that's another thing. But
the thing is, Joe, when you these Stone
Island jumpers I bought, they'll last forever.
They will last forever.
Forever and ever and ever. I wore Stone
Island jumper yesterday.
No, I tell you what the best t-shirts
are. They're a pack of Levi t-shirts and
they're but they don't have Levi on
them. They're plain but they're Levi and
I think they're like two for 12 or two
for 13 and they're Bro, they're so nice.
They never get hard. They never um you
know. So yeah, you get what you pay for
to an extent. Like I said, I'll never
buy Stone Island ever again in my life.
cuz it's just had it, have it, you know.
But you know what I mean.
Um, but no, if you go if you go you can
only get them from Amazon now, but
they're they're Levis's and yeah, cheap.
I had to do something. I was I've won
quite a bit of money the past two
months, Joe. So, I thought I'd treat
myself to the jeans.
and you wear where where they're mani
they've got like a thing on the back and
if I had jeans I didn't have that at the
back um I wouldn't wear them that's how
funny I am that I'm mad like that
you know it has to have that thing at the back
but like I said when I bought them
before they weren't that they weren't
that expensive they were like 110 which
that that is worth it
110 120 is definitely worth Ammani jeans.
Cuz think about it, you only ever have
Joe two jeans. I don't know about you,
but I only have two jeans. A black pair
and a dark blue pair with stitches.
That's like literally
that's literally it. Like a black pair
and a blue pair with rips.
That's literally it. Two jeans. That's
it. I I wear basketball shorts most of the time.
Yeah. Again, Joe, but there's a
difference. There's a difference between
buying a Primark t-shirt and two Levi
t-shirts for £18. You understand what I'm saying?
There is That's I wouldn't class that as
designer. When we're talking about
designer, we're talking about like Stone
Island and [ __ ] Gucci and [ __ ] All
of that stuff's unnecessary. But I mean
like if you do pay a couple of pound
more then you you you do see the quality
difference. Does that make sense?
There we go.
I mean I've I've got All Saints t-shirts
which are quite expensive. They're like
30 They're like 28 to 30 something each
but they last forever.
They last forever.
Trust me. Like you can wash them a
million times and yeah, I'd never wear
Primark. And here's the thing, Joe. I
tell you something. Yeah. I only have free socks.
Literally only have free socks. Yeah,
cuz I hate socks. Literally. Yeah,
they're like ankle socks. I hate socks.
So I don't [ __ ] um want
um yeah just free sock me free sock.
So do you like the look of my uh football bet?
I wish these fold phones weren't so expensive, bro.
Uh, it's called a washing machine.
Well, I've got more. I've got like five,
but um I uh you only need three socks
because I don't like socks. I hate them.
You just wash them in it. I hate socks.
So, obviously I'll wear socks when I'm
wearing trainers and stuff, but I hate socks, bro.
I just don't like socks, bro. They I
don't know how people sleep in them. So, yeah.
Yeah, it's called a washing machine.
Cuz I have socks.
Cuz I've got socks, matey.
Some people do. Some people sleep in socks.
Some people sleep in socks, bro.
Oh, I need to sign up for this porn
thing as well before I go out drinking
on Friday. I do need to sign up for this porn thing
cuz I was watching this porno Joe and
it's really I said I did before but I
didn't really. I'm actually going to
like sign up for this um porno
cuz I was watching this porno and it was
really getting to my head Joe. It was
really really getting to my head and I
want to really join it bro. I'm being
serious. So before like going out
drinking I need to get that out the way you know.
like my mom and sister will probably
disown me if I join the industry to be honest.
There is a chance they could, but you
got to think about you. You know,
I was watching this porno greasy and um
she was Australian and he was American
and it was in a shop and then she just
starts like sucking his dick and that
and then the customer comes. It's just
mad that that vintage porn really [ __ ]
with your head.
really [ __ ] with your head, bro. That vintage porn
stuff with like Johnny Sins and that
that doesn't bother me. It's just so
fake. It just looks so fake. Obviously,
it's all fake, but it's just
it's just boring because we just like,
you know what I mean? So,
and she was Australian and he was American.
She started giving him a [ __ ] Yeah.
But yeah, I'll be out on Saturday.
Uh, Friday. Sorry. What? Saturday? Yep.
[ __ ] hell, man. I'm going to a nice
Thai restaurant tomorrow with more with my mama
with my mama. Yeah.
Anyway, do you like my football bet? So,
Spenny Moore and Barrow both score no
draw. Sutin and Telford both got no
draw. and slow
action some pronounce it got no draw. Yep.
Yeah, I think that's uh good to be honest, mate.
You wouldn't like my wardrobe then, Joe.
If you don't like designer clothes, you
wouldn't like my wardrobe.
Isn't that right, Greasy? Isn't that right?
I've got like just a little top that's
like 200 pound.
Stone Islands are £300. Yeah.
>> Rocket with them jeans.
Oh, do you know what happened yesterday,
Joe? When I was going to my sisters, it
took me like half an hour to find a
place. You won't know this cuz you don't
live in London, but there's like
apartments that are like there's like 40
of the same [ __ ] names. It's like
court, this court, that court, and
there's about 50 different ones of them.
When I used to deliver food, mate.
Sometimes you'd be there for about 10 15 minutes
cuz they'd be all the same. It' be like
this court, that court, that court, that
court. And you'd have to find mate.
There's about 50
plus of them.
Madness. [ __ ] madness, bro.
I wouldn't mind though. No [ __ ] will help you.
No [ __ ] will help you, mate. No [ __ ]
will help you.
Do you reckon Virgin Boys ever owned a
200lb pair of jeans?
Nah, I don't think so. We can't afford it.
Bit out of his price range.
You reckon Virgin Boys ever been to a steakhouse?
Don't think so. I think it's a bit out
of his price range. Yeah.
I saw that Frankie thing you was on
about, Joe, and I was thinking of giving
it a little whirl. Yeah,
thinking of giving it a little whirl.
But I never so
it's called Frankie Stars or something, isn't it?
Something like that. Yeah, man.
Do would never Joe don't like designer
clothes, but he'll happily gamble gamble
his money away.
What do you think of that greasy £200 on
a pair of jeans?
I think it's absolutely lush.
That's what I think. Don't know about you.
Yeah, I think it's absolutely lush.
Uh, I don't know what it is.
What do you think though, Grezy?
200 a pair of jeans. Well, actually they
were 190, but it's more than 200 pound.
Do you think it's worth it if the jeans
last you two and a half years?
That sounds weird. A website where you
wank and can get money for it.
Strange, isn't it? So, what do you think? Anyways,
£200 on a pair of jeans. agree with you.
That is absolutely lovely, mate.
If Virgin Boy wears the jeans, he might
actually get laid.
He stands a good chance of losing it, mate.
What do you think, Grezy?
Are you into designer clothes, Greasy? You know,
you'd happily gamble your money away,
wouldn't you, Joe? But you won't buy designer clothes.
I'm going to buy Laney a pair of UGG
boots for Christmas.
Yeah, a pair of Ugg boots. Laney wears
my Ralph Lauren top. You know the the
the beige jumper that I used to wear a
few years ago when it used to fit me.
Remember the one when I when I met
Ant-Man the first time in Sheffield?
Laney wears it now. Yeah. Yeah, man.
Oh, I wish I went out with my sister on
Saturday. It sounded like right fun
to people we know and stuff, but too tired, you know,
but there's always Friday. Yeah.
Yeah, man. You're trying to get me to
gamble again, e,
you're trying to get me to gamble again,
ain't you? You [ __ ]
I can't wait for Friday. I'm going to
have a nice drink. I got my haircut last
week, so look all right. Nice jeans, nice blazer, nice top.
Joe, we're going to make a certain person jealous.
The last one I had was I put 50 on the roulette
and I got it to 150.
I like these little pinches. I wonder
how much I've won if I've calculated the
one the wins up over the past
two months. I think it's quite a lot.
The football, the roulette.
Yeah, I think it's quite a lot, isn't it, Joe?
Yeah, it's quite a lot.
Yeah, I'm going to get a certain person
jealous on Friday. Joe, don't you watch that.
I'm gonna get a certain person jealous.
I'm such a [ __ ] Although
you got to be honest, aren't I such a [ __ ] Joe? You know? Yeah.
That [ __ ] is obsessed with me, bro.
That [ __ ] is really really obsessed with me.
It's a bit cringe, isn't it, Joe? Very cringe.
Leave me alone, you virgin. Joseph Barah
he said he's talking about saying 5.7K
the most I've ever shown is 5.7K but the
thing is Joe I think lifestyle style
matters a lot would you not agree with me Joe
would you would you would you not agree
with what I'm saying about lifestyle So,
you know what I mean, bro? I think it's
a lot of it is uh lifestyle, you know,
is also a big thing. Okay, so I showed
5.7 grand. I was eat I was eating
steakouses almost every day, designer
clothes, [ __ ] traveled all over the
country, [ __ ] out twice a week where
someone's got 13 grand and hasn't even been abroad.
Like it's lifestyle is a big thing and
it's also how much you also get.
It's about how much you get, how long
you can show that money for and what
your lifestyle is like.
You understand? It's also about
if the [ __ ] goes abroad again and and
you can see he's still living life and
he still has that amount of money, then
yeah, I'd say that's decent.
But the thing is, you can't show that money now.
So that's that's the thing. You can't
show that money now
cuz you don't have it now.
So that's literally that. So
it's very much to do with lifestyle,
outgoings, how much you get every month.
It's all that kind of stuff. It's not
just, you know,
unless you're showing like a [ __ ] million pound,
you know? So
Ask yourself this question. Why did it
take a [ __ ]
What do you mean, bro?
I mean, I don't go out much now because
I just don't want to. It's not because I
can't afford it. I can afford it. I can
go out every week if I want, but I just
would rather not. I'm going to go back
to every two weeks at some point. When
I've had a long enough break, I'll go
out every two weeks. I won't go out every week.
Maybe every two weeks.
You don't enjoy it as much every week. I
think it's like Yeah.
So, if you can't show the money now,
then it doesn't matter, does it? You know.
Yeah. Exactly. Exactly. You can't I mean
I could still travel the country if I
wanted to every week.
I mean I can still
I think the tip is Joe to win a big
amount of money so you'll be set for a
very very very very long time. I think
that's like the whole thing is you win a
lot of money to last you for a very very long time.
That's the smart That's the smart thing, you know.
I mean, I was thinking of going out
drinking every week just to piss bomb off,
you know, just to say like, "Yeah, I can
go out drinking every week. I can afford
it." You don't know what people have and
you don't know what people don't have. I
was thinking of doing that to be fair.
Like, no [ __ ] bro. I actually was
thinking of doing that
cuz they think that I haven't got money
just because I don't sublet the house
anymore. But I [ __ ] well do. They
don't know what people have, what people
don't have. This is what people's This
is where they they [ __ ] up with this
community. They [ __ ] up badly because
they think everyone's got the same life as them.
They really think everyone's got the
same life as them.
That's where they [ __ ] up, you know? So yeah,
that's why they [ __ ] up badly, bro.
But yeah, like you said, when they have
it or they want it. Yeah.
Well, I could have still showed money,
but I didn't want to show these people
money anymore cuz every time you show
them money, they run away. So,
cuz I was showing the same amount of
money for a very long time
and no one shows you nothing
cuz Yeah. If you show like if you show
13 grand or you show like money or whatever, um
that's supposed to be money that you've
got for like a rainy day.
So you should always have that money cuz
it's or like just like just to have No,
not even rainy day funds. No, you that's
a separate account. There's different
accounts people have. You know when
people work there's different accounts.
They have like a rainy day fund. Then
they have like like which is emergency.
Then they have uh savings and stuff. So
when you're showing £13,000 that's
supposed to be money that's going to be
there for a very very very very very
long time which is the whole point that
you show it off. No, but if you can't
then you know what I'm saying. That's that.
There's different accounts. There's a
savings account. There's a [ __ ]
Yeah. Savings account,
e Yeah. Emergency fund, holiday payment.
When people work, there's different
things, you know.
Know what is the point of that though?
What's the point of saving 3 years to
show 13 grand and had no life because of it?
That's just to me is mental. Doesn't
that seem mad to you, Joseph Farra?
That seems mental, bro.
Yeah, that's what I'm saying. So he
That's ridiculous if you still can't you
can't show it. I said the same thing to
Bomb. Show that money.
Show that money in um yeah
in a year's time. Um yeah, in a year's
time or whatever.
Yeah, I went to the pub, man. Had a nice
Weber spoons breakfast.
I'm thinking, you know, what's the point
of putting 150 on a football bet? You
might as well just put that on roulette in it.
I'm going to hit big one day, bro. Trust
me, I am.
And we'll hit like 50 grand one day.
Don't you worry.
That 100 to 550 was nice.
100 pound in, 550 out. That was lovely.
[ __ ] lovely. That was,
wasn't it, Joseph?
That was lovely, mate.
Just what the doctor ordered.
We don't see you put many football bets
on, Joseph Ferrar.
Why don't we Why don't we see you put
any football bets on? Joseph,
why don't you put any football bets on Joseph Ferrara?
Yeah. What do you What chance do you
reckon that's got coming in? That treble
both score no draw. I think it's got a
good chance. You know that you know that
time. Yeah. When I when I met that
Finnish woman the day after, was it the
day after? No, it was Tuesday. A couple
of days after and I won that football
bet. They both score no draw. the
Darlington and uh
what's the other one? Can't remember the
other team. [ __ ] 120. I got 380.
Oh, bro. I wish I done it on a both
score, no draw.
It was a both score, no draw as well.
But yeah, it was a both score no draw.
I wish I had that 120 on it, mate. It
would have been lovely, ain't it?
But they don't always come in to both
score no draws.
I don't think the northern This is the
Northern League I betted on, but they're
not all playing like normal.
They're easy to get both score no uh
both teams to score on the Northern
League. The South League, any National
League is e is easy.
Yeah, I was going to do them, but I done
the Northern League.
I'd done the Northern League. Yeah.
Yeah. the Northern League,
but they're not playing properly then.
Oh, [ __ ] sake, man. Some money, bro.
You know what I say?
Have a little spin, Joe. Have a little spin.
Have a little spin, matey.
I like that global draw roulette in Lad
Brooks. I might do a session on that
like 150 on it or something.
What do you think, Joseph? Farah. Not even.
Hopefully we get someone on Friday.
Probably not, but
I want to go to this tie restaurant. For [ __ ] sake.
£190 jeans. E almost £200.
A certain virgin could only wish they
could afford that, mate.
Only they would only a certain virgin
would wish, mate. in that.
I ain't going to wash him for a month.
I'll buy some Lush trainers maybe the month after. Oh, Lush.
You can never cuz he's skin. Because
he's [ __ ] skint. That's why
L couldn't even do it. Yeah.
He hasn't been on today, has he?
Do you want to Do you want to p or do
you want to do it dirty?
No, I was actually thinking of like
calling out that Terry properly and
smashing his face in, but
you know, like really smashing his face
proper like big time, bro.
Oh, bro, I could beat him with one hand.
Jesus. You know, I could beat him with
one [ __ ] hand. Ah.
Yeah, I'm thinking of doing it, bro. I
swear to God, that little [ __ ] annoys
me, bro. I swear down.
Just beating the [ __ ] up.
Breezy. So, do you wanna
do you want to do you want to do it dirty then?
Do you want to go for a drink or do you
want to do it dirty?
Do you want to do you want to go for a
pine or do you want to do it dirty?
Yeah. I had my hair cut off Friday, so
it should still look good
for Saturday. Right there. Sorry.
Do my hair nicely.
Yeah. Meet me then. Yeah, dude.
Why do you want to do it, Dy?
Oh, uh, candy man.
I treated myself to a new pair of jeans.
Well, they've not come yet. I've ordered
them. They cost me £200.
I thought, you know what? Let me treat
myself to a nice new pair of jeans. Why
not? My trainers are still looking quite fresh.
So, I've got two trainers, one nice pair
and then one Harachis. I just walk
around and I was thinking, "Yeah, let me uh
let me um treat myself to a new pair of jeans."
[ __ ] 190 with basically £200.
Cuz when I wear jeans, Tanny, man,
they've got to be the same ones. I
always have the same pair of jeans. They
last two and a half years, but like I
say, it's a good investment, isn't it? So
obviously it's out of a certain person's
price range of course, but um not mine,
mate. Not mine.
Not mine, mate.
Yeah, cuz he's [ __ ] skin.
Just like Lord J's [ __ ] skin.
They're both little skin flints. I'm
surprised they don't [ __ ] get on.
I'm going to show the jeans when they
come. They're actually trouser jeans. Yeah,
like I said, a certain version went there, mate.
Went [ __ ] there, mate.
Nah, mate. Nah, no m no no bum bum.
You like my train is
mad. My mom's shoes cost £40.
And there's me to spend £200 on [ __ ] jeans. Um,
maybe when he next visits. Yeah.
Yeah. Any next visits?
A skint and a [ __ ] skin
and a [ __ ] skin. Any job?
Any job, mate?
Any any job, mate? Any [ __ ] job,
mate? No, you're not working. No, mate.
No, no job, mate. No, no, no job, mate.
No, no, no job, mate. No, no.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, man.
Virgin boy needs to get laid. Oh,
my favorite trainers are the Vapor
Maxes. They are lush.
Yeah, they are [ __ ] lush.
[ __ ] lash, mate.
Yeah, them Vapor Maxes are the best. I
think they're so nice. [ __ ] they're
like £200 as well. [ __ ] expensive. Yeah. Jesus. Whoa,
that's kind of pricey. I'll show you my
ones. I don't know. I don't actually
know which ones they are, but I don't
need a new pair of trainers right now.
So, I just rock these with the jeans, I guess. One sec.
I don't know which ones these are.
Don't know which ones these are.
I'm going to wipe them actually.
They still look brand new, huh?
Ready for when the jeans come.
What do you think? You reckon they still look fresh?
I think they do.
I bought these.
Wait, I I think I bought them like four months ago.
Yeah, I bought them months ago.
So, they're still fresh.
Think about to buy another 200 pair of
[ __ ] jeans, bro. Might be skinn after
that or would I? Nah, I don't think so.
But wish I going away soon as well. So
be jeans or
Yeah, I think they still look fresh. I'm
going to wipe them anyways. I get these
special wipes, but I don't have them.
They're like £8. I need to pick them up. Yeah.
And they look pretty fresh.
Yeah, have to look after these things
nowadays, bro. They're so [ __ ] expensive.
[ __ ] they're special wipes you get
from JD, but they're not these ones. And
they're actually they're nice.
I've never really been into like
trainers, bro. Like, I buy an expensive
black pair of trainers and one shitty
pair and that's me done. I've never been
one for collecting trainers, bro. All
you need is is a nice black pair.
A nice black pair
and that's it. And and one for walking
around. So good ones and ones just to do
stuff like the gym and that's it. Never
been into these trainers.
Nope. Why would I be going approaching
today? It's Tuesday. Nah, bro.
Not at all. I'm going out on Friday.
Halloween, isn't it?
No, I was out today, bro. I went to the
pub. I got a breakfast.
I won't be rotten.
>> What's that there?
>> What the [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm going to And then Yeah, they
still look pretty fresh to you, so I
don't need a new pair yet. Maybe I'll
buy a new pair next I don't know, month.
Who knows? Probably not, though.
Why would I go approaching today? It's
Tuesday. I'm going out Friday. It's
Halloween and I'm not expecting anything either
cuz I know that it's like I said, it's
never going to change here. So, I just
want to go out for a drink.
Oh, this is lush, isn't it? Like, the
train is greasy.
These will go nice with my expensive jeans.
I should have got a pack of Levi T-shirts.
It's like two for like £15.
That with the jeans and this. Oh, mate.
Bob's your [ __ ] Bob's your uncle, eh? Yeah,
they're plain ones, but they're made by Levi.
I don't know how much these cost me. I
think they were 150.
I like the air bubbles. I think they're nice.
Oh, what a weird thing to say.
What a [ __ ] weird thing to say, huh?
Me undo the laces.
That was a very weird thing to say, huh? Yeah.
You know that guy on Instagram that uh
gives people free trainers. He says,
"Oh, I can see your kicks. They're
looking a bit worn out." Well, he won't
be saying that to me, bro, when he sees me.
He won't be buying me a new pair of trainers.
Yeah, he he buys people on the street
new trainers, like random people. I
said, "Oh, he won't be stopping me then, will he?
won't be stopping me, bro.
>> Yeah, he comes up on my Instagram. Won't
be [ __ ] stopping me.
Yeah, I follow him. I like how he cleans
trainers and stuff. Yeah.
Yeah. I thought somebody would have noticed him.
No, I like the bubbles, mate.
Yeah, I'll show you my morning jeans,
right? I was like, "Oh, I need to buy a new pair."
Look, these are my old pair.
Yeah, these are my old pair. They done
good for 3 years.
Yeah, they done good for three years.
What can I say?
They're still wearable really,
but the but what happened was I was in
the toilet and the button broke. I done
that and then the button [ __ ] broke.
Yeah, the button broke. So, uh,
luckily I was wearing a belt.
Yeah, they were all last year's. I was
wearing my Stone Island jumper
yesterday. So, with the new jeans
I might wear I was wearing this yesterday.
on my birthday. It's It's [ __ ] gorgeous.
Wait, hold up. What's that? Look where toothpaste maybe. Yeah. That's toothpaste.
Yeah, I wore this yesterday.
So this year with the trainers
and the money jeans. Oh mate,
I could wear this as well. Look, this was £200.
Obviously a certain skin virgin can't
afford it. But again, we're not we're
not uh we're not we're not we don't
bully on this channel. I might give this
to Virgin Boy.
I should give this to Virgin Boy. That's
the closest you'll ever get to designer
cuz he's [ __ ] skin.
Cuz he's a [ __ ] skin flinch.
Because his skin Yeah. [ __ ] skin flinch.
>> Yeah. I'm not I'm never buying Stone Island again.
No, I only bought them jeans that were
200 pound because um
I can't wear any other jeans but Ammani jeans.
I don't think I'll ever buy Stone Island again
to be honest. Nah.
Yeah, I bought um some Ammani jeans, Mr.
B. £200 they cost me. I'm waiting for
them to come.
Yeah, I ordered them this morning. [ __ ] lush.
[ __ ] lush, mate.
Is that where you go?
All I Bro, all I need is two pair of
trainers, two pair of jeans. That's me done.
I've got a pair of jeans from like years
ago when Pat Mustard was still in here.
They still lost.
Would you like to see them, boss?
And yeah, I'm going to wear them jeans
for two months before washing them. I'll
just freereeze them.
Yeah, I'll freze them.
Virgin boy can't afford designer stuff.
He's too [ __ ] skinned
a [ __ ] skin flick.
Your girlfriend don't exist. So that's a
bit hard when your girlfriend don't
exist. Oh, I'm getting a dressing gown.
By the way, my mommy's going to buy me a
dressing gown with a hoodie on it.
So that's lush.
What's that all about? Because they cost £200
and I want to expand their lifespan. Obviously,
I mean, it's it's [ __ ] obvious, though.
But you have to wash them sometimes
because they tighten up when you wash them.
I mean, I'll only be wearing them like
every two weeks.
Yeah. I'll buy a new pair of trailers
maybe next month. Maybe. Um yeah.
Well, how they're not going to be
sticky, you [ __ ] idiot.
I'm going to wear my blazer, my
turtleneck, and them jeans and shoes.
Going to wear them on Friday
because you wouldn't be on here talking
to us right now if you had a girlfriend.
You need to get a life. That's something
we know that you definitely don't have a life.
I think you should go and get a life, dead.
Yeah, definitely need to get a life. A
lot of people here need to get a life to be honest.
Virgin boy needs to get alive
cuz he ain't going to pop it like that.
He ain't going to pop his virginity if
he never gets alive, is he? So,
ah, you're an idiot. Teams don't need to
be washed every day. Yeah.
And you're blocked. Bye-bye. I know
exactly who this is. Bye. Get a life.
Get off YouTube.
Uh uh uh uh.
I know exactly who that is, by the way.
Get alive. Get off of your jobs.
Get off my your jobs.
You need to get off the your jobs, Ruby.
You need to get alive. Oh,
it's that um
it's that Bubbles guy. You know who it
is. You just said
da da da da da da.
Greasy likes the side men.
Greavvesy likes the sideman candy.
Yeah, he said Emma Watson's good-looking
when she was a [ __ ] kid.
Yeah, when she was a [ __ ] kid. He's a
[ __ ] pedo, bro.
Why would you find a kid cute? He's a [ __ ] nons.
Yeah, he's a nons [ __ ] Peter.
I was watching some more GTA San Andreas
videos. Greasy. It says, "Oh, facts
about GTA San Andreas part one, part
two." It's so interesting, bro. They're
still rinsing that game. 20 [ __ ] one
years. It was it was it 21st birthday on
the 26th of October.
And it's still the best game out there, man. Yeah.
Yep. Something like that.
Still need to go my sister. I still
haven't done that yet. Here's attractive
copying. I can't get over that, bro.
Sometimes I think about it like I'll be
chilling and I'll think about it. He
said she's attractive. Candy man. You
wanted to fit in fit in with the crowd.
I can't get over that. You didn't want
to feel left out.
He didn't want to feel left out.
Yeah, my mom knows about Franklin.
He didn't want to feel left out. Quezy,
bless him then if he didn't want to feel left out.
I'm not sure. Do they?
I don't know, man.
What are those? They cost me [ __ ] £190.
You said that she's attractive.
You said she's attractive.
Listen, you wanted to fit in. You didn't
want to feel left out.
Bless him, daddy. If you didn't want to
feel left out, we
wave. You didn't want to feel left out. Bless him.
Bless him if he didn't want to feel left out.
Copycat. A little copycat.
You a little copycat.
You know, anyone can find anyone
attractive, but [ __ ]
to say someone's gay because they don't
find someone attractive. Yeah. That is
copying. That is fitting in. Trying to
fit in with a crowd. Cuz everyone used
to say that to each other.
If you don't find Cheryl Co attractive,
you're gay. Yeah, that's that was the
trend back then. And that is literally
copying because she's not attractive.
And I've been with more women than him.
[ __ ] skin virgin.
Some of the things that [ __ ] comes out
with is is mad.
He's [ __ ] mad. He's he's [ __ ] he's
he's a mad virgin. He's a mad virgin, you know.
[ __ ] mad virgin, man. Yeah.
200B pair of jeans. [ __ ] hell.
No, no, no, no.
Worth it, bro.
Yeah, he's a M. Do you know why I
stopped coming on YouTube Candyman? I
tell you actually one of the reasons why
I don't come on here much anymore is
because you know when I sit there and
and call him a virgin and stuff, people
always jump to his rescue.
Oh, he's not a virgin. He's got a
girlfriend. Nah. But then when he talks
[ __ ] about me, no one says anything.
That's one of the reasons I stopped
coming on here cuz I found it very very
odd. No one would back me up even though
I proved I had sex and stuff and but
then they they'll say, "Oh, we got a
girlfriend." No, no, no.
Not much. No,
I don't come on much anymore. I know.
Do you not find that weird?
Sandy, they'd stick up for him, but not me.
Strange, isn't it?
That's why I thought, oh, maybe I
shouldn't be on here, you know? Yeah, basically.
Yeah. Where's Ricky gone? He's gone
quiet since I put the approaches up.
Oh. Um, yeah. They go for him.
Yeah. He sits there and convinces
himself that I've not had sex with women. um
every day, bro. He sure goes on about
that USA, is he? He's [ __ ] obsessed.
Very, very obsessed.
He thinks I'm a virgin because he's a
virgin. It's madness. Whoa. D Yeah.
Well, well, it is and it isn't
No one spoke about women today.
>> Well, you're wrong because no one spoke
about women today.
Yeah. It's it's like it's it's a hard
one. It is and it isn't. But where he
lives definitely definitely is not London.
Definitely not London, mate. He always
used to say, "Oh, it it counts as
London." No, you're not London. Neither
is your nonad. You don't even sound like
you're from [ __ ] London.
No, you you're not London, mate. Nah.
How can Orington be [ __ ] London?
Gromley is not London. I don't care what
anyone [ __ ] says. I'm telling you it
ain't [ __ ] London.
That's like saying slow was London.
Slow. They've got their own accent which
they don't even sound like us, bro. So,
yeah. I mean, you get to [ __ ] you get to uh
you get to Brmley from [ __ ] Orington.
Um, you get to [ __ ]
Brmley from um
You get to Brmley from um
um you get to Romney from
Victoria and it's nowhere [ __ ] near.
It's nowhere near London. And he doesn't
even sound London.
That's not even a London accent. It's
[ __ ] nons Kent [ __ ] accent.
And stop going about this 13 grand that
you showed ages ago. [ __ ] show it
now. We were speaking about this um
Candy man. Yeah. It's not about what you
you can show. It's about how long you
can show it for, how much you get a
month, and what your lifestyle is like.
Unless it's like a million pound you're
showing. Do you understand? It's about
how long you can show
the same amount of money for
what your lifestyle is, how much you get
a month. That's what it is. Do you understand, bro?
If you can't show that same amount of
money in six months,
then it's kind of like nah.
That's the thing.
You know what I mean, bro?
I'm so glad I don't gamble the way I do anymore, bro.
I used to hate that. I used to hate losing.
You remember Candy?
It wasn't lush. It was [ __ ] stinking, bro.
It was [ __ ] stinking. I might have a
go on the new Frankie, though. Maybe.
Doubt it though.
I don't really [ __ ] with them machines.
I played it the other day when I put 50
pound and got it to 150, but
I don't really
Yeah, [ __ ] with them, bro.
I done my football bet ready for
Saturday. I'm going out Friday. So
yeah, could do. But
so Bonty man got 200 trainers and I got 200 jeans.
No, I really do. Do you know who I want
to [ __ ] up? I want to [ __ ] up that
[ __ ] Terry, bro.
Yeah, I learned the football bet for
Saturday cuz I was near the I was near
the betting shop. So I thought because I
don't live anywhere near a betting shop.
So because I was there, I just thought why not.
Yeah, because I don't live near a betting shop.
And then I would have to go back out to
do it. That's what I mean. Where I used
to live, I used to live
walking distance between B shops.
if you get what I mean. So yeah.
Yeah, man. Yeah, I done a football bet.
I don't know about I don't know. Both
score no draw three teams.
Yep. Candy man. That's wide on
virgin boy skin in his little bed sit
with no bed. No money in it.
Try to get a woman on Friday.
Probably will fail, but
There are some people that have not even
been on a date.
But saying that, right, I don't even
feel like I'm lucky that I've even had a
date or got people. I don't see it as lucky.
Nah, I don't even see it as lucky,
Grezy, cuz I put so much effort and so
much money and so much traveling in.
It's not even It's not even lucky, bro.
Yeah. Oh, I should get that Chucky
thing, but it's not going to be in time for Yeah.
There's people that's not been on dates.
Yeah, because women are addicting as [ __ ]
Women are addicting as [ __ ] That's why
we're saying that I don't use this. I
don't use escorts.
I used to be addicted to roulette and women and curries.
That's all you need in life, eh?
Yep. They're [ __ ] [ __ ]
I I still can't believe that USA. Is he?
She's a [ __ ] absolute [ __ ] isn't it?
I can't believe how she turned into so
much of a [ __ ]
Uh, all women. All women.
Do you reckon I should have went to
Scotland last week and met that woman? Um, Gravesy. Nah,
not yet. What they will do the more I meet them, you know.
What is that?
You don't want to know. Yeah.
Never done it in my life. You weirdo.
You absolute weirdo.
I was sending this woman my dick picture.
What happened there, bro? Phone died.
Yeah, my phone died.
Yeah, man. This woman keeps ignoring me
on Instagram. I keep calling her, sent
her my dick picture. She keeps clicking
on a message. I'm not going to stop
until she blocks me.
I will not stop until she blocks me. Greenso
in it. Stop being a [ __ ] annoying
ignoring idiot [ __ ]
You know what I mean, bro?
I don't need donations, matey.
Yeah, because it's annoying them ignore
me. My my whole goal was to get them to
block me. I don't like someone sitting
there ignoring me on purpose, Candy.
I just want them to block me. That's it.
They keep kicking on my message, being annoying,
being a stuck up [ __ ] Yeah,
you can tell they're doing it on purpose
to be annoying as well.
Yeah, I'm going to I'm going to pull on Friday.
On Friday, I'm going to pull.
Yeah, I'm going to pull on Friday, bro.
Of course, I'm going to pull.
>> Yeah. Why Why would I pull? Of course
I'm going to pull on Friday, bro.
It's not going to be like the other
million times I've gone out and tried.
Why would it?
I'm looking forward to this meal that
lady's taking me to.
Nah, pull your mom.
The dirty slapper.
You like that one, Gucci? Oh gosh.
The Franklin's on the telly.
with that cute greasy. Bro,
all women are all the same. We already
know women are all the same.
I mean, I was joking. Of course, it's
going to be the same, but I just want to
go out for a drink anyways.
Yeah, we already know women are all the same candy.
It's nothing new, is it?
I won't mind, bro. I know they're all the same.
Women are all the [ __ ] same. We
already know all of that.
Of course, they were the same. Uh no,
I'm still going to try with women.
Do you remember Candy man? Go on um go
on dating apps for sex.
Oh, do you know that Hugh guy? I caught
him talking [ __ ] about me. [ __ ]
[ __ ] He will never come back on his
channel, will he? Nah.
The guy's skin and he's trying to talk about me.
Nope. Even good looks is not good enough.
Even if you're good-looking, you still
won't get women.
They've got unrealistic standards. Even
if you are good-look
and there's no skill either. You can't
change somebody that's got unrealistic standards.
Why would I turn gay?
How about I just live life without a woman?
How do I know? Because I am decent
looking when I go out. And again, the
problem stems from social media. It
doesn't stem from an individual.
So, I'm not saying we're not talking
about my looks. This is not a
conversation about my looks. Thank you
very much. You can take your
insecurities elsewhere. But the problems
stem from from social media. It's not an individual, you know.
We're not talking about my looks. We
don't have insecure people on my
channel. Thank you very much.
Anyways, Joe, why would I why would I turn gay? you know. Um,
well, do you tell women that moan about
men to turn lesbian, Joe? Thought not, mate. Thought not.
Nah. Didn't think you did, did you? Nah.
Double standards, but who cares?
That's not going to bother us, you know.
Nah, so many double standards. Hey, I
find the double standards quite
interesting to be honest.
Well, no one else does. Well, it's
funny, Joe, because let me tell you
something. I've never heard somebody say
to a woman, "A man don't owe you
nothing." Never in my life. And I've
been on Reddit for years. I've been on
the internet for years. And I have never
ever ever heard it.
Never ever heard it in in all the years
I've been on the internet. I've heard
people say women don't know you
anything. I' I've heard him say to other
people, but I've never heard that.
Um, no one spoke [ __ ] about USA when she
tried to meet me as soon as she met me.
No one had a problem with that.
But if you try to meet a woman within a
week of speaking to her, we're calling
the [ __ ] FBI, mate. You're going down. You know,
you know what I'm saying? You You
approach a woman, Reevesy,
a and and you try to meet her within a
week. I'm coming to get you. I'm coming
for you, son. But a woman, oh, she can
meet you straight away. That's
completely fine. But you tried to meet a
woman within a week. You're too pushy.
You're coming on too strong.
I don't think we'll ever know what that
means, Joe. I don't think we'll ever
know what that actually means. Coming on
too strong. I'd love for one one day for
somebody to to sit there and explain to
me what coming on too strong means, but
I don't think we'll ever know to be
honest. It's just something that some
people say, but it don't really mean
anything, you know?
Bit weird. Bit [ __ ] weird, but you know,
you know what I mean?
You can understand the double standards, right, Joe?
But no, I've never I've never had a woman say
uh I've never had somebody say to a
woman, "A man don't owe you anything."
I've never seen that.
Never seen that. And I think that's what
my problem was is it's not that they say
it to men, is they never say it to women.
What do you mean a balanced approach and open mind?
I get what you're saying, bro, but
that's easy. Yeah, I get what you're
saying, but it's easier said than done, Joe.
You know, it's uh it's that's that's
very easier said than done. You know,
you understand what I mean? It's like,
you know, when you say go out right and
don't let it bother you, technically,
yes. But it's not as easy as that,
you know, because when you put time and
money in and you get nothing out of it,
it's not good, is it? You know, let's
let's It depends on the It depends on
the circumstances, you know.
Like if you went out and you spent 150
and you got three numbers that didn't go
anywhere, oh well, you know, it's not
that bad. But you can get 10 numbers and
not even get a date.
That's the That's the problem. It's very
hard to stick to it, you know,
like I can go out and and I'm and I'm saying Friday, you know,
and I'm hoping it doesn't bother me. I'm
sure it won't bother me, but I'm hoping
the next day it doesn't bother me
either. I'm hoping now that last time I
got 10 numbers,
didn't even get a date. I don't think it
will bother me now. I know like it's
never going to happen in this country,
you know. It's if that that is what you
needed to to maybe not let it piss you
off ever again, then
I'm hoping it doesn't bother me. I don't
think it will to be honest.
But yeah, you shouldn't let it bother you. But
that's it's hard not to let it bother
you if if you you know, especially when
there's no reason for it. like you're
not fat and ugly and stuff, but it's we
shouldn't let it. But it's you can't
help it, you know? Like you're telling
me getting 10 numbers and not one single
date wouldn't annoy you. Wouldn't annoy
you, Joe. That's disgusting. And the
fact that I spent £500 as well.
Do you understand what I'm saying? It's [ __ ] up.
That is disgusting, bro. Like you can't
you you can't even say to someone that
that is [ __ ] you know.
But yeah, I'll be out on Friday.
Hi, Joker. Ordered myself a nice pair of
Ammani jeans. They cost me £200.
Well, £190 to be exact. So, yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] hell. Yeah.
Yeah. I've never seen somebody say to a
woman that a man doesn't know anything. Nope. No.
Yeah, but it's the only thing that you can do.
Yeah. It's not going to work 99.99999%
of the time, but there's still a very,
very slim chance that it will work.
Think about it. If I didn't approach,
I'd be a virgin. I'd be like nonslegs.
Yeah, but I I know that. But that's the
only thing you can do
except leave the country, which is what
I'm doing. If I didn't approach, there'd
be no USA. There'd be no Sig. There'd be
no no one.
So, you understand? Why do you think I
don't approach sober? cuz
it's I can't be bothered. I know it
doesn't work. I'm not scared. I can
approach anyone, but that I'm going out drinking
because that's all you can [ __ ] do.
There's nothing else you can do.
No, it's not working.
Nothing works in this country.
I've even offered people [ __ ] money.
It don't work.
What's the alternative until you can
leave, which I'm leaving next month, or
if you wanted to stay in this country,
what's the alternative?
If you still have hope, which I don't
have hope anymore. I'm going out cuz I'm
going out. What's the alternative?
Use dating apps that don't work.
You understand what I'm saying? So, you know,
this Ba guy is a is a white night, lad.
What? So, be happy that
you're never going to have sex again.
No, the alternative is No, the
alternative is is you enjoy your life
just using escort or you join the porn industry.
That's what the alternative is. That's
something that will work, you know.
Well, that's the whole point of me
joining trying to join the porn
industry. That's that would work.
That is what would work.
Yeah, you could join the board industry.
There's a few options. You can join the pool industry
or you leave.
There's nothing. What else are you going to do?
I got a football bet on for Saturday.
I'm going to go for some drinks on Friday.
My mom's taking me to a nice restaurant. Um, yeah.
I'm obsessed with [ __ ] Joe.
But USA is treated me as a transactional thing.
You buy my meal, I give you sex. That
was pretty transactional.
So, it's okay for women to see me as
transactional. That was very
transactional. There was no love. There
was no substance. just nothing.
But I I'm I'm not allowed to to to to to
see things as transactional, you know, no,
I was thinking about that yesterday. You
know, that whole USA thing, bro,
when her friend was trying to be cocky.
Does her friend really want to go there
with me, bro? About Oh, yeah. Like if
you went there was I think they said if
you went the first time I was going to
get people out for you. I was like are
you mad bro? I bring who you [ __ ]
want. The one I was on the I was on the
phone with for like 5 hours.
Bro, you're not going to bring anyone.
See like that's that that kind of [ __ ]
pisses me off. Then I was thinking about
doing Terry in, you know,
really thinking of smashing that [ __ ]
in, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. So that's it.
But it's still better than nothing, is
it? Okay. Put it this way, Joe. Okay.
Put it this way. Let Let me Let's use
this analogy. Yeah. Let's use this analogy, right?
If I didn't approach, okay, okay, let me
let me let me use this analogy. If I
didn't approach, I wouldn't even be able
to talk to a woman. Okay? If I approach
If I message a woman on Instagram, I'm
not getting a conversation.
If I message a woman on Facebook, I'm
not getting a a conversation.
Do you get it? You're not getting even a
conversation out of someone. You know,
at least if you approach someone, you
can get a combo. If you get the number,
they could talk to you.
You know, that's [ __ ] up. Do you not
think that's so [ __ ] up?
Like, just hear me out for a minute. Do
you not think that is so mad?
That is kind of mad, isn't it? Like,
it's not even about a date. It's about
even if you wanted to have a
conversation with a woman, you would
literally physically have to go out and approach. Mad.
That is mad, bro. That is [ __ ] mad, isn't it?
You know why that is? It's cuz of all
the simps. All the white knights.
It's all It's because of all the white knights.
And the simps, isn't it, Joe?
They [ __ ] the game us. They They [ __ ] up
the game for us.
The white knights [ __ ] the game up.
Yeah, they [ __ ] it up for us, bro.
Them [ __ ] white knight [ __ ]
Isn't that right?
Uh, no negativity on my chat. All right.
Yeah, he's a simp. When will these
people realize that singing will never
get them laid?
They sit there all all their life virgins
defending women, but women don't like
them. They never they will never learn,
will they? These people will never
[ __ ] learn, mate.
And the only reason Natalie got back
with Monty is because she felt sorry for him.
She done it out of pity. It's mad, isn't it?
Is that right? Joseph Farah, you know?
No. No. No. It never because they were
already together. It hasn't. Because
they were already together. That's different.
That's different, bro. Because they were already together.
It wasn't somebody that he's never been
with before. See? Okay. That 19year-old,
right? Do you know how many times she
used to come back to me? I never sed once.
I never sed once. It He had already been
with her. If he hadn't already been with
her, she wouldn't have got with him.
They had already been together.
Like that 19year-old came back to me a
good four or five times and I never sed.
I ignored her and she kept messaging me
like they had already been together.
That's the difference. These white
knights are doing it to people that
they've never [ __ ] been with.
And women still don't like them. It's
mad. It's [ __ ] madness.
Yeah, sorry about that.
Yeah, but they don't even give you the
chance, dojo, Joe. But does it does it
matter what I want? Cuz even if you want
a relationship, you're not even going to
get a relationship. So why does it matter?
I mean, why does it matter about sex and a [ __ ]
I mean, you can't even get a date. And
also, no, there's been times where I've
met people before that I would have
waited for sex.
I mean, yeah, we want sex. We want a
[ __ ] but if we meet someone, that's
worth it. We're not going to expect it straight away. I mean,
we're not going to [ __ ] expect that
straight away, are we? So, I mean, it
could be anything. It could be sex, a
relationship you want. you're still not
going to get it. So why why does it
matter whether it's sex, a relationship, a [ __ ]
Let's just Okay, let's just say for
argument sake, right? I want Okay, let's
just say that I want a relationship.
Okay, let's just say that I want a
relationship, right? And I and I can
wait a month, two months for the sex.
Okay, and then what? What? Women are
going to suddenly stop pretending that
they've got boyfriends.
Would I wait six months? Yes, I would. I mean, yeah.
Yeah, I would.
But let's just say that you wanted a
relationship. People are not just going to
I don't put any effort into getting a
woman. Wait, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Let me I'm not reading this correctly.
You're you you don't put any effort into
getting into you haven't put any effort
into getting a woman.
Nah, I haven't traveled all over the
country. I haven't approached thousands
of people. Nah, you're right, bro. It
must be a different PJ. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Must be a different PJ, bro. Yeah. Um,
did you watch my approaching videos, Bubba?
One second, Joe. Stay out of this a
second, please. Um, did you watch my
approaching videos I put on my channel?
I mean, I'm pretty sure there was
there's two videos right there where
um, they said they weren't interested
before even getting to know me. Pretty
sure there is a few where I've had
conversations and they haven't even
given me the chance.
again. You might want to go on my
approaching videos, man.
Yeah, you might you might want to watch
my approaching videos and come back.
I assume Joe's already watched them.
This is what I mean. You This is what
I'm saying is that you dismiss people's
struggles, Joe. This is my whole point.
You're talking about sex and [ __ ] and
all of this [ __ ] It's all irrelevant.
If you watch my approaching videos, you
would know how it's irrelevant. I mean,
you of all people, Joe. I don't waste my
time on these other people because
they're just [ __ ] white knights and
you're never going to get through to
them. So, they can live their life how
they want to live. But, I mean, I put up
approach videos for you. I put them up for Ricky.
I mean, when did any of them women give
me a chance to get to know me?
So, so it's like you're you you seem to
dismiss people's struggles. That's my
whole point. Joker, you can show these
people, right? Women leading you on. And
I don't care about it anymore, bro. I'm
over it. But I'm just saying it as a
thing. Yeah. You could show these people
women leading you on. Women saying
they're not interested before you even
finish your sentence. You can show women
[ __ ] with you and they will sit there
and still be like, "Nah, never
happened." No, no, no, no. They'll
literally nod their head like a dog.
Like, you can't get through to these
people, bro. That's why they they can
live their life and you live your life.
If they want to if they want to sit
there and defend women all their life
and be virgins, that's their life, bro.
Maybe they're happy with that.
Yes, but dating apps don't to work,
which we've been over this a million times.
You know what I'm saying?
Dating apps don't work. So, you the only
thing you have is approaching. That's
the whole point.
Literally, the whole point is that's all
you've got. We're aware that it's 2025.
So, no, you don't want to understand the
ebike. You You don't want to understand
it. And I've been on plenty of second
dates, but you don't want to understand
it. Trust me, you you you don't want to
understand it. You You really really
don't want to understand it.
Because even if somebody showed you
differently, you'd still deny it. So,
you really really don't want to
understand it. What you do want to do is
just simp and white knight. you you
seriously don't want to understand it.
You know, I've put enough evidence out
there in black and white, like a black
and white cat, and you still deny it. So,
I think we're going to I think we've
come to the um conclusion that we're
always going to agree to disagree
cuz the thing is, Candy, man, they're
arguing with black and white evidence.
I don't know how people can argue with
black and white evidence.
Do you not find that weird how how they
they like saying one thing is another?
But they've actually been shown what
they've actually done and they still
defend them. Crazy. But again, people
can live their own life. Like I said, if
they want to defend women and be virgins
and [ __ ] that's that's up to them, bro.
I don't give a [ __ ]
And also friends wouldn't um
friends wouldn't um friends wouldn't
hook you up cuz everyone's out for themselves.
If dating apps don't work, why are they
still in business making money? Uh
because people pay for the subscription
because they get conned. I mean, again,
I done a video on dating apps.
I mean, what what's the whole point of
this conversation? I don't understand
the whole point of this. You're saying
one thing, even when I show you another,
you still sit there and and deny it. So,
what the [ __ ] and then you're saying
I'm not a nice person all because I've
shown evidence of what women's done. The
whole thing is ridiculous. The whole
argument doesn't even make sense.
No, no, no. Everyone's out for
themselves in that way. Whether they're
good friends, whether they're bad
friends, literally everybody is out for
themselves. Probably even family
members. I would I was I I would go as
far as saying even your family members
are out for themselves.
Uh, my logic doesn't my my logic doesn't
suck suck ass because I've shown
evidence. Anyways, we're going round and
round in circles. I'm not having this
conversation. It's boring. I've put the
evidence out there. If you want to deny
it, that's on you. Good for you. So, yeah.
I mean, it's not ridiculous.
I'm not going to sit here and argue,
bro. Like, I put videos out there. I
don't care. Like I'm not going to sit
here and argue. The evidence is there
for a reason. If you can't be bothered
to watch it, that's on you.
So yeah, that's ridiculous. It's You've
seen evidence and that's it. Deny all
you want. I don't care.
Yeah. Okay. Good for you. Anyways,
moving on out. Pointless conversation.
Yeah, pointless. These sips were never
ever going to learn. So, just leave them
to it, bro.
Anyways, moving on now.
Uh, the reason why I'm moving on, Candy,
is because we're just going back and
forth, back and forth, back and forth,
and it's just pointless because no
matter what you show them, they're just
going to deny it. So, cuz it doesn't
suit them. So, I mean, there's no point
of this whole thing. So, yeah,
pointless. Absolutely pointless. So, yeah,
I'm not approaching today
and it won't change cuz I've done a
million different approaches before.
It doesn't change. So, yeah.
I mean, I put videos up where they say
they're not interested straight away. I
put videos up where the dating apps
don't work and I'm still having people
argue with me. It's madness.
Well, I feel bad for them. I really do,
man. I really feel bad for them. But yeah, it's crazy,
man. So many simps. So many white knights.
Must be autism, is it? I I definitely
think it's autism. This whole white
knight in It's definitely autism, in it, you know.
I think it's autism here. Definitely.
They're defending women and [ __ ] It's
definitely definitely autism.
you know, and then we're talking about
[ __ ] and sex. That's got nothing to
do with anything, you know. So,
I didn't ask them out immediately.
I didn't ask them out immediately, mate.
If you actually watch my approaching
videos. Anyways, we're going round in circles. So yeah.
anyways, moving on now. I'm not getting
into this [ __ ] argument again. $89 $900.
Yeah, I'm not Nothing's worse. I don't
even know why we're talking about this
again, bro. I don't give a [ __ ] I'm
going out Friday cuz I want to go out.
I don't know why they keep going on
about it. I don't give a [ __ ] Like, I
know what women are like. I know they're
all the same. I don't give a [ __ ] I'm
not moeding about it.
I don't give a [ __ ] about it. They're
the ones that keep bringing it up.
Yeah, you will be single forever as
well. White nighting women,
you know, defending women all your life.
Sad. Sad, sad people defending women.
Sad, sad bastards.
You know, why is there so many white
knights and simps? I don't understand
it. It's They're never going to get
laid. Women don't like them. I don't
know why they defend women their whole lives.
Yeah, I'm going to the restaurant tomorrow.
I don't know why they do it. I'd love to
know why they do it, but they're never
going to answer, are they? They
literally think it will get them laid.
It's just mad, bro, why they do it. I
don't know why they do it.
And the irony is you've been with more
women than them. That's the most that's
the most [ __ ] up thing about it. You know,
it takes a certain person with autism
to ignore black and white evidence.
Like black and white evidence. Even when
they're showing black and white
evidence, they're like, "Nope, no, no,
no, no, no,
nah, bro. Definitely, definitely
definitely not." And this incel has been
with more women than you. There's no
chance of you ever getting laid. Women
don't like white knights. Women don't
like simps. They hate them. But you
still defend them. This is what makes me
laugh is that they don't want white
knights. They don't want simps. But they
still defend women.
They're like, "These people, most of
these people are virgins. Women don't
like them." And they still defend them.
That's why I think it's autism. It's
because it doesn't make sense. This is
what I mean. It does not make sense.
You've got these white knights that have
never been anywhere near a woman trying
to tell you that you're an insult.
Trying to tell you that you're wrong. It's mental.
It is mad. It is crazy.
Really is, bro. Really [ __ ] is.
Oh man. So
[ __ ] All women are perfect. What a white night.
So many white knights
are wild sympa.
They're all [ __ ] white. You get them
in the [ __ ] club as well, you know.
Ew, a s.
a simp appears. Joker.
Ew. I'm going to have to block you, bro,
if you keep saying this stuff. It's
cringe as [ __ ]
And this is why you're still a virgin.
Saying stuff like this, ebike is why
you're still a virgin, lad.
Um, no. Because I already know the
answer. I can tell you.
I I I cuz I cuz I know the answer. But
you don't need to know that, do you?
Because that's got no relevance to me.
I already know the answer. I don't need
to ask them how because that has got
nothing to do with me.
That's got nothing to do with me.
I don't compare myself to strangers.
Waste of time. comparing is a waste of
time. And it's a weak argument as well.
It's a very very very weak argument.
Very, very weak argument. Comparing is ridiculous
considering meeting somebody is based on
luck and some people can never get lucky.
So that's why it's literally Well, I
need to block this [ __ ]
this little s, this little [ __ ]
little self projector. Um, the answer is
is they met before Instagram when they were kids.
They met as kids.
Yeah, they met when they were young kids.
Yeah, stop talking about yourself,
benefit claimment. Yeah, stop talking
about yourself like that. Stop self
projecting your fat, ugly virgin life
onto me. Anyways, um yeah, they met when
they were kids when they were like 11.
That's how they met Joe. Yeah. That's
got no relevance to me in 2025.
Yeah. They uh they met as as kids. Yeah.
Met as kids before. Yes. Like I said, social media,
like I said, it's got no relevance to me in 2025. you know.
Yeah, they met through kids. They met
they met when they were kids. Sorry.
So why why is what's that got to do with me, bro?
There was this guy that was 35. He said
he's never been on a date. No, it's
[ __ ] So why why do you want to know how
they met? Anyways,
why why do you want to know how they met, bro?
Is that supposed to mean that I'm going
to meet someone?
There there's just people in this world,
Joe. Listen. Listen. There's just people
in this world that's just not made for someone.
That's that's just what it is. There's
no there's nothing about it. It is what
it is. There's just people
that are not made for anyone
like me, like other people.
I don't know what the big deal is.
It's there just there's just not someone for everyone, you know?
Yeah. I don't know what the big deal is.
It's not a big deal. There's not someone
for everyone. That's it.
So, I don't give a [ __ ] either way.
Yeah. There's not someone for everyone.
100% there's not
I mean look how many times I had to go
out and approach just to get the text I did crazy crazy lad
n it's not to do with the location it's
to do the whole the whole of England and
[ __ ] I've traveled all over the country
it's a westernized problem lad
it's a westernized problem uh I I mean,
if you Okay. Okay. Put it this way. If
you live I think if you lived out if you
lived out of London, if you lived out of
London, then yeah, you might meet
someone in like 6 months or a year, but
you wouldn't just meet someone straight
away. But I've been to Leeds. I remember
when I went to Leeds cuz this black guy
kept banging on about it. He said, "Oh,
you should go to Leeds. You should go to
Leads." I think it was one of the last
places that I went to. This guy used to
speak to this black guy on um this form.
He said, "Oh, yeah. You should go to
leads. You should go to leads. Went to
leads, bro. Got nothing. Not even a
kiss. I swear to God. Yeah. I didn't
even get a [ __ ] kiss.
You won't meet someone straight away.
You know, bro, you're not going to
You're not go Oh, bro. It's not London.
Okay, Candy. I've traveled all over the country.
I don't know if you're new to my
channel, but I've traveled all over the
country, bro. It's not because it's London.
It's the whole of the west. It's the
whole of the West. So yeah,
bro, we're not talking about my looks.
Get your insecure ass out of here. No one's interested.
You're never ever going to make me feel
insecure about the way I look. You're
wasting your time, honestly.
But yeah, Candy, it's not Why do you
think, Bro, listen. Why do you think
it's London's the problem?
Why do you think London's the problem, bro?
Why you Why do you think it's London and
not anywhere else? I've been to
Manchester 10 times and only had sex
once there. I've been to Manchester 10
times, bro. and I've been to Liverpool.
Uh, it's not about personality.
Again, we're not going to go over this.
I put the evidence out there already.
I'm not going to argue. It's not about personality.
It's about personality. Once you've already [ __ ]
passed the [ __ ] unrealistic standard
threshold, then it's about personality.
Personality is like the the third thing
they go for. It's [ __ ] That
personality thing is absolute bollocks,
mate. It's a cover up. It's an absolute
Cuz if it was about personality, Yeah.
you'd be going on dates constantly.
Whenever you go out and you approach
someone, people would be giving you the
chance to get to know you. You know,
it's not about personality.
It's about they've got unrealistic
standards and they're stuck up. It's not about personality.
You don't get to know someone's
personality within 10 seconds, mate.
They say it's about personality, Candy,
man. Yeah. Oh, there's Oh, here we go.
Millions of people in relationships
again comparing. It's always the same
argument. There's millions of people
that are single. Most of the people that
I know are single.
Most of the people I know are single. So
that just destroys your argument.
They are single as a Pringle. Yes, they
the [ __ ] they are. Whether it's
WhatsApp, whether it's Instagram, and
people that have got no connection to
each other. Most of these people are
single. So if there's millions of people in relationships,
there's millions of people um single. I
don't know how many people are single.
I'm guessing it's got to be millions
because candy most of the people that I
know they are single. Even my sister's
single now. All of the people I know are
single. I know some people in
relationships but most of them are
single. They are, bro. They are.
They really, really, really, really are.
So that argument
doesn't even make sense.
So many people that are single. Look,
even these women that gave their number,
I'm wasting my time. They're single.
Single. Single women. Single men. But
there's millions of people in
relationships. But yet so many. Yeah,
you are a ma.
Yeah, stop talking about yourself. You
are a ma. Don't talk about yourself like that.
You are a ma.
Stop picking on yourself.
But yeah, they are most of the people
are single here
cuz I approach a lot of people
and these people are single.
But there's millions of people in
relationships. Well, there's got to be
millions of people that are single then.
If there's millions of people in
relationship, there's got to be millions
of people that are that are single.
There's got to be. There's too many
single people that you come across. You know,
most people I would say more people are
single than in relationships.
Men anyways. It has to be because all of
the people that I come across.
But again, it's pointless trying to
explain something to a [ __ ] So yeah,
they say it's about personality candy,
man. It's [ __ ] Absolute [ __ ]
Because you know, if you if you was a 10
out of 10 man, this is how [ __ ] up it
is. And you said that you was a non, a
woman would probably still get you.
That's how bad it is. You know, they've
done experiments on this before.
They've done experiments on this before, bro.
You could say that you you like kids and
they probably would still get with you.
I swear to God, bro. I'm not even
talking [ __ ] Someone's done a Tinder
experiment on this before. So, yeah.
So, that whole personality thing is [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] Absolute [ __ ] Just
like men don't go for personality to
begin with. I don't know why why are we
even talking about this, bro. It's [ __ ] ridiculous.
But bro, no, it's true though. No, no,
bro. Listen, somebody done a Tinder
profile of a man saying that he was a
child predator, right? I don't think
they said he was a N, but he said that
he was a child predator and women still
wanted to meet him, still wanted to get
with him. And then the average guy, they
weren't interested in him.
So that tells you that it's not about personality.
If you're not someone's physical type or
preference, they're not even going to
give you a chance.
It's obvious. It's not about personality.
[ __ ] sake. I don't know why people
keep saying that about that personality
thing. It's again, it's a cover up.
It's not personality at all.
So, it's just a lame excuse. So, yeah.
Anyways, we're blocking you now. You're
boring. Bye-bye, Bob. Bye-bye.
So many [ __ ] simps. What is wrong
with these insecure simps? madness
always bringing hate on my channel,
aren't they, Candy?
I think a lot of these these white
knights are self- projecting as well.
Yeah, I think a lot of them all um self projecting.
That's why they're virgin in the first
place. You know,
there's not mill if there's millions of
people in relationships,
there will be millions of people single as well.
There will be millions of people single.
There's got to be them. But these people
don't leave the house or they don't know
about life. You will meet a bird soon.
No, I won't. Last time I went out,
Joker, was six weeks ago. I got 10
numbers and I didn't even get a date. I
think that that ship has sailed. Being positive,
that ship has sailed, bro. You You're
not going to meet anyone. That's not
being negative. That's being real. I got
10 numbers and only one replied.
I don't think I'm going to meet someone somehow, bro. So,
yeah, that's you're not going to meet if
that doesn't tell you you're not going
to meet someone. I don't know what will
to be honest.
I mean, like I said, I'm going out
Friday cuz I want to go out. So, yeah, that's that.
Tanny, man, you're saying about keeping positive,
but I got 10 numbers and only one replied.
Yeah, there's no positivity to be had after that.
That's delusional. If you're trying to
be positive after that, you're delusional. So,
and I don't know. Yeah,
you're right, Joker. It's totally going
to be different than the other million
other times I've tried.
Yeah, today uh Friday will be the day, won't it?
I don't even know why I entertain you on
here. You're all [ __ ] idiots.
You're absolute idiots, aren't you?
I mean, this is why I don't really come
on here much, cuz you're you're just
[ __ ] idiots, isn't it?
No other way to describe you as
other than just Yeah, [ __ ] idiots.
You actually are idiots, aren't you on here? Absolute idiots.
Why go out if I know the answer? Okay,
for the minute of time, I'll repeat
myself again because I want to go out drinking anyways.
I don't have no hope because I don't
approach sober anymore because there's
no hope because I'm going out drinking
anyways and there's nothing else to do.
It's It makes sense. No,
I didn't go out for 6 weeks. I've had
the money to go out. I've had the time
to go out, but I haven't for 6 weeks. 6
There's no hope. You're an idiot, you know.
Yeah. Okay. Yeah. Thailand is something
to be positive about. Yeah. You
can't tell me that I'm going to meet
someone in this country. And I can back
up my claim and I'll back it up for the
simple reason is that the last time I
went out, I got 10 numbers and only one replied.
Now, that tells me everything that I
need to know along with all the other things.
That is insane. So, I want to go out
because I want to go out. If there was
hope, you would have had a date out of
one of them 10 numbers. You would you
would have met one of them again, but
you didn't meet any of them again. So, I
don't think you're suddenly just going
to fall into a relationship or I mean,
you can barely get a conversation out of someone nowadays.
One out of 10. We got 10 numbers and one
out of 10 replied.
So yeah, I don't think you're you're
suddenly going to fall into a
relationship or start getting sex
somehow. Joseph Fra, you know, insane, bro.
Yeah. One out of 10 replied, sir. So
you're all idiots on here.
You absolute [ __ ] idiots on you. On
here you are.
[ __ ] absolute idiots, mate.
How come you s idiots on here? Joseph, huh?
And Joseph says the past don't dictate
the future. Well, it does. Yeah.
Yeah, you've got to think positive
because the next time you go out, you're
suddenly going to meet someone, right?
Well, we'll see in it. Let Well, time
will tell, won't it?
Uh, well, actually, the way you think is
to do with your life experiences. So,
I've I've had good experiences. Not really.
Not really. I've basically been [ __ ]
over by every single woman.
So, to be honest with you, no, I really
haven't had any good experiences,
which is how I know they're all the
same. But that doesn't matter anyways, does it?
I haven't really had good experiences.
That's also another reason why I don't
try anymore because it's not about
boyfriends. Joseph Fra, it's not about
you approaching somebody and them saying
that they've got boyfriends. See, you
think that's what the problem is. That's
not the problem. Or somebody walking
away. That's not the problem. See, you
seem to think that's the problem, but
that can't be the problem because every
single time you go out, every single
time you go out, you get numbers, right?
That's not the problem.
You know, it's a bit annoying, but
that's not the problem. The problem is
is the leading on and the ghosting and
people going on dates to waste your
time. That's what the problem is.
And obviously, yeah, getting numbers
that lead you on and the numbers that
don't reply. It's not about people just
saying that they've got boyfriends. I
think it's a bit more to it than that, you know. So,
get 100 numbers. Do you know how long
that's going to take to get 100 numbers?
And you're wrong because I think I've
got over 100 numbers and I haven't even
got a date.
Pretty sure the last day I went on was April. So,
I think I must have got over [ __ ] 100
numbers since then.
No, I'm just going to wear I'm going
out. Yeah. Well, I'm just going to wear
normal clothes. No fancy dress. No, I'm
just going to be wearing normal clothes.
You could do what I do. Never say never.
Anyone can do it.
Anyone could [ __ ] do it, man. Why Why
can't you do it? Huh? But
yeah, it's also the bad experiences.
It's not just about people saying that
they got boyfriends.
That's not what the problem is.
It's the leading on the trolling
which people seem to dismiss. So yeah.
Wow. It did [ __ ] me for two weeks. So
yes, but that's not going to work, Joe.
Because just because you meet somebody
that's got the same interest as you, it
doesn't mean they're going to get with
you. Okay, let me put it this way. I
would say a lot of women have got the
same interests as me. You know, cooking,
traveling, same types of food, etc.,
etc., etc. Yeah. Horror movies.
I'm pretty sure there's a lot of women
out there, ones I've met personally,
that have got the same interests as me,
but they still won't get with me. So,
it's not about that, you know? Like,
mate, I've got approaching videos on my
channel. If you can't be bothered to
watch them, that's on you, you know?
That's on you, bro. Like if if you don't
want to watch them, that's
that's that's your fault, man. I'm not,
you know, I'm not going to um
I'm not going to explain it. So yeah,
but that's what you have to do, Candy
man. You have to go out. You have to
approach. You have to get rejected. You
have to waste money just to be in with a
chance to get a date.
Crazy how life works, isn't it?
It's crazy how it works, eh? Not really.
Oh, the the the what the girl tenant
unblocked me by the way, but I haven't
unblocked her, but I can see she's unblocked me.
Yeah, she can [ __ ] right off. Stupid
but no, I don't. No. Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] sake. Yeah.
Yeah, it's [ __ ]
It is [ __ ] It is [ __ ]
And people always like
twist things as well. Like say you
approach a woman, right? and say and and
and they don't talk to you. Somebody
will be like, "Oh, well, how would you
feel if a woman?" They'll be like, "Oh,
how would you feel if a fat woman who is
ugly comes talking to you, but that's
twisting things cuz you're not fat and
ugly." So that they'll twist things to
what suits themselves. Um,
my friend I think I got Yeah, my friend
done it for me.
But yeah, they say things to twist. They
they twist things to make it suit
themselves. What they mean is what would
you do if a if a normal woman approached
you? And I can tell you exactly what I
would do if a normal woman approached me.
Um because it's happened before. So
they're they're actually twisting things
by saying fat and ugly. You're not fat
and you're not ugly. So why are we
talking about fat ugly women?
See, it's all things to suit their narrative.
So that's they they do things to suit
themselves. They say things to suit
themselves cuz why are we talking about
fat ugly women?
You know that's make making stuff up.
And yeah I have had average women
approach me before.
I mean I can tell you exactly what I done.
Stig average to below average. She approached me.
Uh there's no such thing as leagues. Uh
firstly, well there is such thing as
leagues but not the way that you think.
Yeah, there is such thing as leagues but
not the way that you think.
It's not to do with looks or anything.
But yeah, there's such thing as leagues
but not the way that you're thinking. So
yeah, Sig approached me, [ __ ] her, had
another woman approached me, gave her
the time of day. So yeah, when when
normal or even below average women
looking below average uh looking women
approached me, um I got with them so I
could actually answer you what I actually did.
So what what's the what's the point,
you know? Oh my god, we're not talking
about my looks. Get out of here with
your insecure ass. Jesus Christ.
You're never going to make me insecure.
Stop talking about my [ __ ] looks.
We're not talking about my looks. Jesus Christ.
Oh my [ __ ] god. I've never said below
average men get ignored.
Stop talking about my looks, bro. When
you're sat behind a keyboard fat and
ugly. You're never going to make me
insecure. Stop wasting your time.
Stop coming on here with your
negativity. We're not talking about my looks.
You're never ever ever going to make me
insecure. Ever. So, just stop wasting your time.
Stop hating, bro.
Same old [ __ ] with you [ __ ] And we
all And we all end up seeing what you
people look like, fat and ugly. So, stop
talking about other people's looks. How
many times has someone got a comment
here? Yeah. And talk about someone's
looks and we all see what they look like
when their camera comes on, you know.
Yes. I said average. I never said below
average. I said average.
Yeah, that's what I said. I said
average. There you go. You got your answer. Jesus Christ.
Self projecting talking about money again.
Yeah, they're all idiots on here. This
is why I don't come on here much anymore, Joker.
You don't really see me. I'm sure you're
sub. It's just They're all idiots on
here, isn't it? You know,
they're just idiots.
Oh, bye-bye. Boring. This is all boring, bro.
[ __ ] white knight simp idiots. Why I
don't really come on here anymore, bro.
I can't be asked with it. I won't be on
for a little bit after today either.
Just like middle-aged ugly people that
self project. It's boring as [ __ ] Just
little low lives. This is why I don't
waste my time on him anymore, bro.
Ugly creepy weirdos that ain't got a life, you know?
I'd be [ __ ] man. Really
sat there talking about people's looks.
When they're fat and ugly themselves,
ain't got no life. Just like when they
call people skin, their skin themselves.
Same old boring thing. Same old repeating.
This is why I don't waste my time on
here, bro. Joker lad.
Franklin gone flying.
little self projectors.
The same atmosphere would it Jo.
It's the same atmosphere on here. What
atmosphere is it? What the H.
This is me right now, bro. Oh [ __ ]
See me? I can show my face.
Some these people can't show their face.
I can show my face. None of these people
can show their face.
These people can't show their face.
Yeah, bro. Your little self projection
doesn't bother us. It's only about how
you feel about yourselves.
Don't forget I'm skint, right? I'm also
bro. Your little idiot self-p projection
methods don't work with me, bro.
They might work with someone else, but
they don't work with me because you know
with these people like yourself
that it's only self-p projection.
So that's why nothing you say bothers
us. You're all idiots. We all know what
you people look like when you put your cameras on.
We all see what you people look like
when you put your cameras on, bro.
Like you don't make anyone insecure or anything.
You need to get a life. You're a bunch
of [ __ ] idiots.
I'm trying to [ __ ] uh There we go.
So, when are you people actually going
to get a life anyways? Get a life and
get a job.
How many How many years you been on here now, man?
When are you actually going to like get
a life, get a job,
and stop self-pinged on the internet
[ __ ] years? We're all sick and tired
of it now, you know?
Come on, man.
Yeah, skin. You know, the thing is you
you guys come here, you talk about IQ,
but all you do is repeat the same [ __ ]
You're boring. Skin, skin, skin, skin.
Oh my god. Have you got any new comebacks?
Same old repeating with you people.
Same old repeating.
If you weren't skin, why you sat on
YouTube from the time you wake up to the
time you go to bed? Again, self projection.
You people self-project your life
onto other people. Yeah, whatever.
Bye-bye, idiot. Self projector.
So many self projectors on this
community. What the [ __ ] man?
So many self projectors. This is why I
don't come on here, bro. It's always the same atmosphere. No,
same self-p projecting negative losers.
That's why I don't waste my time, bro.
Nothing happens to Peter Belly, bro. Hello. Self injecting losers.
It's [ __ ] mongos. I swear to God,
this community is full of It's the same atmosphere.
Every time you come on here, it's the same atmosphere.
Same little low lives.
Same self projecting repeating people.
That's all it is on here.
Same atmosphere. You know what an
atmosphere means, Joker? It means like a
vibe. You know when you go into like a casino,
same repeat, same atmosphere.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, it's just the same repeating fat
ugly people that's got no life, no
looks, no money. You would have thought
they would have got a job by now. It's
been [ __ ] 10 years.
You know, you would have thought that
these people would have got a life in 10
years. You know what I mean, Joker?
You would have thought these people
would have actually got a life and got a
job instead of sitting on YouTube all
day. They're [ __ ] mongos, bro. absolute
mongos on this community. Yeah.
I sound depressed. No, I'm all good,
man. I'm all good.
I just don't like this repeating community.
No, I'm all good, actually, bro.
Nah, not depressed at all, man.
Not at all at all.
It's just a [ __ ] community in it. Same atmosphere.
I'm going to boring
same self projectors, same atmosphere.
It's a horrible atmosphere. And this is
why we call them mongos, the Joker,
because they're so disabled that they
even got an IQ to create a different atmosphere
or to come out with different comebacks.
It's the same repeating people. That's
why you don't see me on here much, Joker.
It's the same repeating people that
ain't got a life.
Is that right, Joker?
You need to stop trying to troll me,
Joker. Seriously, bro.
Like, I'm not Timmy Eldridge. You really
need to stop it, bro.
Because what's going to happen, bro, is
that you people are going to keep
pissing me off and then I'm just going
to call you all out, bro, and embarrass
all of you. Like, and it ain't even
going to be funny. And I'll start with
that Terry. He will be the first one
and I would just create a madness on it
again. So, and it ain't going to be funny, bro.
So, like you're best off just not [ __ ]
trying to troll me basically. Bye-bye.
Do you want to see me do that, Grezy,
then? Yeah. Do you want to see me call
all of these [ __ ] out?
And no one will beat me either. Nobody
will beat me.
I assure you, lad.
And trust me, Grezy, no [ __ ] will beat me, mate.
You believe me, is it, Grezy?
Terry's not going to beat me. Monty's
not going to beat me,
you know. None of these people will beat me, lad.
Because I'm a big strong Turkish man.
Isn't that right? E.
No. Even Monty won't. Even Monty won't. Lad.
Do you remember Timmy Greavesy? I'm
going to knock him out.
Did you see that video, Joker? I'm going
to knock him out.
You saw it, didn't you?
You saw it, didn't you? I'm going to
knock him out.
I'm going to knock him out. Come on, lads.
I'll knock him out, Gregy. I will knock him out.
Why Greavvesy? I will knock him out.
Come on, lad. Do you remember Grievy?
What website was that on Grezy?
What website was it on?
Do you want to have a pint or do you
want to go around the corner and do it dirty?
What website was that on? Who's it?
Yeah, but what about Harry Potter?
What about Harry Potter?
Yeah. You can't watch Harry Potter on
YouTube, can you? Wow.
It needs to be monitored, don't it?
It needs to be monitored.
is YouTube needs to be [ __ ] monitored. >> Yeah,
needs to be monitored.
I'm not sure why it's [ __ ] not.
Anyways, I'll be back later.