Right. I'm back. Yeah.
>> [clears throat]
>> Yeah, man.
Went to Weather Spoons to get some breakfast.
Yeah, madness, bro. Absolute madness.
Going for the meal tomorrow.
Not today. It's fine.
I won't be going out Friday anyways, so
it's all good, bro.
Fourth week now. This is going to be the
fourth week where I've uh planned to go
out and ain't gone out. By going out, I mean drinking.
Nope. No point. No point um dealing with
women that are all the same.
No, that's dead, bro. [ __ ] dead. Yeah,
>> that's a fe
Glad to be back now. Yeah.
All women are the [ __ ] same.
They're all [ __ ]
That was so toxic this morning, bro. I
was shouting and everything about to
calm me down.
Yeah, it's bad. It was really bad.
They say women aren't all the same.
I need to meet 9 billion people
in order for me to have an opinion. Nah,
they're all the [ __ ] same, mate.
So, so obvious.
So toxic. So so [ __ ] toxic.
That's all it is.
Well, we'll see if the first on Reddit replies.
I said to Laney,
um, where are all these good women hiding?
Nowhere. They don't exist. There's no
good women out there. They're all the [ __ ] same.
I had this [ __ ] white knight message
me, bro. [ __ ] earlier.
These women are such cowards. They can't
even defend themselves verbally. They
have to get random people to message
you. They're [ __ ] such [ __ ]
Put all that [ __ ] all over her story
knowing damn well that people from her
Instagram is going to message me. Only
one did, but still. Yeah, they're all
the same, bro. Women are all the same.
It's so obvious.
You don't need to meet 9 billion women
to know that. You just go by your
experiences that they're all like that.
They're all the same. I was telling Lady
about it earlier.
Women are definitely all the same, bro.
Whoever doesn't think that they're
[ __ ] stupid if they don't think women
are all the same. Honestly,
ignorant, arrogant [ __ ] That's
what they are. Perfect way to describe them.
Same old. Well, Friday is cancelled anyways. Um, yep. One second. Yeah.
All women aren't the same. You don't
know all women. Yeah, right. They are
[ __ ] same. Cory, help me lad. All
women are the same.
Elaine had to [ __ ] calm me down earlier, bro.
No, they're definitely all the same.
Nah, this [ __ ] pissed me off earlier,
bro. This stupid woman on Instagram sat
there ignoring 400 messages. Then I
started spamming her like pictures. Then
she put me all over her [ __ ] story,
you know? And uh
then she put me all over her story and I
had this little s messaging me, bro.
They're all [ __ ] All of these
women are [ __ ] I said to I said to
Laney, "How many more times am I going
to give them?" Right. Yeah.
Am I going to give them the benefit of the doubt?
Like, how how many more times are you
going to give them the benefit of the
doubt, these women?
Like, seriously, how how many more
times, bro? Cuz we've been giving them
the benefit of the doubt for years. like [ __ ] years, you know. So, yeah.
Yeah. [ __ ] them, bro. I'm not going out
Friday. I said I was going to go on a
drink Friday, but no, I ain't doing it, you know.
are such cowards
and they report you to Instagram as
well. They start [ __ ] and then they
report you when you give it to them back. Sorry.
Yeah, they are [ __ ]
I was like I really wanted to hurt someone, bro.
Like I'm not even joking. I really
wanted to smash someone up.
You know these these women are [ __ ] They're cowards.
Arrogant [ __ ] [ __ ] egoistic.
They're so big until [snorts] it comes
to when they meet their match.
All of these women, Kyrie, they're all
big until they meet their match.
Then they play victim and get white
knights to message her and say that
you're stalking them. You know what I
mean? They're [ __ ]
And then putting all of my [ __ ] on her
[ __ ] story. Yeah, you little coward.
I told you I'm going to make you block
me. Don't sit there and ignore me, you
stupid [ __ ] I hate them, bro. I hate
them more than Ant-Man. Like, you you
This is why I gave up. This is why I
gave up the dating [ __ ] and the women
That's why I gave up. This was somebody
from ages ago, bro.
That's why I gave up cuz I know they're
all the same. I've been saying for the
past four weeks, look, Blad, I'm going
to go out trying and I haven't done it.
I'm done. Done, bro. I'm telling you,
I'm done. Done. Literally. Yeah.
There's no point. The women are all bad, bro.
There's no point. I've gave them the
benefit of the doubt for years and years
and years and years and years. I'm not
doing it again. Simple.
And then she's like, "Oh, yeah." Yeah,
she doesn't want to talk to you. I don't
want to [ __ ] talk to you. Why the
[ __ ] are you messaging me? That's what I
said. I was like, "Okay, well, she's
blocked me. Why are you messaging me? I
don't want to talk to your white knight
ass. So, why are you messaging me, you
little [ __ ] s,
[ __ ] These women are [ __ ]
cowards, bro. Can't even [ __ ] defend themselves verbally.
What coward losers they are, eh? [ __ ] Yeah,
I hate women, bro. I hate women. Seriously.
I candy, bro. Did you hear what
happened? I had this [ __ ] Do you
remember that woman, right? Uh, so you
know the one that I met on Reddit a
month and a half ago and they were
talking normally and then they started
ignoring and they would literally click
on a message 300 times and keep
ignoring, ignoring, ignoring. I was
like, "Fuck this. You're not going to
sit there and keep ignoring me." I just
wanted them to block me. They live in a
different country. I was sending them
pictures on my dick, everything. And
they kept looking at it, looking at it,
looking at it, not replying. So, I went
on their picture and I spammed it about
a million times, bro. Like, I spammed
the comments and then she blocked me and
then she put all of the [ __ ] that I done
on her story and then I had this little
[ __ ] white knight messaged me saying,
"Oh, I'm her boyfriend. She doesn't want
to talk to you." I was like, "Firstly,
she didn't say she had a boyfriend.
Secondly, I don't want to [ __ ] talk
to you, right? So, she's blocked me for
a reason." Yeah. Well, why are you
messaging me? You little white knight
little [ __ ] ugly bastard. If this
guy lived in England, bro, I'd be
meeting him today. I hate white knights.
I hate [ __ ] that defend women to
look good. She is a coward. She has to
get other people to message me cuz she's
so much of a cowardly bastard [ __ ]
right? To say anything herself. That's
the thing with these women, Candy Man.
They're all whale and big and egoistic
until they meet their match. We've heard
we we've heard it and seen it all
before, have we not? with these [ __ ]
women. They're all big until they meet
their match. And I mean in in a verbal
sense, not a physical sense. They're
[ __ ] I told this guy to go [ __ ]
his mother and stop [ __ ] messaging me
unless you want to meet. That's what I
said. [ __ ] little s, little white
knight. And then he blocked me. And then
I went on my mom's phone and I called
them both out. I said, "You ugly, dirty,
stinky, [ __ ] brownkinned foreign
cunts." That's what I said to them. So
it it ruined my mood, bro. And I've not
been in a bad mood for like 6 weeks.
Ever since I gave up dating, I haven't
been in a bad mood until today, bro.
But my mom was trying to calm me down
and everything, bro. It's annoying. It's
toxic. And this is not even me approaching.
And it's that bad. So yeah, Friday's
canled. I'm not going out Friday. That
decides it. So yeah, bro. I'm done now.
Yeah. Fourth week I've said I'm going
out. Not going out. So yeah,
I really want to ruin a woman's life,
bro. I really really want to ruin a woman's life.
Not like beaten up or like anything like
that, but like really really [ __ ] them over.
Bad bad bad bro. Like you don't understand.
And I said to Laney kindly, man, like
how [snorts] many more times do you have
to keep giving these women the benefit
of the doubt and then them then proving
they're all the same? Like how like how
many times you have to keep doing it?
Cuz I've been doing it for years, bro.
Then trust me, they're all the [ __ ] same, you know?
And they live in South America, so
obviously I can't meet them, bro. Like,
if if I lived where they lived, I would
I would slap her in front of him and
slap him in front of her.
I'd sat them both up in front of each
other. I hate them. I hate women.
You know, I told Damon about it. I said,
"This is the same as your ex. You're all
big and hard and egoistic when you think
you're dealing with a [ __ ] s or a
white knight. But as soon as someone
defends themsel, oh, report them to
Instagram. Oh, get the white knight to
message them." Yeah, that's another
thing, Candy, man. I can't type on
Instagram now for seven days. So, they
start [ __ ] They act like [ __ ]
[ __ ] And then when you're not a
white knight that licks their ass, they
pay victim and report you and call you a
stalker. Oh, bro. Come on. How many
times have we heard this before? How
many times have we seen this before?
[ __ ] [ __ ] That's what I called him. Yeah.
I was going mad, bro. My mom had to calm
me down and everything
cuz obviously I don't gamble anymore. I
don't get mood swings. I'm chilling,
bro. Like, I haven't I don't I don't get
bad moods anymore, but this can't really
put me in a bad mood.
Certain women, they need telling about
themselves. And what I mean by that is
all of these white knights
inflate their ego time and time and time
again. They inflate their ego and then
they think they're better. And they need
someone like me once in a while to tell
them about themselves, bro.
Not all of them obviously because
they're all [ __ ] and they're all
[ __ ] But you know the ones I'm talking
about certain types of women they they
need telling about themselves because
they've never had it because obviously
they're they're white you know the
[ __ ] white knights and simps and [ __ ] So
like them. So these women need telling
about themselves bro.
You know how it is. You know, mad.
So that's the story. Candy man.
I said, "Damon, that's what your ex is
like." Yeah, I told Damon all about it.
Damon, however the [ __ ] you say his
name. I said that's like your ex. He was
big and bad and ugly until somebody
stands up to her.
Yeah. Yeah. That's what it is. Madness.
You need to ruin I need to ruin one of
these women's lives, bro. I swear to God.
really need to ruin one of their lives. Like
I don't know, bro.
That red star is still a loser. Cory,
still stalking me, but will never beat
me. Typical keyboard warrior.
Typical keyboard warrior, eh? Another
stalker that will never meet anyone that
won't leave his mom's basement.
Sad people on here, lad.
That's their life, isn't it?
That's their life. Dear,
you know what, Cory? I could understand,
right? if if they if they will meet
someone, but they will never ever meet
anyone. They'll just continuously doing
this continuously keep doing this. And
when that Terry comes on my channel
again, I'm going to his area by the way.
As soon as this [ __ ] comes back on my
channel, I'm going to his area. And so
I'm practicing what I'm preaching here
is like they How long is this going to
go on for this back and forth? You
either pack it up or you meet someone.
But they don't. They just do this
continuously, but they'll never meet
anyone. So, like I said, when Terry
comes back on this channel, I'm going to
his area straight away
because like I really want to do
something in today, bro. I really want
to really hurt someone, bro. This stupid
[ __ ] was pissing me off. And this white knight, you know,
I hate women, bro. I really, really hate
them. Like you really don't understand
my hate towards them. That's why I don't
go out drinking anymore. You know,
toxic. That's what it is. It's toxic.
Whenever you deal with women, it's toxic. So yeah, that's it. Listen,
I hate them, bro.
Let me see.
Yeah, bro. We know they're obsessed.
They've been obsessed for years, lad.
They have the same attitude. That's
another thing with these women. Have you
noticed for people that aren't all the
same candy man? They have a lot of similarities.
They have all they've all got the same
attitude for people that are apparently
not the same. Concerning as [ __ ] it.
That's quite concerning.
as me. If I met another man that was the
same as me, I'd be very, very concerned.
Very, very, very, very concerned.
If I met somebody that was exactly the
same as me. But these women, you meet so
many of the same ones for people that
are all different. Now, me, right,
I'm I'm I'm me as a person. There's no
one that's the same as me. I mean,
you're never going to meet someone
that's the same as me. Women, you say
all women are different, but they all do
say and act the same way. No one acts,
says the same stuff as me because
there's no one like me. Do you
understand? They are or the same. That's that, you know. So,
they must not be living on a planet Mars. No,
cuz I've never met anyone that's the
same as me. Never.
They all have the same attitude. They
say the same stuff. They act the same
way. But they're apparently not all the same.
That's strange, isn't it?
Yeah. Get [ __ ] mate. They're NPCs. So obvious.
Same attitude as well. Well, anyways, that's that
You're not the same. You don't know all women.
You don't know all women that
get Don't know where
They're not all like that.
You don't know all women.
[ __ ] off, mate. They're all the [ __ ] same
red star. You little gay boy. Instead of
stalking me every day, why don't you
come and meet me, you [ __ ] loser.
You [ __ ] gay boy. Yeah.
Anyways, I'll be back later.