Yeah, I I I clocked on to that fast. I
I caught that early on. Yeah.
Yeah, I call that early on.
You can't troll a guy like me, bro. I've been uh
too far long in this game.
Too far along in this game, bro.
Yeah, I knew it. I [ __ ] knew it.
I [ __ ] knew it. I just knew it.
You were trying to get me to go all the
way to Scotland and not show up. I
wasn't born yesterday, mate. I knew it.
I caught it early on. I caught it early
on. What they were trying to do. It was
too obvious. It was too obvious.
It's going all over the internet.
Anyways, so you know that uh person that
was um trying to meet me, right? It was
It was [ __ ] I knew it was I knew it
was it was too obvious. It was It was so
obviously a setup. I knew it. I knew it,
bro. I I caught it early on,
like within the next day. It was too
obvious. And I'm I'm speaking to the
person on Reddit. They messaged me. I
said, "I knew what you were trying to
do. Getting your friend to [ __ ] with me,
you little dirty little rape victim. You
dirty little rape victim cunt." And
another thing is, right, you're saying
that you've made other people rope kill
themselves. You're not going to get me
to kill myself. You little stupid little
rape victim. You little rape, you little
victim [ __ ] Cuz they told me, bro, and
I knew it. I knew it straight away what
they were trying to do. It was too
obvious. It was too obvious.
You know, you want to call me dumb, bro.
You can't even troll people properly,
you [ __ ] stupid bastard.
You know, how about you tell me where
you live in Ireland and I'll come and
smack you up in front of your boyfriend
cuz that's where this [ __ ] lives in
Ireland. How about that? I'll happily
[ __ ] do that, bro. If you want, I'll
happily do that. I'll come. I'll smash
your [ __ ] face in. I'll smash your
boyfriend's face and I'll take your
[ __ ] BMW. How about that one, you
stupid [ __ ] I'll try I'll [ __ ] with
you. And she, oh, you troll, bro. How
did you troll me? I was in my bed. I You
didn't stand me up. I didn't go anywhere
cuz I knew what you was doing. It was too obvious.
You know, I'll give her the same offer
as I gave to USA. Izzy,
these women, Bob, are [ __ ] [ __ ]
bro. They were giving me mood swings.
Uh, when I woke up earlier, bro, I woke
up and I went on my [ __ ] phone, bro.
And this stupid [ __ ] was [ __ ] uh
trolling me, bro. Uh, sorry. Just this
uh stupid white knight was messaging me
over that [ __ ] that was ignoring on Instagram.
Bro, I hate these women.
I hate them, lad.
I hate women, bro. I hope they all get
raped. I said this to my mom, bro,
earlier. I swear to God I did. I swear
to God I did, bro. It's madness. It is a [ __ ] madness.
Yeah. And that one on Instagram, I said,
"Why are you messaging me? [ __ ] off, you
little white back. Go suck your mom,
bro. Yeah, I'll message your friend
whenever I want and you're not going to
do nothing about it. I don't want you
messaging me now. [ __ ] off. Yeah,
I hate women, bro. I [ __ ] hate them.
I hope they all get raped. Swear to God,
bro. They [ __ ] scum of the earth.
Yeah, I swear to God, bro.
changing your [ __ ] number cuz your
number's going all over [ __ ] dating apps
dating apps and um
dating apps and uh
women are evil. Bob, you know that woman
that kept ignoring me on Instagram?
I spammed her whole page, bro. And then
she blocked me and then she put me up on
her story knowing that
um people that went on her story would
message me. They're such cowards.
They are such cowardly little [ __ ]
They are cowards knowing damn well that
someone that watches that is going to
come for me like will message me. Do you
know what I mean? They're cowards. They
can't even defend themselves. That's why
they're rape victims because they can't
defend themselves. Yeah. 100%, bro.
They can't even defend themselves.
That's why they play victim.
They can't even stand their ground.
They're [ __ ] weasels.
That's what these women are, bro.
They're [ __ ] absolute weasels. Yeah. Yeah. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Getting some little white knight to
message me and that. I told him to go [ __ ] himself.
Yeah, I told her, "Stop ignoring me."
Then I started sending her my dick and
everything, spamming her whole
Instagram. Then she blocked me. Then
some white knight started messaging me.
I told him to [ __ ] off and go suck his
mom. And if he lived there, I'd be
smashing his [ __ ] face in. And and
this one in Ireland, I'm going to give
her the same offer. I am going to give
um offer as I gave USA. I'll come and
smash your face in in front of your
boyfriend and I'll smash his face in in
front of you and I will [ __ ] do it,
mate. Because it took me about an hour
and a half to calm down earlier. My mom
had to calm me down. I said, "No, I'm
going to [ __ ] [ __ ] these [ __ ] out."
And I [ __ ] him up. I swear to God,
Grezy, they're lucky they live in
[ __ ] South America. I said, "Oh,
these little rape victims need teaching
a [ __ ] lesson, lad."
Um, I think her friend uh heard the
stuff that I said about women. It was
too obvious. It was too obvious, bro.
Because think about it, bro. Yeah.
They've they've literally
heard the stuff you've said, right? And
then someone messages you of an Irish
number that claims that they're living
in Scotland, right? And they want to
meet you all of a sudden. It was too
obvious. It was too obvious, bro. It was
too [ __ ] obvious. No, her friend
lives in Ireland and apparently she
lives in Scotland, but she doesn't even
live in the UK. It was too obvious,
Greavvesy. It's too obvious, isn't it?
Right at the right at the end, right at
the end of England, past England to
Scotland. What's the chances that you
live there of all places? It was too
obvious. I could I could smell it a mile
off, mate. You know, it was too obvious.
I said, "You're calling me dumb. You
couldn't even troll me properly, you
stupid little cunt." And you're saying
about how you're going to get people and
how you've got someone to kill
themselves before, bro. How about this?
I'll come to Ireland and I'll [ __ ]
bully you in front of your boyfriend.
And I'll bully your boyfriend in front
of you. How about that one?
No, because they were trying to set me
up. You [ __ ] idiots. Do you not
understand? They were trying to set me
up. Her friend was in on it. She doesn't
even live in the UK. She was pretending
that she lives in Scotland. She messaged
me on WhatsApp saying, "Fucking come and
meet me." I knew it was [ __ ]
How could have I [ __ ] the fend up when
no one was there? It was a setup. That's
what I'm saying.
I'll come to Ireland and slap you up in
front of your boyfriend. I'll slap your
boyfriend up in front of [ __ ] you.
You [ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
Yeah, bro. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. This is the
story, right? Okay. Look. So, I was
speaking to some
Oh, there's so many, bro. I was speaking
to this woman uh on Reddit,
right? And she said she's 29 and she's
uh she can't find someone. And I was
basically telling them like bit of my
background, my story and stuff, right?
And uh she was like, "Yeah, yeah, yeah."
And she's like, "Oh." She says she'll
give me a chance or whatever. So she
messaged me. Then all of a sudden she's
blocked me and she's like, "Oh, they've
sent me everything that you've said
about women." No, no, no, no, no. So
naturally, she's blocked me. Then I got
a message a few weeks later, which was
the other day, of her friend, her friend
saying, "Oh yeah, um, sorry it took so
long to message." I was like, "Bro, it's
so obvious. It's a setup because your
friends already blocked me for the
things I've said and it was an Irish
number. Then she claimed that she lived
in Scotland." And it's like, nah, it's
She tried making me go all the way to
the end of Scotland. It was so obvious.
It was so obvious. It was so [ __ ]
obvious, bro. Like if if it was like
London, if they tried getting you to go
somewhere in London, then I think you
might you might have done it to be
honest with you, but it was too obvious.
It was too too too too obvious. Like it
wasn't Wales. It wasn't And obviously
the fact that like a woman's not going
to meet you straight away like that. It
was too obvious. It was too obvious, is
it, Grezy? Yeah.
And then she's messaging me now on
Reddit. I said, "Fuck you and [ __ ] your
boyfriend and [ __ ] your mom, bro. Yeah,
you said that you've made people kill
themselves and you've made fun out of
people killing themselves. How about I
come to Ireland next week? Yeah.
So, bro, it's not even that though, is
it? Have you seen my approaching videos, Pokemon?
I mean, it's it's not about that though.
You seen my approaching videos and the
messages? Nah, you probably didn't, did
he, Greasy? To be fair, didn't suit him, did it?
Nah, it didn't suit him. But that one in
South America really pissed me off, bro.
Because what it is, Greavesy, is some of
these women, not all of them, even
though they're all [ __ ] Some of these
women, they need telling about
themselves. This is what happens, Grevy.
You remember we was talking about
narcissists, right? These women, they
get their egos inflated by these simps,
by these white knights, brother. Yeah.
And they need telling about themsel. And
they give and they do this [ __ ]
behavior. And you know what the guy
called me? Grezy, the white knight that
messaged me. He called me a stalker. H
typical. You get called a [ __ ]
stalker when they can't stand up for
themselves. [ __ ] loser. How the [ __ ]
did I stalk the [ __ ] You gave me your
Instagram. I messaged you. I was going
to have you keep ignoring me. How am I
stalking someone? That's That's their
favorite word, Grezy. Their favorite
word is stalking. That's their That's
their favorite word, mate. Yeah. When
they can't defend themselves, that the
losers, it's either they run to the
police, they run to a white knight, or
you're a stalker. It's so obvious, isn't
it? It's so obvious, Greasy. Yeah.
Trying to get you you got you was
getting other people to message me when
you blocked me, knowing that there were
there's a good chance that people was
going to come after me because you can't
defend yourself, you [ __ ] coward.
Yeah, that's what she is. Cuz that's
what a lot of these women need. They
need telling about themsel, bro. They
do. Some of them really really do, bro.
They need putting in their place. Like
verbally, not like physically, verbally.
Bro, I told her you're not going to sit
there and ignore me. I told you I I'm
not going to stop until you block me.
And then she kept doing it and I spammed
the whole Instagram page. I'll show you
it, bro. Look,
I'll show you. I spam that [ __ ] bro. I
done it about 100 times. And then I
didn't stop there. I went on my mom's
phone and started slagging him off.
Yeah, you stupid [ __ ] ugly stupid
[ __ ] Ignoring little rape victim [ __ ]
Yeah, this is what I mean by it's toxic.
This is why I didn't want to get into
this [ __ ] again, bro. This is why I did
not want to get into this [ __ ] with
these little rape victims again. This is why, bro.
Because it's so toxic. This is why I
didn't want to get into of this anymore.
I didn't want to get into it anymore,
bro. With them. It's negative,
you know. That's why, bro, I didn't want
to like I wanted to stay away from all
of this [ __ ] but they keep dragging
me in, dragging me in, dragging me in.
Don't sit there and ignore me. And they
done it on purpose as well. They went on
my message about five other times. I
didn't like them. They don't even live
in the same country as me. It's
principle. You need telling about yourself,
you know. Um, and how did they find I
don't know how they found her. I don't know, bro. Yeah.
So I I assume she tried to set me up
because of the things that I said.
She could have played it right if she was smart.
But you'd have to be very smart to fool Peter Belly.
Like it's the same as that USA. Izzy
Grezy. I messaged that Damon earlier and
I told him the story about this South
American woman. I said she's just like
your ex, a narcissist. a [ __ ]
narcissist that can't stand their ground
when they cause all of this [ __ ] [ __ ]
and then they and then and then they
say, "Oh, stalking. Oh, get the white
knight to defend me." They're so
cowardly, these women, Grezies, they
they can't even stand up for themselves.
That's the word. They literally can't
even stand up for themselves.
They're so cowardly.
Do you not agree with what I'm saying,
G? Am I lying? Oh, get the white knight
to do it. I told the white knight, "Fuck
off." I said, "I don't want you
messaging me. You stupid ugly little
[ __ ] Yeah, because trust me, it's going
to hit right one day, bro. And one of
these people are going to live in
England and I will disrespect a woman in
front of any man and smile about it. I
don't care, bro. You know what I'm
saying? It's annoying.
Yeah. I said the same thing to USA. Is
he? Yeah. I think it was in the summer.
I think it was. Yeah. At the end of the
day, right, I will come there and I'll
tell you about yourself in front of your
boyfriend, in front of a man. I will do
it cuz I'm sick of your [ __ ]
Do you understand, bro? I think I
[ __ ] must have woke up the whole
[ __ ] neighborhood this morning. I've
had enough of it. It's cowardly. You're
a coward. Stop putting me all over your
story. So, because all that's going to
happen is when someone messages me,
they're going to get owned. When someone
messages me, they're going to get put in
their place. So there's no point getting
anyone messaging me, bro, cuz I'll just
put them in their place. So yeah.
Yeah. Like you've blocked someone,
right? Because you that I've spammed
them and they don't want to speak to me.
Okay, whatever. Yeah. So why are you
getting some random stupid ugly [ __ ] guy
to message me? Why would you block
someone to then get somebody to message
me? That does not make any sense because
you can't fight your own battles.
Uh, no you didn't. And it wasn't off
Instagram, it was Reddit. So, try again.
It wasn't It was uh It wasn't Reddit, it
was Instagram. Sorry, it wasn't
Instagram. It was Reddit.
Like, you know what I'm saying? You've
blocked someone, Greasy. Yeah. It's
always other people that's got to that
that they that has to fight these
people's battles, right? It's the same
thing as Okay. Oh, I'll give you an
example. I hate bringing this up. It's
similar to the USA Izzy thing when I was
on the phone to USA Izzy's friend for 5
hours. And I said this multiple times to
her, bro. Why am I on the phone to you
and not her? Why are you talking for
this [ __ ] You know, I said this
multiple times, Grezy, cuz it doesn't
make sense. They're cowards. They give
it, but they can't take it. That's what
it is. Cuz most of the guys they come
across are white knights and simps and
push pushovers. And then when you
finally tell them about themselves,
they switch. That's what these women do.
This they switch. They're snakes, lad. So
they're snakes. They're absolute snakes.
That's what these women are, snakes.
Yeah. My mom calmed me down and stuff.
And And it's a shame because I haven't
been like this for ages, bro. Since I
gave up, I don't get back. I don't go in
I don't uh get in bad moods.
I don't have bad moods.
You know what I mean, bro? Like I don't No,
I'm never in bad moods, bro. Like I'm
just chill, man. But that annoyed me.
And then her friend was like, "Yeah,
that's another thing. Oh, you're lucky
you didn't come the first time. I would
have got people." I was like, "Yeah,
really? Would you got people on me?"
You'd get people on me. No, you
wouldn't. No, you [ __ ] wouldn't,
mate. No, you [ __ ] wouldn't the first
time, mate. Cuz it's me or them, bro.
Are you [ __ ] mad? I don't give a [ __ ]
about I told Damon straight about his
ex. They're cowards. That that, you
know, I said, "This is similar to your
ex." What I've just had to put up with
on this [ __ ] Instagram [ __ ] Another
cowardy [ __ ] woman who thinks she's
better than everyone. Typical, mate. They're typical.
And the way they switch as well, Grezy.
These women, the way they switch,
it's so [ __ ] weird the way they switch, bro. You know,
if I was in South America, bro, one of
these people would be getting done in
today, bro. I swear to God. I'm not even
joking, bro. No, I'm not even joking. It's annoying. You know,
and you was doing it to be a [ __ ] You
went on 400 or so messages on purpose to
be a [ __ ] Yeah.
You did do it to be a [ __ ]
Yeah, I'll tell the white knights about
themselves. Bro, it's probably best I
don't go out nowadays cuz I'll end up
knocking some [ __ ] out. So, there's it's
it's a good thing I don't go out
nowadays cuz I will [ __ ] knock one
and I'll smash their [ __ ] face in,
bro. You don't know the amount of times
I had to stop doing something to
someone, bro. Like I still told them
about themselves, but I mean physically
because obviously I didn't want to get
nicked and [ __ ] But bro, nowadays I
don't give a [ __ ]
you know what I mean? I I'll happily
[ __ ] smash one of their faces in,
bro. You little white knights.
You know what I mean? It's mad, bro.
You've blocked someone, so why have I
got someone messaging me? If you've
blocked someone, you've blocked someone
for a reason, lad. You know what I mean?
If you block someone grievy, you've
blocked them for a reason.
No, but then I've got some white. I told
them [ __ ] off and then what happens is
they start [ __ ] and then they run off.
So it's all just like what the [ __ ]
These some of these women, bro, they
really need telling about themselves.
They really really need telling about themselves, bro. You know,
all on the same website you can watch
Harry Potter on, Greezy.
The same website you can watch Harry
Potter on. Eh,
how about that?
No, it's not even funny, bro. It's
[ __ ] annoying, you know, when you
first wake up and you're dealing with
that [ __ ] This is why I gave up with
them to get away from this, you know?
And then you got these people trying to
tell you Pokemon that women aren't all
the same. Get [ __ ] mate. You're
having a wank about they're not all the
same. Get the [ __ ] out of here. How I
said to I said this to Laney right
earlier. I said, "How many more times do
I have to keep giving these people the
benefit of the doubt?" And I think I had
a point with what I was saying with
that. How many times do I have to give
these women the benefit of the doubt
for them to prove that they're not all
the same? I mean, we've already done it
god knows how many times.
How many more times should we keep doing
it, bro? And the answer is none because
they are all the same. [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
Yeah. Bye-bye, [ __ ]
Oh, it was that Jamie Thompson. Yeah,
good one, bro. Good one. But Jamie, you
knew that weren't going to work.
You knew it wasn't going to work though,
James. It was too obvious. It was too
obvious. Oh, it was you. I knew it was I knew that.
Yeah, I knew that.
I knew that was the thing. But, bro, it
doesn't matter because it didn't work
what you was trying to do. I knew it. I
I [ __ ] knew it, son. >> [laughter]
>> Oh, no. But no, but here's the thing,
bro. This person, I found them posting
on Reddit. They didn't find me. I found
them. They didn't find me. That's the
thing. This person, I found them.
No. No. But what I'm saying, lad, is I
found him. I found that account posting.
So what they might do is they might what
he probably does is he posts pretending
to be someone similar to me. So I reach
out. Yeah. But it weren't going to work.
Jamie, that was never going to work. You
made it too obvious. You made it so
obvious about that person in Scotland.
It was so obvious. Scotland of all
places right at the end of Scotland.
Really from where I am. It was too
obvious. It was way way way way way too
obvious. You know, even if they said
Birmingham, they might have got away with it. Yeah.
So, he what he does is he posts in in
hopes that I um reach out to him. Ah,
no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yeah, you're never you're never going to
be peace with me, mate. >> Yeah.
Am I in it too deep now, Greaves? Am I
in it too deep? [laughter]
You're calling me dumb, bro. You
couldn't even troll me, bro. You
couldn't even stand me up, lad. Look.
Okay, let me tell you this, Jamie. Look
how I stood that woman up. I made her go
[ __ ] all over the pub. All over. All
over another pub, mate. Cuz I'm not dumb
like you. It was never going to work.
You made it too obvious. It was too
Yeah, but I knew it. I knew it, bro. I
knew it. I [ __ ] knew it.
I [ __ ] knew it, bro. It was too
obvious. It was It was way too obvious, bro.
No woman just messages you and wants to meet you.
Nah, no way, lad. No way.
This guy is obsessed with me, bro. This
fat [ __ ] [ __ ] is obsessed with me. Yeah.
Yeah, that guy is a proper stalker, bro. [laughter]
But the Instagram was one was real, bro.
That's something completely different.
Yeah, these women do need telling about themselves.
They definitely definitely do.
But it happens in clubs as well, bro. If
you tell them about themselves, they run
to the bouncers and stuff. Like, if you
just tell them about themselves,
it's toxic. Dating is toxic.
Nice try though, Jamie, lad.
No. Uh-uh. I've been speaking to them
for like a week maximum.
Yeah. So, what he does is he posts as a
woman. I know what he does now. Ah,
clever bastard. So, he posts as like a
woman looking for advice that's similar
to me. So, I message them. Yeah.
This guy's got too much time on his
hands, bro. Fever. But he's got he's got
no [ __ ] life, bro. This fat mong has
got no [ __ ] life.
Ah, that's what we're doing now. Okay. Yeah.
Yeah. This guy's a sad bastard, bro.
That is sad as [ __ ] man.
Yeah, he's a proper stalker, lad. Proper
stalker, this guy.
Yeah, I see what he does. I see what he
does. Yeah, he's a low life, though.
Nice try though, Jamie. But you have to
wake up pretty early to fool Peter
belly. You made it too obvious. You made
it way way way too obvious.
Bye-bye, [ __ ] You made it too obvious,
bro. Like me. If I was going to stand
someone up, you wouldn't say Scotland,
bro. If he said London, he could have
had me. There's a chance. Small chance.
But you could have had me cuz
I would have probably went out in London
anyways. He made it too obvious. It was
too obvious, lad. It was way too obvious
because think of it. The person's a ma
and they're telling you to go all the
way to Scotland. Now, you're not going
to go all the way to Scotland for a
month and the chances are it's [ __ ]
which it was.
Do you know your friend that you was
dealing with? Breezy the narcissist. Was
they were they a man or a woman
Yeah. Wait until you deal with a woman
one. They're even worse. They're even
worse, bro. They get other people to
fight their battles. Yeah, that's what
the women ones do. They're they're
losers. Proper proper women are losers, bro.
It wasn't on Instagram. It was on WhatsApp.
It was on WhatsApp, lad. It wasn't on
Instagram. None of it was on Instagram.
It was Reddit and then it was Instagram.
Sorry, it was Reddit, then it was
WhatsApp. Not Instagram. It wasn't It
wasn't Instagram, bro. It was Reddit and um WhatsApp. They
made it too obvious. It was way too
That guy's got no life, bro.
No, they are [ __ ] No, no, no.
Bro, they definitely are [ __ ] Yeah, I
can see I see what he does now. Yeah.
Yeah. He's got too much time of his on
his hands, bro. That is mad. That is
[ __ ] This guy's got too much time on
his hands. He's a low life.
They're not normal people. There's
nothing normal about them. Normal
people, Grezy, don't act stuck up
cowards and have all fight their battle.
That's not what normal people do. They
don't put people and them in the same
sentence. They're not people.
There's nothing about them that's [ __ ] people.
They're [ __ ] scum of the earth.
They're not people. They're evil.
You tell me what people grievy get
orbiters to fight their battle for them.
A verbal battle.
No, they're definitely definitely far
from people. Lad,
I'm going to stick to what I'm saying.
Greasy. Listen to what I'm saying. So me,
there's nobody like me because I'm a
unique individual. I'm a man and there's
no other man that's the same as me, that
says the same stuff, that acts the same
way, that does the same thing, that you
know, you know what I'm saying? No, no
one is the same as me. Because why is
that? Because I'm
People are not all the same as me. You
understand what I'm saying? Whereas
these women, people sit there and say
that they're not all the same, yet they
say the same stuff. They act the same
way. Um, they act the same way. They
have the same mannerisms and they lead
people on the same way so many times,
but they're not all the same. Is that
two examples for you, bro? You know,
also, um, yeah, that one from South
America reported me on Instagram, so I'm
banned for seven days. So, they're so
cowardly, um, Grezy that they will make
sure that you can't even defend
yourself. So when they block me, they
reported me and I can't talk for seven
days. So they're that cowardly that they
won't even they'll make sure they
they'll try their hardest to make sure
you won't even be able to defend
yourself. They're [ __ ] retards, bro.
They're not normal people. I don't know
why you're saying that they're normal
people. They're not normal people.
There's nothing normal about them. They're scum.
I was saying this to my mom earlier as well.
Madness. Absolute madness. They're not
[ __ ] normal people. They're scumbags.
Yeah, that's a different one. Yeah.
Yeah, that's a different one. That's a
real one. That is That is from
Instagram. This one is Reddit and WhatsApp. >> [snorts]
>> Yeah, that's a different one.
Yeah. So, she made sure I couldn't
defend myself. Yeah.
Okay. Let me explain this to you. Okay.
Right. The Jamie Thompson one. Okay. Let
me explain this one more time.
Somebody posted on Reddit that they were
29 and no one approaches them, right?
Bye-bye little self projector. Uh they
posted that they can't find someone. No
one approaches them and they were 29. So
me being messaged them and they were
saying about how Yeah. Yeah. Can't
believe uh someone give you a chance or
whatever. And then
Right. And then um yeah, they saw things
that I said and then then they stopped
talking to me. Then they blocked me.
Then a couple of weeks later, some
random person messaged me on WhatsApp
saying, "Oh, this person gave me your
number. I thought we we would hear off
the same person I was speaking to on
Reddit." That turned out to be Jamie
Thompson. They were under an Irish
number. They were under an Irish number.
And um yeah, they'll come to Scotland.
We'll meet up. I said, "Okay, let's meet
in Glasgow." Um,
so yeah, and then I didn't go and then
it turned out to be set up.
Does that make sense? Very weird.
Does that make sense? And then Yeah. And
then the South American one, that's
completely different. And that was just
someone I was talking to and they turned
because the where they're so fake and phony Pokémon,
they can't keep it up for too long
because they're fake and phony. These
women are fake and phony. So they can't
keep it up. They can't keep the fade up
for for too long. You understand?
They're fake and phony, lad.
The South American one's definitely real. 100%.
Yeah. So that's that's basically what that is.
That is weird. That is very [ __ ]
This guy is a proper proper stalker in here.
Nah, he's a proper stalker. This guy, bro.
Yeah, he's a stalker, mate.
So, he goes online basically posing as
women. Yeah, he's a sad case, man.
That's insane, bro.
Yeah, he's basically pretending to be
people. He's a sad bastard, bro. He
takes it to the next level. Yeah, his
life is literally dedicated to stalking
me, bro. Like, he's worse than that Red Star.
[ __ ] sab bastard. But yeah, Bob,
they're definitely definitely not
people, bro. They're definitely
definitely not people.
They're definitely definitely not
people. People don't do that. People
don't act like [ __ ] and then play
victims and get all beat and or uh
orbiters to fight their battles, bro.
Nah, people don't do that. They're
anything but people. They're scum of the earth, bro.
And I haven't been proven different. So,
uh, haven't been proven otherwise. So,
until I'm proven otherwise, that's how
I'm always going to think, lad.
You don't get why people troll me. Uh, jealousy.
You're younger than them. You're better
looking than them. You got more money
than them. I mean, it's pretty obvious
why why people troll me, lad. Well, [ __ ]
with me cuz they can't even troll me.
I don't get what you mean, Gako. Lad,
that doesn't make sense what you just wrote. So, yeah,
they do it because they're old, fat,
ugly people that ain't got a life. They
don't leave the house and they cling on
to anyone that's got better looks than
them, that's younger than them, that's
got hope on like them.
It comes down to jealousy with these
fat, ugly bongos.
When are they going to get a job and get
off of YouTube, get some money, get a life?
About [ __ ] time, is it?
Got self projecting.
Idiots get blocked on my channel. So yeah. Yeah.
So that's where we're at then. Yeah.
See, no one's the same as me. You can't
find someone that's the same as me. You
understand? Because I'm um different.
I'm unique. I'm different. These women
are not different. These women are all the same.
That's why there's so many similarities
between them all because they are all
the same. There's no one that's got the
same similarities as me because I'm
different and everyone else is
different. Women are not different.
Women are all the same.
So, I mean that there you go.
How you can say they're just people.
Bro, if I if I lived in South America,
that woman would be getting slapped and
that guy would have been getting slapped as well.
Toxic. That's the word. Toxic.
That's what these women are. They're toxic.
are hating me.
Really, really do hate them. So,
I've never been proven. I mean, like I
said, Bob, how many times you have to go
out and give them the benefit of the
doubt? I'm not going out Friday either.
No, that South American thing put me
off, bro. No, not that. Nah. Done. So,
this will be the fourth week now. I've
planned to go out and haven't because of them.
Because of these women, this is like the
fourth or fifth week now. I have planned
to go out and I have not done it because
of these women.
It reminds me of why I gave up
cuz they're all the same. They're all scumbags. So, yeah.
Yeah, I know. They're real. They're real
scumbags. They're evil. Yeah,
they're evil scumbags. That's what they are.
Yes, I won't be out Friday. Nope.
There we go. I I have to just say now I
don't think I'm ever going out again in this country.
Like, let's just be real. Let's just say
it how it is, you know? Oh yeah.
So yeah, that's where we're at.
But yeah, they're definitely not people.
Women are definitely definitely not
people. They're scumbags.
Stop calling yourself a M. Stop bullying
yourself on my channel. It's not nice.
No, I haven't. No, I did have a good
time. What? Spending £500 and getting 10
numbers and not getting a date? You
think that's a good time? No thanks. I
don't think it is.
Nah, that was the last time, lad. That
was the last straw for me, lad. [ __ ]
that. I am not doing that ever again,
bro. I'm leaving in a couple of weeks
anyways. So, I'm out of here, lad. [ __ ] that.
Yeah. And it's not even that. It's It's
women that I deal with on the internet
as well. It's not even people that I
just people that I approach. It's the
lies, the [ __ ]
Yeah. unrealistic, ridiculous standards
making you think you're ugly when you're
not. And it's just toxic. The word is
toxic. That's what it is dealing with
women. It's toxic. That that's all that
can be said.
No, they're coming tomorrow.
But it's not a problem. I'll just go to
my sisters or something with the jeans.
It's I'll find something else to do. I'm
not going out drinking. No. No. No
point. Nah. I'm all good, bro.
It's toxic. Dealing with women is a
negative. It is a toxic. Today
was the first time I have been in a bad mood
for literally about 6 weeks.
Well, maybe four weeks cuz I was pissed
off for like two weeks after that. Bro,
I this was the first time I've been in a
bad mood cuz that [ __ ] on Instagram.
So, all women are the same. Lies,
[ __ ] stuck up. Wonder where all
these good women are. I asked my mom
this earlier. She couldn't answer it.
Um, went to a pub and had some
breakfast. Wonder where all of these
good women are, eh? They don't exist.
They don't [ __ ] exist. And if they do
exist, they've got unrealistic [ __ ] standards
thinking that they're better than
people. There's no good women out there.
I'm sure I'm sure me of all people, Bob,
would have found these women by now. If
there was good women out there, I'm sure
I would have found them. I'm sure me of
all people, someone that tested this
theory out a million times, would have
found them. But they I didn't find them
because they don't exist,
you know? Nah, there's no good women out
there. They're all [ __ ]
Do you remember that one that lied about
not she wouldn't get with me because I'm
28 and she's 23? And then it turned out
that she had been with a 28 year old
before and I'm thinking what's the
reason for that? You know, I'm not ugly.
There's nothing wrong with the way that
I look. I look after myself.
I still groom when I can, you know, like
[ __ ] what the [ __ ] type [ __ ] is that?
Like we can use like a couple of different examples
because it proves that it's not about
personality with these women.
It's never been about personality with these women.
So I don't know why people keep lying.
That one she's usually, "Oh, you're not
Muslim. Oh, you're not Muslim." Yeah.
If I went out on Friday or Saturday, I
could tell you exactly what would happen.
I could literally bet all my money on
exactly what would happen and I'd be right
because it's been the same old for many
many many many years now you know.
Nope. I'm not trying again. I'm leaving.
Nope. I'm leaving in 3 weeks. You can
try, but I won't be there.
No, I'm never trying again here, bro.
I'm leaving. I'm leaving in 3 weeks. I
ain't trying again.
just over 3 weeks. But yeah, nope. I'm
not trying again. I've got nothing left
to prove. I'm not somebody that thinks
I'm always right that has to say I I
told you so. So why would I go out just
to say I told you so?
It's going to be exactly the same thing
as it all as it has been for years. I am
not wasting my time.
They've clearly got unrealistic
standards. They're clearly stuck up.
They're clearly not grown in their head
even when they're the same age or older
than me. I've got nothing left to prove.
There's nothing left for me to prove here.
Stalked. Never stalked a woman in my
life. Basically, when a woman says that
someone's stalking her, nine times out
of 10, it basically means that you've
defended yourself against a narcissist.
So, the way they try to cover that up is
by saying that you're a stalker. Like,
what these women do is they [ __ ] with
people that they they deem themselves
more intelligent than and they see you
as a white knight and they see you as a
s and then when they realize like you're
not going to stand for their [ __ ] yeah,
they play the stalk. They say that
you're a stalker. That's just something
that they do.
Yeah, because they have no intelligent
argument in them because they're thick
as [ __ ] and they're narcissists. So they
sit there and say, "Oh, you're you're a
stalker." That and they get other people
to try and fight their battles as well. Verbal battles.
You know, you block someone. Yeah. I've
got somebody messaging me.
So, and that's somebody in South America
now. So, you know, that's these women
really do need telling about themselves, bro.
You've never been called a stalker. Good for you.
Good for you, lad. I'm happy, man. What
do you want? A brown medal, a gold one?
A silver one?
Yeah. Good for you, lad. Yep.
I got called a stalker yesterday. I
don't know how I'm a stalker. Why?
Because someone gave me their Instagram
and I kept messaging them. That's not
what a stalker is.
They really don't know the definition of
stalking these people. I've been
stalked. And trust me, it's not nice.
And they they call you a stalker when
they can't have an intelligent debate
with you. So they just call you stalker.
[ __ ] idiots, mate.
[ __ ] absolute dicks. Yeah,
that's that is in it, lad.
Stalker [ __ ] spamming someone.
A stalker. Really?
Yeah, I hate these women, lad. I hate these women.
I really, really do. Madness, bro. >> [snorts]
>> Uh well to be honest with you bro okay
the thing is okay answer um it does work
the thing is okay none of these
countries are perfect now
none of these countries are perfect like
okay I'm explain so if you if you go
Thailand there's some women that you
can't get. You're not going to get every
single woman. There's some women that
you can't get. Mainly women like in
their 20s or 80, 90 year olds. You're
not going to get 89 year olds anyways,
but women in their 20s. You can still
get 30 year olds that want
relationships. It's similar to South
America. You know, you could still get
people there. Obviously, a lot of them
are [ __ ] but you can still get
something in these countries. They're
not as good as they were 10 years ago,
yes, but here you won't get nothing. You
won't even get a 40-year-old. So,
they're not perfect by a long shot, but
you can still get things in these countries. Um,
yeah, you know, South America and
Thailand, you and Philippines, you can
get women, but obviously a lot of them
are [ __ ] Here, they're all [ __ ]
Every woman in this country is a [ __ ]
just like America and England. Worst
places ever. America and England, bro,
is the worst.
when trying to um meet a woman.
But yeah, they're not perfect, lad.
What do you mean? Of
course you can go Philippine and get a
woman, bro. Ant-Man shows me him with a
woman every [ __ ] day. And he doesn't
have to pay them either. They're from
Tinder. You can still get women in
different countries, but not here.
But that one in South America was a [ __ ]
There was this one, I tell you, there
was this Thai one before and she lived
in Dubai and she was a [ __ ] [ __ ] She
was a proper proper proper [ __ ] She
thought she was better than me cuz she
lived in Dubai. And bro, she was nasty.
Again, had to go on my mom's phone and
had to tell her about herself because
she had blocked me. Bro, it's all they're all
these women are all the same, bro. Yep.
They're all liars as well.
Trying to say that you wouldn't get with
me cuz I'm 28 and I'm 23.
You're 23 and I'm 28. So what, bro? I'm
better than you.
So yeah, that's the thing. Pokemon,
I was mad this morning, bro. It took me
ages to calm down, lad.
But then they say that women aren't all the same.
Yeah, right, bro. Yeah, [ __ ] right.
You'll notice that these women switch as well, Pokémon,
they switch. Like, you'll talk to them,
they're fine one day, the next day you
try to hit them up, never hear from them ever again.
They're they're rats, bro. They're snakes. Not available.
Oh, just Oh, you know that one trying to
that was trying to meet me the other
day, Candy. Man, it was a setup. I knew
it was. Oh, that was just some woman's
Instagram that I spammed. Um,
bro, [ __ ] uh.
Yeah, it was a setup, lad.
One nighter is best. You can't even get
a one nighter. You can't even barely get
a conversation out the [ __ ] let alone
a one nighter.
Yeah, good luck with that. Even getting
sex is impossible.
Uh, her friend told me it was, which was
which was Jamie Thompson. It was Jamie
Thompson behind it the whole time. Yeah.
I knew it was a setup. It was too
obvious. It was too obvious. It was way
because of um It was too obvious because
of um that what you wanted me you want
me to go all the way to Scotland. We've
we've been speaking only for a couple of
days. It was too obvious.
Yeah, they say that you can get laid,
but if you try and speak to a woman,
she'll pretend she's got a boyfriend.
It's a hookup culture, lad. You go on
dating apps and you can't even get a [ __ ] match.
They're just idiots, lad. That's all
they are is idiots. That's it.
Yeah. So, it was too obvious. It was way
too obvious, man. It was way too [ __ ] obvious.
Way too obvious.
Um, yeah. What? What's the chance? You
just live in Scotland.
Ah, [ __ ] off, mate.
And this South American can't piss me
off because I can't reply to my friend.
I can't type for seven days now. [ __ ] madness.
What the [ __ ] man? These women are
Nope. I haven't approached for 6 weeks
and I'm never doing it again here.
Nope. Haven't done it for 6 weeks.
Now you get to a point where you realize
all women are the same, Candy, ma'am.
And you could only give people the
benefit of the doubt for so long. I say
so long. I've been giving them the
benefit of the doubt for about 5 years.
Nope. I'm not going out again. No chance.
No chance whatsoever. I am not going anywhere but Thailand. Yeah.
Nope. I ain't going out, bro. I get I
got 10 numbers and I didn't even get a
date. I'm all right, bro.
I was out the other week getting
numbers. Was I? I haven't been out for 6 weeks.
You must mistaken me with another person.
Nope. Haven't been out. I wasn't out. I
haven't wasn't out last week. Haven't
been out for 6 weeks. You got the wrong
person. Cuz ain't been me, mate.
I'll never try again. All women are the same.
Just going for walks, chilling. It goes
fast, man. Where I've dealt with so much
of their [ __ ] for so many years. Time
just flew by.
Just chilling, bro. Playing GTA, getting breakfast.
Nope. Not interested. I was supposed to
go with my sister last week, but my
sleeping pattern was [ __ ] up. Not
interested. I'm leaving. The only thing
I'm interested in is leaving in 3 weeks.
Nah, it put me off, bro.
I don't have any pals. Well, that's self
projecting because everyone has seen me
with my friends and you're banned. No
self-p projecting negativity on my
channel. Thank you. You know the drill.
You know the rules. Um, so no, I was
supposed to go out last week for my
birthday, but I never bothered with the
Saturday. Nah, I'm done. I'm ready to leave.
So, yeah, that's how I feel now. I'm
that for it, you know.
Oh, no, I didn't.
Actually, my mom need No, I didn't.
She still needs to get
supposed to buy me. I went to my
sister's on my birthday, but I was
supposed to go on a Saturday. My
birthday was a Monday, but no,
I'm not interested.
I don't even get bored now, lad.
Yes, you did. I went over to her house
on her birthday.
I could not go out. Yeah.
And try again here and I would be okay
with it. I wouldn't get bored. I
wouldn't want to go out. I wouldn't get
urged cuz I know what women are like. I
know they're all the same. It's toxic.
It's [ __ ] depressing. Um especially
when you mix it with the hangovers, bro.
Like you don't even get bored. There's
like no urge people want to go out
anymore because they're all the same.
So there's no point dealing with them. Simple. Oh yeah. Yeah.
You get to that point in the end.
Surprised it took 5 years to be honest.
It should have been a lot sooner.
And like every time I think about going
out, I'll come across like a [ __ ] Like
today that's self American. I was
supposed to go out on Friday.
Nope. Well, I don't stay at home
thinking about the negatives. I just
stay at home and just play GTA or go for
walks. And I honestly don't get bored. I
don't get bored at all. It's so mad. I
don't even get bored.
Don't get bored at all. Maybe because
the weather's [ __ ] Maybe if it wasn't,
I would get bored. But I don't get
I'm just so glad I gave up. Like I feel
like I feel so relieved. And I I said I
was going to go out on Friday, but
because of this South American [ __ ] I'm
not going out now. Every time I think,
let me let me go out. I come across a
[ __ ] on the internet and it reminds me
why I gave up.
Like I said this to Admire. Yeah. We you
know how I always say, I'm going to go
out this week. I'm going to go out this
week. And you said, "Oh, you're going
out again. You know, it's always going
to be the same." And then the day comes
and the day comes and the day comes and
I'm like, "Bro, I didn't go out." I
literally like, "No, I didn't bother."
And that it's been like that for weeks, you know?
So, yeah. All women are [ __ ] the
same. I don't want anything to do with
any of them. They're scumbags. They
cause nothing but trouble. Toxic
toxicity they cause. like this morning.
There was no need for that. You know,
they are truly truly evil and no one's
ever going to change my mind. And and
I'll answer you why they will never
change my mind. It's because I
personally have given them the benefit
of the doubt to prove me wrong a million
times and none of them can. End the
story. It's not up for debate. End the
story. Just like you like to dismiss my
things and ignore my things, I've gave
them time and time and time and time and
time and time and time and time again to
prove me wrong and none of them can. So,
at the end of the day, I don't give a
[ __ ] what anyone says. Simple. That's it.
That's where we're at, lad.
But no, I don't get bored. I generally
don't get bored. No.
Got the money to go out. Got clothes to
go out. Got jeans coming tomorrow. Could
easy guy if I want to, but nah.
Nah. I think it's because I've been
through so much [ __ ] for years. Um, it
did used to be like that when I still
had hope, but I've got no hope here. So,
I possibly can't go mad because there's
no hope for me here of ever meeting anyone. So,
like, nah, I'm good, man. I'm saving my
money. Um, chilling. I watch like a lot
of GTA videos.
Like, so many of them. Nah, I'm good,
bro. Nah, 99% of people haven't dealt
with the [ __ ] that I've dealt with for
with with these women for years. I
haven't They haven't dealt with the bad
experiences I have had with these
[ __ ] women for years. That's why
probably 99% of people [ __ ] lose it
when they don't [ __ ] go out.
It's not happening. I'm not going out.
I'm telling you right here, right now.
I'm not going out.
I am not going out. It ain't happening, bro. So,
it's not happening. I'm done forever.
And you can blame women for that. And
you can blame this country in South
America for that.
I'm not somebody that's going to say, "I
told you so." And that's all I'll be
doing by going out. I'm not doing it.
I am not doing it, lad.
99% of people haven't dealt with the
[ __ ] I've dealt with cuz obviously they
haven't tried as much as me. So that's why
I'm more than happy sitting in looking
at my nice bank account watching GTA
cuz I don't have to deal with that toxic
[ __ ] When you go out you have to deal
with toxic women the same I've got a
boyfriend the same leading on. how old
that gets when you're dealing with that
[ __ ] constantly, constantly, constantly,
constantly. And when you stop, you feel
like, "Oh [ __ ] life is good. No
makebelieve boyfriends, no people
leading you on. It all stops. All of
that [ __ ] stops." That's probably
why you don't get bored. This is what I
said to Ant-Man. This is why you don't
get bored because you get addicted to
the peace and quiet.
You don't even lose it. It's like, "Oh
[ __ ] no more make believe boyfriends.
No more I'm not interested. No more
you're too young for me. No more you're
too old for me. No more leading." You
know, all the toxic [ __ ] that they do. It stops. So,
and obviously I lost hope as well. So,
what's there to be bored about, bro? You know,
see, I don't lose at all
cuz I know it will always be the same here.
You know what I mean?
It'll always be the same here with these
women. So, there's nothing to be bored about.
Like I said, if the weather was better, then maybe weather [ __ ] So yeah. Yeah.
What makes you think? Okay, let's let's
let's use your analogy, right? What
are the chances
that I will go out Friday and all of
these bad things that's been happening
with women is not going to happen all of
a sudden? Can you can somebody give me
the odds? What's the chances that I'm
going to go out? I'm not going to hear
I'm not interested. I'm not going to
hear I've got a boyfriend. I'm not going
to hear you're too old for me. You're
too young for me. Um, and I'm not going
to get numbers that leave me on what
what, one in a billion maybe. I don't
fancy them odds.
I really, really, really can tell you
right now that I don't fancy them odds
because I've never done the [ __ ]
lottery. So, that's that. So, it would
always be the same here, you know?
Not I'm not interested. I've been out
drinking, socializing many, many times.
Nah, I'm done.
Nope. You know what? It's It's easy to
say, "Don't expect anything." It's very,
very easy for someone to say, "Oh, you
know, if if you don't meet anyone, it's
very very very very easy to say that."
But unfortunately, it doesn't plan out
that way because when you go out, you
are going to approach someone, you are
going to deal with their [ __ ] you are
going to get numbers, and you are going
to message them numbers the next day.
And it goes round and round and round in circles.
So it's like
it's it's it's not as easy as that. You
know, this is what I was trying to
explain to Joe. It's not as easy as
that. Of course, you're going to expect
something. You've been trying for
[ __ ] years. There's nothing wrong
with you or the way that you look. You
should be getting something
cuz if you didn't expect anything, you
wouldn't be going out in the [ __ ] first place. So yeah,
there's no way you can talk me into
going back out after getting 10 numbers,
not a single date, and spending £500.
There there's no one that can talk me
into going out again, bro. It's over.
That's the end. Simple. You can blame
the women for that. You can blame the
bad experiences. You can blame all of
these women that are apparently not all
the [ __ ] same. Yeah,
you can blame them [ __ ]
Them [ __ ] women. Yeah. So yeah,
I was depressed for two weeks after that
as well. Proper proper depressed.
Yeah, like two weeks I think it was. Yeah.
No, I never had plans to go out again after that.
What should I get today? I think I might
get a tandoori chicken rice, you know. Yeah.
No, no, no,
no. I just had a life, Brad. I just had
a life, lad. Was doing stuff. Sometimes
I come off here for a bit because it's
the same atmosphere, same repeating
people, same self projectors. So, yeah.
So you're never going to meet anyone in
this country. What I can't deal with
Pokemon is the lies.
This woman saying, "Oh, you're too old
for me. I'm 23, 28. I wouldn't date you
if you're not Muslim."
And then you find out that they've been
with a 28-year-old before. And it [ __ ]
with your head because you're not ugly.
There's nothing wrong with the way that you look,
you know? And to be honest with you, no
one has ever made me insecure. Like, no
one has ever made me insecure, bro. like
but they were very very close very very
very very close and it's never been
anyone on this community and that's when
you know you need to leave you know you
need to give up them because
I always just thought oh you just look
well well you look like a normal person you know
yeah but there's no reason to be
rejected because there's nothing wrong
with the way that I look and they didn't
know my personality
Um, Pokémon, there's nothing wrong with
the way that I look and they didn't know
my personality either. So, you know,
they even use their religion as an
excuse. And it's like, hold on, you're
not ugly. There's nothing wrong with the
way that you look. I'm not putting up
with this [ __ ] anymore, you know? I'm
not putting up with this [ __ ]
anymore, you know, with them.
Yeah, but what you're missing my point.
I'm trying to say that there's nothing
wrong with the way that I look, so it
shouldn't be happening.
You know what I'm saying? There's
nothing wrong with the way that I look,
just like there's nothing wrong with the
way other people look. And they don't go
for personality either. If you are not
their exact type, they will not give you
a chance. It's not about personality, bro.
You know, we've done dating app
experiments. We've done You know what I'm saying?
So, why am I going to go out when no one
likes me in this country? It's [ __ ] ridiculous.
They've already made their, you know,
they've already made their they've
already made it clear that you they
don't like you in this country, which
doesn't make sense cuz you look decent.
You look normal. So why are you going to
go out and hurt yourself, bro? It's stupid, you know.
And that's what's not good for your
mental health as well. It's not good for
your mental health.
Today was the first time I've been in a
bad mood for like I said, Yeah. 6 weeks.
Yeah. I just been chilling, bro.
And there's nothing wrong with the way
that I look. So, what is it then?
Pokémon. What is it?
Cuz they don't know my personality. That
personality thing is old now. Cuz they
don't go for personality. That's Well,
that's the last thing they go for. It's
not the first thing they go for. So,
what is it?
You get me, lad? like
like maybe like I don't know like
somebody that has a beard or somebody
that doesn't have a beard. If you're not
their exact type, they won't even give
you a chance.
So why am I going to deal with their
unrealistic standards when I'm not ugly?
To be made for them to try to make you
feel like you're ugly. I'm not having
it. I'm not dealing with it no more.
Oh, we didn't get with you cuz you're
not Muslim and you're [ __ ] and I'm
better looking than know probably. These
are examples. They're people that I
don't know, but they're examples, you
know, even though they don't live in a
different country. They're examples.
There was nothing wrong with the way
that I look as al as long as other other people look.
So they'll still use 101 different
excuses to not go on a date with you. So what?
And then you need to just accept that no
one likes you in this country and love.
So that's that. They didn't like Ant-Man
and they don't like me. So that's that. Yep.
Yep. But if I was a white, if I looked
fully white and I was a nine out of 10,
she wouldn't use that as an excuse.
Oh, I've heard so many [ __ ] excuses
in my life, bro. With these women,
anyone would actually think you're fat
and ugly. The way they go on, anybody
would think that you're fat and ugly.
Yeah, she was using Palestine.
Um, I've had some mad ones. People
saying that they don't speak English.
Oh, bro, there's been so many.
That Pakistan one, I tell you what she said. She said
I said, "It's Peter. Why did you block
me on WhatsApp?" Hey Peter, I'm going to
change my number and purchase O2 SIM.
That's why I'm removing everyone from
WhatsApp. And I said, why? And they
didn't reply. So, bro, if it means
living your whole life without sex, so
be it, bro. I've lived my whole life
without sex, you know, I don't give a
[ __ ] You know, I've done it for 20 had
sex obviously, but you know, I've been
by myself for majority of 28 years. I
can do the other 28 years by myself as
well. I'm not dealing with their [ __ ]
I'm not dealing with it.
I've got more respect for myself than to
deal with their [ __ ] ever again.
And I've got money. I can go out every
[ __ ] week if I want.
But I'm not doing it. So
why? Because she's a woman and that's
all they do is is [ __ ] They're full
of [ __ ] All of them. You know,
I would love to know what their problem is, bro.
Yeah, she is a bullshitter. And she
didn't reply to the last message. She's
a bullshitter. She's another one that
said, "Oh, I can't date you because
you're not Muslim." And I said, "Okay,
well, I'll convert to Muslim." Oh, well,
I'm not looking for anyone anyways. [ __ ]
off. You know what I'm saying? Like, I'm
not dealing with their [ __ ] bro, anymore.
dealing with their [ __ ] anymore, bro. Sorry.
Yeah. They they they they
What it is with these women, right, is they're narcissist.
No, I'm not going out Friday, bro.
Friday's been cancelled. thanks to some
[ __ ] from South America. Um, no, that's
canled. Um, the thing is what it is with
them Pokemon is they're narcissistic.
Let me explain to you. So, it goes back
to the if you're not their exact type.
Instead of saying, look, you're not my
type. Um, you know, for this reason or
that reason, I can't get you. They want
to blame something that
can't be controlled.
It's a it's a form of narcissism.
There's so many different traits of
narcissism. So they'll say, "Oh, well,
you don't know about Palestine or you're
not Muslim." They because they're such
narcissists, they can't tell the truth
and be honest. Oh, I like someone with a
beard or no beard or blue eyes or
[ __ ] green eyes. They have to be the
victim, you know? And obviously by them
making up [ __ ] and lying, um,
they're trying to manipulate you. It's a
form of narcissism,
you know? So that's why they do it, you
know, just like when they say that
you're too um old for them. It's it's
being a narcissist. Um because they
don't want to admit that they've
rejected somebody for such shallow
reasons such as having green eyes, not
blue eyes. Yeah. It's that pathetic. So yeah. Um
So they will make up stuff like, "Oh
yeah, you're too old for me. Oh, you're
not Muslim. You know what I mean? But
and you know the worst one for me,
right, is when you approach, this is how
people try to twist [ __ ] as well. When
you approach a woman, people will be
like, "Oh, well, what if a fat ugly
woman approached you?" Well, that's
twisting things because I'm not fat and
ugly. And I have had below average women
approach me before and I've slept with
them if you want to know the truth. So,
what what what's that supposed to mean?
If if a fat ugly woman approached me,
firstly I'm not fat and ugly, so I don't
know why we're talking about fat and
ugly people. It's got nothing to do with
anything. Again, this is to try to twist
things into their narrative. You
understand? By talking about fat and
ugly people. It's very very u
manipulative what what what they're
doing. Um and yes, I have had below
average women um approach me and I've
also approached them. So what what have
you got to say about that? What have you
got to say about that? because I have
approached below average looking women
and they have also approached me and I
got with them. So, did that answer your
question? Yeah, just a little bit.
So, I don't know what what point they're
trying to get at with that, but yeah. Yeah.
And it's like all you do is come across
people that play games. Pokémon.
You'll always keep coming across people
that play games.
Even at 28. Yeah.
Even if they're 37, like that Australian
one. They all play games. They're all
the same. Women are all the same, lad.
And I'd say there's more narcissistic
women than there is men.
Defo. Most of narcissists I've come
across are women.
because they know that they're shallow
and they don't want to admit it. They
use excuses like Palestine and
stuff like that.
You know what I mean? So imagine having
all of this [ __ ] happened to you for
years and then you give up and it stops.
It feels good. Huh? Okay. Yeah, you
might not get sex, but you won't get
that anyways or whatever. Like, it's so
so what, bro? You know, it's not worth it.
And then all of a sudden, all the [ __ ] stops.
It's a relief, you know. Sorry.
But yeah, Friday's cancelled, mate.
Yeah, Friday's cancelled. Uh, Eric Yeah.
Uh cuz my sister mentioned it. My sister
mentioned it and I had to set her right
on a couple of things. I said, "Yeah,
that [ __ ] was being passive aggressive
and she was being a [ __ ] which is why I
led which is why I done that." And I
said she got a lucky escape mate because
I was going to take her to the
steakhouse and make her pay for it.
Trust me, I would have royally [ __ ]
her over, bro. Trust me, if she agreed
to it, you know,
but these women are all different.
They're not all the same. Yet, they've
got the same attitude, the same
mannerisms, the same excuses, the same
[ __ ] and the same mind games. But
they're not all the same. Nons quote.
non legs quote let's say 2K15
but they're not all the same but I would
be but me personally I would be very
very surprised if I found somebody the
same as me I would be very very very
very very very very surprised cuz no
one's like me cuz I'm different no one's
like me cuz I'm actually different
just like you'll never find a man
the same as another man because men are
not the same. Women are generally all
the same. That's the difference because
they have so many similarities for
people that are apparently different.
Think about it. Poke mom. Don't they all do
similar stuff? Play victim lead people
on [ __ ] Bullshitters.
They do a lot of the same thing for
people that are not all the same.
Surely to God if if if women weren't all
the same, right? Then men would be doing
the same thing as them because women are
not all the same like that. Wouldn't
wouldn't you get men doing the same
thing as them?
Yep. Yeah. She turned into a right [ __ ]
and I weren't dealing with it anymore.
Yeah. I weren't dealing with that [ __ ]
anymore, bro. I was not dealing with it
cuz of um Yeah, it weren't worth it.
Yeah. She started calling me mate and
stuff. I said, "Mate,
mate." I said, "Hold on, hold on, hold
on. You're calling me mate. I'm not your
[ __ ] mate." I said that to I don't
like people calling me mate. It's or
women. It sounds horrible. It sounds
common. I said, "Listen, I'm not your
[ __ ] mate, firstly." Yeah. Let's get
that out the way. And yeah, she turned
into a proper [ __ ]
That's why I [ __ ] her off. Yeah.
Yeah. She turned into a proper proper
proper entitled [ __ ] Really really
really bad [ __ ] bro.
Because they're all the same. Cuz women
are all the same. That's why
they're all the same because they watch
the same [ __ ] Tik Tok, Instagram,
they've all got Instagram brains. Tik
Tok brains. Tik Tok batteries. They're
all the [ __ ] same. They watch the same [ __ ]
No, it's just a [ __ ] term.
So, what do you think the problem is? Poke.
That Italian one was a [ __ ] as well. I
caught it early though. I caught it
early. I did catch it early, but I
thought, "Fuck it. Let me just let me
just try. I got bad vibes. I can always
I can rule people out, bro. Because of
women are all the same, so they're not
horrible. But it's like I I can tell you some
when I said, "Oh, let me buy you a
drink." She was like, "Oh, that's not
really necessary." I knew straight away
she was a come straight away. But I like
to give people benefits, you know, the
benefit of the doubt. Um, you know, and
lo and behold, it was it was a point it
was it got to the point where I was
actually depressed going on the dates
because I knew it was always going to be
the same old with them. It was always
going to be the same old.
Nah, bro. I'm not going to the bookies.
I'm all right. I've got enough money.
No, I'm good, bro. Probably go sleep in a bit.
I got a lamb shank today. So, looking
forward to that. Supposed to have it
yesterday, but I wasn't really hungry. I
woke up hungry. But yeah, I I it got to
a point where I already knew what the
date was going to be like. Pokémon. Yeah.
And it's not it's not a good mix when
you mix alcohol with bad experiences cuz
you're drinking and you're still [ __ ]
from the next you're still [ __ ] from
the night before when you were drinking.
You're still [ __ ] from the night
before, right? And you're having to deal
with these ignorers and then it's it's
not good, bro, for your mental health.
Like I said, if you was thinking of
trying again, you need six months off,
bro. At least 6 months.
But I don't know. And I got the money. I
can still go out and try.
Got more than enough money. I've got my
200 lb dreams coming tomorrow. So, but
nah, nah, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You know, I learned my lesson with gambling
to not go overboard and not, you know,
get into that gambling habit. I still
gamble occasionally, but you know, you
know, a wise person learns from their mistakes. So,
if I'm bored, I'll just go to my sisters or something,
you know, which I don't, like I said, I
don't get bored.
I know for a while I don't get bored,
but I don't really get bored, lad. I'm
addicted to saving money and not
spending it. I think I don't know. I
don't know why.
But I have I think I've definitely broke
my record now. That's how fed up of it I
got in the end, you know. Yeah.
But they obviously don't like me in this
country. So Yeah.
But they are cowards. They definitely
Getting these orbiters to fight their battles,
you know, mad.
It's so toxic. Yeah,
if I stop using the internet.
Yeah, probably, bro. I'd have to go gym or something.
But where I've had so many bad
experiences with women and I eventually
lost hope, there's nothing cuz before
the hope used to drive me mad, you know.
I used to have Michael Jackson say, "Go
out and try again, PJ."
you know, like maybe two years ago, I used to um
used to have like um you know,
I used to have hope and it used to drive
me mad. When I used to have hope, that's
what what used to drive me mad.
Um and I would get bored and I would
just go out,
but now obviously I don't. that I have
got the money to do it obviously, you
know, but I just don't see the point.
I don't know. I think it's because I've
done it so many times, bro. I mean, what I got for Saturday. So, yeah.
And obviously I'm not going to go to escort because um
Yeah, cuz it was pissing me off, bro. It
was pissing me off. The [ __ ] blocked me.
He didn't get some white knight to
[ __ ] message me.
Yeah, it's annoying. I don't like cowards.
And that's what these women are. They're
[ __ ] cowards. Sat there ignoring me
for god knows how long. And I What I
done was I went on her pictures and I
started spamming it. [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] and then they done a [ __ ] story
on me in it. They blocked me and then
they put me up on a story knowing damn
well there was going to be at least one
person that messages me when you've
blocked me. You cowardly [ __ ]
So it's toxic. That's what I mean by
And if you ask my mom like I don't
gamble. I don't shout.
I don't gamble. Um
I didn't gamble. I don't gamble like a
lot. I don't shout. I don't do any bad
things. I just mind my own business. So
when she sees me like that,
you know what? And she hasn't in a long
time. It's kind of like what the [ __ ]
I speak to my sister obviously. I speak
to my mom. My other sister wished me
happy birthday. Didn't reply. Just love
her hearted it. Oh, they probably I
probably would never talk to her again.
But that's just like choice. So you can
see where how far I've come, you know.
And then you have these [ __ ] pissing you off.
Got a little simp [ __ ] boyfriend
messaging me. If that's even her boyfriend
saying that USA is he
it's like what I told I I messaged Damon Pokemon.
It's like I I messaged Damon saying,
"Oh, I had a problem with this [ __ ]
earlier. It reminded me of your [ __ ]
ex. They're all [ __ ] big until they
meet their match, isn't it?"
Yeah. Charlene. Obviously, I don't speak
to the other one.
That's his triar, you know.
But when I pointed when I joined the
porn industry, they'll probably all
disown me. So, well, obviously, I've got
to think of myself,
you know. I've got to think of myself, mate.
You know, that's what you got to think
of, you know.
Yeah. I said that woman is like your ex.
Stamon, a narcissist.
Well, no, I didn't really apply yet. I
still need to I still need to apply, lad.
Cuz if I if they if they accept me, I'm
doing it, lad.
I'm doing it.
You have to apply. When they email you,
you have to send them a picture of your dick.
So, I don't mind, you know.
Oh, I do remember a Pokemon them women
were laughing at you, mocking you.
I don't give a [ __ ] about the pay. I
just care about the [ __ ] the fact that
you're going to be banging loads of people.
That'll be lush.
Absolutely lush, mate.
They're laughing at you.
You know, it's the truth, don't it?
Why can't I get attached anymore, Pokemon? [laughter]
Yeah. Why could I get attached for so
long? I couldn't get attached for like 2
years. What was that all about? Mhm.
Ah, my finger hurts from biting it too much.
Look how much I bite my fingers.
Oh, look at that.
Yeah, but Yeah, but why Pokemon?
Yeah, but why Pokemon? Why can't I H. Yeah. Why?
Well, I can try and message Sig. I guess
I can try and find her number and
message her. You know, Sig. Sig was all
right, ain't it?
Yeah, I suppose I could try and message Sig.
Well, yeah, but I got with Sig though,
didn't I, Pokemon?
Yeah, but I obviously could get attached
cuz I got reig, didn't I? [clears throat] Huh? Yeah, [laughter]
you're back. O, did you see the Monty
and Rice fight all on the same website?
You can watch Harry Potter on. [laughter]
It's a dangerous website, is it? Yeah, [laughter]
it's a dangerous website. Yeah.
Yeah, but it's mad to think it was the
same website you could watch Harry Potter on. >> [laughter] >> Yeah,
I want to knock that Terry out, bro. I
want to go to that Terry's area, bro.
And knock him out. Show his face on
camera, bro. Take his terrible trainers
off and and strip the [ __ ] bro. Just
strip the [ __ ] and make him [ __ ] walk back naked, you know? >> [snorts]
>> Yeah. Really?
There you go. Nah. Nah, bro.
So what if I was black then Pokémon?
Were they making excuses if I was black?
Do you think they'd make excuses if I
was black then?
I can't wait to get these new Ammani
jeans, bro. Coming to my [ __ ] £200
virgin boy. I can't afford that.
So, what am I going to do then, Pokemon?
And man was like, well, it will never
change, will it?
That's what he said. Yeah. [laughter]
You take my money, I [ __ ] take yours.
It's a hookup culture, so they say.
Ricky Millington went quiet. He was
trying to say that it was how I acted
around women. So, I thought I'd show him
a couple of approaching videos where
they didn't let me finish my sentence
before saying that they're not
interested or they've got a boyfriend.
And ever since then, he's disappeared.
Pokémon, we we haven't heard from him since,
which is strange
indeed. It is uh strange.
He said it he said it was how I was acting
with these white knights Pokemon.
You can show them black and white
evidence and they'd still be like, "Nah,
nah." They would still defend women. You
can show them black and white evidence
of their [ __ ] behavior and they'd be
like, "Nope, no, no, no." There's you
can't reason with them. You can't reason
with white knights. So there's no point
even trying to change their mind or talk
to them or cuz what's the point, nad? A
woman could kill a baby and they'd be
like, "Nah, the baby had a bad
personality." That's literally what
they'd say. Like there's there's no
getting through to them, lad. They want
if they want to defend women and be
virgins all their life, let them, bro. I
don't give a [ __ ]
Maybe they're happy with that. Maybe
it's the way they were brought up. Yeah.
Remember they say go to pubs and bars.
Go on the dating apps. Pokemon.
They say go on dating apps. Madness.
Gamblin's the only dopamine rush you get really.
When you win money gambling, it's
[ __ ] dopamine rush, isn't it?
Yeah. What's the day today? Wednesday.
[ __ ] starving, man. We got a lamb shank.
I might just have that. I need to save
some money, bro. Really?
Spend some money.
There's this woman that says she can't
find a man in London. And I messaged her
Pokémon and no reply. She said she's 30.
She lives in London. She can't find
someone. So, I messaged her and nothing.
So, when they're moaning, they can't
find a man, they're mocking the men that
actually can't find someone. Like I've
said before, they're mocking men that
actually can't find someone. Yeah.
Can't find some on my ass. Yep.
It should be damn right illegal.
saying they can't find anyone.
It should be illegal.
I I personally think it should be illegal
messenger. No reply.
Yeah. Antman said Antman said that they
contradict themselves because they say
they want a nice man, but they always
end up with men that beat them up and
cheat on them. So, they contradict themselves.
That's what Ant-Man says. Ant-Man says
that they contradict themselves
because they end up with these kinds of
people that they say they don't want.
Which is true, isn't it?
It's true that
What do you think the problem is? Why I
can't find anyone Pokemon?
What? What do you think the problem is? Yeah.
You know what I understand? The double
stand is now, right?
Say you approach a woman
and you try to meet her within a week.
Everyone would be like, "Oh, you're
trying to meet her too fast. You're
trying to meet her too fast. You need to
wait a bit longer. You're trying to meet
her too [ __ ] fast. But USA, Izzy, she
wanted to meet me within the first
message. But that's okay. But you tried
to meet a woman within a week, mate. I'm
calling I'm calling the FBI because
that's a crime. That's also double
standards cuz they will use every excuse
in the book
what you're doing wrong. Like, oh,
you're meeting them too fast or you're
not meeting them fast enough. They'll
use all these excuses, but when it's to
do with a woman, well, as you can see,
she she tried to meet me within the
first message, but that was all right
because she's a woman. So, she she gets
she gets a pass. You know, it's all
right for women to send me love hearts,
but when I send them love hearts, that's
a crime. That's why I said to Ricky,
"Oh, so it's okay for them to send me
love hearts, but I can't send them love
hearts back." Bit sexist, isn't it?
That's a bit sexist, lad. Jimmy,
was he back on YouTube?
Also, if you don't eat a woman out, they
call you gay. poker bomb. But if a woman
doesn't want to sick suck dick, that's completely fine.
Please don't tell me this [ __ ] with
Monty and Timmy still going on, mate.
It's [ __ ] boring now.
Oh, [ __ ] that. I can't be watching that, lad.
Not that [ __ ] cuz that [ __ ] just makes
me want to get involved.
I hate watching it. It makes me want to
get involved, lad.
Do you remember Pokémon? If you don't
buy attractive, you're gay. You little copycat.
Your little copycat
wanted to fit in with the crowd.
He didn't want to feel left out. He
didn't want to feel left out. Bless him.
He wanted to fit in.
Why did you watch the video where Monty
and Timmy and Mike met? Do you want to
go for a pint or do you want to do it
dirty? I was dead, bro. I was dead.
That's going to be my new saying. You
want to go for a drink or do you want to
do it bad? >> [laughter]
>> all on the same website you can watch
the side men on. No, it can't be true. Like, [laughter]
do you want to go for a drink or do you
want to do it bad?
Or do you want to do it [laughter] bad?
I [clears throat] was dead when I heard
that cuz I was watching Mickey Mouse at
the same time. [laughter]
Why do you want to do that? [laughter]
I think they all made up. You watched it
then, didn't you? Nah.
So, why did he say if you don't find her
attractive, you're gay Pokémon? I'm not gay.
I just don't find her attractive.
Why is he um
See, he kind of [ __ ] himself up with
that whole police thing, you know, cuz
if it wasn't for that, he could actually
come in and talk. And I'd want to know
why he feels the need to be a copycat.
You know, that's why I've always liked dogs,
you know? I've never liked cats and I
don't like copycats.
You little copycat.
You little copycat. wanting to fit in
with a crowd.
That is definitely someone that's
insecure about their sexuality.
He says that if you don't find her
attractive, you're gay.
She's [ __ ] not. She's [ __ ]
stinking. She's [ __ ] ugly. And I've
had more women than that virgin.
No, she [ __ ] bloody well isn't.
No, she's [ __ ] well ain't.
Nope. King's not here. He doesn't live
here. Oh, he only comes for sleepovers.
Yeah, I would give her one one punch in
the [ __ ] mouth. [ __ ] fat can. Oh,
not much. Just chilling, bro.
We had beef with a South American [ __ ] earlier.
Had a little white knight [ __ ]
messaged me out to put him in his place. Yeah.
So many double standards, bro. They're
It's interesting to talk about. You know,
you try to meet a woman within a week,
mate. You're trying to meet her too
fast. But if a woman wants to meet you
within one message, you go, girl, that's the spirit.
Yeah. Um, she was ignoring me. Don't
remember the one that was ignoring me
and I spammed her. She blocked me and
she got a little white knight boyfriend.
Um, who I didn't even know she had to
message me. I told him about himself.
He said, "Get your own girl." I was
like, "You blocked me for a reason, but
you're messaging me, [ __ ] dickhead."
All the all the reason not to go out on um Friday.
Nah, bro. I'm done. I'm never going out
in this country ever again. Approaching.
I'm done, bro. Six weeks and still going.
I ain't I ain't going out, lad.
No, that just reminded me of that USA
Izzy and her Pokemon. I would cl her in
her face but her [ __ ] friend.
That USA Izzy friend thinks she's [ __ ] tough.
He actually thinks he's tough, bro. Madness,
you know. Yeah. He says Cheryl Cole's
attractive to fit in.
Yeah. But he says it to fit in though.
He doesn't want to feel left out.
It's the name. It's not the It's not the
person. It's the same. It's Sorry, it's
the name. Sorry. It's anything to fit in.
anything to fit in with the crowd.
Yeah. I said she said she'll be my 25th
and she started coming on to me. I don't
care who your cousins are, bro. I'd cl
you all in your [ __ ] face.
You know, I'll cl you all in your face.
I said the same thing to Damon as well, bro. You know,
we need a new [ __ ] uh It's like that
damn, bro. He would get smoked. He really would.
Yeah. These women always get other
people to fight their battles.
If it's not her dad, it was her friend.
If it it wasn't her friend, it was [ __ ] Um,
I think I spoke to her sister once. It's
always someone, you know, but then
it's mad. They're all the [ __ ] same.
Yeah, I gave up, bro. In the end, it was too depressing. Yeah.
Good old dam.
No, it wasn't it wasn't amazing. It was very dangerous
and depressing. It wasn't amazing at all.
She's lucky I didn't kill her, bro.
Really, really is.
I should have gave up from then to be
honest. I should have just gave up.
Really from then I should have gave up, bro. Nope.
I'm not tempted at all to go out Friday.
I'm going for this meal tomorrow.
Definitely going tomorrow. I get my
jeans tomorrow and I'm going for this
meal tomorrow. Definitely not tempted.
Nope. That South American woman put me
off. No. [ __ ] that. That's stinking,
bro. You know, no.
>> They're not all the same. You don't know all women.
>> I know [ __ ] more women than you, you [ __ ] virgin.
No one can say it [ __ ] better than
me, can they? Pokemon.
I know more [ __ ] women than you.
You don't know all women. This is what
he used to say cuz he's a [ __ ]
[ __ ] He used to do this. Look, he
used to say, "You don't know all women.
You don't know all women. They're not
all the same.
They're not all the same. You don't know all women."
What a [ __ ] [ __ ]
What an absolute [ __ ]
They're not all the same.
Why does Virgin Boy say they're not all
the same when they are? Huh? Nah.
But I'm going to make sure the next
woman that pisses me off lives in
England so I can actually get them. And
any white knight that tries to [ __ ] defend them?
Why are they such [ __ ]
She reminded me of that Italian one that
I went on a date with. Just [ __ ]
That's what they are. They're just
[ __ ] They get like that in
Thailand now. They're just [ __ ]
I don't know.
So, this woman that said she's 30 and
she can't find anyone in London still
hasn't replied back to me. She said she
can't find single men. [laughter]
Yeah, I was with um Q that time as well.
I was with Q.
Yeah. And he walked in on me fingering
her. He said, "Is everything okay here?"
And we were like, "Yeah."
I didn't ask her, bro. She just went She
went to pee, right? And then I went to
pee and then like I could see her
[ __ ] like I could see her mini in it
and I just started fingering the [ __ ]
out of her, bro.
She didn't say stop or anything. She
just got fingered the [ __ ] out of, bro.
And then Q come like two minutes later
he says is everything all right here
like uh yeah [laughter]
it was a madness but Yeah. [laughter]
Oh, [ __ ] hell.
So, what happens when you approach women
in fabrics? Um, Pokémon, cuz obviously
people say go to clubs, don't they?
You have to go to bars.
They say you go to like clubs and stuff like raves.
Yeah. So, what do you think will happen
if I approach in Fabric's Pokémon?
Like I pay £35 to get in and I start approaching. Huh?
Yeah, this guy tried white knighting me
in it cuz I was kissing her and touching
her boobs and stuff and he was like,
"Oh, that's childish." I said, "I do
what I want, you little white knight."
He's just he's just jealous because she
went for me and not him.
Do you remember the Indonesian fella? He
got scarred for life in it cuz the woman
didn't like him but wanted but kissed
the army lad's friend.
That Indonesian fella. He got scarred
for life, didn't he? I was live with the
Indonesian fella like six weeks ago. You
didn't Did you You must have missed it. No,
I was live with the Indonesian fella. I
know he's your favorite. Yeah,
he was just sat there like a dog. like a pedigree dog. Yeah.
Oh, he saw it. Yeah. He couldn't
approach that. That's when I got 10
numbers. 10 numbers. Not even a single date.
Poor Indonesian fella. [laughter]
Madness, isn't it? Yeah.
Yeah. I'm going to get some tandoori
chicken and rice, I think.
What do you think?
Chicken and rice.
I'm starving, man.
Get that rice. Yeah, maybe I get some
pizza. I don't know. I'm hungry as [ __ ]
Do you remember the [ __ ] in the alleyway? Pokémon.
It says 40% of £40, but you can't get
stuffed crust. And I want the pizza to
have stuffed crust. So,
I want stuffed crust. And obviously if I
want stuff cost I'm going to have to pay
a shitload of money and I'm not paying that.
Oh, this looks lush. Tandoori spice, curry base
sauce, tandoori chicken, onion, green
peppers, red chilies, and mint yogurt drizzle.
Oh, that looks nice.
So, you can't customize it. You can't
get stuff crusted. That's the thing. And
I watch stuff crust,
but it cost too much money, bro.
There's a lot of nice uh pizzas.
I could get that pizza again. Yeah.
But it's going to cost too much money to
have it stuff crushed cuz you can't
personalize it on the deal.
[ __ ] dirty bastards.
Yeah, but I prefer Papa John's to be honest.
Let me try Pizza Hut.
My favorite is Papa John's, then Pizza
Hut, then Domino's.
Yeah, but I don't live next to one.
I don't live next to one, bro. I don't
live too too far, but you'd have to get a bus. No,
no, no, no, no. because there's not one here. Right.
Any size pizza $9.99.
[snorts] Okay, this could be good.
Any size pizza. Yeah.
Oh, here we go. Yeah, this this is a
good one. This is a good one.
So, I think I'll just get a meat feast. $11.99.
Large stuff cross 1498.
Cheesy bites is 1598.
I do like the cheesy bike, but we'll go
with stuff crust. We'll see what it says in it.
Yeah. 1797. That's still not bad. It's
still under 20.
Oh, but is it not is it halo? We need to
check this one isn't halal cuz I don't
want [ __ ] turkey bacon. Yeah. 1797.
Yeah, that's not bad.
So, with a drink, it's like 20 pound.
That's not too bad.
What do you think, Grezy?
No, that ain't bad at all.
But maybe I should create my own one.
But I need to make sure that one's not.
But I fancy that Papa John's one. I was
going to get a meat feast from Pop um
from Pizza. I was going to get a meat feast.
Papa John's is the best, but can't um
but I need to make sure that pizza is not halal
cuz turkey bacon is [ __ ] stinking, done.
No, it's really stinking, bro.
Cuz some Ps are allow
Oh, it doesn't even deliver to this address.
So, we're [ __ ] there.
Looks like we'll be going hungry tonight. [laughter] Greasy.
Well, I want that Papa John's one, but
bro, it's too expensive.
They say it doesn't deliver to this area.
We'll be going hungry tonight. Not
having it for
not having it for toffee.
No, I can't just get it, bro.
I've already been Weather Spoons. I had
a breakfast earlier.
I don't drink anymore. So,
all right. Let me see how much do you
want to know how much this pizza will be, Grezy?
But it doesn't let you do stuff crust on this
on this um thing.
It doesn't let you do stuff crust.
It does, but you can't do it on this.
You have to go do it on the app.
Yeah, it's £24 without the stuff crust. £26.
So, you're talking30, bro, for a [ __ ] pizza.
So, that's a nogo. We can't do that.
Yeah, we're talking about 30 pound, bro,
for a [ __ ] pizza. I'm not paying that.
Right, let's have a look at Domino's. Um, Right. So,
yeah, this could be good. 10% off your
order when you spend £30.
Okay. What's the TMC's?
Yeah. So if you spend £30
20 off when you spend £50
40% off when you spend £40 get 50% off the app.
Right. Let me try the
Okay. So, create your own. That's what I
always do anyways. Yeah. See, it's
included in the voucher, but on the Papa
John's one, it's not.
Right. Large pizza.
Always get the same toppings.
Domino stuffed crust. Toppings. Okay. Onions, ham, mushrooms,
some dory chicken.
£38. What the [ __ ] This is why they've
got the all of these. Why the [ __ ] How
the [ __ ] does it come up to this amount
of money, bro?
It's the 40% off we want.
No, this is insane, bro. What the [ __ ]
So, it's actually 40 the 40.
We want the 40 one off. That's why
they've got these [ __ ] deals is cuz
they're so expensive.
So, we need to spend £40.
I am doing that, bro.
Yeah, maybe if it's cheap enough. Um
or I'm going to have jalapenos, I think. Jalapenos.
Yeah. Okay. Jalapenos, onions, double ham,
double hand turn.
That's 36 pound one.
Okay. £40. Okay. So
that makes it £24.
But this is a lost pizza. This is a lush lush pizza.
No, cuz I like to make my own and it
needs to come to 40 anyways before
I can get the offer because it's 40% of
£40. So, I need to spend £40 either way.
And I like to create my own one. Anyways,
the good thing with Domino's is they do
a nice Coca-Cola.
They do nice Coke. Like it's real Coke
and it's I remember going Domino's when
I was in Leeds. Oh, [ __ ]
When I was in Leeds.
So, it's come to 30 pound.
Nah, it's too much, bro.
It's [snorts] too much. Pizza and a
drink, bro. It's too much.
I don't know what I'm going to do then,
bro, cuz it's too much.
No, that's too much, bro.
I can't pay that. I would have paid like
25 or whatever, but I can't pay £30.
It's too much. >> [laughter] >> Um,
I really want to pop a John, you know.
Should I get it? Greasy.
We'll let Grey decide.
Stuff crush. Extra green jalapeno,
onions, ham, chicken. Not really.
It's a lot of money, is it? £30 for
pizza and a drink. Yeah. [snorts]
I can't get Papa John's, bro.
Should we just get Papa John's?
But then, no, but the problem with if
you go Papa John's, they only sell
Pepsi. So, I'm going to have to go out
and get drink anyways.
Uh because they do Pepsi. They don't do Coke.
I have to get it from the Papa John's
app. Anyways, one second. I need to
download the Papa John's app. There's a
glitch with this. Uh I'm saying
30 for [ __ ] beat. Let me see how much
it is on Papa John's. [ __ ] it in it. Yeah,
I'll have to go out and get Coke. That's
the thing. Don't like Pepsi. It's rank
right. Let me I'm on it now. One sec. Okay. So,
upgrade to stuff crust. Yes, please.
So, it's going to be £27.
£30 just for the pizza. It's ridiculous,
bro. I can't pay that.
Maybe there's like some deals somewhere else.
It's too expensive.
What about this medium pizza?
XXL Papa meal deal. One plastic side,
one XXL pizza.
Ah, here we go. What's this? Papagon's
meal. One large pizza. One second.
There's got to be some sort of deal on
here, bro. That does stuff crust. Okay.
Okay. Here we go. One second. No, no,
no, no. One sec.
Here we go. Lovely. 1899.
Okay, we got it. Um,
yeah. Okay. Yeah. Lovely.
Sure. This is it. No.
Yeah. £21. Yeah, that's more like it. I
don't mind paying £21
cuz I can't have it with stuff cost. It
is stuff crossing. Let me make sure this
is stuff cross before I get in this.
No, I'm not I'm not [ __ ] fussy. I
just don't want to get [ __ ] ripped off.
Okay, so I'm going to order it. Uh
Ben and Jerry's large tub 64 pound50.
That's temp. I'm more than this. Hold on.
I want barbecue wings. £7.
One second. Let me speak to lady. She's
doing some barbecue or something.
Hold on. Oh, what is this?
Bro, order that. Yep.
There we go. Lovely.
getting in these little bits.
No money in it.
Oh, I hope you're looking forward to this. Graves,
are you looking forward to this? Grezy,
you [ __ ] better be, matey. Oh, [ __ ]
It's going to be lush.
So the good old times, eh?
Need some coke though.
Yeah, I got my money back the next day, bro. No.
Stuff cross tastes so much better, bro.
Yeah, I was going to go out Friday. Um, flat Eric,
but I don't want any more bad
experiences with women.
I don't want no more bad experiences.
They're [ __ ] bad [clears throat] people, bro.
So, I've given up here.
Going for a meal tomorrow. So, yeah.
Nah, there's no point. You're not going
to pull. You're not going to meet a
woman. So, what's the point?
Absolutely pointless if you're not going
to meet anyone, I'd say.
Doesn't matter. Okay. It's going to be
busy and and and what the women are not interested.
There could be one woman. There could be
one woman. There could be a million
women. I'm not interested. So,
doesn't matter to me whether it's busy
or not, does it? Cuz they're not
interested here. So yeah,
Yeah. So, no, I won't be out. Wan, brother.
No, just women being the same old shitty
[ __ ] as they always are.
No, same old.
Just like it would always same older
women in this country. You don't expect
any different, do you? No.
I'm not going out. So, there's no point
in answering it because I'm not going out. So,
he was thinking about me. Thanks,
That's nice, man.
No, I wouldn't. Cuz the last time I went
out, I got 10 numbers and I didn't even
get a date.
I don't believe you, Eric, cuz I went
out six weeks ago and I got 10 numbers
and I didn't even get a date. So, I
don't believe you.
Nah, not interested. Yeah.
What do you mean? Why am I not closing
10 numbers? I got 10 numbers. I messaged
them the next day. Only one replied and
they said they were going to meet me,
but they never. So, I just gave up after that.
I did try to close them. They didn't reply. You pillock.
So I am
[ __ ] illic. Yeah, they're not
interested in this country.
So there's no point going out trying
when people don't like you in this
country. That's the way I see it.
They're all the [ __ ] same these women, lad.
That's why I gave up.
Uh, do I think they have a boyfriend? Um,
no. No, I don't think they've got a boyfriend.
No. They're full of [ __ ] That's what
they are. Full of [ __ ] They're [ __ ]
They're just [ __ ]
I dealt with a South American woman
today. She was a [ __ ] She kept ignoring
me. I spammed her. She blocked me and
then got some white knight to message
me. And then she's telling me that I
need to go to therapy, but she's sat
there [ __ ] ignoring me.
No, she's the one sat there ignoring me
300 times. [ __ ] stupid [ __ ]
I went on my mom's phone and told her to
get raped. [ __ ] scumbag. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. She got like I said, so she
she blocked me
and then some guy messaged me. I said,
"Don't even think about comment on my
inbox, you [ __ ] white knight." So
when I was spamming her, she put it up
on her story knowing damn well that
somebody was going to message me.
Like they're so cowardly they can't even
fight their own battles.
These women are so cowardly they can't
even fight their own battles. They're
ignorant as [ __ ] I told him [ __ ] off.
Don't even think about coming on my
[ __ ] inbox, you little [ __ ]
These women are all bad people. Like
there's no doubt in my mind all these
women are the same. She was fine
normally talking and then the day after
she kept being an ignorer and she's been
doing it for over a month just being an
ignorant stuck up ignorer.
And I kept spamming her, sending her my
dick. She was still ignoring. Then I
went on her picture and then just
started spamming her. And then she then
then then it then I got her attention.
Uh she was brown South American.
Then then she started being a [ __ ] I
went on her pictures and just started
spamming her um
spamming her photos and then she um she
blocked me. Yeah. She was being a [ __ ]
and she was doing it on purpose as well.
Put it in the freezer.
Sorry about that, man.
I don't like pepi. That's why I had to
get the coke separate. Oh, yeah.
But yeah, man.
What is wrong with these women? flat Eric.
Yeah, she's added to my bad experiences of women.
Yeah, there's been many of them bad
experiences with women cuz all women are
the same obviously. So, yeah.
Yeah. sort of being an ignorer.
I had one woman say she wouldn't get
with me um cuz I'm too old for her flat.
She's 23. I'm 28. Yeah.
Yeah. Um I found out she'd been with a
28-year-old and I'm thinking, "What the
[ __ ] I'm not ugly. I look normal flat
and I'm being treated like I'm ugly. [ __ ] that.
That's why I gave up, lad. That's why I
gave up. It was no good for my mental
health. It's no good for my mental
That's why I gave up, you know.
No, she ordered a Coke.
I don't know what the problem is. I
think I look all right, don't I? Flat
Eric. I think I look normal.
Like I'm not saying I'm like extremely
good-looking. I just look normal. No,
like a normal person.
Um, you know what I'm saying, bro?
I just look like a normal person.
So, what's all of these excuses about?
Yeah. So, what are all of these excuses
about? Oh, you're too old for me. I
can't get with you cuz you're not
Muslim. What is all of these mind games
and [ __ ] about?
I don't get it.
You know, they say that they go for
personality, right? But they don't even
give you a chance. It's [ __ ]
They're more shallow than men. Women are
more shallow than men. 100.
Women are more shallow than men. Yeah,
I know. Candy. They're more shallow than
men. Women are more shallow than men. 100.
cuz they always say to me, "What would
what would you do if a fat ugly woman
approached you?" And I'm thinking, "But
I'm not fat and ugly, so why are we
talking about fat and ugly women?" And
then I say, "I have had below average
women approach me and I've gotten with
them." I have approached below average
looking women. So you don't have an
argument, you know.
Yeah, there was one I told you about
this. Well, I told someone about this,
but they're not here now. You know that
Muslim woman that I was um meeting?
She's like, "Hey, Peter, I'm going to
change my number and purchase O2 SIM.
That's why removing everyone from
WhatsApp." So, I asked her why she
blocked me. It's just [ __ ] after
[ __ ] after [ __ ] with these women.
No one's grown in their [ __ ] head.
[ __ ] after [ __ ] after [ __ ] So >> yeah,
>> that's all it is. That's all it will ever be. You know,
they're all the same, lad. How people
sit there and say women aren't all the
same, I shall never know, lad.
I shall never know how they say they're
not all the same.
Right, I'm going to try and finish this
whole pizza this time.
Saying that I probably have to offer
Laneia a slice and you're going to see
how it's much harder now with the stuff crust.
I don't think I'll be able. Okay, if I
do it, Grezy, you have to give me £500.
Would you do it? Would you give me £500
if I do it?
I don't know about that, bro.
I'll try my hardest. Let's see how good
I do it this time.
20 pizzas, 200 jeans. Ah, virgin boy
could never grieves. Eh, virgin boy could never.
Virgin boy could never
right. Where is it? Pizza.
I can't wait.
How many slices do you reckon I'll be
able to eat?
I don't have the jeans. I don't have the
jeans. The jeans are coming tomorrow, lad.
Obviously, Virgin by um can't afford 200 pound jeans.
Want a woman? I really want to ruin a
woman's life. Candy, man.
Nah, I can't eat all of it, bro. I'll
try to eat as much as I can.
But it's going to be harder cuz the the
crust is stuffed, isn't it? Yeah,
I want to ruin a woman's life, Candy, man.
But yeah, they're all full of excuses.
Oh, I can't get with you cuz you're not
Muslim. Oh, I'll become Muslim.
Cuz they don't want to admit they're shallow.
That's why they make excuses because
they don't want to admit they're shallow. Caliban,
come on, pizza. We're waiting on you.
We're going to gobble you up.
Going to gobble you up.
Waiting for it to be out for delivery.
Getting in his little bed [ __ ] with no
bed, no money in it.
Virgin boy skin sh.
Come on, hurry up. Be out for delivery.
You reckon a skinned virgin could get a
pizza like this?
I don't reckon he could afford it, mate.
What do you think?
Ah, money is live. [laughter] Yeah.
Come on, pizza. Yep.
Hurry up. I'm hungry.
I'm really hungry. I'm waiting for this pizza.
Oh, it's on its way. We one sec.
Why can't I track it anymore?
Right. So about 10 minutes it says
their number there. So that's fine.
Yeah, their numbers there.
If I go out on Friday, Greavvesy, will I hear boyfriend?
Do you reckon I would hear it? Greavvesy. Well, no. And boyfriend.
Not [ __ ] funny, bro.
Yeah, I'll leave you on camera.
Somebody on Reddit said there might just
be too many stuckup [ __ ] in your
country. That's what they said, Bob
Bills. They said, "Well, you look normal
and you sound normal. Your approaches
are normal. Maybe there's too many
stuckup [ __ ] in your country."
That's what someone on Reddit said to
me. I think they were right. They said,
"Maybe too many stuckup [ __ ] in
whatever weird country you live in.
Oh, it should be here soon.
You reckon I'll get lucky?
What do you think, Gregy? Do you think
I'll get lucky? But why would you think that? Why this time
I'll get lucky, but not the other million times?
So, you think this time
out of all the million times that I have
gone out and got nowhere, I'll get
lucky? Nah, I don't like their mods, mate.
I I I don't like their mods cuz I went
out like a month ago and I got 10
numbers. Nah, I don't think so.
I don't like their mods.
Why? Why this week of all weeks?
Why would it be different than any other time?
Nah, I'm not going out loud.
Do they? They said that to me last year,
didn't they, Grezy? Oh, go out for
Halloween. Go out for Halloween. Went
out for Halloween. Nothing.
Yeah. [ __ ] right off, mate. I'm not
buying into that again.
You said that last You said that last
year as well. Oh, go out for Halloween,
go out for New Year's, and I got nothing
then either. [ __ ] off. Yeah,
you said that last year, didn't they, Grezy?
Carry and rice. [laughter] Uh,
see I want to I would do a video
attempting to eat a whole pizza, but the
thing is is obviously I have to give
Laney a slice
if she'll even eat it.
You know, I can't say no. You know what
I mean? It's selfish.
So, it wouldn't be proper.
That's the thing.
Yeah, look, the mod started an argument
with me then he banned me. Greavvesy
anything to feel powerful. Eh,
they need that power, don't they? They
need that power.
Is that right, Grezy? Yeah. Um,
it doesn't say.
Where the [ __ ] are these [ __ ]
That woman on Red's horrible.
Yeah, the weather's horrible out there, mate. One second.
Give her a blow. What are you talking about?
Hang on a sec.
Okay. So, yeah, Laney said she'll have one.
Nope. Another football bet for uh Saturday though.
[ __ ] The weather is [ __ ] out there, man.
It's [ __ ] prison.
Where the [ __ ] is this [ __ ]
It's been longer than [ __ ] 10
minutes. Do you remember that greasy?
Where the [ __ ] are these [ __ ]
I want my pizza.
Never mind my mind. I'm going to have
these bastard cornflakes.
Do you remember that one? You greasy. [laughter]
Let me ask him where he is. a second. Hold on.
Guy better give this pizza mate.
Yeah, this is on its way. One second.
It gives you a number, but it's not
their number. Where the [ __ ] is this
Oh, says he's arriving.
Oh, is that him? Right. Quick pee before
he comes. Oh, it's coming.
Quick pay. Quick pay. All right.
[snorts] I might say to him, "Thank you, cunt."
Sorry, that's a minute.
Thank you, [ __ ] [laughter] Outland.
Where is he, bro?
It's got to be him, isn't it?
Yeah. Why is he calling me? You got to
go straight, you [ __ ] idiot.
Thank you, [ __ ] No, I'm not saying
that, bro. I don't think I've got the
balls to say that, man.
Like, he actually understands. Yeah.
Yeah. Papa John's here.
We [ __ ] in here.
Oh, it's freezing, man. It's bare cold, bro.
>> Yeah. Thank you, bro.
Oh, here we go. Got the goods.
I'm going to make you a little f You silly [ __ ]
I don't get suffering with me. [laughter]
Oh, look at that.
Oh, you're telling me this looks smaller
than the other one.
Virgin boy can't afford that. Virgin boy
can't afford that with his [ __ ] skin. No.
It's out of his price range.
You can't feel the B. That'll be his price range.
Right. I'm going to eat it. One second.
Let me just give last right.
Yeah, it's smaller than this one I
think. But the the it is stuff crusted.
So it is stuff crusted. So
it's the same. This one's stuff. It adds
a lot of fat to it. The virgin boy can't have it. Mist,
it tastes so much better though Five rings. Frames.
This makes it so much nicer.
>> [clears throat]
>> Next time I'm going to have to tell you advice. that side.
Look at this.
I must be doing well. Well, that's the irony
of people that know about other people's
lives. Isn't that right, Groovy? People
don't know how much I have. People don't
know how much I don't have.
That's the irony of not knowing
someone's life. Is that That's the whole
thing of not knowing someone's life.
Isn't that right, Gy? Ah,
Coke is so much nicer than Pepsi. Nothing wrong. No.
Well, why wouldn't I be doing well, bro?
I've always had money.
Why wouldn't I be doing well?
I've got a pair of 200 pound jeans
coming as well.
Yeah, that's coming tomorrow. Morning jeans.
Yeah, need a new pair of jeans.
Why would I be doing well, bro? These
people come here and call people skin
cuz they're skin.
It's obvious, isn't it? Right. It's like
what Monty used to say. I said, "Money,
why do they call me skin?" And he's
like, "Cuz they're skin."
That's lovely. It's cuz they're good. Oh,
getting harder now. Don't forget it's
crush. So that adds on to the calories.
Yeah, but you people ain't got cars and a mortgage.
That's the thing.
And even if you did have a mortgage and
cars, bro, none of you ever got lives.
But the thing is, bro, it doesn't really
matter because none of you people in
here have got lives.
I know most people my age don't have
mortgages. Most people my age live with
their parents in London. So, your guess
was very, very wrong. And there's loads
of people that don't drive.
The only thing Gregy agrees with me on
is the narcissists. And bro, it doesn't
matter. Even if you did have a car and
you did it, bro, you ain't got a life.
So, who cares?
And most people my age don't have a
mortgage. You're delusional.
They don't have a mortgage. Most people
my age. Not in [clears throat] London.
They don't mate. So
yeah, you ain't got no life experience.
This is what I mean. If you actually
went out and had a life, you know this thing. So yeah.
Oh, there we go.
a wild sympathies.
Yeah, you got it right. You're talking about yourself.
Yeah, you got it right about yourself.
Yeah, cuz you're talking about yourself.
So, yeah, you got your own life, right?
That's you, not me.
So, you're talking about yourself.
You're a virgin. You're a Peter. You
ain't got a mortgage and you ain't got a life.
>> Yeah. You're talking about yourself.
What's up? Oh,
that's a big old device. So the projectile
I might do it.
These people are such self projectors, aren't they?
They're proper mongos over here, aren't they? Proper mongos.
We all know they ain't got a life, mate.
The people in this community ain't got a
life. It's obvious. [ __ ]
It's going to melt
to me now.
Agreed with me on the narcissistic
women. I like
you agreed with me on the narcissistic women.
They get orbit.
They get orbiters to fight their battles. [snorts]
Isn't that why?
No one cares about his repeater.
>> [clears throat]
>> No one cares.
They can't even stand up for themselves.
They're such cowards.
Women are cowards, bro.
>> [clears throat]
>> I could have finished a lot and that's
actually one but
I don't can do it.
King could do it in it. Yeah. They don't
allow pizza. Well,
team could definitely do it if he was
allowed it. But they can do it. I don't
know how they do it though.
You sure you don't want another slice?
Do you reckon Do you reckon King could eat all?
But how could he eat all but Huh? Huh? He's greasy.
He said King's greasy.
Yeah, King could do it. [clears throat] and rice.
Why did you say that music? [clears throat]
So bad [ __ ]
>> [clears throat]
>> stuff. If it would stop fast, I would
have done it.
Yeah, I know. I know. I know. [clears throat] No, bro. [ __ ] me. M.
The barbecue sauce is so nice. The
spread all over.
I got three slices left for later.
Oh, barbecue. You know when I used to go
subway, I always used to have barbecue sauce.
I always used that barbecue sauce. Always.
Have you ever had Subway? [clears throat]
How can you ever lose it?
[clears throat] The barbecue sauce is
[ __ ] Penny, bro.
That's why I love the barbecue sauce.
I don't get my vitamins anymore from USA
is do I boozy?
She used to give me vitamins in it.
Remember that boozy?
A What would you do with me? What would
you do without me on YouTube?
Oh, I'm stuck. Mama,
I need my I need my vitamins. Yeah.
You need to have this pizza.
I can't finish them. then free.
Okay, I will finish these three on one
condition. You want me to finish them
right now? Yeah.
Re has to go on Virgin Boy's recent
[snorts] community post and write, "When
are you going to finish it? When are you
going to lose it, Virgin Boy?
And when I read it and you've done it, I
will do it.
I'll finish it.
All right then. One more there.
Oh. Oh, but you don't mind it when he
calls me a [ __ ] virgin, do you? When
he didn't talk [ __ ] about me, you don't
back me up. But soon as I go for that
[ __ ] we got all of you little simps
backing him up. This is my [ __ ]
problem with you [ __ ]
you know? Oh,
[ __ ] the [ __ ]
[ __ ] back me up. Yeah.
Fine. I'm not finishing it.
No, it doesn't bother me. I just find it
weird, lad. No, it doesn't bother me. It's weird
cuz um everyone sits up for him when I'm
falling in. He's an actual pedophile.
But when he says stuff about me, no one says anything.
Oh, with you. That account is back. By the way,
that account is back. You know the one
that said they were mocking you,
laughing at you. That account's back.
Did you see it earlier, Grooie? Let me
try and get it. Oh, I can't get it up.
The account's back on that Pokemon account.
Who the [ __ ] is that behind that
account, bro? There's been several
different ones. Who is it?
It's not Joker.
They were mocking you.
They were laughing at you.
Yeah. Who is it, bro? It ain't It isn't
Joker. It isn't Joker. I don't know who it is.
You know who I'm talking about. it. It's
just they come on the different accounts
and I knew it was them
cuz I like Sig not Peter Belly's mama.
They knew straight away. Boozy
not because Peter B already found his mama
can't get attacked because he's already
found his mama.
is already found his mama
because he's already found really.
Have you ever smelled a dog a dead fox
before? I have. It's [ __ ] stupid.
Yeah, there was a dead fox across the
road. Took ages to [ __ ] get rid of
it. And whenever you'd walk past it, it stink.
Oh, mate, you can smell it a mile off.
I'm sure you smell a dead fox, didn't
you, Greasy in your time? H.
Oh, that was nice. I'm eating a rest later.
Isn't that right, Greasy? H. Oh, yeah.
Maybe that account you greasy that dusty
showbiz. Yeah, he was a snake. Whenever
I caught somebody being a snake, they
never come back. Like Ricky, that Hugh
once they they snake you and you catch
them, they never come back. Oh mate.
>> Yeah, I put it outside, bro. I'm going
to have the fre.
>> They're all snakes in it, Grezy. Oh,
but it still doesn't beat a t-bone
steak. T-bone steak will always be the goat, bro.
T-bone steak would always be the
absolute joke. It's hard to beat a nice
t-bone steak, mate.
So, who's my mama? Greasy. I'm missing
my my vitamins.
I've got a vitamin deficiency now
cuz I don't get the vitamins anymore.
the um the calcium graz
because he's already found his mama.
Peter belly can't get attached because
he's already found his mama. Sig, not
Peter Belly's mama. Greasy.
Sig is a woman that had a one night
stand with Grezy,
but it just didn't feel the same. Grezy,
you know, the kisses and the boobs, they
just weren't the same. Griezy, you know? Yeah,
because he's already found his mama. Oh,
that's cute. It gym.
Me, King Grezy, sat there having some
pancakes and I'm playing GTA San Andreas. Bless you.
Bless you then, Grimzy.
So you know where this Jamie is this you
know where this Jamie guy is stalking me
Grezy just Jamie Thompson. It's not the
same website you can watch the Sideman
on is it? It's not is it?
Well I'm arguing with him. Yeah. It's
not the same website is it?
[ __ ] stalking [ __ ]
It's not the same website, is it? [laughter] Nah. [snorts]
Yeah. Women are such cowards, Grezy, man.
They can't defend themselves.
They need to um
they need to get other people
They need to get other people to fight their battles
and play victim.
That is USA is all over it. That is that
South American is is that is that Morgan all over.
It's all over in it.
D uh Damon hasn't replied back to me.
He said, "I need to find God." He said,
"Only God can save you. Only God can save me." Wow.
I used to hate them times when I used to
get nicks over YouTube. Greavvesy. It
was scary. Bro, you get police on the door,
they'd come and pick you up. You'd be on
a in a cell for like 21 hours. Yeah, it
happened a couple of times over YouTube.
It's not funny. It's not funny. It
happened a couple of times
like with Truman and that. Yeah.
I [ __ ] woke up to a load of old bill once, mate.
I swear to God, it was 5:00 p.m. I
remember it was 5:00 p.m., bro.
I woke up
to a load of old bill.
Been in a police cell for [ __ ] 21 hours, lad.
21 hours. I was in the police cell for
21 [ __ ] hours.
Yeah. It's happened a few times.
So, was that on the same website you can
watch the side men on?
We usually ending up in a police cell.
Well, the last time with nonslegs, I was
there for 48 hours. [laughter]
Yeah, I was there for 48 hours cuz I had
to go I went to court. I stayed in
24 hours. Yeah.
And I had to go court. It was like 48
hours. Then the court let me go. Oh. And
I hid my phone somewhere and I I went
back for it.
That skinned virgin has caused a lot of
trouble, mate. He just needs to get
laid. He needs to lose it. Stop being a virgin.
Yeah. You weren't lost in a police cell,
Grezy. You'd have a panic attack.
I didn't I was right the last time I was
in the police cell. I don't think I got
anxiety. Did I? No,
I don't think I did.
But I thought I was going to go prison.
That's scary. It g I thought I was going
to [ __ ] go in prison. Grievy. Prison over YouTube. >> [laughter] >> Wait.
Wait, hold on. Before I say it a third
time, I want to show you something. Right.
Right. I said prison over YouTube.
Right. Hold on. But look, hold on.
Where's the remote?
Oh, where's that [ __ ] in the remote gone?
Where's that [ __ ] in the remote?
Where's the remote gone?
Oh, here it is.
Look, I want to show you what I'm
watching on YouTube. [laughter] >> What?
That's why torch anyway
if you don't win the gold screen weapons on [clears throat] weapons. Dragon By.
What site is this? [laughter]
Marty's life got ruined over this site.
What website is this?
Yeah, but Monty's Monty's kids got took
took off him over this website. Looking [laughter]
this isn't YouTube. This isn't YouTube, is it? No. Oh, [laughter]
>> I crazy.
Look, I'm watching Alf.
He's my favorite.
>> What are you doing, you [ __ ] are you doing? [laughter]
>> [ __ ] are you doing?
>> Excuse me. You [ __ ] up big
time for kids. I'll tell you. If I can
tell you again, I'll [ __ ]
>> What website is this? Seriously,
huh? It's like daily. [laughter]
It's Daily Motion, isn't it? [laughter]
I'm going to watch some rainbow.
I'm safe on this side of YouTube, aren't I? Grezy. [laughter]
Bungle the bear. Oh, he just come up straight away. [laughter] crazy. Where's F?
One second before
your just clean bathroom smells great
until the next rush. Use the green
bathroom to activate. No batteries or
electricity needed. The breeze bathroom
is a unique little diffuser that
constantly fights odressions for up to
15 days. Enjoy just clean fresh.
The green's bathroom.
You never know in full ste. [laughter]
>> This is the bit that makes me laugh.
Is this the same website Monty's on? [laughter]
>> This is what Timmy Elg is on here. [laughter]
Oh, let's have a look. [laughter]
Yeah. One second, Monty man. Yeah. Yeah. Look.
Yeah, they are.
>> Very weird. Weird. Yeah.
So what can you start >> [laughter] >> All >> set >> foreign.
You want to have a dream? Have a drink.
Turn the camera. Turn the camera. Don't worry.
>> All on all on the same website, Ruby.
All on the same website. But you know
what's so mad? If it wasn't for me,
right? If it wasn't for me,
if it wasn't for me, um, he wouldn't be
he wouldn't be on here.
He wouldn't be on here if it wasn't for
me. That's mad, is it? If you think
about it, creepy. Like, if it wasn't for
me, he wouldn't be on here.
Turn the camera on, lad. Yeah.
Well, that woman I was speaking to in
France, the one that said anyone will
do, blocked me, Grezy. She blocked me
cuz I told her to get uh I told that
other woman to get raped. She said that
was too far. Oh, but it's okay for them
to do what they [ __ ] do, Grevy, isn't it?
It's okay for them to do what they [ __ ] do. [ __ ] [ __ ]
My name is Jamie Hag. Remember [clears throat]
Greavvesy when the Harry Potter class
when they were still kids
talking about what they're going to do
with their first paycheck?
That was the same website Grezy probably.
I'm going to send that to her body. [laughter]
Did you [clears throat] report Virgin
Boy by to the benefit Steven Alward?
Did you report virgin by?
You reported virgin boy by didn't you?
You reported that skin virgin, didn't you? Lovely.
You reported that skin virgin. Did you?
That skin virgin [ __ ]
You've got anxiety in it. We
What have you got tick squeezy?
Seems anyone will do.
Is she right? That woman from France.
Seems anyone will do. [laughter]
Seems anyone will do. You don't know
anything about me. All you know is that
I've got a vagina.
One of them said Greasy. You only know
that I've got a vagina.
That's what she said. That's funny, is
it? What the [ __ ] are SPS ticks? What's that?
Oh, that one. Oh, bless you then if
you've got sweaty back syndrome. Oh, bless. [screaming] Bless you.
Where's my mommy gone? Graves.
She don't want to know you, Grezy. She
don't want to know you.
All right with you, boss.
Yeah, there's not going to be any newies anymore.
Now, all women are evil. I have to stay
away from them. They're bad people in
general, Grezy. The complete opposite.
I'm staying away from them. They're evil.
They're evil people.
I like sleeping. Grievy. I'm happy with
just chilling and sleeping.
Bless Grezy. He's older than me and barely traveled.
Oh, bless you then, Grezy. Well, bless.
You never been to London then, Grezy. Huh?
Me and Grezy should meet up.
Yeah, me and Greavvesy should meet up.
Why don't you like USA? Is he greava? Izzy,
what's your problem with her? Yep.
It's quite cruel.
Yeah, that's quite low, isn't it?
Yeah, that's quite low.
You've been stalking me for two two and
a half years, she said. Grievy. The good
old stalking card. Eh, that's a
narcissist's favorite word, stalking.
It's a narcissist's favorite word.
Yeah, it's a narcissist's favorite word.
I was a [ __ ] mad [ __ ] weren't I, Grezy?
You need to do something about these
[ __ ] [ __ ] women.
Bless you, Grezy.
When was you conceived, Greavvesy?
I was conceived on Valentine's Day.
They were mocking you. They were
laughing at you.
And them [ __ ] were laughing at us.
Them Yankee [ __ ] were laughing at us.
And I just couldn't let it lie. I had to
cause [ __ ] million, didn't I, mate? Oh, Grezy. >> [snorts]
>> What I do? I'm going n nights in a bit.
You know what that means, Greavves? I'm
going n nights.
Going to watch some GTA San Andrea videos
and then go to sleep. Yeah,
[ __ ] sick of these [ __ ] women,
Bob. They need to pay these women. Gosh,
I'm in my little nesticles. Yep. Isabella. Huh?
No, I told her I was a landlord
and she said, "Oh, a little landlord."
And I said, "Yeah."
Said, "Oh, you're a little landlord.
I said, "Yep,
I want to beat her up.
She's a meanie." Is that right, Grezy? Yep.
I shouldn't have said that. Should have I grievy?
I wonder what she would have said if I
told her I hated women.
What do you think, Grezy?
If I told her that I hated women,
what do you think would have happened?
I should have mentioned that. It
What do you think would have happened if
I mentioned that Grezy?
What do you think she would have said,
Steven Howard, if I told her I hated women? Huh?
I should have mentioned it.
What do you think would have happened? We
should have told her I hated women.
Where is he?
>> Yeah, I should have told her after then.
Yeah, I should have told her after.
What do you think would have she would
have said if I told her Greavves I hate
women and stuff?
Do you reckon she still would have
[ __ ] me? Grezy,
do you reckon she still would have
[ __ ] me? Grey,
what do you reckon she would have said? Answer
me, Grezy. Don't be so rude.
What do you think she would have said?
What do you think she would have said, Greasy?
Crazy to reckon she would have still
kissed me if I told her I hated women.
Do you think so? Graves there.
I want to hurt her, Grezy. Is that normal?
I really want to hurt her. I want to
beat her up. Greavvesy.
I want to beat her up. Greasy.
Is that normal?
No, I Why is it not normal? She's evil,
though. Grieves. Why is it not normal? She's evil.
One sec, lad. Yeah, man.
No, I just want to hit her, Greasy, cuz she's naughty.
I'll punch her in her boobs, Greasy.
I'll punch her in her boobies.
Greasy. How's that one?
She's very, very naughty. That one. Yeah.
Well, it will never change, will it?
Is Antman right Grezy? He's like, "Well,
it would never change, will it?" I
showed him some approaching videos.
He said, "And you'll never change."
He said, "I'll never change." We
will never change, will it?
I can't believe she took my milk away
from me, Grezy. I could deal with them.
I could deal with them. I could do with
them boobs or like cornflakes. Greasy. I
So I could save money on the milk, you know.
you know, using the boob for like milk
for the cornflakes,
you know, cuz I like cornflakes.
Would you have would you like some of
her milk as well, Grezy? Would
you like some of her milk?
It's okay. I'll just uh wait.
You wait until it's been made? Yes.
I'll just wait until it's been made.
Oh, that was funny [ __ ] bro. I was
watching that last
winter. Last winter. Yeah, I will just
wait until it's been made.
Yeah, mom is sleeping in that bed in
Albert in Stratford.
Yeah. Do you reckon she could feed baby Peter? Grezy,
why were her boobies so big, Grezy?
Yeah, big boobies.
Why have they all got that westernized
look, Grezy? These women, they're like
NPCs, aren't they, bro?
They're NPCs. I think it's too much
watching Tik Tok in it, Grezy. I think
it's the [ __ ] they watch.
Yeah, they've all got that nasty
westernized stare in it.
They're NPCs. Too much Tik Tok in it.
It's cuz they all watch the same [ __ ] on
Tik Tok and that, isn't it?
To be honest, it doesn't seem
I'm watching these approaching videos,
Grezy, and this guy when he approaches
women, they do seem more open in America
than they do here.
even though they're all the same [ __ ]
and that. Like if you you go around London,
you go around London trying to speak to
someone like that
and they uh they will never be open like that. Bro,
what USA is his boobs are full of milk. Grezy,
I don't think any milk come out.
[snorts] I don't think any milk come out
when I was sucking them. Greavves.
Maybe they did. Yeah.
She pulled up the Calvin Klein top and
they come dangling out. Greavvesy. Grezy,
the slower the better, Grezy. The slower the better.
Is that right, Grezy?
He's found He's got a new woman, doesn't he?
He's got a new woman. Yep.
Still goes to the gym and stuff.
I was innocent in that situation in it. Yeah. Nope.
We both got abandoned.
I don't know why she I don't know why
she adopted me if she didn't want me. Graves. E.
There's no way you're still messaging
me. I've explained this isn't going to
work and I really need you to accept that.
I said, "No, I'm not accepting it.
You're my mama." Grezy,
I've been so nice about this, she said. Grievy. Yeah, really.
She's been so nice about
You haven't been nice. You're a meanie.
You dumped me, mama. Yep.
I think you like her Greavesy USA is he
Yeah, I think you like her.
No, I'm here, bro.
No, I'm here.
>> Yeah, but you like YouTube, Greavvesy.
Yeah, you like YouTube though.
Oh, bless you.
Thank you, [ __ ]
So, you're really saying, Greaves, you
don't care about women, though?
I think you do care about women, Grezy.
I think you're obsessed with women. [gasps]
Yeah, they get good money though. They
get good money.
You can't deny she's attractive.
Cheryl Cole's so attractive, isn't she? Um
um Grey, she's so good-looking.
So good looking.
She's so good looking, isn't she?
Oh, the guy that made Family Guy is born
the day before me.
Day before me he's born. Oh, that's interesting.
I didn't know that. Mhm.
They got a lot, bro. Yeah.
Oh, Virgin boy is mad.
I'm not having a drink next.
Never, bro. Never. Not interested.
Yeah. Never lad.
Yeah, too many bad experiences with women, Bob.
Too many bad experiences with women. Nope. Not that. Yeah.
Anyways, I'm going. Yeah. See you later.