They reported my mom's Instagram. I
think it's been bad.
>> These women are such losers.
They are [ __ ] losers.
You got like
170 something [ __ ] days to appeal it.
These women are such cowardly little losers.
[ __ ] absolute losers, lad.
Yeah. Must have reported my mom's uh
Instagram cuz I was giving them a load
of [ __ ] [ __ ] losers.
They act [ __ ] and [ __ ] to people
that they think are simp white knights.
And then as soon as anyone defends
themselves, they report them. [ __ ]
hell. Women are such losers. It's unbelievable. Losers.
That's what they are. Losers.
It's got muted.
Hope he didn't get banned.
on Facebook right now, lad.
No [ __ ] on Facebook, mate.
An arrogant son. Hope her [ __ ]
Instagram ain't perma banned.
really bit a
that's not good. Wow.
These women are losers. Absolute losers.
They're such losers. These women, I
swear to God, bro, they really, really are.
[ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah, I gave them [ __ ] on
my mom's Instagram and they [ __ ]
reported it. Losers. Not so big then,
are they? When someone stands up to them, losers.
Women are such [ __ ] losers. The
amount of men, right, I see on Reddit
get called losers. These women are
My account didn't get banned.
They didn't ban my [ __ ] account.
Losers. They can give it, but they can't
take it. [ __ ] losers. I get little
rape victim [ __ ]
See, on [ __ ] YouTube, we've actually
got somewhat freedom of speech.
Yeah, these women are such losers. It's
bad enough that they get the white
knights to fight their battles, verbal
battles, then they have to report people. [laughter]
They are [ __ ] losers.
[ __ ] losers. Hope they will get
raped. All of them.
That's coming from my mouth, [ __ ]
No one else is.
They're [ __ ] losers.
so they can give it but they can't take
it. That's what I mean with these little rape victims, you know.
It has to be, Mom, because I put the
right email on it. Well, you're not on
the right email, bro. There's no way
you're on the right email. This is not
I'm going to message all their friends
on Facebook and [ __ ] with them now.
They got your Instagram deactivated.
Instagrams don't normally get deactivated.
They're [ __ ] such losers. This is
narcissism at its finest. So they give
it, right? Right. So they give the [ __ ]
right? And then can't give the [ __ ] back
and then get these little white knights
to fight their battles because they're
[ __ ] losers. And then as soon as you
say something to them, they're getting
people's Instagrams banned. My
Instagram's never been banned. So I
don't know why they've why they've um
banned yours. Why they've deactivated yours?
Does it come up? No.
No. That's mad. Mine's never been deact
They never deactivate mine.
>> Yeah. I don't know. Yeah, it's [ __ ]
You're [ __ ] up, is it? >> Yeah.
Grievy would love this. This is
narcissism at its finest,
isn't it? That is narcissism at its
finest. I'm going to [ __ ] with all of
their family now. I'm going to message
their family and [ __ ] with them over Facebook.
Do [ __ ] Yeah, that's what I'm gonna
[ __ ] do. [snorts] Yeah, I don't know.
Just Just leave it. Just leave it.
Mad, is it?
And you want to Yeah, bro. So, you want
to talk about um narcissism? Grieved me.
They literally got my mom's Instagram
banned cuz I went on their account and
gave them [ __ ] They can give it, but
they can't take it.
They can give it, but they can't take
it. Oh, the narcissism. Isn't it greasy?
Oh, the narcissism is lush, isn't it?
They can give it, but they can't take it. Huh?
Do you agree or do you agree?
See, my Instagram's never been banned.
And they're not they've never deactivated mine.
These women are such cowards. They're
not so big when they meet their match,
are they, mate? They'll do anything to
stop somebody having a voice, you know?
They're such [ __ ] losers. No wonder
men rape them. I can see why they get
raped now. [sighs and gasps]
Yeah, I can see why men rape them. They
[snorts] deserve it. Dirty little stinky [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. I can see why they get raped. They
deserve it. [ __ ] Give them a good
raping in their [ __ ]
Yeah. They give them a good raping in
their [ __ ] That'll teach their fragile ego.
Yeah. When they get a raping in their little [ __ ]
That would that will teach you, mate.
When they get raped, it's lovely. Cuz
that's the only time their egos drop.
The only time they stop thinking they're
better than someone is when they get raped. Literally.
Yeah. They run a mile. Yeah. [laughter]
You little rape victim.
And what can they do? They can't get the
police involved because they live in a
different country. So what can they
really really do? This is the joys about
it as well, Grezy, is when they don't
live in your country, they can't get the
police involved because they live in a
different country. I mean, they can call
the police, but the police are not going
to do anything.
Yeah. They do anything to when they get
a taste of their own medicine, they get
the white knights to defend them. Um,
and then when that doesn't work, they
will literally like report you to
Instagram. I don't know how her account
got deactivated. M I thought she was
going to get muted cuz my account's
never been deactivated. I just get muted
for like seven days.
So yeah, that's mad. Then they ban
people. [ __ ] losers. Absolute losers.
I wouldn't mind if they could actually
give it back. Give back what they give,
but they can't. They're losers. Women
are losers, bro. Proper losers.
Yeah, proper losers, lad.
if they could give back what they if
they could get give you back like if
they can give back and it's like even if
you if you're like somebody that just
messages them and you agree with them if
you don't agree with them they block you
straight away. It was the same with USA
Izzy and my friend when he wasn't buying
her [ __ ] he then uh she then blocked him
because obviously she was making up
stories. So unless you're an orbiter, uh
they won't uh they won't talk to you.
They'll block you. So you have to be an
orbiter. They're losers. These women are
losers, bro. I'm surprised not many
people on Reddit know it.
And you can see the cuntiness in their
eyes as well. Look at this [ __ ] [ __ ]
I'll put her all over [ __ ] I message
her whole family. [ __ ] with her, you
know. And guess what? You're going to be
called a stalker, Boozy. You're going to
be called a stalker. Yeah,
[ __ ] losers. Why are they such losers and cowards? [snorts] Now,
another thing, Greavvesy, I've got a
bone to pick with you. That woman that
said that she's 30 and she's living in
London and she can't find anyone. I
thought, okay, all women are the [ __ ]
All women are the same. All women are
[ __ ] But let's give them one last
chance to to to take what this person is
saying is the truth. So they live in
London. They can't find anyone. Um t
that's what they're going with, right?
So I when I messaged them yesterday
saying, "Oh, I live in London. I'm a
similar age to you. Let's go, you know,
let's go out. We'll have to cook them
for a meal." Um not um drinking because
I don't really drink anymore. But they didn't reply.
But they said they're struggling to find
people grievy. They're saying that
they're struggling to find someone um
that's single. And I thought, oh, me
being me, let's let's test this theory
out, right? But they didn't reply.
Now, you could say they're busy, right?
And you know, or they don't use Reddit
anymore because to be fair, their last
post was a month ago. But this morning,
um I made a new account pretending to be
a woman and I've messaged her saying,
"Oh, I'm a woman and um you know, I'm
similar age to you and I can't find
anyone now." And this person better not
[ __ ] reply to this cuz if they reply
to this Grezy, I'll be going up the
[ __ ] wall, mate. Because you said
that you couldn't find anyone.
And you opening my messages when you
think I'm a [ __ ] woman, you know? So,
is it that you can't find anyone really
or you just mocking the the average guy,
you know? That's that's that's that. Only
time will tell. She better not open that
bloody message. And she thinks I'm a
[ __ ] woman cuz you said that you
can't find someone.
My new favorite word now is bloody.
Grezy. Bloody. They're not bloody
interested. I bloody can't find someone.
Bloody. I've still got some pizza left,
Grevy. I'm going to heat up in a minute.
Yep. Told you it wasn't going to waste.
And I'm going for a lovely meal today as well. So yeah,
bloody. That's my new word, my favorite
new word now. Bloody.
See, the thing is, Grey is most of the
most of the people that are narcissists are women.
You know, all most of the narcissists I
come across were women, but they're not
all the same because you don't know all
women. Grezy, you don't know all women.
You don't know all women.
Don't forget, Grezy, you've got to meet
nine billion women to have an opinion.
Virgin boy logic. You need to meet every
single woman in the world, even though
all the ones you have met have been
[ __ ] to have an opinion.
Isn't that right? Yeah.
Bro, I swear to God. Yeah. If if one of
these women lived like in in England, I'
I'd pull up posters of them. I would
really really pull up posters of them,
bro. Like that's that's basically what I
would do. I'd pull up posters of them
around their uni or around their
workplace. That's how I'd [ __ ] with
them. I'd pull up posters me. Yeah.
Yeah. And let's see who could go without
calling the police first cuz I bet you I
I would win. You know, I would win.
put up posters that they have a
pedophile on that get their head smashed in. Yeah.
Uh, Adman contradicted himself.
Um, Greezy, now I think he contradicted
himself. Can you hear hear me out and um
tell me uh I if if that is true. Right.
So, I'm saying he contradicted himself.
Okay. I explain it to you. Yeah. And
tell me if I'm right or tell me if I'm
wrong. Does that sound fair? So he
messages me saying, "Oh, it doesn't, you
know, some women are married. They just
don't like me and you. Women get to
choose their guy the guys they go for,
but they don't like me and you." And I
was like, "There is no me and you." And
also you is it is it 80 90% of the
population or is it just me and you? You
might want to make your mind up because
one minute it's me and you, then it's 80
90%. Then he says, "Oh, well, it doesn't
matter if it's 80 90%.
You're not getting laid. You are not
getting laid and it it doesn't matter.
It probably is 80 90%, but why does that
matter? It's it's you that's not getting
laid." I was like, "Huh? How many times
have you compared yourself to other
people?" Oh, how does he do it? How does
this guy do it? Um, you know, other guys
do it. You know, how many times have you
heard that? But me, when I say it, 80,
90% of [ __ ] people, it doesn't matter
whether they do or don't because it's not you.
I mean, he contradicted himself then,
didn't he, mate? He really, really did.
Because I've, that's what I've been
saying to you all along, that it's not
going to change our situation, mine and
yours, whether a fat guy does it, a
good-looking guy does it. That's what
I've been saying to you the whole time.
You know, you were still in England.
Now, you basically contradicted
yourself, didn't you?
Am I right, Greavvesy, or am I am I
right or am I right? Cuz he's saying
that it doesn't matter about other
people. And basically, in other words,
he's saying, don't compare yourself. It
doesn't matter if they're getting laid
or they're not getting laid. But you
constantly compare yourself to other people.
You constantly constantly constantly do it.
Oh, other guys do it. There's some lucky
[ __ ] out there.
How many times did did we used to hear that Grezy?
So yeah, he contradicted himself. Well done.
I feel sorry for Laney now. She doesn't [ __ ]
she doesn't have a Instagram.
Okay. Basically, okay, I I'll explain it
to you. Okay. So
he was saying right that 80 90% of
people he said that me and you I said oh
these women lie about getting married.
He says yeah it's easy for women um but
they don't like me and you. And I said
there is no me and you. I gave up. And I
said at the end of the day what about
all the 80 90% of people that you say
that they don't like? You said that they
don't like 80 90% of people. And then he
was like, "Oh yeah, but 90% of people
probably don't get laid, but it doesn't
matter about them because it's not going
to change your situation." And I was
like, "Uh, but you continuously compare
yourself to other people. You always
say, "Oh, other guys do it. How does
this guy do it? How does that guy do it?
There's some lucky bastards out there."
And I was saying to you the same thing
that comparing yourself is not going to
change your situation. So now, and now
you're saying the same basically saying
the same thing back to me.
So you're contradicting yourself.
So his IQ is so low that he doesn't even
realize he's contradicting himself
cuz I have been saying that to you the
whole time. It's not going to change
your situation, how other people do it.
But now you're telling me not to compare
myself to them. Madness.
Yeah. He contradicted himself.
Do you not find it wi would you agree
Greavvesy that most that the that it's
women that are the or more narcissist
men? Would you agree on that that they
they are the they are more narcissist than men?
For me personally,
I would say so.
You know, why are you telling people to
turn gay, bro? Why does people keep
talking about people being gay? No one's
gay. No one's turning gay. You need to grow up.
You need to grow up with that gay [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] so pathetic and childish. You know,
turn gay. Turn gay. Turn gay. It's not
even funny, bro. It's childish. Very,
very, very, very childish.
But more women are narcissists than men.
They are. They generally generally generally are.
No, they'll never change. They're [ __ ]
They I'm trying to think if I've ever
met a good one. Nah, never.
Yeah, but we don't like men. We're not
sexually attracted to men. So, how about
we just turn asexual?
Why would we turn gay?
You know, I hope you tell women that
moan about men to turn lesbian.
I hope you tell them to turn lesbian.
Uh, that boy. No,
I hope you [ __ ] tell them to [ __ ]
turn uh turn uh lesbian when they
[ __ ] [ __ ] emone about [ __ ] men.
You wouldn't do that, would you? Double
standards. Am I right or am I right, Grezy?
Am I right or am I right? I think the
most annoying thing about dating is the
double standards. You know, I generally
think it's the double standards. I think
that's a big part of it, isn't it,
Greasy? The double standards. I think if
there was no double standards,
um I think it'd be all right, you know.
Do you agree that I think that's a big
thing, the double standards? If there
was actually equality, then it wouldn't
be too bad, you know?
Yeah, it wouldn't be as bad. No.
Do you think Ant-Man contradicted
himself? What he said to me?
That boy. I think I'm right by saying
that he contradicted himself. I said
you're basically you you've actually
contradicted yourself now.
Yeah, you've actually contradicted
yourself now and you don't even realize
because you're telling me to not worry
about 80 90% of the population, but you
constantly compare yourself to other people. So,
or or he could be a hypocrite. It's one
of the two. He's either contradicted
himself or No, it's more No, he
contradicted himself. Yeah, contradicts
Definitely. But it could be either
hypocrite or contradict, but he
definitely one of them. So
there's no me and you, lad. There's no
me and you. I said he needs to make up
his [ __ ] mind as well.
I don't even know why I'm talking I
don't even know why I'm talking to him
about it. I mean, he left to get away
from this [ __ ] It must be so so
annoying when he's got some guy
messaging him about women here. I mean,
he he left to get away from it. Poor [ __ ]
You know, the poor [ __ ]
um left to get away from it. Do you know
what I mean, Grezy?
But he does still like hearing it
sometimes, you know? Yeah.
They're not all the same because you
don't know all women
[ __ ] on Facebook now Yeah.
Is that how hearts beat? [ __ ] hell, man.
Give me a bit of anxiety. That is
They're not all the same. Is that how women
do I have to beat them?
But yeah, that Jamie Thompson is is a
proper proper stalker. He's obsessed
with me. His life is dedicated to me,
bro. Stalking me. He's worse than that
Red Star coward.
Yeah, he takes the absolute [ __ ]
biscuit, bro. He ain't got no wife. He
ain't got no life. He ain't got no
money. What he does on Reddit? No way.
He poses pretending to be women. Nah,
that guy ain't got nothing in his life.
Believe you me, buddy. Yeah.
Yeah. Right. I'm going to heat this
pizza up in a minute anyways. All right. >> [cough] >> Right.
Yeah. And and people also play dumb when
you show evidence of what women's done
and stuff. They all they all they also
play dumb greasy.
They like dismiss your struggles and
remember things that suit themselves.
Uh if that makes sense. Sure it [ __ ]
does make sense. It m
suit them these people.
Don't shoot them.
I'm making this pizza up. And I'm no,
we know you like that, Grecy. Oh, we
know you like that. >> [laughter]
>> Get some food today.
Where's the pizza?
Chuck it out. job, mate. Oh,
that's looking quite tasty. She t
you know bedet you're going to sit there
on a [ __ ] £1,000 a month and your
shitty out of London council beds it and
try and tell me your women are to
[ __ ] say you're having a [ __ ] lot.
You're going to sit there in your little
out of London
plant shitty beds sit on a,000 pound a
month and try and [ __ ] tell me
they're not all the same. Are you ski
virgin [ __ ] Yeah,
you saying yes. £13,000 to save in three
years is absolutely [ __ ] scing show it now.
Talking of skin, you got 200 pound jeans
covered today, mate.
Something that you can't afford cuz it's
out of your skin bur budget. Right.
Can't show it now. Can you virgin boy?
Cuz you ain't got it.
My accent is a lot [ __ ] stronger, man.
My accent is a lot stronger. at some
[ __ ] head versions.
You know that's what the [ __ ] dad
said they had to [ __ ] read it out.
You know, you [ __ ] skip bastard. You
never had [ __ ] 200 pound jeans cuz
you simply can't afford it.
I'm a [ __ ] mad [ __ ] All right, I
think we can all agree I'm a mad [ __ ]
Apart from a virgin [ __ ] like that
virgin skin virgin but you know right coming
I won't do that again. I didn't know
they could just deactivate you like that.
>> Did you like the cross? Yeah.
What do you think of it? [ __ ]
[ __ ] [ __ ] James. Half
the [ __ ] money
going to [ __ ] change.
I'm going to look up the [ __ ] percentage out there
and that's been burn [ __ ] virgin.
You know what man?
Sorry mate. You know there
a certain person doesn't have a mom cuz
their mom [ __ ] starve them
and he don't [ __ ] all about it. Little
So you know you know I get like this mate.
You know what I mean?
My mom's never sold me.
Sorry, we're just enjoying some pizza.
I bet your mom never gave you a picture,
did it? Yeah.
Did your mom [ __ ] serve you? Bye-bye, [ __ ] Go away.
You've been taking an L all your life,
you [ __ ] virgin. Get off of YouTube
and get a life.
You've been living an L all your life,
you [ __ ] virgin [ __ ] You
like it when I'm in these moods, don't you, music?
I like when I'm in these lost moods.
And the reason I'm [ __ ] with her is
because she got my mom's Instagram banning
enough to give it,
but you can't take it. Typical woman
narcissist, but they're not all the
same. says the virgin in the bed [ __ ]
with no bed and no money in it because
you can't show me no [ __ ] Bing BL.
But I I can tell you, mate,
you're not going to sit there in that
virgin skitty bed with your [ __ ] rat
looking face with no beard on it and try
and [ __ ] try me
not being all the same [ __ ] virgin.
But here's the thing, Green. It's not
all women, is it? It's not But it's not.
It's not only women that do this, is it,
Grezy? It's not only women that want to
appease cuz they're so much of a loser
that they can't give it back. You know
where I'm getting at with this, don't
you, Greasy? You very much know where
the line is. I mean, yeah, women do it,
but it's not only women that do it. I
can name someone. The skin virgin,
£1,000 a month, no bed, no money.
Couldn't take it anymore. He was so much
of a loser. He had no fight left in him.
The [ __ ] loser. He was so much of a
loser that he had to run to the police
cuz he couldn't take it anymore, could
he, mate? What happened to just sticking
to YouTube, Greasy?
What happened to just sticking to
YouTube? But he was so much of a [ __ ]
loser. He had no fight in him. Him and
that [ __ ] ugly girl with the
disabilities that he had to run to old
Bill, didn't he, son? Cuz he couldn't
take me. You couldn't fake me. You had
to get old Bill involved because he's a [ __ ] loser.
Am I lying? No, I'm not, mate. No, [ __ ] not.
[ __ ] a loser. Guys,
you must realize meet up, don't you?
You want people to meet up in real life, don't you?
You don't want no YouTube people doing
your [ __ ] do you? You like the meetups.
H You like the meetups, don't you?
You think they're very dust.
You don't want [ __ ] just YouTube people [ __ ]
You know what I mean, lad?
You want you like me?
No. One second. I'll be right back. I'm
just finishing this pizza. Two seconds.
You don't like him when old Bill was
cool, do you?
called, do you?
You don't like it when the old bill was
called, do you? Cuz that just ruined
everything. That ruined all the fun. What? Um,
briefly, would you say that? Um, um
[clears throat] would you say that
most of the Reddit mods are white knights?
Would you agree on that one that most of
Reddit mods are white knights? Would
you would you agree on that one then? [clears throat]
You you'd agree on that one, wouldn't you, mate?
Sorry, bro. I'm just like super super
super super [ __ ] hyper, lad. Super hyper.
Little white knights.
What? Be a low life and control a
website all day. That's pretty sad if
you ask me, don't you think, Grezy?
Don't you think it's pretty [ __ ] sad
to sit on a site all day modding it?
That's pretty [ __ ] sad if you ask me. You know,
that's that's a [ __ ] That's [ __ ]
sad if you ask me, lad.
So, anyways, you want me to meet this
Terry and smash his face in Grimsy?
Cuz I will do it, bro. And I will
actually violate the [ __ ] Do you really
want me to go and smash his face in
and show everyone his m face and make an
example out of him?
But saying that, no one would would say
anything anyways, would they? Cuz we all
know what this website's like.
Cuz Grezy, you know, Monty, he says that
people don't go for Virgin Boy because
Virgin Boy goes for me. And if Virgin
Boy don't go for me, people go go for
Virgin Boy. But that's not true though.
If I leave YouTube, only like two people
will go for him. Maybe three. Nah. Nah.
They like nonsense on here, bro. Maybe
two people. No one else would. No. Yeah. >> [snorts]
>> Did I? Yeah.
So, do you reckon this woman will reply
to me when she thinks I'm a woman? Grezy. [snorts] >> [snorts]
>> a narcissist. Skinn Bit
not money in it.
No bed. No money in it. Because I was
giving that woman some [ __ ] That's why
I'm saying they can give it, but they
can't take it. And she blocked me and
her little ugly boyfriend blocked me. So
I went on my mom's Instagram and gave them [ __ ]
I said, "You little [ __ ] rape victim,
cunt." You not so big now, are you?
Happen to hide behind simps, you [ __ ] loser.
Yeah. So they can give it, but they
can't take it. These women. They can
give, but they can't take. At least men
are not [ __ ] cowards like them. Women
are cowards and they're losers.
Yeah. Yeah. And I messaged her on
Facebook as well uh not so long ago. I
said, "You dirty little South American
brownkinned little [ __ ] You and your
ugly [ __ ] boyfriend. He needs to rape
you and shove his dick down your [ __ ]
throat. You little rape victim." Yeah.
I'm not having that [ __ ] bro. Yeah. I'm
the last person to [ __ ] around with,
bro. Even if it's online.
Another one that's met their match and plays victim.
We've seen it and heard it all before,
haven't we, Grezy?
>> They're not so big, are they? When they
meet their match,
they hide behind simps and white knights.
They are narcissists.
But all women aren't the same because
you haven't met all women. All women
aren't the same. They're not all like that.
>> Really, bro? [ __ ] off, man.
>> Tell Co is attractive. You can't DENY
SHE'S ATTRACTIVE OR YOU'RE GAY. [ __ ]
virgin. [ __ ] skin virgin.
[ __ ] skint virgin [ __ ]
They give it, but they can't take it.
Isn't that right?
If I knew where this woman lived, I'd
smack her in the face. Bro, you know
when I used to like deal with these
women's toxic [ __ ] Yeah. The ones that
live here. When I'd get the numbers and
then they'd reply to negativity. If I
knew where one of them lived, I would
badger them up, bro. In front of any
man. And and I'd want to do it in front
of a man. I would only do it in front of
a man. I would only do it in front of a
man. Um because to show you that no man
is going to go anywhere near me when I'm
doing what I'm doing, bro. But again,
this is what I mean. It's all toxic.
This is what I meant by dating and women
is toxic. This is why I walked away from
it and I didn't want anything to do with
it anymore because of this [ __ ] It's
toxic, you know.
It's toxic. It's negative,
[sighs and gasps] you know. So, yeah.
Toxic and negative. So yeah,
I hate women. That boy. I [ __ ] hate
women. Laney knows the score as well.
Laney knows the score. Yeah,
I'm going to message some of her family
members now. Actually,
why not? You got a simp to message me to
fight your battles, so I'll message your family. Simple.
Where is it?
Going to message some of her family
members now. Yeah. One sec.
You know, you want to be a coward. I can
do it right back at you.
Lovely. One second.
Yeah, I'll be a [ __ ] to you.
Yeah, here we go. Message some of our family members.
I mean, why not? [ __ ] not.
Got off some family members there.
Here we go. I'll just go for the family.
Me? I'm a crazy bastard. You got my
mom's [ __ ] Instagram blocked. You
I'm going to message her family telling
her that she's a lesbian. She's a dirty
lesbian. Um because uh she put it on
Reddit that uh she hasn't come out yet.
So, I'm going to tell all her family
members that your daughter is a dirty
dirty lesbian. Hopefully, she gets a
[ __ ] smack around her face that'll
teach her to be a [ __ ] [ __ ] all her
life. Yeah. One second.
Yeah, I'm going to tell.
Yeah, there we go.
That's her mom. I think.
[ __ ] it. I love getting these [ __ ]
back, bro. I love it, mate. I love it. [snorts] One second.
Any more family members?
play with fire you get burnt.
Oh, don't message the family. does what
I [ __ ] will
miss her family.
You want to be a [ __ ] do you? Let's see
how much you're laughing after this, you little [ __ ] Yep. What's there?
These women need to be told about themselves, lad.
These scumbag women.
Same old uh USA is he uh treatment a
was havoc in people's life will cause
havoc in their life. Simple.
And that's that. That's that message
some of their friends One second. Good job.
That's a big issue now. [ __ ] coward
and an iron bastard. Yeah. >> [snorts] >> Oh,
must have tried to get my [ __ ]
Instagram banned as Huh?
I don't care what you want. I want to
spam your page, you [ __ ] [ __ ] One sec. [ __ ] scumbag. Yeah, mom.
Yeah, that's what these people need,
bro. They need a [ __ ] ego check. They
need an ego reality. Uh, Greasy,
what they need, mate. like that.
Yeah, they need telling about
themselves. These women bar for real. Yeah, man. Yeah.
Yeah, them them mods need that power.
Without that power, they're nothing,
Grezy. And I mean nothing.
They ban people to feel powerful.
They're nothing. [ __ ] nothing.
Without that power,
don't right agree with you. Nothing.
Nothing. [ __ ] nothing without that
power. And I mean nothing, you know.
These women can't win against me. your
I'm a [ __ ] nutcase. I am