Ah, I reckon they're going to come about
midday to be honest, mate. I'm waiting
for these lust jeans to show the virgin
who can't afford it cuz he [ __ ] skip mate. [laughter]
Give me more thumbs up than [ __ ]
free, please, mate. You know, this is an expensive video.
You know, it's an expense. I mean,
should I buy trainers today? I might as well.
I could do if I want to because I'm not
skinned like a certain person. What do
you think? Go JD. Buy some trainers.
Should I buy some trainers? Should I not
buy? I mean, I'm not skint like a certain virgin.
You know, I'm not skint like him. You
know, in my little bed sit with no bed,
nobody in it. See, I can be quite
[ __ ] spiteful. I can, mate. You know
what I'm like. You know what I'm [ __ ]
like, mate. Could buy some traders.
What do you think? Maybe some Viva
Maxes. These jeans are coming, mate. And
they're going to be absolutely lush when
they do come.
As long as you just virgin can't afford
them. Get out of his price range.
Come on. We know that you're going to
cover midday [ __ ] [ __ ] But come on, mate.
I can't wait to show what a lot of
people can't afford
because let let's face it, mate. Right.
Let's let let let's put it right here,
mate. They can smell you a [ __ ] mile
off, mate. Just like if you was to walk
into [ __ ] Waxies, they see some skint
little lanky virgin smell of [ __ ]
wearing charity shop clothes. No wonder
he's still a [ __ ] virgin. If I was
him, I would have I would have went to
the disableds a long time ago, mate. If
I if I had to wear charity shop ugly
skin clothes, I would have, mate.
Yeah, you are autistic. Stop talking
about yourself. I'm going to be adding
you into this video as well. These 200
pound jeans. Oh, I've had more birds
than you, mate. I could I could put
videos up of me kissing me going on
dates. I've had plenty more birds than
you, you little nerd. That's why I don't
need to white night like you. You
[ __ ] bongo. Anyways, when these jeans come,
um, they're going to be dedicated to
you. The skinn virgin in the out of
London meds, mate. It's going to be it's
going to be dedicated to a few people,
mate. This autistic [ __ ] has had more
women than you. Do I need to put the
videos back up again?
I've had more birds, as you call it, you
cringe [ __ ] than you will ever have.
Birds. Who calls it? Who calls a woman
bird nowadays, mate? That's so 2010. A
bird. I don't think I've ever referred
to a woman as a bird in my life. But
again, I'm not a virgin like you and a
Kwanka. So probably that's why I would
do that, mate.
I know the noise. Sorry. I'm keeping it
down a little bit, mate. I'm keeping it
down a little bit. Who refers to a woman
as a bird in almost 2025? How cringe.
How [ __ ] cringe is that, mate? Very
very very very cringe.
That is very very very [ __ ] cringe,
mate. But after all, you're probably
still a virgin living in your mommy's
basement. So don't blame you, son. Don't blame you.
Just playing a bit of Franklin is
chilling, you know. Yeah.
Take note, mate. If you got if you buy
these jeans, you got a good chance of
losing your virginity.
Good chance of popping it.
Mate, we all know about the people that
get women and don't get women. Well, at
least had women. You people have to
white night women because you don't get
women. And because you're so socially
awkward, you think that's the way to get
women. You know, even when you're shown
black and white evidence of them being
[ __ ] and doing what they do in your
little socially awkward, anxiety ridden
head, you think by defending them it's
going to get you laid. But let me tell
you something now, sunshine. It's
[ __ ] not. You're always going to be a
virgin just like the Kent wanker living
in the out of London bedsit. And also
let me tell you something now.
Roford classes as London. They class
Roford as London. Kent not London.
Roford classes as London. I mean I' I'd
pretty much class [ __ ]
you know these places had London even if
they weren't classed as London. But Kent
[ __ ] Kent London. Nah, mate. Nah,
nah, mate. Big big difference. It's like
calling Read in London. It's called It's
like calling Maiden Head London. Not
London, mate. Nah, it's not London,
mate. London, mate.
Not London, mate.
There we go.
Sorry, I have I have to keep it my
volume down now cuz I being a bit loud.
But that's how I get when I haven't took
my medication. But I'm not going to stop
when the jeans come, mate. When the trousers come,
he would he might get laid if he sorts
his ugly looks out. His ugly ratatouille
face. [ __ ] ugly bastard and invested
in a nice pair of jeans. He might pop
it. He might lose it. I can see it
happening. I can see him finally getting
laid and no longer being a [ __ ] dead virgin.
That just makes me laugh when I say that
cuz that's the judge repeating it. The
judge actually repeating it. I mean,
everything I say about you is true.
That's why you have to get the old PO in
that involved, isn't it, mate?
See, I could just imagine him walking
into waxies with them ugly clothes and
that ugly face, smelling the [ __ ] like he does.
Okay, I'm I'm really getting into
trouble now, bro. I need to really calm
my voice down.
But I can imagine him just being in
waxies with them ugly clothes with them
ugly virgin legs and ugly virgin shoes
trying to talk to Well, he can't talk to
a woman because he's got anxiety. So he
couldn't even talk to a woman because
he's got too much anxiety. He can't
function these environments. But I don't
know why I associate him with waxies
because he's too skinned to go there
anyways. So I mean know what I'm saying.
[ __ ] knows. [laughter]
I don't know. He's too skinned and he's
socially awkward and he can't function
there because of his disability. So,
I don't know, mate. [ __ ]
Yeah. Thank you, son. But guess what?
You don't even need to make childish
voices. You're already [ __ ]
Like that. That was a good one. Where
are these bloody jeans? Where the [ __ ]
are these bloody jeans? We need to make
a video to the skin virgin.
The skin virgin, mate.
Oh, I'm so tempted to buy a pair of
trailers now. I'm looking forward to
this. Really, really am looking forward
to this, mate.
Now, oh, it wasn't a both teams to
score, though, was it was a both. I'm
going to do a proper guide on to how to
lose your virginity
to this virgin. A proper guide how to
lose it. How to finally get laid and
lose that B card that's been eldering
you for almost 31 years. So it starts
with the jeans, right? It starts
obviously starts with the jeans, doesn't
it? Of course it [ __ ] does. Of course
it [ __ ] starts with the [ __ ]
jeans. Yeah. Would do, wouldn't it?
[ __ ] well would do, wouldn't it, mate? Yeah.
Ah, would start with the jeans though,
would it? In all, in all fairness,
it's just the way it is. Things will
never be the same.
That's just the way it is. See, I'm
singing. I can sing. I can dance. I can
Mom, I think I'm going to have to go to
JD Smalls to get some trainers
to show this virgin how to actually get
laid. Obviously, he can't afford it cuz
he's skinn, but I should I should I give
the proper guide to the skin virgin?
Should I really give a a a proper guide
on how to lose that [ __ ] V card? That
V card, mate? [laughter]
I'm too funny, aren't I, mate? You know,
I should really make money from this
from this uh channel, right? I can
really make money money from this [ __ ] channel.
How to finally finally pop it. How to
finally finally lose it. Cost me an arm
of an egg this has mate as well. But you
know it's fine. It's absolutely okay.
I'm fine with that mate. I'm fine with
it. I really am fine with it mate.
Stop wearing them shitty ugly little
[ __ ] charity shop clothes. You stinky
virgin. You know what I'm saying?
doesn't need to to to be anything.
Um, so yeah, and obviously you're going
to have to you're going to have to win a
football bet as well cuz you're going to
have to use an ecle because that's all
you'll ever be able to get cuz you're
skin virgin. So yeah, that's how that
goes, you know. Yeah, mate.
lady's fist off now
do I could rain it to be honest with you
Joe I'm a bit bit hyper this morning
because I've got my jeans coming today
I'm going for a nice meal and I'm
thinking of showing the virgin a
complete guide on how to lose your vcard
because after all he's never lost it and
he can't afford 200 pound jeans because
it's out of his price range cuz he's
[ __ ] skin sand but I was thinking
because the jeans are Man, now Elaine's
already had a pop at me. I'm being a bit
too loud. I was thinking I might buy a
new pair of trainers today before I go
for the mill, you know, and then and
then do another football bet to show a
complete guide on how to get laid cuz
you need to get laid, son. You need to
lose your virginity. We've already got
these 200 pound trousers coming today,
son. They're two Well, they're not just
a pair of jeans, Joe. They're 200 pound
jeans, you know. Oh, I've got a story to
tell you. Uh, Joseph Ferrar.
Now, do you remember we was talking
about uh women, right, being
narcissists? So, you remember that one
that kept ignoring me on um on Instagram,
but they're 200 pound jeans, Joe. Now,
here's the thing, Joe. Right, let me let
me let me be fair with you. You know how
you talk about life experience and
obviously clothes are not a necessary.
It's not a necess necessity, right? And
I get that, you know, but obviously if
you had if you had loads and loads of
money, you you could you could buy an
expensive thing. You might have a lot of
life experiences in life, Joe. More than
me. I I I I don't doubt that. You're a
lot older than me. But I can tell you
you've never worn a pair of 200lb jeans.
Now, I'm not saying that, you know, you
can't fool them. I'm not saying that.
I'm just saying, have you ever
experienced getting your little legs
into a pair of 200 pound jeans?
I don't think you have, have you, mate?
So, that's a life experience in itself.
I mean, I don't know. I'm just just
throwing that out there. You know, it's
it's it's some sort of life experience if you
know what I'm saying. Pair 200 jeans cuz
cuz my jeans are the price of your
phone, Joseph. Now, I haven't took my
medication today. I'm a bit I'm a bit uh
Oh, yeah. They You can feel the 200
pound. You can feel the 200 pound. You
know, I'm even tempted to buy a new pair
of trainers today. You know, I was going
to do that next month because I've got a
fresh pair, but I don't know. I might do
cuz I'm not skinned, you know. So, they
they they feel a lot different. Joseph
Ferrar, they're a lot different than
next. A lot. I mean, that's like saying,
Joe, does a 1700 phone feel different to
a 200lb phone? And yes, it [ __ ] does,
son. You know, a400 pound phone feels
different than a 200 pound phone.
Yes, it [ __ ] does, man. You know, you
get what you pay for. You know, that's
that's the old saying speaks truth. You
get what you pay for. Maybe that's jeans.
But no, in all seriousness, they do they
do feel a lot better than than 40 jeans.
Your 40 ones, you know.
So yeah, this is why Virgin Boy is still
a virgin. He I can imagine him in waxies
wearing them charity shops, skin ugly
handme-down clothes, stinking as [ __ ]
with his ugly face trying to speak to a
woman. But he but then all of this stuff
is hypothetically talking, isn't it,
Joe? Because A he can't afford waxies, b
he can't afford designer clothes, and c
he's too scared to talk to women. So why
are we talking about [ __ ] waxings?
He can never function in normal [ __ ]
environments. That's why he's with a [ __ ] spacker.
You know what I'm saying? Well, he can't
afford waxies. He wouldn't be able to
talk to any women there cuz he's too
scared. And he can't afford designer
clothes. So it's all hypothetical, isn't
it? Waste the time picking it up. [ __ ] hell.
So Joe, anyways, do you want to hear
what happened with the woman that kept ignoring me?
You know, and and and it's very
expensive, Rexies. It's £8 a pint pretty
much. Now, I don't think some little
skin virgin in the outer London bed sit
with no bed can afford £8 a pipe, mate.
Okay, so do you remember how she kept
This reminded me of USA, Izzy, all over.
So now she kept ignoring me time and
time again, clicking on my message on
purpose to be a [ __ ] And I I kept
sending her my dick. I said, "I'm going
to I'm not going to stop until you block
me." Because my whole the whole purpose was
to get this person to block me. They
live in a different country, right? And
she kept ignoring, ignoring, ignoring. I
was like, I know what I'm going to do.
I'm going to go on her Instagram
pictures and spam her [ __ ] Spam, spam,
spam, spam, spammed, spammed her [ __ ]
Right. I spammed her [ __ ] bro. And then
she finally she said, "I need to go to
therapy." I said, "You're the one that
needs to go to therapy. Listen, you're
the one sat there ignoring people
thinking that you're better than you are
when you're not." Um, and then she
blocked me. But here's the thing, Joe.
She put her that [ __ ] that I done on her
story knowing damn well that somebody
that went on her story is going to
message me. Knowing damn well someone is
going to message me. So you've blocked
somebody and then you put the [ __ ]
they've done on your story knowing that
someone's going to go for me. So you
block me. You don't want to you can't
fight your own battles. So you get
another little white knight to message
me. It was her boyfriend. She didn't
even say she had I told him to [ __ ] off
and suck his dad's dick. I said, "Don't
you dare think about even coming on my
[ __ ] messages." So this is what I
mean with these women, Joe, is that they
give it whether it's like directly give
it or in an arrogant way, but they can't
take it knowing damn well that that
somebody was going to message me. So you
blocked me cuz you don't want me
messaging you. But you knew damn well by
putting that up somebody was going to
message me and then then she blocked.
The irony is then she reported me. Then
I got blocked for typing for [ __ ]
seven days, right? So, I had to reply to
his story and that. And then he blocked
me. Then I went on my mom's phone,
right? I went on my mama's phone. I gave
them both a mad amount of [ __ ] bro. And
then my mom's [ __ ] Instagram got
deactivated. So, they can give it, but
they can't take it. This is what I mean.
They these women can they're all big and
hard. And I said to Damon, I messaged
Damon, by the way. I told him the story.
I was like, "This is your ex all over,
isn't it? This is literally USA all
over." She gives it, but she can't take
it. She gets all of these orbiters to
fight her battles, which is a verbal
battle. So, I mean, you can fight your
own verbal battles. It's mad. It's It's
Do you know what it is with these the
some of these women, Joe? Not all of
them. They're all [ __ ] but some some
of them when I'm referring to this,
they're used to white knights, right,
and simps inflating their ego, right? To
the point where they start thinking that
they're better than people and they're
this and they're that. And when they
talk to you, they assume that you're a
[ __ ] like them, right? And when you
tell them about themselves, they don't
like it. And that's what a lot of these
women need doing. They need telling
about themselves very verbally, you
know, because they think that this is
that's where the ego comes from. It
builds up and up and up and up and up
and up and up and they start thinking
that they're better than people. They
need telling about themselves, bro. Some
of these women, they need telling about them fuckingelves.
seriously knowing damn well that the guy
was going to message me. Someone was
And trust me, it was giving me mood
swings yesterday, Joe. It was giving me
mad mood swings. Ela had to [ __ ] calm
me down for like 2 hours. It was driving
me mad. And and the worst thing about it
was is that they they live in South
America, so there's nothing I could do,
you know? There's nothing I could do. I
said I was about to say to my mom as
well, you're lucky I'm not rich. You're
lucky I'm not a millionaire, mate.
Because anytime someone would piss me
off, I would just end up going to their
country, you know? Like it by luck one
day one of these people will [ __ ]
live in England, bro. Will live in
England, right? And I will get them,
bro. I will get them. Trust me.
So what? What? Why do I need medication?
Greavvesy agrees with me. They are
cowards. They can't fight their own
battles. They have to get white knights
to fight their battles.
You know, she knew that other people was
going to message me. So why have you
blocked me to get other people to
message me? You loser. You [ __ ]
loser. I said to her boyfriend, "I'll
slap her up in front of you and I'll
slap you up in front of her." How's that
one? Is that fair?
You know, these women are [ __ ]
They need telling about themselves, bro.
They definitely need telling about
themsel. Even Grey agrees with me on the
narcissist thing. He knows. And and
Greavvesy never agrees with me. It's the
truth. It is the truth. They think
they're better than people. They're
[ __ ] They're [ __ ] all their life.
And as soon as someone tells them about
themselves, as soon as somebody right
tells them about themselves, they play
victim or they get somebody else to
fight their battles. Am I lying? Am I
lying, Joe? You said I need medication.
Am I lying? What I'm saying? That they
literally need other people to fight
their battles or they play [ __ ]
victim. Oh, I did get called a stalker.
By the way, a stalker is a narcissist's favorite word.
That's their favorite word. Everyone's
got a favorite word, right? Mine is
[ __ ] Calling someone a [ __ ] Their
favorite word is calling somebody a
stalker when somebody calls them out on
their [ __ ] They they love that word.
Yeah. USA loves that word as well
cuz they've never had someone stand up
to them. You know what I'm saying, bro?
It's They've never ever had somebody
stand and I mean verbally. I'm not
talking physical. We're talking very
verbal like a debate, you know? It's
like they've never had someone stand up to them.
Of course, I would never do it. They
live in South America. Of course, I'm
not going to go to South America. But,
bro, if they lived in England, yes, I
would do it. Yes, I [ __ ] would do it.
The mood I was in yesterday, I I That
was the first time I was in a bad mood
in the past 6 weeks. I don't get bad
moods. I don't get mood swings. I'm just
like, yeah, I'm just normal, you know?
But this is how toxic women are and
dealing with them. That's what I mean.
So at the end of the day, bro, it
listen, there's been times, bro, where I
have wrote negative messages to people
that have ignored and they've replied
back. And if I knew where they lived, I
would be breaking in their house. Yes, I
would, bro. You don't know my temper.
Yeah, you do not know my temper, bro.
Trust me. Yes, I'm not going to meet
them because they live in South America, you know.
Yeah, you can't even disagree with me.
They are narcissists. They need to get
other people to fight their battles
and when somebody stands up to them. I
mean, I'm sure there's there's
narcissistic men out there. I'm sure
there is. But normally, it's women that
are narcissists. Definitely, they are
definitely definitely narcissists. They
give it, but they can't take it. And it
wasn't simply somebody that didn't want
to talk to you because they would have
blocked you. They were doing what they
were doing on purpose. They were being a
[ __ ] on purpose.
you know, I know the difference, mate.
I'm an adult, you know? So,
and I said, and I was saying like, why
are you getting random people to message
me? I'm going to put them in their
place. I don't need to meet them, bro,
to put them in their place. I'll tell
them about themselves. But why are you
getting other people to message me cuz
I'm going to tell them about theirelves,
so there's no point.
Go to Alph America, but you can't turn
up. You said I can't turn up to fights.
So, I've never turned up to a fight on YouTube.
So, I've never ever ever turned up to a
fight on YouTube. No. Is that what
you're saying, Joe? I've never turned up
for a fight on YouTube. Really?
Me? I've never turned up to a fight. Okay.
I've tried to meet Bob. I've met Terry
two times. The second time he didn't turn up.
I have met tried to meet a bomb Terry
tried to meet Nodle Legs. Uh met Timmy and Tiger.
I mean I I I've turned up to to people
and I'm sure there's other ones that I'm
there's other people I've met as well.
Definitely definitely is other people
I've met. I'm trying to think bomb.
I've been all over the country calling
people out. So I think I have turned up
to some people mate
and you can sit there and say all you
want Joe that nonsex is not a fighter.
He was talking [ __ ] about me. I went to
his area two three times to see what he
had to say to my face and I went to his
area. So you can say it doesn't count
all you want, lad. You can say it
doesn't count all you want, but I went
to the guy's area to see what he's got
to say to my face. It very much does
count, bro. Just like if someone done
the same thing to me. It it it it pretty
does. It counts, lad. It really does
count. As much as you don't like to
admit it. I mean, I've traveled 5 hours
away to try and meet someone. They
didn't show up. Trevor Dawson. So, it
doesn't matter if I slapped somebody or
I didn't slap someone. Yes, I did. I
punched Tiger and had him on the floor.
But that doesn't matter. You've said
I've not turned up to fight. Of course,
I've turned up to fight, you silly goose.
I have turned up.
Um, but if this [ __ ] lived in England,
bro, trust me, I would be meeting
beating them. Do you know the reason why
I don't meet anyone on here? I'll tell
you the reason I don't meet anyone on
here, bro. Um,
you went to his area that
I did go to his area, bro. I went to his
area three times.
I went to his area three times, bro, and
he didn't come out. You can sit there
and say that he's not a fighter all you
want. He was talking [ __ ] about me. I
wanted to see what he's got to say to my
face. I went to Orington which is miles
away from me. Even when I lived in Was I
living in Stratford? I wasn't living in
Stratford then. But it's miles away even
from Stratford, bro. It's [ __ ] It's a
[ __ ] to get to. I done it three times
and he didn't not come out. What the
[ __ ] You know what I'm saying? He was
talking [ __ ] about me. You know, and
also another thing, Joe, why? Like
listen listen Joe, I I'll give you an
example. This Terry guy has been winding
me up. Winding me up. Yeah. To the point
where I want to go to his area, smash
his face in, take his trainers off and
make him walk home barefoot. But there's
no point. There's literally no point
because you're all biased on here. You
know, I haven't been calling anyone out
on here. So, and I don't get anything
out of it. These women need telling
about themsel. That woman needs telling
about herself in front of any orbiter.
So, it's like I would love to go and
smash his face in and I could do it, but
we all know how the cookie crumbles on
here. Yeah, big you up. It's forgotten
about tomorrow. There's no point.
There's literally no point,
you know, and I have I have met people
and I have tried to meet people as well.
And I've done Bomb twice actually.
Done Virgin Boy three times.
met Tiger and Timmy
and obviously I've gone to um I'm just
waiting for my 200 pound jeans so I can
do a video to Virgin Boy 7 that he can't
afford. He can't afford 200 pound jeans.
I could just imagine him in waxies. I
was saying Candy man that I could
imagine him in waxies,
right? But then with his ugly clothes,
right, smelling a [ __ ] and freaking
women out. But then I thought well uh well
you know you know uh he can't afford
waxies and he wouldn't be able to talk
to a woman cuz he's got anxiety. So
you said that you've never slapped anyone.
You've never slapped anyone really. So, uh,
um, so I mean, Prime didn't slap me. You
still go on about it. L didn't slap me.
Here we go. This is what I mean with you
people. You're biased. L didn't slap me.
And also, um, Prime didn't slap me and
there's been other people that's not
slapped me. But you still big them up
because you're biased. That's what I'm
saying. That's why people don't waste
their time. I know that when I if I was
to deal with these [ __ ] in South
America, I know what I've done and it's
not a biased audience.
Yes. But Vick Yeah. But Lord J didn't
slap me. Yes. Okay. Okay. Okay. Let's go
by your logic then. Okay. So, you have
to slap somebody in order for it to
count, right? You need to slap somebody
in order for it to count. Okay. Well,
Lord J didn't slap me. Listen, bear with
me before you try and say that he was
asking me to come out. He had two
chances to kick that door in my face,
which is more than a slap. He never I
also tried to meet him again. He didn't
slap me. So, at the end of the day, it's
what, bro? What? You know, see it you
you say what suits yourself, right?
Okay. And I didn't slap Virgin Boy
because he didn't come out. Right.
Exactly. And I didn't slap Virgin Boy
and I didn't hide behind Laney. I was in
front of my mom and he had several
charges to kick the door in my face.
This is what I mean. That's why I don't
waste my time. And also also another
thing is Prime never slapped me. He had
a chance to slap me. He never slapped
me. Also, Virgin Boy would have got
slapped if he had come out. So again,
you're Oh, Mark Samson. That's the [ __ ]
I was missing. I tried to meet Mark
Samson two times fair and square. He
didn't come out about I've not turned up
for a fight. I've not turned up for a
fight. Really? Oh, that's the other
[ __ ] Yes, Mark Samson. I tried to meet
him two times. No one ever mentioned
that. That's what I'm saying. You're all biased.
You're all biased. That's what I'm
saying. You're all biased, mate. Okay.
Okay. Right. L is on here saying he's
going to slap people up. He has Well, LJ
comes on here acting hard when he has
bottled it multiple times. He's bottled
it from LT. He's bottled meeting me a
second time. So, I mean, he comes on
here acting hard. I'm talking about
people that aren't on this community.
Yeah. I tried to meet Mark Samson two
times. He didn't show up.
So, what that's another one that is the
strongest one that I've got, Mark
Samson. And no one ever mentioned it.
And that one is fair and square. I went
to his area. I went live for two hours
on two different days and he was
starting [ __ ] with me and the guy did
not come out and no one ever said
anything about it. That's the one I was
missing. Arsenal Mark. Yes. And I was a
lot younger then as well but no one ever
gave me credit for that cuz you're all biased.
So uh here's the thing. Um Joe Ant-Man
uh contradicted himself today
for the first time.
Now, do you want me to tell you how he contradicted himself
and you can say if you agree or disagree?
>> You the mate. Listen, listen, listen. No
one takes him serious, bro. You said
that two years later. Everybody knew
about him, but no one said anything
until two years later. So, again, we all
knew that. Me and LT knew what he was
about after that, but none of you said
anything until we done it the 30th time.
Okay. So, I showed him a video where
this uh woman um said that she was
married. I said, "Oh, they're full of
[ __ ] in it. Do you think she's married?"
She said, "Oh, probably." Um, it's easy
for women. They get to choose guys um
that they like, but it's not me and you.
And I said, "Well, there's no me and you
firstly because um I've given up and
don't include me in your shit." And I
said, "So, is it me and you or is it 80
90% of the population?" So, is it me and
you or is it 80 90% of other people?
Then he come out with this is what he
come out with. Yeah, listen to this. He
then said that um he said, "Yeah, it is
80 90% of people that don't get laid,
but that doesn't matter because it
doesn't matter anyways because it's
about you. And if you're getting laid or
not getting laid. I said, "Huh? How many
times have you gone on about [ __ ]
other people? Oh, other guys do it.
[ __ ] oh, other guys. Fat guys do it.
How does he do it? How does he do it?"
And you're telling me not to worry about
if 80 90% of people are getting laid or
not getting laid. Contradicting
yourself, huh? How many times has this
guy got on about other people? And he
never said anything after that. But so I
think it would kind of matter cuz it
matters to you as well, you know,
constantly. And he was saying, "Oh, it
doesn't matter. You just need to worry
about," he said, "Oh, um, it if 80 90%
of people are getting laid or not
getting laid, that's them. That's not
you. It only matters about you." I said,
"That's what I've been saying to you all
along when you're [ __ ] comparing me
to other people time and time and time
and time and time and time again when
when you're saying, "Oh, how does other
people do it?" And I said, "I'm not
other people or whatever." So, make it
make sense, you know? We didn't fall out
or anything, but that that's you're contradicting yourself, you know.
Yeah, he is. I think he is definitely
definitely trolling. I think he is. He
is that bit I don't think I think he is
a bit thick but
yeah he is he is
but yeah no he's definitely no I think
he is a bit thick like he's contradicting himself you know
because you constantly compare yourself
to other people now Joe this woman was
saying about how she can't find a man
and she lives in London and that she's
30. Now, I said, "Oh, you know, all
women are [ __ ] They're all the same."
Whatever. But I thought, "Let me give
this person the benefit of the doubt,
Joe." And I was like, "Let me message
them and tell her like um my struggles
and, you know, give her a bit of history
about what I've experienced." And then I
was going to say, "Oh, let's go for a
meal in London. I don't want to drink.
You know, I don't really drink much
anymore. I haven't drunk for ages. Let's
go for a nice meal and see uh what the
score is." Cuz you said that you can't
find someone. You said that you can't
find a man. then no man you meet is
single. So I messaged her and well she
um and she lives in London where you can
meet anywhere in London very fast. Well,
she didn't reply. Now I made another
Reddit account pretending to be a woman.
And let's see if she replies to that.
And if she does reply, I will say, "Hi,
it's me again. I would appreciate in
future you don't moan about not being
able to find a man when when somebody
does uh agree to meet you. Um you're not
interested. Don't moan about men. Please
don't moan about men, mate. You know, I
don't I don't think men are perfect, but
don't moan that you can't find people
when you [ __ ] well can,
you know, cuz they they sit there and
say, right, that that all the guys that
they meet want sex. I don't just want
sex. They say, "Oh, guys want sex.
They're this, that, they're this,
they're that." But that's ridiculous
because all of these women have never
ever gave me a chance. like they don't
give most a lot of people a chance.
They're [ __ ] Absolute [ __ ]
But yeah, that's the first time I've
been in a bad mood yesterday, Joe, for a
very long time.
Very long time.
It shows you how toxic it is dealing with women.
Somebody, it feels like Yeah. When I
finally gave up, yeah, this is just some
[ __ ] from Instagram. I felt like I was
in prison for 20 years and I got out.
That's how I generally felt. So
peaceful, so quiet, no mind games, no
[ __ ] Oh, bro, I generally felt like
I'd just come out of prison. Like it it
felt so good. Like no more games, no more [ __ ] Um,
people still dismiss my struggles. Like
they say stuff, oh, like I'll show them
[ __ ] that women have done and that and
they, oh, dating is hard. And like I
want you to not feel sorry for me, but I
want you to be a bit taken back by it at
least and be like, "Oh, what the fuck?"
Like, you know, like they didn't give
you a chance. That's disgusting. Like I
want someone to say something like that,
but I don't want somebody to feel sorry
for me, but I want them to be drawn back
on how [ __ ] up it is, how [ __ ] up
the whole thing is. Don't just sit there
and say, "Oh, well, yeah, you know." So,
you've asked me what I I want them to
do. I want them to actually acknowledge
how [ __ ] up it is. I don't want them
to feel sorry for me. I don't want their [ __ ] pity.
I just want them to acknowledge that
it's not normal. You know what I'm
saying? That's whatever the [ __ ] normal
is. But you get what I mean? So,
you know what I mean? And that that
[ __ ] bro, in South America, she was a
proper [ __ ] She was a proper proper
[ __ ] If you're going to be a [ __ ] and
you're going to be arrogant, it's like
me. Imagine me starting [ __ ] with
people. And it doesn't matter if you're
a man or you're a woman because we're
talking verbally here. And I have to get
other people to fight my battles. It's
[ __ ] ridiculous, man. So
these women switch though as well.
That's another thing. They switch like a light bulb.
That woman blocked me by the way. That
woman in France cuz I I told that woman
to get raped.
And so she's like, "Oh, I was trying to
help you, but I have to block you." So
me, so you blocked me because I told her
to get raped, but what she's done being
a [ __ ] on purpose, that's completely all
right. Okay. Yeah, fair enough. Interesting. Whatever.
So, it's just what's the point, bro? You know,
it's not even the worst thing to say
nowadays is get raped. It's not really
We've heard it so many times. It happens
so many times. It's not even like, you know. So, yeah.
if this woman really can't find someone,
I'm more I'm more than happy to meet
you. I'm more than happy to give the
last person the benefit of the doubt to
see if these women truly are different,
which I don't think they are. I've
messaged you. You've not responded back.
But you're saying that
you're saying about how you can't find someone.
So it's like
I'm sure there's genuine guys that try
to get with these women that don't just
want sex. I'm sure there is genuine guys, bro.
I'm sure there's genuine guys. No,
that that tried to get with these women. No.
So why are you not replying? You you
live in London. So yeah.
And they try to say that looks don't matter.
Yeah. They say that it's about
personality. They're [ __ ] delusional,
bro. They think it's about personality. Yeah. Right.
I don't know what I don't know what
their problem is, bro. I mean, I have
looks maxed. I I look [ __ ] normal
when I go out, but
they're not interested. So,
[ __ ] weird, isn't it?
[ __ ] up, is it? Joseph.
Well, I'm looking forward to this Thai
food restaurant today as well. So, Should
be good, man.
They moan about not being able to find men,
yet they have so many options. Joe, are
you still there?
There's no way none of them men are are
genuine. No, Joe. Like she said, no. No.
One second, Joseph. For real. She just
said that she's struggling with men and
she lives in London. Now I'm 28, she's
30, only two years. So that means if
she's really struggling and she can't
find anyone, then she will go out with
me now cuz she's complaining.
I really hope she doesn't reply to this message, bro,
because I'm going to be like, "Well,
hold on. You're moaning about men.
You're complaining about men." Oh, and
that one that tried meeting me, by the
way, Joe, in Scotland, um, it was
someone on here.
It was someone on here, Joe. So,
you might want to rephrase the question, you know.
It's crazy, bro. It's like people need
to just stop bullshitting now. They just
need to say the truth. Women are more
shallow than men. And
yeah, that's it.
Then that's it, bro. Like they're way
they're way more shallow than men. Yeah. Anyways, [clears throat]
I messaged her family anyways, Joe.
Oh, I told her family she's a lesbian
because she's a lesbian and she hasn't
come out cuz that's how I found her on
Reddit. So, I was like, you want to [ __ ]
me, I [ __ ] with you.
I should be the bigger person really.
But this is the [ __ ] that you're you're
getting into when you're dealing with women.
That's the [ __ ] that you're dealing with
when you're getting when you're getting
into this stuff with women and stuff. Yeah. Toxic, negative. So, yeah.
Joe hates Reddit, you know. Bey hates Reddit.
Hey, Joseph for Mia.
Right. Where the [ __ ] are these jeans?
1000 p.m. to 2:00 p.m. Oh, okay. Yeah.
1000 p.m. to 2:00 p.m. So, not long then.
It says 10:00 p.m. to 2:00 p.m. N
2 p.m. Yay.
The jeans are coming, Laney. They're coming.
Should I buy a new pair of trainers as well?
I might be a little cheeky chappy. Buy a
new pair of trainers, too. That That
would get the Virgin jealous, would it?
Do you know what? I might I might do I
might do. I'm not sure.
Can I afford it? Can I not afford it?
I'm not I don't know. H
I could pop and and see, you know.
Not sure. I mean, don't know.
I'm not sure.
Maybe. I don't know.
It'd be rude not to, wouldn't it?
It'd be very very very rude not to.
Would it Joseph?
It'd be very very rude not to.
It would be, wouldn't it, mate? Let's
Let's be real here.
It is tempting.
Like I said, it'd be rude not to, mate.
It'd be [ __ ] rude not to.
But then I'd have to go out on Saturday,
wouldn't I, Grezy, and chat up all the ladies?
Isn't that right, Jo? Uh, Grezy, nothing lasts forever. M
I think it will be very very rude doctor
but I always go there and I never see
any trainers I like.
Never ever see any trainers that I like. Mate,
what do you reckon? Should I get a new
pair of trainers?
Should I get a new pair of trainers? Grievy.
Did you say the word? I go and get them, mate. You sure?
Okay. Okay. Why are the are the old ones
still good? Would you say?
Would you say the old ones are still
good or would you say they're they're quite fantastic?
I mean, I've only worn them a couple of
times, but I really want to get the
Virgin boy raging. You see, you know,
I really want to get the Virgin the
Virgin raging. That's the thing.
Let's see what kind of trainers they've
got. Hold on.
Let me have a little look.
You never find trainers that you want
either. That's the thing. It's very hard
to find trainers that
And I'm going to also bring up Joe in
this uh video too.
One second, lad.
Nothing lasts forever.
I'm just having a little browse. Nah,
I like to me my favorite trainers are Vapor Maxes.
They're like £215, but my favorite one
are Vapor Maxes. They're lush. All
right. So, there should be a [snorts]
It's so mad, Boogie, that the price of
Do's phone is the price of my jeans.
Isn't that exciting? Mom.
Uh, it says it's coming between 10 and two.
Do you know um the jeans? Yeah. Sorry,
mama. The jeans are uh the same price as
someone I know's phone. Isn't that so
exciting? Isn't that cool
that it's the same price as someone's
mobile that they probably had for years
and just little thing to cover up my bottom?
Isn't that cool? You know,
isn't that cool?
Would you say that's cool, Grezy?
Isn't that cool? [laughter]
No, I can never get a 200 pound phone.
Greavvesy, not a 1700 one. Obviously,
I'll never be able to afford a fold
ever, but you know, you can tell the
difference between a £400 phone and a
2000 phone, if you if you get what I
mean, Greavves. It still has to be
semidecent. The phone still has to be
semi semi good, you know.
And the 151 ones and 200 ones just don't
do the trick, you know? Yeah.
Because Joe, you're not telling me my
jeans cost the same as your as your little uh well
your little phone.
Isn't that cool? Oh,
what do you think? Graves 200 pound
jeans. I want my jeans. I want my jeans.
My They're trousers. But yeah, it's the
same price as uh Joseph's phone.
We're going to bring the Virgin up as
well. If he wore these, he might
actually get laid. But again, it's all
hypothetical cuz he can't afford waxies.
I really feel like putting these jeans
on and going out, you know, over the
weekend. I got my little football bet on and stuff.
So, you know. Yeah.
That's all right. Nothing lasts forever.
Is that right?
So, what am I what am I going to title
the video as? Greavvesy. I'm going to be
like, "These jeans are the same price of Joseph's phone."
How's that one? And you like that title?
I think that title is pretty cool.
What do you think, Lizzy?
Yeah, I think that title is pretty cool.
I think it's pretty spectacular.
But I'm also going to mention the Virgin
that he'd be rude not to.
Yeah, worth any It's probably worth more
than his old his uh his whole wardrobe. You know,
it's worth the the same price of Joseph
Ferrar's phone. I mean, Grezy, would you
be happy with a 200 pound phone?
Yeah. And wardrobe. A certain person's
phone and wardrobe.
Obviously, Joseph Farah's phone. And um
the virgin's wardrobe. Them shitty
little charity shop clothes. No wonder
he's a [ __ ] virgin. I'll whisper. Do
you know what I'm saying, mate? [ __ ]
skiid virgin [ __ ]
He's been skid from a very young age,
mate. A very young age. And I'll mention
you as well, Greavves. I was just about
to nip out to buy a new pair of
trainers, but Grievy Grezy locked me in
so I couldn't do it.
No, like your main phone.
Nah, your main No, I mean your main phone, Grezy.
Just like a brand new 200 pound phone.
Would that be good enough for you?
Nah. 400 one would be I think a 400 one
would be good. No.
A400 one would be
well it'd be good enough for you. A200
one. Nah. See the thing is with me bro.
I'm so used to having expensive phones.
You can feel the difference between a
200 like even I mean like a free 400
pound phone is still good like that's
good enough but I mean like you can tell
the difference between a 150 200lb one
and a400 one and they just feel cheap you know
but it all depends what you know you're
doing with them. It's just they just
feel cheap, you know?
Just depends, isn't it? But I never paid
£1,700 for a phone. [ __ ] off.
Now, I'm not only going to mention you
in this video, Joseph Farah.
Should I should I title it this these
jeans are the same price of as Joseph
Farrar's mobile phone or telephone? [laughter] H
telephone. So I put telephone games.
>> Uh RM
mail, you silly gay. I I can't. Mom, I'm
sat here waiting patiently for these jeans. >> Yeah.
>> Okay. Sorry.
>> Sorry, but I'm excited.
Sorry, Ma. I'm just excited. I I'll keep it down.
What? Mo, we going for Thai food today.
We're going for
What? Mo, when was the last time I had a
pair of 200 pound jeans?
Cuz Yeah, I thought I'd spend some of
the winnings on a new pair of jeans. Mama. >> Oh,
>> yeah. I was going to say get some
piggies, but I'm not I'm saving my
appetite for um thingy. Sorry, ma. Okay.
All right, mama. Okie do.
Okay, I'll be good. I'm not saying
anything untowards, ma. I'm just excited
for these new jeans.
>> I understand.
>> Okay. Sorry, Ma.
>> Okay, I'll keep it down.
I'm just playing some Franklin.
[snorts] No, I I just I just bought some
new jeans. They're coming today. They're £200 jeans.
That's all. It's the same the same uh
it's the same price of Joseph Ferrar's phone. Joseph Ferrar.
And I me I say, "Oh, Greasy was gonna
Grievy was going to uh I was going to
buy a new pair of trainers, but Grievy
locked me in the house, so I couldn't do
it. So, have I got a date? Why would I
have a date, bro?
I don't go out approaching anymore.
Why would I have a date?
No, he [ __ ] don't.
He's never won Tommy Hilfiger in his life.
No, he's never had he's never had Tommy
for good jeans in all his puff.
No, he doesn't, mate. No, he don't. I've
I've got 200 pound jeans coming.
Well, they weren't 300 pound, bro. Cuz
there's no there's no Tommy Hilfiger
jeans that are £300
cuz Ammani is more expensive than Tommy
Hilfiger and there's no Ammani jeans
that are £300, mate. So I don't think
that's true, mate.
I don't think that's true.
No, there's no way.
Let me have a little look.
No, I don't have a date, lad. Women are
all the same. I go up with him.
his live stream right now and I can't see any chat Joseph.
>> That's my new name for you. Joseph this
these jeans are the same price as Joseph Farer's phone.
Would you believe it? Would you add and
believe? Would you add and believe it? [laughter]
Would you believe and leave it? You get
200 bucks. There's no bucks in this
country, mate. It's pounds.
>> Nah, mate. I've got more than that.
I've got I've got 300 Stony jumpers.
Yeah. £300 Stony jumpers. Mate,
I've got more expensive clothes than
him, mate. I've got four Stone Island
jumpers, £300 each. That puts him to shame, lad.
I'll show you them if you want.
And you know what? I reckon this color,
right, this color would go with uh
breakfast and stuff. I won't make noise.
do you like this. Is
Is it that and the jeans?
Is it Is it Does it look [ __ ] now?
>> Well, it still looks
>> brand new, isn't it?
>> Still vibrate. >> Yeah.
Yeah. So, I was thinking this this would
go with a virgin virgin skin tone.
I can see him maybe losing that V card.
Just wait until these jeans come. Now,
this was a very expensive dry cleaning.
very expensive dry cleaning lad, but it
looks almost brand new. You know, this
is it's still very vibrant. It's still
quite good. I reckon the Virgin will
lose it if he if he if he wears that and the jeans, mate. E
Now, Grezy, listen. Grezy, listen to me
now, son. Nope. It's never been washed.
Grievy, listen to me, mate. You're
telling me Monty man's got more
expensive garments than me? Really?
Okay, let's start. Right. 200 £300£300
3000 £300 £100. You're wet. Rest in peace. Done.
It's done. All you got to do is is show
a couple of stonies, mate. And then
you're bad. You die.
That's That's it. That's all she wrote.
Is that right? Rest in peace. Didn't
even need to show anything else. You
like the Stone Island jumper, Beezy?
You like the Stony Jumper? Does it still
look quite good?
Does it still look quite good, Musy? Be
honest with me. Does it still look all
right? The Stone Island jumper.
Be honest. Be honest with me.
be honest. Does it still look good?
Does it still I mean I haven't worn it
since it come out the dry cleaning. Does
it still look all right? Does it still look wearable?
I'm going to be so tempted to go out on
the piss on Saturday now, mate. Brand
new jeans. Trainers only been worn a
couple of times. Nice stony. I'm going
to be so tempted. Grezy.
So tempted to to to to go out. It'd be
It's like it would be rude not to, you know.
It'd be rude not to.
I might give him If he weren't such a
virgin horrible little [ __ ] I would
have gave him one of the green I would
have gave him the green stony.
If he weren't such an able virgin little
[ __ ] Horrible virgin little [ __ ]
Right. I would I would have and
obviously got the expensive after shave
as well. Now, this is the joy with with
spending this kind of money on these
things is that they last forever, don't they?
They last forever.
Now, I know you said before that
they look second. They look secondhand
because they haven't been dry cleaned.
These things need dry cleaning. You know,
Gravesy, you said 16 You said 1,600
pounders lash in it.
You said, 1600 pound is lash. I might
start getting the 15s out for this
virgin again, mate. Yeah,
I can tell you what Monty's never owned.
I might just own everyone in the video.
Why not? I might just own every single
[ __ ] in the in the video. Not you,
Greavvesy. I'll be nice to you because
you're a you're a good [ __ ] You know,
you're a long-term viewer. But I might
own everyone. Why not? Joe, the Virgin, Monty,
just just own them all. Greavvesy.
Okay with you, boss. Obviously, I have
to run it by you first. I'll do the
Virgin. I'll do Joseph Ferrar. I'll do uh Monty.
I mean, three of them. He's done. Three
of them stonies. He's finished.
Probably even two of them, mate. Because
I've got stonies to go with these jeans. Yeah.
See, people say, "Oh, it's not worth it
spending £35 on dry cleaning greasy." It
is cuz these clothes are worth £1,300, mate.
So, they're very, very much worth it, you know.
Yeah. He's never been to self in his life.
So, I'm going to be like, in case Monty
wants to come and jump on the bandwagon,
you're finished, Monty. You're done.
You're over with. Jeans, two stonies.
Rest in peace.
You know, there's no coming back from
that in case you wanted to do a little
video uh you know, saying, "Oh, well,
I've got you go boss, but you ain't got
Stone Island. There you
go." So, who do you want? Who do you
want me to own on the video?
Do you want me to do Virgin boy Joseph
Farah or because them two are definitely
getting owned. So Joseph Farah,
Joseph Farerra, right? Joseph Farerra,
right? And obviously Virgin Boy. And I
can add Monty if you want, but obviously
I have to I have to run it by you first. You know
who would you who would you want me
would you want me to add Monty as well?
I don't mind, you know, cuz he might
like to get involved. I'll be like,
"Fuck off, bitch." Three things.
I don't know. It's up to you.
It's up to you, ladies. Did I
Kerry and White and Kerry and Rise?
I have to go for some Kerry and rice today.
My mommy's treating me for a meal.
Yeah, but I bet you've never had that
experience, have you, Virgin boy? Your
mama treating you for a meal. [laughter]
I need to be hospitalized. I'm not
normal. Now, I'm not wearing them today,
but I would like to I'm going to script
this whole thing. What I'm saying,
you've never know what it's like to be
tooken for a meal by your mother, cuz
your mother stomped you.
Didn't she mate? You know,
a lot of people are going to be owned
just with a pair 200 pair of jeans,
greasy, cuz you can have all the life
experience in the world, Joe, but you've
never had a pair of 200 pound jeans
and all your puff. guys today. Yeah, Joseph for
these [ __ ] don't let we can't let
these [ __ ] women win, Grezy, can we?
Don't let these [ __ ] women win.
Who's your favorite channel on YouTube?
Is it me?
Right, I'm going to listen some music.
Wait for these jeans and the video incoming.
So, look forward to it. Where is he?