Joseph Farra. Oh,
what did you do, Joseph?
Right, I'm having a little go on
Franklin, my little mate.
Yeah, going to the pub tomorrow. Yep. Joseph.
All right. Go on. I want to play black.
I want to play GTA. Come on.
Why is it not working?
There we go. Yeah.
[ __ ] tired as [ __ ] bro.
I want to eat, but my [ __ ] mouth's hurting me.
Like really [ __ ] bad, lad. Yeah,
they were like, "I'm going to the pub
tomorrow, bro. I ordered some new
trainers." This little kind was trying
to say, "Oh, you said you was going to
get trainers, but you didn't because
your skin." Oh, really? Well, I bought
an over 200 pound pair of trainers, and
I'm sending it tomorrow, mate. I'll be
sending it in the pub tomorrow.
Well, I'll be out tomorrow, bro.
I'll be out tomorrow.
I'm waiting for the trainers to come. So,
yeah, bro. I'll be out. Uh
yeah, like I said,
I'll be out tomorrow, lad. Sending it
like a [ __ ]
And then I started it. I had my haircut
last week, so I should still look all right. Yeah.
Got my brand new trainers coming, lad.
How many numbers do you reckon I'll be
getting tomorrow, bro?
I ain't approached for ages, but I can
still do it, bro. Even sober.
These people, what is it with these
people on here, Pokemon? They seem to
think right just cuz their skin,
everyone else's skin.
Like, why why wouldn't I be able to
afford a new pair of trainers?
I said I was maybe going to get them,
maybe wasn't, and I just bought them.
What the [ __ ]
They think everyone's got the same life
as them, don't they?
Yeah, they generally seem to think
everyone has their life on here.
I'm coming off here soon, lad. Really?
I'm coming off here soon. It's [ __ ] ridiculous, man.
It is ridiculous.
You ask yourself this question, bro.
They got all this money, man. Why they
got a life? Why have none of these
people got a life? Ask yourself that question.
Me, I was chilling. I I gave up dating,
bro. I had nothing better to do. So, but
I still done stuff today. Ask yourself,
they've got all this money. Why they got a life?
Ask yourself that, lad.
Weird, isn't it?
I got a nice football bet tomorrow. Uh,
treble both got no draw, so be getting
on the Guinness.
Don't know whether to wear that Ralphie
tomorrow or the Stonies.
I might wear the Ralphie and then maybe
go out the next week and wear the Stony.
I don't know.
[sighs and gasps]
Okay, I'll wear the I want to wear that
Ralphie, bro. It's like beige. It's nice.
Then I wear the sun. I'll go next week
and then the week after. Yeah.
I don't have
I can afford to go out every week. Of
course, I can afford to go out every week, but
um I just don't basically. So,
it's mad cuz it's like
this is literally like a full-time job,
is it? Dating is like a full-time job
just to get a bit of sex, just to get a
date. It's [ __ ] ludicrous.
You can't like date. It's weird cuz you
can't date and improve yourself at the same time.
It's not a part-time job. It's a full-time job.
The old saying goes, it's a part-time
job, but it's actually a full-time job.
You can't do both, which is crazy.
It is crazy. Yeah. You can't you
actually can't do both. It's one or the other
cuz obviously the amount of time and
money that goes into it as well like the
dating and it's madness. Madness.
I don't know, man. I don't know. It's
[ __ ] wild, lad.
of egg, but my mouth is killing me, bro.
I can't even eat. Oh,
yeah. I'm going to do a little video
tomorrow. Pokemon. Fresh trainers, fresh
street jeans, straight in the waxies, you know.
It'll be sick, man.
Today everything is [ __ ] up though.
What are you doing? What do you [ __ ]
do? What do you [ __ ] do? Yeah.
Yeah. Somebody was singing over that woman. Oh [ __ ]
Well, that's any worse, man.
Know what time they're coming tomorrow, but yeah. One sec.
Hey, bro. [ __ ] I'm good, man. What's
up my sisters? And I'm just chilling
now. I want to eat these pork tops
squeezy, but my mouth's hurting
from yesterday. I think something got
stuck in my gums or some [ __ ]
Yeah, I'll be out tomorrow, lad.
I'll be out on the piss. So yeah, one second.
Sorry, I brought the trainers grieving.
Do you forgive me yet? Do you forgive me?
Please tell me you forgive me.
Do you forgive me, Greavves? Cheers, boss.
I'll be going waxies tomorrow, lad. with
a nice jeans and a nice trainers and a
nice football bet and see what trouble
we can get up to. See what women we can
come come across.
That'd be nice, would it, Grezy?
Yeah, that' be nice, lad. Oh, what
a nice put nice 300 pound aside for the weekend.
300 aside for the weekend, Grezy. That's
lovely, isn't it?
Probably won't even end up spending all
of it though.
To be fair,
it's nice and little.
A pile of Guinness is like £8.
Yeah, she was drunk.
She was drunk, lad.
How much do you reckon I'll spend
tomorrow greasy on drinking?
How much do you reckon I'll spend?
We'll see. Eh, yeah,
maybe 1 150. I have to go out, candy,
man. I bought new trailers. It'd be rude not to.
I'm just basically showing you. Yeah. Do
you remember when I told you yesterday I
was going to buy these trainers? Yeah.
Nothing does work. But what else am I
going to do, bro? I've got a nice new
pair of jeans. I've got new trainers
coming tomorrow. This guy was like, "Oh,
you can't afford trainers cuz you're
skinn." I was like, "Oh, really? I'll
just buy them now then. Simple.
I I'll buy him right now, mate. I'm not
asked. You know, he doesn't mean
anything to me, mate. And I'll be doing
a video to him tomorrow when the trainers come.
But no, nothing does work, lad. It's a one-off.
It's a one-off, bro. How often do I go out?
I just want to get drunk and just [ __ ]
about tomorrow. So,
what's what do I lose, bro? What? £300?
Oh, big deal. If I go out tomorrow and
spend, bro, what have I Well, not 300. I
won't spend £300, but what's the worst
case scenario? But what I lose 300 lb,
so be it, bro. What? You know,
it doesn't mean anything, bro.
Do you know what's so [ __ ] up about
this candy man? Yeah. Is it's like a full-time job.
You can't work on yourself and improve
yourself and try to get with women at
the same time.
And it's not just about money. It's
about the time that you have to put in it.
The time, the money as well, but like
it's more time.
So it cuz it's like a it's a full-time
job. It's not a part-time job. It's a full-time job. So yeah.
But I'll be having fun tomorrow anyway. So,
it'd be rude not to go out with a nice
new pair of jeans and new trainers.
You are a virgin. Stop calling yourself [snorts]
You see how them people are [ __ ]
defending that woman on the train?
madness. And then they were singing.
It's crazy, bro. Really crazy.
I got a nice football bet as well. Yeah.
Yeah. [ __ ] women anyways, bro.
Well, we'll see tomorrow what happens in
it when I approach. Anyways, Candy man,
we'll see what happens.
I'll come back and I'll report it.
Do you know what? There was a time when
I was on a train. I think it was when I
was on the train to Bristol when I was a
bit younger and I was playing some voice
notes out and um
this woman was trying to say to me, "Oh,
you've played it three times. Can you
not do it again?" Bro, obviously I was
younger then, so I never really stood up
for myself, but I would have told her
now, "Fuck off. I'll do what I want."
I would have been like, "I'll [ __ ] do
what I want. Mind your own [ __ ]
business." I've stuck it on women, bro.
Not like that, though. Like when I was
doing the Uber Eats thing, I stuck it on a woman.
I stuck it on a woman, bro.
Oh, you shouldn't ride. I said, "I'll
[ __ ] ride where I want." And then she
was like, "All right, dickhead." I said,
"Yeah, come come here and call me a
dickhead." I parked up the bike. I said,
"Come here now. Let's see what you're
saying now. Don't walk away, you little
bitch." But not like that.
But I would have done it in a different
way than Timmy. I would have just stayed
sat there and just [ __ ]
just kept sticking it on the [ __ ] But
I wouldn't get in her face. Yeah.
I can't wait to go out tomorrow, bro.
Really can't wait.
It's going to be a load of fun.
I'm trying to think how far I should travel. Then
I said I' got out with my sister. So
maybe the week after I go out again. I don't know.
Yeah, I'll be at waxies tomorrow with
the jeans, the trainers, and the football bet.
No, I have to go there a bit later though
cuz I need to go to a certain place.
They don't let people in after certain time. Um
it's going to be quite difficult this
isn't it to try and um
yeah the football back the trainers and the teams
it will be a lovely site you know Um,
I can't go to both. That's the thing.
It's either Waxies or the other place.
No, I want to kind of do waxies though.
I'm trying to think where else we could go.
I don't know, bro. I don't know. We
We'll figure it out.
No, I'm eating my T-bone tomorrow before
I go out.
Yeah, my t-bone before I go out
cuz I didn't eat it. Obviously, I bought
a t-bone steak, but
can't eat it cuz my my mouth is hurting. So,
But yeah, what do you think will happen
tomorrow when I approach Candy?
I want to go somewhere that's got like better music.
I don't know. Um,
I'll be going out regardless anyway.
What do you think's going to happen, Candyman?
And no, I didn't.
I can either wear the Ralph Lauren
or the Stony.
I mean, both look good.
I don't know where I'm going yet, man.
That's going to be the problem with
going to a [ __ ]
wax, don't it?
I mean, I guess we could start there, but
None of these places start [ __ ]
I don't know.
Flip a coin. Why?
Oh, I don't know, man. Um,
flip a coin for what?
What do you think of that idea,
Candyman? Should we flip a coin to
choose which one we go to?
I think that sounds like a good idea.
And obviously next week we'll go to the other one.
Yeah, I think that Yeah, I was going to
do that before like with what location I
go to. I was going to flip a coin before
like just mad stuff like that. Yeah, we
can do that. We can do that.
Heads or tails? Yeah.
What should we do? Flip the coin.
We could do waxes on the Sunday
if we really wanted to. We could do the
waxies on the Sunday.
That wouldn't be a bad idea.
So, we could do obviously. Yeah.
Waxi is good because they're more it's
more older people.
I don't know. Yeah.
Well, I got £300 anyways spare. So either way. Yeah, man.
No, there's no chubs in any of them.
Yeah, there's no chance in any of them, lad. No.
I don't know which one to pick. Uh
cuz if I stay at max waxes and I try to
go to the other one, I'll be [ __ ]
There'll be no Yeah. What's this? Um,
I think we'll do waxies next week. Yeah.
I didn't cook it, bro. My mouth's
hurting me. I want to cook it tomorrow
before I leave and go out drinking.
I don't know what I'm doing tomorrow, bro.
We might have to do waxies next week.
Oh, we can do waxies on the Sunday, but I mean,
no, I think we'll do it we'll do waxies next week.
I think I think that's that's better.
Yeah, I'll do waxies next week.
What do you reckon is going to happen
tomorrow when I go out approaching Jasper? Any luck?
Whoa, the link's there.
What do you think, lad? Oh [ __ ] So funny. One second. Emotional
What's going to happen, Mr. Lotty, when
I approach tomorrow? Do you reckon I'll pull
tomorrow when I do some more. You recognize Whoa.
No one answers any of my questions, man.
No one answers me.
I need to try and eat some [ __ ]
That's not the real Timmy.
Yeah, that's not the real Timmy.
Slug on the run. Yeah, someone's trying
to draw him, but that's not the real Timmy.
So, can you give me some advice, Candyman?
So, how how are you going to get into a
relationship and have a sex life then if
nothing works here, Tandy man?
So, what does one do then?
Answer me that one.
Yeah, maybe. Why do you think it's so
hard here? What do you think the problem is?
Why is it so hard to get a date here?
Like all all all seriousness, bro. Like,
why do you think it's so difficult?
It's weird. No.
>> Why do you think it's so difficult? Oh,
is it him?
>> Hello. How's it going?
>> I can't hear. One second. Stay. Stay in
there. One second. Hold on. Hold on.
>> Virgin. How's it going?
Come on, brother. Why you scared of
words on the screen? Why you scared of
sentences, PJ? You need to man up, bro.
You're not going to be a real man if
you're scared of the f. I mean, me and
F, I've got a hate relationship, but I
still let on the [ __ ] chat. Like, you
>> I could I couldn't I couldn't hear you
properly, 1984. I still let him talk,
PJ. His words on the screen. Why do you
let it get to you, lad?
>> What are you talking about?
>> You You're scared of [ __ ] trolls.
>> No, I'm not.
>> You are, bro. I leave I I leave comments open now, >> brother.
>> I leave comments I leave I leave comments open.
>> [ __ ] slam their fingers and let them die.
>> I leave comments open.
>> Brother, you need to man up.
>> I liked your video on the train, by the way.
>> Anyway, let's be honest, I'm not taking
the piston. You definitely are a virgin.
>> Self projecting again.
>> Hate for women.
>> What have I told you about self projecting?
>> I was not sexist. Right. She I've looked
at the [ __ ] P.
>> What is it? She's a lefty politician.
What is it with you? I own it with you.
>> I own these left [ __ ]
>> Why do you keep calling yourself
>> who loves the UK who wants to ruin [ __ ]
>> Why is it with you and people like
nonsense calling people virgin when
you're one yourself?
>> I don't understand it. It's [ __ ] mad.
Jimmy, why do you why do you call people
virgin when you're one yourself? It's so obvious.
>> I mean, I put a porno out there. I mean,
>> she's a rightwing [ __ ]
>> guy's a [ __ ] idiot.
>> Yeah, right. PJT.
>> The only virgins is you and on this
community, lad. You you like
>> you're the only two virgins on here,
>> brother. You can't be a bit of rabbit.
Anyway, PJ, I'm I'm in I'm in my
destination. I'm gonna go live in a
minute, but brother, just look at me.
You're a virgin. You
>> self projecting again.
>> Self projecting.
>> Just like when you just like when you
call people skin. Self projecting.
>> We don't have self projecting on this channel, bro.
>> About trolls. [ __ ] the trolls.
>> We don't have self projection on this channel.
What's up, brother? Look,
>> we don't have self projecting on this channel.
>> I'll be back. I'll be back. Put the rep
We put the link in. This
>> guy's a [ __ ] [ __ ] man. I swear to
God, he's a [ __ ] idiot.
What is it with him keep calling people
what he Bro? Oh my god. I swear, Candy,
these people give me a headache, bro.
These people really [ __ ] give me a
headache, man. Swear down.
I don't know. Like
what's with them? Keep talking about themselves.
It's weird, isn't it? Why do they do this, bro?
We got some little virgin that keeps
trying to [ __ ] join. He needs to get laid. Madness, bro. Like that.
The only two virgins on here is him and
[ __ ] Lunch. Well, there's other
virgins as well, but
I mean, Red Star is a virgin.
Sat on YouTube stalking men all day.
It is qu You know what's so mad? How
these people try to criticize you,
right, Candyman? But literally none of
them have got a life.
Yeah, you're not coming in, you little
skint virgin. [ __ ] off, nons legs. Go get laid.
Stop trying to be Timmy [ __ ] virgin.
You would have thought these people
Candy man would give up. But nope.
That's how you know they're low lives. Insecure
that nods legs. He's an insecure little
virgin. And every time he does this, it
proves my point even more. He's just a
skint little lowife virgin. [ __ ] 14
grand. [ __ ] show 14 grand now.
Not from [ __ ] years ago. You [ __ ] skint virgin.
You know what I mean? He's the [ __ ]
biggest virgin going. Why do you think
he knows all the tail signs? I don't
understand the point of all of this
[ __ ] No one's going to meet anyone or
what? You just going to keep being
keyboard warriors for the rest of your [ __ ] life.
[ __ ] weird as [ __ ]
[ __ ] what a virgin.
Candy man. Why do you think he calls
people virgins? Cuz he's the biggest one
going. So we know all the signs.
He know all the telltale signs.
Obviously being the biggest virgin
himself. Is that right, Candyman? Um yeah,
sugar really [ __ ] your gums up, bro. I
need [snorts] to stop drinking. I need
to stop consuming sugar. >> [snorts]
>> [ __ ] virgin.
I'll be coming off this community soon
anyways for a long time, lad.
Weird people talking about themselves.
It gets tiring watching it in it, bro. I'm sorry.
What do you think of him shouting at the
person anyways? Grievy, do you think he
was in the right or do you think he was
in the wrong or what?
There's so many simps on this community, bro.
I just don't
So many simps on this community.
Someone was like, "Oh, she's a Oh, she's
cute." I said, "Ew, a simp."
A wild s appears. [ __ ] madness. Absolute madness. Should
I make these piggies? Uh, Grezy, these little piggies.
I got three piggies. I got it from the butchers.
I'm going to get so wrecked tomorrow, bro.
Greavvesy never answered my question.
So, Grezy, do you think people on Reddit
dismiss my struggles or not?
These people really need to stop talking
about themselves on this community,
Greavvesy. It's very, very unhealthy.
These people really, really need to stop
talking about themselves.
Let's go on this thing.
They really need to stop talking about themselves, bro. Um,
look at this guy. No wonder this guy
said on Timmy's thing, no wonder women
are afraid to go out at times having to
deal with incidents like this. S,
I just commented straight away. S,
I just said straight away S.
If you support a man who's generally a
dangerous to women, you're bad as them.
They're talking about Timmy here. To
think people stand and support a man
within a second to go up some bird's
face is crazy.
They're saying this about Timmy, by the way. Timmy.
But women are not innocent. This is why
I can't agree with them grievy. Like
obviously I watched the video with Timmy
and stuff, but they're not they're not innocent.
They're not innocent at all.
About no wonder why women are scared to
go out. What about women that lead
people on? What about women that cheat
on people? It's like
and they're talking about Timmy. They're
not even talking about me. It's It's crazy, bro.
So yeah, I don't know how people defend
women like they're innocent,
cuz they defend them like they're innocent, bro.
I mean, these I can understand
if he was smacking some random woman in
the face for no reason. that's not
argued. But they're going on like these
women are innocent and they're not.
You know, this is that's the [ __ ] that
pisses me off. Even when it's not about
me, cuz they're not innocent.
And she was giving it back to him. And
so what, bro? She didn't even seem
scared. I don't understand. I don't like Timmy.
What? What's your opinion on it?
Anyways, Greavvesy, Steven Howard,
no wonder women are afraid to go out
talking as if they're not [ __ ]
Like, you know what I mean?
Yeah, exactly. Like, I could fully
understand, right, if he's gone and
started on some random woman, like some
rand, but it's not that. Like it's
always tit for tat, tit for tat. And
then you get these little simps with
their stupid little comments. This is
what I mean, bro.
She was mouthing off and she didn't seem
scared. Simple as. So, shut the [ __ ] up.
You know, there's there's no law that
says you can't argue with a woman. You
can't shout at a woman. There's no law
that says that. He hasn't put his I
don't even know why I'm defending this
guy because I why I'm defending is
because I know what women are like. This
is the thing is I I know what they're like.
Um and it comes across as I'm defending
him but I'm not because the thing is
when you defend Timmy Candy man.
The thing is when you defend women uh
when you defend Timmy Candy man he just
snakes you. But my honest opinion, uh,
Candy, is that, uh, these people that
are defending that woman is a s. They're
white knights. Clearly, clearly white
Um, because he didn't put his hand on
her. She was mouthing off. And yeah,
about no wonder women are afraid to go
out. Women are not innocent.
Women are not [ __ ] innocent at all.
So I don't know why someone would even
write a comment like that, you know.
So they lead people on, they troll
people, they take the piss, they make up
stories, they act like most of the
narcissists are women.
So why are these people going on like
they're innocent? She didn't even seem scared either,
which is strange to be honest with you. I you know
that's what makes me think most of this
community canny man is autistic.
The way they defend women and and the
irony is Candy man is I'll go out
tomorrow and I and I and I'll get more
out of women than these people ever will.
That's that's the irony of it with these
with these white knights. These white
knights that sit there and defend women.
It's [ __ ] insane, lad.
It is insane, bro. And that's the
maddest thing is I'm the one arguing
against and I'll probably get further
than they will tomorrow. Huh?
I reckon it's autism me, bro. I reckon
it's uh I reckon it is autism, you know,
cuz it's [ __ ] weird.
there and defend them like they're [ __ ] children. You know, madness.
These people are weirdos on this
community, aren't they?
And by the way, that money that Red Star
showed is absolutely nothing. Couple of grand maximum.
Um, again I'll say the same thing as I
said to your boyfriend. Show the same
amount of money
in 6 months. Well, no, not 6 months, 3
That seems to shut a lot of people up
when I say that. You know
what I don't understand with these
people is if they've got all of this
money apparently, why have they got no
life? I I I don't understand it.
You know me, like I keep saying to you,
I took a break from dating. So, I was
just like done with the [ __ ] you
know, done with the whole [ __ ] of it
all, you know? So, I just chill and it's
winter now. Like,
cuz people constantly don't have a life
on here, you know?
Same thing goes for you, bro. A couple
of grand. What kind of clothes do you
have? How much money do you get a month?
What's your lifestyle?
You know, all of these things come with
it when you show money. You do realize that
cuz I could put £500 online right now on
roulette, right? And I could win,
say, for argument sake four or five
grand. And I can show you.
And I can show you four or five grand,
right? But can I show you four or five
grand in 3 months? No.
So what's the matter, bro? Doesn't
The whole thing is ridiculous, you know. Yeah.
trying to tell people they can't afford
a new pair of trainers cuz I was
debating whether to get them or not.
I might go for a nice meal on Sunday. Yeah.
Yeah, I think I might do.
What the [ __ ] is all that about out there, bro?
I'm going to do these pull tops in a bit. Anyways,
save the T-mo for later. I'm sorry.
Tomorrow, not later. Yeah.
Right. Where is this? Great.
Okay. What's it? Yeah,
that situation ain't even that bad. It's
like when I shouted at that woman in the
in on the park in the park and that the
[ __ ] [ __ ] deserved it
cuz I knew she was going to waste my
time again. There was nothing physical.
There was no like what can you [ __ ] do, bro?
She look rehab for Tim.
Rehab required for Tim. This is really bad.
Is it really bad though? Just arguing
with a woman that doesn't seem scared. Yeah.
These people really ain't got a life.
These people are absolute simps
on here, bro. Absolute simps.
How can that Jimmy Jazz call anyone a
loner when this guy sits on YouTube from
the time he wakes up to the time he goes to bed?
And the guy probably lives in London as
well, by the way.
Like, we all kind of think he lives in London.
These people are [ __ ]
The more you you see these people in
this community, the more you just want
to come off of it. They're actual
[ __ ] low lives.
Like no [ __ ] bro. They actually are
just like [ __ ] [ __ ] on here, man. Absolute [ __ ] Madness.
Madness. Ma ma m
These people really got no life on
there. It agrees either. These people
really ain't got a life on there. Dad
simps on this community in it.
I hate even like like that, bro.
No, no, no. Jimmy Jazz definitely
doesn't have a life. People like that
Clint and and Okay. Okay. Let me tell
you something, bro. Yeah. What I'm doing tomorrow,
Jimmy, Jazz, and Clint hasn't done in
over a decade. They don't even leave
their house, bro. Most of these people
in this community, they don't even leave
their [ __ ] house. You do realize that?
They're just sat on YouTube, ain't got a
life talking about other people.
weird as [ __ ]
I don't know how you can laugh at it.
They're [ __ ] weirdos on here, bro.
I'm going to be making some piggies in a bit, Grezy.
They need that power on Reddit, don't they, Grezy?
Their mods need that power because
they're nothing. And I mean nothing without it.
Isn't that right, Grezy?
They need that power. [snorts]
Do you want to go? Do you want to see me
go and smash Terry's face in Grezy?
You want to see me go and smash his face in.
I hate these people in this community,
bro. I really hate them little
self-projecting [ __ ] They're just
all old, ugly people that are depressed.
You do realize that
on here, bro? They're just
cuz listen, bro. Why? Answer me this
question then, bro. Why haven't they got a life?
They're sat on here. Yeah, bro. Listen.
They're sat on here calling people all
the names under the sun every day from
the time they wake up to the time they
go to bed. But
none of them have got a life. It's weird.
You'd ever see me [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm going to make some piggies in
a bit. Like I said, the [ __ ]
I'm tired, man.
One second, bro.
Right. Do you want me to make these
piggies now? Easy.
Want me to make these little piggies now?
Oh, I'm [ __ ] tired as [ __ ] I want to
make these piggies.
I'm going to have to run it by you
first. Crazy. I'm going to run it by you first. Huh?
Where is he? Grezy.
Okay with you, boss.
I need to make these I need to make
these pork chops, bro. I'm [ __ ] starving.
Okay with you, boss. [laughter] [snorts]
Is that okay with you? No. No. He does
it like this. He does it like this. Okay, boss.
Okay with you, boss.
Right. One second.
Second. in there. Right.
Let me do these bastard porkies.
Bastard cutting pork chops. Oh, [ __ ]
cold, is it, man?
That's quite big. They only cost
>> I'm going to just have them with egg.
Look, I got three of them. I got three
I got three of them for [ __ ] um
I got three of them for uh two pound something. Yeah.
That's quite cheap.
I wonder why this obviously is pul pork
is cheap over but that seems very cheap. [clears throat]
One second, bro.
Do you like that? [snorts]
>> Why is that bottle like that?
Why did Why did it bottle end up going
like that? I don't get it.
Virgin, can't you?
That's what I say to the virgin. Is it
[ __ ] [ __ ] sleeping?
of the [ __ ] splin
these people actually copying my my [ __ ] st
my little wordsy bloody
you like that word greensy oh [ __ ] [snorts]
How are you [clears throat] going to lose it?
How are you going to lose it?
I'm going to lose it. Virgin boy.
That's nice, bro.
I'm going out drinking tomorrow.
Well, I'm just warm. I'm just heating
this butter up.
Put these piggies on.
Yeah, put these piggies on, man. [ __ ]
tired as [ __ ]
Why? Why? Why? What's wrong with women in pubs?
Why? What's wrong with women in pubs, lad? H
what's wrong with women in pub today? One sec.
I'm going to get someone to buy. Oh, no.
No, no, that that's not what people on Reddit say.
That's not what people on Reddit say, lad.
People on Reddit say you go to balls and
clubs and stuff and it's a numbers game,
bro. But that's not what people on Reddit say. So
yeah, that's not what people on Reddit say, lad.
They say you'll meet someone and stuff, but
yeah, I'm I'm going to take their advice.
What? What are people on Reddit wrong then?
Are you saying people on Reddit are
wrong or what?
But people read it wrong.
>> Stop calling me Peter. It's cringe as [ __ ]
Oh, the piggies on now.
Look at that guy. You see
the piggies are on. Yeah.
Yeah, I know.
Stick with an escort. But we'll see you tomorrow then
still the same. Yeah, sure is [ __ ]
the thing is the pork chops are not
cooking very slowly.
Wait a minute. Y
in the bed suit with no bed, no money in it.
Why is so,000
that he can't even show in like [ __ ]
3 months? What's that supposed to mean, bro? You know,
Yeah. She says she doesn't want any
That red star needs a life, bro. He's a
sad sad bastard. I don't know how long
someone can sit online angry but will
not do anything to anyone. It's so sad.
And at this point, bro, it's like you
just pity them. They don't bother no
one. They don't psychologically [ __ ]
with anyone's head. They're just sados.
They're just weirdos.
That's what they are on there, man.
They're just [ __ ] weirdos on the internet.
That's how long they can do this for, bro. No.
Let me look. They're fat and ugly people
on here. That's what I mean. They cling
on to anyone that's better looking than
them and younger than them.
That's what they like on here, bro. Let
me have a look.
Where's his fingers?
I can't see his fingers.
Is there a video where he showed his fingers?
Bro, it's not even about fake money.
That money he's showing is literally nothing.
Oh yeah, you can. Yeah, I've seen it.
Yeah, that's what I mean, bro. They're
all fat and ugly on there. They're fat,
ugly, depressed people that ain't got a
life. That's what I mean.
Fat, ugly fingers. Yeah, that's what I
mean. They're fat and ugly here, bro.
You not understand why these people do
what they do. They're fats, ugly, depressed,
no life, no money. That's why they they
they go for anyone that's better looking
than them. Anyone that's younger, I've
got better looks. That's why they go for me.
I'm not perfect, bro. But if you compare
me to these people that I'm better
looking than them, I'm younger than
them. I have a better life than them.
So, I mean, it's not even necessarily
about money. I mean, you have enough
money to do what you want, but you're
better looking. You're younger than
them. Your life is better than theirs.
That's why they go through you through
their fat, ugly bunders,
cuz why else would they sit online every
day and not have a life doing this?
Yeah. Yeah. Pat Mustard. Yeah. Could be.
But the Thanos,
look, look at what Timmy done. He he
went arguing with a woman. No one's
going to go for him every day.
Um, no one's going to go for him every
day. But you know what I'm saying? They
go for me cuz I'm better looking than
them and younger than them and they hate it.
Um, that's why they do it. It's like
what Ronald Pump said was right all along.
was right all along. Ese
little [ __ ] No money in it.
You got a fragile ego.
Little fragile eagle. They're going
better looking than them, younger than them.
And it kills them. They can't do
anything with their lives. They just sit
on mine talking cuz they're nobodyies.
Trust me, someone that's got a better
life than me don't do that, mate.
A lot of it on this community comes to jealousy, bro. You know,
and you got to think they say, "What's
there to be jealous of, bro? They're
fat, ugly people in their 40s and 50s.
They're [ __ ] losers, man. They be
jealous of [ __ ] most normal [ __ ]
people. Do you understand? They're fat,
ugly, got no life.
I'll be having a [ __ ] life tomorrow, Dad.
sat there and they it's like they take
their frustrations out on other people.
That's what they do in this community
because they know they're too old and
they can't change it. They go for the
younger better looking one and they
target these people. That's what Red
Star does. That's what Pat Mustard did.
He probably is Pat Buster to be fair.
It's madness, isn't it?
It's just bitter [clears throat] bitter uh
old age [ __ ] pensioners, isn't it? Yeah, man.
What can you say?
Oh, I've got ice cream as well. Where is he? [clears throat]
Oh, I'm going to have this with a lovely
egg. I got mushroom, but
won't be bothered to do that.
Look at these lovely BS. Oh.
Look at that.
Looking nice and slow.
You're telling me that thing with the
woman on the train and Timmy, that was
the same website as the sideman. Greezy,
that was the same website as the side men.
Nah, it can't be.
It can't be. No.
Nah, it can't be. Cuz this should be monitored. Oh man. Oh no.
I feel like Spongebob with his little spatula music.
You know, Spongebob with his little spatula. >> [laughter]
>> Where is he? I need his little spatula. My pleasure.
These look like lovely porkies with the Lovely porkies.
Can I have the Ben and Joey's ice cream
after the pork chops? Crazy.
That okay with you, boss.
Okay with you, boss.
I haven't had a Ben for ages.
It's okay with you, boss.
Nah, won't make me sick that.
No, not at all, man.
Oh, Greasy is always thinking of my
health, aren't you, Greasy?
The egg can go on relatively soon. Yeah,
>> I might send this to that Muslim woman.
That Muslim [ __ ] that was giving me the runaround.
That [ __ ] that was giving me the runaround. We
might show her a load of pork.
Okay with you, boss.
Is he okay with you boss if I do that?
a [ __ ] load of pork. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Dude, are almost
two of them almost done. Oops.
This one's a bit thicker.
Delete my channel. I'm not deleting my channel, boss.
I'm going to Waxies tomorrow with the Ammani jeans.
I've got trainers coming tomorrow. These
trainers are worth more than any
trainers you've ever had. And you know
why? Because I'm not [ __ ] skint like
you, you bastard.
I'm not a [ __ ] scoop like you.
Cooked up some pork chops.
Cooking up some a lovely pork dinner.
You also copied me with that. You
started eating pork when I started
eating it. No, [ __ ] off. I'm going to
the Irish pub tomorrow with my Ammani
jeans and my trainers.
You can get [ __ ] mate. Yeah.
You can get a [ __ ] son. Oh,
let me hit the oil up.
The egg pan oil for supper.
Do I J?
>> Yeah, I'm not deleting my channel.
You're a [ __ ] s.
Why am I deleting my channel?
Why are you such a [ __ ] s? What is it
with you keep defending women? Huh?
You [ __ ] s. It's never going to get you laid.
Stop defending women. Yeah.
Lover is a big s.
Isn't that right?
Why such a simple
Where the heck go?
There we go.
Oh. Oh, lovely. Absolutely lovely.
Got enough butter on it. Sorting. There's enough.
Look at that egg. [ __ ] lovely.
Just kill it. I am
pretty [ __ ] good on J.
When you going to lose it? When you
going to lose it? When you going to lose
When you lose it when you lose it when
you lose it. Huh? When you lose it,
I'm referring to Virgin boy if you don't
know cuz he's never going to pop that [ __ ] V.
Oh, it's that one here.
He's never going to pop that [ __ ]
Chevy, is he?
Do you think he'll ever pop that cherry with you?
These two are ready.
Yeah. And two are ready. [snorts]
>> [clears throat]
>> I'll give you a view on these. Yeah. Almost ready.
Well, there might just be a time to be better. One second.
Let me take Let me take Let me have a
bite of it here. That big delicious. [clears throat] One second. Oh, yeah.
Very tender. One second. I'll show you.
We have no code by the way. I'll show Surious. One second. Wait.
How's this crazy?
How's that for shot for size?
They taste [ __ ] piggylicious.
Piggy fuckinglicious, mate.
It's a bit hard. That's >> [snorts] >> Wow.
How do I do the lip?
Did I look good? Mhm. Eight.
>> [clears throat]
>> These would have been finished by now,
but obviously my mouth's hurting,
have to kind of eat on one side.
It's [ __ ] stinking it is, bro.
I'll finish him. Don't you worry about that. Virgin boy.
Let's do that.
How you doing? How you doing? How you [clears throat] Hey, thank you. I'm having [snorts]
Steven Albert, why does Timmy call me a virgin? Why does
why does call me virgin? How can I be a
virgin when I have sex with women? Yeah.
That is [ __ ] stinking, bro.
That pain in my mouth is absolutely
[ __ ] stinking, son. Absolutely [ __ ] stink.
Really is stinking, bro.
L absolute [ __ ] pumpkins done.
I know Virgin M is never going to pop that cherry.
I know it. You know, he's not even doing
anything to lose his virginity.
Why would I a [ __ ] virgin?
He knows all about virgins cuz he's the
biggest one going. Steven Howard virgin. Big virgin.
He calls people a [ __ ] virgin because
he keeps looking in the mirror every
time he's saying it because he's the bigger one.
He's the alltime virgin. >> Whoa.
Well, I say better than it.
Now the only two versions that are guaranteed on is is Timmy and V.
They're the only two guaranteed ones. Guaranteed virgins.
He's a big virgin. He's a big virgin.
He's a big con virgin, you know.
He's never had sex.
He's never know what it feel like to be
inside a woman to be a virgin.
I'm having some nice ice cream.
That helps the gums cuz it freezes it, doesn't it?
Oh, that is L.
Steven Howard. Who's more welltraveled?
Me or Grezy? H.
Who's more welltraveled would you say boss? Wrong me. Mhm. H
I'm going to pull tomorrow.
I'm going to [ __ ] pull tomorrow.
Steven Howard, you watch.
No, I have a boyfriend. No, nothing. Yeah,
if I don't get I've got a boyfriend
tomorrow, I'll give you the TV.
I'll give [clears throat] you the
[ __ ] TV. Yeah.
I don't want to hear I've got a boyfriend tomorrow. [snorts]
You don't want to [ __ ] hear it.
This cookie though is nice. Yeah. [sighs] [snorts]
This It's a weird community this, bro.
Is it? It's a [ __ ] weird community, man. M.
This tastes like USA is boobies. Yummy. M yummy. Very daring.
Taking a baby away from it. Mama,
they taste very dairy, bro.
Let's set up a GoFundMe
to help Virgin Boy get laid
cuz he's never going to get laid. Never.
He's never going to get laid. Yeah.
Yeah, LJ is not blocked on here anymore.
Come bring your little mates. You know
you say Izzy's boobies were tasty.
Give me my vitamins.
Yeah, I need my vitamins.
This tastes like her boobies is cookie ice cream
the milk and stuff
you know that's why I need a woman
because I need to be fed kindly ma'am
like my nutrients and stuff especially
in the winter, you know.
I need to be fed.
I can still remember her little booby
longs coming out of her bra. Candyman. Oh, bless. Yeah.
A little Calvin crime top.
Oh, this is nice.
That was my mama. She abandoned me. Candy man. Candy ma'am.
If I don't get I've got a boyfriend in a
pub tomorrow, I'll give you my TV
and I'll give you £1,000. How's that?
I'll give you £1,000 as well. Deal. [snorts]
What? I mean in the pub
on the street they're going to say about
I mean a pub.
Sounds like a plan to me.
I don't want to hear about [ __ ] boyfriends tomorrow.
Well, if I don't hear it in any pub or
club tomorrow, I'll give one of you it
cuz they can't have a boyfriend if
they're in these bloody pubs.
Yeah. USA. He had natural boobies.
There were natural boobies,
not fake ones. Yeah.
Oh, this is lush.
No, she's not. He's got another girlfriend. No.
Candy man, can I ask you a serious question?
Please answer me this. Why do people on
Reddit dismiss my struggles?
Like I'll show them like where the women
have led me on and done stuff and they
don't seem to really acknowledge it.
They just go on to talk about something
completely different and they'll
continuously they'll give advice but
they'll never touch on what I've shown
them. like the leading on the make
believe boyfriend the make believe
boyfriends they never really
acknowledge it. He doesn't really it
doesn't seem to suit them. Does that make sense? But yeah,
they don't seem to suit them.
You let me
really say much about it which is strange.
Seems it doesn't suit them, is it? You
know what I mean? Is it?
What do you think, bro?
I didn't say anything.
Why do they Why do they never
acknowledge it, Candy Man?
Seriously, does it not suit them or something? Answer. Oh, bloody.
Yeah, but why don't they acknowledge it,
bro? Like, why don't they say anything
when I show them my struggles?
Why do they dismiss it?
It's like that Ricky Millington candy.
He was saying to me that the problem was
because I was loving the women's
messages and stuff, but they were loving
my messages as well.
And I showed him some approaching videos
and he ran away and never come back.
I don't understand yet.
Well, there's women do strange
It doesn't suit them, does it? Candy man. [clears throat]
No, I'm a bit sad.
Can you answer my question, Jensen?
If I ask you a question, can you answer it, Tensson?
Why do people in Reddit keep dismissing
my bloody struggles?
I'm not talking to you, Ma. You're
another one that dismisses my struggles.
So, I don't know what you want. What I
was saying is why do they keep
dismissing my struggles, Zenzen?
They are they don't acknowledge it and stuff.
It's really weird.
They just don't really say much about it.
I'll show them like me being led on and
they don't really say anything.
Dens, they just ignore it.
Why do you think they ignore it, bro?
What do you think their problem is? I
tried to show them my experiences and stuff.
Tension, why do they dismiss my
struggles? Answer me.
Why don't they say anything about it?
I'll show them like women leading me on
and stuff and they don't really say
anything. They pretend it never happened. Huh? Okay.
Well, I'm going out tomorrow drinking.
I'm doing some approaches. So, hopefully
I can find a girlfriend.
Hopefully, I can find a girlfriend
tomorrow, Jensen, when I go out approaching.
cuz this is bloody pissing me off now. I
need a sex life. I want to have kids and stuff.
I don't know.
Yeah. Hope I find a girlfriend to buy him
cuz his blood dating apps don't work.
[snorts and clears throat]
I tried it before, but they told me that
they had boyfriends and stuff. Jensen,
I've tried the calfs.
Did you watch my approaching videos, Jensen?
Did you approach Did you watch my little approaching ones?
What did you think of them, Jensen?
They told me to approach women on
Reddit. They said that um women go for
personality and stuff. And then when I
approached them, they all said they had bloody boyfriends. Jensen,
Look, I've already tried in Libraries.
It doesn't matter where you approach them.
They're the same everywhere, lad.
It could be a library. It could be a
bar. It could be a pub. It could be a train station.
It doesn't matter where it is, lad.
They're always going to be the same.
It's not [ __ ] People go to pubs and Yeah. [snorts]
Why do you think it's so hard dating nowadays, Jensen?
What do you think the problem is? Cuz
I think I look quite normal. What do you think, Jensen?
[snorts] I look quite normal, but when I
go on dating apps, I don't get any matches.
Jensen, I think I look normal, don't I?
I assume I just look like a normal uh
a normal person that dresses normal and
stuff, but when I go on dating apps,
they don't get don't get any matches.
Rate me out of 10.
I think I'm like a six or a seven or
something. I don't know.
I think I'm like a six or a seven. But yeah, hope tomorrow. Doubt it.
All I keep thinking about is sex. Candy,
man. It's horrible.
I have to stick with escorts the rest of my life.
Yeah, you either stick with escorts for
the rest of your life or you go Thailand.
Basically, those are the two options.
I don't mind trying tomorrow. It's been
a while. I got some new clothes and stuff, bro.
It's unlikely, isn't it, bro? Come on.
Let's be real.
My [ __ ] gum is throbbing, lad.
It is absolutely [ __ ] stinking that pain.
[ __ ] stinking. It is, bro. It's like
that foot thing in my mouth.
That foot thing was a [ __ ] Remember
that grievy? Oh my god, bro. I never
never experienced anything like it before
or or since.
That was horrible, mate. That foot thing was mad.
It was scary as well, bro. I couldn't even walk.
I The tenants had to cook for me,
bro. I remember when I had to go to the
doctors. It took me like [ __ ] 40
minutes to walk to the doctors, bro. But
normally would take like 10 minutes.
Oh, what's the pain you What's the worst
pain you've ever had, Grezy?
Yeah, I got a toothache.
Nah, no. Candy, man. I had something
called paranial tentonitis in my foot
and it took six weeks to heal, mate. Oh,
mate. It felt like somebody was smashing
your foot with a hammer
constantly. Like you couldn't even walk.
You couldn't even walk. And um
it'd wake you up, you'd actually wake up in pain.
It was absolutely stinking, bro.
And like when you'd think it was getting
a bit better,
um when you you'd be thinking it's
getting a bit better
and then you walk and then bam, you're
back to limping again. I remember I went
on a date with it. I was limping.
Ah, my gum, bro. I got a [ __ ] I got a
toothache right now. I got a gumache, bro.
But I can't take any more cocoonal. It's [ __ ] stinking.
Bro, it's stinking, bro.
Bit of lamb got stuck there or something.
So you're definitely not you're
definitely not obsessed with women, Greavvesy.
Yeah, that paranal tentonitis I think is
the worst pain I've ever had.
That was that was stinking, bro.
Yeah, but don't you want boobs and stuff?
Don't you want boobs and sex, Squeezy?
When I see a good-looking woman on the
street, I think of her as a candidate
for baby Peter Weezy.
I wish I could be like that, but I don't
have no desire to try anymore. I'm just
trying tomorrow because there's nothing
else to do.
I still have the drive and stuff, but
just don't have the desire to try, you know?
Yeah, women are not better than us.
They're bloody well evil.
I got a nasty toothake, bro. Nasty toothache.
[ __ ] hell. Let me try and get some
ice or something. One second.
a little bit better.
Oh, that's lush.
That's what I had to do with the foot thing, mate.
That's why I couldn't work for a while.
I was supposed to start start the job sooner,
but I couldn't start working sooner cuz
I had that foot thing.
Oh, I just want to cuddle up next to a
woman in bed. Greasy.
I just want to cuddle up with a woman in
bed. Is that normal?
I want to make some babies. Yeah.
Is that normal candy man?
I need my vitamins.
[snorts and clears throat]
Can you tell USA
Can you tell USA easy to give me my
little vitamins? Grezy,
I need to be fed.
I need to be fed, Grezy.
I want to be fed
[snorts] by my mama.
Did you like us his boobs? Grezy,
do you want to touch them boobies?
Joseph Ferrar said, "Grezy, why don't
you just live your life without worrying
about money and women?"
Is that true, Greavvesy?
How can you not worry about women?
Yeah, but how can you not worry about
women though, Grezy?
How can you not worry about women
when we need sex and stuff?
We need sex and boobies and stuff. Back
a couple of years ago, if I didn't kiss
or touch a woman's boobs for two weeks,
I'd be depressed.
Grezy, that's why I had to go out to the
O'Neals and touch some women and stuff.
Well, you hate women. I hate women as
well. I just like their boobies.
I don't like I just like their boobies and stuff.
I hate the simps to be honest with you.
Like they're going on like Timmy hit her
for no reason.
She wasn't innocent. Women are not
innocent. Like if he just goes and hits
a random woman or something, then yeah,
it's different, you know? But they're
defending these women in the wrong context.
I've got a feeling this Candyman is Dusty Showbiz. Mom. Mama.
Yeah. The only good thing about women,
Jensen, is that they have boobies.
Yeah. She wasn't vulnerable or innocent.
They're [ __ ] but they still they
still defend women.
Yeah, they still defend them, though.
Do you like Do you not like boobies, Jensen?
I really want to get a woman pregnant. Grezy
just for a laugh.
Is that cute? Greavvesy.
I want to get a woman pregnant for the
laugh. For a laugh.
I don't know. I think it'll be cute.
Why not? Caddy,
no. I want to I don't I don't want kids.
I just want to get a woman pregnant. Candyman,
I don't actually want the kids. I just
want to get a woman pregnant. That's all.
Yeah, that candy man is definitely Dusty Showbiz. 100%.
100%, mate. It's too obvious now.
Welcome back, Dusty.
He was asking about him the other day,
weren't you, Greasy?
Yeah, that's definitely him, mate. Definitely him.
Welcome back, boss.
I don't want to be a parent. I just want
to get a woman pregnant for the LS.
Do you not understand, Gre? I just want
to get one pregnant for the LS.
that basically I caused all of their I
caused all of their hormonal changes
with my willie, you know. Yeah.
with [snorts] my little Willie. You know,
I do want to I want to get
imagine I got that sig pregnant G we
would have be a little baby from New Zealand.
I remember when I was sucking this
woman's boobs in the clubs before. She
was like in the club [snorts] before she
was like I'm not a cow.
I said you are. I need my milk supply.
I said you are a cow. I need my milk supply
and my vitamins and stuff. Oh
yeah. She laughed and said she said
she's not a cow. I said you are.
My [snorts] mom said once someone's met
you, I don't think they can ever forget you.
Yep, that's right.
Yeah, that's definitely right.
I remember when I got my Willie sucked
in the alleyway by that American. It
felt so good. Grezy.
No, they don't. They just don't reply
a lot of the time.
My sister's [snorts] like, "You
definitely want to go out next weekend." Yeah.
No, I'm not telling it again.
If I got a woman pregnant, I would steal
all the milk.
Yeah, I'd steal the milk with the
be my milk. Yeah. Yeah,
I like milk.
Yeah, I've been with maybe two Americans.
That one in Boston was evil, Jensen. She
was a meanie. She led me on and mocked me.
She led me on and mocked me. She used me
for a steak dinner.
It was all a lie.
Yeah, I hate Americans.
They are weird.
She was a meanie. That one. Yeah.
She had nice boobies though. [snorts]
Yeah, I like boobies.
I like fingering as well.
I fingered a woman before behind the club. Jensen.
She was peeing and stuff. I was peeing
and I saw her peeing outside a nightclub
and then I started fingering her
and she kept kissing me. Yeah. Oh,
this tooth fake is unbearable, lad.
Yeah. I had sex with this woman from New Zealand
and her [ __ ] stunk. I was like, "Can
you give me a blowjob?" She's like, "No,
you have to eat me out." And I said,
"I'm not eating you out." And then when
I went near her her her fanny, it stunk.
And I was sucking her boobs for like an hour.
You can ask her.
Yeah. I was sucking them nonstop for an hour
cuz I need boobies. Yeah.
So, we just [ __ ] She wasn't going to
[ __ ] me at first, but then she did.
I don't know why these women go out
Candyman if they're just going to tell
everyone they've got boyfriends
or, you know, like 90% of them.
Tell 90% of people.
I don't know why they even bother.
It's so expensive as well, is it? That's funny. Nope. That's all.
I like boobies.
Boobies are fun. Candy man.
Stick had good boobies. USA had good
boobies. The one night stand I had on my
birthday had good boobies as well.
I had a one night stand two years ago on my birthday.
She [snorts] gave me a [ __ ] as well. Yep.
That was lovely. [snorts] Uh times Yeah,
Grey loves boobies as well.
Grey, do you think about boobies all the time?
You think about boobies all the time. Gy Grezy.
So, Grey, why am I addicted to boobies? Huh?
Where is he? Why am I to babies?
Yeah. So, how do I get the nutrients back?
So what do I just need to find any woman then we
do I just need to find any woman?
And it be any woman then grazy.
What? But can it be can it be uh
I've already been to Liverpool. They
weren't interested there either.
I've already been to Liverpool
approaching. They weren't interested there.
I don't think I'll find a woman there
cuz I've already been to uh I've already
been to Liverpool. I remember it actually.
Uh when I went, they said they had a
boyfriend. One said not interested. Very rudely.
Uh yeah, get [ __ ] I'll find a woman.
Will I? Yeah.
Would I? Would I? Really? Yeah.
Oh, I the wrong clubs.
I don't think so, mate.
I have I've been to Liverpool before.
I've only been once.
So what? It can be any woman then, Greavesy.
So it can be any woman's boobs.
Oh, does it have to be a specific person's?
I can't remember, bro. It was a couple
of years ago.
I went I was by Matthew Street.
I don't know, bro.
I've been all over the country
approaching women, lad.
It was Matthew Street.
So, how how how often will I need to be
fed then? We
How often will I need to be fed?
They're just not interested in this country dension.
The one that I shouted at in the park
had nice boobies. Grezy,
I need to find one with big boo boos to
be um a good candidate
for me and baby Peter
and make sure that they don't we don't
run out of milk and stuff, you know,
cuz I have to give baby Peter some milk as well. Yeah,
the one in the park I shouted at she her
boobs was big enough.
She can give baby Peter some milk in it.
You're not my mommy. Yuck. Yuck.
You remember that one?
Maybe I can try and find Sig's number
again and message her. The one I had the
one night stand with. See if she can
give you some milk. Baby
one had big boobies too.
No candy man. I need feeding.
I wish I bit on USA Izzy's nipples now.
I only sucked on them. I didn't. I wish
I bit them now. Boozy,
we need to stop talking about boobies.
I'm starting to feel something in my toa.
now. We need to stop talking about this
squeezy. You're a bad influence.
Cuz now I feel something in my todd.
So leave it out.
You know how excited I get and stuff.
Stop talking about women and boobies. Wooy. Stop it. You know,
Sarah Sarah's got no boobies.
You know, Nons's um disabled girlfriend.
She's got no boobies. No,
there's that that guy in Chicago. Yeah,
remember that guy I was telling you
about that guy in Chicago?
He's my age and he says he hasn't had
sex in two years
since he was in a relationship.
I don't know how he lasted that long.
That's mad, don't you think? Two years.
I can't. I need my milk supply.
It's a long time to not have sex.
You know, if you're younger and you
don't have sex, it can cause depression
and stuff, mood swings. A few years ago,
like maybe four years ago, I'd get an
escort like once a month. It wouldn't
have to be all the time. And when I
finally done it, I felt better. I'd
wank, but then I just get horny again
and wank get horny again. But then when
I had sex with the escort, it lasted a
while. And then
Yeah. Not nowadays. I don't really not
bother that much now.
Yeah, he told me one day I should visit Chicago.
I never got his name or socials, but he
said one day, yeah, just come to Chicago.
That's what he told me. Greasy.
He must be back there now. Is it
Now I can't stop thinking about USA's boobies. Greasy,
thanks to you.
Yeah, thank you so much, Greasy.
Let me have a little look.
What the [ __ ]
Yeah, I just watched it. Does he drink
every day? That Timmy? He must drink
every day ain't it?
about this Timmy thing.
Greasy, do you know what annoys me about
this Timmy and Monty thing is they met
up, they didn't do nothing, and now
they're still going around in circles.
Like, but they met up and they're still
going around in circles.
So, what's the point of people even meeting up?
Cuz it just goes around in circles.
Do you get what I mean?
And Monty says, "Oh, he's disabled. I'm never ever
going to um
I'm never ever going to hit Timmy cuz
he's disabled." But now they're going
around in circles again.
It's boring, bro. You know,
do you remember that woman, Grezy? You
haven't told me what kind of values you
look for in a woman. Seems anyone will do. Yeah.
Seems anyone would do
That's cute. Is it groovy? Yep.
Women are evil. Greasy.
Say Izzy used me. She knew I was looking
for a relationship and she played on it.
She played she played on it to get what
she wanted. The steak dinner.
I can't get over Timmy's on the same
website you can watch the sideman on. bad.
Timmy needs to get off YouTube. He's
going to end up dead.
I used to like that little I used to
like that 19year-old giving me a
[ __ ] Greasy. It felt absolutely lush.
See my big dick in someone's mouth. It
almost never fitted, you know. It was so
my dick's so big and she's only got like
a little mouth.
It was so funny.
My todd is quite big,
so it won't fit in everyone's mouth. You
need to have a big mouth. Yeah. Uh,
Gravesy, do you watch porn? Huh? Thank you.
Do you watch porn, Grezy?
You don't watch porn, do you?
You watch porn, Grezy.
Why? I thought you didn't like women.
Oh, bless you.
We can't let them [ __ ] women win. Greasy.
Don't let them [ __ ] women win.
regard that these [ __ ] women win Greezy. Yeah.
So, what women do you think is the best
looking woman I've been with, Greavves,
that you've seen me with?
Which one do you think's the best? Yeah.
Well, I'm going to sleep now. Good night.
Be with you tomorrow.