Man, [ __ ] on my way back now. [ __ ] madness. Madness, mate.
The [ __ ] make this country, man.
I to walk a stream. Hold
on. Hold on. One second.
One second. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
One second, bro. I'm
one second, bro.
I'm a bit like [ __ ] but let this Bro,
this guy's talking bare [ __ ] bro. I
told a guy I'd give you I'd give my
number and I'll take him around the
corner. Bro, the guy's a [ __ ] If you
can't do anything outside your work,
stop acting like a [ __ ] Yeah, they
got told about themsel. There was four
about I was by myself. Literally, I was
by myself and they did nothing. Bro,
you're an idiot. I told them to [ __ ] off
and and and I told them to go back to
where they come from. What was their
excuse? This is what I mean with you
people, bro. You're full of excuses.
You're full of excuses, love. This is
what I mean with these people.
Bro, this LT is full of [ __ ] [ __ ]
excuses, bro. I told a guy multiple
times, come around the corner after work
and I would give him my number. Yeah.
And the other people was not even
working. And I stand I stood in the
exact same place. This guy is a [ __ ]
bro. Yeah. He's the same as Nons. He's
got an ego problem.
>> He just doesn't like to admit that when
when when black people in the wrong.
He's a [ __ ] idiot, bro. This guy is a
[ __ ] Nazi, bro.
This guy, this LT is full of bollocks,
bro. Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
This L2 guy is an absolute [ __ ] bro.
I swear to God, he has got something
wrong, bro, with this. This guy has got
something wrong with him, bro. I swear
to God, bro. I told the guy I would give
him my number and we can go around the
corner multiple multiple times. And even
the people that wasn't working, I told
them about themselves. What the [ __ ]
more do you want me to do? This guy is a
class A little [ __ ] bro. I swear to God,
this LT guy is a [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
Remember who started this [ __ ] Yeah. It
wasn't me, bro. Yeah.
This LT is full of [ __ ] Yeah. He
doesn't like He's got something wrong
with his himself, bro. He's got this ego
problem about him and his skin color,
bro. I swear to God. Mother's life, bro.
Swear to God, bro.
>> This He's got something wrong with him,
bro. I swear to God. The guy got told
about himself cuz he started on me.
Yeah. You [ __ ] idiot.
[ __ ] absolute [ __ ] bro. [ __ ]
about big up them people, bro. I told
them to [ __ ] off and told them back to
where they to go back to where they come
from. They sat there like a little
[ __ ] There was four of them. There was
only me. Do you see what I mean with
these people? They continuously make
excuses. This is what I mean with these people, bro.
Little mongos, bro. Yeah. You show you
shoving a dick in someone's mouth, bro.
They say nothing, bro. Yeah. And I'm on
a packed [ __ ] train. I don't give a
What did you want me to do, bro? The guy
started on me. I told him about himself. [snorts] What?
community, bro. This is what I mean with
this community. These people always make
excuses just like this London T. Bro,
just tell this guy to come and meet me
right now, bro. What? [ __ ] this, bro.
Yeah, tell this guy come and meet me
right now, bro. I've had enough.
Constantly making excuses, bro. Bro,
they started it. I stood up for myself.
I was by myself. And you're still making
excuses. You're still making excuses.
But this guy started it. I didn't start
on a guy because I felt like starting on
somebody because they were black or they
were white. You little [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah. It's because this guy has got has
got a complication with his skin color.
Bro, he's a [ __ ] idiot, bro. This is
what I mean. Yeah.
And I'm the one in the wrong cuz I stood
up for myself. Oh, because he's working.
Bro, I told a guy about himself multiple
times. Yeah. I didn't move once. These
people constantly make excuses, bro.
It's the same thing as they do for [ __ ] Timmy.
Yeah, and that was the only one I
recorded. Yeah, you [ __ ] these people
on here, bro. They're full of [ __ ] bro.
I can't be bothered with them, bro. I
swear I can't be bothered with them.
>> This LT guy is a [ __ ] absolute
[ __ ] He's an absolute [ __ ] trying
to use work as an excuse.
Oh my god. Yeah. No, no, no, no. I don't
care, bro. I told him about himself and
I also told them I told them to [ __ ] off
and go back to where they come from. And
the staff come out. And the staff come
out and stood in front of me. These
people on here, bro. Honest to God, you
can't remember women, bro.
Yeah. And then he kissed his teeth at
me. Yeah. No. He asked me for my ID.
Yeah. And I said, "Oh, do I look young
or something?" Then he kissed his teeth
at me, bro. That's why I started on him,
[ __ ] Yeah. For someone that works,
you [ __ ] idiot. You people
continuously make excuses. Yeah. You
continuously make excuses. And he kissed
his teeth at me, bro. It wasn't the fact
that he just asked for ID. He kissed his
teeth on me.
This is what I mean. You people
continuously make excuses, you know.
This is a prime example.
This is a prime example what I mean with
you people on here, bro. A prime
example, you know?
Like, do I have to go and do this LT and
myself, bro? Like, I'll happily do it. I
don't care, you know? And I'll say exact
I will say exactly the same thing. I'm
sorry, but I don't give a [ __ ] bro. You know,
I told them, hold on, hold on, hold on,
hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold
on, hold on, hold on a minute. One
second. One second, one second. I told
them to [ __ ] off and go back to where
they come from and they sat down and
done nothing and they weren't at work.
Yeah. So, stop making excuses. Why is
this He's got something with his skin
color. I'm telling you, this guy, bro,
I'm telling you this guy, he's another
nons legs. Yeah. It's to do with
people's skin color. He does not like it
when someone's backed down like a [ __ ]
Yeah. He does not like it when someone
has backed down like a [ __ ] This is
what I mean. Bro, you're an absolute
[ __ ] I I'll tell him about himself,
bro. And he know One second. One second.
You're a [ __ ] Fanny, bro.
With these people, it's constantly
excuses. It's constant excuses with
these people. Bro, tell your friend to
come now, bro. Tell your friend to come
now. Get this guy on this live stream
right now, bro. I'm going to wait in all
day, bro. And I'm Listen, listen.
Listen, listen. One second. One second.
One second. Tell this guy to get his
friend now and run me out of my house.
Yeah. Listen, listen, listen. Yeah. Cuz
you continuously want to make excuses.
Yeah. Cuz you took an L, bro. That's
what I mean with you people. You just
You do the same thing with Timmy. Yeah.
Let me call this guy out right now, bro.
[ __ ] this. I'm this
One second, bro. One sec. One sec. One
sec. One sec. One sec. One sec. Hold on
a minute, bro. Hold on a minute. I told
them to [ __ ] off, mind your own
business, and go back to where you come
from. And they weren't working, mate.
They were sat at a [ __ ] table. And
they started on me. You people are a
bunch of [ __ ] [ __ ] You do the
same thing with Timmy. Tell this LT.
Yeah. To get his boy right here now,
bro. Yeah. I'll give him the address
right now. Tell him to get his friend
right now and see if he's going to run
me out of any house. But watch when I
get back, bro. Watch when I get back,
bro. [ __ ] this, bro. [ __ ] this 100%.
Yeah. He does not like taking an L, bro.
This is what I mean. The guy started on
me. He kissed his teeth at me, bro.
Yeah. He kissed his teeth at me, so I
stood up for myself. Yeah. Just like
them four people. I told What did I tell
them four people? To [ __ ] off and mind
your own business. Did I not? Did I not
tell them to [ __ ] off and mind your own
business and my trainers are worth more
than the hell out of it? Did I or did I not?
You know what I mean, bro? I [ __ ]
did. I told them to [ __ ] off and mind
your own business, you little [ __ ] Did
I not say that or did I not, bro? Cuz I
might I might be a different person. And
I also stuck it on another guy. Yeah, I
also stuck it on another guy, lad. I
also stuck at another guy. Yeah, we're
telling him to shut his [ __ ] mouth
then, bro. Tell this LT comment this
live stream right now, bro. Listen,
great guys, you always get laughed at,
bro. Yeah, laughed at, bro. I told them
to [ __ ] off back to where they come from
and they did nothing. Am I lying? [ __ ]
the bouncer, bro. Look, [ __ ] the
bouncer. I told them literally to [ __ ]
back to Newcastle and they done [ __ ]
all. [ __ ] the bouncer for a second.
Yeah, they done nothing, bro. The staff
had to go in front of them, bro. You
know what I mean? That guy, do you know
why else is commenting? It's because the
guy is not white. He's got something.
He's insecure about his skin color. It's
weird, bro. I don't know what this guy's
problem is. Yeah. You keep talking about
your friend. Tell your friend to come now, bro.
>> Tell your friend to come now. Yeah, I'm
going to be at the yard. Tell your
friend to come now and smash the
windows. I'm staying up all night, bro.
Yeah. Laughing at me, bro. I told them
to [ __ ] back to Newcastle. We all saw
the story, mate. Yeah, we all saw what
happened. Yeah, we told them I told them
to [ __ ] back to Newcastle and mind their
own [ __ ] business. So, you keep
making excuses all you want, bro. No one
cares. We all saw what happened, bro.
Yeah, I told them to mind their own
[ __ ] business. [ __ ] ugly [ __ ]
Did you not Did you not see what I said,
mate? Well, I told them to [ __ ] off the
little [ __ ] and not one of them four
people that weren't at work come and
done nothing to me, bro. Cuz they will
never do nothing to me. The four little
tramps sat down and done nothing, bro. I
was walking away. Yeah, I went to the
next location. You [ __ ] [ __ ] You
[ __ ] [ __ ] Everyone saw the video,
[ __ ] Bye-bye. Now,
bro, I'm Get this LT guy to come on my
live stream right now, bro. Tell this
guy to come on my live stream right now.
Right here. Right now, bro. Forget
today, bro. Forget today. Yeah, forget
today. Yeah, forget today, bro. Tell him
Tell him to get his friend to come on my
mom's door, bro. And I will go outside
that yard and it won't be a problem.
Yeah, bro. I walked away to go to the
next place. I told them about
themselves. Ugly [ __ ] skint, right? And
they done nothing. What did you want me
to do, bro? Sit there and start smashing
people in front of a woman, you [ __ ]
[ __ ] Yeah, the guy kissed his teeth
at me and I told him about himself. What
did he want me to do, bro?
Yeah, it's a weather spoon, bro. The guy
kissed his teeth at me and I told him
about himself. I offered to give the guy
the number to meet me after work and he
didn't want to do it. He started it,
bro. We're not going around starting on random people. >> Yeah.
>> Him and his little friend. Bro, I'm bad
at his friend up now, bro. Yeah. No
one's at work now. Yeah. So, tell him to
come out. Yeah, bro. I swear to God, I'm
going to end up hurting this guy.
Seriously, bro. Like, you don't understand. Yeah.
They always make excuses, lad. I done
nothing. I told a guy that he weren't
going to do nothing. I told a guy to
punch me several times. You make
excuses. This what you That's what you
are in this community. Told I told them
to [ __ ] off back to Newcastle. I told
them to [ __ ] off back to Newcastle the
[ __ ] and mind their own [ __ ]
business if you listen carefully,
[ __ ] Yeah. Which is exactly the
same as I'm saying now. I told them that
they're a [ __ ] and my trainers cost
more than their outfit and they done
nothing. And there was four of them. Not
only one of them, there was four of
them. Shout it from no one. Bro, who who
am I [ __ ] it from? I told the guy,
touched me straight to my face. I
pointed to my face and he done nothing.
He's a [ __ ] He ain't about that life,
bro. He is not about that life. Just
like LT is not about that life. And
you'll discover when this comes on this
live stream. Yeah, bro. Brother, I pointed
I pointed right here, brother.
right here, brother. Yeah. So, to punch
me in my face cuz he kissed his teeth at
me. Yeah. And then the other four
people, I told them about themselves and
I stood in the same place, bro. I didn't
walk away from that one. Not at all.
Yeah. You're going to catch me. Good
luck with that, bro. You're never going
to catch no one, bro. You're not going
to do nothing. Shut the [ __ ] up, bro.
You little [ __ ] Yeah, [ __ ]
Yeah, you keep telling yourself that,
bro. You don't scare no one.
Yeah, I was shaking, bro. I told them to
[ __ ] back to where they come from. Newcastle,
>> bro. I told the security about himself.
I called I told him to suck his mom and
he done nothing,
>> bro. I told the security guard to suck
his mom. Also, I got another video about
owned a woman, by the way, Greavves. I'm
going to put it up because at the end of
the day, I started this community. I
started this community with Timmy and
I'll go down with him, bro. If I need to
go down with Timmy, I'll go down with
him, bro. I don't give a [ __ ] I'll put
the video up when I get back. Yeah. I
told her, "You don't tell me. You
[ __ ] immigrant. You little [ __ ]
Shut the [ __ ] up, you little [ __ ]
You You always make excuses."
I told the guy, "Do you know why LT is
commenting, bro? Let me tell you
something, bro. Yeah, cuz he has got
this thing about skin color." Yeah. I
don't know why this guy,
he's weird, bro. And then he sees me
sticking on some guy and his ego gets
hurt. Yeah, that's what it is. What did
you want me to do? I told him my
trainers are worth more than what he's
wearing and [ __ ] off for my enjoying
business. Did I not stand up for myself?
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
Tell this LT guy to come on here, bro.
Anyways, [ __ ] him, bro. No one owned me
at all. I stood in the same place, bro.
And another guy, right? Yeah. He was
saying, "Oh, you're on cocaine." I said,
"We're not all a crackhead like you."
And his friend was pulling him back,
bro. I didn't record it. I said,
"Cocaine? We're not all a little
crackhead like you, bro. Keep walking,
bro. You don't know me, bro. I stood in
the same place.
I stood in the exact same place." Yeah,
you little [ __ ] [ __ ] You little
[ __ ] [ __ ] I stood in the same
place and I told them about themselves,
but you constantly make excuses. And I'm
going to put this video up of this woman
as well. I'm going to put this video up
of this woman as well. Any luck? I got four numbers.
>> Yeah, I got four numbers, bro. That's it.
Four numbers and Yeah. [ __ ]
basically, bro. But that's not the
point. I should What the [ __ ] did you
want me to do? There was five of them
and one of me and they done nothing.
You constantly make excuses, bro. This
is what I mean with these people, bro.
Constant. They [ __ ] constantly do it,
bro. [ __ ] [ __ ] That's what they are.
[ __ ] absolute [ __ ] bro.
Listen, bro. Yeah.
I will rust this guy, bro. It's not even
a joke. No, no, no, no. It ain't even a joke, bro.
Bob, no. It's not even funny, bro. It
ain't even funny. It ain't even funny,
bro. Yeah. One second.