All this LT
back in the article now [ __ ]
that [ __ ] ass. This guy
[ __ ] little [ __ ] He's got
something wrong with his skin, bro. This
guy, I'll tell you what it is. Yeah, I'm
going down with Timmy, bro. I'm telling
you straight right now. I'm going down
with him, bro. Yeah, I'm going down with
him. Timmy, I'm going down with you. I
don't give a [ __ ] [ __ ] this YouTube,
bro. We join it together and we'll do it
together. I The thing is to me I don't
give a [ __ ] what anyone says about me.
You understand to me I don't give a [ __ ]
what anyone says about me mate. Yeah.
[ __ ] [ __ ] it, bro. Yeah.
Don't give a [ __ ] what any of these come
say about me, man. Yeah.
You know what I'm about, brother. You
know what I'm [ __ ] about. Yeah. This
black guy starts kissing his teeth up on
me and he starts making excuses. Bro,
the guy's a [ __ ] The guy's a [ __ ]
bro. He's a [ __ ] [ __ ] This LT is a
class A [ __ ] bro. I swear to God, he
is a [ __ ] bro. Yeah. You want to keep
talking about your friend? Tell your
friend to come now, bro. Tell your
friend to come now, bro. We'll wait all
night for him. Yeah. [ __ ] dick sick.
What is it, bro? Listen. It's got
nothing to do Listen, bro. It's got
nothing to do Listen. L2. Yeah. It's got
nothing to do with skin color, bro.
Yeah. Your man took an L. He started
kissing up his teeth. Yeah. I gave the
guy several chances to punch me. It's
not about the badge. Yeah. If you know
you got a badge, stop running up your
[ __ ] mouth then. This guy is a
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. He's a [ __ ] bro.
Yeah. You little [ __ ] bro. Yeah. I'm
not scared of this guy, bro. I'm not
like [ __ ] n legs. You know what I mean?
What I mean when he's [ __ ] man. [ __ ] [ __ ]
That's a [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
He's a proper [ __ ] He
a guy start kissing up his teeth.
Yeah, if you're working, bro, stop being
a [ __ ] then, is it? What the Is that
is that your excuse now, bro? Because
someone's working, bro. We'll have the
same conversation tomorrow, bro. Yeah,
we'll have the same conversation tomorrow, bro.
Cuz he's black and he took an L. This
guy is so insecure, bro. It's
unbelievable. The guy is so insecure.
Proper insecure, bro.
It's not even a joke. It's [ __ ] weird, lad.
It's not even funny. It's weird as [ __ ]
Yeah. And I'll put this video up right
now. Just me sticking up these these
women. Do you want me to go back from
tomorrow then, [ __ ] If you want to
keep making excuses, huh?
Full of excuses, mate. Just like full of [ __ ] excuses.
told me about myself students. Are you
[ __ ] mad, bro? Yeah.
Not even funny, bro. The guy constantly
makes excuses cuz he knows the guy is
black and he knew the guy freaking L.
That's what it's to do with, mate. It's
Siri skin color. He's He's a frag he's
got a fragile ego.
You're with friends. If you're with
friends, why are you clicking on
someone's [ __ ] email, bro?
This guy is full of [ __ ] This LC guy is
full of [ __ ] bollocks, mate. Yeah.
Yeah, I sent it, bro. I got four
numbers. It was bad. It was really bad.
And two of them were French. Yeah, I did
send it and it was bad, bro. [ __ ] bad.
Yeah, it was [ __ ] bad today, bro. So
many sucker [ __ ] Yeah,
so many sucker [ __ ] A funny, bro.
They ain't funny.
We got an escort as well.
Let them contact him. Bro, listen. The
guy listened kissing up his teeth. Yeah.
So, it doesn't matter. Yeah. Bro,
listen. Just was I scared of them, bro?
Listen. Tell me. Tell me. Was I scared
of them, bro? Yeah. You saw the video.
All right. Cool. Cool. Cool. You saw the
video, bro. Was I scared? Was I scared
of any of them, bro? Are you mad? Was I
scared of any of them, bro? when a staff
had to go in front of one of them. [ __ ] off, bro.
Was I scar? Was I scared of them, bro?
Was I scared?
No, I was not scared of none of them,
bro. I told them about themselves. I
told them mind business. I [ __ ] off. Yeah,
but LT wants to make excuses because the
guy's black. Yeah,
that's what it Cuz the black guy took an
L and he doesn't like it. Rob, it's not
about skin color, you [ __ ] Yeah,
they started on me. Them for other
people was not working. Yeah, I was by myself, [ __ ]
[ __ ] absolutely full of [ __ ] These
clumps are, bro.
I'll put another video up. I don't give
a [ __ ] I'll I'll go down with Timmy,
bro, if I need.
Right. If you I I'll I I'll listen. I'll
go down with Timmy, bro. I'll put the
video up right now.
They make up excuses on this community,
bro. How did I [ __ ] myself, bro? The guy
was kissing his teeth. Yeah, that's what
I had to go. Don't kiss. Don't start
kissing up your teeth on people, bro.
Yeah. If you're going to use you as an excuse,
know what I mean, bro? It's not about
Listen, the guy was black. He took an L.
He could have been white and took an L.
What is with you and [ __ ] skin color,
bro? Yeah, Grezy. The guy, he was asking
me for ID knowing damn well that I'm of
age. I'm a grown ass man. Yeah. Then he
started kissing his teeth at me. Yeah.
And I said, "Listen, bro. Like, what the
[ __ ] What the [ __ ] are you doing, bro?"
Like, he kissed these teeth and I and I
confronted him about it, bro. Yeah. If
you can't do anything when you're at
work, stop kissing your teeth at people.
Simple, bro. You was kissing up your
rack teeth. Yeah. And someone told you
about yourself and you didn't like it.
And them other four people, I told them
about themselves as well, bro. Yeah. And
I told other people about themselves.
He's like, "Oh, you've been taking
cocaine." And I said, "I'm not a
crackhead like you, bro. I don't do
drugs. I'm not no [ __ ] crackhead like
you, bro." Yeah. And his friend moved
them away. You don't know nothing, bro.
Yeah. You don't know anything. The guy
started kissing up these teeth multiple
times, bro. Yeah. Where else is this
[ __ ] going to happen? [ __ ] [ __ ]
bro. And I'm going to put the video up
where I had a guy a woman because you
know what? I don't give a [ __ ] Yeah.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. This wasn't
a club. This was a Weather Spoons, bro.
Yeah. It wasn't a club. It was not a licensed club.
Yeah. And I'm going to I'm going to put
this woman up now as well. Yeah. I got a
[ __ ] by the way, paid an escort. But
yeah, that's not the point.
I got four numbers. One of them was sober.
These people always make up excuses.
Constantly make up excuses, bro. Oh, the
guy was at work. Well, what about them
four other people then, you [ __ ]
[ __ ] That ain't a black guy that
weren't at work, huh? I told them to
mind their own [ __ ] business. What am
I, a [ __ ] octopus? [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
I'm going to put this video up with me
and this woman
to LT. Yeah. So, he really understands
this, bro. Yeah. But, listen, listen,
listen. I I mate, I've got a video up.
I've got a video up. It's coming on
right now. Yeah. Hold on. Hold on.
I don't give a [ __ ] bro. I don't give a
[ __ ] I'll go down with Timmy. You know,
and he'll still backstab me. I don't
give a [ __ ] bro.
I had to deal with a lot of stuckup
[ __ ] yesterday. Yeah. Yeah. I had to
deal with a lot of stuckup [ __ ]
yesterday. Do you understand me, bro? a
lot of them, even when they were nice
and their friends. Let me start. Let me
do this video for LT, bro. Because if he
really wants to go there, bro, if he
really wants to go there, bro, he's
going to get his friend hurt, bro. It's
not a joke. Yeah. And then what are you
what excuse are you going to use then, bro? Yeah.
Like, bro, it's not about what is it
with you and people's [ __ ] skin
color, you [ __ ] absolute melt. Yeah.
them four people that weren't students,
they started butting in and I told them
about their [ __ ] self. Mind your own
[ __ ] business. You know what I mean?
Mike, listen. No, no, no. Hold on, mate.
I'm I'm telling you [ __ ] now, bro.
Yeah, I've had enough of it. I've had
enough of these [ __ ] Yeah,
you make up excuses constantly. Bro, I
stood in the same place, bro. There
weren't no me and Mike, no me and Timmy.
I was by myself. Yeah. What? Cuz a black
guy shut himself. What? You don't like
it, bro? It ain't a white guy can [ __ ]
himself. What is it with you and your
little fragile ego, bro? Huh? What is
it? The guy, you not kissing your teeth
up at me, bro. It was a weather spoon.
Yeah. I clearly, the woman, there was a
woman before that that was defending me.
Yeah. There was a woman that was
defending me. Yeah. Before they had let
them in, say, "No, you clearly see it
was a Weather Spoons. It was not a
licensed pub. It was not a licensed
club. It was a [ __ ] spoons. Don't
give me that [ __ ] bro. Yeah.
You know what I mean? And there was
actually a woman defending me actually
before that. Before them four people,
bro. Yes, there was. Yeah. You don't
like you don't want to do anything with
your stop [ __ ] kissing up your teeth
then, bro. You know what I mean? Stop
kissing up your [ __ ] Ros Clark teeth
if you're not going to do nothing. Simple. Yeah.
And yes, Greavves, I'm very aware that
it's the same website you can watch
[ __ ] the Sidemen on, but I don't give
a [ __ ] anymore.
Yeah. And you know what? If Timmy snakes
me one more [ __ ] time, that's it.
That is [ __ ] it.
Yeah. If he snakes me one more time,
bro, I'm I'm not having it, Michael. I
swear to God, I'm not having it,
Michael. Yeah. Let me let me set this LT
guy straight, bro, cuz he seems to have
this complex thing about his skin color. Yeah.
I didn't go around starting on some
random person cuz they were black, bro.
Yeah. Do you not understand?
And some woman did agree with me. She's
like, "Oh, he looks his age." Yeah.
Yeah. Yes, she [ __ ] did with the
other people. Yes. The [ __ ] they did, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. I got my W. No. No. No. No. Candy.
Listen. Listen, bro. Yeah. I don't know
what this LT's problem is. Yeah. This
black guy was started kissing up his
teeth. That is what he done. And I stuck
it on him. Oh, you don't go for a man.
Oh, you don't go for a man. And then
when somebody goes for a man, it's all
of these bloody excuses. It's all of
these bloody excuses, mate. Yeah. You
didn't use the same excuses. It's cuz he
was a black guy and he weren't about
nothing. Yeah. Not because he was black,
just cuz he's not about nothing. You
didn't say nothing, bro. When I went to
Kenji's area. Yeah. When I went to Kenji
and the guy shat it, bro. Yeah. As soon
as I walked in the [ __ ] door.
Yeah, that's what it is. You got this
thing about skin color, bro. You do. I
don't know what it is with you and skin
color. The guy was a [ __ ] He was a
[ __ ] Yeah. I told the guy I'll get his
number and I'll meet him out of work.
Yeah. I don't know how much more clearer
you need it to [ __ ] be.
Madness, bro. [ __ ] madness.
You constantly make excuses. Constantly,
constantly, constantly make excuses.
Well, cuz the guy was a black guy, bro.
You know why? Cuz a black guy took an L,
bro. He doesn't seem to think they can take L's.
Why? I don't know. Why? What is it with
you and black people, bro? What? What is
it? What is it? What is it? Huh? [ __ ] [ __ ] man.
Yeah. And it ain't even funny, Bob. I'm
not even joking. I'm going to watch
Spongebob when a bit greasy
or continuously make excuses. And we
know the LT would make excuses if the
guy weren't [ __ ] black. Yeah.
I had to deal with a lot of [ __ ]
yesterday, bro. A lot of [ __ ] Don't
worry, I can take it. I'm a big boy,
bro. Yeah. But when your guy is kissing
up his teeth Yeah. Don't start crying
when someone tells him to go for it, bro. Yeah.
You know what I mean, Breezy?
You want to go for it, mate? You want to
go for it? I'm sure you remember that.
Ain't it crazy? You remember that, don't
you? You remember that? And I stuck it.
Do you want to talk for me, mate? This
guy. I I listen, Michael. Give Give your
honest opinion on that video. Give your
honest opinion on that video, bro.
No. No. No. No. No. Give Give me your
No. No. Michael. Michael. Listen, bro.
Yeah. We've known each other [ __ ]
years now. Yeah. You tell me what the
[ __ ] going on, bro. Yeah.
It's not funny, bro.
Yeah. So, I got a couple of numbers.
It's over. I threw a lot of [ __ ]
yesterday, LT. A lot of [ __ ] you know,
but I can take it. I'm a big boy, mate.
Yeah, he wants a link. Yeah. Uh,
I'm not defending you anymore, Timmy,
bro. Yeah, cuz I've just put up subbing,
right? I don't want to hear your [ __ ] anymore. Mhm.
I'm going to do this video for LT as
well. Yeah, cuz you talk about people
winding people up.
I put a video up. I've I've stuck it on
women today, bro. I've done it myself.
Yeah. So what? Let you know if someone's
got to say something to me, they can say
it to me, bro. I don't give a [ __ ]
Nothing to do with the situation. It was
cuz the guy was black and he done
nothing. Yeah. I mean, you told me, bro.
Yeah. He would have got [ __ ] turned
upside down and you know it. Yeah.
That's why you're making excuses. Yeah.
Tell everyone about the story, bro. When
your when your boy got his teeth smashed
by a security guard.
Bro, stop talking a load of [ __ ]
bro. The guy shated. Yeah. You know,
it's clear to [ __ ] see.
No, let Timmy come in, bro.
I'll put videos up. I don't give a [ __ ]
I'll put videos up. Don't give a [ __ ]
bro. What? What? What? What? What is it,
Timmy? What is it on?
Well, I'm watching Mickey Mouse is a bit greasy.
No, tell me what you think of the video,
Michael. Give your honest opinion, bro.
You're not going to get blocked. You're
Go on. Tell us. Tell us. Go on. Go on,
bro. Tell us.
Tell us, bro. Tell us.
I'm a big boy, Michael. I'm a big boy.
I'm going to do a video to this LT. No
winding up, no [ __ ] Straight to the point. Yeah.
Like, I'm not these little trolls that
are trying to piss you off, bro. Yeah. Believe that. >> Timmy.
>> All right, P. I'm not going to snake
you, please. I'm not.
>> Timmy, listen. Listen, listen. I backed
you. Listen, brother. Yeah,
>> I'm backing you.
>> Relax. I'm backing you. Just listen to
me. Calm down, please. Listen. What?
What's this py London Taylor done this time?
>> You know, he's he's constantly talking a
load of Listen, Timmy, you watch the video.
>> Take the London Taylor on. I'll take the
>> Timmy, brother, listen. You've seen that
video. Yeah. Am I scared of any of them?
No, I'm not.
>> PJ, do you know what it is, PJ? Don't
take this personally. I'm not snaking you.
>> I've lost money today as well, but I've
been bowed out by the family, right? talk about.
>> Did you watch my video? >> Yes.
>> Was I scared? No, I wasn't. But you know,
>> PJ, what it is, we're all gamblers. Hear me out.
>> Timmy, I don't gamble today.
>> Oh, I'm just talking about
>> actually. No, no, no. Actually, tell a
lie. Guess what, Timmy? One team let me
down today for [ __ ] I had a I had a
treble both score, no draw, and
Spennymore [ __ ] me up.
>> Well, bloody hell.
>> Yeah. Yeah, but that was 20 pound, bro.
But no, bro. Like, I don't Timmy, I
don't know. Listen, I know we've known
each other years. Yeah. And I used to
gamble a lot, bro, when when I first met
you. I don't do it like that anymore. I
I swear to God, bro.
>> Like, so what's the Paky London Tyler
been saying yesterday?
>> He to Bro, it's cuz the black guy took
an L. Do you know that bouncer? Yeah. He
kissed his teeth at me and I confronted
him and he weren't having none of it.
Yeah. And And that's what it is with LT.
It's all full of excuses with this guy, bro. Yeah.
>> Come on. The key done the keys only done
your windows in, mate. That's [ __ ] all,
mate. You should have climbed through
your window and got you for [ __ ] sake. That's
>> It's [ __ ] It's [ __ ] [ __ ]
with these people and I've had enough of
it to me. I've defended you multiple
times and you sn every time.
>> PJ, am I snaking you now? No. Can you
>> No, but you have done when I used to
stick up for you and Pat mustard.
>> PJ, I'm not a fan of Pat. Pat will be
owned. Trust me. But listen to me, PJ.
Can you explain to me what has happened tonight?
>> Yeah. No, I'll tell you what it is to
me. Yeah. I tried to get into this
Weather Spoon. Yeah. And the guy asked
me for ID. And I'm thinking, bro, I got
a beard. It's weird. Yeah. Okay,
whatever. I showed him the guy the ID
and the guy starts kissing up his teeth
and I was like, bro, don't kiss your
teeth at me, bro. And he starts giving
me a dirty look. I was like, no, I'm not
having that, bro. Like a normal person wouldn't.
>> What happened?
>> Yeah, I'm alive.
>> So, you having a drink, right? Go
through it with me clearly.
>> I tried to get into a Weather Spoons.
Yeah. And the guy asked me for ID, even
though I look of age. I said, "Okay,
whatever. Give him my ID." Then the guy
starts kissing up his teeth. I said,
"Don't kiss your teeth at me and don't
look at me like that." And I swear to
God, that's what he was doing. Then he
starts [ __ ] saying, "Oh, you're not
coming in. You're not coming in." And
then we start, it started from there. I
was like, "Whatever, bro. You know how
it is, Timmy. What the fuck?"
>> Well, I beat up a bouncer. I beat up a
bouncer 3 days ago. Now, I could put the
video on YouTube, but you know how lefty
insensitive from there. Oh, you beat a
bouncer up. Oh, I'm getting the police.
Oh, fantasy sto This LT is full of
excuses. Yeah. This This [ __ ] bouncer
started it. Yeah. If he can't fight
anyone, don't kiss your teeth to me, bro. Simple.
>> Why aren't you punching PJ?
>> Why did I punch him, bro? I gave him the
chance because over and over and over
again there's cameras. I shot Listen,
the thing I I wanted to prove to me I
wasn't I wasn't scared.
>> I beat I beat up the [ __ ] casino
bouncer on camera, PJ. I didn't give a [ __ ] >> when >> Thursday. >> Really?
>> Yes. And if I had your phone number, I'd
send you the video, PJ. But I don't
trust you because I don't want it on YouTube.
>> Well, you actually beat him up.
[laughter] But he well I said basically
I said you're a slave to the cocking
gambling industry and he took it to
heart and he thought he meant he's a
slave to Africa and he grabbed me by my
arm and said don't you grab me by my
>> I was shaking I was shaking cuz it was
cold bro I'm in my Stone Island job but
I was shaking cuz I'm cold bro no one
was scared of any of them I told Timmy
was I scared of any of them you know I wasn't
>> no but why didn't you punch him PJ
>> you know what the [ __ ] you know what I mean
>> PJ that was me I would have punched him
>> no but Timmy what happened the other day
with you and that woman and stuff.
>> Well, can I explain what happened on
that? Right. I have never been called
sexist by calling someone love. Right
now, okay, PJ, [clears throat]
I own it. I should have walked away. I
should have just said shut up and got
off the train. That's all I should have
done. Right. I I've calmed down now, PJ.
>> Maybe I went a bit too far, but I Right.
I've spoken to many people on this. I
was talking to the woman at Audi today,
right? And I said, she said£4 said keep
the you know, there she said, "Thank
you." And I said, and I asked her, I
said, "Do you get offended if I called
you up?" She said, "Not at all." Right.
>> It's around Wolverampton. It's very laidback.
>> And um basically to cut a long story
short, I told her about the video. I
showed it. And the woman at Aldi said,
>> "You should have been the bigger man."
And walked away, but she said, "At the
end of the day, you you've done nothing
wrong. She provoked you. You weren't
sexy. She didn't say, "Oh, get your
tongue out, love. Get your tits out,
love." You know, you didn't do anything
like that. But at the end of the day,
I've I've never come across so such a
lefty. But the problem is social media
is PJ. Hear me out. People twist things.
You know that. I know that.
>> Yeah, I know. I know. The thing is to
me, I'll stand my ground. I don't give a
[ __ ] You know what I mean? You know
what I'm like?
>> But PJ Pat Mustard twistes things. Lord
Egg, who's got no life, who sits on
YouTube all day telling people to delete
their channels, but he's the biggest mug
who spends all day.
>> They all twist things, bro. They all
twist things. They all twist things. Of
course they twist things PJ. And the
reason why they're twist things is
because they sit there all day in their
houses with their gigantic earphones on
like the Bojo, right? Even Shagger I
call Shagger the male version of the Bojo cuz
>> Listen, let me tell you something to me.
Yeah. I tell I tell you Listen, you know
the other day on the train with you and
that woman. I tell you let me explain to
you why I defended you. Yeah. Because A
right listen she started it. B she
didn't look scared and you didn't hit
her. If you randomly hit a woman to me,
I would say that you are in the wrong.
Whether it's a man or a [ __ ] woman.
PJ PJ, she hit me in the chin four
times. Now PJ, if she wants to go to the
police, she's gonna be a fool. Right, PJ?
>> We live in a world, right? Hear me out,
PJ, which is very lefty, right? With
these new laws coming in like Mass
Miller, for example, right? He's
triggered because I've laughed at his
content. Even the video with the woman,
I've laughed that right. And I gave him
a like on the last one because it was
funny. I like the cing couch. Now, Mass
Miller hasn't given me a love heart cuz
he's triggered, right? With with me,
>> even negative comments, the reason why I
give them a love heart is because it
doesn't bother me. PJ, I find it funny
when people talk the same [ __ ] Come on.
This community is finished. Lord Jay's
community is finished. Slugs community
is finished. Discord community is
finished. [ __ ] Shaggers community,
it's all finished because all we do is
talk the same bollocks.
>> Same [ __ ] Yeah. 100 finished. And no
offense. in your community. I mean, look
at Mongol. Have you seen the [ __ ]
state of his live stream tonight? He's
>> I would love to I would love to go. I
would love to go and smash him up.
>> PJ, you don't understand. He is going to
get hurt. Let him show up in front of
Discord. Let him invite the Mong because
he I called him out Thursday, PJ, and he
[ __ ] ran off his channel cuz the blue
dot w Mongol is going to get hurt. You don't
>> 100%. [ __ ] [clears throat] him, bro. Yeah,
>> he's a [ __ ] nonsim.
Jimmy, you're running again.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You're not going to meet anyone.
>> You see what I mean? See what I mean?
>> Jimmy, you're running again.
>> What are you Yeah, I am in my mouth [laughter]
about it. What are you going to do about it? >> Jimmy special women. [laughter]
You need money to order a woman about Jimmy.
>> Why did you run off?
Why did you run off? Answer the question.
>> I've never ran off to me.
>> Yes, you did.
>> I've never ran off to me. I've never ran off.
>> Yes, you did. Put them on to me. Stick
them up. Stick on to me.
>> Timmy, stick them up. Come on, Mom.
Please, Timmy. Put these videos up.
You've got Please, please. I beg you.
>> [ __ ] [ __ ] Go back.
>> But why not now? Why not now? Give up.
You've been to a special school.
>> Hey, my name's Timmy and I've been to a
[ __ ] to school.
>> I've got videos of money running off from Monty.
>> You No one off from you, Monty. Stop
talking [ __ ] I've got videos of
you. You shat it in the whale when I
call youimmy. No ran off from you. You
[ __ ] idiot. Everybody knows you're a
bullshitter. Discord knows a
bullshitter. Discord you like a you [ __ ] [ __ ]
You are being used as aim. You made you
got twatted in your face by me, man.
>> Oh yeah, I got twatted by you.
>> You already got you already being
punched in my face. Woman on the
training me harder than you.
>> Jimmy, you're actually getting [ __ ]
money, man. It's all about for you, mate.
>> You did not do anything.
>> That woman would have knocked you out to me. >> Fantasies.
Do you mean you're a fantasist to me?
>> Meet me tomorrow. No, Jimmy, [laughter]
you are a fant
you gay [ __ ] I will
>> You can't even read a book, you [ __ ]
>> I can't read a book. Okay. How do you
spell How do you spell How do you do the alphabet?
>> How do you spell Wednesday? No, no, no.
Do the alphabet. Do the alphabet. I'll
read the book. How do you spell Wednesday, Mongol?
>> Jimmy, come on. Do the alphabet.
>> Come on, Jimmy. Do the alphabet.
>> The alphabet. You do the alphabet.
>> Come on.
>> A B C D E F G. Come on, Timmy. Join in.
>> You got one letter, one [laughter] funny.
>> I actually didn't.
Come on. It's not funny. It's not funny.
Oh my god. What a [ __ ]
[ __ ] simmyimmy. [clears throat] It's not funny.
Jimmy, come on. Johnny taking the piss
out of you, lad. No wonder they're
taking the [ __ ]
out. A B C D E F G H I J K L M N O P.
>> Come on.
Mongol. This is beyond repair.
>> Well, spell Wednesday Mongol this clever
Mongol. Even PJ can
>> just spell. Come on. Discord. >> Spell.
>> Oh, anyone can spell
L. A p L E. That's apple. You nons.
>> You two need to pack it in.
>> What? Pack what? Oh, you're about Monty
man's a packet. Yeah, Monty man. J.
>> Yo. Yo, do you know what's going to
happen next time? It's >> allow
PJ, you do know Monty man got ripped off
by a homeless py for half a gram of [ __ ] cocaine.
>> Listen listen,
>> why are you lying, Mongol? What are you lying for?
>> Someone robbed someone.
You said you're never going to hit him.
>> Monty, you said you're never going to
hit him again cuz he's disabled. No. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'm not going
back to him.
>> Listen one second. Just stop talking.
Listen one one second. Let me talk.
Please stop talking. Don't you talk.
What? Listen listen. What do you two
want to do, bro? Like serious. No. No.
Listen. Just listen to me. Please. Like,
no. Listen. Listen. What do you two want
to actually do, bro?
>> I want to put him in P.
>> You want to just leave it or what?
>> No. No. I want I want to
>> This can't keep going on forever, bro.
>> Birmingham City Center.
>> It's going to like you can't keep doing
this forever, bro. Like, you either like
leave it. You either leave it, bro, or like
>> I'm not the one running away, PJ. I've done videos.
>> I'm not the one shot on YouTube women.
Monty, listen. Listen, Monty. To be
honest, Monty, to be honest, it wasn't
that bad. The train thing weren't that
bad as people were making out to be fair.
>> Come on. Come on. Come on.
Only what I want to know is why the [ __ ]
is Money Mike holding a woman back?
That's my problem. There's not one Jimmy
doing. Why did money Mike sort Timmy
out? He said he sat there laughing at
Timmy going for a woman.
>> That's my problem. How can you go about
me when you said
>> you know what I mean? Attacking a woman.
>> You said you said on camera, I'm going
to wipe Pat's kids
around circles repeating. Didn't he just
talk about repeating a minute ago?
>> You're going to wipe someone's kids. You dirt.
>> No, you said
videos. You said on video videos I'm
going to wrap your kids pat and I'm
going to startimmyimmy
videos. Does it matter
to me videos?
>> You can't go into someone when you
exactly the same. Don't show off the
nons. Why would you want a teenager be
on a bus? You're the n what I said to
Pat mustard was a full grown adult. The
difference is it's a full grown adult
who I said it to. That's the difference.
I I sent it to a full grown adult.
>> The difference is that you offered
alcohol to kids on a bus.
>> I got I got trouble both draw one team.
So it's okay for you to make Pat
mustard's kids, mate. Stop trying to use excuses.
>> Well, Pat must have been putting
pictures on should
>> that makes it okay.
>> Well, does that make it okay
my kids? No. Does he does it? But there
you go. play these games. That makes it okay.
>> It does make it okay. But for putting my
kids up here, you
>> just admitted on national YouTube that
it's okay that you're going to bite Pat Mustard's kids.
>> No, no, no. I think it's okay for me to say that.
>> Said that, [ __ ] You've just said that.
>> It's okay. So, it's okay. No, what I'm
basically saying to me. So, it's okay
for Pat to pop or pop kids.
>> Yeah. It's okay to offend your family.
It's okay to stick up for your family.
It works. Of course, it is. Can you
stick up for your family saying I'm
going to wake Pat's kids? You are the biggest to
a man to a man to a to a man to me. It
would have been wrong if I said it to a
kid now. It would have been wrong if I
said it to a kid, but I said it to a 4 man. [ __ ] listen
no no [ __ ]
what said they want to mong
what I said to >> speak
a [ __ ] to me that's what I'm saying I
don't give a [ __ ] what I said
>> [ __ ] so you don't give a [ __ ] what you
said so you you aditting you a nonsense
No, don't don't give a [ __ ] what I said.
>> Come on, Jimmy.
You are, mate. [ __ ] wrong.
>> Timmy, you're weirdo.
>> Talk to me. I'm going to
>> He's a [ __ ] weirdo.
>> No, you're the weirdo nunch, mate. You're
>> a [ __ ] weirdo. He thinks it's okay
for a man to put someone else's kids up
on YouTube and me to sit there and watch
it for me and sit there to watch it.
Have I [ __ ] have I [ __ ] said that? You
are a sick n Mongol. You are a sick [ __ ] nons.
>> I did it to you actual nons.
>> Mongol I'm going to batter you mate. You
dirty nimmy batt yourself.
>> Mongol knock yourself out excuses.
Stopimmy knock yourself out. Even Nat G
has told you that me and Mike are about
it. Especially Mike. So I suggest being
carefully mong you will get hurt money tomorrow
>> money got wiener
>> money man can't even give a woman satisfaction
>> why do you keep moving addresses cuz you
know me and money will [ __ ] fill you
in you're a coward
>> man you've had plenty of time come to me houses
>> you have plenty of times come to me addresses move
>> have you this crowd have you heard it
this crowd Me and my m could have been
coming to your house.
>> You're a coward, bro. You're a coward.
>> Wait till wait till we go live again on camera.
>> YouTube move as many times.
>> Set up time, pig. I think it is going to
be set up time again.
>> Moved more times.
>> I think I think Tim is going to get set up again.
>> I think Tim is going to get his jaw
snapped this time. I am going to not be
like next time in my jaw absolutely
broke this time. will meet me this time.
>> I'm not going to give him a little tap this time.
>> [ __ ] running away.
>> No, this time I'm going to give him a
little tap. I'm not going to kill sorry
for him this time.
>> I'm bored of your [ __ ] You either
meet me or
>> Yeah. Yeah. I'm getting bored of this
[ __ ] as well actually to be honest with you.
>> Cuz you know I'mimmy
now. This is full of [ __ ]
Where are you?
>> I am going to
I'm going to [ __ ] you.
>> What do you mean? Where are you? Where
are you? You don't understand
mate. Come to And it's on.
>> You're not involved in because you come back.
>> What do you think of the video?
>> That is full of [ __ ]
>> I'm in When are you back? Tomorrow.
Tomorrow. Are you back tomorrow, Jimmy?
Seriously, city center now. You [ __ ] coward.
>> Listen, listen. I'll meet you tomorrow
at the train station. First thing in the morning. Yeah. >> Extra
station first thing for you in the
morning. Oh, you don't dictate to me.
>> There she set up right there to me. Yeah.
>> 12:00 Mongol. 12:00.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I'll be thinking in the morning. >> Mongol.
>> Don't you worry, Jimmy. Don't you worry.
I'll be at the train station in the
morning. You haven't even got the bus.
>> Waiting for you. You been ripped off by
more black dealers. You
>> is going to get his jaw tomorrow.
He's going to be in hospital.
Embarrassing. This is embarrassing.
>> He's going to be getting his jaw fixed
for you cuz his jaw's going to actually get broke.
>> Is George getting PJ? Is George getting broke?
>> Stop this [ __ ]
>> PJ is getting broke. PJ,
>> I promise you broke down.
Yo, Joe is getting snapped.
Swear down, man.
>> Your jaw is actually getting snapped to
me. I swear down there on my two girls
lives now. Your jaw's getting snapped.
>> That's no [ __ ]
>> Tell money Mike is getting it first. Yeah. >> Madness.
>> Tell Money Mike is getting his jaws out
first. Yeah. And then you're going to be
getting your jaws now straight after
Money Mike. Yeah.
>> But Timmy,
I'll put that video up for you. You
know, TV where I was arguing that woman
in the weather spoons. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. Pull it on, PJ. Pull it on.
>> I'll put it up cuz I don't give a [ __ ]
Monty. I don't need to white night. I
don't care. You know what I mean?
>> So, what's your opinion about like you
smell a [ __ ]
>> What? Timmy? >> Yeah.
>> They're all [ __ ] [laughter]
That's my opinion, is it, Grezy? Yeah. I
want to know why LT keeps being a little
[ __ ] and why he's got
>> Because LT's right. LT's right.
>> LT is not right. L2 is not right. Of
course, he is the way you go for women.
The way you go for women. No, no, no.
This black guy kissed his teeth at me.
Yeah. And I And I'll offer him out, bro.
Yeah. If you're working, you should be
kissing your teeth off at people, should
you then, bro? Am I lying? Which you
probably don't even know what that
means, do you?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Like that's what they do,
PJ. Look down at you. But they need to
know that they in our country, >> bro.
asked about like that. Either way, either way,
>> either way, PJ, either way,
>> but he wants
>> Why do you take piss out of women, PJ?
>> I do. Cuz I can and I will. And I'll
defend myself. I don't give a [ __ ] And
if this LG's got a problem with it, he
can tell his friend to come meet me
tomorrow. I don't give a [ __ ] I'm not
scared like you, Monty. I don't care, bro.
>> LT, just go and try him out yourself.
>> Tell him to get Listen, bro. If he wants
to keep using
>> LT just go and sort him out, LT just go
out, bro. He makes Listen, do you know
why? Listen. Do you know why he was
making excuses for that worker? Cuz the
guy was black. Not cuz he's a worker.
Cuz the guy's black. We all know it,
bro. Yeah. He seems to think black
people are stronger than white people
when it's not to do with skin color. I
don't know what is why he says this [ __ ]
>> It's nothing to do with
>> You know, it's not to do with skin
color. You do realize that?
>> No. No, what what what pissed me off
with? No, it's got nothing to do with
skin color or nothing like that. They
all go to gain sources because we had
them slaves, didn't we? But they they
need to remember that white people were
slaves [ __ ] like that. You know what I mean?
>> Cuz if I was starting on a white guy, no
Monty, if I was starting at a white people,
>> sorry, Monty, if I was starting at a
white If I was starting at a white guy,
Yeah. Yeah. at work, LT wouldn't say
anything. It's because the guy was black
and we all know it. Yeah, that's what it is.
>> Yeah, but you can't listen, PJ. You're
just [ __ ] back anyways.
>> Did you Monty, did you not start on a bouncer?
>> Did I not start on a bouncer?
>> Yeah, you did. Yeah. Yeah. Cuz you was
being a [ __ ] Am I lying?
>> Did I start on a bouncer? You did start
on a bouncer.
>> Yeah. There you go then. You was being a [ __ ] No,
>> they was being a [ __ ] Me or the bouncer?
>> No, the bouncer. That's why you started
on it because you would been a [ __ ] in it. No.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So, yeah. So, whatever it
>> There you go. That's what I'm saying.
But LT uses that as an excuse. Oh, is he
can't fight cuz he's at work. Well, then
stop kissing your teeth at people then,
bro. You know what I mean?
>> Yeah. But it doesn't matter about or whatever you make
>> like I stand my ground either way. Yeah, good.
>> Either way, don't buy down. This is But
don't know why London Taylor needs his
mates to fight his battle through him
when he needs to go and do you in himself.
>> Teddy's friend come and meet me anytime,
bro. I don't care. I don't give a [ __ ]
about his little [ __ ] friend. I'll
meet him tomorrow. Whatever. Just go on
YouTube tomorrow anyway. I don't care.
London needs to go and do it again.
You need to go. Listen, you need to go
and do Timmyian, but you haven't. So what?
>> I've done it for twice already.
>> Yeah, the same argument. How How are you
when you're having the same [ __ ] argument, >> huh?
>> The [ __ ] idiot. Yeah. What about you and [ __ ]
LT? Same argument.
>> No, no, no, no. It's not the same
argument because I haven't for ages. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Oh, still still there. Still that amist.
>> His friend can come anytime he wants.
I'm not scared of his friend. >> Yeah.
>> Yeah. But LT, he's got nothing to do
with LT's friend. It's LT's problem to
deal with you. It's his problem.
>> It's a madness. It is a madness, bro. Yeah.
Listen. Yeah. This LT guy. I'm going to
I'm going to I'm going to kick Monty now
anyways. Yeah, I'm going to do a video
to LT. Yeah, no [ __ ] no winding up,
no nothing. Yeah, you right. You just
stop this skin color [ __ ] Yeah, she was
being a [ __ ] Her friend weren't saying
nothing. I was talking to her friend. I
was talking to her friend, bro. And
right, I was talking to her friend and
uh her friend was all right. Her friend
never said nothing. Like this is why I
avoid going out. Yeah. This is the
reason why I avoid going out. LT,
listen. The guy, the black guy got
owned, bro. He weren't on no smoke. Work
or no work. Yeah. Stop making excuses.
Yeah. You didn't make excuses for Kenji
when I went to his workplace and he shut
himself. So why the [ __ ] are you Why are
you work? Why the [ __ ] are you making
excuses for some black guy? Cuz he ain't
about it. It's nothing to do with
whether he works or not. You're using
excuses. It's constant excuses with you. Yeah.
No, it wasn't. It was as if weather spoons.
This is why I tend to not go out cuz
it's toxic. I got four numbers in the end anyways.
Like anyways, bro, I'm not I'm not
[ __ ] She was I was even talking to
her. That's not thinking about it. And
she starts running up her mouth. What
are you gonna call me? [ __ ] Timmy.
This is why I don't get into this. And
and the thing is, Pokémon, yeah, you're
not going to believe this [ __ ] that
there were even people that actually
liked me and their friend come and
coped. It happened a few times yesterday
as well where I was actually getting
along with someone.
Um, what happened? I just went home, bro.
And it's like, um, yeah, I just went home, lad.
Oh yeah, I'm banned for Simmons, by the
way, for calling someone a [ __ ] Yeah, I
called a staff member a [ __ ] and I'm
banned forever. Yeah, what a country
this is, lad. So, I went home. No, I
went back, got an escort, and went home.
Simple. The end. It's why I don't do
this [ __ ] anymore. It's too toxic. Yeah,
but I'm scared. LT, why are you making
excuses for the black guy? little fanny.
What about the four people? I told I I
told him to [ __ ] back to where they come
from and that they're a [ __ ] And none
of them was doing nothing to me, bro.
Yeah. There was also another guy as well
saying, "Oh, are you on cocaine?" I
said, "Bro, we're not a [ __ ]
crackhead like you. We're not all a
bro." I was mouthing off to them, bro.
And I was all by myself yesterday,
bro. The black guy weren't about
nothing, bro. He's a little [ __ ] How
did I know that? That that would have
triggered your response,
bro. You're a [ __ ] That black guy
knew he was going to get [ __ ] up.
Yeah. Don't look at me like that, bro.
Yeah. Even a woman Even a woman was
agreeing with me. I was shaking cuz it
was cold, bro. Shaking. I was stood in
the same spot, you [ __ ] idiot. This
is what I mean. You're always going to
make excuses. Shaking. Shaking. I was
stood in front of his face, bro. The
camera was in front of his face.
You little [ __ ] [ __ ] I told the
guy to [ __ ] off the little [ __ ] and
mind his own business. [ __ ] off. I told him,
you know, I told him to [ __ ] back to
where they come from. Did I not? Did I
not say that to them? But you people
always make excuses.
I told them to mind their own [ __ ]
business, which is something that they
need to do, bro.
and [ __ ] back to where they come from
because they probably never been told
that before in their life. I'm a big
boy. I can take this [ __ ] I don't care.
I'm not ass lad.
This LT is a melt, bro. Yeah. Come and
call your boy to come meet me tomorrow,
bro. Come meet me tomorrow, bro. Come
on. Come on. Meet me tomorrow, bro.
Let's Let's see what you're about, bro.
Come on. Come on. Get your boy to meet
me tomorrow and I'll batter him up, bro.
Yeah. And let's see if you're going to
use the same excuses as you did with
that black guy.
Was I shaking? Maybe I was [ __ ] cold.
Yeah, I ain't scared of no [ __ ] There
was five of them and it was one of me. Yeah,
madness, bro. And it's too toxic. This
is why I don't bother. All right,
Pokemon. This is honesty to honest to
God why I don't bother. I met someone
yesterday. Uh they were from Manchester.
I approached them sober and they were
okay. They were nice. Whatever. But bro,
it's toxic, bro. Yeah. This is why, man.
Don't bother with this [ __ ] no more.
I was talking to her friend and then she
started getting all rude. I was like,
"Oh, I'm going to record." I was like,
"No, don't touch my [ __ ] phone." And
them white knights, you saw them white
knights, they were really trying to get
involved. Yeah. But that LT needs
putting in his face, bro. It's not that
the guy was at work. It's because the
guy was black. Yeah. And you got this
thing about Bro, what what is one of the
first things? Listen. What's one of the
first things I said to that black guy?
Give me your number and I'll meet you after work.
Am I lying? Is that not one of the first
things that I said to that black guy?
Yeah. Don't kiss your [ __ ] teeth at
me, you [ __ ] Like, you know, bro, do
not kiss your teeth at me. And the thing
is, bro, I'm the same sober. Exactly the
same. I'm a crazy [ __ ] Yeah. So what?
Stop using work as an excuse. We all
know, mate, multiple times security
guards have [ __ ] people up multiple
times and they ain't lost their job.
Yeah. So stop talking [ __ ]
And that was And she weren't even the
one that I approached.
Yeah. And I also had it yesterday where
I was talking to someone and their
friend cop blocked me. Uh, Pokemon.
I got banned for calling someone a [ __ ]
Mad. [ __ ] mad. Dad.
I said, "My trainers are worth more than
your whole outfit, you little tramp."
Yeah, but you seem to [ __ ] dismiss
that, didn't you? Didn't you, mate?
And then this guy was saying coke. I
said, "Mom, you're a crackhead, mate.
That's you. You little crackhead, man.
Don't take no cocaine. I'm not a
crackhead like you. You think we're all
[ __ ] like you, bro. You think we
all need people to fight our battles like you. Mad. Mad, bro.
It's not even funny. It's mad. Oh, but
the black guy's at work, so uh Yeah.
Well, the black guy was going to get his
head smashed in. Yeah.
You're going on like we're going around
starting on on on random ass people.
Yeah. That's what it is.
I swear to God, it's getting worse. This
country is getting worse. Pokemon, it
actually is, bro.
You get people that actually like you.
Yeah. They're actually speaking to you
and then you have people coping. I had a
woman defend me before I stopped
recording, by the way, if you wanted to
know the truth. I had a woman defend me. Yeah.
I had a woman defend me saying, "Oh, he
looks his age." No, no. Yes, bro. There
was Yeah. In a group. Yes. Before I
started [ __ ] recording
and I said it's because of his little
ego. He's got a little ego, bro. Yeah. I
said the guy wants to ask people for ID
cuz he's got a little ego. Yeah. He was
probably bullied at school, bro. It's
not [ __ ] what we're saying. You want
people to say the same thing to you sober mad.
It's not funny, bro. It ain't even funny.
And then you get stuck up people Pokémon
and then you call them a [ __ ] You're banned forever.
It's like, bro, like the country is is
in in the shambles, bro.
It is in the shambles literally.
So you're obviously a man's shadow
because as soon as the black guy gets
confronted, you're ting [ __ ] now. Yeah.
Yeah. This LT always watch your stuff, bro.
I'll put my [ __ ] up. I own it, bro. I
told a [ __ ] about herself in Weather
Spoons. I told this black guy about
himself. Oh, but he's working. But he's
working. Oh, is that the Is that the
excuse why the guy's a [ __ ] Cuz he's working. Oh, well. Yeah.
Her friend was actually all right. It
was her other friend, which is always
the way. She drunk my [ __ ] drink as well.
It doesn't matter if her friend was 19.
She's got a mouth of her own. Yeah. She
can defend her [ __ ] self. Yeah. If
somebody doesn't want to speak to
someone, they've got a mouth of their
[ __ ] own. Do you understand? Yeah.
It's madness. It ain't even funny as
[ __ ] It ain't funny, bro. It's toxic.
Yeah. She said nothing throughout the
whole video. Yeah. But drunk my drink.
She said nothing
at all to me, you know.
Yeah. And I'm going to do a video to LT
as well, bro. Like, if you really want
to go there, bro, do you want to do it
bad? Like, if you really want to do it
bad, bro, we'll do it bad.
You know, I'm not [ __ ] around anymore, bro.
Yeah. You can leave it or do you want to
do it bad? You know,
it's not funny, bro. It ain't funny. Yeah.
Or do you want to do it bad? Seriously? Yeah.
Her friend said nothing the whole time.
Her friend said nothing to me, bro.
The country is [ __ ]
Oh, let me get I tell I tell you why I
got banned from Simmons Grezy. Cuz I
called someone a [ __ ] Yeah, cuz I
called somebody a [ __ ] a staff I called
a member of a staff a [ __ ] about three months ago.
Yeah, the country is [ __ ] lad. The
country is absolutely [ __ ] You know,
at the end of the day, yeah, I'm I swear
to God, you're never going to meet a
woman in any of these places, bars,
clubs, whatever. You're going to meet a
woman, you know, if if you go on the
street one, I don't know, bro, but this is insane.
I got [ __ ] locked the [ __ ] out of as
well. Multiple times when their friend
friend clearly liked me. Yeah.
Like it happened a few times, bro.
Not funny, bro. Yeah. That LT is a joke,
Cuz the black guy got owned. Cuz the
black guy got [ __ ] owned, bro. That's
what he didn't like. Yeah. cuz he's got
this thing about black people. He's got
this thing about black people. Yeah,
that's what it is. Am I lying, Grezy?
Them students got told about themsel and
they done nothing. And there was four of
them. Yeah. Remember who stood in front
of them, bro? Remember who stood in
front of them? Yeah.
Who's who stood in front of who, bro?
What do you think of the first video,
Grezy? Do you think I was scared of any
of them, bro? No black guy, no white
guy, bro. I weren't scared on none of them, bro.
All because, listen, if that if that was
the case, right? Because the guy is a
bouncer. What about when Kenji was
working? You had no problem with him working,
but the black guy was Well, then mind
your own [ __ ] business, bro. Yeah,
we're not talking about fighting, but
mind your own [ __ ] business. I'm
having a conversation with someone,
right? Mind your own [ __ ] business.
You're not even from here, you cheeky [ __ ]
Yeah, it doesn't matter what you are,
you mind your own [ __ ] business. And
they got owned verbally as well. Yeah.
This is the problem with people in
London. They can't mind their own
business. Right. Here's the thing. Did
What about when we went to Kenji's area?
What happened with that one? That was
okay. Even though he was at work because
the guy wasn't black,
you know. This is what we're This is
what it is with LT. It's a fragile ego.
I could get beat up by a white person. I
could get beat up by a black person. It
doesn't matter what color they are, bro.
What is it with you? Huh? What is it
with you, bro? And I'm going to leave
the comments open when I do this video.
I want you to explain. You're not
blocked. No one's getting blocked.
I had to put up with a lot of [ __ ] yesterday.
And then you got these little crackheads
trying to tell me I do cocaine. I don't
touch no [ __ ] drugs, bro. I barely
even drink anymore.
I told him, "Bro, listen. You are the
one that's on cocaine. You are the
crackhead. Stop projecting to me, bro.
Do not project your [ __ ] onto me, boy.
You little crackhead. Mind your own
[ __ ] business. If I'm arguing with a
bouncer, mind your own business. Have
you ever heard of mind your own
business, bro? Because when someone told
you about yourself, you didn't want none
of it. So, what are you doing? Winding
yourself up." and other people. You know,
bro, listen. You know what I mean? You
told me, man, your guy, you told me that
an African bouncer smashed your [ __ ]
friend's [ __ ] teeth in. Did you not
tell me that? Did you Did you not see
multiple times what bounces do to
people? Don't say, "Oh, he's working.
He's at work. Oh, he's at work. Bro, get
out of there, bro. You're funny. You are
straight up funny.
Yeah, we all know it.
You are straight up funny, bro.
You know what I mean?
So, what about when I went to Kenzie's area then?
But he sat there like a pedigree dog. Am
I lying, Grezy? He sat there like a
pedigree dog, bro. Yeah. No one's saying
about physical. Physical. Physical, bro.
The man sat there like a pedigree dog.
And guess what? If he kept running up
his mouth, he would have got sparked
out, bro. Simple. Yeah. He was sat there
like a pedigree dog, bro. Am I lying? Am
I lying, bro? Am I lying? Tell me if I'm
lying. He was sat there like a pedigree
dog, bro. Cuz if he started running up
his mouth, I would have went in his face.
Yeah. Like a little pedigree dog, bro.
You chat [ __ ] Yeah.
What did you think when the video got uploaded, Grezy?
But the guy was giving me evils, bro.
That's why man started on him, bro. Yeah,
I also got banned for some for calling
someone a [ __ ] Would you believe it?
Would you? I didn't believe it.
This country has got so Listen, bro.
Yeah. If he run up in his mouth, I would
have got in his face, bro. Yeah. I would
have got in his face. What is it? Cuz
the guy's black. Oh, LT, your little ego
is so bad, isn't it?
I got an escort at the end of the night
as well. She sucked my toodger. Cost me 120. Yeah.
Man couldn't even mouth off. He was sat
there like a pedigree dog. Like a little
pedigree dog. Like a good little boy. He
would He would have got [ __ ] up, bro.
One punch. He would have been out, bro.
I'm telling you,
[ __ ] Madness, it gives I only went out
for a [ __ ] drink.
I only went out for a [ __ ] drink.
It was sat there like a pedigree dog, bro.
Like a good little dog, bro. You know
what I mean?
So what do you agree with me or do you
disagree with me? Agree with me. Again,
you can disagree whatever you want. Like
I'm going to talk to this I'm going to
talk to this LT guy, bro. On a real
note. Yeah. This ain't no winding up
[ __ ] This is me telling you straight,
bro. What did you tell me about what
happened in Matt McDonald's, bro? What
did you tell me about what happened in McDonald's?
That guy could have easily got trouble,
bro. If you wanted it,
if you started running up his mouth, it
would have escalated. Yeah. You're not
to kiss your teeth at me, bro. I'm not
one of your little bed bedrooms, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, you're like a little pedigog,
bro. I'm not banning anyone, bro. Yeah,
you talk about this walker guy multiple
times. Run me out of my house. Run me
out of my house, bro. Yeah, run me out
of my house. That's what I'm I'm saying
to you, bro. Yeah.
This is why I don't do this [ __ ] bro.
Abandon, bro. Man knows where he is.
Come and smash my windows now, bro.
Yeah. Come and smash my windows now and
make me leave my house, bro. Yeah, since
you want to keep using these excuses.
Oh, the guy was at work. The guy was at
work. The guy was at work. LT, you're
full of [ __ ] Multiple times. You're
full of [ __ ] If you're Listen, listen,
listen. This LT, he he's he's like
nonsakes in in in a different way. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Our man says I need to leave cuz
it's going down a really really um dark slope. Yeah.
It's the truth. Don't it bro?
I was so close to pouring that drink
down that woman's face, bro. You don't
understand. You really, really don't
Yeah, I can understand with about
whatever come down. But then when you
got [ __ ] buting in with someone
that's got nothing to do with them.
Yeah, this LT is full of [ __ ] I'm gonna
make a video Tim, bro. No winding up. No
trying to get a reaction. This is
straight facts what I'm going to be
spewing, bro. Yeah, this is going to be
spewing. I ain't trying to get no
reaction. I ain't trying to be no
keyboard warrior, bro. Yeah, simple.
Yeah, it's seven people's been proven
wrong before, so nine is going to be
proven wrong. Simple.
Yeah, this LT guy, bro, he's got you
want to twist things to suit your narrative.
Simple every time. You know what I mean? Yeah.
And you told me about your man, listen,
got his teeth smashed in, bro. That guy
could have tried it anytime he wanted
to. You told me straight, bro. Yeah. You
told me straight that what happened in
McDonald's, your boy got his teeth
smashed in by a bouncer. Did you not say
that? Did you not say that, bro? Did you
not say that? Yes, you did. Yeah. You
think that guy is going anywhere near
me, bro? No, he ain't. No the [ __ ] he
ain't. Like he couldn't even talk
wicked, bro. Like a smart person. Yeah.
Could talk wicked and get you to beat
them up, bro. The guy was like a
pedigree dog. A pedigree dog. Yeah.
People was not going around looking for trouble, bro. Yeah.
need to mind their own business. This is
something that you need to understand as well.
This [ __ ] will escalate, bro. Like, you don't understand.
It's a madness, bro. It's a [ __ ] madness. [ __ ]
They use constant excuses. This is what
I mean with these people, Joker. They
use excuses time and time and time
again. I got somebody to call me out to
go to their workplace. Oh, well, they're
at work. It's constantly excuses with
these people, Joker.
Yeah, it's constant excuses. Yeah.
You know what I mean?
You got something wrong, bro. No, Joker.
I'm not scared like you, bro. Yeah. I'm
not scared like you. You don't need to
tell me why it's smoke and not smoke.
I'm not scared like you, B. Yeah.
Simply cuz the guy was black. Yeah.
It was simply cuz the guy was black. That's it.
Asking me for ID when I'm a 28-year-old
man. Are you mad, bro? Like, get get
away yourself now. Like, this is this is
not a nightclub, you know? Like, what
this guy? And then you got other people
butting in. What did you want me to do,
bro? I told them about themsel. Yeah,
[ __ ] idiot. You make up a load of
[ __ ] excuses every single time of
this little weasel community, bro.
I expect people to lose their jobs when
my man was the one that was kissing
these teeth up. We didn't go around
starting on somebody cuz simply they
were black. You understand? He wanted to
be a [ __ ] I told him about himself and
that's it. Like, bro, you make excuses
every single time. Yeah. This is what I mean.
No, it's not. He was asking for ID to be
a [ __ ] Then he started kissing his
teeth at me, bro. Yeah. You understand?
And then even that, even still, bro, who
are they to start getting involved in
other people's [ __ ] It's between me and
him. And there was a reason for it. Yeah.
Do you know what I mean, bro? Yeah. Simple.
Do you know what I mean, lad?
Do you know what I mean? It's cuz the
guy was black and then the other people,
it's none of their [ __ ] business to
be honest with you, is it? I had to deal
with a lot of [ __ ] yesterday and it
weren't even people that I was speaking
to. It was not even people that I was speaking to.
They were like [ __ ]
the friends or whatever, bro. It was
mad. It was mad mad toxic yesterday, bro. Yeah,
I want to do a video to this LT, bro.
See what he's saying in it, bro. Yeah,
cuz I'm not thick like all of these
other people on here.
You know what I mean, brother? Like, it's mad.
Do you think we just started on a random
person that worked because they were
black? Is that what you really think,
mate? How many places do you think
people go into within a night? Yeah.
And stop talking about people. Listen,
Harry, mate. People went to Liverpool
and you didn't even show up. So, I don't
even know why you're talking [ __ ] Yeah.
You know what I mean? What is it with
you and black people and white people?
What is it with you ego? I don't
understand this [ __ ] bro. You know,
Rob, listen. I'm not scared of no one,
bro. And we are not talking about him
and what he does. We're talking about
what you are writing. Yeah.
Listen, I'm not scared of anyone, bro.
So, like, you're not you're not scaring me.
I've not made a single person up, bro.
I'm not going to get over I'm not going
to go over all of this [ __ ] again
with you. Yeah. People know who I've
tried to meet. People know who I've met.
Harry, you didn't do anything when me
and London Taylor went to [ __ ] Liverpool. Yeah,
I'm scared. Okay, bro. Whatever you say,
bro. Yeah, whatever you say. Yeah,
whatever you say, bro.
Yeah, whatever you say, bro.
Whatever you say, bro. Whatever you say,
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
Whatever you say, bro.
Yeah, bro. So, I'll go down with Timmy,
bro. I don't give a [ __ ] You know what?
I'm like, I don't give a [ __ ] You know,
students that ran their mouth and shut
up when I told them about themsel. This
guy is really pathetic. Pretty lad, you know.
Madness, bro. Madness.
[ __ ] This guy is so full of excuses,
you know. Work, no work. The guy is
[clears throat] full of excuses, bro. You know,
bro, listen. No one cares. Shut the [ __ ] up. Yeah. Yeah, man.
You're not going to send anyone
anywhere, bro. You're boring. Very very
[ __ ] boring, bro. You're not sending
anyone to anywhere, bro. Yeah,
this guy is so full of [ __ ] He is so
Oh, will I come out this time? You're
boring, bro. You're boring. Shut up. Oh, mad.
You watch me. Thank you, man. Yeah.
Cheers, bro. This LT is a [ __ ]
buffoon, bro. He actually is. Like, hey,
I swear to God, he actually is, bro.
Yeah, me and River Spoons. Yeah, man.
I feel I can talk to myself better than
Timmy, to be honest. This LT
needs to get his facts right. This LT
really, really needs to get his facts right. You know,
you need to stop kissing up your teeth
at people, brother. Then if you can't work, lad.
They're not 14. Anyways, I don't care.
I'm not asked, lad. I'm not asked.
Right. I got caught blocked yesterday as
well, even when people were liking me in
that. It is getting worse this country.
I swear to God, it is getting worse, bro.
Yeah, you're boring, bro. Stop repeating yourself.
Anyway, I'm going to do a video to LT
anyways since he likes to jump on as
soon as a black man gets owned.
Yeah. Anyways, one second. I'm going to
leave the comments open for him as