Oh, why have I got this ugly [ __ ] face on my
YouTube? This ugly bastard.
Virgin still a bit drunk.
Well, that was actually sad yesterday,
bro. Yesterday sort of proved the point
with these people with they don't leave
they don't leave their benefits trying
to [ __ ] call up pubs and try and get
people kicked out now. They were trying
for like [ __ ] 40 minutes. [ __ ] sad
little bastards. That just goes to show
that, you know, these people here ain't
got nothing in their lives, bro. I said
it from day one. Listen, these people on
here Yeah. fat, ugly, nothing going for themselves. Ac um
um came across a platform to
self-reflect on and that's all they do.
[ __ ] hell, bro. I was reading the
comments. People trying to get you
banned from [ __ ] pubs. Imagine that,
bro. Imagine being that level of sad.
Like, it's a madness. [ __ ] madness,
bro. All cuz they're sat in Bubby's
basement. Can't go out. It's a madness,
bro. It is madness. It's funny,
though. It's funny, bro.
One solid thing, man.
[ __ ] I got the sneezes, bro.
I wonder how Bob's doing, eh?
Oh, well, that's bad though. Trying to
get people kicked out of pubs, bro. That
That would never That's never going to
work, mate. In a [ __ ] normal
pub. Why are they even That's what I'm
saying with these little spastics on the
earth. They're so sad. I actually went
back into that pub as well. They're so
sad. They got nothing going for
themselves. I feel sorry for them,
bro. I just took two painkillers, man.
Hopefully it eases the
uh I woke up with a banging [ __ ] headache. arms
[ __ ] I'm gone after today. Anyways, I said yesterday,
but probably over. So, yeah, after that done,
simple justic YouTube. really
hot. Really bad. Um really bad
heartburn. Really bad heartburn,
brother. That's going everywhere.
Yeah, I I remember trying to briefly
talking to Cerry and that. Yeah, same
old. It's a replica of [ __ ]
yesterday, bro. Every time you go live
on this YouTube, it's like a replica of
the last time. It's the same retards,
the same repeating, the same self
projecting, and literally it's never
ever different. It's the same same
obsessed people. But that I mean that
happens even when you're not on YouTube. Obsessed people,
stalkers, weirdos. Literally,
man. Hey. Yeah, I went out yesterday. I
got very very drunk, man. I was kind of
on this instant date with this American
for about half an
hour. No, I'm very wary of I just No,
bro. I sent it all day
yesterday in the club and then Well, I
think I don't know about four. I didn't
get anything out the for like, "Oh boy,
hopefully this is not going to be a
Thursday where we don't get nothing." So
then I just met with him. I just
approached this American and we just
spent like half hour together. So she's
here for a few months. So we shut we
plan to meet again. Yeah. It's not good,
bro. No, I mean it was what it's one
solid number to me. So I [ __ ] you
know one's better than nothing. I lost
100 pound on fish and frenzy. [ __ ]
hell, man. Spent about 150 yesterday.
No, I think I must have spent about 200
quid. 200 [ __ ] pound yesterday, man.
[ __ ] Just to get drunk and shorts, e
these people's trying to get me banned
from the pub, Joe. They were trying to
get me banned from the
pub. Yeah, I was hearing it yesterday,
bro. Like, I've got a boyfriend. It
wasn't It wasn't pissing me off, man. I,
you know, I know what it will be like
here, you know, and to get one solid
number. I thought it's better than nothing.
So, and I still remember what happened
yesterday. You're putting that [ __ ] I
didn't [ __ ] it for no one. Yeah. I said,
I'll put my feet where I want and I
stayed where I was. Yeah. You need to
know the definition between actually
flapping [ __ ] brother. Yeah. Cuz I
don't flap it from anyone.
And they were trying to get me kicked
out of the pub, Joe. They were trying to
get me kicked out of the Because that to
them, man, is is is a big thing, Joe.
You understand? Like you you going out
drinking in the pub is so big to them
because they've got no money, because
they're scared to leave the house. They
got no confidence. They they they could
never do anything as simple as that. And
it is as simple as that to normal
people. But with these people, they they
have nothing in their life. And and
that's not even me like trying to be
nasty and that. It's being real, you
know? Like I'm not even
drunk. Yeah. I was, bro, I was trying to
be I was trying to be friendly. Yeah.
Yeah. And the guy was being a dick,
right? And I was a dick back, saying, "I
put my feet where I want." Well, it's a
bit weird. He's being rude. Well, not
rude, but he wasn't even being rude.
Like, he didn't mug me off, mate. If he
came to mug me off, he would I would
have put a glass for his head. He was
just being a dick.
And but to be honest with you, there was
a few people in the pub that um well
only two people that pub. They're just
they're just [ __ ] man. So, but
some people were like in the end, you
know, obviously they were normal people.
We met our old guy and stuff, but I
don't like London as man. I don't like
anyone in London. I hate him. They're
[ __ ] He was He's just a [ __ ]
wasn't he, man?
Yeah, just like a lot of people in
London are [ __ ] in
it. But what makes me laugh is right
these people in London will tell people
to mind their own business, but they
never mind their own business. they
always need to get their beaky nose and
stuff like say for examp I remember
before right um so they're they're fine
on to talk you know
because they they are the ones that get
into other people's business and
Scottish people do it as well but then
when you're asking a question apparently
you should mind your own business but it
doesn't even make
sense yeah like even in the bookies they
do it as
well it's a weird country, bro. I can't
wait till I can get out of there to be
fair. You know, funny is the first
uh No, that was from weeks ago. That's
what I'm saying. He's still obsessed,
Joe. The virgin is still
obsessed. And Joe, yeah, you know, after
today, we're not going to be on YouTube
after today for like two, three weeks or
so. You're going to see who is the one
that's getting tormented. You're gonna
see the one who is psychologically
[ __ ] up every day being a, you know,
um, being on YouTube and being obsessed
with me. You're gonna see when I don't
post content and I don't react to these
people, cuz I don't react to these
people anyways. Who's the one that's really
obsessed? Yeah, that was weeks ago, bro.
I was with this American yesterday, man,
for a while. And she was actually nice
to be fair, which is surprising because
I don't like Americans, you know? I have
history with them and but she she
actually was all right to be
fair. So like we was just drinking
and yeah, she was all right. It's the
first one I done on the
street. Oh yeah, I got kicked out of
this club as well cuz apparently they
had complaints because apparently I
called Oh. Oh, they do. You know, I'll
tell you why I got banned. You know why
I got banned? Because I called a
bartender a [ __ ] Imagine that, bro. No
stuff about women. No stuff about kids.
No stuff about They said, "Oh, you said
the bartender was being a cunt." Yeah,
she was being a bit of a [ __ ] I didn't
call her a [ __ ] to her face. Like, wait.
So, all you got to do is say the word
[ __ ] to get thrown out of somewhere.
[ __ ] it off, man. Listen, I'm not
keeping these. Do you know what I'm
going to do from now on? Yeah. I'm just
gonna go to the website. I'm just gonna
go to the p to like the pub because it's
it's mad. And and and and as I Okay, I
call it [ __ ] I was like, oh, was it
because I was talking to people? I mean,
isn't that what a nightclub is for? To
go and socialize and speak to people. It
seems this country has it backwards, you
know. So, and then he said, "Oh, you
come back in 3 weeks." I said, "I'm not
coming back in 3 weeks." I'm not coming
back ever. You know, the moment you bar
me for stupidity using the word [ __ ] is
the day I never keep you in business
ever again. That's it, bro. They're the
ones that lose custom. And and at the
end of the day, like there's so many
places in London you can go to and you
don't even need to go to any places. You
can just go on the street and do it.
But, you know, I'm one of these people
that will go somewhere three times a
week and spend loads of money. Lay us
out, bro. No one else. Trust me. Cuz
there's days where they don't get busy.
I don't care. I'm not coming back in
two, three weeks or 3 weeks. You banned
me for a stupid reason. I'm never coming
back. That's it. I think that's fair
enough to be honest. What do you think,
Joe? I wasn't abusing stuff. I was I was
just saying that she was being a bit of
a [ __ ] Westernized Canadian. Horrible.
That's what they are. That's what they
are. Well, how was I abusing the staff?
I think I said what to one of the people
that Yeah, she's a bit of a [ __ ] That's
not abusing staff, bro.
What? Calling from the [ __ ] Come on.
But [ __ ] them anyways, bro. [ __ ] them. I
don't want to go back
anyways. So yeah, she was being a
[ __ ] man. Just like they're all
[ __ ] in London. [ __ ] [ __ ] I
hate London. I hate England. I hate westernized
people. They're this absolute [ __ ]
It's like Ant-Man says, it's like wherever you
go, it's the same people. like same
people, same attitude. He's right about
that. Wherever you go, same women, the
same men with the same attitude, same
women with the same attitude, with the
same people that they go for. It's It's
actually true. It's actually actually
true. It's the same people you see like
even the men, same
attitude. It's strange,
man. Yeah. [ __ ] them. Anyways,
yeah. Yeah, she's been a [ __ ]
lad. But anyways, man, isn't it mad? The
first approach I done on the street
again is the first one I got again. E,
sometimes it goes like that, man. I was
not going to go back
home without getting a number. I was not
going to do it.
And I lost some of the fish and frenzy
as well, which made it harder because I
wasn't in the mood. And I still had to
go and do it. I still had to [ __ ] Oh,
it was hard,
bro. It was [ __ ] hard,
lad. Yeah. Seems like street approaches
on the one,
man. Well, it was cold this day. Feel
like it's going to be cold again today. [Music]
Yeah, I went to the bookies a few days
ago. I was in the shopping center and I
spat on the machine. I had to get out
there, bro, before I end up getting
nicked and it I had to cuz I would have
got nicked, trust me. So, I had to leave
where another half abroad um probably
within two three
months. Yeah, man.
Like I wasn't wrong. I'm not saying
like, "Oh [ __ ] I was wrong about what I
said about women." No, they are [ __ ]
They're all [ __ ] They're all
westernized, horrible people. But I just
don't really say much about it anymore
cuz what's the point of wasting our energy, bro?
Stupid. Don't like the one
then. Yeah. within the next 2 3 months.
Joe, I love how when I call Sean a
virgin, because he is a virgin, you
defend him. But when people call me a
virgin, even though I've proved I've had
sex, you don't defend
me. That's not
nor Yeah, I speak to this woman for
ages, man. We got some drinks and that.
Yeah, I actually went live and uh you heard her
talk. Yeah, you defend that virgin, but
you don't defend
me. Even though there's people in
marriages that don't even have sex, but
he's not a virgin, apparently.
I'd love to know the type where where he
finds the time to have sex when he's
constantly on YouTube being obsessed
with me. That's what I that's what I
would like to
know. But no, just cuz someone's in a relationship with
someone doesn't mean anything. No, I m I
didn't even get [ __ ] chance
to. Did I get I got a boyfriend
yesterday? I definitely got that.
Definitely definitely got that about I
think I got
it. Yeah, [ __ ] three times maybe
before getting hit that bug.
Yeah. Yeah, I did. Definitely did
imaginary boyfriend in it,
Joe. It's like they're It's like they're
NPCs. Do you like the Guinness though?
It's like they're actual NPCs.
And then the other ones, right, they
just had like no
enthusiasm. They've all got imaginary
boyfriends. It's crazy, is it, bro?
Imaginary Casper the ghost boyfriends in the [ __ ]
madness. It is mad.
She wondering it, bro. [ __ ]
Yeah. Oh, I did speak to American as
well. She's been a [ __ ] as well. They're all [ __ ]
man. I was telling these people in
Canada as well about it as well. They're
all [ __ ] It doesn't matter where from
where they're from. Canada,
America. That American seemed nice. I
don't know why. Maybe she's she was I
don't know. America, Canada,
England, Australia, they're all the
same, bro. They're all the same. The
only The only the only place they're not
like that is like [ __ ] Asia, the
whole continent of Asia, cuz they're not
addicted to Tik Tok. They're not
addicted addicted to [ __ ] Instagram.
They're the only kind of different people you'll
find, you know? It's a madness.
I always end up spending more than I
wanted to when I go out though. It's not
good, man. It's not
good. Especially when you're meant to be
[ __ ] saving money, you know? Yeah. Yeah,
man. You don't answer my question, Joe.
So, why don't you defend me when these
people call me a virgin, even though I
prove I've had sex? when Sean has never
proved he's had sex, all he's shown is
his downy ugly
girlfriend. Like, it's mad. So, because
he's got a fat, ugly girlfriend, that
proves that he's had sex. No, bro.
There's people that are in relationships
that don't even have a dick. There's a
guy that had to get his dick removed.
Listen, I'm telling you, [ __ ]
he is a virgin. Yeah, I'm telling you,
he's a virgin. Like even even in normal
circumstances, if people in
relationships and they have sex, he's
never had sex. He's the biggest virgin
of all time going, you know, people in
relationships that don't even have sex
anymore. People in relationships that
don't have a dick, you know, like, and
it's true as well. [ __ ] off. That
doesn't prove anything. He's a virgin.
And he's always been one. Typical
virgin. He is, mate. typical
virgin. That's why he calls me one
because he's a virgin himself. The
biggest one going. So he know all about it.
Yeah. Well, I lost 120
yesterday. Jesus, I'm tired,
bro. I'm [ __ ]
knacking. Yeah, I just took some pain
when I woke up.
Yeah, Terry. These people don't torment
me. They torment themselves. Think of
it, bro. I don't even need to be on
YouTube and they're obsessed with me
every day. They don't torment no one.
They're little keyboard warriors, just
like my niece could
be. My niece could be a keyboard warrior
at six, seven years [ __ ] age. You
know what I'm saying?
Oh, I got Laney. Um, a mother's uh I was
going to I was going to say I've got
Laney, but uh yeah, she might be
watching, so it'll kind of give it
away. Oops. Never mind.
Yeah. Oops. Never mind.
Why do you seem to get more success on
the street, Joe? Eh, some madness.
E, I think she literally just got here
from America, I think. Oh, no. Not another one, eh?
No, not is what it is, eh?
matter. I don't really speak to anyone.
I don't speak to any of them anymore. I just don't be
honest. But look how jealous they were
of me just going for for a drink in the
pub yesterday. Like that triggered them.
What? And that's how you like I don't
want to keep repeating myself, but
that's like that's how you know these
people ain't got nothing in their lives
because they were trying to get trying
to get me kicked out of the pub. Joe,
they were trying to get me kicked out of
pub, you know. [ __ ] you could just
tell, bro. These little basement
dwellers was just sat there. These little
[ __ ] Yeah, they're [ __ ] They're
such [ __ ] man. They are. It's such a
It is such a [ __ ] disabled community.
Why do you think you you know you can't
really be on it for longer than like 3
days? It's a proper [ __ ] community, man.
Yeah, there's a proper disabled community. Yeah.
I did eat before I went to bed. I woke
up a heartburn. Well, having a heartburn
throughout the night to be fair.
Yikes. Do you think Virgin Sean will ever
go? Yeah, it's I know. It's a madness,
isn't it? It's a madness. They're
[ __ ] They're [ __ ] spastnics.
They're dowies, bro. honestly. And and
and yeah, that's what I don't get. They
they want content, but then they get
your channel banned and then ultimately
they stop getting the
content. These people were abused as
children. They were neglected as
children. But we all knew no Sean was
starved by his mom, which is why he's on
YouTube being dead obsessed because he
was starved by his mother, you know, and
put in the hospital. True story. Yeah,
they want content. And then they also
your channel banned as well. But yeah,
they're they're [ __ ]
proxmatastics. Like I said, these people
are still obsessed with me even when I'm not on
YouTube. So I live in their heads. I
actually live in their
head. Cuz you can't say it's for
reaction, Joe. Because even when you
don't react to them, they still do
it. They will still do it. Even if
you're not watching, even when you're
not reacting, they will still do it.
That's the difference between me and Timmy. You understand?
Yeah, mate. You could just tell they
were sat there in their little basement
jealous of somebody drinking a p
pine cuz their anxieties don't
Yeah. Yeah. But I think the people that
want him back are the ones that didn't
dox him. I think that's the whole point.
Yeah, it's just the it's just a gay
community, bro. Embarrassing community
for the self-reflectors
show. What do you think of that, Joe? Little
self-reflectives. Little self
projectors. But why are they so obsessed
with me, Joe? I don't understand, man.
It's kind of creepy cuz they don't
torment no one. They don't ruin anyone's
life. It's just cringy, you know? They
don't do anything but ruin their ruin
their whole life. So ruin their own
life, man. The day somebody mind went
free to myself, that's [ __ ] madness,
bro. Like they don't torment no one.
They don't psychologically [ __ ] no one.
No trial, no Sean. I don't know why I
say they do. They're the ones that are
psychologically [ __ ] in their brain
every day when they can't shut up about
you. you realize they're the ones being
tormented. Think of it, bro. You've only
got to react to them or respond to them
when you're on YouTube. They have to
battle with jealousy every single day of
their life. They have to battle through
jealousy of you and how you're better
than them in every way. And it and it
and it and it kills them every day,
whether they're on YouTube or not. Like,
think of it. They're the ones that are
psychologically the ones suffering.
Nobody else. Nobody else is
psychologically getting [ __ ] up. When
is it? I'm not sure,
man. Do you mean like approaching or
just like out of like do you mean
approaching or going out of London or
what? Probably not in England. I'll
probably scrap England,
man. Thought I'll probably scrap England.
Yeah, the weather's going to [ __ ] again.
I don't know, man.
might get a breakfast
today. I think I need one, man. I don't know,
man. I spent a lot of money yesterday, so um
yeah, I don't know, bro. [ __ ] No, mate.
Yeah. Well, when I meet this American
again and if it goes if it goes well,
I'll be going back to America with her.
I take me back with with you. You know, no danger.
Yeah. You don't answer any of my
questions. You ask me question, you
don't answer to any of
mine for some
reason. Yeah, Blackpool once and for
all, bro. We'll get round to it. We'll
it. I don't know what I'm expecting to get in
Blackpool to be
fair. Uh, big [ __ ] So,
um, why are these people so obsessed
with me? Even when I don't react to them
and even when I don't watch them, why
are they so
obsessed? Oh [ __ ]
The pub I like has not opened yet.
Yeah. No, no, no, no, no, no. Okay,
okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay. So,
okay. Right. So, let's get this let's
get this straight. So you will spend all
your life every
day trying to get a twominut trying to
annoy somebody to get a two-minute
reaction. Bro, that only says something
about your life, no one else's. So you
will spend all day doing community post,
video, community post, community post,
and you will do it right just to get a one minute
reaction. Bro, is that an achievement?
Like the difference is is that people
used to do it to Timmy because Timmy
used to react every time and it was
funny. You know what I'm saying? These
people will do it nonstop, non-stop,
non-stop. And even though And that's how
you know they're sad because they will
do it even when they don't get a
reaction in hopes they do get a
reaction. They would do it for 10 years
just to get reaction cuz they got [ __ ]
all going for themselves. It's like when
you try and tell me, Joe, how, oh,
Sean's um had sex, but he hasn't had
sex. But he hasn't. He hasn't had sex
because he has no time to have sex. He's
on YouTube every
day. Yeah, of course. Like, think of
think of Virgin Shaw, right? And he is a
[ __ ] virgin. He's three years older
than me. Never been abroad, never been
on a plane, never had sex, never even
left England, period. Like, imagine
that. That's no achievement for a
[ __ ] 30 year
old, 2 and a half years older than
me. No money, no nothing. Think about
it. They got nothing going for
themselves. Literally nothing. And and
them people that tried to call the pub
to get me kicked out like that would
ever work. You didn't even know what pub
I was in either. So try
again. Little basement dwellers. Little
dwellers. That's what I call him, man. Yes,
mad. No, he won't always have the
relationship because I've had normal
women. No, Joe. No. No. Because I have
had chances to be in a relationship. And
I would rather be in no relationship
than be in a relationship with a Downey,
a special needer. I'd rather not be in a
relationship with somebody that's
special needs and can't even string a
sentence together, you know? So, even if
I had a girlfriend, you'd still tell me
I don't have a girlfriend, so it doesn't
matter. Like, mate, I basically had one
over the summer, but you're still going
to tell me I don't have one. So it's
like no matter what people show you,
man, you will still tell them that they
don't have one. Mate, listen. I could
win the lottery today, be in a
relationship, and you will be like,
you're a virgin who's never had a
girlfriend. That's literally what you
would say. How hard it is to keep a
relationship, mate. He doesn't keep a
relationship, lad. Yeah, he's in my
head. Yeah. How hard it is to keep a
relationship. He doesn't keep the
relationship because he's on you, mate.
He's with a Listen, he's with a
[ __ ] He's not with a normal woman.
Yeah. And even if I had a girlfriend,
you'd still tell me I don't have a
girlfriend. You This is what you little
mongos do on here. You selfreflect.
Think of it. Right. Sean is unhappy with
his sexist relationship. Why do you
think he stalks Morgan? Why do you think
he can't get Morgan out of his head?
Because he knows that I've had better
women than him. And it kills him. And it
kills him every day. He hates the fact
that I'm better looking, had more women,
and had more money than him. You can
talk about a relationship all you want.
He hasn't been with others. He is a
[ __ ] virgin. Listen, he says that
he's been with this person for 3
years. Do I have kids? No. Welcome to
the channel. No. I was speaking to this
American about kids yesterday who I was
with for like 30 minutes. She seemed all
right, but time will tell, eh?
I don't really like them though. To be
honest with you, Kad Can Canadian women
are the worst to be honest with you.
They're abs if you're watching this,
you're a [ __ ] Yeah, Brooke, if you're
watching this, [ __ ] you.
Yeah, you better women, but they haven't
lasted. It doesn't matter, mate. I'd
rather Listen, I would rather have
normal women that didn't last than be
with a disabled woman. I'd rather have
nothing. Do you not understand that? I
would rather have nothing than have a
disabled woman. Do you think I go out on
the street approaching disabled women? I
would rather have nothing and have had a
and and had a few short-term
things, you know? I would rather have
nothing. I'd rather be sat there with
[ __ ] all to be
honest. So, it's not the fact he's in a
relationship and he's or he's not in a
relationship. It's who he's in a
with. It's who he's you. I've already
been in love, mate. I've experienced
love and I would rather have nothing
than have a special
leader. Who is this Nick, by the way?
I'd rather have nothing. So, it's not
the fact he's in a relationship. He's
not in a relationship. It's who's he who
is he in a relationship with? Joe, why
don't you tell everybody who he's in a
relationship with? Yeah. And I think
that will narrow it down.
Yeah, I've had way better. I've had way
better women than that virgin. But bro,
listen, I'll give you example. I've
shown all of you money. I've shown all
of you me I've shown all of you like me
having sex and you still call me a skin
virgin. So like you'll come up with
something different, mate. You will come
up with something
different. And I was basically in a
relationship last last year. Not like a
full-on one, but I was seeing somebody
and banging them like every other day.
But I guess that doesn't count, does
it? Yeah, it doesn't make sense, bro. It really
doesn't. It's very hard in these westernized countries,
Nicks. I come across a few [ __ ] yesterday. Yeah,
London. Yeah, Brooke, if you're watching
this from Canada, Canadian women are
[ __ ] It's time and place. So they
call you skint when you're raging and
you've lost money, for example. No, they
do it every day, mate. Cuz they're skint
themselves. Look, I give you an example,
man. They tried to get me banned from
the pub. Yeah, that says a lot about
their lives. And they didn't know what
pub I was in. And they'll never know
what pub I was in. They don't know
places that I go. Even all the place I
go. So again, these people must be skin.
If they're the ones that are sat at home
doing all of this, there's something
wrong with their lives, bro. I'm telling you.
It just triggers them. Anything you do
triggers them. It could be traveling,
steak, gym, [ __ ] drinking in a
[ __ ] pub. It It triggers them because
it cuz they don't have no life, you know? Yeah,
man. I don't think it's going to happen in this
country. But yeah, and and the reason he
calls me ugly Joe is because he knows
I'm better looking than him. Deep down,
he knows I'm way better looking than him
and I've got more money than him and
I've been and I've had more women than
him. Better women than him. Doesn't
matter whether it's lasted or not. It
doesn't really matter, mate. Lasted
didn't last. The point still stands, you know,
like I've been abroad.
I've been on planes. He
hasn't. So, who's the one that's really winning?
yeah, I can tell you an account, Joe.
Yeah. It's called All Night
Mike. Yeah. And he does video after
video after video. And even though I
don't react to him, I don't even go on
his channel. But the rare time I do go
on it, it's the same old,
bro. It's the same old. And I'm
thinking, bro, what is wrong with your
life, man? The fact that you're doing
this every day on YouTube just to get a
one minute reaction. And then what
happens when you get the
reaction? Like, it's all well and good
getting the reaction, right? Yeah. I
think what the point I'm trying to make
is the time and effort that they spend
trying to get your
reaction, you know?
Yeah, you can.
Yeah. Yeah, Nick, she
can. I want a baby with this French
woman and I'm I would call it Pierre.
Peter in French. I actually would I'd call it Pierre. [Music]
Yeah, I would call it
PM. Do you know what's so mad is
like the friend French people are rude.
It's either they're very rude or they're
very nice and outgoing. It's it's
there's no like in between. They're It's
very weird, man. But all of the French
women are trolls. Like I've dealt with
like about four or five of them and it's
not even like they're even [ __ ]
French. It's crazy, man. Like they they're very
like they're either very rude or very
nice and trolling you. Like there's no
in between. They're [ __ ] man. I hate Canadian women, me,
but I'm speaking to this French woman. She seems
nice. But it's I think Canadian women
are the worst. Me
personally, yeah, that bartender was a bit stuck
up. Um, they're all they're all stuck
up, man. But yeah, Canadian women
are I do want to go Canada though. I do
Canada. I don't like the people. But
yeah, that's where Britney was from. The
one that rejected children. Britney from Canada.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, it's hard mixed uh to find someone nowadays
like cuz um uh obviously the dating apps
don't work and stuff so you kind of have
to like go out and approach people but
when you approach
people most of the time they just
pretend they got boyfriends or like give
you the runaround. Like I was in a ball
yesterday approaching. I think I got
like I got a boyfriend like three times, you
know, like three
times. But women just have to exist. I
had a nose bleed
yesterday. Straight weirdly
enough. Yeah. Would anything kills that
virgin? Yeah. I will find Nah, bro.
You're not, you probably won't find
someone. If you if you was going to find
someone, you would have found someone by
now. And it doesn't even matter whether
you do or you don't anyways. But I'm
trying to say that's the reality of
it. You in order for me, like if I was
seriously trying to find someone, I
would have to go out I would have to go
out approaching every day. I'd have to
make it a full-time
job. And that's that's serious [ __ ]
bro. You know, I'd have to make it a full-time job.
And yeah, I'd have to make it a
full-time job. That's that's it in
it. But yeah, don't care,
man. Let's just hope this American is
not a bullshitter. Yeah. [ __ ] you, Brook
from Canada, you [ __ ]
[ __ ] She's like, I'll go get some help, PJ.
[ __ ] you, man. [ __ ]
idiot. Brooklyn, Canada. Bless you. Bless
you. But no, I think I think Pierre from
Paris would be the cutest him meeting
his little baguette
Joe. His little baguette in his little
hand by the Eiffel Tower. A what a lovely sight.
What a lovely site, mate.
Yeah. Yeah. It's crazy,
man. But yeah, so you're going to bother
every So you're going to bother somebody
on YouTube every day until you get a
reaction. Bro, what does that say about your
life? What does that say? And the thing
is, Joe, you know, with people like
Nons, you do realize that posters are
not going to work. They will work, but
they're not going to work long term,
right? The only thing that will
work is if he was dead or in
prison, that's what somebody said to me
before, and it's the truth. Unless he
was dead or in prison, he will never
stop. Even if he got a restrainer, he
would never stop. He's his autism
is out of control. Like you think Timmy
and and that's why certain that's why
people like him need
incarcerating and sectioning. Why do you
think people get
sectioned? Where did he get his bad
autism from? I wonder,
man. Don't think his dad had it to that
level and his mom probably didn't have
it. Where did his autism come
from? It's crazy. It's so bad. It's so
it's like you'll meet
somebody once. Bear with me, right?
Because you're going to say that I've
done it, right? When they were basically
a kid 11 years ago and they're still
obsessed. They've got videos like, "Bro,
with the Morgan thing, I allowed it
after a while, you know, and I thought,
this was a woman. This was not a man."
And like, you was intimate with them.
But that never went on more than [ __ ]
two years. And then you just gave it a
rest after a while. This little virgin
never stops. This is This is exactly
what I'm trying to say to you. This
virgin never ever
stops. So, is he gay? Is he jealous of
you? What What is it like? I I really
really really really want to
know. Gay jealous wants to [ __ ] you.
What is it?
I mean, I'd love to [ __ ] some people,
but you would see you don't see me
obsessed every [ __ ] day, you
know? What do you
think? It's weird,
eh? Yeah, that would stop it long time to be
fair. Oh, I told Chase about himself
yesterday as well. I said, "Listen, any
if I find out that you snagged me, I'm
going to come back to Wales and I'm
going to put up posters of you. Let's
see how big you are four years down the
line when you're running to train
stations where you know I'm not." I told
him as well, bro, like you are so lucky
that you did not tell me where you and
Nons was. I'd beat you both with one
hand. That's how bad it is. Like, I
would beat them both with one hand,
lad. It's not even a [ __ ] joke. I
would smash them both up at the same time.
Sorry the joke.
Yeah, man. He's [ __ ] n bro. This is
wicked. Yeah, it's the
truth, man. This this place is
weird. Yeah, it's weird,
lad. So, I'm [ __ ] I can't even go
back to sleep. Wait for this [ __ ] pub
to open. Yes, I'm scrap. And then um
yeah, [ __ ] probably chill. I can't go
back to sleep, man. I find it hard. Like
when I'm hung over, I
can't I find it like really hard. I
don't know about you, but [Music]
I need to poo as
well. I need
to maybe I could have
a could have a shower now, but I
probably just save. I need to get some um stuff.
Oh, I thought
you my [ __ ]
foot Monty's yesterday last night. He
doesn't let me
on. Monty hates me, bro.
It ain't got nothing, bro. [Music]
But here's the thing. I know you'll come
to London again, bro.
Peace. I know you'll come to London
again. Why don't you let us know when
you're back in London with Sean and I'll
slap the [ __ ] out of both of you,
bro, at the same time. I'll do it by
myself as well. I don't need weapons.
I'm that confident.
Okay, that's never going to happen, bro.
Just keyboard warriors always be key warriors.
Oh, one second. I need to go do this. One second.
[ __ ] skin just stop
[ __ ] [ __ ] in Florida.
Yeah, was a uh friendly soul, wasn't
he? Hope was a friendly soul.
Jesus. Yeah, he was he was a friendly soul, wasn't
Yeah. B and then just go out. Doesn't
make sense. You
know they go
out especially cold outside. [Music]
Yo, this American had yesterday. She had
the [ __ ] old uh Morgan
fringe. She had the [ __ ] Morgan
fringe. She had the Morgan fringe, man. Oh
[ __ ] No [ __ ] way,
bro. You know what I mean? But basically [Music] What is
it? Right. I need
to place open for a while.
Um there stuff's
cold. I don't know what I'm doing, bro.
I'll go live later, but after today,
definitely want that. I want that
breakfast, but that place isn't open until later.
I don't know, man. It's [ __ ] up, man. [Music] Well, not sure. I
think time eight.
Um, I could have a
bath, but then what's
up? [ __ ] it. I'll have a bath. [ __ ] it.
No, I just have a bath here. Just change
boxes. Anyway, I'm out of be back later. Peace.