Oh, I just had some sausage and mash.
I feel [ __ ] tired as [ __ ] now. I'm tired.
These little nerds are weird on here.
These little old pathetic nerds.
[ __ ] spastics on here, aren't they,
bro? I just went on a great guy's
channel where they comment on my video.
[ __ ] you now, bro. These old men are
really, really pathetic.
They need to [ __ ] get laid cuz
obviously they're still virgins. Not
talking like I [ __ ] do you know what
I'm saying, mate? But [ __ ] virgins.
Absolute stupid little virgins.
They're idiots on here. They're idiots.
I wish they understand that white
nighting will never get them laid. It
will never get women liking them. But
you can't argue with autism. You can't
argue with disabled people. You know,
you you you can't, mate.
You you you can't, mate. You know,
you can't you can't argue with disabled
people, bro. You really really can't.
I feel bad for them.
I can't believe that just browsing
is still on here talking about my attitude
even though I said what a woman said to
that guy about his forehead. These simps
are really really pathetic, man.
really really really pathetic, lad.
Hey, I'm just chilling, bro. I had some
sausage and mash.
Bro, there's so many white knights on
this community, isn't there, lad?
So many white knights.
So many little simps. I wish they would
believe me that white nighting will
never get them laid, but can't argue
with stupid people, can you, lad?
literally sat there.
Now, I just watched a video the great
guys put up of me. They're just sat there, bro.
They've got a worse attitude than me.
Why do I have an attitude? Cuz I I said
that that woman was cop blocking me when
I was trying to talk to her friend. Why
is Why do I have an attitude?
They're just little simps. They're
really They're just old pathetic people
that don't leave the house, is it? It's
got to be old pathetic people that don't
leave the house.
All the irony talking about my attitude.
You want to see the the attitude these
women have? And again, I'm an impartial
person, by the way.
Just so you know that.
Yeah, they're weird, bro. They're weird.
I don't get these FIFA on I really don't.
They seem to make up the rules as they
go along. Candyman.
Yep. They make up the rules as they go along.
You got LT trying to threaten me like
I'm scared cuz I told you what it is.
and you're saying, "Oh, don't say I'm
stalking you when it starts again." Bro,
I I'm not scared of you. I don't know
why you're you're piping [ __ ] At the
end of the day, you're the one that
commented on my channel and I've pointed
out how you're a hypocrite and now
you're getting assy about it. That's
your [ __ ] problem, not mine. No one
asked you to come on my video and start commenting.
Yeah, I put content out there. You
wanted to comment, setting absolute
[ __ ] And I told you how you're saying absolute [ __ ] Simple
idiots on there, bro. I swear to God,
there is [ __ ] idiots on there, man.
They really are. Yeah.
I'm [ __ ] tired as [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, that that uh
that just browsing is a keyboard warrior.
This JJR guy said, "Oh, where's my
mates? Where's my mates? You saw my mate
last month." Again, self-p projecting.
This is what it is with these little
mongos on here. It's just self-p
projecting their life time and time and
time and time again. Do they ever give
it a [ __ ] rest
talking about themselves? No, they
really don't. Do they
self projecting constantly? That's their
life, bro. It really is.
Really [ __ ] is.
What? What the [ __ ] man?
Yeah, it is on video.
That's how you know they're little
virgins. The way they just sit there and
defend women, whereas I don't even give
a [ __ ] about it, bro. I don't give a But there's
all these mates. What a complete weird
prick Loki is. This is what I mean with
these people. They're self projectors.
He's good at repelling women coming from
someone that's probably never been laid.
This guy's self projecting.
You know what I find so weird? I I find
so funny is how many people on here
can be obsessed with people that they don't know.
They're so obsessed with people that
they don't even know. Not to say people
can have opinion, people can't have an
opinion, but do not find it weird how
these people sit online for years being
obsessed literally for years with people
that they uh people that they don't
know. Like sometimes when I scumble
through the comments, I scumble through
the comments, it's the same people.
Same people that you've seen for years.
Shane was like, I put a pint over his
head. That was never going to happen.
Greasy needs going in on the little
cabbage flacker simp. How about you do
something in real life, Jimmy Jazz, you
little keyboard warrior. Yeah, you can
go in on people if you want. Yeah, just
do it. Just don't do it behind a
keyboard. Do it in real life. [ __ ]
that's why I don't like reading these
comments from these [ __ ] mongos, bro.
It annoys me
little nerds. That's what these people
are. Just little lowife nerds. That's
that's that's that's all they are.
Just the real man's way of handling
rejection. Didn't even get rejected.
Actually, if you actually watch
properly, I got coped by a friend. This
is what I mean with these little nerds.
these nerds on here, lad.
Negative, fat, ugly little nerds wring
the same [ __ ] every day on this community.
I don't bring it up anymore.
I don't bring up. You know what I find
so funny is how that autumn was um
so fast to come on my channel when there
was negativity, when there was drama.
She was so fast to come on my channel.
But yeah, uh but yet um
but yet she's never come on my channel before.
Isn't that funny?
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
I guarantee you, yeah, 90% of these
people in this community are virgins,
lad. I'm so sure. I'm absolutely so sure, lad. [snorts]
I'm sure they're little virgins.
I'm telling you, bro. These people on here
like these weirdos.
These look weirdos.
Oh, they're [ __ ] weirdos on here, man.
Oh, the great Oh, yeah. Yeah, I get it. Yeah. Funny.
I love how that Alton thinks I'm a freak
because that Weather Spoons video, but
all of the things that women do, they
dismiss it. It doesn't bother me, bro.
Like, it doesn't even bother me if I get
numbers and they don't reply. It doesn't bother me,
you know? I I don't give a [ __ ] me. I
just don't understand these little nerds
on this community.
these little self-p projected nerds that
don't even leave their house kind of
obsessed with the same people for years, you know.
Yep, that's me.
weird. It's a weird community, mate.
Yeah, they were [ __ ]
Well, no. One of them was a [ __ ]
The other one was all right.
The other one was all right. They never
said anything but her.
You want to call me a freak, mate? But
yet women are the ones that have got attitude problems.
They're mad. Do you know what? And I'm
like I said, I'm a completely unbiased
person. And I'm giving you my review on
it. I told you what they said about that guy's forehead. Like
I told you, no one said anything. You know,
they're the ones with a stinking attitude.
They might want to practice what they
preach. And it's me giving an unbiased
opinion. I I don't give a [ __ ] you
know? That's it.
I don't know what is it. It's with these
just these people like just brows and
then these white knights. I don't get them.
Yeah. So I don't understand, bro. It's just browsing.
And then you got LT that apparently
doesn't watch me yet. He's on my video straight away
when it's to do with a black guy and
then he's trying to threaten me.
Uh, bro, is this guy for real?
Guy's an idiot, lad.
He can't answer my questions cuz he
knows I'm right. Cuz he knows what I'm
saying is the truth. He knows I'm right.
That's why he has to resort to like stupid threats.
He knows what I'm saying. True.
Yeah. LT wants to meet you. By the way, Timmy,
you said that you couldn't do anything
to me cuz you was at work. Yeah. Right.
That's what you said. But when I was
having a go at that gay guy in the
bookies that was working there, you had
no problem with it.
You had no problem with it. Yeah. When
that guy in the on the bus was arguing
with me. Yeah. Sticking it on me when I
was younger and I didn't do anything.
Like what was it 3 years ago? Maybe
four. It was years ago. Yeah. So then by
your logic, I won then because I
wouldn't be able to do anything back to
him cuz he could do anything back to me
because he's working. So it's always
excuses. It's always It's always
Nah, he's never bullied me. Like, none
of you have ever bullied me. You can't
bully someone you will never meet.
Nah, none of you people can bully
yourselves, let alone anyone else.
You people bully yourselves. You don't
bully anyone else. You can't even meet anyone.
All right, Timmy, do you want the link?
Yeah, bro. No one bullies me.
There was five people yesterday and
there was only me.
Yeah, by myself. Still wasn't scared of them. So
if you want to go by that logic, you know,
so then if I battered a guy on a bus,
then the excuse would have been, "Oh,
well, well, he's working. He can't hit you."
See, you people always twist [ __ ]
That's why I can't be bothered with it anymore.
That's why I can't be bothered with it.
You twist [ __ ] You call people virgins
that prove they've had sex for [ __ ]
sake. How more simple can you be?
How more simple can you actually be? You know
madness. Absolute madness.
No, it's not funny.
It's not brilliant. It's not funny.
That's why I don't go out much
deal with [ __ ]
women with attitude problems, people
that are on cocaine. That's why I don't
bother. Like, I like a peaceful life,
bro. I don't like drama.
I don't like dramas, lad.
I approached [snorts] someone outside
the train station. Guess what they said
to me? They're 16.
How many times have you heard that one before?
Just to throw that out there. Even
though they weren't 16.
They say a lot of the same stuff for
people that aren't the same. I've said
it a million times.
I've said it a million million times.
They say a lot of the same stuff for
people that aren't the [ __ ] same, mate.
That's worrying. That's very, very Yeah.
But I went out yesterday to have fun
anyways. I always I always know it was
going to be the same old. That's why it
doesn't bother me. I don't give a [ __ ] lad. Yay.
Cuz it will never change, will it? So,
nothing left to moan about, bro.
Did you uh watch my video to LT? Can you
give me your uh can you give me your
unbiased opinion on this one? Grezy,
who who do you think's right, me or LT?
And then this Autumn wants to call me a freak.
Okay. Right. Okay. I'll explain it to
you. Right. So he's trying to say to me, yeah, that
I'm a I'm a coward or whatever.
Basically, in other words, because I'm
starting on someone that apparently
couldn't do anything to me back because
he risks losing his job, right? But
here's the thing. When I was arguing
with that gay guy in the bookies and I
was running up my mouth about him, he
didn't have a problem with that. Nope.
Nope. Even though someone in the bookies
is more likely to
lose their job than a bouncer
like doing something to you, but when it
was a white guy in the bookies, no, no
problem. Not a problem at all. You can
do what you want. Yeah. But then it's
then as soon as it's to do with a black
guy, right, who's about to and I'm
arguing with them, oh well, they can't
do anything because they're going to
lose their job. No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no. [ __ ] me, bro.
You know, like, and also another thing
is it's not even just that. Let's go by
his logic. Yeah. He doesn't listen to me
because he knows I'm right. That's why
he has to resort to frame. Okay. Let's
let's go by this analogy then. Yeah. So,
do you remember that black man on the
bus that was running his mouth about me?
Yeah. Yeah, I did do that. Yeah. Do you
remember that? Do you remember that guy
that was running up his mouth, the old
man about 4 years ago, and I didn't do anything? Yeah.
So then if you you remember that when I
was on my way to Admirals and a guy was
saying he was an old black guy and I was
on the bus. You remember? So if we're
going by his logic, then that must mean
that black guy didn't win then, did it?
Because that would mean then if I
started on him, you would be using the
same excuse that he can't do anything
because you're at work.
So you contradict yourself. So actually,
so for someone that's that that you're
apparently calling me disabled,
yet I've got more common sense than you.
Really? What about them other four
people? Done nothing. What about What
about the people in the Weather Spoons
next to me? Done nothing.
Yet there were clearly white knights.
Am I right, Grezy?
So that means that black guy on the bus,
he didn't win then because he's working.
So if I was to uh start on him, he
couldn't do anything back to me cuz he'd
lose his job. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Okay. Okay. Yeah.
Yeah. Whatever. Man,
there's a guy in the bookies that wanted
to fight me, bro. He wanted to come
outside and he wanted to fight me and he
was working there. And he had a pole.
And he had a [ __ ] pole.
Yeah. And he had a pole as well. And
this was a bookies.
See, this is what they do on this
community. They twist things. This is
what I mean. It's like when I prove I've
had sex, they still call me virgins.
Yeah. When I call virgin boy, who's
actually a virgin a virgin, everyone
backs backs him up. They always twist
[ __ ] on here, bro. It's whatever. Is it? Yeah.
Then he's saying, "Oh, when it starts
again, bro, no one cares what you're
going to start again."
No one gives a [ __ ] what you're going to
start again, bro.
I ain't [ __ ] asked. You know what I'm saying?
But yeah, I'm glad you enjoy the
content. I didn't enjoy at all. It's
negative. It's toxic.
Um, and yeah, I mean, I didn't like it
at all. I don't think it's funny. I
don't think it's clever.
I'd love to go out and none of these
things happen, but unfortunately they do happen.
And in the pub, I was talking to her friend.
I was talking to her friend Grezy
or her sister, whoever the [ __ ] it was.
And she was being all right. And then
she started butting in having an
attitude for no reason.
I mean, what the [ __ ]
And then I just told her it's just
easy. These women really really have bad
attitudes. Really really have bad
I told you about what what one woman
said about that guy's forehead. You know,
it's how these people
sit there and and and and defend them,
bro. I shall never know. And again, I'm
impartial as well. I'm just I'm just
somebody that went out, had fun, didn't
expect anything because I knew it was
going to be the same old. But I can tell
you what they done. I can tell you what
they said, even when it wasn't to me as well.
Now ask yourself, Grey, why do we never
hear about this stuff?
Cuz I know we me and you won't we won't
come out the best of friends, you know?
Uh uh why why why do we never hear about
this stuff? Is it ignorance or what is
it? And I'm impartial, bro. Like I said,
I'm I'm impartial.
I'm not going to become depressed. I'm
not going to Bro, I'm just a bit tired.
I'm good. Why do we never hear about
their stinking attitude
like we do men's? And trust me, a lot of
them have a bad attitude.
Entitled. A lot of them were [ __ ]
A lot of them were. And again, I'm impartial, bro.
So why do we never hear about this stuff?
It seems very much blame the man for everything,
you know? Why is that? Is it like
anything they do
um is okay or like I don't get it. Is it
like everything that they do is they get
away with it or what?
I can't believe that woman said to that
guy that oh he should give up. He's got
a big forehead.
That's madness, bro. And they talk about men's personality.
And they talk about men's personalities
like mad. Absolute madness.
Like it might sound funny to you. It
might sound funny to you, bro, but it isn't funny.
It isn't funny. It's toxic as [ __ ]
you know? Really, really is toxic. Madness.
And again, we're not talking about the
makebelieve boyfriends. I don't give a
[ __ ] about that.
>> That's just always going to happen. I
mean, but I mean that I mean the
entitlement and [ __ ] and the [ __ ] they
do. Why is this never addressed?
It got so bad. I'm thinking they're
never going to clubs and bars again.
Just like approaching on the street.
It's that bad. Uh, Greasy. It's really Germany. Yeah.
But her friend didn't say anything to
me. Otherwise, I would have just like
walked or whatever.
I don't know, bro. I don't It's just all negative.
It's all negative, lad.
So, who do you think's right then? Me or LT? Grievy?
If you say LT, you're not going to get
banned. You're not going to get blocked.
I don't want people to agree with me
just for the sake of agreeing with me.
So, who who who do you think's right?
Gre me or LT?
I want impartial people on this channel.
I don't want people to agree for the
sake of agreeing with me and disagree
for the sake of disagreeing.
I think I've got a good point
for someone that's apparently disabled, you know.
No. Go on, Grezy.
Go on, Grezy. Who's right?
So go like I think go by that logic then.
So basically, so then what what you're
saying? Okay. So basically then that
black guy in in in that black guy in the
bus is a coward then grievy because he's
having a go at me knowing I can't do
anything. I can't say anything because
he can't do anything to me cuz he's at work.
So that's basically saying that then isn't it?
it doesn't make sense.
It seems very much that he doesn't like
it because the black guy lost.
That's all it is. Cuz he was black and
he was a man. So the only thing that
they could do is say, "Oh, well, he's at
work. He's at work. He's at work."
[ __ ] me, bro. How many excuses does someone have?
How many excuses does someone have, lad?
Oh, I love salted popcorn, man. I love salted popcorn.
I don't know, bro. It's just weird, is it? Yeah.
And what about them four people as well?
What about them four people as well?
Did you see what I said to them four
people? I told them to [ __ ] off, you ugly [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm glad I [ __ ] stood up for myself, bro.
Are you glad I uh stood up for myself, Grezy?
Who's that cute that I stood up for myself? Grezy?
Who do you think stands up for themsel
more? Me or Timmy?
You remember when Timmy was arguing with the bouncer? Huh?
Who do you think?
I said my train is worth or worth more
than your outfit, you [ __ ] silly
Why don't they mind their own business?
Well, I don't understand why they don't
mind their own business.
[ __ ] Jordy bastards.
I stood up for myself.
Yeah, I should I should have, but my my
main problem was with the guy cuz they
were just they were the ones saying I think.
No, I all I all I all I had to say to
him was mind your own [ __ ] business,
you ugly prick. That's good enough, bro.
There's nothing really else.
I should have talked about his leg
shaking, but I didn't notice it until I was watching.
I should have said, you're telling me
I'm shaking. Your [ __ ] leg is [ __ ]
shaking. Up, down, up, down, up, down,
up, down, up, down. But again, I didn't
notice it until I watched the video back.
He was shaking his leg, bro. Did you see that leg?
[ __ ] ruler in his mate. Yeah.
How do you reckon the Virgin would have
coped in that situation, Grezy?
The open virgin.
How do you reckon a virgin would have coped?
The skinned virgin it.
He might get [ __ ] defeated in it. Virgin boy.
Virgin boy with a shy's neck locks
[ __ ] skint boy. [sighs] Yeah.
Oh, one woman replied back to me.
Okay, one's replied back to me,
but the problem is she's French.
I met a couple of French women
yesterday. They seemed all right, but we
all know what they're like, don't we, Grezy?
Oh no, here we go again.
But here's the thing, Grezy. They're
[ __ ] liars, bro. these women that say
they've got um
there was this woman in America, right?
I spoke to this American yesterday. She
was so stuck up. She was like, "Oh, I've
just come here." Yeah.
She was like, "Oh, I've just come here.
Oh, I've just come here."
She was like, "Oh, um
what did she say?" She was like, "Oh, uh,
she said she's coming for school or
something." And then she says she has a boyfriend
without getting to know me. She was so stuck up. Um,
but your boyfriend, but you moved here
from America. How do you have a boyfriend?
And then a French woman actually did say
that. She had a boyfriend.
Yeah, she said she had a boyfriend.
She's come here to see her boyfriend.
They're so They're so full of [ __ ] They
love that boyfriend word in it.
I don't know why they go out,
waste money when there's a cost of living crisis.
They go out, spend money
knowing that then they're just going to
tell everyone they've got a boyfriend.
Because I see them do it to more than
one person. Greasy. I saw them do it to
more than one person.
They do it to They done it to more than one person.
There's a cost of living crisis. By the way,
if you didn't know, Grezy, if you don't
go to central London and you go to local
pubs, a lot of these pubs are empty.
A lot of these pubs like Weather Spoons,
I'm surprised they stay in business.
But they will go out, spend their money,
when obviously mo most people in this
country are [ __ ] skint. Let's be fair
here. Most people in this country just
to tell everyone they've got boyfriends.
[ __ ] mad. That's [ __ ] madness, isn't it?
The friends don't really say they've got
boyfriends. Most of the time they don't.
Old time they do, but mostly they don't.
Must be against their religion to lie.
Eh, if you catch my drift grievy,
it is strange, isn't it? Most of the
time they they don't.
Most of the time they will never say
they have boyfriends.
Just like Muslim people.
But yeah, this one replied.
I'll message her later some more or
something. At least I got a reply here.
I want that one from Manchester to reply.
That's the one I want cuz I approached
her sober with her friend.
He says that's for the 40y old virgin in
the making. I said that's you. I went on
the uh video that virgin boy by done of
me and Sig and he says 40y old virgin in
the making. I said you must be talking
about yourself. You big virgin.
The big virgin's talking about himself.
You big big virgin.
If I knew it was projecting all along, I
would have told my mom to not waste my
[ __ ] her [ __ ] time explaining the
escort situation to you.
You know, I thought you was being
genuine. I didn't know you was calling
me a virgin cuz you want cuz you're one yourself.
I would have never got my mom to explain
the situation to him, Grezy, if I knew
that it was just projecting.
And I was like, oh, it's cuz he's a virgin.
I get it now. Oh, he's a big virgin.
Oh, I see.
It's that French woman replied.
How did it go? Dreadful.
I got five numbers and only one replied.
I had to deal with a lot of bad attitude from women.
A lot of toxicness.
Just Yeah. Same old.
Oh, mate. I'm waiting for Scream 7. Grezy.
So, I've got one that was replied. I'm
hoping this other one replies.
[snorts] Yeah, I'm waiting. And there's
one uh New Year's Eve coming out or Dece
or the bride or something. Yeah,
something like that.
Yeah, just the same old [ __ ] Anyways, Bob,
basically, it will never change.
Then I went to an escort, got a [ __ ]
cost me 120, and yeah.
I love horror films. 250 including
my meal today. I had a five guys. Yeah. 250.
So, it weren't too bad.
Wasn't too bad. And I mean I got an
escort as well. So
with the five guys. Yeah. 250. It's not that bad.
But yeah, same old Bob. It will never
change in this country, will it?
And it will [snorts] never change, will it?
And you'll never change. Bob the Builder. So
[snorts] got nice jeans, nice trainers.
Do you like my trainers?
I sure did.
Her jaw was hurting from sucking my
willy greasy. I said just a little bit
more. It's coming. It's coming.
I said wheezy.
Yeah, I said it's coming. It's coming.
Oh, I saw that Lord Jay's uh video with the Vindeloo.
He can't handle it. I watched that. It
reminded me of the [ __ ] virgin.
He reacts the same way to Vindaloo.
Oh, I had sausage and mash. Wy
add sausage and mash with onion gravy just now. Yeah,
it was really nice.
My mommy made it for me. Yeah.
Did you see [ __ ] L J not being able
to eat the vindaloo?
Madness. I acted like L J when I had the
Caroline Reaper burger and that's the
hottest thing you could eat in the world.
I had to sign a leaf and then I was like
L J when I was having that [ __ ]
Reaper burger. But Vindeloo nah mate easy.
I've grew up I've been eating Vindaloo
since I was a baby. grave day.
Yep. Since I was a bubin.
So I grew up on it. Yeah.
I'm only joking, bro. But it's not hot to me.
What's hot is that Dave's Chicken.
There's a place called Dave's Chicken
and it's unbearable, bro.
That is hot. That is hot. That Caroline
Reaper burger is hot. Maybe I'll try
I'll go there again and try and finish
it this time.
Cuz the last time I tried a Grezy, well,
it almost [ __ ] killed me.
But I'm think maybe this time
I might be able to do it.
I might try it again. Yeah.
This guy is an idiot,
Listen, LT, stop your little threats,
bro. You don't scare me, bro. About go
outside in 30 minutes, bro. You're
boring as [ __ ]
Boring as [ __ ] Oh my god. How many
years have you been doing this for?
You're boring as [ __ ] bro.
This guy is so boring. He needs to get a
life. This is supposed to be a guy,
right, that's got kids.
This is supposed to be a guy Yeah.
that's got kids. He's such a
bullshitter, bro. We just know. Yeah.
That he's a catfish as well.
He's a [ __ ] Bro, this guy here is a
[ __ ] bro. I'm not even giving him
attention, bro. I'm not even giving this guy attention.
I am not giving this guy attention, bro. Yeah,
but he hates all of these excuses.
[ __ ] pathetic, bro. Absolutely pathetic.
Get a grip.
Seriously, bro, get a [ __ ] grip.
This comes from a little ego. You know that, bro.
This all comes from a little ego.
Yeah, it comes from a little ego. I'm
not I'm not entertaining his little ego, bro. No,
by the way, this is someone that doesn't
watch me, by the way.
This is someone that doesn't go on
YouTube, by the way. Yeah.
[ __ ] absolute madness. Absolute madness. Yeah.
guy is so boring, bro.
So boring. How someone could have such a little ego.
Madness, it absolute madness. Madness. Yeah, bro.
bro. This guy is saying, "Yeah,
this guy is saying this is gen This is
generally an awful body and he's got
time. The world's got I just showed my
girlfriend the photo and she's gone off
her food. Your girlfriend don't exist.
Why don't you show everybody your body?"
Hold on to this guy who's made this
account 12 years ago. Why doesn't he
show everybody his body?
Why don't you show everybody your body?
Why does he not show everybody? He
should show everyone his body, bro.
This is what I mean, bro. They're
absolute idiots on here.
You should show everybody. You should
show everybody your your body and your
makebelieve girlfriend. You little
[ __ ] weasel. This is what I mean with
this community. It's full of weasels,
bro. It's full of absolute weasels. Yeah.
I've already had food. I had sausage and mash. Yeah.
This LT is a loser, bro. Proper proper loser.
Proper proper proper loser with a little
fragile ego. He's like nons. They're
they're the same, bro. You know, they're
actually the same in in ways, you know,
bro. In ways these two are exactly the same.
You know that? In ways they actually are.
It's madness. Madness. Absolute [ __ ]
Really, really, really, really madness.
So, because a black guy got owned by
myself, started it, and shat himself.
You're starting random beef, bro. You
need to sort your little ego out.
Trust me. I can tell you one thing for
now, bro. No one's running me out of my
yard. I can tell you right here, right
now, that no one's smashing my windows
and getting away with it. It is autism.
You're calling someone disabled, bro.
You're talking about how you're not
arguing with someone cuz they're
disabled, yet you're telling a disabled
person apparently to step outside their house.
Like, you know what I mean? All cuz that
black guy shat himself.
All cuz he shatters his pants. Do you
know what I mean, bro?
You know what I mean? It's a madness.
It is a [ __ ] madness how little
someone's ego can be.
I've never known someone Yeah. with such
a little ego, bro, than them two. In my
whole life. I swear to God, I actually
[ __ ] haven't, mate. I've met a lot of
people. I've met a lot of people, bro.
A lot of people, you know.
[ __ ] idiot, bro. Absolute [ __ ] spaz.
Spazz in a [ __ ] half, lad.
Absolute spaz, bro. It is. [snorts]
Yeah, we know that, brother. We seen the video. Yeah. You know
why are you getting involved with
something that's got nothing to do with
you? Cuz one of your people started [ __ ]
and couldn't back it up.
Yeah, literally they're the same, bro.
They're the same,
but they're different egos in different
ways. Like virgin boy, he just thinks
everyone's a virgin like him.
He just thinks everybody is a virgin like him
and he convinces himself that every day
because of his little ego.
This person come on my channel very
quickly for somebody that doesn't go on
YouTube. Do you know what I mean? Yeah.
For someone that doesn't go on YouTube.
Madness, bro. Madness. [ __ ] madness.
Oh Jesus Christ. You would have thought
at some point somebody would have grew
up. Do you know what I mean?
You don't want to listen to me because
apparently I'm disabled yet you want me
to fight someone but yet you call me
disabled. Just make it make sense.
It's like nothing anyone says on this
community makes any [ __ ] sense.
Really really really really doesn't. Mad. Absolute madness.
Absolute [ __ ] madness.
But the thing is, Greasy, if this guy
was white, there'd be no problem.
If that if this guy was white, there
would be no problem. If this guy was a
woman, there'd be no problem.
You know, you know how mad that is.
If that guy, if that security guard was
white, there'd be no problem with that.
[ __ ] little [ __ ] Uh, I got a
treble both score, no draw. And I got
two, both score, no draw, and the last
game was 2-0. So, I just needed one goal.
Yeah, bro. One go off. And it would have
been a treble. Both score, no draw. I
got a double both score, no draw. I just
needed a [ __ ] last goal. It was sickening.
Yeah, it was sickening, bro. Sickening, mate.
I'm surprised I got two to be fair. They
were both 2-1 and the last game was 2-0.
I just needed it to be 2-1. I was hoping
they were going to score in the last
minute, but they never.
Even with the whole USA easy thing, you
didn't really get anyone to do anything.
Yeah. Even with the whole USA thing, you
didn't get anyone to do anything.
uh 237 off 20 pound
even when I was going at USA is you
didn't start this. So what is it? What
is it with you and black people bro?
Uh Spenny Moore and Barrow
Barrow was two and they just had to score basically.
just had to score.
Uh, sorry. Spending more just had to
score, but they never 20237.
Good return, isn't it? Of 20. [ __ ] bastards.
I might do a double both score no draw
to be fair. [ __ ]
Imagine I had £150 on just two teams
both score no draw madness.
Why has this guy got such a little ego, bro? Yeah. Yep. 237
just one goal away I was. That's why I
never do three teams. That's why I never
do three teams. Never do three teams.
[clears throat] This guy is [ __ ]
funny as [ __ ] bro.
You know, he done the same thing with the battals.
He's he's done the same thing with the
battals, bro. Do you remember the battals? Yeah.
But if it was a white man,
there'd be no problems. There'd be no
[ __ ] madness, bro. Absolute madness.
And that large a thing is ridiculous,
bro, because the guy stood behind the gate arguing.
The guy stood behind the gate arguing
and he done nothing.
Is that better for you?
Uh, I was speaking to a friend and then
she cop blocked me
and then she was trying to tell me to
she was trying to be rude and that and
then I just started back to her and
yeah, that's it.
See, he has to be the hero.
He has to be the hero. Look at these
people. Look at these these people in
Weather Spoons, bro. Nope.
I just went to the next place. Nope.
Yeah, that's funny, bro.
Yeah, that's funny, lad. That's funny as [ __ ]
that is funny as [ __ ] bro. Yeah. >> [sighs]
>> Yeah, it was who I was talking to her
friend and she cop blocked me. I had a
few women cop block me yesterday
when I was getting along with their
friend. I would be getting along with
their friend just about to exchange
numbers and then their friend cocked
their friend [ __ ] blocks me. It happened
twice yesterday. It happened two times yesterday, bro.
Yep. It happened two times yesterday.
Don't know what her name was. She didn't tell me.
These women have really bad attitude problems, bro.
That's why I don't understand. I don't
understand these white knights. I
really, really don't understand them.
I really, really, really, really don't understand them.
I seriously don't understand these white
knights. And like I said, I'm unbiased
as well. I'm unbiased. I'm not biased.
They've got bad attitude, bro. Bad attitude. Yeah.
Bad attitude, mate. Bad attitude.
[ __ ] the bouncer.
Yeah. They'll never learn. They'll
continuously defend women. They'll
continuously be virgins. That's how
they're brought up. Grezy,
that's their life, bro. If they're happy
doing that, then leave them to it, in
it. And again, I'm unbiased. I went out
yesterday to have fun, knowing damn well
that, you know, it's not going to change
here. I just went out to have fun.
I went out to have fun. You know what I mean, bro?
But like it's still like and I'm telling
you what like what's happened and [ __ ]
and they were rude as well to like even
people that weren't me
but it's strange we never hear about this
especially in America like cuz they like
it in America as well. So
yeah and then they'll start get they'll
start calling them a stalker.
Yeah. They'll start. Yeah, but then but
if you stand up to them, they'll call
you a stalker, lad.
Yeah. LG is starting his [ __ ] again, by
the way, cuz he's got a little ego and
he's obsessed with black people.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. He's He's obsessed
with black people.
You stick on a white person, it's
completely fine. No problem. no matter
the situation. But you soon as you argue
with a black guy,
right, you argue with a black guy, we
hear 101 different excuses
and we see that name on the channel
straight away, my boy. Don't we, Greasy?
[ __ ] pathetic, bro.
I could understand if you was being racist,
then obviously you're insulting every
single black person, but you done
nothing. But you done nothing but
[ __ ] stand your ground. I swear we
heard excuses before near the [ __ ]
water fountain in Travalga Square.
There's always excuses.
Always excuses. And I said to LT, "Well,
what about the white man in Patty Power,
the gay man who I was slagging off? You
You didn't You didn't mind then, did you?
He He didn't mind then, did he?
He didn't mind then. No, cuz the guy's
white and not black. Wow.
And why are we even talking about the
bouncer? There was different people that
weren't the bouncer.
There was four people. There was three
people in Weather Spoons
that tried to get involved.
So it's not it wasn't one person. There
was multiple people that wasn't the
bouncer. So what, bro? Were they all working? Yeah.
[ __ ] off, mate. [ __ ] off. Yeah.
[ __ ] bullshitter. Absolute
Absolute [ __ ] bullshitter, bro.
You know, he told me that a bouncer
smashed his friend's teeth in before as
well in a in a mile. He told me that e's
friend E's friend Where was
he? He didn't come with me. I just went
by myself. I was out by myself.
and he told me um yeah Mhm.
He told me that his message friend's
front teeth out and that was a bouncer.
Did the guy lose his badge? Yeah.
[ __ ] bullshitter, bro. Absolute
This guy's got a little ego.
Yeah. And I ran my mouth back to him as well.
I don't know why they get involved.
He started he asked me for ID and then
he started kissing these teeth up.
Then he starts kissing up these teeth
like huh? Are you okay, bro? Seriously?
Yeah. You can see the westernity in their eyes.
They're NPCs, lad.
Yeah, they're NPCs. So what?
They're literally NPCs. Yeah.
Them four that four of them were [ __ ] bro.
They were [ __ ] I stuck it on them
and they ate one none of it.
And it was four of them as well. Well,
two of them were women. Okay. Well,
there was two of them, you know.
Yeah. Timmy and LT's meeting now. That's
[ __ ] hilarious, bro. So, this is all
started again, Grezy, cuz of me. Cuz I
defended myself. This is all started up again. Yeah.
This is basically all started again
because of me.
Yeah. Defending myself.
All cuz I defended myself and made some
content on my channel.
Yeah. Would you believe it?
Would you Would you believe that, lad?
Would you believe that?
Yeah. Would you believe it, bro?
[ __ ] But Greavves, I didn't even do
anything but defend myself.
Am I a lion? I don't know.
I'm the root cause for defending myself.
Would you believe it? Huh?
Mad. Is it mad? Yeah. >> [laughter] >> madness.
Absolute maza, bro.
I'm blocking this guy from my channel
anyways after today. Yeah,
I'm blocking this camp.
Yeah, I definitely am.
Do you remember the good morning videos
on the train and everyone looked back?
And everyone looked back.
Huh? Do you remember
the good morning?
So, he didn't mind me owning Kenji. He
didn't mind me owning that gay [ __ ]
He didn't He didn't mind me owning Mark
Samson. But then when it's a black guy,
there's a big problem with it. Grezy. So
even when you win fair and square,
there's a problem with it.
You know, fair and square, you know, I
even gave him the opportunity to meet me after work.
And actually, they can put their hands
on you. And do you know how I know this?
Because the second last time I went out,
Yeah. this Polish bouncer tried putting
his hand on me. Yeah. And the drink
almost went everywhere.
Yeah. That that was that was the last
time. And did he lose his badge?
Did he lose his [ __ ] badge? No, he
never. No, he never.
And the drink almost went [ __ ] everywhere.
Just excuses, man. Absolute excuses.
For real. For real, bro. For real. For [laughter] >> [laughter]
>> probably. [laughter]
Nah, it's not even funny, Grezy. It's
not even funny, bro.
It's not even funny.
It ain't even funny, bro.
Dying on the same website you can watch
Harry Potter on.
So this this just tells me though that
you can never ever fair fight with these
people. Then you can never fight fairly
with Asian people and you can never fair
fight fair with uh black people either.
This tells me now. Yeah. Yeah. This
Yeah. This tells me this now, bro. This
tells me this now.
I got banned forever in a bar. Uh, Candyman,
cuz I said that a member of staff was
acting like a bit of a [ __ ]
Countryy's a joke, ain't it?
Country is a joke, lad.
country's a joke, mate. Oh,
such a joke then.
Yeah, I remember I got banned for like
approaching two women.
Joke. It's a joke. This country,
it's a country designed to annoy you.
I've always said,
yeah, it's a country designed to annoy you. Yeah. madness.
It is a country designed to aggravate
you in it.
I approached like two people and they
didn't complain about me. Obviously,
they didn't, bro. Like, they I remember
this. This was a few months ago. So,
it's like, hold on. So, dating apps don't work.
And you're a single guy. Um
approaching [ __ ] what, two people?
Um, and then you get banned. Oh, [ __ ] me.
I was only banned that day, though. They
let me back in the end. But I was like,
what? I mean, what's the [ __ ] point, man?
That's what I'm saying. It's a country
designed to annoy you. That's what I mean.
The country is a joke. Yeah.
The women's attitude are so bad. The
candy man. Yeah.
I approached this this woman with this
guy who I met in a pub in a in a in a in
a bar and he was dressed up and we just
went approaching. Yeah. We just went
cuz we thought [ __ ] it. And I approached
her. She said she had a boyfriend. So I
spoke to other friend and then there was
like three of them and then I said can
you like my friend wants to talk to your
friend um if she's single and stuff and
then she's like oh he's got a big
forehead. He might want to sort his
forehead out first.
No girls violated me in any Weather
Spoons. You need to take that [ __ ] out
your eye. And it's like this is the
attitude that we're dealing with, bro.
Even though they weren't talking about me,
it doesn't matter, bro.
No, no, no girls. And no girls. So yeah,
and I don't I can't be bothered with this anymore,
Fanny. Man, I can't be bothered with
this [ __ ] anymore, bro.
I can't be bothered with this whole
thing, bro. I wouldn't have even
uploaded the videos if I knew it was
going to trigger a certain person's ego.
I wouldn't have even uploaded any of the
videos, bro. Guy's weird.
No thoughts on the woman talking about
that guy's forehead. No.
Don't suit you. Nope.
Doesn't suit you.
No, don't suit you.
Just dismiss it in it, lad.
It wasn't me. It was someone else.
So, is that all you took out of it? I'm
done, bro. I can't be bothered. Ah,
I I can't be bothered, bro.
I really can't be bothered.
Oh, I can't be bothered. They It's like
they dismiss any bad thing women women
do, bro. There's no point trying to get
through to them, bro. Just leave them in it.
Just leave them, bro. Please. Like, they're just
they're just idiots.
Uh, if you aren't compatible with women,
[ __ ] off. Oh my god. Just [ __ ] off.
I need a break from these white knights
and these simps.
Yep. I think I'm taking two weeks off uh tomorrow, lad.
Fresh start. I'm coming off for a couple
weeks. Week, two weeks. I need a break
from these little white nights. [snorts]
I need a break, lad. Ah, my head.
My [ __ ] head.
My [ __ ] head, bro. I can't be asked. My head. [clears throat] No.
I can't. It's so mad how they've got the
ability to dismiss any bad thing women do.
Madness. Madness. Madness.
They're idiots, lad. Absolute idiots.
Yeah, I have.
You know what I think it is? Cuz I think
what it is with these people that they
where they had a dad in their life,
their dad made them respect women or
something. That's why they've grown up
to be like white knights and simps
even though women don't like them.
Um but they maybe that's what it is.
They've been like they've been taught
that way by their dad.
No, they don't have high standards.
They've got unrealistic standards.
Everyone should have high standards.
Anyways, I don't care, bro. Like, I'm
not asked about this [ __ ] Anyways,
I can't be bothered.
I really can't be bothered. Yeah. Okay.
I'm deleting them videos tomorrow
anyways. Well, I want Kieran to see them and stuff.
Uh, no, I'm not chasing women. I'm
approaching women, trying to meet women.
That's not what simps do.
Well, you wouldn't you wouldn't think
women have unregistered standards cuz
you're a white knight.
Duh. Of course you wouldn't think that
cuz you're a white knight.
Obviously you don't think they've got unrealistic standards.
They just want a guy Oh, that's definitely bomb.
Uh one's messaged me back.
I'm going to message them tomorrow.
Yeah, that's bomb. Definitely definitely
bomb. This is what I mean. You can't win
with these white knights. You can't win with them.
You're talking about a job, friends, and
a nice personality when I've literally
told you about women yesterday that have
a stinking attitude. You can't win with
these white knights.
What they think is not the real world.
Yeah. What they think is not the real world.
These people really don't have
experiences with women. Yeah. Yeah,
but I'm not moaning about it anymore.
I'm not complaining. I'm not complaining
today, am I?
I knew what was going to happen.
Well, at least I think one other one
will reply to me. I think one other one will reply.
The one from Manchester, but uh I knew
what was going to happen, man. So,
there's nothing to be No.
nothing to be um
if they want people with a nice
personality, LJ, they might want to sort
their personality. They might want to
sort their personality out first.
They might want to sort their
personality out first if they want
somebody with a nice personality.
Is that right, Grezy?
They might want to sort their
personality first. Fill it out first.
I've got anxiety today, bro, from the
drink. From the drinking last night.
Oh, it's stinking.
That's why I try not to drink rum.
This is why I try not to drink rum.
This is why I try not to drink rum lad.
I tried to stick to beer, bro. Oh, the
next day it gives you mad. It makes you
feel like [ __ ]
That's why I just tried to stick to
beer. Like, get this. I just It's like
mad anxiety, bro.
Isn't that right, Candyman?
They're good, man. >> [snorts] >> Boring bombs. Boring. You're boring.
Is that right? It's boring.
Boring. Fat ugly projectors. Oh, boring.
That's why brakes are important on here, lad. Yeah,
there's a lot of white knights on here.
A lot of white knights.
I don't drink much. This is the first
time in six weeks.
Yeah. You know what I find weird,
Candyman, is how these people are so
obsessed with me. They don't even know
me and they can spend
all their life on YouTube obsessed with
me, someone that they don't know. It's
mad, isn't it? Yeah.
It's mad, is it, bro? Like, you see the
same accounts for years.
You seen the You see the same accounts
for years, Candyman. Same ones.
What do you mean, bro?
What are you talking about? Yeah.
Yeah. Because they're projectors.
Yeah. They still come on here every day
trying to call me skin. Yeah, bro.
Because what these people do on here is
they they self project.
Everyone knows that. Like skin, ugly, no
friends, no future. It's all themselves
they're talking about. Everyone knows that.
Yeah. He was as ugly as I knew he'd be.
He's as ugly as I knew he would be.
Yeah. But he's not the only one that
does it. Loads of people do it. Red
star. They're just self projectors. Self projectors. Yeah,
they love calling people skin, but the
reality is these people are sat on here
every day and they ain't got a life.
Even in the summer, that that's what
makes me laugh here. It'll be a nice day
outside and these people will still be on YouTube. Mad. Yep.
No, it does. You're missing the point.
It doesn't matter if it's a long way.
I'm saying that these people on YouTube
even in the summer
cuz their skin
Yeah, these people are skin it. Yeah.
Uh probably still recovering from my hangover. Yeah,
I'm just chilling tomorrow. What's it tomorrow? Monday.
Doesn't matter what my goal is, bro. Doesn't matter.
Well, I'm leaving. I'm going Thailand in
two weeks, so
I guess that if you really want to know.
Oh my god, you're boring, bro. You're boring.
Yeah. Trying to provoke a response. I'm
telling you how you're contradicting yourself.
I'm telling you how you're contradicting yourself.
Yeah. So you're and women are not going
to reject me. There you are.
You are contradicting yourself, Rav.
It's easy. You say that you don't want
to. You don't want to you don't want to
you don't want to uh listen to me
because I'm disabled yet you're trying
to threaten me but you're saying I'm
disabled. Bro, you're boring as [ __ ]
Yeah. You got some issue.
You got some issue with race, brother.
You need to sort it out, bro. You got
some something. You got something with
your skin color, bro. I don't know what
it is. Yeah, bro. You can be where you
want to be. That's on you, bro.
That's You can be where you want to be,
bro. No one's asked.
No one's asked. Nobody has asked. I
don't care, bro. Yeah. Stop making
excuses for some guy because you shhat
it. Yeah. And that's why you're doing
all of this [ __ ] cuz you know that I'm
right. You know that what I'm saying is the truth.
You know I'm right as well. You chat
bare [ __ ] bro. Why are you even
commenting on my videos?
Yeah, bomb. No one cares about your self-p projecting.
It doesn't bother us.
Yeah, that's self projection. No one cares.
The guy who was on the job. One second.
One second. One second. Guy that was on
the job. Firstly, I wasn't threatening
that woman. I was telling her about herself.
Wasn't threatening her. Was nowhere near
her. Wasn't going to punch her. No.
Bomb. You're talking about yourself.
self projection. Do you want me to put a
link up right now and you can join?
Yeah. One second. Let me finish, please.
Yeah. Can you keep typing over me?
Right. About a job. Why did you not have
a problem with me sticking on that white
guy and Paddyy Power?
He was on a job. You had no problem with
that, right? Hold on. You had no problem
with that? Yeah. Oh, look.
One second. One second. One second. One
second. Listen to me.
Listen. Stop talking about yourself.
Right. Firstly, benefits. No. Yeah.
You're talking about yourself anyways.
Listen. No. No. No. No. No. One second.
One second. One second. One second. Right.
[ __ ] the bouncer. Right. Forget the
bouncers. Yeah. What about
one second? Someone sent me a voice
note. Two seconds. Hold on, please.
just responded. Right. So, I've got two
responses now. Okay. LT, I wasn't
avoiding you. Sorry, bro. I had to
listen to something. Right. Listen, bro.
Yeah. It's not about It's not about It's
not about the bounce. Listen. Listen to
me. Yeah. So, what? Going by your logic
with the bouncer. Yeah. So that must
mean that Do you know the black guy on
the bus? So that means he's a coward
then, isn't he? Then that black guy from
four years ago that was arguing with me
on the bus is a coward then, isn't it?
Cuz he can't do anything to me because
because he's at work. If you're going by
that logic, bro, [ __ ] the jobs. [ __ ] the
bouncer. Yeah. What about them four people?
What about them four people? Right. What
What about them four people that I stuck
it on? They weren't working, bro. They
weren't working, bro. Yeah.
Yeah. They weren't working. What about
them three guys in the Weather Spoons?
They weren't working, bro. And there was
three of them. You're constantly full of
[ __ ] I don't even know why you're
commenting on my videos, bro, when you
say that you don't watch me. Yeah, you
are full of excuses. Yeah.
Yeah. But bro, the guy started it,
brother. The guy started it. We didn't
just start on some random black man,
bro. Yeah. The guy started it.
Yeah. So, we got two replies, by the way.
So, two out of five. Well, we should get
another one. Yeah. He started it, bro.
Yeah. by kissing up his teeth and asking
me for ID. Yeah. Why is he asking the
28-year-old for ID, bro?
You know what I mean?
You know what I mean, bro?
You You got something wrong with your I
don't know what it is with you and your
race, mate, but it's weird, bro. It
really really is weird.
Really really really is weird.
Why is he asking a 28-year-old for ID
and kissing up his teeth? Bro,
if you really know you can't do
something, if you really know that you
can't do something, why are you doing
that [ __ ] bro? Why are you doing that
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no. I'm not making disrespectful
videos. I'm telling you how you're how
you're being a hypocrite. Now, if I was
to making disrespectful videos, I'd be
talking about your race and I would be
talking about your kids or something
like that. I told you how you're
contradicting yourself. How is that
disrespecting you, bro? Cuz I'm pointing
out facts. Allow it, man. Please. Yeah.
I was by myself yesterday, bro, and
there was five of the [ __ ] You
constantly make excuses, bro. And stop
talking about L J. Yeah, you need to
stop talking about L J.
You need to stop talking about L J as
well, bro. The guy, he he stood behind
the gate and he argued. Yeah. Yeah. He
stood behind the gate and he argued.
That's what he done. Okay. He didn't
hide behind the gate, bro. He stood
behind the gate and he argued. Yeah.
Okay, bro. Who the [ __ ] cares?
Yeah. I don't know why you keep bringing
that up. Yeah. No, I ain't opening no
door. I'm going to sleep, bro. No one's
told you to come. That was on you. No
one's called you out. That was on you, bro.
That was on you. Simple. You chose to
get yourself involved. That's on you. Simple.
You need to get a life, bro. Honestly,
get a life. That's what you need to do.
You're still coming on YouTube trying to
scare people, bro. Come on, bro. It's
We're It's [ __ ] 2025 and you're still
doing this lame ass [ __ ] Pathetic.
Yeah, it's pathetic, bro. Yeah. Oh,
proper proper proper
I'm in the middle of trying to [ __ ]
speak to someone as well. Bro, you're an idiot.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. Okay, so what about them
four people then? Okay, what about them
four people then? Okay, okay. Yeah,
yeah, yeah. Whatever. What about them
four people then?
Yeah, I'm an opportunist with women and
people in the job, bro. Listen, listen,
listen, listen. Okay, then. So, that bus
driver is an opportunist then? That bus
driver is an opportunist then? Yeah,
that bus driver is an opportunist then.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So, that black
bus guy then didn't win then. Yeah.
Yeah. He's an opportunist, bro. There
was four people that I stuck it on by
myself and they didn't do anything.
There was two guys next to me on the
table that didn't do anything.
Yeah, I told a woman about herself. And
what am I supposed to not do that? Am I
supposed to let people act like a [ __ ]
Am I supposed to act let people act like
a [ __ ] You're an idiot, bro. You're an idiot.
I'm not an opportunist as well. And stop
using him as being on on a job as an
excuse. I told him to come and meet me
after work. I told him I'd give him my
number. Stop using him being at work as
an excuse cuz it's lame, bro. It's lame.
Yeah. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. Listen, listen, no. The
students were [ __ ] I had a woman
that agreed with me, funny enough. I had
a woman that was in her 30s that agreed
with me, but I didn't record it. She had
gone in by that point, brother. I had a
woman that agreed with me. Yeah. It's
not the fact that they agreed. It's
their [ __ ] that can't mind their own business.
It's their [ __ ] that can't mind
their own business. It's not about that
they thought I was right or wrong. Yeah.
It's because they can't mind their own
business. And again, when they're told
about themsel, they shut up. It's the
same thing in London. Yeah. And I had a
woman actually agree with me, by the
way. I wish I recorded it now. She's
like, "Why is this guy asking you for
ID? You're clearly of age." I said, "I
know. The guy must have a little ego." I
told her, "I just turned 28. I've got a
beard." She's like, "There's no way you
look." And then her friends was trying
to get her to stop because they wanted
to get in the pub. So, I actually did
have someone agree with me. Actually did.
They started it by saying, "He's going
to spark you out." And I said, "No, he's
not going to spark me out." Why are you
butting in? Why are you butting in?
Why are you butting in, bro? Keep out of
it. Why are you even buttoning in? I
don't get it.
Why are you but that's what I said to I
said why are you buttoning in?
Why are you butted in? Huh?
But yeah, I did actually have a woman
agree with me.
Do you not understand that these people
in London are [ __ ] Like they were
always but in other people's business.
It doesn't matter what it is. They're
just [ __ ] They're entitled
the men and the [ __ ] women. >> Yeah.
I'm not [snorts] posting anything
anymore on YouTube, by the way,
cuz you always twist [ __ ] So I I'm
never posting anything ever again,
you know. Yeah, cuz you always twist
[ __ ] That's why I'm never putting
anything on here ever again.
Yeah. I was speaking right to some woman
and she wasn't being rude to me and then
her friend started getting rude and I
was not going to have someone be rude to
me. But apparently I bullied women. Why?
Cuz I'm not going to let somebody from
another country try and tell me where I
can and can't go. Sorry about that,
mate. I'm not going to put anything on YouTube anymore.
Never again. Her friend never even said
nothing at all. Her friend didn't say
anything to me the whole time.
Her friend said nothing to me at all. Nothing.
Cuz if her friend sat there and said she
didn't want to talk to me, I would have
walked away. I don't give a [ __ ] bro.
But she got involved trying to act rude.
So, I told her about herself.
Like, I had I had some women right talk
about this guy's forehead yesterday. Like,
bro, I don't give a [ __ ] when they get
told about themsel.
That's why when I watched the Timmy
video, I didn't give a [ __ ]
I didn't give a [ __ ] bro, cuz I know
what they're like. They're entitled
[ __ ] rude [ __ ] You don't know
what they said to this guy talking about
his forehead and that, bro. Some guy
that I was with. Yeah, [ __ ] them, bro. [ __ ] them.
Absolutely [ __ ] them. You think I'm
going to sit Do you think I'm going to
let someone just sit there and and and
talk to me like that? Are you mad, bro? No. No. No.
But I'm not uploading anything on
YouTube anymore, bro. Nothing.
Nothing ever again.
Nothing ever again are you seeing on this channel.
So you can keep saying I go for women and
I'm not posting anything anymore.
So like that. I'm not posting nothing no
more cuz you always twist [ __ ]
And trust me, if that woman was talking
about my forehead, bro, she would have
got she would have got a good telling
off, she would have got a good telling
off. I'm not uploading anything anymore.
Yeah, I'm not I'm not uploading nothing
no more, bro.
Yeah, I'm not uploading anything anymore.
So that's what that's what your excuse
would have been with the bus driver then
is it? So when he was giving it the big
if I started giving it the big back to
him which I never your excuse is going
to be oh well he was at work anyways.
This was like four years ago is it four
I think it was about four years ago but
you had no problem and he was running up
his mouth but yet they can't you can't
say anything to them because they can
lose their job. I ain't uploading
anything anymore, bro. You can [ __ ]
yourself. I'm not uploading anything anymore
cuz you just find ways to twist [ __ ] I
can't be asked. You find ways to twist
[ __ ] all the time.
So, think what you want, bro.
Yo, you're you're an idiot, bro. You're
that still can't be off. I can't be [ __ ] You know,
he's constantly twisting [ __ ] all the time. You know,
and you must be really pathetic if you
would let a woman like that talk to you
like that, bro.
If you would let a woman talk to you
like that, you're mad. Some women that
you don't even know, bro. Like, you you
got no respect for yourself, bro.
Listen, do you know why I don't go out
anymore? I don't go out much anymore
because I can't be bothered with their
[ __ ] Cuz I've got more respect for
myself than to deal with their bollocks.
Yeah. Absolute bollocks. You know,
they've got disgusting ass attitude,
bro. I don't know how people can sit
there and let people talk to them like
that, but that's on them, bro. But it Yeah.
Mad. Absolute mad.
Like, she could have easily said, "Okay,
let's just use it as an analogy.
Somebody wanted to buy in here." They
could have easily said, "Oh, uh, yeah,
I'm just having a nice night with my
sister or a friend. Um, really not
interested in speaking."
Then you would have just walked away.
That's not being rude. But if they're
blatantly being rude, you can't go
around being rude and then start moaning
and crying when someone tells you about
themsel in a yourself in a non-threatening way,
bro. You can't play two sides of a coin.
There's a way of saying things.
It's it's like obvious, bro.
Like there's a way of saying [ __ ]
You think you can just go around getting
rude to people and nothing will happen?
Like it's mad. If you went around going
being rude to people, bro, like you're you're mad.
It's madness, bro. They're entitled
[ __ ] with attitude problems. And I'm
not and I'm not biased. That's the
thing. I'm not biased. I'm someone going
simply by what I experienced yesterday.
[ __ ] the past.
[ __ ] all the other [ __ ] I don't care
about the past except from yesterday. Yeah.
You know what I mean?
>> Yeah. I tried to provoke you by saying
that you contradicted yourself. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah, man. I I tried to provoke you. Yeah.
Yeah, cuz I told you that you're
contradicting yourself. Yeah, I tried to
provoke you. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Because you you wouldn't have said
anything if that guy wasn't black. How's
that provoking you, bro? That's speaking
the truth. How is that provoking you?
It's not provoking you, bro. It's facts.
You wouldn't say anything if that guy
wasn't black. That's not provoking you,
bro. That's going by what we've seen.
That's not provoking you. That's not
provoking you at all, bro.
Cuz you had no problem. Why? Okay. So,
why didn't you have problem with me
sticking on that white guy? Why did you
have no problem me sticking it on Kenji then? Go on.
Go on though. Go on. No, listen. Listen,
listen, listen, listen. No. When I went
to that Kenji's workplace, right, and I
No, bro. They buted in because they done
it to butt in. Yeah. They cuz they
couldn't keep their nose out, brother.
It wasn't what we were all thinking. It
wasn't what Cuz I told them about themselves.
No. No. No. Okay. Well, I told them
about themselves and they done nothing.
So what? So what? I told them about
themselves and they done nothing and
they weren't working. So what? Like, you
know, we can make it we can make excuses
all day long, you know,
but it doesn't matter who's right or
who's wrong. They shouldn't be getting
involved. It's none of their business.
Yeah. It's not for them to even say
anything. And I've already told you a
woman actually did agree with me. There
was a woman that agreed with me. There was.
And then her friends was like, "Oh, just
shut up. We want to get in and that."
And then she was like, "Bro, she did.
She was agreeing with me. She got involved.
cuz you you know
I should have touched him. I should have
touched him. Bro, I I I asked the guy to
give me his number so I could meet him
after work. Did I not? I think what I
done was the right thing. I wasn't being
racist. I wasn't being that rude. I was
I was I I was I was sticking it on him.
Yeah. And I told him, "Listen, give me
your number. We'll meet after work."
A man that's about something would have
done that. You're just full of excuses,
bro. You're full of excuses. You're full
Germany. Generally, full of excuses. And
at the end of the day, Yeah. At the end
of the day. At the end of the day. One
second. One second. Yeah. But he didn't
know. But he didn't. But he didn't know.
But he didn't. So that's that he didn't
and I've had a B to try put his hand on
me before 2 months ago and the drink
almost went everywhere. So
he could have easily escalated that
situation and still kept his job. Like
come on, we're not idiots, mate. We've
all seen what bouncers have done before.
It's got nothing to do with race. Okay
then. It's got nothing to do with race.
Okay. So why do you have no problem with
me sticking it on the white guy and
Patty Power? Why do you have no problem
me sticking it on Kenji?
Go on. If if it's not If it's not to do
with race, then why didn't you say
anything when I stuck it on these two
people that were white? You had no
problem, bro. You had no problem. You
thought it was funny.
Huh? You thought it was funny, bro.
You thought it was funny. Especially the
gay guy. You thought it was funny. But
it's not so funny when it's a black
person. Bro, you're an idiot. [snorts] Yeah.
It's not funny when it's a black person,
though, is it?
So why do you have no problem with them?
No. One second. Why did you have no
problem with Kenji and the guy on Patty Power?
Why did you have no problem with that?
You know, why why did you have no
problem with that? And the only reason
you got pissed off with Morgan is cuz I
kept going on about it over and over and
over and over and over and over and over
again. But why didn't you use the same
excuses with Kenji and that white guy in
the Patty Power then?
It's a simple question. Go on.
Yeah. Okay. Whatever. So, you're not
going to answer me then? So, you're not
So, you're not going to So, so what
you're saying is then So, never start
with on someone ever again that's at
work. Is that what you're saying? So if
someone's at work, So if someone's at
work, never start on them though. So
never start on anyone that's at work
again. Okay, understood. Is it? That's
your logic. Yeah. So if someone's
working, never start on them ever again.
Okay. Cuz I there was a guy in Bet Fred
that was wanted me to come outside and
fight him and he had a poll. So which
one is it? Make up your mind. So don't
start on something that's working. Huh?
So we don't we avoid these problems in
the future. What what's what is it then?
Don't start on someone that's working.
though. Okay then.
So then that guy, that black guy that
was talking [ __ ] in the bus, he's a
[ __ ] then, isn't he then? So that must
mean he's a [ __ ] Yeah. Okay. He's a
[ __ ] then. Cuz I can't fight somebody
that's working. So he's a [ __ ] then.
Okay. Yeah. When he was sat there
calling me a wanker. He's a [ __ ] then.
Yeah. going by your logic.
No, I wouldn't. No, I [ __ ] wouldn't.
No, I wouldn't. Was any of them people weak yesterday?
No. It could be literally anyone outside
and I still wouldn't go out.
I still wouldn't go out, mate.
You know, see the thing is you don't
understand. Yeah. This is what you don't
understand. I've put myself at risk many
many many many many times. Whoever's
behind that stupid Arnold account, you
haven't. I've put myself at risk
multiple multiple multiple multiple
times. What you're saying does not make
no sense, bro. I want to I want an EGW.
Yeah. You want to talk about Terry? Bro,
listen. Terry, bro, do you know how
badly I want to go and smash that Terry
in? But I don't go to his area because
we all know what happens. We all know
what happens. We all know what happens.
And I could easily beat him with one hand. So,
but I don't go because we know what what
it is on here. So, actually, you're
wrong. Actually, you're [ __ ] wrong.
Actually, you're [ __ ] wrong on that
one. Yeah, man.
Yeah, man. You're right. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. You're totally right. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, I've been really wanting
to smash that Terry in with one hand,
but we all know how the cookie crumbles.
That's why I don't waste my time. Does
that mean I'm scared?
Does that mean I'm scared?
No, it doesn't.
So, stop talking [ __ ]
Yeah, I ain't scared of no one, bro.
I've put my [ __ ] I've put myself
Yeah. on Yeah. Skin big nose. You're
talking about yourself, bro. I've spent
three months of your benefits in the
past week. Yeah. Stop talking about yourself.
Yeah. But the only skin people is
yourselves. You are skinned.
Yeah. No one's fighting your your your
uh battles. Yeah. Simple.
These people are retards. I'm not
posting anything anymore, bro. I'm not
posting anything anymore. Yeah,
I'm not posting anything anymore.
Scared of blacks. Nice try, mate. See,
this little keyboard warrior wants
people to stop being racist so other
black people can fight his battle. He's
a [ __ ] You're [ __ ] bro. I've put
myself at risk on this community
multiple multiple multiple multiple
multiple times. Multiple times.
Yeah. More than Timmy ever has and ever will.
Scared of [ __ ] blacks. This guy's a
[ __ ] idiot, bro.
Yeah. I pick my targets. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I know, bro. Yeah. Just like when
I tried to meet Bomb. Yeah. I picked my
target there. Just like when I tried to
meet Mark Samson two times. I picked my
target there, didn't I? Yeah. Yeah.
Didn't I, mate? Yeah. And all them other
people I tried to meet who I didn't even
know what they looked like. Yeah. I
picked my target there as well, didn't
I? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay, mate.
All of these people I've tried meeting,
some of them that I didn't even know
what they look like, but I picked my
targets. Okay, buddy. Yeah, you keep
telling yourself that.
He looked harmless. Well, he kissed his
teeth, but he was being a [ __ ]
So, I mean, yeah. Uh, you would never
done that to a strong. Uh, yes, I did.
I've got a video of me sticking on a
Polish bouncer and he's big as [ __ ] Uh,
yes, I have. I've already done it. And
this one was white.
You know what I mean?
Because they ain't got a life, Bob.
Because they ain't got a [ __ ] life. That's why.
Uh, yes I have. Uh, yes I have. And I've
got the video of it. Yes, I have. And a
guy was like three times my size. But I
ain't posting nothing anymore because we
all know what you people do.
We all know what you people do.
I ain't doing this no more, bro. I ain't
doing this no more. Yeah,
I've tried to meet all different kinds
of people, all shapes and sizes.
To be honest, LT is the one that picks his targets
if I'm honest. And that's not even me
trying to like that's not even me trying
to provoke you. Like, he does pick his targets.
He does. He does pick his targets. or it
comes across that he picks these
targets. I've tried to meet all
different kinds of people on here.
That's definitely definitely not me. I
don't anymore because I know that you're
all biased in that. I ain't got a plot
to piss in again. Self- projecting.
Talking about yourself will get you
nowhere, boy. Talking about yourself
will get you nowhere. No girlfriend, no
friend. Yep. Talking about yourself.
How many accounts are you going to make
to keep self projecting? Boring as [ __ ] So boring.
You need to come out with some Well, you
can't come out with better insults cuz
you're self projecting.
Anyways, you're banned.
Um, these women I got two replies back
out of five numbers,
but I think one will reply back or they
should reply back.
So, two out of five, which is better
than one out of 10 in it. So,
that's what it really should be, you
know, two out two out of five. Not bad
really. But yeah,
I don't know.
Yeah, I'm scared of blacks. This guy
just wants people to start being racist.
This one in Manchester I was speaking
to, I I approached her sober and I met
her and her friend, but she hasn't
replied back, which is strange. Um,
the bounc only ask you for ID, you
clown, you're 28. Why would you even
take offense that if not got sorry about
35 asked uh do you want me to answer
that question? I can answer that
question. I've got an answer for that.
Um the answer for that is
um because I look like a grown ass man
and I've got a beard. That's probably
why I take offense to it. I don't look
young. That's the thing. I don't look
young. You know what comes up in
conversation most times when when you
you meet these women and we always talk
and we guess each other's ages. Bro,
they always guess my age. No one tells
me I look younger than I'm 26. So is it
funny how all of these people are
telling you that you look 26 to 28, but
one bouncer thinks that you look below 21.
They look very very very very of age. You know,
at the end of the day, if you was like,
listen, if you was 23 and you looked
young for your age and you had no beard,
right? Then, okay, yeah, you look young.
I I would understand it. But, bro, like
I buy my mom cigarettes all the time.
They never ID me. I never got IDed anywhere.
The guy was just trying to show off. And
that wasn't that he kissed his teeth as well. Um, so
bro, have you seen my beard, bro? Like,
I'm pretty sure I look like I'm almost
30 to most people,
you know? So,
yeah, you might be 35 and get IDed, bro.
You must be looking young, bro. Cuz I
don't get IDed anywhere.
Like, is this these people here are
really [ __ ] [ __ ] aren't they?
I've got a [ __ ] beard. I look like
I'm almost 30.
What the [ __ ]
bro? He was asking ID to show off. It
was a pub, bro. It wasn't a nightclub.
It was a pub.
Is this guy really trying to tell me
that I look Bro, I'm not posting anything anymore.
anything anymore, lad.
Now you're saying that YouTube's my life
and I know it.
Can you stick to the subject, please? We
was talking about IDs. We was talking
about IDs and people looking young. I
answered it. Stick to the subject. Don't
Don't change the subject. and go on to self projection.
Yeah. Stick to the subject, bro.
Stick to the subject.
You're changing subjects. Why are you
changing the subject?
Oh my god. You [ __ ] off.
These guys are idiots, bro.
These guys are idiots.
These guys are absolute idiots, lad.
But there's just going to be content on
this channel from now on anyways.
There's not going to be no moaning about
women. There's going to be um
none of that [ __ ] There's going to be
actual content on this channel if stuff
does get uploaded.
You can only moan about something for so
long, bro. You know what I mean?
It's [ __ ] dead as [ __ ] lad. You know
where's Joseph Farra?
He always goes away on the weekends.
So LT, you even said that if I beat that
Charles fair and square, you'd have a
problem with it. Yeah.
Do you remember you said about that
Charles? See? See what I mean, bro?
Yeah. See what I mean?
Anyways, I don't care about
I don't give a [ __ ]
Oh, so Stephen Howard. Yeah. I don't
know. Treble both score no draw and I
got two out of [ __ ] three. Both
score, no draw. Just needed one more
goal to make. There was two of them were
2-1 and the other one was 2-0. I just
needed one more goal. No. Bastard.
[ __ ] bastard, man. So close.
And you told me I'd never get them both. No draws. two bets.
Yeah, but it was only £40. I'm still up over £1,000.
I'm going to do a double both score no
draw on Saturday. I think
stick like 150 on it.
It's not hard to pull off. Not in the
lower leagues. It's not.
I'm going to do a both. I'm going to
stick 150 on a both score. No draw. Yeah.
Yeah. It was only two 20 notes, bro. I
won £100 on roulette as well. Yeah.
When did the FA cop playing again?
Let me reply to this person. One second.
just replying to this woman.
Oh, it'll be December.
Well, I'll just do I'll just do the
South League and the Northern League. Yeah.
No, no, that's not true, bro. It's not
true. Cuz I got into other pubs.
No, no, no, no, no, brother. The ones
where they check people's names and
stuff is when they scam people's ID.
That pub does not scam people's ID. And
I also got into other pubs. So if you
try to go into a nightclub in central
London, they scan your ID for the reason
that you've just said. Yeah. So yeah. No.
And I'm not a creep like you either.
Nah, we're not all creeps like you.
And I'm not arguing with retards, bro.
I'm not arguing with retards. It's a
waste of my time. If you don't get
things, that's your problem, bro. Yeah, [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] nerd.
I'm sick of these nerds on this [ __ ]
[ __ ] community, lad.
Yeah. Go away, you little white knight.
Go away, you little white knight. I'm
never uploading anything for this
community again, lad.
Too many simps and white knights.
I'm never doing it again.
Never ever doing it again. I think I'll
just post my football bets.
Too many white knights and simps.
Cringe as [ __ ]
We need a break from them, bro. I need a
break from them. These are white.
Little white knight.
Little white knight. Uh, no, that's not sing. No. No.
That's not sing.
No, no, no. Big difference.
Simp is people that will lick women's
asses for no reason. Somebody
complimenting someone in person is not sing.
Simp is like you see a [ __ ] below
average looking woman on Instagram and
you're like, "Oh, you're the best
looking woman. I want to marry you,
babe." Like, no, bro. There's there's a
big difference. People's allowed to
compliment people in real life. There's
a big difference.
No. No. It really, really isn't. Complimenting someone. Yeah.
No, there's a big difference.
You're allowed to compliment somebody
and try to get to know someone. There's
a there's a big big difference between
simp and white nighting and and a compliment
cuz simps don't have the balls to speak
to women in real life. That's the thing.
That's the actual thing about it.
Anyways, let me reply back to this
woman. She just messaged me.
Yeah, you keep telling yourself that,
you little weasel.
Anyways, I bet back. I'm going to
message this woman who I got from
approaching. You can't say the same
thing. You'll never be able to talk to a
woman in person. You little white knight. Get up.
Y little weasels on this community.
Yo, little weasels. Little white knight.
Little virgin. Little nerds.
Little simp little white knights.
[ __ ] little virgins.
Well, I learned my lesson. By the way,
I'll never posting anything ever again.
At least I know the solution.
These white heads do my These white
knights do my [ __ ] eding, mate.
Don't do my [ __ ] eding.
You can't bet me any money. You don't
have money. This is what this community
is about. It's just fat, ugly, depressed
people trying to
make everyone else depressed like them.
It's the weasel community. This
community is full of weasels.
Fat, ugly, depressed people. Mazer.
Yeah, I was being a [ __ ] Talking
about yourself again, lad.
Talking about yourself again. So projection. Uh Ricky,
why do you go quiet when I put my
approaching videos up? And stop going on
Nons's channel saying that I'm jealous
that he's got money, mate. I've got more
money than him. I've been to more places
than him and I'm better looking than him
and I've never had to resort to a
disabled girl. Yeah, I don't know why
you write [ __ ] on his channel. You
little white knight.
The irony of you talking about money yet
you live in hull. Oh, the irony. The
[ __ ] irony. What's the chances of
that? E like you're boring, bro. You are boring.
And I've already explained it about a million times. you know.
Yeah. Simple. Why are you white
knighting as well, Mickey? Ricky, you
want to make up your mind. Jesus Christ.
You can't make up your mind to save your life.
And then you say that I get women, mate.
You don't get women, mate. And I'm not
your [ __ ] mate. Cuz if you got women,
you wouldn't resort to white knighting.
Again, make up your mind. Is it women or
is it me? You need to make your mind up
because a year and a bit ago you was
talking about how women are picky and
how they've got unrealistic standards.
So make up your mind, mate,
as you like to call people. You might
want to make up your mind before talking
[ __ ] in the future.
I've caught you in I've caught you on
your virgin I've caught you on your
virgin boyfriend's channel multiple times
talking absolute wank.
on your virgin boyfriend's channel
talking you utter [ __ ] [ __ ]
I mean, what's changed in uh what's
changed in two years, bro? Society is
only getting worse.
Just make up your mind.
So many white knights.
So many white knights. It's so hard. White lights.
White lights, lad. Yeah.
You'll meet me in hell tomorrow.
[ __ ] off, [ __ ] I'm coming off this
[ __ ] anyways tomorrow for a week or two.
So, just giving you the heads up.
Yeah, I'm coming off for a bit tomorrow.
Yeah, from tomorrow.
It's the same atmosphere.
The same atmosphere. Yeah.
Yeah, you're right though. It is the
reality of dating. It's disgusting, isn't it?
These people like Ricky will never get
anywhere in life white nighting.
Never, never, ever, ever, ever, ever.
These people twist [ __ ]
you know? Why is it okay for Now, I
could do a video saying like what these
women done yesterday and stuff, but
there's no point because they're white
knights. So, there's no point getting
into any debate or any argument or
listening to anyone, bro. You know what
I'm saying? With these little white knights,
these people were brought up to lick
women's asses. It doesn't matter what they do,
they were brought up to
lick women's asses. Anyone that's got a
had a f father figure in their life um
has been brought up to lick women's
asses no matter what they do. So,
uh I'm not your [ __ ] mate firstly.
So, you're not calling me mate cuz I'm
not your mate. Um, so obviously people
with a father figure have been brought
up like this.
That's just the way they were raised and
I'm not here to tell them otherwise. Yeah.
So, so what's your opinion on that woman
uh talking about that guy having a big forehead?
What was your opinion on that, Autumn?
What was your opinion on that woman? Uh,
saying that that guy needs to sort out
his big forehead.
Bit rude, isn't it, for people that go for personality?
I mean, people are so scared to say the
truth. That's why I get I get so much
[ __ ] because I'm real about this, you
know, about these stuck up [ __ ] in
this country and I say it and I don't
care. You know,
these women are stuck up [ __ ] in this
country with [ __ ]
nasty ass attitude.
So what if you told them about themsel?
These people are [ __ ]
proper proper white knights.
Proper proper proper white lights, bro.
I swear to God,
mate, I've took a week off YouTube. I've
took three weeks off of YouTube.
You people can't take a day off of
YouTube. And of course I'm going to come
off. I have to take breaks off YouTube
otherwise I'd have brain damage
cuz it's the same atmosphere on here.
That's why you need a break from it
because you'll start [ __ ] developing
brain damage. I ain't [ __ ] putting
anything on here anymore, lad.
Autumn, I'm not putting anything on here
anymore about women or ret.
I don't want to do it anymore.
Too many white knights.
Too many too many too many white knights
sat there defending women that have got
[ __ ] nasty attitudes.
Mad. Absolute mad.
This is madness, bro.
I'm not putting anything on him anymore.
So I got two replies anyways. So,
so these people's logic, Reeves, is
women are allowed to have attitude and
be rude to you, but you're not allowed
to say anything back to them.
Seems a bit unfair, isn't it?
That seems a bit unfair, doesn't it?
Like talking about that guy with a forehead. bit unfair.
What happened to equality?
I mean, it's madness, isn't it? It is actually madness.
It's not like it's your mom or it's your
wife or it's somebody that you [ __ ]
know. Do you understand? Mad.
So I'm wrong in that Weather Spoons
video, by the way, cuz I stood up for myself.
Madness. So they want So they expect you
to sit there, right, and let a random
woman abuse you for no reason that you
don't even know. And as soon as you
stand up for yourself, you're in the wrong. I mean,
I had it worse than Timmy. I mean, the
person got involved and they started being rude
and I'm supposed to just sit there and do nothing.
Like, what's what's your opinion on that, Grezy?
So, you're supposed to sit there and
take abuse from a random ass woman, huh?
Crazy, eh? Crazy.
So can I go around? So can I go around
start being rude to people for no reason then?
So can I go around like Okay. So then
can I go to a train station and start
being rude to people then and cry about
it when somebody gives it to me back? You know
they're idiots. They're absolute [ __ ] [ __ ] spastics.
Proper proper white knights.
Little virgins. That's what they are,
bro. Like, you're going to sit there and
take abuse from a random ass person.
And then when you stand up to a man,
then it's another excuse. Oh, well, he's
he's at work. Okay, he's at work. Then
you stand up to four people and then
there's another excuse.
So like it's just pathetic, bro. Is
honestly honestly just pathetic at this
point. They've got excuses for everything.
They got excuses for everything, bro.
Yeah, that Ricky Minan doesn't get no
women, bro. He's a white knight.
He doesn't get no women.
If he got women, he wouldn't be sat
there saying about how picky women are. You know,
if that woman was talking about my
forehead, bro, God forbid.
God forbid what I would have done.
God forbid what I would have done, bro.
Well, what I would have said, you know,
who in their right mind,
bro, you can't even come on a hangout
and talk because you're that disabled.
So, shut the [ __ ] up.
Like, you uh you can't even come on the
[ __ ] Hangouts and talk, you [ __ ]
Laugh at yourself. Apply that laughing
emoji to your [ __ ] self, you know,
you little white knight. You little s.
That's the worst thing about the
internet, you know, bro.
So, let's see if I can go around, start
being rude to people, and then play the
victim. Let's see how that would work
out. Hey, Grezy. Huh?
Let's see if I go around being rude to
people if I can then play the victim.
How do you think that will work? You know
what? Do you think Greezy? Do you think
it's fair game if a woman gets rude,
tell her about herself? You know,
I think it's fair game to be honest.
So, they're allowed to act like [ __ ] to
you and you can't say anything back to
them. They're not your mother. They're
not your sister. They're not your wife.
Why would you take [ __ ] from a random person?
See, it's easy for these people to sit
there and say these this stuff,
you know, and that's common for me, by
the way. That's common for a patient person,
you know? So it's okay for like if I
went if I went right and started being
rude to women for no reason. I would get a bolican
greasy. I would get a bollockin.
You know, let's just put the shoe on the
other foot. If I went to a bar and
started saying, "Oh, you're fat. A
woman's fat." For no reason, what do you
think would happen?
It is madness, lad.
These little simps, the little white knights. [sighs] madness. Absolute madness.
So they say that you're picking on women.
You then stick on a man, then he can't
do anything because he's at work. Okay,
we'll stick on two men that aren't at
work. Excuse after excuse after excuse after excuse.
Am I lying, Grezy? Huh? [clears throat]
Am I lion?
Don't move. They gone.
Excuse after excuse after excuse. It's
like what they do
just gets dismissed.
But I just told you a couple of [ __ ]
up things they done yesterday and it
just got dismissed.
[ __ ] him, bro. [ __ ] them. >> Yeah.
So crazy. Why are you not allowed to
stand up to yourself when a woman's got
a bad attitude? Huh?
Why are you not allowed to stand up for yourself? Huh?
No, you're not. Because when you do
griev, you get told that you're bullying women.
You get told you're bullying women. So
clearly you're not.
What an absolute bell end. No wonder he
has no friends, no social skills. Up
talking about yourself again. What is it
with these 40year-olds keep talking about themselves?
Why do these 40-year-old spastics keep
talking about themselves every day on
YouTube? I really don't understand it, bro. You know,
hang on. PJ said it's over in the West.
Even got a fake trip plan. How are those
men with women? Uh, that's not their
girlfriends. This is what I mean.
They're [ __ ] spastics on here.
They're [ __ ] bongos. This is, bro,
Grezy, this is why I don't come on here,
bro. This is why you do not see me on
here for a couple of weeks because
they're [ __ ] mongos. It's the same atmosphere.
This is why, bro, I [ __ ] off. Like, have
you noticed that I I'll be [ __ ] off,
bro, for a couple of weeks.
It's because it's the [ __ ] community.
They're mongos, bro. They're absolute
[ __ ] mongos. That's what they are,
bro. This is why I don't waste my time
on here, bro. This is why you see me
gone for weeks and you think I'm dead. Yeah.
Am I lying?
They're absolute. They're just
depressed, ugly 40year-olds that ain't
got a life, that can't get off of
YouTube. That's what they are, bro.
That's literally what they are in this
community. sad, fat, ugly people that's
got nothing in their life but YouTube.
I'm going to prove this again tomorrow
when I'm gone for two weeks and these
people can't take a day off of YouTube.
These [ __ ] fat ugly mongos that have
got no money, no life, no job. When are
these people going to get a job, bro,
and get off of YouTube?
These little [ __ ] mongos.
These little [ __ ] sad little mongos.
Sad little mongos.
Sad little disabled people.
That's what they are. Same atmosphere.
They're [ __ ] And they constantly
constantly make excuses.
Constantly constantly constantly make excuses.
Yeah. Oh, I'm going to wait until Kieran
sees that [ __ ] and I'm deleting this, bro.
So now they're going to have no content
now. Just live streams. They're going to
have no content.
It's the same spastics every day. You go
on one [ __ ] thing, you see that Clint
account, then you see another account.
It is literally the same spasticated
people every day
on here, bro. Literally on here. I don't
have them back for like a week. Little bongos.
Little sad sad bongos.
That's what they are.
They're [ __ ] mongos on this
community. Hey, proper proper skin mongos.
Sad, depressed, fat, ugly people.
They're the ones with no life. They're
the ones with no social skills. They're
the ones with no money. They're the ones
that can't take a day off of YouTube.
Bro, when I was out yesterday, they were
sat in their bedset, sat alone, no
money, waiting for content because they
ain't got no life.
Every time, bro, these people get
people's lives wrong when they keep
talking about themselves, but yet they
somehow still think they're right.
But yet somehow they still think that they're right.
Mad in it. [ __ ] madness. Yeah.
So, I'm gone for a couple of weeks anyways tomorrow. So yeah,
that's that and it. Yeah.
I don't want to see any of these people on YouTube.
Yeah. Of course they would. They're
haters cuz that's all they've got in
their life is hate. Bro, these people
are fat and ugly. Fat ugly muners that
ain't got no life, ain't got no money.
That's why, of course, they'll always
hate, bro. They'll hate if you do good
or bad. Cuz what it is with these people
is they're depressed. They're self-p projectors.
They're self-projecting fat disabled
people that can't live without YouTube.
And it's been proven many many many many
many many times.
And I need to stop putting stuff on my
channel as well, lad.
I need to stop putting stuff on my channel.
That's another thing.
They chat [ __ ] They chat bare [ __ ] bro.
They they chat bare [ __ ]
Debor, bro, they're fat, ugly people
that ain't got a life. Oh, they are.
They constantly make excuses for men.
They constantly make excuses for women.
I can't be bothered with them, bro. Not
men, like people working and stuff. You
know what I mean? [ __ ] them now, didn't it? Yeah,
they're fat, ugly, lonely people that
ain't got a life.
They ain't got no money. You remember
that little [ __ ] trying to say that I
can't afford a pair of trainers?
Bought a pair of trainers. You have
[ __ ] isn't it? Yep.
They don't work,
bro. 90% of these people don't work.
They don't work. Red Star Clint, they
don't work. They're all sat indoors skin.
Yeah, that Red Straw uh Clint,
there's a few of them.
They're [ __ ] skinned, ugly, depressed
people. They got a life. Low lives.
Sad, depressed, ugly, fat people. You've
even seen that guy, bro. You've seen
that guy um Red Star with his fat, ugly fingers.
what it is with these people, right? Yeah.
I'm better looking than them. I'm
younger than them. I've got a better
life. I've got more of a life than them,
bro. Yeah. My life is better than
theirs. Yeah. And that's why they hate
every single day. And my life is not
perfect, but bro, to them people that
are sat on YouTube with no [ __ ]
money, can't leave the house, my life is
perfect compared to theirs.
I mean, bro, like that's why they hate and [ __ ]
They're old, fat, ugly people. So, yeah.
Yeah, I I'll delete I I'll delete
YouTube. I can delete YouTube, man. It's
not my life like it is these people's.
It's their life, lad.
No, it's not even stress, bro. It's just
the excuses and the white nighting. I
can't stand, lad.
They say that you go for women, you go
for man, you go for man, they've got another excuse.
They always have excuses, bro. It's just
[ __ ] It's the white night and I can't stand.
I don't even go on Reddit anymore. So yeah,
I'm in my little nesticles.
These little bug goes need a life. Yeah.
And stop calling people talking about
people's social skills. gym. I've got
friends. I've been with women. You don't
even leave your house. Stop self-projecting
your fat ugly life. We don't all live
your fat, ugly life, bro.
We don't all live your fat, ugly old lives.
Did I prove that the other day when I
bought the trainers?
We don't all live the same fat, ugly
lives as you people. Jesus Christ. Yeah.
And I'll be coming off of YouTube
tomorrow for two weeks, and I hope you
do the same.
I hope I don't see any of you people
when I come back cuz I'll be going on
every single channel and I don't want to
see none of you people on YouTube.
What you are is your fat, ugly, old,
depressed people that try to bring other
people down to your level.
Bitter, old, ugly, jealous little low
lives. Banger. That's what you are.
[ __ ] spastics as well.
Create a different atmosphere for once
in your [ __ ] life if that's not too hard.
You sad little bastard. Talk about my
social skills. [ __ ] you don't even
leave your house. Little self projector.
Self projecting little bastard.
Well, can you take a day off of YouTube?
Can you take a day off YouTube?
Can you take a day off of YouTube? No,
you can't. So, shut the [ __ ] up.
You take a day off of YouTube.
I don't think you can.
Well, you don't even leave your house
and you're talking about people's social skills.
Oh, allow it. I've took two weeks off of
YouTube. You can't take a day off for
I'll be off YouTube tomorrow for two weeks.
Let's see if you can do the same.
And when I come back, I'm going to go on
every single channel to see who's been
on to see who's been on YouTube. Yeah. So, yeah. [ __ ] mad.
What makes me laugh is that they call
people skint, but they're the ones sat
on YouTube every day.
But they're sat on YouTube every day.
But they tried to criticize others. It
makes me laugh, isn't it? These little bongos,
but they tried to criticize other people. Yeah.
Didn't know that, mate.
I can't believe LJ can't take a Vinderoo.
He really, really, really can't take
Spice, can he?
He's not the only one though.
I mean, the Orington Virgin can't.
Yeah, the Orington Virgin can't.
I can't do I've already done three days.
I've done three weeks again. Stop self projecting.
But anyways, back on to LJ.
Yeah, you can't take spice that [ __ ] [snorts]
I've already done it, mate. I I I the
foul challenge, bro. How bro, I had a
Grim Reaper burger. I had a Caroline
Reaper burger, brother, which is the
hottest thing you could have.
Yeah, I had to sign a leaf before eating it.
I'm pretty sure I can, mate. And I was
acting like Lord J on that one. But that
was a Caroline Reaper burger. Yes, but
it's hotter than a foul.
Listen, bro. But it is hotter than a
foul. It's Bro, a Caroline Reaper burger
is hotter than a foul.
Yes, it is.
You know, I tell you, bro, I can eat
extra hot at Nanos.
Yes, I have had a foul.
Yes, I have. And it's not h it's not
hotter than a Carolina Reaper burger.
You have to literally
uh sign a leaf before having it.
Uh I am going to teach you about it
because I have had it when I had CO.
Yes, I have had a foul.
That's the only thing that I'd say is
too hot for me. Dave's chicken. Nando is
not Madras. Nope. Vindaloo. Nope. Foul.
Nope. The only thing that's too hot for
me is Dave's chicken.
That is [ __ ] hot,
you know. So, I have had a foul. I had
it when I had CO.
I have had a foul.
No, no, no, no, no, no. It's called a
Carolina Reaper Burger, mate. It's It
almost killed me.
Yeah, I remember it. I might do the
challenge again, bro. That Carolina Reaper burger
is worse than a foul. Yeah, I'll have a
foul next time. I'll do I I'll do I'll
do a foul challenge if you want me to
in a couple of days if you want me to.
And it's nothing like that burger, mate.
That burger almost killed me.
And I've been having and I've been
having spice for [ __ ] years, mate.
Trust me, I've been brought up on spice.
And trust me, that Carolina Reaper
burger is way hotter than that. It
[ __ ] is. Like, you can barely take a
bite of it, bro. Your mouth's burning.
They said three and 10 people could
finish it all.
I'd like to try again someday.
And you all your insides are burning and everything.
You just sickening it up and that. Yeah.
Yeah. I'll do a foul.
I'll do one. I don't mind.
Vindeloo doesn't bother me.
But it's like the girl tenant, man. That
girl that used to pay rent, she had some
of my V vindaloo before and she couldn't eat
uh more than one mouthful of it. She was
like, and I'm just I'm just scoffing it.
I'm just scoffing it, bro. You know?
Yeah. Vindaloo. I'm used to Vindaloo, bro.
Win to lose.
See, virgin boy needs a coma.
The skinned virgin in the bed sit needs
a little coma. Candymana.
That's more for him. A little coma. Chicken coma.
Yeah, that Carolina Reaper burger is mad, bro.
That is mad.
When you have to sign a leaf here, you
know you're [ __ ] in for a madness.
No, I've never tried it.
See, sometimes I have Madras, sometimes
I have Vindeloo. It just depends.
He's under so many different accounts.
But even when I have Chinese, I always
get like Delapinos in the I always get
spice in the chicken fried rice with the
beef tain in the winter. Anyways, it
gives it that extra kick, you know.
Yeah, foul is hot though. I've had a
fail before when I had CO.
Yeah, that was hot. No, no, no. That was
But it ain't as hot [clears throat] as
the Reaper burger.
It isn't, bro. Trust me.
Feels like your insides are burning and everything.
The moment you have to sign that leaf,
yeah, you're you you're just going to
get anxiety. You know that.
At least I got two repliers.
That woman in Manchester didn't reply.
That was a good conversation. You can
always fathom like who's going to reply,
who's not going to reply.
That was strange
cuz she seemed down to earth.
Maybe she replied tomorrow or something.
Just coming back from uh she said she
drove, didn't she? So maybe she's tired.
Strange, isn't it? Normally you can tell
who who replies and who doesn't.
[snorts] Strange though. I did think
they were going to reply. They were
right. And I met her and her friend. Strange.
And the other two, I didn't think they
were going to reply, but they did reply.
That is strange. That is strange. Um,
yeah, I'll try it. I'll try it.
Like even Dave's Chicken, like even if
you get a medium, it's so hot. I don't
know why that place is so hot.
See, this is so [ __ ] up. Like, you
know, when I done these approaches and I
got two people that spoke to me, you
wouldn't get that online.
You wouldn't get that online. You could
message a woman and they they wouldn't
even speak to you.
So weird, isn't it?
I feel sorry for young men. Bless their
little hearts. The [ __ ] they have to go through
to meet a woman.
Why do you get a lot of people from Kent
that go to that Simmons? You get a lot
of people from Kent that go to Simmons in London.
It's strange, isn't it? [clears throat]
That's weird. I think it's cuz they see
like magic mic and stuff. I don't know. [ __ ] weird. Oh. Oh god.
Oh, this woman's I got some good looking women, bro.
Who is this?
Oh, another ignorer.
They changed their picture, but they
don't reply to you.
Oh, that got mixed up there. So many
stuck up [ __ ] in this country, bro.
So stuck up.
Stuck up [ __ ]
Oh, that's an event in London.
Strange, is it?
If I was a virgin, I'd go out
approaching every day. But I don't want
a woman that badly, bro.
And I'm not going to
put up with that [ __ ] just to find
someone. Does that make sense?
It'd be nice if you could find someone
genuine and stuff,
but uh like it's not worth putting
yourself putting up with their [ __ ] to
find someone like it ain't that deep, bro.
It ain't that deep. Whereas obviously if
you was a virgin like virgin boy
obviously you used to lose your vcard
you used to lose your replay
you know but it's not worth it if uh
it's not worth put up with their [ __ ]
just in order to try to find someone
if that makes sense.
The [ __ ] the games, the toxicity.
It's not worth it.
No, it ain't worth it, lad. >> [snorts]
>> Virgin boy just killing his little bed [ __ ] you know.
What the [ __ ]
Oh, that virgin boy.
All right, boy. One sec.
Had to fill up some space before I use a WhatsApp again.
I was trying to think of an insult, an
Australian insult, but I couldn't think of one. >> Yeah,
>> she don't want to know you. Should
I play some roulette? Stephen, I would
like some roulette. Nah. Nah, mate.
I do that [ __ ]
No, thank you.
Is that good that I can afford jeans and
trainers? Steven Howard,
200 lb jeans, 200 five 210 lb trainers.
Virgin bike can't do that.
You need a [ __ ] virgin fing.
Yeah, I spent 500 pound 23 trainers.
Well, 210 on trainers. Yeah, I spent 250 yesterday. Yeah.
Yeah, sick it.
Yeah, man. I could have done with that
football bet yesterday coming in, mate.
No, I'm confident anyways. I don't need
new garments to be confident.
I'm confident anyways.
No matter what I wear, I can go out
approaching in some shorts. I'd be confident.
Uh, I could have done with that football
bet coming in though, mate.
All I needed was Spymore to score.
All I needed was [ __ ] Spenny more to
score. The bastard [ __ ]
Bastard [ __ ] man.
Just one one go away. I would have loved
to rub in people's face. I got a treble.
Both got no draw.
I'll try and get one next week.
I'll try and get one up next week. Hey,
you understand what I mean? Is it Candy?
Man, it'd be nice to meet someone and
stuff, but I'm not putting my I'm not
like dealing with toxic [ __ ]
Um, just in order to find someone. Do
you get me?
Like, I'm not going to go out every week
dealing with negativity in order to find someone.
I'm not going to put up with their [ __ ] Um,
you know what I mean? It's just not worth it.
Just doesn't seem worth it. Find someone.
One second. Slender. Yeah, man.
It's always going to be the same there,
Jim. You know this.
I know. I almost got the treble both
score and no draw. Almost though. I
almost got it.
Just spending more. I needed to score.
It's not hard to put off. I'll get it
next week. Not three teams, but I'll get two teams.
It's not that hard on the lower leagues. Yeah. [snorts]
Yeah, I'm going to put £150 on a both
score no draw double.
That'll pay a lot of money in it.
It doesn't matter where I put the bet on, lad.
That doesn't matter, does it?
Yeah. Imagine that 150 on a both score
no draw double
be lovely wouldn't Nah. Uh yeah.
What do you reckon the chances of
getting laid these days if you're a
virgin, Steven Howard? Like, say you was
a virgin and you was just starting off
trying to get laid. What do you think
the chances are? Why?
Yeah, you could. I mean, you'd have to
approach on the street every day, but
that that USA is once in a lifetime.
That was one in a lifetime, bro.
Oh, that's even more better words, isn't it?
You remember go on the apps.
You remember Candyman go on the dating apps.
Showing the apps.
Candyman go on the dating apps.
Timmy's my friend now. Steven Howard.
Yeah, Timmy's my friend now.
Yeah, Timmy is my friend now. Is it mad?
So me putting that video up with a
bounces basically caused a lot of [ __ ]
in it for Timmy, Michael, and LT. That's madness.
So I am the root cause, isn't it?
Are you there, Grezy?
There's this guy kind of man that I
spoke to right
about 10 years ago. Some black guy,
right? Used to speak to him when I was
like uh no, when I was about 16. And the
thing is, bro, yeah, he said something
to me before. He said that he was uh he
said that he was on a bus before in
Brixton with his sister and he said,
"I've got to get off this bus. There's
eyes." I would never forget it, bro.
Even to this day, he was like, "There's
eyes on me, bro. There's eyes on me. I I
need to get off this bus. There's eyes
on me, bro." I was howling, bro, for
like 10 minutes. And now that like I
stalk him on like um social media and
I'll always message saying there's eyes
on me. He says that you need to grow up.
He says there was eyes on me on the bus.
Like he's got YouTube. He's tried to get
away from me several times and I'll just
make an account and he knows exactly
what I mean when I say that. There's
eyes on me. [laughter]
There's eyes on me on this bus. He said
to his sister, "There's eyes on me. Yeah,
[laughter] you know what that means, is
it? Candy man,
it's some black guy, bro.
Yeah, [clears throat] it is.
I think Virgin boy needs to get laid.
What was that?
Yeah, there's eyes on the bus.
There's eyes on you. Oh,
you can't deny she's attractive.
You little copycat.
That's how catchy that is. You little copycat.
That virgin's born on February, isn't he?
Yeah. That virgin's born on February.
The skint virgin. Yeah.
I need to go a bit. I'm tired.
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> Bro, that French that there was a woman
from France. She was taking a piss.
She said, "I'm not actually in the UK."
Bro, they take the [ __ ] piss these
women in it. I'm not actually in the UK.
They're [ __ ] [ __ ] isn't it?
I'm not actually in the UK. I was
pissing myself laughing, bro.
You're not going to lose it like that.
You're not going to pop it like that. virgin.
I was out drinking yesterday.
That's why I'm sleepy.
Oh, I'm so sleepy.
I'm a sleepy Bubba. I agree.
There's this guy that I was speaking to
13 years ago and he said a saying that
when he went on the bus with his sister,
he said there's eyes on him. He told me
the story that he went to Brixton cuz we
both live in London and he said he will
never go there again. He said there's
eyes on me on this bus. There's eyes on
me. I was dead, bro. I was laughing for
like 10 minutes and now I I find him on
his social media. He goes on 13 years
later. I'll find him and say there's
eyes on me.
The eyes are on you still. And he will
say grow up. He blocks me on everything.
He remembers it. There's eyes on me,
Greavvesy, on this bus, bro. There's
eyes on me.
There's eyes on me, bro. Heck Exactly. Kian Rice. Kevin Rice,
did you like the little Aussies? Greavesy.
Did you like little Aussies I was arguing with?
Do you like it? Grim
I can't believe I caused all of that
[ __ ] Grezy. Just cuz I put a video up
of me arguing.
Am I the cause of all of this, Gregy?
Am I the one behind it all? Imagine
if I didn't get Monty on this community
greasy. He would still be Kaye and he
would still have his kids. He would
still be with Kaye and have his kids.
That's mad, isn't it?
I was watching Stew a little earlier.
I was watching this a little earlier.
Greavves on YouTube.
It's the same website Monty lost it all
and he [clears throat] still won't get off YouTube.
You like Stew a little, don't you, Grezy?
You like five guys, don't you?
Why did that Aussie Izzy drink my drink?
I can't believe she nicks my drink. Maybe.
Did you like them, Grezy? >> [snorts]
>> They ain't interested in this country. agrees.
No, I want to beat up virgin boy.
I want to beat up virgin boy and
just getting virgin.
sec 21st of February 1995.
We know your date of birth.
You nasty virgin. Hello.
Yeah, you can't deny she's attractive.
Yeah, but you can't deny that she's attractive, can you?
You can't attract. No. Oh, no. Copycat.
You little copycat is virgin by a little
copycat. Where is he? Is he a little cat?
Is he a little cat? Little copycat.
Is there no copycat?
Oh, self projecting.
Is he all copycat? Little copycat.
There's no copycat. Hello copycat.
A little copycat.
I can't stop saying it cuz he is a
little copycat, isn't he?
Likes to fit in with the crowd. We
No, cuz he's a little copycat.
He's a little copycat.
Steven Howard, why does he say that
several Cole is attractive?
Why does non leg say Cheryl Cole's
attractive? Go on.
[snorts] Why does he say that?
He says the bloody fit in with the crowd.
He doesn't want to feel left out.
Crazy. He doesn't want to feel left out.
He wants to All he wants to do is bloody
well fit in. Bless him.
All he just wants to fit in with the crowd.
He just wants to bloody well fit in.
You know, we've all been like that.
He wants to fit in with the crowd. He
doesn't want to feel left out, you know.
Hello. Hello. Copycat. Right,
I'm gone. See you later.