Oh gosh,
I'm stuffed. Where's he? Too much ticker ticker. Oh. This [clears throat]
Oh gosh. Does it do that?
I'm just doing my little bedding.
Why does it do that?
Oh, I told you I'd do the co video,
mate. Cost me 45 [ __ ] quid. Bloody
hell. And yes, I said it. Bloody. Cuz
that's my favorite word. Oh man.
[ __ ] lost 80 pound on the bloody
roulette, didn't I? [ __ ] sake.
Gosh darn it. Yeah,
I think we're going to have to ban
Joseph for all our channel, lads.
Well, our channel, my channel. Yeah, I
reckon I'm going to have to ban Joseph Har.
Hey, with you, boss.
or they have to run it by
first as always. We always got to run it by bloody [ __ ] you know.
Nah, it's fine, bro. I'm a big strong Turkish man.
I lost 80 pound in the bookies, Grezy. I
was about to go home, lad. I lost 80
pound on a [ __ ] roulette, mate. A
[ __ ] raiding. I was about to do a [ __ ] U-turn.
It was about to be a [ __ ] U-turn.
Lost on a global jaw rulet. [ __ ] sake.
You know, I got some tasty donuts, by
the way. I'll show you in a minute.
I'll be out again on Saturday. I need to
find a new mama.
You know, I can't afford to do keep
going out for these cries and stuff,
Grezy. I can't afford to do that
multiple times a week. I need to find a new mama.
You know, it'd be cheaper.
So, I'd have to go back every week now
to try and find a new mama.
You know, I lost £80.
Don't know how you deal with it. You I
don't know how you deal with these
losses, lad. I get [ __ ] mad when I
lose. I hate losing.
Don't know about you, but I [ __ ] hate
losing. I do.
I [ __ ] hate losing, Kieran.
Are you the same or [ __ ] hate it?
[ __ ] hate losing me.
Oh, [ __ ] hate losing.
It does my [ __ ] night and it does. Wait,
no. The thing is with Jodo, when I have
a go at nods legs, he says he's got a
No, when I have the go at nods legs, he
said before he can't be a virgin. He's
got a girlfriend. He's got a girlfriend.
Yeah. When he goes at me, he never
brings up the story where like um I I
put a porno out there. Um when I had my
dick in a woman's mouth, when I was in
bed with women, they're fast enough to
defend that virgin, but no one defends
me. And having a disabled girlfriend
don't mean you've had bloody sex. I
prove I've had bloody sex.
You know why do people do that? Why do
people back that [ __ ] nons
stuff about me, lad?
I got some donuts.
Got some tasty donuts. Yep.
I kind of like a lot of crispy things to be fair.
Yeah, but see what I mean though,
Kieran? They back him up when I call him
a virgin, but when he goes at me, no one says anything.
Weird, isn't it? Uh,
>> which one should I take?
>> Answer me, G. Answer me, Kieran. When he
calls me a virgin, no one says anything. Oh,
I think I'm going to have a plain one for now. Oh gosh.
No one says anything to me when he calls
me a virgin. That's not fair, is it?
I wish you was here to have some place
to go. That's crazy with me.
Yeah, I'm sick of I'm sick of the
biasness. That's why sometimes I come
off of it, lad. Exactly. That's why I
come off of it
cuz I've actually proved I've had sex.
I've proved I've been with women. He's
never proved he's had sex, but you get
all of these little mongos saying, "Oh,
he's got a girlfriend. He's got a girlfriend."
Um, I'm not sure. I think they were like
123. No, no, no. They were more than that.
Like 15 maybe. I got close of it. About
15 quid. I spent about 150 today, I think.
Yeah. So Joe Joe is supposed to Joe is
supposed to not like nonslegs, right?
He's supposed to not like nonsex. Um
he's supposed to not like nonslegs, right?
Oh, he used to be impartial, but I've
never seen someone back me up when this
[ __ ] has called me a virgin.
Well, they back him up. They're biased
as [ __ ] They are biased. I don't know
if it's jealousy or they love nonsense.
It's either that they're jealous or they love nons
cuz it is [ __ ] weird.
Yeah. Yeah. Is autistic. [ __ ] autistic.
I bought lady some [ __ ]
Wanted some bags. So, I wash some [ __ ] Yep.
You saw my bed in there now.
Oh, that was a nice um Indian
£45. It cost me 80
over 100 pound today. [ __ ] weird. And also, yeah,
they are biased. How is biased as well?
I think they're either jealous of me or
they're not nons. It's one of the two, lad.
What life experience have you never had?
Yeah, you need to do some stuff, bro.
You need to I've done a lot of traveling, son. You know,
you haven't even been Scotland. Why
don't you go to London and go to a curry
house with you?
That coffee was nice though. I'm not
going to lie. It was making me sweat a
bit, but nothing like [ __ ] Nor was
going on, but
it was uh
it was making me sweat towards the end.
But sweat was pouring off my [ __ ] head.
Yeah, but I was nothing like it, man. I
only had one coke.
Took me ages to get down there as well,
Greg. It was cho block.
You know what that means, don't you,
Grezy? Chocolate block. I bet you gre I
bet you king would like a lovely donut.
But he's not allowed donuts. Oh gosh.
How many donuts there are?
Oh, bless you then.
lost £8 on [ __ ] roulette, man.
£80 on roulette. See what I mean,
Kieran? It's [ __ ] disgusting, man.
I didn't put any more in because I I
would just end up smashing the shop up.
You know, I like that. You K, you know
me. I'll just end up smashing the place up.
I'll just end up doing a [ __ ] shop here, mate.
But I I just gave up after 8 month.
Yeah. I'm a big strong Turkish man. I've
been having curry since I come out of lady's tummy.
Since they snipped their cord
since they snipped their cord.
Since then I've had um Yeah,
we need coffee. Basically,
I can have one more. Oh, I want a strawberry one. [snorts]
I'm so fat. Oh, me donuts. Strawberry one.
It's for good. I don't know my mama anymore.
So, I don't get the nutrients and the milk.
So, I kind of miss my mama.
I kind of miss my mommy.
It'll be 3 years in April since I met my mama.
I can go as fast, isn't it?
Yeah, see that's in the summer it's
fine. It's fine in the summer.
The summer is completely fine.
But I need the nutrients in the vitamins in winter. You know,
I give her steak, she gives me milk.
That's going to offer in it.
I give her steak. She gives me milk keys.
Would you say you like all of these
donuts, Greasy? There's one called
Reese's Peanut Butter. I think it's that
one. And it's got peanut butter.
Oh, I love Reese Peanut Butter.
Hurry up. Dry. I want to make you and
get in it.
Come have some donuts. You're more than welcome.
Bring your mates. Bring your little Something's fing.
Oh, Monty's just gone live. This just
popped up. It pops up when you go live.
Oh, gosh darn it.
So, Grezy, why why is it when I got with other women,
they weren't the same, Grezy,
even though they had like big boobs and stuff?
Do you reckon?
Oh, this is jam.
No, I don't like jam.
I don't really like jam to be fair.
Chuck that one. All the other ones I
know I like 100%.
I don't like jam. Yeah.
I tell you two things I don't like.
There's not a lot I don't like. Sweet popcorn and jam.
I hate sweet. I love popcorn and not sweet popcorn.
So why is it not the same if I get with
other women? Greavesy,
why is it not the same then?
When I get with other women, why is it
not the same then, Grezy?
Cuz they have boobs and stuff. So, why
is it not the same as my mama? Huh? What?
I didn't see him. But why is he not the
same then, Grezy? Why is it not the same?
No, I didn't see it, lad.
Answer me. Why is it not the same? Yeah,
but why Yeah, but why are the other
women not my mama? They had big boobies, too.
Yeah, but they have big boobies as well,
don't they? Grizzy
Peter Belly can't get attached anymore
because he's already found his mama
because he found his mama.
I'll be on the piss again Saturday. So,
there's some there's going to be more
tasty content to be had, Grezy.
There's going to be more tasty content
to be had.
>> Okay with you, boss.
Obviously, I've got to run it by you
first. Okay with you, boss.
Nope. Didn't get it, lad.
No, I didn't get it.
Obviously, [snorts] I've got to run it
by you first.
Yeah, I see that top, but I don't see
what you talking.
doesn't come up. You see? Yeah.
I'm starting to miss a booby stitch. Huh? [snorts]
Just snuggle up to
what videos. Okay, let me see.
Gosh darn it, Beezy.
So, you're 29 next year, isn't it?
You're 29 in March. No,
I'll look at your videos. One second.
I need to go on the live stream.
One second, bro. [clears throat]
So, you're 29 in March.
trying to find your account. I can't. I
need to go on my live stream to click on
your account and I can't do it. One second. Nope. One sec. [clears throat]
One second. Are you okay?
I'm I'm watching it. I'm watching it.
Mother [ __ ] [laughter] Best suckling. vegetables. Crazy. >> [laughter]
>> Yeah, she is my mama.
She looks like me, in it. How do you
know it's my mama though? Stitch jam.
Do you want to go for a pint or do you
want to do it dirty
or do you want to do it dirty, Grezy?
Which one? You want to go for a pint or
do you want to do it dirt or do you want
to do it bad?
Huh? Just answer me in it. Do you want
to go for a pint or do you want to do it bad?
I don't want to do it bad. You believe
me now and it gives you that I can do it
bad. Is it
me now? I can do it bad. Don't you? Huh?
Yep. You believe me now, don't you?
Yeah. Greasy believes me now. Oh gosh darn it.
Yeah. Did Did you tell him about my mama? Greasy.
Gosh. Darn it. Did you tell him about my mama? Huh?
Well, when he's live again, let me know
in it. I want to tell him about my mama. [laughter] Yep.
Tony Holly, let me have a
I'll be trolling someone else for a
change on their live stream. That'll be
interesting. Okay, I got him. I got him.
Says he's going to go live later. I want
to sub to him.
I'll be trolling someone else for a
change. Grezy, that's mad, isn't it?
She said breastic cause.
He said breasticles. Grazy
should have told him my mother.
You can't get attached anymore because
he already found his mama. [snorts] Yeah.
Were laughing at us. Crazy.
They were laughing at us.
>> Where were they?
Because you already found his mama.
He's already found his mama. One second.
What I do want to do it bad, huh?
Oh, look. He's still doing videos. He's
still doing videos. Greavves. You're on
the same website you can watch the sideman on.
Now they're going to have the same
argument for three months.
Timmy and Timmy and Monty's going to
have the same argument now for three
months. [ __ ] this. I'm not listening to
It's the same argument and it grieves me.
What did Timmy say? You can't really use
that chestnut. He said you can't really
use that chestnut. [laughter]
He said he just wants to smash Monty's
face in Grezy. [laughter]
Oh, I love salt and vinegar. Greasy. Oh god.
It's just the It's the same argument. See
Did you see the community posty? Yeah. [gasps] [laughter] [snorts]
Thank you, Captain.
All right, Captain.
Yeah, he is. He's the biggest virgin
going. Just like Nons Tiny Tim.
He's the He's the [ __ ] biggest virgin
going. the big Oh [ __ ] my bloody phone.
He's the biggest alltime virgin. The
virgin of all time. He's a big He's a
[ __ ] big big virgin. He's a big
virgin. You know,
he's a [ __ ] big virgin.
No, he's a big virgin. He's a big
virgin. He's a big virgin. Don't give me
that [ __ ] He's a big virgin. Just
like nons. Big virgin, mate. [ __ ] off. You know,
I lost 80 pound today in a roulette.
I'm not happy about that. actually makes
me quite sad. >> Yes.
The [ __ ] is Squidward in Kanya? Yeah. Right.
Wait for this bed to dry. One second.
Well, I got randomly blocked,
so I won't be asking that person out. All right. Okay.
All right. Let's get some other ones.
What are the maps?
Oh, is that your name?
What is that?
Don't follow Yeah.
Come on. Drive. I said
Uh, did I get any replies? [snorts]
I was just talking about them. So, I got five numbers.
One of them blocked me. The other one I
was sending voice notes. We were sending
voice notes. They blocked me. And then
another one replied back to me saying,
"It was really nice to meet you as
well." I said to them, "Did you get back
to France?" Okay. They didn't reply.
Messaged two others and they didn't
reply. So, same old [ __ ]
Out of five, two blocked, one replied,
and the others didn't reply. Well, one
must in the voice notes. Just [snorts]
the same old [ __ ] in it, Bob. Bills.
Just the same old England. It is what it is.
What? What more is there to be said?
Just the same old England. [gasps]
I mean, what did you what did you expect, lad?
Yeah. Obama's sending me voice notes and
they're randomly blocked, which is strange.
It will always be the same here.
I might go out next. I might go out this week. Uh
I know I didn't go out,
but I didn't approach. Why did I
approach? I went for food not to
approach. Why did I do any approaches?
I coped all right. It was all right. Yeah.
Yeah, it'll always be the same here, bro.
It would always be the same here.
So, I lost 80 pound on the roulette, by
the way. 80 [ __ ] quid on the
roulette. What a load of bollocks.
I was very mad at first, but then I was Yeah,
they just aren't interested in this
country. Bob bills.
It goes against what everyone else um
says, you know, lad. [clears throat] Yep.
I was almost going to go back home cuz
it would give me mood swings, but I just
went anyways. Yeah. To uh
I just went out. I just Anyways, yeah. 80 pound.
Yeah. [ __ ] [ __ ] in it. [ __ ] bro.
So, another weak no date by the looks of it.
[clears throat] Another another no date. Bob bills. Yep. Yeah.
But I still feel a bit hung over, you know.
Not as bad, obviously. [sighs] Yep. So yeah.
What a madness, isn't it? Bob the
Bob the Builder.
What does one do? >> [sighs]
>> Why would I go out tonight when I went
out last week?
Are you a [ __ ] or something?
You must be a [ __ ] Why am I going to
go out today when I went out Saturday?
No. when you know damn well it's just
going to be the same old [ __ ]
No, I'll go out Friday, bro.
No, I'll go out Friday.
Why am I, bro? Why am I going to [ __ ]
go out today? Why am I going to go out
on a Monday?
I feel sorry for you, bro. I like you,
man. But I do feel sorry for you
that you actually think it's going to
change in this country. You're crazy,
bro. You're actually mad.
Yeah, I don't need to I don't need to
drink, bro. I'm not an alcoholic.
I'm going out on Friday.
Yeah, I'll go out on Friday.
Yeah, I'll go out on Friday. Bro,
>> you still think there's hope in this
country? I feel sorry for you, bro.
What you do?
There's no hope here, lad. None whatsoever.
Didn't you know that
there's no hope in this country?
Never had him. But I'm going to go out
for a drink anyways on Friday.
Yeah, I think I should have like £1,300
left, I think.
So, not that much.
Yeah, man. Money just goes when you go
out drinking in it. It's [ __ ] [ __ ]
Yeah, it's [ __ ] [ __ ] in it, bro.
Yeah, there is no hope. I knew that.
That's why I don't mind going out, bro.
I don't mind about it.
I don't mind about it cuz uh
cuz the thing is like
cuz there is no hope. You see? So,
obviously since uh second last time I
went out when I got the numbers, I
didn't get a date. You just know that
there's there's no hope, bro. And it
maybe one day you'll get lucky. Maybe,
just maybe, very slim chance, but it's
fairly unlikely. You know, you we can't
even get dates. So, like I said, if you
can't even get a date, then doesn't look
good, does it? So, all that Xbox noise. So, yeah,
that's how it is, isn't it?
But it's fun to go out every like two
weeks. Not every week.
Not every week. It isn't fun every week, but
I mean it depends and it I don't know.
I'm still trying to meet someone at the
same time even though I know very very
very unlikely. But I mean if I was
already in a relationship or whatever
then yeah like every two 3 weeks but
I don't know. I don't know bro.
Yeah I was waiting but I wanted to smash
the shop up.
Yeah, it was 80 pound, bro. I wanted to
smash the [ __ ] shop up like
[ __ ] you know, man. Yeah.
Sometimes I like going out on the Friday
cuz on a Saturday you can do your football bets
and just be in all day and just chill.
That's why I like um going out Friday
sometimes, sometimes Thursdays. >> [sighs]
>> I got an escort as well.
I spent like500 pound. Huh?£500 [ __ ] pound.
[ __ ] Isn't it bro? Uh
yeah, it's the escort so expensive, is it? Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, man. £45
45 lost £80 spent 20 on donuts and coke and [ __ ] So >> yeah.
Yeah. That was £45, bro. But we're not
[ __ ] skinned like LJ, are we mate?
You know, we're not skinned like that [ __ ] So, oh man,
no, no, no, no, no.
Yeah, it's lush, bro. Lush. Lush. Lush. Ah.
Yeah. It's so hard to pull in this
country. People sit there, Bob, and say
you can get laid easy. You go on dating
apps and [ __ ] They're [ __ ] idiots.
They're just [ __ ] idiots, aren't
they? Bro, I'm surprised that woman in
Manchester didn't reply.
She seemed genuine. See, I like to give
people the benefit of the doubt, man.
Like me. Like I said, I like to give
people the benefit of the doubt. But nope.
That surprised me. I thought like she
would have replied today cuz obviously
if she was driving back, it's like 5
hours. She might have been tired.
Strange, isn't it, bro? I like to give
people the benefit of the doubt. They
seemed all right. Don't they all seem
all right, bro?
Don't they all seem all right? Yeah.
Surprised they didn't reply back? I am surprised
cuz normally you can guess who's going
to reply back, who's not going to reply back.
Two reply backs. Yeah. Then
45 quid that middle cost me.
Oh, did I make you uh did I make you hungry, lad?
Yeah, they make you hungry, bro. I'm
[ __ ] tired now. Oh, [ __ ]
Now I have like 14,300 13,400 to last me
a bloody month. Greasy.
It's not great, is it, lad?
It's not great, is it, matey?
Yeah, man. I only spent £500 over the weekend.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
I spent like £1,000 in it.
I spent like £1,000 in it. Really? Think about it. [ __ ] sake. A greasy. Oh,
what do you think? We usually go out on
Friday or not.
Is that okay with you, boss?
It's okay with you, boss. If I choose to
go out, is that okay with you, boss? Why not?
They've all got bloody boyfriends.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Okay with you, boss. Why is that not
okay with you, boss? Huh?
Yep. I have done. Yeah. Approaching.
I just don't have the energy for it anymore.
When my sex drive used to be high and
stuff, I would do it. But it's like um
I'm not going to disrespect myself in
order to find someone. Does that make
sense, Greg? I'm not going to humiliate
myself in order to find someone. Whereas
back then, I didn't care. you know, like
when I was horny and whatever, but I'm
not going to disrespect myself. Um,
and humiliate myself and deal with games
just to find someone. I'd rather just not.
So, I think it's a right thing, you know.
I think it makes um [ __ ] [snorts]
perfect sense. Huh?
Cuz it's always the same [ __ ] with them.
You know what I mean? I don't mind going
out once in a while. You know, it's fun or whatever. But
yeah, it'd be nice to find someone, but
not to the point where I'm going out
every day and approaching. I'm not doing it.
If, like I said, if I was a virgin or
something, then it'd be different. Or,
you know, I tried enough, bro. So,
I don't know why it's so [ __ ] hard,
man. Don't know why that person was
voice me then randomly blocked me. It's
just weird. They're too stuck up.
It's like there's no
just too um Yeah. stuck up.
with a 19year-old.
But a 19year-old
that was in the summer
was not summer. Was it in the summer?
Yeah, it was in the summer.
So quite a while ago [snorts]
I think it is now. Yeah.
You can't even get that. You can't even
get that anymore.
So I can't go out Friday, Grezy. Is that
what you're saying?
So you're saying it's not okay with you, boss.
Is that what you're [ __ ] trying to say?
So, it's not okay with you, boss. No.
I said, "Can I go out drinking on Friday, boss?"
Is that okay with you, boss?
or if there's any rules or whatever. I'm
not going to get my haircut until next
week, I think.
I will still be single at Xmas. It's not
I could be, I will be.
There's no could be. I will be.
Why? Why wouldn't I be single by Xmas?
I've been single all this time.
Well, why wouldn't I be? Why wouldn't I
It's not a could be. I will be.
So there's no could be. I will be.
Yeah, that's that's that is it.
There's no could be about it.
That Chloe's made me tired, lad.
It's not white. Mhm.
I'm tired, bro. [ __ ] me. Them donuts and that food. [snorts]
Yeah. L went to Iceland cuz he's skinning it. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Is that right? Crazy boss.
Why won't I be spending Christmas on my
own? Would I, you idiot?
I'll be going to my I'll probably be
spending it with my mom and sister.
You spend a lot.
You spend a lot when you go out drinking, Bob.
Jeez, we spend a lot boss.
What? You blew 260 in two days. Oh.
Yeah. I spent about like 400
Friday uh Saturday to now. Yeah.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
I feel I'm going to go on a big uh
broulette session at some point, right?
Yeah, that was 400 500. That's 900.
So, I'll be left with like £1,300 or
something like that. Yeah.
Should be all right for the month.
Oh boy. It's expensive, is it, man?
I don't mind, bro. I don't mind. I kind
of like the stress of money. Not the
stress of it, but you know. I don't
I mean, I can work, but it's just I
can't bother. I can't be bothered working.
Get back to like,500. I'll be all right in it.
I'll be all right, I guess. A
yeah, 100% I am.
I get my I get £800 in a couple of days. So
tempted. Yeah, but I'm not going to
It is tempting, but I'm not going to.
See, that's the cycle. You get you deal
with [ __ ] with women, which again, I
expect it's to be expected. So, you deal
with [ __ ] with women
and then then you want to buzz cuz you
don't get buzz from women. Then you try
to gamble to get buzz. So, you just
constantly go around in circles.
You understand? So, you're constantly
always going around in circles.
You understand? Until you obviously leave
until you leave uh England, you will
always go around in circles here. But I
ain't gambling, bro. I'm not doing it anyways. So that's
Yep. I told him about himself.
So it will always be the same cycle till you leave.
I could lose 500 pound right now and
just not go out for the rest of the month.
Obviously, I'm not going to do that, am I?
I'm not going to cuz I'm have like 600
pound to live off.
No, I already lost 80 earlier. I'm good.
I'm good, bro. I lost £80 earlier, so
I'm not gambling again. Nope. No.
Earlier before I went for the curry.
Yeah, I went for the before I went to the curry.
I never did chase my losses in the first place.
I never did. So
yeah, it's £80
like global draw roulette.
It doesn't matter if I played online or
I didn't play online Kevin. It was going
to be the same anyways.
It doesn't matter, bro. Don't worry. Um,
yeah, I'll be out on Friday anyways and
I'll be doing a football bet. [sighs] So, That's up.
It will never change, will it, Kieran?
And you'll never change. So
that's that in it. Kieran, get used to
it or leave.
Well, it will never change, will it?
I have like,300 pound to last me a month. Karen,
it's pretty [ __ ] E, 13,400 pound to
last you a month. It's pretty [ __ ] E,
It's pretty [ __ ] ain't it, Kieran?
Yeah, it's all right. But if I go out
drinking and [ __ ] might sp No, I won't
spend that much.
It's all right, bro.
I'm just tempted to go big on roulette,
bro. I really am tempted.
I'm not going to do it, though. I'm
tempted to [ __ ] bro.
To just do madness on roulette. [ __ ] do that.
Yeah, there's a site I play at called Spin Dog.
I hadn't I didn't put any of the £500
back. I got £500. I didn't put any of it
But I lost 80 today. That was the first
time in ages.
That was the first time in ages, guys. [sighs]
Like, I'm going to do a football bet,
though. Definitely. I'm going to do a
football bet on um Saturday.
I don't know. I might do a double both
score, no draw. I don't know.
What? I put 30 on three four teams.
I'm not doing it, bro. I'm not doing it.
I ain't doing it, lad. [snorts]
You got £300 in it.
So what are you what would you do if you
wanted to go out drinking K and you
couldn't do it in it?
You couldn't do it, could you? You'd be
[ __ ] up in it.
Yeah, you'd be [ __ ] up in it. Kieran.
Yeah. If you wanted to go for a drink,
you'd be [ __ ] up.
Yeah. I can't be doing [ __ ] like that anymore, lad.
It's a stressful mood swing life. I
can't be doing [ __ ] like that anymore, bro.
Why don't you go out drinking?
Why don't you go out drinking here and
get some birds?
Yeah, I got older and wiser and the
money's dried up as well. But it's not
No, it's not about the money really,
bro. I can still afford to do it, but I
uh even when I had the house, bro, I
stopped for months, bro. I think I used
to gamble every month, every two months.
So, even when I had the house and I
still have money now, I still don't do
it because it's the mood swings and
you've already got to worry about women
as it is. And I don't want to worry about money.
I don't want to worry about money as
well as worry about women. You see,
you understand? That's that's what puts
me off it. And then mood swings and Yeah.
I can't meet anyone on puff.
I can't beat anyone on puff. I can't get anyone.
No one's bloody interested. You know,
the thing is, oi Kieran, you know, if
you go central London, you drink [ __ ]
If you go central London and you drink rum,
right? If you go central London and you drink rum. Yeah,
you go central London and you drink rum,
right? It they water it down, bro. I
done like 40 in 20 minutes. It was
crazy. It's so watered down. That's why
you need to drink beer. They can't water
beer down. They water that [ __ ] down, bro.
So when they water it,
so when they water it down, you drink it
quicker. Whereas Guinness, they can't do
that. Guinness will [ __ ] you up, bro.
You like three Guinnesses?
But yeah, obviously you don't go out
like me, do you, K? But yeah, I'm older
and wiser now. That's why I don't do it.
The gambling, it's not about that money.
I can gamble right now if I wanted to,
bro. I gambled earlier. Just the mood
swings and [ __ ] that, bro.
I don't go out drinking much anymore,
but I'll go I'll go again this week just
cuz why not? [snorts] Yeah.
And all the women say they got
boyfriends anyway, isn't it, Kieran?
They all got bloody boyfriends.
They've got bloody boyfriends, don't they, Kieran?
Gosh darn it. Gosh
Just [ __ ] darn it, mate.
You're not right.
Oh, I want to have a baby, Kieran. I
want to meet someone and have a baby.
A baby Peter. Should
I had baby Peter with USA? For [ __ ] sake.
Wonder what would happen if I stayed
there. Didn't leave after sex.
Well, guess what, Grezy?
Now I'll never know. Jesus Christ.
You always do your balls in gambling,
don't you? [ __ ] Kieran. You always do
your bollocks in
Dy's bollocks. Doo doo doo doo. Timmy's
done. He's bollocking. D sometimes.
Tmy's done his bollocking. Doo doo doo
doo. Timmy's done his bollocking. D
Timmy's done his bollocks in D
sometimes. That's cute, isn't it? Yeah.
That's like me though. When I turned
that £100 into£500, I was buzzing, bro.
I was buzzing, lad.
Cuz I had a [ __ ] weekend and then I [ __ ] Yeah.
Jimmy's done his bollocks in D sometimes.
Yeah. So, I liked how chat earlier when
you win they they do anything not to pay
you out in it.
Yeah, that is true. They'll do anything
not to [ __ ] pay you out.
The [ __ ] bastards and it. Yeah.
Yeah. He was like [sighs]
and I had a hotter than Vindeloo and I
weren't [ __ ] acting like that. It did
make me sweat towards the end.
Like he's Everyone's got a different
tolerance. When I was having that Grim
Reaper burger, that's the same reaction
I had to LJ having that Vindaloo.
That almost killed me, bro. And trust
me, you can't hold it in. Yeah.
I made some friends around there cuz I
always used to go to the curry house and
that uh I said the curry industry I
guess what it's called. That's what it's
But you can't hold it in, bro.
If he had that Caroline Reaper burger
Kieran, he'd be finished. He'd probably
end up in hospital, bro. Because it
almost killed me, bro. I remember I was puking everywhere. Yep.
So when you gambling again anyways Karen
Yeah, I'll go in a few weeks. So,
so what will happen if I win like 30
grand online Karen? You reckon I'll pay?
You reckon I'll pay, lad?
You reckon I'll pay or what?
If I want like 20, 30 grand, you reckon
I'll pay me?
What about 5K?
I might go to Nottingham and have a gamble.
There's a casino I can get in Nottingham
if you want me to go Nottingham. Uh Kieran,
last time I went to Nottingham, I got a [ __ ]
by a woman in the hotel.
It was lush. Grievy. It was a lush
weekend with Antman. I went home on the
Monday. Yeah, I stayed another [ __ ]
night, didn't I?
Yeah, I stayed I stayed another night.
cuz I went out with Ant-Man on the Saturday. Um,
and so I was I met I got a Snapchat in
it and we was talking and then she's
like, "Oh, you want to meet?" And I said
to Anman, "Oh, I might have to stay
another night, mate. I might have to
stay another night." And he's man was
like, "Has she got any friends for me?"
And I asked her, she's like, "No." So I
met her at Spoons and then [ __ ] we
just went to the hotel.
We was kissing. She was touching my dick
and every time she moved her hand, I put
her hand back on my dick. We g we
had big boobies as well.
Yeah. Then she sucked my todd cuz we
couldn't [ __ ] because she was on her
period, you see.
Yeah. She was on her period.
I never again
a few times. Oh, ling mate here.
Yeah, Rock City is uh is good, bro.
You get loads of slags there.
Should I go Nottingham on Saturday? Grezy
Oh, I hate that Charlie vouch. I'd love
to slap him in. He's a [ __ ]
Very bad. That never happened.
Never happened, mate.
The thing is with London, uh, it's very
westernized here in the women think
they're better than they are.
Autistic friendly. I know that was jokes.
All right. L skinting it. Ken
L is skinned, bro. It's so obvious,
isn't it? Who the [ __ ] would get a
Vindaloo from Iceland?
He's skin. [laughter]
He's [ __ ] skinting skin. Flint.
Yeah, you know he's skint, bro. He's skinn. >> [laughter]
>> their skin. Antman said that he almost
shhat his underpants. [laughter]
You know, sometimes I think that guy's a
troll, bro. Honestly, I think he's a
troll. Sometimes he says underpants. [laughter]
I have you ever called Have you ever
called Have you ever called him underpants?
Trope is autistic friendly. Yeah.
Autistic friendly. [laughter]
That's jokes, isn't it? I can't watch
him and Monty, though. It's the same
argument, Kieran. I can't watch it, lad.
Ah, I can't watch it, bro. It's the same
argument, isn't it?
It's just the same [ __ ] argument. And
you know, do you know when you watch it,
the more you watch it, Yeah. the more
you want to get involved.
The more you want to get involved,
you understand? because it's so
annoying. It's the same [ __ ] City argument.
See what I mean? Look, they're still
going at it. Here, [ __ ] Meet me, [ __ ] See?
It's the same argument, Grezy. Is it not
the same argument with them two?
With them two [ __ ]
It's the same argument, is it not? These
are not the same argument.
Imagine we me and USA easy does a
cooking video together. Greavvesy
cooking t-bone steak.
Autistic friendly. I know it's jokes.
Yeah, I did.
Yeah, I did. I did, bro. Years ago.
Yeah. Yeah. What was his name now? He
was a fat guy. I was thinking of this
the other day, actually.
Yeah, I did. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I met him
New Year's Eve.
Yeah. Oh, what was his name? [ __ ]
I can't remember his name, bro.
It was weird.
Do you still have his channel? One New
Year's Eve, I met this guy when I was
going around sending it uh a few years
back and uh he was all right. I forget his name.
W Glenn was it?
I can't think of his name.
It was weird, wasn't it? Do you have his channel still?
No, not Bob.
Yeah, Jim. That's the [ __ ] Oh, you
[ __ ] have you got a better memory
than me, mate.
Yeah. Yeah, Jim. Jim. Yeah, he he was a
pretty good [ __ ] He was
you should have saw USA's boobies,
Kieran. You would have loved them.
You would have loved them, lad.
Taking a baby away from its mama.
My bed's in the dryer, by the way.
I'm tired, boss.
Kieran, I'm tired, boss.
Nah, he deserved it. He was trolling me,
bro. He trying to use me for cocaine and
money and [ __ ] Nah, nah, nah. [ __ ] him, bro.
He's a nasty little troll. He was just
trying to use me as well.
I wonder what happened to him.
Do you still have his channel? Oh,
that's his channel, isn't it? Yeah. No,
I was thinking of him the other day, lad.
Oh, that's the con. Yes.
Wait, are you sure that's him?
No, that's not him, is it?
It's not him, is it?
He looks different.
Oh yeah, it is him. Yeah,
I want to comment on his video saying,
"Do you remember me?"
It was mad, isn't it, lad?
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> I'm going to knock him out. Who said
that grieving? Come here, lad. [laughter]
I'm going to knock him out.
Come here, lad.
Come here, [laughter] lad. Who said that? Greavvesy.
Yes. He said Shrewsbury is autistic
friendly. Grezy. [laughter] Yeah.
Oh, that fantasy story is annoys me,
bro. [ __ ] Northern Irish ma.
[ __ ] Northern Irish [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah, it's good you remembered his name,
Greavvesy. I didn't.
Women hate him as well. That's why he's
still a virgin.
Yeah. So, you can agree that even Joe's
biased though, is it casual? Even though
he might be all right sometimes, he's
still biased because like we said, he
doesn't say anything to non-stigs when
he's called me a virgin. So, he must be
slow in his brain or something, bro.
It's like what you said. Yeah. They're
biased, isn't it? Yeah.
Yeah. Bias is it lad?
Yeah. But everything's all right. What?
Like I said to you, why has he said
nothing when he's called me a virgin?
But when I call him a when I call him a
virgin, oh, he's got a girlfriend. Oh,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no. That's what I mean.
But yeah, I get you. Yeah, lad. Yeah,
that's what I mean. That's why I don't
like that Joe either.
So, who wait? Who's got more chance?
Who's got who's got who's got more
chance of being a virgin, bro? Someone
that's proved they've had sex or
somebody that's with a disabled girl.
Come on, bro. Who Who's who who would
you believe more so that's had sex?
You know, the only person that hasn't
defended him is Greavves and Steven
Howard. So, we know that he's definitely
the brothers. It's like that Ricky Millington.
He's like, he's got a girlfriend, bro. A
disabled girlfriend. That does not mean
he's had sex. People have seen me have
sex. It's like what you said. It's it's it's uh Yeah,
that Ricky Millington's trying to say
I'm jealous of him and I've got more
money than him. I've been on holiday
before him and I've been to more places than him,
but I'm jealous of some little skin virgin.
The guy's an idiot, bro.
[sighs and snorts]
Guy is an idiot.
I think me personally, lad.
Yeah. Then I caught him talking [ __ ]
behind my back on N's legs.
Yeah. I caught him talking [ __ ] Then he
come back on my live stream and I said,
"If you got anything to say, say it to my face." Yeah.
I said, "You got something to say? Say
it to my [ __ ] face." Then he [ __ ]
ran off. So yeah,
that's usually what happens, isn't it?
[gasps] Do you understand the key
with a lot of these people, they'll be
cool to you on here, but then they'll
talk [ __ ] behind your back.
I don't know if you've noticed it or
not. That's what happens on there for some reason. Yep.
Do you remember when USA is commanders
community? She's like, "What the [ __ ] Yep.
Yeah, Reddit's full of nerds. You know,
the thing is, Kieran, they ban you on
there to feel powerful.
The mods ban you to feel powerful. Do
you not realize it's a power thing?
Cuz they can ban you and you can do
nothing about it.
It's all It's all to do with power.
I don't know if you noticed that with
Reddit or I'm sure you've seen it. They
need to be in control. Without that
power, they're [ __ ] [snorts]
Yeah, it was funny, isn't it? I thought
it was funny, bro,
when they messaged USA. Is he? Who was
the root cause of it all? Greasy.
Cuz I done a video of the bouncer and
then all of a sudden Timmy and [ __ ]
LT started arguing. All because of that video.
All cuz I done that video. cause a lot
of [ __ ] don't I? Yeah.
Is that my crazy? Yeah. >> [laughter]
>> How's that?
I think you like USA, don't you, Kieran?
Yes, she deleted her WhatsApp. Must have
changed her number properly this time.
Yeah, I do remember it.
It was some troll account. Yeah, it was
like 3 4 years ago now.
Yep, I remember that. Yeah.
No, she didn't. How do you know that?
What? USA is e Yeah.
Oh, yeah. Sig Yeah.
Yeah. He's a virgin. He is. He said
[ __ ] 40 year old virgin in the
making. That's you. You are a virgin.
You're a big virgin. And you know what
the maddest thing is? I may just can't
go to the police on me and no one says
anything about it. They think that's a win
because they're disabled. They think
going to the police on someone that's
them winning. They think that's them winning, lad.
For some reason they think that's a win
because they can get the police involved
and that's [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
They'd still call you a virgin.
Even if you was a porn star, they'd
still call you a virgin. Isn't that right, Kieran?
Oh gosh, the car's knocked me for six.
Knock me for six.
He's a [ __ ] He's a crazy virgin,
mate. He's a mad virgin.
That Ricky is a little geek. You know
that Ricky, you could just tell that
he's never seen a woman naked. The way
he just simps some white knights. People
that do that are people that don't get
women. Never had a woman. Well, people
that never had a woman in their life.
They're the only people that white
night, bro. You know that.
Do you remember the weather spoons? the
three white knights.
They wanted to get involved in it. They
wanted to get involved, but
nah, mate. They weren't going to go
anywhere near Peter B, were they?
[sighs and gasps]
That's starting it.
Do you remember that account? Uh,
Kieran, don't let that
Don't uh let them Don't let them [ __ ] women win.
Do you remember that account, Kieran?
Don't let them [ __ ] women win.
Do you remember that one? Don't let We
can't let them [ __ ] women win, can we? Grezy,
who you reckon that cat account is? Cuz
I thought it was Joker, but it isn't.
You take my money, I [ __ ] take yours. Kieran,
>> you take my money, Kieran. I [ __ ] take yours.
Do you remember when Ant-Man said that?
[gasps] You want to take my [ __ ]
money? I'll [ __ ] take yours. [sighs]
Do you remember? Yeah.
Yeah. Did you like them?
[laughter] Do you remember when I put
the posters up, Grezy? Everybody was
waiting for the notifications. They were
all sat there waiting. I said, "I'm
going to do posters of this little
virgin pant." And no one believed it.
Do you remember? No one believed it. Yeah,
everyone was waiting, bro. LT, do you
remember? Everybody was waiting. They
were just sat there waiting in the womb.
Bam. You got a load of notifications
on the same website you could watch the
side men on.
Yeah. A [ __ ] virgin. And he ran to
the old bill cuz he's a [ __ ] loser.
He He was a [ __ ] loser. He had to get
the police involved cuz he couldn't
handle me. You know what I'm saying? But
no one says that. They think it's a win. [laughter]
You like the porno, Grezy? I've still got it.
Yeah, the porno. I've still got it, lad.
Yeah, it was lovely, wasn't it?
She was sucking my willie.
Yeah, she was sucking my willie, bro. I
used to give her money. She used to
drive to me.
She used to drive to me. We used to [ __ ]
We used to [ __ ] all night long. Clearly, [laughter]
she was autistic friendly. Yeah.
Yeah. We was [ __ ] weren't we? Yep.
Did you like the poor Kieran?
You can see the westernity in their eyes.
In it, you can see the westerinity in
their eyes. Grezy,
that dirty westernized look they give
you in it.
That dirty look. Yeah.
Have you ever had a filling greasy?
What's it called when like you got a
gum, right? And it it's a bit swollen
and it's sore. Is that like a root canal?
What do you call that? Is it a root
canal or what?
What's it called?
That's what I got. I need to go a dentist, bro.
It's like a bit swollen here.
It's [ __ ] stinking, bro.
It's like a root canal or not an absess.
You know how to fill him. Yeah.
You like the dentist, Greavves? Are you
scared of them? My mom's scared of
dentists. I don't mind. They're me.
Yeah. What's everyone waiting for?
wanted to come out.
Yeah, I love tent. I love dentists. I
love it when they clean your teeth.
So, what is he outside Monty's? What? [laughter]
This ain't going to stop, is it? This
ain't going to stop with these two
[ __ ] I can't do it with these two [ __ ] Quezy
Someone's going to end up dead on
Someone's going to end up dead on here.
All right, Gregy. Someone's going to end
up dead on here in it.
Yeah. His name was uh Faith. No.
Yeah. It wasn't over YouTube, was it?
I might go on low J's and wind them up,
but they're just repeaters on there.
They're just repeaters on there.
Should I go on there? It's just full of repeaters.
Yeah, but they're repeaters, man.
They're [ __ ] repeaters.
So, I joined it. Why?
I'm going to join. [ __ ] it.
I'm going to join Lord Asia for two Comes. [gasps]
Oh, I got kicked.
He He kicked me, mate.
Cuz he knows I own him with a curry.
That's why. He knows, isn't it? [laughter] See?
See what I mean? He kicks me cuz he
can't handle me. Yeah. Yep. See? [laughter]
See what I mean? It can't handle me.
It can't handle me, lad.
The repeat is on there. It's the same repeat people. Yeah. [laughter] Is it Yeah, bro.
This is a weird community.
Look at Autumn Rose saying, "All right,
gorgeous to LJ." Wow,
what a [ __ ] [ __ ] You know,
these people are [ __ ] [ __ ] on here, bro.
Yeah, the repeaters.
They're repeaters on here. Is it Steven Howard?
Him and his iced curry. He's [ __ ] skin.
Who the [ __ ] gets an icing curry? He's
[ __ ] skin, is he? Bloody.
Yeah, that's my new little my little my
new little word now. Steven Howard. Bloody.
Do you like that word? Bloody
Iceland curry. Cuz he's [ __ ] skint. [laughter]
Cuz he's [ __ ] skinnier than a [ __ ] skin flint.
That's why. Skinner than a [ __ ] skin flint.
He's [ __ ] skinny. >> [snorts]
>> Timmy keeps doing videos, man.
Autumn Autumn Rose is [ __ ] stinking,
son. Autumn Rose is stinking.
Look at all the little simps. [laughter] >> [laughter]
>> Oh, look at the little simps. Look at
all the little simps on LJ's channel.
Look at the little simps. The simps. >> [laughter]
>> Look at all of these ships.
See, LJ doesn't let me on the hang cuz
he's [ __ ] skinn. He's skint [ __ ]
skin flint. That's what I mean with these people.
Skint than a [ __ ] skin flint.
We got skint [ __ ] skin flint, mate.
You [ __ ] skimp, hunt you.
Yeah, that autumn rose uses filters.
Yeah. See me, I don't use filters.
Nah, mate. Don't use any filters. I
don't need to use filters.
For what reason would I need to use filters?
just naturally pretty, you know.
You can't beat us. [laughter] You know,
Right. Let me get this bed out the
[clears throat] washer. Dryer. Sorry. Wash. >> [laughter]
>> It's [ __ ] done. [laughter]
The bed's [ __ ] done. You heard that?
The bed's dumb. [laughter]
The bed's done, mate. Let's put this one
back here for a little bit. [ __ ]
it's [ __ ] damp, lad.
You know what I mean by that? It's [ __ ] damp.
[ __ ] damp, bro.
Oh, [ __ ] me. The bed's damp. The bedding's damp.
stuck it in the dryer.
You [ __ ] virgin. [laughter]
You virgin, can't you? You [ __ ]
skin. Hi, Steven. Lo,
it's skint [ __ ] skin.
Yeah, he's skintlin.
A [ __ ] skin.
And a [ __ ] skin, man. [laughter] Oh.
Oh, I'm sorry. Oh [ __ ]
You are, Grezy. Sorry, I was just
brushing my lashes. Can you hear me? Oh gosh.
Can you Can you hear me, Grezy? Can you hear me?
Can you Oh,
Can you hear me?
Can you Oh, gosh darn it.
Making my little Betty B.
I'm getting my little Betty Bes in a
bit. Grezy, that curry knocked me for six.
That was delicious. Oh gosh. Yeah.
Oh gosh darn it.
I look better now. Getting it. [laughter]
I had to put the bed back in the dryer
cuz it was damn [laughter]
I had to put the quilt back in the dryer
cuz it was damn
Is that funny? Yeah, the do was damp to
put it back.
It was [ __ ] [laughter] Yeah,
[laughter] you catch a cold.
You'll catch a cold if you [ __ ] put
on you. You'll be like the virgin
getting in the bed in the bedit.
I fancy a bottle of Coke. I got a
bottle, like a little bottle. I got a
small bottle, but I really fancy a uh
you know, I fancy like a smaller bottle, but
I don't know shocks in it.
Yeah, the quilt was damp.
No, I need to stay off the coat to be honest.
I need some. I like Coca-Cola.
I really, really like Coca-Cola.
I'll just get one from McDonald's.
I Kieran, do you like Five Guys? Gosh,
I'm really dry. I think that's that
curry's made me really dry or something. Huh?
You had five guys caring.
Lord, they've run out of Coke in
McDonald's. That's not How is that even possible?
They can't have.
How have they run out of How?
That doesn't make any sense.
I need a Coke, man.
Yeah, it tastes like a proper burger,
doesn't it, Kieran? It's like a proper
It tastes like a proper burger. How a
burger should taste. Yeah.
Oh, gosh darn it. You know all about
these things, don't you?
Who is this? Autumn Rose
really you worked at?
Bless you. Then
you're a cockney, aren't you? Um
Karen, you're you're a cockney.
Yeah, you're a cockley, aren't you, lad?
Hey, you're a cockly lad,
aren't you, mate? Yeah,
you're a cockly [ __ ]
You're a cockney [ __ ]
N you're cockly, mate.
I'm I'm not cocky, am I?
>> Yeah, I'm not cocky, am I?
No, I don't think so.
Well, I was born in East London. I'm
from East London, so maybe you could say
I am, but I don't think I am.
I can't believe the [clears throat]
[ __ ] Orington virgin is trying to say
[ __ ] Romney in Orington's London.
Nothing to do with [ __ ] London.
Well, I was born in Leighton,
which is not far from Stratford.
I moved to Stratford, which is right by
Bow. It's like right next It's like 5
minutes away from Bow.
So, I was born in Leighton Stone Whips Cross Hospital.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] Kent.
I can't get over that. Kira, did you see
when Timmy, Mike, and [ __ ] Monty met?
Michael's like, "Do you want to go
around the court? You can We can go for
a pint or we can do it bad.
Do you want to do it bad or do you want
to go for a drink?
Or do you want to do it bad?" I was
dead, bro. Or do you want to do it dirty?
He's a M. So does that make me a cockney
then? I was born in late I was born in Leighton stone.
People from slow people from slow is not
a cockney are they? They're farmers. Yeah, [laughter]
their father's on
Yeah, people from SL are farmers.
Yeah, they're farmers, aren't they?
They got like a uh it's not as it's not
as much as Bristol, but
it's I don't know. It's hard. You can I
got a friend that lives in he's from Braracknel,
you know, Braracknel, like towards
Reading and they kind of do have an accent.
It's like a country accent, isn't it? Yep.
I'm good with locations.
Of course I'm good with locations, lad.
How do How am I not good with locations?
You silly goose. I've traveled all over
the bloody country. And have you know
sunshine multiple times? Yeah.
Is Watford London?
Yes and no. There's been an argument for
years. Some say yes, some say no.
Of course I know locations. You silly goose.
What? There's been an argument that that
argument's been going for years. Whether
it is, whether it isn't.
Well, obviously Luton's not London, you
[ __ ] [ __ ] It's Bedfordshire here,
bro. I've traveled all over the country.
And you're asking me if Luton's in
London, bro. I've traveled all over the country.
Luton is in the county of Bedfordshire.
Luton is not London. It's got nothing to
do with London. There's no London Luton
airport. Luton is not London. It's Bedford here. Next question.
No, that's one of the only places I've not been.
How can you say I'm not good with
locations, Kieran? I've been everywhere, bro.
I know capitalism.
I have been to great Yeah, I have
actually. I've been to Norwich. I've
been to Great Yarmouth. Yes, I have.
Yep, I have actually.
Northern and great Yarmmouth. Yes, I have Yeah.
Was he mocking me or something, de lad? Mhm.
Sorry. just said this to this guy.
Whatever [ __ ] said that
I need a McDonald's coke, man.
You know, you just need a McDonald's coke.
I said I've been to most cities.
Abedine's not a city. Lancaster's not a
Derby is not a city. They're not cities.
Then places you listed are not cities.
I tried to join. He keeps kicking me.
Okay. There are a few places and most of
them are not cities.
Right. Abedine is not a city. Peter is
not a city. Derby is not a city.
Derby is definitely definitely
definitely not a city. So yeah,
we never said ho. We never said h.
So that's like 5% of places,
right? Don't let me start listing places
I have been to. So
yeah, I mean, I've still traveled all
over the country. So yeah,
I've still traveled all over the country. You know,
we didn't say no. We was Yeah, but bro,
okay, I'm not going to list all the
places I've been to again. I've been to
I've been all over the country, bro. H
Derby is not a city.
Derby is definitely definitely not a city.
They must be new cities like you just
said cuz they weren't cities before, bro.
So, do you want me to name all the
places that happened?
Do you want to do you want to you want
me to name all the places that happen?
Yeah, they say it's in Yorkshire. Yeah,
but they all sound like [ __ ] Jordies.
I know. It's weird. It's Yorkshire, but
they they sound Jordies. They don't
sound like they're from Yorkshire. It's weird.
Derby must be a new city cuz it never
used to be a [ __ ] city.
You know, never used to be, mate. Oh,
and I have been to Derby. What am I
talking about? Happen to Derby when I
went to Nottingham. I have been to Derby.
I've been to more cities than I've not been.
So, that says it all.
Yep. I know. I've been to Middlesbrough.
The last time I went to Newcastle.
Yeah, I went there. It was a [ __ ] bro.
When I went to Newcastle. When I went to
Newcastle, the women approached me.
Would you believe it? E.
Would you? I didn't believe it. No.
Get it. Get the rhyme. Get the rhyme, mate.
Oh, you forgot one as well. I haven't
been to Blackpool,
you know. I haven't been to Blackpool either,
but I've been to most places. So, yeah.
No, it isn't. It's not the fourth
biggest in the UK. No, it isn't, mate.
Yeah, it's not the fourth biggest in the
UK. No, it's not. I can tell you
I can tell you the first three. The
first is London, then Birmingham, then Manchester,
and I think the fourth one is
[ __ ] What is the fourth one? It's like
Edinburgh know or Nottingham.
I can't remember the fourth one, but
it's not Derby. It ain't Derby, mate. What?
Oh, it's Glasgow. Is it Glasgow?
I didn't even know it was Glasgow. I
thought it was Scotland.
Then it's Sheffield. Oh, I didn't even
know that. No, it's not Derby.
Nope. Wrong again.
Manchester, then Glasgow, then Leadeds, then Liverpool, then Sheffield.
I didn't know Glasgow was the
fourth. I didn't know that. That's strange.
>> I didn't know that. I thought it would
have been Edinburgh.
I bet if you went to Glasgow, it' be
easy to pull. Less competition,
less stuck up people cuz they're not rich.
Isn't that right, eh?
Isn't that right? really delayed.
I remember I went out on the pool in Scotland.
I remember when I went out drinking in
Edinburgh. Do you remember that? Uh here.
I got smashed, bro.
But they were kind of snobby. I don't
think any said they had a boyfriend
though. I don't I don't think they did.
I do [clears throat] remember Edinburgh.
I remember banging the escort and then coming back.
Big ass ceilings, bro. Big ass ceilings.
I'll never forget that. And I went on
Fever Street. I went on I went all the
way there, bro. I went on a plane and
then I went on [ __ ] Viva Street and
then [ __ ] Yeah. Good times, bro. Good times.
Oh, on Viva Street. Got the location. I
done Newcastle. I [ __ ] escorts loads
of places. Manchester, Newcastle, Nottingham, Edinburgh.
Sheffield when I met them people.
Yeah, I used to go on the pool
and then [ __ ] use escorts. Yeah. Yep. Might
take this bending out the dryer in a minute.
I wanted you know Riffrat said.
Yeah, I was brickling. Do you know what
Rifraat said? Riffrat said, "Tim, you
need to seek help. Your family should be
stepping in at this point before you
either get arrested or get really hurt."
I'm dead, bro. That is funny.
What over YouTube?
What over YouTube is it? No, All
right, I should be ready now. [ __ ]
Yeah, it's dried out. Gy, I had to put
it back in for half hour is damp.
Yeah, I had to put it back in, lad. Oh,
that's absolutely lush.
Can't wait to get my little body in that. that, lad. Oh gosh.
Oh gosh darn it. Darn it.
You silly little [ __ ]
Where's the virgin? You virgin little
[ __ ] King Bit.
I'll [ __ ] you. I'll [ __ ] you up, you little virgin.
I'll [ __ ] you up, mate. You know what I mean?
[ __ ] you up you little virgin.
You know I [ __ ] you. Oh, [ __ ] you up you little virgin. Little virgin.
There a bongo in it.
He's a snake in it.
When are you going to get a job?
When are you skinned people going to get a job?
a job? Eh,
it was working long days. It was
Oh, because he wouldn't get off of YouTube.
All because money wouldn't get off.
I [ __ ] do you in your little virgins, aren't you? that
you want some you. Oh,
I wanted to get in this little nest. My
little nest. Crazy.
Gosh, I'm so tired. Good night.
It's not funny. Tommy,
>> what are you going to do? me in the oven now. [clears throat]
You don't feel you like
taking the baby away from it. Mama,
that's cool. It Hey,
you want some? You want some virgin?
You want some?
You [ __ ] want some? You
You want some? You want some? Want some?
You want some? You [ __ ] virgin. You Oh
yeah, I had to get into fresh bed.
The only bad thing with a dryer is it
takes the smell up.
That's the only bad thing when you put
it in the dryer.
Oh, when you [ __ ]
I was thirsty.
That curry really dried my mouth out. It
was quite yummy, though.
Oh, I'm in my little nesticles now.
Oh, yeah. It's not as good when you put
it in the dryer.
It takes the smell off. Oh,
you want some?
You want some? You want some? You want
You want some? You want some, you little
virgin? You want some? You want some,
you little virgin? You want some?
You [ __ ] want some, little virgin?
You want some?
I'm going to try and join uh Lord J's again.
I'm going to try and join Lord J again.
Let's have a see.
In before manta.
In before link for manta.
N put a link up.
Nope. Nothing, bro.
Yeah, it's the same repeating.
Well, I want to join you.
Yeah. See, he kicked me.
See, I got kicked. You can't handle me.
Yeah, he kicked me out.
I won't try and joy again then. Whoever money Oh gosh.
Oh gosh. Darn it.
See, I I unblocked him, but he never
comes on my channel cuz he knows he got defeated. Mr. Ly.
Nah, they haven't said anything that bad.
Yeah, I'm reading what they're saying.
No, it's not too bad. That Ricky
Millington's a snake.
PJ needs to show this man how to pull women. >> [snorts]
>> Yeah, they're all [ __ ] idiots, lad.
Yeah, they haven't said anything that bad, bro.
Where's the [ __ ] Orington virgin?
Come on, you [ __ ]
Come on, you virgin [ __ ] You know, let's go.
Did you notice that though? Um, Steven Howard,
when I'd called him a virgin, everyone
would jump to his rescue saying, "Oh,
he's had a girlfriend.
He's had he's got a girlfriend. He's got
a girlfriend. But when he calls me a
virgin, no one says nothing to me.
[ __ ] off you bloody virgin.
Listen, you educated [ __ ] just because
you're in about living in a [ __ ] in a
greater London Bower in your mom's spare
room. Well, actually, where my mom lives
is considered London.
It's actually considered London.
Well, actually where my mom lives is considered London.
It's actually considered London and also
Robford is considered London as well.
You are nothing to do with London. You [ __ ] virgin.
It is East London. Chad Wall Heath is
East London. You your little Virgin
area, right? But it's six minutes away
from Roford. You don't live in London.
You live in Kent. Little Kent Wanka.
Little Kent [ __ ] Little Kent version.
You know what I mean, mate?
It's definitely definitely London. Yep.
Where's Joseph Ferrar?
I kind of miss him when I don't see him
for a little bit.
You're right, miss Mr. Lotty. I'm
feeling a bit sad. I'm feeling a bit down.
Some of the numbers reply back, but then they stopped.
Now I'm feeling quite lonely now, Mr. Lotty.
I'm thinking, would I ever would I ever
meet Mrs. Right?
Would I ever meet Mrs. Right? I don't think so. Nope.
Be nice to meet Mrs. Right.
But I don't think she's out there. Oh gosh. Gosh.
How do you feel about that Steven Howard
about I almost got a treble both score
no draw. I got two out of three.
Ah bet you weren't expecting that was you? Huh?
Yeah, I got I got two out of three, bro.
I'm going to do a double both score no
draw on Saturday.
Okay with you captain?
Is that okay with you captain?
Okay with you, Captain.
Obviously I have to run it by you first.
Is that all right with you, Captain? Captain Clan.
All right, Captain.
That Steven Howard
that Steven Howard, Captain
You all right, Captain?
All right, Captain.
Yeah, I'm going to go out drinking
Friday, Stephen H. Is that all right?
Is that all right, lad? Right
with you, K.
Is that all right with you, K?
Okay with you, Ken.
All right, Captain.
How much do you think you need in your
bank account, Steven Howard, to go out drinking comfortably?
How much would you say you need, boss? 5K.
No, don't be silly. 5K is is too much.
Don't have 5K. It's too much. No, seriously.
No. On a serious note.
That's silly. You silly goose.
I don't have 5k, matey.
Do you have 5k matey?
Yeah. Not me, bro.
I ain't got five grand, matey.
I lost 80 pounds today on the roulette. Yeah, not 5k.
Not 5k, matey.
So what happen if I go out approaching on Friday?
If I go out approaching on Friday, what will happen? Steven Howard,
I might pull in it.
I might pull a woman.
What do you mean it will be the same?
How would it be the same?
I might I might meet a woman for have a
girlfriend and stuff.
People on Reddit tell me that I might meet someone.
People on Reddit say I might meet someone. Huh?
Yeah, but I might meet someone. I might
get laid in it, Steven Howard.
Yeah, it was madness last week, wasn't it?
I bet you found it funny, didn't you?
Yeah. You liked it, didn't you, mate? Yeah,
it was great fun. Great fun.
I'll be out again on Friday.
See what trouble I can get up to.
This is so bloody expensive nowadays
going out. Steven Howard
so bloody expensive. You
It's too bloody dear.
It's too bloody dear, lad.
No. If you go if you get Guinness, you
can do it with like £50.
If you only drink Guinness,
you can do it with like £50.
If you only drink [clears throat]
Guinness, you can do it 5060 pound. But
you have to drink Guinness. You can't
drink rum because they water the [ __ ] down.
I've done it on 30 before. I've pre-
drunk before. I've done it before where I've pre-drunk.
Yeah, I've done it before where I've pre I've pre-drunk
and um spent like 30 pound the whole night. So,
I have to do something like that to be honest
cuz it's too expensive, isn't it?
It's too expensive now, lads. [ __ ] 13.
I have like 1,400 pound for the month.
It's not that bad, is it? Steven Howard,
what do you think? £1,400 for the month.
It's not that bad, is it?
Not that bad, is it, bro?
What do you think? Nah. Yeah.
Virgin boy will ever get a job?
Do you reckon he'll ever get Do you
reckon he'll ever pop it?
You reckon he'll ever lose it?
Ever lose that VC card?
You can go to the off license and get beer.
Yeah, you can go to the off license and
get beer as well
in it. Uh, Steven Howard.
That virgin's mad. I can't keep up with the virgin.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You go to off license to
pre-drink a beer.
I think most people pre-drink, don't
they? Uh Steven Howard,
I'm sure most people pre-drink. No.
Yeah, I'm sure they do.
No, you just go to Tesco, you get drunk
on the beer. Like I said, I've spent £30
before on a night out.
Yeah, about 30
skin virgin skin virgin.
You want semi-kinned virgin? Obviously,
you're going to buy a couple in the bar,
is it? You'll buy like two.
Yeah. Yeah. But you'll buy like two. I'm
sure you'll buy a couple obviously. Is it?
You'll buy a couple.
Not Guinness though. They can't water down Guinness. Yeah, exactly.
[ __ ] Guinness cuz they can't water down Guinness.
Obviously, they can't water down
Guinness, can they? No. Yeah. I'm set.
I'm checking out.
It will never change. Steven Howard Never that.
Uh, you leave the country.
That's all you do, right?
You leave England.
You go to Asia.
You go to South America.
That's the That's it. That's They're your options.
Or you join the porn industry.
You join the porn industry. You use escorts.
Or you go to Asia.
All right. What the [ __ ] bro? What else is you?
You know what I mean? What else do you do then? Nah. Ah,
why did you get robbed? Oh,
what the hell? Yeah. So,
get used to it or leave Steven Howard. >> [snorts]
>> That's jokes, isn't it? Yeah. You know
a [ __ ] skin flint. Steven Howard,
how much money
How much money How much money does
Virgin Boy have? You reckon?
He skated in a [ __ ] skin flow.
You reckon he's skinting skin flint?
So you reckon he's skint [ __ ] skin flint then?
Is that what you're saying, lad?
So you're saying that he's skinting skin flint?
Is that that what you're saying, lad?
Is that what you're saying? He's
skinnier than a [ __ ] skin.
What you [ __ ] saying, mate? What you [ __ ] saying?
He skin a [ __ ] skin flint.
He's skinting in a [ __ ] skin flint.
He got mad because I bought designer
gums, didn't he? Steven Howard.
Then he was going to report me. The
[ __ ] cheeky virgin.
Who is he? >> Yeah.
Said he was going to report me. I didn't
know it was a [ __ ] crime to have more
than you in life.
I didn't know that was a crime. Is
that okay? I'm having more than you.
That bloody crime.
>> Yep. Didn't know it was a [ __ ] mind.
You [ __ ] murder him. your [ __ ]
version. Can you
[ __ ] virgin? Can you know what I mean?
Yeah, nasty bird.
I [ __ ] love that me, you know. It's
[ __ ] ace, bro. You nasty virgin. Bam.
You horrible virgin. Can Steven Howard,
you nasty [ __ ] You nasty virgin.
Well, I'll be back. Yeah, let's go see finger lobsters.