Fire on fire.
I'm having a chill day today, I think.
It's a nice chillax today.
No, I'm not fighting little mongos in
this community. [ __ ] off.
You can [ __ ] off. I'm not fighting any
of you little mongos.
By the way, do is a non-suporter. Yeah.
on you. Joseph supporter.
These leagues are playing today, aren't
they? I might have to put a bet on the league, lad.
Oh, you got pain today.
>> Don't mind if I do, son. Don't mind if I [ __ ] do.
Go on YouTube.
So protect himself projector.
Yeah, I'm I'm going to put 130 on two teams. Yeah. Temp.
I put 150 on two teams, bro.
It's not worth the risk, is it?
Is it matey? Mhm. Mhm.
You need to stop trying to troll me, bro.
Your IQ is too low to try and troll
someone like me, you lad.
Please stop it. Thank you. Stop it.
You're not intelligent enough. Please, lad.
Back it out.
You're really bad at it. Bye-bye. Yeah, man.
Yeah, I'm tempted to put some money on
that uh football
on the football
if it loses it. [ __ ]
That's the problem, is it? If the news Mhm.
No, I won't put a bet on it and then it
will come in.
You know how it is, bro.
I might just do a bow star, no draw.
Yeah, I might just do a bow. I don't know.
Definitely do a bat.
I don't know, bro.
might just do 80. I both got no job.
I don't know.
I don't know what bet to do.
I might just 100 pound on two teams. Both s
I don't know, bro.
Where is she at?
Let me see what the odds are.
How you going to lose it?
So, the odds are
the odds are right to be fair.
Just going to do the football bat.
So we got £100 on it. You get 315 profit.
Yeah. So they get you uh
so they get you 315 back
northern league and South League.
I think that's decent to be honest. Yeah,
I think that's not bad.
It feels about returning.
>> Yeah, I don't think that's a bad return. No.
Nope, you're not knowing the teams.
Nope, I'm not telling anyone the teams
cuz people stalk my bets. No, no, mate.
Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope.
So yeah, I can't tell you that, lad. Sorry.
Yeah, we all need some money, mate.
I do this football bet.
If it's even worth doing that,
I'm thinking of doing a bow score no draw.
Me I'm just thinking of doing a bow
score no draw.
I'm not added one I'm not adding one more team.
I'm not bro. But I'm adding one more
team. It always [ __ ] you up there.
No, I can't be bothered to do it, lad. I
don't want to lose money.
To be fair, I don't want to lose money. So, so yeah.
Don't want to be losing money, matey.
No, it's not 700, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
How's it going to be 700 pound? Probably
like five, maybe 450, 500.
Nah, I'm not going at that.
[ __ ] that, bro.
It's time to run. Mhm. Yeah.
But I put at 150 on two teams would be even more obviously bucket. Pointless.
Absolutely [ __ ] pointless.
Might as well [ __ ] damn roulette if you're [ __ ] Yeah.
How much is a both score no draw? I
might put both score no draw on it.
What is it?
It doesn't even say both score, no draw.
Where's the option?
Both teams to score. No. What?
>> [clears throat]
>> Oh, that virgin boy. Yeah,
we should try and do a correct score
like two. Imagine that predicting it. 21.
[clears throat] [ __ ] me, bro.
That'll be sick, isn't it? Yeah,
it would be.
I don't know what to do, bro.
I'm just going to stick 100 on two
teams, I think. [ __ ] it. Yeah. Should
I not? I don't know, bro.
I was a good idea.
I'm so indecisive.
I'm so [ __ ] indecisive.
I'll probably be off.
No gambling for me.
I know. I'm so bored of it. [ __ ] that. [ __ ] me.
don't want to be like that bloody skin plonker.
That skin [ __ ] up. Oh [ __ ]
Yeah, man. I'm just chilling today, bro.
That's why I'm on YouTube.
That's why I'm on.
Anyways, one, bro.
See you, man.