Yo yo back now [ __ ]
done a lush football bet
on a lovely football bet.
Yeah, that is lush.
That is a lush football bet. That is
So that bloody bet comes in then won't we mate?
Ain't no [ __ ]
I ain't no [ __ ] skin virgin
I'm mad. Me in it. I'm [ __ ] mad. I'm
a [ __ ] lunatic.
Never leave that [ __ ] skint alone, do
you? No, no, no.
Yeah, it said it returned £47
and I realized I clicked the wrong team. Yeah.
Hopefully this bet comes in.
Put 120 on it. Oh, the joys.
Joys of talking about people that you
don't know. Hey, here's L. Coca-Cola.
This bet better [ __ ] come in, lad. Come on. Wait a second.
That one should do the trick.
I just £120 both teams to score.
I lost 80 pound on the roulette
yesterday. So I just put this £120 on
both teams to score. Yeah.
returns 366. So hopefully it wins. Yay. Ferrar.
Yeah, we'll see.
But I I got a good feeling it will, but
it probably won't to be honest.
Kitty Minister Harris Bedford Town and
slow and bath.
Yeah. Whatever. When I put a 120 it said
£47. I said £47. [ __ ]
really [ __ ] £47 and I realized I I
went on the wrong team. But yeah,
[ __ ] better come in, mate.
It [ __ ] better, dude.
It be nice if it doesn't it [ __ ] sake.
Don't know. Don't care. Go and ask him.
So yeah. Have you done any bets today?
Hey, you're a nons lover. Do f, you do
realize you're a nons lover, is it?
That's the level. Yeah, that's what I
forgot to say. You're a uh you're a non
lover, aren't you?
Yeah, you're a nons love you.
You love nons legs.
Kieran knows it as well.
Well, when I was calling him a virgin multiple times,
self projecting. Uh
when uh I was calling him a virgin
multiple times, you always stick up for
him. But when he slabs about me, you
don't say anything. So, you're a you're a non-sl.
Yeah. I don't use the word bacon. That just sounds
stupid calling someone a bacon. So it it
does to be fair.
Hey, I'm getting better though. Is it
Joseph Ferrar? I didn't moan about the
four numbers. Well, four or five
numbers. I didn't go anywhere, did I?
You proud of me?
You proud of me, Joseph? I didn't moan
or wing, did I?
Uh, two replied,
I didn't moan or wing, did I?
Why is that Joseph Ferrar?
Why didn't I moan and winge?
Right. But it's possible that I'm a
virgin even though I put I've proved
I've had sex.
Okay, then. So, what's more likely
somebody to be a virgin? Somebody that's
in a relationship with a disabled girl
that's got disabilities
or somebody that's actually proved
they've had sex. As sick as that is, I
would say it's the person that to prove
they've had sex is more chance of not
being a virgin than somebody that's
dating a disabled girl. I mean, as
ridiculous as it sounds, the person
that's had sex, no, no, no, no, no. It's
not that you said that. It's when he
calls me a virgin, you're not to his
rescue. You're not to my rescue. But
when he calls me a virgin, you're like,
"No, he's got a girlfriend. He's got a
girlfriend." No, no, no, no, no. But
then when he runs his mouth, you never
say about the [ __ ] pool nose I put
up. Or when I've got my dick rammed in a
woman's mouth, you [ __ ] nons lover.
You [ __ ] n loving [ __ ]
You [ __ ] absolute [ __ ] pity fiddling lover.
You know, you [ __ ] get me started,
mate. Don't get me [ __ ] started. I'm
not in [ __ ] need.
But yeah, basically that. Yeah.
No, but seriously, you It's more chance
somebody dating a disabled girl is a
virgin than somebody that that's
actually proved they've had sex.
So that's that.
So yeah, you're all biased on here.
We all know that. You love nons.
And trust me, it's not impossible. He is
a [ __ ] virgin. He's never had it in
his life. And that's coming from
somebody that's proved they've had sex.
So what have you got to say about me?
There you go.
>> Well, like when he he is a virgin. He
proves he's a virgin
every [ __ ] day. Yeah,
Tim's a virgin. Bomb's a virgin. Don
Legs is a virgin. There's a few virgins
on here that we know of.
Did you like my co video, Joe?
Who the [ __ ] gets a vinderoo
from the [ __ ]
from [ __ ] Iceland? Who the [ __ ] gets
a microwave [ __ ] vindaloo if you're
doing a challenge? Oh, that LJ is absolutely skint.
He is absolutely [ __ ] skint mate.
He's skint [ __ ] skint flling.
He's skint [ __ ] skin.
So anyways, um, back to the subject.
Um, why don't you say anything when he
calls me a virgin then? I never see you
say, "Oh, he's put a porno out there.
He's got uh, you know,
he's uh, dick shoved up a woman's mouth."
We never see or hear any of this.
H strange. If I didn't know myself, I'd
say you're [ __ ] biased, lad. To be
honest, you know. So, you're an idiot.
You're a non-slaver. He is absolutely a
virgin. He can have a million disabled
girlfriends and he would still be a
virgin. So, he's a big virgin. All the
signs are there. I swear my life that
he's never had sex ever in his life, lad.
You know, ask yourself that question.
Ask yourself that question, lad. Cuz
when I'm calling him a virgin, you're
straight to his rescue. So ask yourself
that question. Don't ask me that.
>> Yeah. And the way he talks about USA,
Izzy, and Sig, he it's his lack of sex
life cuz he's a virgin. I I've known
this [ __ ] right? I I know him better
than he knows himself.
And he's always been a virgin. And he
will die a virgin, you know. I know this
[ __ ] better than he knows himself.
I know him more than anybody on here,
you know. So what? What the [ __ ]
you know? [ __ ] off. You little nod lover.
I'm not a virgin, but I can't defend
someone who does that and boots because
anyone do that. Oh, really? Okay. H
Manchester one didn't pay 19year-old I
[ __ ] her twice didn't pay New Zealand 19year-old
Manchester one night stand on my
birthday the one in Nottingham
there's been several that never got a
petty from me mate
especially the first time try again I've
just listed you four
is there any missing. I don't think so.
Sig the one on my birthday. 19year-old
Manchester Nottingham USA is he
try again. These were none of these were paid for.
So try again matey. Try again.
you didn't see me in a woman's bed.
Uh, I know I'm not a virgin, but I'm
saying you're straight to his rescue
like Superman the S when I'm calling him
a virgin. Oh, he's got a girlfriend.
He's got a girlfriend. But when he calls
me a virgin, no one says nothing. No,
no, no, no, no, no. The point is you're
defending him because he's a n cuz
you're a nons lover, which is what what
Kieran says. Oh, he's got a girlfriend.
He can't be a virgin. He's got a
girlfriend. No, no. But when he calls me
a virgin, absolutely no problems. It's
cuz you're nonsovers. You like nonsers.
This is exactly what I mean. You love
nonsers. You're a nonslover. That's what
I mean. Yeah. It's the truth. Shouldn't
the question be, "How can someone be a
virgin if they've literally proved
they've had sex, not somebody that's
been with a disabled girl?" They all do
it, bro. They all do it. Every single
time I go at this [ __ ] Yeah. Every
single time. Right.
Um, I don't want a disabled girlfriend.
I've said this multiple times. Having a
disabled girlfriend is not a W. I've
been with normal women that don't have
disabilities. Having a disabled
girlfriend is lower than me. It's the
lowest you can get. It's worse than an
incel. Having to target somebody because
they've got disabilities.
That is lower. That's the lowest of the
low. Right. We've heard her talk what,
once in 3 years, cuz she's got disabilities.
Having a disabled girlfriend is the
lowest of the low. And it's lower than I [ __ ]
And it's not even that she's disabled.
She's not disabled. It It's He's not
even happy with her. Think of how many
times he does videos of me, talks about
me, talks about all of the women I've
been with. He's an insecure virgin with
a fragile ego. I know. Like it's the
same thing as when I talk about LT. I
know all of these things, you know? I I
I'm not stupid. It's like when I talk
about [ __ ] LT and, you know, other
people, you know, I can I can read them
like a [ __ ] book. I know them better
than they know their [ __ ] self, you
know? So, having a disabled girlfriend
is not above me in any kind of universe.
It's definitely definitely not planet
Mars, mate. And he's not even happy with
her either. That's another thing, you
know. He doesn't come get off a YouTube
and live his life. He's an in he's an
insecure little virgin. How many times
does he go on about all of these women
that I've been with that I don't even
give a [ __ ] about? Again, insecure
virgin. Someone in a happy relationship
wouldn't care. They wouldn't even be on
here doing this every single day because
he doesn't get sex in his relationship.
This is where all of this YouTube [ __ ]
comes from. He's an unhappy virgin. And
I don't give a [ __ ] that he's got a
disabled girlfriend. He is absolutely a
virgin and I'd bet my life on it and I'd
bet [ __ ] every every single penny
I've got on it.
And in my opinion, I think he's gonna
[ __ ] die one. And before you say
anything about me, I put the Poor out there, son.
Why would he be with her?
Why? Why would he be with her?
One sec. One second. Someone's messaging
me. Why would he be with her? Um,
why would he be with her? >> Um,
cuz he can't get better.
It's that simple. It's that simple.
Because he can't get anything normal.
Cuz he's an ugly [ __ ] And obviously
because he sees me that I've had better
women than him. It kills him cuz he's a
big virgin with an ugly face and disabilities.
He has to stay with her cuz that ugly
[ __ ] can't get nothing else. [ __ ] hell, mate.
Yeah, my mate. Yeah. Yeah.
Yes, sunshine. That's what it is. That's
what it [ __ ] is, son. That's what it [ __ ] is.
I know it. You know it. Come on, son.
Come on. Come. Who Who else is he gonna
get with? He can't get a USA, is he? He
can't get a [ __ ] that 19 year old.
No. No. He can't even function in normal environments.
Did you see his community post? Did you
see his community post, lad?
Did you see his community post where he
said that he's going to try and get my
money stopped for buying designer
clothes? So what? Because I've got more
money than you and I'm not a skin [ __ ]
in a bedset. You're Is that a crime? Is
that a crime, officer? Cuz I don't have
to shop in a charity shop and shop for
ugly clothes cuz I got no money like
him. That's a crime.
Lock me up officer and [ __ ] throw
away the key, mate. I didn't know it was
a crime of more than an outer London
skinned virgin who made charity shop
clothes. I didn't know that was a crime.
I thought I was entitled to do that.
Saved a bit of money, won a bit of
money. Why am I not allowed to treat
myself to some fancy stuff? You know, I
like nice clothes. I like nice
restaurants. What's the problem? I don't understand.
I know that. I I'm fully aware of that,
mate. I'm fully aware of that. I'm fully
aware of that, matey.
I'm fully aware of that. It's not a
crime being able to afford things
because he can't cuz he's [ __ ] skent
throwing off his daddy's savings. You
know what I mean, son? It isn't. It
[ __ ] isn't. You know that. I know
Now, do you believe me, Joe, that I'm
not scared of anyone? I stuck it on them
four [ __ ] Yeah. Did you see them four
[ __ ] I stuck it on? And they weren't
about nothing. They weren't about
nothing. Did you see the Weather Spoons,
mate? The [ __ ] three white knights. [laughter]
They were debating whether to get
involved or not, weren't they, mate?
They going to get involved. They'd get a
[ __ ] bolican, wouldn't they, mate?
They'd get an absolute [ __ ]
bollockin. You know it. I know it. You
know it. I know it. Isn't that right, Joseph Farerra?
Joseph Farra. Isn't that right?
They already got their I would have
[ __ ] knocked their [ __ ] block off.
Is that right, Joseph Farra?
So many [ __ ] [ __ ] in this country, bro.
So many [ __ ] [ __ ] in it.
So many of them, mate. So many of them, you know.
What do you think, Joseph? There are so
many of them.
Yeah. Yeah. And I was Well, I wasn't
scared of them. Well, true. But I I
think the main thing is I wasn't scared
of any of them. I think that's that's
the main point. I wasn't scared of any
of them. Um but that's just basically like to
show you what happened. I was on that
Tony's uh live stream yesterday,
Greavvesy, and I said, "My mama left me
as well. I miss her breasticles. I'm
trolling someone else for a change." [laughter] Yeah.
It's mad, isn't it? Yeah. But I think
the the thing is, Joe, um, No, I don't
think the bouncer was scared. I don't
think the bouncer was scared. I'm not
saying he was scared, but he wasn't
going to do anything and he would have
never done anything. But I don't think
he was scared. But the point is, I'm not
scared of any of them. That's the point.
You see them four [ __ ] Why can't
people [ __ ] mind their own business?
You get that up north as well, Joseph.
They just they're so entitled, right,
that they [ __ ] that they they think
they can butt in other people's business,
you know? I don't understand it. They're
not on no smoke. They don't want to do
anything. So, why just
everyone's got their own problems and
stuff. They, you know, in life, I don't
know why people don't just mind their own business.
do us all a favor. But
yeah, that that that restaurant was very
nice yesterday. Joseph Ferra. Oh gosh,
that's a bit of ticker.
Nice curry. Oh, mate.
You can't beat it, can you?
I woke up with a bit of a tiny bit of
the shits, but nothing that bad, bro. So
yeah, not nothing that bad.
It was all right to be honest.
Yeah, LJ really can't take spice, can he?
And like I said, Joe, you can't hold it in.
You can't hold it in, mate. You can't
hold it in.
You really, really can't hold it in. You
remember when I done that Caroline Reaper
uh burger challenge Jose Farah?
I was like I I'm I weren't [ __ ] I
couldn't hold it in. Do you remember?
No, mate. No. [laughter]
No. That was lethal.
That's the only place that's able to
defeat Peter Belly. Like I said, I've
been I've been having curry since I come
out my mom's tummy. Rezy since the
umbilical cord got snipped.
Since that little cord got snipped [clears throat]
from separates me and my mama, I've been
I've been I've been eating curry.
No, that Caroline Reaper burger, bro.
Bro, I couldn't finish it.
Every [ __ ] every bite, mate. Every
[ __ ] bite was And even if you get hot
from Dave's chicken, it's too hot, bro.
like hurries and stuff and jalapenos.
They don't they don't do anything to me.
But that I don't know what the [ __ ]
they're putting in that, bro.
I'll try it again someday. I think I
finished quarter of it. Gravesy,
did I finish quarter of it?
I didn't get the shits the next day cuz
I sked it all up.
No, Dave's chicken is nice.
They don't have a Davis chicken by you,
do they? Joseph for? Nah.
No, they don't, do they?
I like the new whip, by the way. I saw
your video, Joseph, for all. I'm loving
the new whip. Do you know what that means, Grezy?
Yeah. I used to have coffee when I was a baby.
Yep. with my little milk bottle. I'm a curry muncher.
[ __ ] curry muncher, lad.
Don't know why I deleted all my video. I did. Joseph Farah,
if this bet don't come in, I'm killing myself,
Joseph. And you'll never see me ever
again. How's that make you feel?
Uh, how does that make you feel?
You don't have a Dave's chicken where
you live, do you?
So, yeah. What you saw the other day is
one of the reasons why I don't go out much, Joseph.
It's too negative, too. I like peace and quiet, bro.
As you get older, you do uh prefer peace
and quiet, you know?
You know that, right?
I could go out and approach every day if
I wanted to. I just don't have the
energy for it.
I just don't have the energy for it.
It's not worth it, Joseph. It's like
what I said to uh Bob. Yeah. Okay. It'd
be nice to It'd be nice to find someone
and stuff, but it's not worth
basically the energy every day and the
gains and the toxicity that comes with
it. It's just not worth it. It's just
As simple as that. Like generally to
find someone, it's not worth it.
Obviously, we go out, when we go out,
that's just like a one-off thing in it.
And we go out anyways, but I mean to
actively try to find someone, it's not
worth it. Nah,
not worth it at all.
The games, the [ __ ] I can't be
bothered with it, bro.
Yeah, rather not.
I approach him every day. Like I said,
if I was a virgin, like nons, I would
then it would be a different story. But nah,
it's fine, bro. Look,
I'm not on the SP. What? You think I've
got anxiety, Greavves? I don't have anxiety.
Oh, Greavves, you get Techly. Get Techly
tea bags. They're the best ones.
Yeah, you need to get Techn tea bags.
I'm hoping this bloody bet comes in today.
be a lovely little win. 366 great
British Sterling pounds.
Those it for sake.
Yeah, I done one bet like this before
and it come. I would have put more on
it, but I was like I don't know about
that. I think 120 is the limit.
What's the most I put on it? I think
I've put one.
Yeah, I think it was 120 130.
I was going to do a both scar no draw as
well. Joseph Ferrar.
One one of these days I'm going to get
the free. Don't you worry about that. I
bet if this wins today it's going to be
a both score no draw just to rub it in.
Isn't that right, Joseph Farah?
Just to rub it in, Joseph.
It happened before when I've done the
120. I on a double both score uh double
both teams to score and it was a both
score no draw. [ __ ] [ __ ]
That would have been lovely. I think
that would have been like over a thousand.
But I was just happy with the couple
hundred. Bob, you know me. I'm easy.
I'm easy. Joseph, you know me.
Yeah. Did you see my comment, Joseph Ro?
Because I don't have USA anymore. I need
to have these curries to give me
nutrients and warm me up cuz obviously I
don't have the milk anymore.
I don't have a milk anymore. So, in the
winter, I need to find like a substitute and stuff.
Quart 8 it starts. No, quart 28. Sorry.
Quart 8.4 Quarter 28,
but it flies by. I'm kind of scared. I'm
not going to lie.
I'm a bit nervous, bro.
But I think it will win. I'm hoping it [ __ ] wins.
I'm really hoping this bet wins, bro. Like serious,
it's not funny if it loses, matey.
And I'm going to do another one next
week if it wins and keep trying to win
every week. You should do a football
bet. Joseph Ferrar,
do you think it's going to win? Joseph,
do you think he's got a good chance?
You think it's got a good chance, Joseph? Fra,
you think? Do you think it's got a good chance that? Whoa.
If I was you, I'd pick the same one I
done, but they were both score no draw.
Thank me later.
You think it's going to window this bet?
All I know is there's loads of [ __ ]
goals in this league.
I can't believe I done a treble. Both
score no draw, man. And two of the games
was 2-1 and the other one was 2-0.
[ __ ] hell, man. I was so close.
It's a bloody mug's game. Joseph
and reply back.
She says, "Hi, Peter. It was really nice
to meet you as well." Haha. I said, "Oh,
but did you get back to France?" Okay.
Never heard from them again. Oh, gosh darn it.
Gosh darn it, Joseph.
I'm so surprised that woman in
Manchester didn't reply back. She
actually seemed all right to be honest.
Like I was saying, you can normally tell
who's going to reply back, who's not
going to reply back.
It's mad that I actually didn't think
they were going to reply back at least.
That's weird, bro.
They can never complain. They can't find
men. They can never ever complain, delayed.
No, they they can't complain.
Yeah, slow. There's always both gone.
There's always both teams that's gone.
The slow game and the Kitty Minister game.
So that's why I picked them to be fair.
I got some donuts as well, by the way. Joseph Fra. >> [sighs]
>> You know who's starting to get on my tits? Jo,
you know who's starting to get on my
tits? That [ __ ] fantasy stories.
He's starting to get on my tits. You
know, more than anyone. More than any
[ __ ] going, bro.
I was getting these thoughts just to go
to Ireland and slap him up, but we all
know the cunt's never going to meet
anyone. Yeah, bro. He was He was pissing
me off yesterday.
You know that fantasy stories.
He's a little nick. That's what he is.
Little [ __ ] He is. That's what he is.
Yeah, he's a [ __ ]
Yeah, he's a [ __ ] Joseph for
how can he run away from Pat Master to
get run off of YouTube for a year and
then come back and giving it the big end.
How does that even make sense?
Do you understand Joseph Ferrar?
Joseph Ferrano. It doesn't make any sense.
There's a Ferrari.
Let me show this. Murder
my little nestles now. Oh gosh.
Is that cute? Joseph. Oh gosh darn it.
It's absolutely okay to not be able to take spice.
There's nothing wrong with that. It's
all right. You know,
it's absolutely fine. It's absolutely okay.
[snorts] You know, not being able to take spice.
I need to change my picture, Franklin,
but I need to change it.
So I just rang for I want a cup of tea, He's mama.
Is that cute? Joseph,
soon as I come out the tummy. Well, bless.
Oh, we need these [ __ ] [ __ ] don't we, mate?
We need these [ __ ] to [ __ ] Don't we'll be [ __ ]
won't we, Joseph? We will be [ __ ]
No, we won't be [ __ ] bro. We'll be
Not like that bloody skin virgin. Anyways,
not like that skin wanker in the bed
[ __ ] Joseph Fra can't be mate. [ __ ]
can't be skin like him, mate. He's a
[ __ ] skin [ __ ]
A [ __ ] skin bastard.
Bring more money than you is not a crime lad.
You [ __ ] nasty little virgin.
Virgin boy is jealous because he can't
afford designer clothes.
He is a proper insecure virgin.
Someone in a happy relationship doesn't
do this every day, matey.
They don't. Happy people don't do this.
Ask any happy couple that you know.
They tell you tell you the [ __ ] same thing, mate.
There's this little Oh, yeah. Yeah.
I'm not a bully.
Okay, I'll fight you. Come to London.
I'll beat you up.
All right, then. I'll give you I'll have
a fight with you. All right, then. Come
to London. I'll beat you. I'll beat you up. Come.
How many sugars did you put in? Ma,
three. Oh my god. Are you trying to get
me to have diabetes or something? Ma,
you are, aren't you?
Scooby-Doo wants a word. Scooby-Doo want
Scooby-Doo wants a word with you.
He says that if you if you carry on
smoking, he's going to cut your tongue
off. That's what Scooby-Doo said. It's not me.
>> Yeah. He had a baby.
So, how long have I been eating curry?
Since the biblical call got snipped.
Am I a curry muncher?
We'll go. We'll do that tie thing
next Tuesday. You said it.
>> Oh, that ticker, man. I love it. You
know when it comes out. Yeah. You know
>> You know Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> You know when the curry comes. Do you
know when the ticker comes out? So, I
love when it gets it gets a little bit
stuck where it's so fresh. You don't go
on, do you? And you try to and it gets a
tiny bit. It's a bit sticky. Yeah.
>> We'll have to go to another restaurant
at some um Yeah, we will go.
So, what do you prefer? The Indian or
steakhouse? It's hard, isn't it? That's
You can always
>> Yeah, that is true. 100%. 100%.
>> Yeah, 100%. Yeah.
Or or Thai food, you can't do no
or Thai food.
But if you if you have somebody from
that region cooks for you like I had
with the tenants, you would never want
to eat out again. It's so good. You want
you wouldn't even want to eat out again
cuz it Yeah. But um Yeah, I get what you
mean. Like if you get a t-bone, you just
cook it in a pan, then you just grill
it. Good grill it. Perfect.
Yeah. Yeah. With the Indian, it's Yeah.
roast dinner. Same is it. You can buy a
nice leg of lamb. Yeah.
The Hawksmore one's nice.
Chinese is that's the one of the hardest
to um Have you been to a Chinese
restaurant? I think I've been once.
Yeah, I think I've been once.
We'll go with a KFC bucket.
What do you mean, mama? You don't like KFC? Yeah.
Okay. Then what other western do you
like then? Okay. So the state one. No,
because so the Indians your first then >> Yeah.
>> And then you
>> Yeah, but the burgers you can't No.
Well, you can actually. I was going to
say GBK you can if you if you get them
right mint. I don't do them good, do I?
>> But do I do it good? >> Yeah.
>> But do I cook it? Fine.
>> It's like Five Guys. Every time you eat
Five Guys, it just tastes so homemade,
fresh. Everything about that, it's just
overrated. If it was cheaper, but it
doesn't beat GBK. Gourmet Burger Kitchen
is better. What do you think?
But I like Tai as well.
>> Yeah. I wonder why that place got shut down.
>> We're going to we're going to we're
going to have you try the Carolina
Reaper Burger and we're going to record it. Why?
I tried it. Do you remember?
I'd love to see you try the Reaper Burger M.
Why? Mama, you'll die in it.
Okay. What about the lamb pow then?
>> I don't [laughter] [ __ ]
Oh, a kuma. I know someone that can only
have a coma. There's a few people.
Yeah, but I had the power there.
Do you think I could handle the the power? [laughter]
Do you reckon I could I could handle the pow?
Yeah. But then as I was looking at Bill,
sweat started coming off me. It didn't
affect me, but it makes me sweating
that. That's what I had when I had CO.
The last time I had it was when I had CO.
No, but I was like it was pouring off
me. It was pouring
>> cuz it's funny.
I still prefer I still prefer the lose.
It's good. Maybe like January the power.
I don't I don't know why someone would
have it that hot.
I can handle it, but it's still like I'm
in the middle. But that gap,
but I can't have that [ __ ] Dave
chicken, mate. I don't know what they're
putting in that [ __ ] Mom.
That Carolina Reaper burger. What was in
it? It must just be full of I don't know
what it is. It's got to be a specific
like three bites and that was it. That
it weren't even half. No, I couldn't do
it anymore. It defeated me. I was like,
it was like a tiny bit of it and I was
like trying and every time you take a
bite, it was like someone was getting a
lighter to your mouth. You couldn't do
it. You can't do it. Yeah. [laughter]
Yeah. Well, you're going to try it. [laughter]
All right, mate. Okay, I'm good. Okay, go away.
Sorry, I'm having my cup of tea now with free sugars.
Outside Morrison Sims, isn't it? Outside
Morrison Sims, in it. [laughter]
You horrible cany. [laughter]
Who Who else can only have a a chicken coma? What? [snorts] Who? Who? Me?
I don't know what's going on, Grezy.
I think it's a load of bollocks. What do you think? [sighs] Oh gosh.
You just run you over, Franklin. It's not nice.
It's not nice running people over, is it, Grezy?
Why are you running people over for you silly goose?
What you do, little kiss?
Is that cute? Greasy little kiss.
Maybe if this football bet wins, I'll go
to another restaurant today. Grievy.
Okay with you, boss.
Again, I've got to run it by you first.
Okay with you, boss. >> [gasps]
>> if I want to go to another lost restaurant.
Is that okay with you, boss? [snorts]
You're my financial advisor.
Okay with you, [laughter] boss. >> [laughter]
>> Okay with you, C. [laughter]
Oh, just having a little wee. >> [laughter]
>> a little [ __ ] H Oh gosh.
[ __ ] hell. [laughter]
My little cuppper.
I be my little cuppper. Lobby.