Lovely
lovely bit of popcorn now matey.
I'm [ __ ] I'm a mad cut me
[ __ ] mad bing popcorn now. H
m Hm. M cool.
See Monty and Timmy going around in circles again.
Round and round in circles they go. I can't watch it.
I can't [ __ ] watch it, mate. It's the
same [snorts] argument
every [ __ ] time. It's the same bloody
argument. Bloody hell. Yeah,
it's the same argument.
Every time we go on, right?
And with monology, man. It's the same bloody argument.
It's the same [ __ ] argument every time.
It's weird, isn't it, Bob?
Same bloody argument. What the hell?
It's the same argument.
Oh, see have be out.
Yep. I done a football bet. £120 on two teams.
I mean, I rarely gamble. So,
I don't know why you're asking me this
because I won't be gambling for a month after today.
win or lose. So
that's uh that's a thing. Pays £366.
So it's good enough for me. Yeah. 244 profit.
That's good afternoon. Yeah. Yeah. [snorts]
This need to stop arguing. It's the same
argument, bro. Every time.
Yeah. Same argument. Yeah,
we never got Monties yet. You see the
same people on there every day. Do these
people not have lives or something or bills?
You see the same people?
You see the same [ __ ] people?
Have you noticed that as well, lad?
You see the same [ __ ] people.
They must not have have lives or anything.
Where is it?
Yeah, they must not have lives, lad.
I've done a lot the past couple of days.
I'm just chilling for today. I'm tired, man.
I'm just tired.
I walked to the betting shop, walked all
the way back. Yeah,
it's all right, but it's a bit boring.
It's okay. It's a bit boring though, but
it's the same people every day.
The same [ __ ] people every day, you
know? That's why you don't see me on
here sometimes for a little bit. It's
the same atmosphere.
That's why you need a break sometimes,
you know. Same people, same atmosphere.
Yeah. So, like I said, out of them five
numbers, two replied.
I might go out this week. I might not. Depends.
I like to do [snorts] it every two
weeks. I think it's more funner that
way, but who knows?
[ __ ] knows what I'm doing now.
Fire myself. I'm not frightened.
Huh? I'm not frightened of no one, bro.
I ain't scared of no one. I don't know
why you're on my channel saying
frightening you for nothing, bro. No one
frightens me on here.
No, I'm not putting any more videos on
anymore like stuff like that because of
uh people on here are all biased. You
stand up to a man, they make excuses.
You argue with a woman, they simp. I
can't be bothered with it, bro.
Yeah, they're all biased on it. You know
what they're like, I just won't post
nothing in the future. You know,
you know how these little mongos are, lad.
People are really going
People are really going in on Timmy, aren't they?
Oh, gosh darn it.
Well, I'm not frightened. Why are you
saying I frighten myself for nothing?
Cuz I'm not scared of any of these
people in here.
Are you mad, lad?
I ain't scared of no [ __ ] now.
Never will be.
I advise you to keep it that way
cuz it's just the same argument with these people.
Really? No. No. Nah.
These people are just bullshitters on
here. They're just little low lives.
That's all they are.
I called Joseph a non-slover earlier.
Joseph F. He is a He is a N lover.
He's a proper proper nons lover.
All biased on here.
It's like what K said, you should you
shouldn't trust anyone that's not
blocked by the Virgin.
You know what I mean? Yeah.
It's weird, is it, lad?
That Joseph F is a bit fishy. Is it Bob Bills? Hm.
He doesn't see how it's possible how
somebody with a disabled girlfriend can
be a virgin,
but he sees how it's possible for
somebody that's proved they've had sex
to be a virgin. It doesn't make any
sense, does it?
Somebody that's actually proved that
they've had sex.
I mean, that's more proof than someone
with a girlfriend. Wouldn't you agree?
Would you would would you would you
agree that someone that's had sex
it it's more believable that person's
not a virgin than somebody that's got a
disabled girlfriend girlfriend?
I I'm pretty sure the person that that's
proved they've had sex is
is that's definitely,
you know, that's definitely proof. No,
these people in this community love nonsense.
That's why they like they like nons legs
because he's a nons. They like nonses on
here, bro. They do.
Yeah, man. 100%. Yep.
Do you not understand the point I'm
getting at, Bob Bills?
That's why I come off of YouTube for two weeks.
That's what That's why I come off of
YouTube for two weeks.
Nah, I'm not providing content anymore.
No more videos.
There's no point entertaining a biased
audience. I mean, that's one of the
reasons why I stopped meeting people for fights.
Nope. I'm not doing any videos.
um at all just live streams
cuz you're all biased on here. You're
all biased. You all make excuses. You
stand up to a man, there's excuses. You
tell a woman about herself, [ __ ]
there's a load of excuses.
Virgin boy talk [ __ ] about me. People
like Joe defend him, but then uh when I
talk [ __ ] about Virgin Boy, sorry,
people defend him, but then when people
talk [ __ ] about me, no one defends me.
The [ __ ] with you?
All my live streams now are just to talk
to Greavvesy and Steven Howard.
No more standing up to men. No more
arguing with women. All the madness I do
is not going to be recorded now. You
ruin that for yourself.
So yeah, man. [snorts]
Yeah. And it's not even that. It's not
even the women as well. Uh it's not
about the women. It's not even just
women uh indigo. It's also about men as
well. Like they make excuses. Oh, the
guy can hit you or no, no, no, no, no.
And I blatantly stuck it on a few people
that night. It's not just about women.
And I might ban Joseph F Grezy
cuz like I said, when I speak [ __ ] about
virgin boy, he's like, "Oh, well, how
could you be a virgin if you got a
girlfriend?" Well, how can I be a virgin
when I prove I've had sex? So, it's like
what Kieran says, anyone that's not
blocked by nons is sus.
So, we might have to block him, lad.
He's a nons lover.
Ask him. He'll tell you, mate.
No, no, no, no, no,
when I talk [ __ ] about Virgin Boy,
right, and say, "Oh, he's a virgin. He's
a virgin." Joseph F comes to his rescue
like Superman every time and says, "How
can he be a virgin? How can How can he
be a virgin? How can you be How can he
be a virgin when he's got a girlfriend?
How can he be a virgin when he's got a
girlfriend? And yet when he goes at me,
he's he's nowhere there. He's nowhere to
be seen. How can I be a virgin?
Okay, wouldn't the same logic apply? How
can I be a virgin when I've proved I've
had sex? So, he's a non-slover. We don't
have nonslovers on this channel.
So, no, no, no. It's not okay to
disagree. It's not okay to disagree
because when you talk [ __ ] about me, I
don't see you bringing up the Porno Stig
USA, the one in Manchester. So, yeah,
that's that is it.
I know. It's just a thing that annoys
me, bro. You know, you know, it's just
just one of them things, you know, greasy. So,
yeah. I mean there it's absolutely
possible that he's a virgin cuz he is a
virgin. A skin virgin.
Yes, he is a skin virgin.
I don't see anyone defending me when
he's calling me a virgin.
Right. No, but what I'm saying Indigo
is he's not blocked on Nlegs's channel.
Right. So when Nonss goes at me, why do
I not see Joseph F defend me?
like he does nonslegs.
No, no, but that's what I'm saying to
you. You're saying, right, that oh,
there's no way he can be a virgin
because he's got a girlfriend. But then
when he goes at me, he doesn't bring up
the fact that I've literally put a porno
out there on YouTube and all the women
I've slept with and I've recorded it as well.
So, I don't know, man. He's on his last
legs with me, matey. He's on his last
legs with me. H
nothing, man. Did you see my football
bet, Steven Howard? So, yeah.
So, somebody with a disabled girlfriend
can't be a virgin, but someone that's
proved they've had sex can be a virgin.
How does that make sense? You know
it's on my community post.
Look at Mickey Ricky Mill saying Bath
won't score. Of course B's going to
score. You [ __ ] idiot.
Of course they will.
How do you know, bro? Who's going to
score? Who's not going to score?
How the [ __ ] do you know, bro?
How do you know who's going to score and
who's not going to score?
>> What a [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
How would you know who's going to score
and who's not going to score?
It's [ __ ] football, mate. It's
[ __ ] football. What the [ __ ] would
you know, bro? You know everything or something, man.
ball for SC. We'll see about we
The bet's [clears throat] coming in
though, isn't it? Uh Steven Howard, the
bet's coming in.
The bet is coming in though, ain't it?
I think it's coming in though that bit, mate. [snorts]
What do you think, Steven Howard?
It's not about Yeah, the odds. It was
the same odds as well, it was the same
odds as last time on a football bet.
Why wouldn't B score go against SL, bro? SL [ __ ]
It's probably cuz it's more likely. That's why.
So, there was one that paid 47.
Yeah, there was a bet that paid 407, but
I wanted to pick slow. So, Come
on. Let's hope we can't win it. Hopefully.
How does Ricky know if Bath's going to
score or not going to score?
They're literally lower leagues, mate.
They're probably going to both score no draw, probably.
Yeah, it'll probably both score no draw
to be fair.
It's coming, bro.
Last time I done 120 on it, it returned
380 and it won.
I could do winning some money, bro. [snorts]
It loses, it loses.
I'm not doing no more content. No more
No more content.
Last time I put up content, I got a load
of white knights, a load of excuses,
and some random black man stalking me.
So, get [ __ ] No more content.
And I kicked Timmy off again. So, no more content.
content is banned on this channel now.
Sorry. Banned on this channel.
Yeah, content is banned on this channel now, lads.
It's simply excuses.
Sorry. It's banned.
Banned. Bam. Bam. Bam. Yeah.
Yeah, man. Bad, lad.
No more content, dude. Dad,
just right in the stream now with no more content.
This is the excuses and [ __ ] and the white lighting. No, [snorts] no, no.
Look at all that [ __ ] that caused Greg.
I had Timmy starting on LT.
I had these load of these white knights.
I had a load of excuses. I had LT going
at me. [ __ ] that.
I was like, "Oh, you people are full of
excuses. Even when it's not women, yeah,
you can get you can get [ __ ]
You can all get [ __ ]
You can all get completely [ __ ]
Here's a fun fact as well. Even when you
prove you've had sex, people still call you virgins. Simpletons.
That's the definition of simple.
Yeah, you get [ __ ] bro.
Show me white lights.
A wild simple bears.
What is he?
A wild simp.
Oh yeah, Timmy was calling me a virgin
earlier as well, man.
So even when you prove you've had sex,
they still call you a virgin.
Even when you prove you've had sex. [ __ ] madness.
Ain't it a crazy? Even when you prove
you've had sex, they still call you a virgin. Mad.
These people are mongos.
I can't stand watching Monty and Timmy
because they just keep going around in circles.
Have you noticed that, Greg? They're
having the same argument and no one's
meeting and it's [ __ ] annoying watching it.
Excuse after excuse after excuse, same
argument over and over and over and over again.
And I wouldn't mind Greasy. They met as
well. The thing is they met. The thing
is it's not like they didn't meet again.
Six years later they met. So they've met
but now they're still having the same argument.
How does that make sense? Roy
did you meet? Right. You planned to meet for ages.
Yeah. I hope it's coming, bro. Fingers crossed.
I could do with the money to be honest.
It doesn't win, it's fine. But be nice
if it does.
It would be nice if it does.
I think it will.
So, yeah. They're just full of [ __ ]
They just have the same argument over
and over again. I can't be [ __ ]
They have the same argument group. None
of them is going to meet.
And they make it impossible to meet each
other as well. They make it impossible
to meet each other as well cuz they're
two spastics. Do you understand?
Cuz they're too [ __ ] That's why.
Is that right, Gia?
Hope that bet wins, mate.
What do you think, Lucy? You hope it wins?
I hope it wins, matey. Oh, damn.
I done 120 before and it won.
Let's hope this guy will win as well.
I'll be kicking myself if it's a both draw.
It won't. Bath or Bedford won't score.
Well, we'll see about that, won't they?
Both or Bed Bath or Bedford won't score?
I think they will.
What do you think about this bet,
Stephen? Now, do you think it's coming in?
I think it's definitely coming in, mate.
That bet's definitely coming in, mate.
What do you think? 70% chance. Yeah.
What makes you say 70%?
about watch this bro. Same [ __ ] argument
over the [ __ ] game, you know. [snorts] Yeah.
So anyways, so why um
um so why is it when I go at non legs
Steven Joe comes to his rescue like
Superman saying, "Oh, how could he be a
virgin? He's got if he's got a girlfriend."
Um but yet
when he calls me a virgin, no one says anything.
That's why we need to get rid of this Joseph F
Steven. That's why we need to get rid of him, lad.
We can't have biased people in our chat, you know?
So, how can he be a virgin if he's got a girlfriend, but
somebody that's proved they've had sex
can be a virgin?
H strange. How's that? How does that one
work then? Just just out of curiosity,
how does that one work? So someone
that's has a disabled girlfriend can
definitely definitely not be a virgin,
but someone that's proved they've had
sex can be a virgin.
>> Yeah, but why does he not bring up the
one night stands that I've had?
I know that's what I'm saying, but I've
proved I've had sex. That's what I'm
trying to say to you. But he doesn't
bring that up ever. Weird.
Why did Why did Reddit make you mad?
I don't go on it anymore cuz the the
Reds the mods just ban you in it. They
fear different opinions.
The moderators um they fear different
opinions, lad. So
yeah, they fear different opinions. So
well, why are you not bringing it up then?
Yeah. Yeah. It doesn't matter what he
thinks. He doesn't bring it up. No, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Hold
on, hold on, hold on. It doesn't matter
because he didn't bring it up.
And then he and then he asked me, "Oh,
uh, what women have you been with that
you haven't paid?"
What women have I been with that I
haven't paid? Is this guy for real?
19year-old Sig USA. Is he
[clears throat] Manchester Nottingham?
The one that I had a one night stand
with on my birthday.
Four or five different women that I
picked. I didn't pay a penny. Your point
is what? What's your [ __ ] point?
I got a [ __ ] in the alleyway. I
didn't pay them nothing. I don't even
think I bought them a drink. That's what
I'm saying on here. They're biased, lad.
That's why there's no more content going
on this channel.
No more content.
That's what I mean, bro. So, I'm going
to put no more content on this channel.
And it doesn't matter whether he thinks
I'm a virgin or not. He doesn't bring it up.
Why does he not bring it up? But he
brings up his disabled girlfriend. [snorts]
A lot of people on here really are simpletons.
Really, really, really, really are simpletons.
I don't know why they love him. He's a
nons. And the thing is Monty says that
it's because he goes for you and if if
he stops going for you, people will go
for him. But no, they don't. The only
people that go for him is Harry Fraud and Shagger.
Harry Fraud and Shagger are the only
people that um go for him if you're not on YouTube. Yeah,
people don't go for that virgin
except for like I said Harry Ford and
Shagger is the only one.
No one else does. They like nons on
here. That's what I mean. They're nons lovers.
It's not because people are going for
me. You [ __ ] idiot.
Yeah. He's never going to pop it. He's
never going to lose that V card.
Yeah. Ricky Millington's a non-sleg
supporter. [snorts] Yeah, he's a Yeah,
he's he's a non-sl. Yeah.
Yeah. Did you see my football bet?
[ __ ] hopefully it wins, bro.
I'm [ __ ] hoping it wins.
I don't know. I don't care about it,
bro. It's boring. They're just going
round and round in circles. I can't
listen to it. It's the same argument every day.
I put it on my community post.
I put my bet on my community post.
This is the same old [ __ ] They just go
back and forth and back and forth and
back and forth,
back and forth, bro. I can't I can't
bear listening to it. >> [snorts]
>> It's just the same argument. And even
when they do meet, they just end up
having the same argument after anyway.
So, it's just the same old [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. I put my football bet on my uh community post. hopefully. Yeah.
Yeah. First time football's been on on a
Tuesday for a while. Eck [sighs]
that's a good bet.
You reckon it's going to come in? Yep.
I might go out Friday. I might not.
Might wait till the week after. I don't
know. I don't know what I'm doing yet.
Do you think that bet's going to win, doggy? Doggy,
it's less than last time. Last time it
was 380 I won. This time it's 366. So
H. Could you imagine
them [ __ ] Australian [ __ ] [ __ ] off.
Yeah. Hopefully it [ __ ] wins, mate. I
could do with the money, mate. You know
what I'm mean? I could have done with
it, mate. You know what I mean? Could
have [ __ ] done with it.
These little meals and [ __ ] going out
doesn't pay for itself, does it? We
sure doesn't pay for its [ __ ] self. Oh, [ __ ]
Nah. Nah, bro. I just could do with the
money in it. Not low. No,
but I could do with winning extra money
in it. That's all, bro.
How much do you uh how much do you think
is low on funds?
No, I still got some money, bro.
How much is low on funds to you, Grezy? >> [sighs]
>> No, it was a setup.
Yeah, he should have [ __ ] He should have
minded his own [ __ ] business.
No, I've got over a thousand, bro. I've
got over a thousand.
I've got over a grand still. Not bad, bro. Yeah.
I'm not low on funds.
Yeah, he should have [ __ ] minded his
own [ __ ] business then, shouldn't he?
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] Okay.
What about What about 600? What about
600 to your name, Grezy?
I don't know, bro. Maybe she wanted my
dick in it, but her friend didn't let
me. Her friend didn't let her.
Isn't that right, Grezy? H,
what about having 600 to your name,
Grezy? Would you say that's short? Nah,
of course I love a curry, mate.
I only have two bills.
I [snorts] need to pay this £33 bill.
Then I'm done until the 27th and then
Frank Franklin comes out. Yeah, I've
only got two bills. Nah,
he didn't want it, bro.
And [ __ ] him anyways. What about them
other little [ __ ] [ __ ] that were
running up their mouth?
them other little [ __ ] that were
running up their mouth. They didn't want
none of it, bro. Them four little posh [ __ ]
with the shitty little trainers. Yeah.
Yeah. They're both skin.
Yeah. I got five numbers. Two replied
and stopped. Same old same old England.
What more can you say? It's just the
same old England
in it, Mike.
England will always be the same old England.
Yep. I don't know. I done a treble both
score no draw on Saturday and I got two
out of three. Two of the games was 2-1
and the last one was 2-0. Bastard. All I
needed was Spennymore to [ __ ] score.
I'm going to get one one day. You watch.
You [ __ ] watch, bro.
It's cuz they love him. Because they're
nons lovers on here. Do you not
understand? They love nonsers. We was
just talking about this, bro. They're
biased as well on here.
So, I got £33 bill
and then I've got Yeah. 33 pound bill
Franklin, which is 15. That's like at
the end of the month.
Uh, [ __ ] sake, bro. Yeah, Mom. [ __ ] madness.
But yeah, they all based on it anyways.
That's the point we were making.
I'm getting addicted to these
restaurants, you know, bro.
I'm getting very very addicted to these restaurants.
So, I spent £600 over this weekend along
with my garments.
Oh, dear me.
Madness, isn't it?
120 on this bet restaurant. I still got some donuts.
[ __ ] me, bro. £45. Yeah.
donuts for 20 with a drink. Gums were
over 400, then 600 over the weekend.
Madness, isn't it? Yeah.
Nah, of course not, bro. [ __ ] sake.
They're not tight. They're completely fine.
They fit completely fine.
They're slim jeans. They're supposed to
look like that.
I got the same old trainers yet because
they're my favorite trainers. I don't
like any other trainers, but then
they're classics. Classics never get old. fun.
Yeah, classics never get old. So, yeah,
I got two good trainers, by the way. I
got them ones and I got the Nike ones
that I bought in the summer. Yeah,
you would be happy with 600 pound to his
name. I [ __ ] wouldn't.
600 to your name? Nah.
Well, obviously Curry because I'm a curry muncher.
Greavvesy would be happy with 600 pound
to his name. Bless him.
See me I I I like to have like over a
thousand in my account.
Even though some people are like [ __ ]
they were saying you got trainers from me's catalog.
Yeah. Stop making up stupid rumors on my
channel, bro. We're not all like you.
Stop talking [ __ ]
Yeah, stop talking [ __ ] I've been
on everyone's channel today. No one said
that. Stop talking [ __ ]
Never ever got anything from a catalog
in my life.
Stop talking [ __ ] on my channel, bro.
Joe's already on his last legs.
So, yeah. Greasy, you're happy with 600
pound in your account? Yeah,
you're mad, bro. [ __ ] mad.
Ela's catalog. Stop talking [ __ ] mate.
Yeah. Did he say that, bro? He would say
that cuz he's a jealous little fat hater.
Oh, well maybe he did say cuz I don't go
on his channel.
Yeah, he's a fat little disabled hater,
bro. Of course he would say that cuz the
guy's skint and he's got no life and
he's got nothing but YouTube and
stalking. So of course he would say
that. I've been on everyone's channel
but that one.
Yeah, catalog. Nah, that's the joys of
talking about people that you don't know.
you. He seems to think everyone is skint like him.
This is people's problem on this
community. They think everyone's got the
same life as them
and they get proven wrong time and time
and time and time and time and time and
time and time and time and time again,
but they still don't know. So, you know,
Baredford won't score.
You [ __ ] better do, mate.
Nope. I don't go on that channel, lad.
Yeah, that red star is just a fat, ugly
stalker that ain't got a life.
Yeah, he's been doing it for years, bro.
No one cares. Yeah, man.
I don't got any channels. See, I didn't
even know cuz he's just a low life. Just
like his boyfriend.
Isn't that right, Steven Howard?
You actually think that [ __ ] You
actually think that football bet's going
to um come in?
You actually think that's coming in? Actually, bro,
it's all right if it doesn't, but it
would be nice if it does. I'm not going
to sit here and deny that, bro.
You know, I'm not going to sit here and
act rich like these people, bro. I'll
still be going out on Friday. [snorts]
Is that what he said? Let me have a look.
Let me see
the lane's catalog.
Oh, cool. Why do you say that?
I can't see it.
I didn't see that bit, bro.
Yeah, I got it from Elaine's.
Elaine's catalog. [clears throat]
How could have I got it from Ela's catalog?
Elaine's catalog. Really, bro? I wish.
He's a [ __ ] loser, is he, bro?
Yeah. Really? So, what about when I went
out spending 600 pound over the weekend?
Was that a catalog?
So many jealous people in this community, man.
I swear to God.
Yeah. So many jealous people on here.
It's still nothing to me now. I've
already spent over £1,000
the past week.
I can still stay in hill to no tails
right now if I wanted to.
Again, you're not my financial advisor.
You don't know how much I have. You
don't know how much I don't have.
You know, that was the whole point of
ordering the trainers. Well, well, I was
killing two birds with one stone as
well. It's still nothing to me.
But what, bro?
Nothing on, bro. Nothing. Nothing's
going on. We're just chilling, man.
Do you see my football bet? Yeah.
Yep. Just chilling.
done a football bet for quarter to 8. So
we'll see what happens there.
Have you seen my bet? Do you think it looks good? [sighs]
Why would I get trainers and jeans from
catalog, bro? I've got my own money.
Bit noisy in it. Bit [ __ ] noisy, bro. Yeah,
we might get the first half if we're lucky.
Uh, Izzy, good for him.
No [snorts] one cares.
Yeah, good for him. No one cares. Stop
making [ __ ] up.
I'm the wrong person to try and scare.
It's not going to work, bro. You can't
scare a You can't You can't scare a guy
like me. Yeah.
Yep. Weirdo. Bye-bye now. Yeah. What do
you think the chances it's going to kind of man?
H you think he's got a good chance?
Oh [ __ ] bro.
No, no, no, no.
Just have to wait and see it. No. Nope.
Yeah, I did. Yesterday
I lost 80 pound.
If I can win this football bet, bro,
I'll be happy, man.
I could do with a win on this football bet, bro.
[ __ ] hell, man.
Yeah, I could do that. Coming in, lad.
Greavves says if you got 600 pound to
your name, you're not sure.
No, I like to have over a thousand, bro.
I [snorts] like to have over a thousand.
Like 1.3, 1.5.
I done pretty good though. Trainers,
jeans, going out, haircuts, and [ __ ]
I've done pretty good to be fair.
This football bet will be lovely, mate,
if it comes [clears throat] in.
But even if it comes in, I don't think I
I don't know if I will go out this week.
I don't know. It depends how I feel.
No, we'll be we're going out regardless
if it wins or it doesn't win.
There is no point to be fair. It's
always the same old it.
That's why I used to go out every two
weeks. It's not cuz of money. Even when
I would win football bets, I'd still [ __ ]
Why? Why bother? Yeah, why bother? It's
always the same odd. [snorts] Nah.
Why did you say why bother?
Cuz it's always the same old, isn't it?
I think cuz there's nothing else to do in it.
At least I didn't get pissed off about
the women's situation uh this week.
Nah, after the last time I went out,
nothing is going to like surprise me
now. You can get 10 numbers and not get
a date. I don't think there's much
that's going to surprise me. You know
what I mean?
Right, I'm going to go anyways cuz I
need to speak to some people on Instagram.
Um, and I'll be back
with hopefully some good news that I won
the football bet. But yeah, I'll be
back. I think be back in a couple of
hours. I need to catch up with some
people. So yeah, man. In a bit.