All right, we got it in the first half,
lads. That is a banger.
That is a banger, bro. Sick.
In the first half as well. [laughter]
That is a banger.
I don't think I don't think I've had
like one of them before since the [ __ ] Yeah.
Traveling days, bro.
Yeah, that's a banger.
That is a banger
in the first half as well.
Yeah. Nice. Nice pinch pinch.
Should have put 500 [ __ ] good on the
but I never
Yeah, that's a banger, bro. In the first
half as well. [ __ ]
I hope it don't end up being a [ __ ]
boat score. No [ __ ] draw.
That is [ __ ]
Hopefully not, bro.
That'll be [ __ ] sh [ __ ] [ __ ]
Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro.
People should have got in on that
[ __ ] But I should have put more on it, bro.
I didn't think it was going to come in, man. [ __ ] did.
I got it, bro. In the first half.
I call it early. I call it early, bro.
There was some early [ __ ] goals.
Yeah, man. I got it early. I got it
I got it early, bro.
I knew it. I [ __ ] knew it, bro. Bro,
I [ __ ] I should have put more on the
[ __ ] but I couldn't, bro. You know, I
couldn't like risk that. I hope this
ain't a both score, no draw.
Darlington was scoring and all of that
as well. And I said, "They better not
[ __ ] score, bro. These other ones
better not [ __ ] score, and then this
one doesn't." See, Ricky Millington
doesn't know what he's talking about
about Bath weren't going to [ __ ]
score. The guy doesn't know nothing,
bro. The guy's an absolute fanny.
Uh, he's a fanny, bro. He doesn't know anything.
Yeah. The guy's a [ __ ] Class A
[ __ ] bro. Class A funny. He doesn't
know nothing. Yeah. Yep.
I get money in a couple of days as well. So,
that Ricky is a [ __ ] idiot. He
doesn't know anything, bro.
He's a fanny, bro. He's an absolute fanny.
He's a funny, bro. He doesn't know [ __ ] all
Yeah, it's lush, isn't it, bro? Lush.
It is [ __ ] lush, mate. And we got the
trainers and the jeans as well.
So, I would have never put £500 on it, bro.
I wouldn't have ever put that amount on it.
I just wouldn't have. Nah.
So, I got all that money back from the
weekend. Basically, I spent a lot, bro.
Go out this week.
I don't know, bro.
I think I might do.
It's not money or anything. Obviously, I
got money, but
first half as well, lads. First half as well.
It's probably going to be I hope this
ain't a both score no draw.
Better not be a both score no draw, bro.
No, I've got it right here. I'm not
going now, bro. Closing at 10. I'm
nowhere near bookies either.
Yeah, I'm nowhere near bookies either.
Yeah, I'm nowhere near. But uh we c we
caught that early. All that other one
saying cuz that one pays more. Hold on.
I hope they never scored.
Yeah, I knew it. But I caught it early.
I caught it early, bro. I caught it
early. As soon as [ __ ] Kitty Minister
Yeah. and M2 scored and one was one. I I
caught it early, bro. I caught it early, man.
Yeah, I caught it early, bro. I've been
analyzing this [ __ ] for weeks. Yeah,
I should have put more on it, but I'm
not greedy, bro. To be honest, I'm happy
with a 366.
I'm happy with it, bro. Whatever.
Yeah, I'm happy with that, bro. Yeah, man.
Yeah, that was sick, man. It paid 20
less than the last one. So, yeah. Yeah.
No, I am I am happy with it.
Uh £366, bro. 300 It's £366, bro.
It's fine, bro. No, I am happy with it.
I got all the clothes money back and
some of the thingy. Well, I got some of
that money I spent over the weekend
back. So, well,
all of it back.
I got all Well, most of it back. So, I'm
not greedy, bro. I'm happy with that. Yeah. 366 pound.
[clears throat] Oh, [ __ ]
I don't I just had a Chinese, by the way.
Yeah, I had a Chinese lad.
Still a good return, is it? 366. I think
it is now.
Yeah, I think it's all right, bro.
How about doing a bit tomorrow? Do
another one Saturday. Yep.
Virgin boy stand in his little bed [ __ ]
with no bad no money in it.
>> What do you think of that?
In his little bed sit with no bad no
money in it.
Nah, it's funny as [ __ ]
Yeah, virgin boy will always be skin.
It'll always be a fing skin flint.
Skin a fing skin flint.
Oh yeah, my mom actually did tell me
about that comment. Clothes from the
from the charity shop. Why would I get
closed from the charity shop? We're not
all skint, red star. We don't need to
get clothes from the charity shop.
[ __ ] idiot. The guy is such a [ __ ]
[ __ ] in it, bro.
Yeah, he's a [ __ ] man.
He's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
Red Star ain't laughing now, is he,
mate? Cuz I know he's been stalking my bets.
I know he's been [ __ ] stalking my
bets, mate. He He ain't [ __ ] laughing
now, is he, son? No.
Or the [ __ ] virgin can.
Yeah. Do you think that's a good return from 120?
I think it is. Yeah. That's like It's
like almost 400 pound, isn't it?
Yeah. You ain't laughing at me now,
mate. Nah, you're not. You're not
[ __ ] laughing at me now.
Yeah. 120 to 366 is better than nothing, is it? Exactly. Exactly.
I have the same amount of money this month
and obviously the designer clothes. So
yeah, it's not bad, bro. Not bad.
I'm going to get [ __ ] on uh I'm going
to get [ __ ] on Friday, I think.
Yeah, but what teams are playing? H.
I don't do them leagues. I hope this do
don't [ __ ] score.
Yeah, I hope this do don't score, lad.
cuz I would have paid 400.
Yeah, I done a bit like this before.
Yeah, I done a bet like this before, bro.
120, but we're turning 380. This one's 366. So
that Vicky Mill can go to his
boyfriend's channel and start [ __ ] crying.
The [ __ ] [ __ ]
He doesn't know anything about football.
He doesn't know anything about football, bro.
So, let's have another mad weekend.
Well, obviously I have to run it by
Grezy first. Okay with you, boss.
If I want to have a mad weekend again,
Grezy, is that okay with you, boss?
Is that okay with you, boss? I have to I
have to run it by you first. I did this
time. I I I'll actually listen to you. Huh?
Okay. Well, I'm not going to get a
haircut. I'm just going to wash my beard
and my hair. Next week, I'll get a haircut.
I don't think it's too long, is it?
[clears throat] No,
I think it's all right
if you brush it a little bit.
Yeah, I think so, man. I'll get a
haircut next week. I am not going to one this week. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm happy, bro. One.
I was nervous, bro. I was actually
getting nervous when the football was
starting. I was getting [ __ ] nervous, man. Yeah.
I'm just going to go out on the piss.
I'm just going to go out on the piss on Saturday, bro, and
spend as little as possible. I'll probably pre-drink.
Yeah. And then
I'll pre-drink and then I shouldn't
really be going out to be honest. It's a
[ __ ] waste of money in it.
It is a [ __ ] waste of money to be fair.
But I had a good weekend to be fair,
bro. I had a good weekend drinking,
[ __ ] gambling, [ __ ] escort.
But yeah, anyways, Greavvesy said it's
okay with him if I go out again.
Like I said, you've always got to run it by Grezy.
Okay with you, boss.
make it so.
But this time,
we can't keep doing these 600,600
weekends, bro. You can't keep doing it, man.
Cuz I'm not [ __ ] rich, you know? I
spent about £600, bro, from the Friday
to the [ __ ]
Oh, I'm not scared of anything going
wrong, bro. I'm not scared of anything going wrong.
You know me. I'm a crazy [ __ ]
I'm not scared of anything going wrong.
Been up and down the country by myself.
Been up and down the country by myself,
bro. I ain't scared of nothing. Ain't
scared of no one, bro.
Maybe I'll go to a different city next
week. I don't know. But yeah.
I need to budget like [ __ ] um
cuz my hair still looks okay. So I can
go on and like out for like 30 quid.
I've done it before. 30
free drink to [ __ ] Yeah, 30 quid. I
used to do it when I used to travel
around the country. I used to do it when
I used to travel up and around up and
down the country.
I used to always pre-drink and [ __ ]
[ __ ] I don't know whether I had
money, whether I didn't have money. And
I probably go for a nice meal again. So
I don't want to be spending more than 100 120.
I see 600 um weekends will [ __ ] kill us, bro.
Kill us, bro. Kill us. Yeah,
I just had Chinese.
Yeah, I had Chinese, man.
I already hate that.
So, yeah. What? What do I go? I went out
Saturday. So this week I might go out Friday
and I got the trainers. I got the jeans.
But these weekends are so dear. It's the
[ __ ] escort [ __ ] bro.
It's the escort [ __ ] That's what
[ __ ] kills the money.
It's the [ __ ] escorts. Yeah.
That's what does you, bro. That's what does you.
Yeah. I don't want to be spending more
than like4 on this night out, bro.
Yeah, I've got that. No,
can you pop it then, Virgin boy?
I can go out every day approach him, but
I just don't have the energy for it. And
I can't be bothered.
I don't have the energy and I can't be
[ __ ] bothered, bro.
Yeah. It's not worth it to find someone,
is it not [ __ ] worth it?
When you going to lose it? Are you going
to lose it, Virgin boy?
Oh, Virgin Boys reported me to the DWP
candy man cuz I bought the diner clothes.
A bless him. He's He's such a tryard,
this [ __ ] Is he?
He's He's such a tryard, is he, mate?
He's such a tryard. This wanker.
This wank is such a tryard, mate.
Did you agree?
No, he's a proper tryard, bro.
Just cuz somebody could afford designer
clothes and you can't. It doesn't make
them doesn't mean they're doing anything wrong. You know,
he's such a jealous little [ __ ] is it?
He's such a jealous little virgin. He
needs to get laid. He needs to get laid.
I've been saying this for ages, mate.
Yeah, it won. Yeah, you know,
I might go out on Friday or Saturday.
I'll just do Saturday. [ __ ] it in it.
I'll just go out Saturday. Um, yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] sake.
Deal with their [ __ ] [ __ ] again. It
deal with their bollocks again, will we?
They're [ __ ] [ __ ]
Where's this? Uh, here.
Now we can go back to his boyfriend's
channel. Connie, he can go back to his
[ __ ] boyfriend channel.
You [ __ ] virgin, can't you?
Please don't tell me that's going to be
a both score no draw. Please no. No.
I've got a feeling this is going to be a
both score no draw. For [ __ ] sake.
I got a feeling, man.
I've actually got a feeling it is going
to be, bro.
But I couldn't put that kind of money on
a [ __ ] both score. No draw. It would
have been probably about a thousand to be honest.
But it's fine. It's whatever. I've just
got this feeling.
Uh, I had Chinese.
Greasy. My mommy bought me Chinese. So, yeah.
Yeah. Bath just scored again. That's
going to be a both score. No draw. No, I
don't want more. I'm happy. I'm happy
with what I have. I'm just saying.
No, I'm happy with it, bro.
I want to get Laney some Ugg boots. They're £165, you know.
Yeah, they're £165. UG boots. Yeah.
They're [ __ ] dead, bro.
How you going to lose it? How are you
going to pop it?
How you going to lose it? How you When
you going to lose it, Ruby? That's more
than the question. But when are you
going to lose it?
When you going to lose it, you [ __ ]
virgin, can't you?
You virgin, can't you?
Virgin boy will never [ __ ]
pop that Vard. He'll die one.
Yeah, he [ __ ] would die, won't he?
I might have to go back to the Indian Grezy
to get my nutrients,
you know. I need my [ __ ] nutrients.
It's getting [ __ ] ridiculous now.
Yeah, I need my nutrients. Greasy.
Need my little nutrients. Greasy.
Need my nutrients.
You like that weekend madness, didn't
you, Grievy? You weren't expecting it,
was you? Then all of a sudden, you saw a
couple of uploads. It's [ __ ]
annoying, bro, cuz sometimes I'm trying
to watch the side men. I'd be watching
the Sideman and all of a sudden I get an
upload from Timmy Eldridge.
Yeah, you get a [ __ ]
get a [ __ ] upload from [ __ ] Timmy
Eldridge. [ __ ] annoying, you know. Yeah.
Yeah. You liked it, didn't you, Grievously?
Yeah. My mom saw the videos. I said,
"Oh, did you see them?"
She said, "Yeah."
I mean, we're not even talking about the
bouncer, bro. [ __ ] him. What about them
four [ __ ] that I stood I stuck it on
them, bro. I said my trainers cost more
than your [ __ ] whole outfit.
All about them [ __ ] They couldn't even
stand up, bro. They would have got dropped.
They would have got dropped, bro. [ __ ] the bouncer, you know. Yeah.
Or do you want to do it bad, Greasy? Huh?
Do you want to do it bad?
Greasy, do you want to go for a pint? Do
you want to go for a pint or do you want
to do it bad?
L got a microwave. Vindeloo,
do you know why, Breezy? Cuz he's absolutely skint
skint than a fuking skin. flint.
That's why Grezy because he's skinting skin flint. He's skinting
He's skinting skin flint, mate. Yeah. Oh gosh.
You like when I say that, Grey? Oh gosh.
Try and find a new mommy on the weekend.
Is it? I'll go out, Grezy, and try and
find a new mama.
What do you think of that, Greavvesy? Me
trying to find a new mama
cuz these Indians are getting too expensive.
They're getting way too expensive.
Tony calls them and breasticles. [laughter] Who
Who calls them [ __ ] breasticles? Breicles.
Oh my god. I've never heard that one before.
USA had breasticles.
How comes USA has breasticles grievy?
But I don't have breasticles.
Answer my question, Greavves. I know
you've heard me. Stop ignoring.
Stop ignoring me
before I come and do you.
Before I come and do you.
How's that one?
Oh, you [ __ ] birding [ __ ]
Yeah, she's a man as well.
You [ __ ] virgin [ __ ]
Well, I'm gone. Yeah.
Be back tomorrow. Peace.