[ __ ] both got no [ __ ] draw. The bastards.
[ __ ] both score. No [ __ ] draw. [sighs]
[ __ ] sake, man.
Always the way is it. Just to rub salt
in the wound.
Just to [ __ ] rub salt in the [ __ ] wound. So
[ __ ] bloody bastards. Gosh darn it.
You do that to tease me. I know it.
Oh, they're [ __ ] bro.
[ __ ] It was a both gone draw as well. [ __ ] bastards.
I would have been like, "Fuck those work."
I know, bro. But [ __ ] there was a
boat. It's always both score no [ __ ]
draw every time you win isn't it? It's a
big risk that one. Oh, and Dover scored
by the way. You know, if I done do
instead of slow, it would have been 400
instead of 366.
But it doesn't matter anyways.
They're bloody bastards, mate. I'll get
that both score no draw next week. Don't
you worry about that.
I'll get four next week. Don't you worry.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
I'm tired now.
[ __ ] bastard. Is it
all right, bro?
Who the [ __ ] is that?
It ended both score no draw. How much
would that been 120?
Probably about a thousand is it? I think
something silly like that.
Yeah, I think [ __ ] Nons needs to lose
his V card.
I reckon he he needs to pop it. What do you think?
I reckon he needs to pop that [ __ ] you know.
When you going to lose it? When you
going to lose it? When you going to lose
>> Your skin can't [ __ ] bastard.
I'm shattered. Oh, gosh darn it. I'm so sleepy.
I'm so bad with keeping that fan on all
night. You waste a lot of electricity.
But it's all right. It's okay.
Sure. It'll be fine. Yeah.
Of course you don't.
Of course you don't, mate.
Oh [ __ ] [ __ ] boy.
Virgin boy. What's that? tomorrow's the it's the Yeah.
I can't believe that both gone dry. It
always happens. The [ __ ] bastards.
[ __ ] Darlington was as well. [ __ ]
Bastards, bro. It
at least spenny M weren't both score no
draw. I done them last week. I done a
treble both score no draw last week.
Nope. Who replied and stop replying?
Same old England, isn't it, bro? It will never change.
If I done Kitty Minister, Darlington and
Slow both score no draw, that would have
won, which is what I was going to do last week. [ __ ] [snorts]
Here we go. It will never change, will it?
It will never change, lad. Never.
Yes, there's always both scores. No uh
in on the slow game. [snorts] Always. Oh gosh.
Is that cute Bob saying that? Oh gosh.
Yeah, it is. Oh gosh. Yeah. [ __ ]
going out drinking. [ __ ] bollocks in it.
How does this Scottish trans says she
doesn't dismiss my struggles? Of course
she dismisses my struggles. Don't be so foolish.
I'm addicted to this vintage porn. You
know, Bob Bills.
Yeah, vintage porn. Some of these videos
were in the 1990s, 1980s. Yeah.
in both SC bastards. [ __ ] bastards.
Oh, bastard [ __ ]
They are bastards. Anyways,
I'm gone. Yeah. Be back tomorrow. 100%.