Sorry I not I'm not long come back. Oh yeah,
I got T-bone steak for tea this evening or supper,
you know. If I fall asleep, then it will be supper,
you know. So yeah, I just took my meds
to calm me down. Oh, what the [ __ ]
There's something wrong with this Xbox.
Oh no, it's actually
>> Yeah, man.
God, I got tempted to approach today,
bro. [ __ ] My phone was on 1%. So, I
couldn't do any cuz obviously I wouldn't
have been able to got their number. [ __ ] sake.
This is This is what I mean, bro. Oh my god.
And it's not I'm not even going to use
the excuse that oh it's cuz I weren't
looking my best because I would do it
anyways if my phone was charged. [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
That Westfield Stratford and then they
full of [ __ ] stuck up people as well.
Stuck up women.
I had to get some bits. So
back now anyways.
[snorts] to collect the winners. The
goes Oh, [ __ ] hell.
Saturday's going to be a madness.
I'll make it one. Don't worry, mate.
Oh, Franklin, you've gone flying. Oh, he
does. Thank god. Quite vicious.
That's quite vicious. Oh wow.
Yeah, there was this woman on the train,
bro. The train was going slow as well.
And [ __ ] my phone was on 1%.
There was loads and loads of people and
it's like, should I do it? Should I not?
I only know the result. My phone's on
1%. So just didn't bother doing it. Yep.
You can't even [ __ ] go out in peace,
you know. You can't even go out in bloody peace,
you know. And I did see a bit of Monty's
live stream. He was like, "Oh, this is
how you go around not hiring people."
[ __ ] off, mate. If I go to a [ __ ]
shopping mall and I see some women, I'm bloody approaching.
If my phone's [ __ ]
you know, not 1%. I'm [ __ ] doing it,
mate. So, you get [ __ ] You know,
you literally can't help but do it.
You know, you're single. Why not? Why
can't you talk to people in the mall and stuff?
London's a crazy place. You know that
when you go back. Yeah.
But saying that it's not even just
London even. Well, I mean Rockford is
London, but I mean I mean like proper
proper proper East London, you know what
I mean? [ __ ] me.
Yeah, I got five numbers. Two replied
then stopped replying.
Just the same old [ __ ] is it? I was on
the train today. I had to pick up my
winnings and go to the [ __ ] uh
butchers and I saw this woman on the
train, bro. I was so tempted to do it,
but my phone was on 1%.
So, obviously, naturally, I didn't do it.
My phone was on 1%, so obviously I
couldn't get their number if I don't
know my number off my heart.
Oh, it's so [ __ ] up for me, bro.
Cuz I'm not scared to do these
approaches and I know what I'm going to get.
This is that that's the [ __ ] up thing
about it is because I know what I'm
going to get and I'm not scared to do
it. And I went to the mall as well. If
my phone went on 1% I would have done it
obviously, but there's no point doing it
if my phone's going to die because I
can't get their number.
Oh, [ __ ] sake, man.
I'll be out again on Saturday anyways. So,
[ __ ] sake. I would have done it as well.
Even though I know I shouldn't because
it's going to be the same old [ __ ]
Don't even go out in peace.
Don't even go out without being tempted
to do it.
It's bad, is it, bro? Bad.
But yeah, I got five numbers
and two replied stopped.
But it will always be that way, ain't
it? There's nothing anyone can say now,
bro. What the [ __ ]
Like, Saturday is going to be the same.
It will never change, but there's
nothing else to do. So, I'd rather have
somewhat of a [ __ ] life, you know
what I mean?
Um, so yeah,
got my jeans, got my trainers,
got money, so why the [ __ ] not, you
know? What else am I doing? So yeah,
I'm glad it doesn't bother me anymore,
though. I'm glad it don't bother me.
That£500 thing I think needed to happen
because I've got no hope. So, because
I've got no hope, it doesn't drive me
mad. I whatever. It's It would always be that way.
You know, of course I don't have no
hope, but there's nothing else to do but
go out. So, what you know what I'm saying? So,
it's the hope that drives you mad. Once
you finally lose the hope,
um, then you, you know, you're good.
That's what happened with me. So, if you
get 10 numbers and not get a date, it's
very unlikely you're going to meet
someone. So, I don't really give a [ __ ]
about it anymore. Just going to go and
just do this thing.
Look what happened, bro. I got five
numbers, only two replied. I'd done 600
pound over the weekend. So
the [ __ ] man.
That's that that's life in it, bro. Yeah.
And there'll always be numbers.
And I was trying to explain this to this
uh Scottish transgender. Yeah. I was
trying to I was trying to explain this.
I said, she was like, "Oh, yeah, but you
don't understand, some women don't want
to give their number and they feel
pressured." I was like, "But that's not
the problem. Why are you talking about
that? We're not We're not talking about
people giving their number and not
giving their number. That's We're not
talking about that." You know, we're not
even talking about people that say
they've got boyfriends. It's We're not
Did we just talking about that? That's
not all that happens when we go out.
you're always going to get [ __ ]
numbers, bro. You know, um,
so it's what it's what they do when you
get their number. It's got nothing to do
with people not giving their number. That's
a very very small part of it. Like,
yeah, I went to um, Westfield. I just
come back from the butchers, got T-Bone,
staking that. I saw some women out
today, joker, but I couldn't do any
approaches cuz my phone was on 1%. I
didn't plan to do any approaches. I
didn't even plan to leave the area
today, but I thought, "Oh, let me just
go stra go to the butchers." [ __ ]
There was one on the train, bro. I was
going to do it, but my phone was on 1%,
so I couldn't get their [ __ ] number,
which is a good thing to be tried to get
their number, which is a good thing
because you know, you know, they're just
going to say they got a boyfriend and
that. So, and I went for I would have
100% done it, bro.
If that if the phone wasn't on if the
phone died by that point, I would have
done it. [ __ ] [ __ ] is it? Oh [ __ ]
Oh [ __ ] Joker. [ __ ] bro.
No, I'm going out Saturday, mate. No,
I'm going out Saturday. I'm I am going
I'm going to go out Saturday, then I'm
going to go out the week after that.
Uh, it doesn't know, it doesn't get me
worked up anymore. It doesn't get me
worked up anymore, believe it or not. I
got five numbers last week
uh over the weekend, bro. And two of
them replied and stopped replying. I was
like, "Oh, whatever, bro. It doesn't
bother me anymore because,
you know, it would always be the same in
this country. So, at the end of the day,
when you go out, you're you're playing
at your own risk. It's not going to work
me out, bro. And work me up. It won't
cuz I know what it will never change.
So, I don't give a [ __ ]
Because the thing is, bro, I when I went
out the last time, not Saturday, the
last time before that, I got 10 numbers.
I didn't even get a date. I mean, what's
going to get worse than that, bro?
Nothing. So, it doesn't work me. It
doesn't get me worked up.
cuz I know I'm leaving anyways. So
I know I'm leaving and I know what to
do. So it doesn't bother me, bro. yeah.
Well, obviously I'm still going to
approach when I go out.
I just do it because it's something to do, bro.
I know there's no hope in this country
and they're not interested in this
country. But I mean, there's nothing
else to do in it.
So, I'd rather be doing that than sat
around doing nothing,
you know? I've done good, bro. I got new
trainers, new jeans, I've got money. So,
[ __ ] I don't work. So, I mean, I'm
not doing sitting [ __ ] indoors all
day. I did stay in yesterday cuz I was
tired. I've been on the go. So,
but yeah, pretty much. Oh [ __ ]
Yeah. And I'll get my haircut next week
and then go out again next week. Or
maybe take a two week or maybe I'll take
a two week break.
I don't know. I'll do I'll figure
something out. I don't know. Bro,
joker. You know when you go to them
clubs? Yeah. They [ __ ] water them
drinks down, bro. Yeah. When I was in
[ __ ] Simmons, they watered that [ __ ]
down, bro. I done like 40 pound in like
10 minutes. They watered it down.
They watered that [ __ ] down, bro.
Yeah. I'm going to stick to Guinness, bro.
Bro, that's why if you if you go to they
can't do it with Guinness. They can't
water down Guinness as much cuz if you
try to down a Guinness, bro, it will hit
you. Whereas with them [ __ ] with that
rum [ __ ] bro, it's like water.
It's like you're drinking [ __ ] water, mate.
Yeah, I'll be sticking to beer.
Yep, it was £7 for a single. I was getting singles.
I just got to go to the off license, get
[ __ ] on beer, then go uh thing in it. Yeah, man. Joseph Farah.
Joker. Joseph Ferrra.
Oh, bless you then if it makes you bloated.
Oh, I don't know what to wear though on
Saturday. I might wear my Hilfiger coat
with my bear top and my trainers or
should I wear this? Or should I wear Stone Island
or should I wear Stone Island? Oh, I
love Baby Guinness shots. Yeah, I love
Baby Guinness shot. Don't worry, bro. On
Saturday, I won't be spending more than £50.
Yeah, two weeks I won't be I won't be
spending more than £50. Don't you worry
about that, mate.
I will not be spending more than £50.
Mark my words, I won't be.
Nah, I might do that next week. Nah, I
might do that next week when I get my haircut.
No. Yeah. Well, that's a different story.
Yeah, but that's a different story
though, isn't it?
Well, I went out with a turtleneck
blazer, got 10 numbers, I didn't even
get a date.
You'd actually be surprised. The more
shitty you look, the more success you get.
That's the weirdest thing about it. The
more [ __ ] you look, the more success you
get. I know.
I've gone out tracksuit, scruffy beard,
and I seem to have done better. Yep.
I'm And I'm not getting my haircut this
week. I need to wash my hair when I go out.
So, yeah, I'm going to be like this. I'm
going to go out like this.
Obviously, I'm going to wash my hair and
that, wash my beard, and just go out
and get a haircut next week.
I'm not getting a haircut this week.
I got one not so long ago. So, next week. Yeah,
next week I will. Yeah,
pretty much. Yeah,
I'm just going to wear Stone Island.
I'm going to wear Stone Island
with the trainers and the jeans, brush
the beard, wash my hair obviously,
and yeah, get a haircut next week.
Wonder how many numbers we'll get on Saturday.
That woman was going to get approached
on the [ __ ] train today, bro. [ __ ]
me. If that phone went on 1%.
She reminded me of this woman. She was
like, "Oh, what do you prefer, boobs or
bama?" I said boobs. She said, "Lucky
for you, I've got both.
Then I started sucking on her [ __ ]
tits and she's like, "Oh, I'm not I'm
not like I'm not a cow."
I said, "Yes, you are." See, I've always been a booby muncher,
you know. I've always been a booby nibbler,
you know, a booby nibbler and a and a
and a curry muncher.
She said, "I'm not a cow." I said you
are a cow.
I need my protein.
Have I ever done Have I ever called
approach on a on a on a train conductor?
No. Yeah, I was going to do some
approaches today, Grezy, but my phone I
went to the mall. I went to the
butchers, but my phone was on one [ __ ] percent.
So, I'm not even going to [ __ ] use me
not even looking my best as an excuse because
I would have done it if my phone wasn't
about to die and then it died when I was
at the mall. So, cuz I didn't plan to go
that far today. I went to I went to
Weather Spoons, had a breakfast.
[ __ ] some women's getting it
Saturday, Greavesy. We can't let these
women win. They're laughing at us, mocking us.
We can't let these women win.
We cannot let them win, can we?
We can't let these [ __ ] women win.
Grezy, can we?
I collected my little winnings.
I gave Laney £25 to get her nails done.
I'm such a I'm such a good son, aren't I, Grezy?
I'm such a good son, aren't I?
We can't let them like keep us sexless and stuff
and laugh at us and mock us.
What do Well, you should bother with
them, Grezy. You need your milk like me.
Well, you [ __ ] should do.
I've got a t-bone steak later for supper. Grezy.
Yeah, but I need my I need my I need my
milk. No, Grezy.
They don't cost more than 25. They're £25.
No, it isn't. It's £25.
That's how much it was. That's g. Yep.
It isn't 40 minimum. When I get my
haircut, I pay 55
cuz I get a full surface like my skin
cuz obviously I get my skin I get
everything done, bro. But I do it like
once a month, every six weeks. So I
don't mind paying it to be honest.
And the smell stays for like 4 days. So
I just pay it.
No to my mama.
No, I ain't going out today, bro.
No, I ain't going out today.
I might go out Friday.
I'm even going out Friday or Saturday.
No. Friday or Saturday. Um,
either one's good. So, I done Saturday
last time, so maybe I'll do Friday.
Maybe I'll do Friday. I don't I don't
know. I don't know what I'm doing. I'm going out.
Do you like my little Marley jeans,
Joker? My little train is
Red Star's jealous. He was trying to say
I got it from the catalog. The catalog?
Nah, not the catalog, mate.
Not nothing to do with the catalog.
Why the [ __ ] would I get [ __ ] that
from the catalog?
I've never used a catalog. That's Monty.
Sing your way into a woman's bed. I
can't. They've all got bloody boyfriends. LDS.
I'm sure they do.
I woke up to [ __ ] notifications um
from Timmy Aldridge. Greavvesy.
[ __ ] Timmy Aldridge
[ __ ] What is it with this clown, bro?
That's their favorite line, isn't it?
Candyman. That's their f That's their
favorite liny lad.
I reckon that Candyman is definitely dusty.
Definitely. I can smell him a mile off.
I can smell him a mile off, mate.
I can smell you, mate. All the way from here.
I think this is definitely that dusty showers me.
I got this feeling. Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] me. You know what I might do,
Grez? I might go to Cardiff uh next week
and get a
a kebab. Remember when I was telling you
about that chicken uh chicken kebab that
you can't get in London? I might do a
little video dedicated to you.
You can't get in London for some reason.
I'm so tired.
I'll travel all that way just to get a kebab. Yeah.
I can't stop watching this these 1980s
1990s porn grey
this [ __ ] vintage porn. Oh gosh.
Yeah, I'm angry today.
I remember when I went to Wales the
first time, I snugged three women.
Yeah, I I I kissed three women. Grezy
and I robbed one of their clearest
if I remember correctly.
Yeah, I remember the first time I went
to Wales, bro. I remember the first time.
I've been there three times here. Nope.
I'm in bed. I'm in my little nesticles.
I can't wait to have my delicious T-bone later.
I can't wait.
I absolutely can't wait. Oh, [ __ ]
So, but the [ __ ] uh
I haven't done a football bet for
Saturday yet. Virgin boy has gone quiet.
Where's Virgin boy?
I think the skin virgin's [ __ ] dead
or something. Joker.
He'll lose it one day, mate. I've got
faith in him. He will lose that V card one day.
I reckon one day he'll lose it.
Should I ask the manager uh if he can
come with me this week, Grey? cuz
obviously we had problems last week, lad.
I'll be out again Saturday, Pokémon.
I'll be out again Saturday. I just come
back from the butchers.
There was a sexy woman on the train, but
I couldn't approach.
Uh, no. Nons. I couldn't approach cuz of
uh my phone was on 1%.
And I'll be in Thailand in two weeks.
So, You'll be by yourself, buddy. You'll
be all by yourself, [snorts]
you know, cuz I don't know my number off by heart.
I don't know my number off by heart. I'm
not the only one that doesn't. So then I
went to Westfield and
you can't even go out without feeling
the need to approach. It's [ __ ] bad,
bro. Obviously, I would have done it if
my phone went um dead.
No, I don't do Instagram.
No, cuz I don't do Instagram. I don't
add women on Instagram or Snapchat.
It's number or nothing. So,
if you've noticed from the approaches,
if they ever say Instagram, I say I
don't have it cuz I don't I don't do Instagram.
So yeah, I don't do uh Instagram
[snorts] or Snapchat really.
When I was in Simmons, mom was like,
"Oh, I'll give you my Instagram."
Snapchat. I said, "No."
I said, "Only number?"
Yeah, man. I didn't plan to go to
Stratford today, but I went back there
to get some food. T-Bone and Yep.
Don't know what LG's problem was last week, Pokémon.
What the [ __ ] was his bloody problem?
But yeah, I'm gone in two weeks anyways,
bro. So it doesn't bother me anymore.
I'm out of here, lad.
What was his problem? Pokemon. Yeah. One sec.
The t-bone a bit later.
I was thinking of you, Pokemon, when uh
I was on a train.
Do you remember taking a baby away from its mama?
Like when you used to mock me and stuff?
It made me laugh. Yeah, man.
Yeah, you are an incel.
Nope. [clears throat] I don't regret it.
Not me. I never regret it.
Nope. I don't regret it ever. If I ever
see someone and don't do an approach, I
don't regret it
because I know the result. So I I never
regret it ever.
like most people.
They're buying out
uh because I didn't. But anyways, but
no, I never regret me cuz I already know
the result. So why would I regret it? If
anything, I feel good that I didn't do it.
Cuz if you do approach, all you're going
to get is the same thing.
So why would you regret not doing it
when you know it's the same thing?
That's there's no regrets to be had.
It's not like a football bet.
Uh it's like a football bet. A double
both teams just go you regret not do you
you you going to do it and then you
don't do it and then it comes in. This
will always be the same here where they
pretend they got boyfriends or [ __ ] you
over. There's nothing to regret, bro. If
you don't do it, you don't do it in it.
I never regret it. There's been ones
before I ain't done.
No, because you're not curious because
you already know the result.
There's no there's no curiosity
because you already know what's going to happen
again. Bro, you're talking to me here, lad.
You're talking to me here, bro.
I've already got nice clothes. I've got
a wardrobe full of nice clothes.
Pretty similar. Yeah. Uh,
I have a boyfriend. I'm not interested. Um,
walk past you, give their number, lead
you on. Pretty much. So,
there's no weed, bro. I'm in Thailand in
two weeks, so there's only going to be you, lad.
There's only going to be you. There's
not going to be me, bro. There's only you now.
Well, there's only going to be you in
two weeks. There's not going to be we.
There's only going to be you. Cuz I'm
out of here, laddy. I'm gone.
So, you'll be by yourself.
You'll be by your your little self. Yeah.
But I won't be I won't be [ __ ]
I won't be um
Yeah, I I I don't regret it. Me, I'd
never regret it
cuz it will always be Antman said it
will always be the same here. You know this. So yeah,
you need to leave.
That's all you.
Yeah, you need to leave the country.
That's that. It's the end of that, ain't it?
What do you reckon will happen when I go
out Saturday, Pokemon?
What do you reckon will happen?
I might just go out all day approaching.
I might just be out all day doing it. To
be fair, I might just go out all day Saturday doing it.
Well, duh. That's why most people go to [ __ ] Thailand.
But I'm not putting any more content on
this channel like bounces and women and stuff because
people just make up excuses anyways.
You know, just look at here we go. You
prove you've had sex, they still call
you a virgin, you know.
Yeah. And I was laughing at her, bro.
And I told her boyfriend about him, his [ __ ] self.
Said everyone was laughing at me yet. No
one was looking at me but them.
Literally, nobody was looking at me but them.
Told them to [ __ ] off, bro. But no more
[ __ ] No more videos anyways, by the
way. No more videos.
Too many biased people.
I told them to [ __ ] off back to
Newcastle, lad. I told them to [ __ ] off.
That's where they [ __ ] come from. Yeah.
Yeah. I should have put £500 football
bet. Oh well. 240 is 240 in it.
It's all right in it, I guess.
It's enough. So,
it was a both score no draw to make it worse. Pokeman.
Yep. It was a no. It was a both score no
draw. Just to rub salt in the womb.
Yeah. Just to rub salt in the [ __ ] wound.
Both score no [ __ ] draw, bastards. Imagine
you had [ __ ] 500 quid on that. E Jesus.
Yeah, but I'm not going to do 10 teams,
am I? You idiot.
Because one's just going to let you down. So So yeah,
I'm going to have to really send this on
Saturday, bro. [ __ ] I ain't got the
energy for this [ __ ] anymore. Poke bomb.
I shouldn't have to keep trying, bro.
I've tried enough for [ __ ] sake.
But I need my milk and stuff. I need my vitamins.
You know what I mean?
They're very weak without them, without vitamins.
You know what I mean? Grezy, I need some milk.
Yeah. If they ain't got no boobies,
Grezy, I won't. I saw this black guy
with a woman.
And uh she was like a six out of 10, but
she had no boobies, Grezy.
So, it's no good to me, is it?
No, there's no milk there then, is
there, Grezy? So, what's the point, you know?
No, I don't want that [ __ ] She's [ __ ] stinking.
I was looking at that autumn, but she uses filters
and she's a horrible [ __ ] And I haven't
seen her boobs. So,
and I haven't seen her boobs. So,
if she has no boobs, then it's no good
for me because there's no milk. You see?
Yeah, I need to be fed, Grezy. I need to be fed.
Why is that, Grevy? I need to be fed.
Everyone else seems to get on, okay, but not me.
Yeah, that one that said I've got both
boobs and oh, she had big boobies.
She was rubbing my dick and I was
squeezing her boobs and stuff,
sucking them as well.
It was a lovely sight. Yep.
I can't go out and find a new [ __ ] mama. Jesus Christ.
It's just depressing, isn't it?
[ __ ] Someone need [ __ ] someone needs
to hurry the [ __ ] up. Like I said, I'm
all right in the summer, but yeah,
I'm just a baby, aren't I, Greasy?
I'm a big baby. Oh gosh. Second.
Oh, this waffle bedding is so nice.
Hopefully we can get someone on this Saturday, bro.
Oh, I've had enough of this [ __ ]
Still don't know what to wear.
Like I said, maybe the coat with the
teddy bear t-shirt, the jeans, and the
trainers. I could wear the Stony,
but we wore the Stony last week.
Do you think we
can't work Greavves? I get too tired.
I'm too tired to work. I like sleeping.
Uh, yes I do.
Uh, do you want to see?
I haven't got a nice button-up shirt.
Are you sure?
I've got a few shirts.
I got Ralph Lauren and I got All Saints.
I've got a few shirt I got a few shirts.
Would you like to see them?
I'll show you them if you want.
They they cost a lot of money.
They're not what they're not like the
ones that Virgin Boy wears.
I didn't actually realize I had Some of
them do need ironing, by the way.
But either way,
see I split things, you see.
So I got this. All Saints.
Yeah. Another expensive.
This is All Saints.
Expensive. Got a logo on it.
This is a cheap one.
This is just some cheap one. Um, this one expensive. This one
Um, and this one.
Why is that got wire? [snorts]
What do you think? Why?
And I've obviously got these stonies,
but I was thinking on Saturday wearing this
with the jeans and trainers,
but then I was also thinking about just
wearing a coat. I don't know.
Got so many clothes, you know. >> [snorts]
>> I got so many bloody clothes.
Maybe the clo and just a t-shirt then.
I don't like shirts. I don't really like them, bro.
How about the Tommy? How about the Tommy
Jer jeans and the trainers?
How about that one? Greezy Tommy Hilfera
coat, teddy bear t-shirt, jeans, and the trainers.
I think that's a good that's a good fit. No. Yeah.
I mean, it's a teddy bear t-shirt, but
it is a design.
It is a [ __ ] design, bro. you know.
Yeah, I already wor I wore a Stone
Island last week, so
yeah, I'll just wear that.
[ __ ] it. Anyways, and then the next week
I'll wear the turtleneck and the blazer.
It's kind of too cold just to wear [ __ ] uh
It's kind of too cold just to wear um
Yeah. just to wear a shirt by itself.
That's more like March, April,
maybe September, you know, like them
kind of months.
But hopefully I find a new mommy.
I'd love to find a new mommy. Grezy, you know,
that will love me
like USA. Izzy loved me, you know.
Bless you. Well, you didn't think I had
button-ups greaves in you, silly goose,
did you? You silly goose.
Oh, I should have had £500 on that bet. [ __ ] sake.
Nah, bro. I'm not greedy. I'm I'm happy
with the money I have.
It was a good month. It's actually been good, Grezy,
cuz I bought the trainers, I bought the
jeans, and I spent [ __ ] like £500
over that weekend.
So, I'm happy with that to be honest.
Isn't that right, Grezy? I'm happy with that.
Yeah, I'm just happy with that to be fair
cuz I bought I spent a lot of money on
like clothes and stuff. So, fine.
Yeah, I'm going to put that coat in a
wash. I've never washed it, you know.
Wash it inside out. Nice teddy bear t-shirt.
Get the [ __ ] in there. Oh,
why do the steak so lush today, bro?
So, do you think Ant-Man was lying when
he said that they're not interested in
this country, Grezy?
Do you think he was just talking [ __ ] or
do you think there's some element of
truth to that?
Do you think there's some element of
truth to that? Yeah.
Well, like I said, I've got a lovely
t-bone for tea.
Oh, bless you, Grevy. You're so silly.
Sometimes I just think about like the
women that I've been with, Grezy, and their boobies.
I don't know who's the biggest ones I'
I've been with. USA Izzy's ones weren't
the biggest squeezy, but uh
I like peppies. I like the chicken. I
like the I get a whole chicken from peppers. Yeah.
What woman do you reckon I've been with
Greg you that had the biggest boobies?
Do you have anyone had big boobies? Um,
Sne had big boobies.
The one in Manchester didn't have any,
so she can't be my mommy. Nope.
That's so cute. Ant-Man
said that uh England sucks, you know.
Ant-Man says England sucks. At least out
in Thailand, you can get sex when you want it. [snorts]
I'm feeling a bit peckish now, Greavesy.
But it's a bit too early to uh
it's a bit too early to have my T-bone
steak. Me thinks
Yeah. I remember when she used to suck my willie.
That's cute. Is it Greavvesy? She used
to suck my Willie. I used to just get it out.
It hardly fit in her mouth. Uh >> [snorts]
>> Oh gosh, belly is rumbling.
I know I'm hungry.
Silly, isn't it? Oh gosh.
Well, I'll be back later. Right.