Yo yo
not good man.
Super parade. What the [ __ ]
No, but I just woke up. I'm going to do
it in a bit.
I've been I've been sleeping, bro. I'm [ __ ] knackered. [snorts]
No, bro. I'm tired, bro. Sure. You know,
I just fell as I just woke up basically.
I fell asleep. I was tired. Going to do
the steak in a bit. Yeah.
[ __ ] knackered, matey.
[snorts] I went to the butchers and I
come back and I just [ __ ] fell
asleep, man. tired.
The skin virgin in the bed shit's been quiet and he bar
that blooming virgin's been quiet.
That blooming virgin
skint virgin [ __ ]
Where's Joseph Ferrara?
He's going a bit quiet.
Oh yeah, true, bro. True.
He needs to get [ __ ] laid, so he
needs to [ __ ] Yeah, man.
Yeah, bro. I'll be out on Saturday.
I'll [snorts] be out on Saturday, D. Yep. Oh [ __ ]
[snorts] Yeah, I was going to do some
approaches earlier, but my phone was on
1% and then it died, so I didn't do him. Jasper.
Yeah, my phone was on 1% so I never
bothered. My phone died.
Is what it is. [snorts] [ __ ] me. Oh.
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> I wasn't so tired today, bro. boys. [snorts]
I lose it. I just [ __ ] woke up, mate.
Where's the bird?
Yeah. You can't get a girlfriend.
I mean, you can't get a girlfriend.
Get a girlfriend. Nelly G's a fat slag.
I wouldn't get with her if you paid me.
I mean, she's a fat slag who I rejected.
I mean, good for him. [snorts] I don't
want someone like that. All of these
people that you're Jesus Christ,
fireworks. All of these people that
you're saying can get girlfriends or fat
ugly munters who I won't go anywhere
near and all of the women I've been with
were not as bad as them.
I mean, I don't want their fat, ugly m
girlfriends. Question is, where's your
girlfriend? And that's where you'll [ __ ]
off. So, there's no point in starting
this stuff cuz you're you don't have a
girlfriend and you're a virgin.
So, I don't know why you're on this channel, Dad.
You can't get one. You can't get a
girlfriend and you can't get laid. Who's
got a girlfriend? Natalie G wouldn't go
nowhere near. Virgin boy's girlfriend
wouldn't go anywhere near. Haley would
never go anywhere near. I' I'd rather
not. Thank you.
Yes. These people don't count as
girlfriends. They're that [ __ ] ugly.
You could not pay me to go near any of them. [snorts]
Where's your girlfriend?
That's a good question, is it? Stephen,
I would delay.
Where's your girlfriend? Um, players
low six. Where's your girlfriend?
Cuz this bastic don't have a girlfriend, do they?
Cuz you said that the spastics like
[ __ ] can get girlfriends. So where's
your girlfriend? You [ __ ]
You said spastics. [laughter]
Sorry, this is too much. I've just woke
up. Stop it. You said the spastics can
get girlfriend. So where's your
girlfriend, you [ __ ] You know,
probably sat there a virgin.
He's probably just sat there a virgin on
YouTube like most of these people
sat there a little virgin.
I would say yeah.
I would say most of these people
I would say most of these people in this
community are virgins. I'm not even
joking about I said this the other day.
Like most of these people on here are actual virgins.
I actually believe it lad generally
generally generally do. I'm not just
talking about nonslegs and [ __ ] Bob.
I mean there's there's a few of them
and Timmy as well. I think I think most
of them are virgins.
So he said he writes a comment then he leaves. Uh
madness. You said that the spastics can
get a girlfriend. Well if that's true
where's your girlfriend? You're [ __ ]
Bit strange isn't it?
But 90 yeah 90% of the people in this
community are defo virgins.
We can tell by the way they stick up for
women, defend women. Um the proper
proper virgins on here, bro. Don't let
them tell you otherwise.
I don't want that energy. I don't want
Taylor. I don't want [ __ ] disabled Sarah.
I don't want any of them. I would I
would go near them if you paid me.
I'm not a virgin. I prove I've had sex multiple times.
[snorts] This is why I don't put up
content anymore. And why I won't put up
content anymore because you always twist
[ __ ] Whether it's sex, whether it's
defending yourself against a man, having
a guy at a woman. That's why I won't put
content on this channel, you know?
That's why I won't put content on this
channel. [ __ ] that. Yep.
Cuz they twist [ __ ]
Nah. Most of you people ain't had sex.
No way. No way.
No [ __ ] way. 90% of this community
has not had sex. 100%. No way.
No [ __ ] way. And the people that have
had sex probably haven't had sex in over a decade.
No [ __ ] way, bro.
No [ __ ] way.
Oh, yeah. No more content. No more No,
I need to do the steak in a bit, bro.
I'm [ __ ] starving.
E a s.
E. Anyways, when are you skin people
going to get off YouTube and get a life
and get a job?
Huh? [snorts] I was out for hours
earlier. I just woke up. When do you
skid people going to get a life and get a job?
That's a good question.
You're on here every [ __ ] day.
Oh, I still got them. Oh, I got some
donuts as well. I need to finish some
donuts after this uh steak, by the way.
Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] Yep. I need
to finish some donuts.
Virgin boy has been quiet. The skint
virgin in the outer London bed. I'm
starting to get worried, mate.
Starting to get bloody worried about
that virgin. Me.
Starting to get worried about that blooming virgin. Indigo.
And yeah, I said it. Blooming.
Maybe you finally got laid. You got got a life. Who knows?
Yeah, I definitely need them donuts, bro. >> [snorts]
>> Why? Reddit are liars, aren't they,
Indigo? They say that you're going to
meet someone. They're bloody liars,
aren't they, on Reddit?
Yeah, on Reddit, they're bloody liars. Indigo Oh,
what you say? Bloody liars.
People say you'll meet some man indie guy
to do the steak. [snorts]
Right. Let me get up. Oh jeez.
Oh, that version boy.
Oh, that virgin boy.
What happened anymore? Oh [ __ ] Uh, no.
I think it'll be long. >> [snorts]
>> Oh [ __ ] >> Ready.
It wasn't a big [clears throat] for some reason, but
bloody took over that [ __ ]
>> [clears throat]
>> I reckon we could
reckon we can build that one.
No, I'm going to P it, I think. P it and
then good it
stay in it, mate.
Bit out of Virgin Boy price range.
Is it Steven?
bit too much for emergent. [clears throat] Huh? Y
have a puppet.
Donuts for afters.
Does it look a good steak? Yeah.
Don't know what's happen with that.
Not as big, but
it's all right there.
to do what All right. That's for Huh? [clears throat]
What? They gave me some.
They gave me some deodorant with my uh
deodorant. It came in my tray with Maya [snorts]
veraccept. [clears throat]
You never know. He might lost his card.
my box it.
Yeah, Stephen, I was going to do some
approaches earlier, but I was in a mall.
I was in the mall and uh
there's women and stuff. I went to the
butchers, but my phone was 1% and died,
so I didn't bother.
Yeah, the one on the train was [ __ ] all made
See the pine up.
There we go. Ready. Feels
pretty if you ask me. Look at that.
Virgin boy started out boy.
I'm all right. I'm [clears throat] not
No. Oh, it needs a bit of lemon. That's
what it needs. Sorry.
Yeah, man. Sorry. I was just talking to someone.
Sorry about that, lady.
All right, boss.
Just whooping up a lovely t-bone, boss.
Is that okay with you, boss? Nope.
>> Good me. [laughter] >> Hey,
just cooking up a lovely t-bone.
Whipping up a lovely t-bone.
That's your financial advisor. That's
okay with me, boss. that please say
I know a certain person can't afford it. It's code
must be 12 bloody quid.
>> Oh, I'm having a kebab next week. I'm
going to work.
This is my favorite.
This is my favorite, bro. Look.
This one. This one here. This is peanut
butter. I'm going to scuff all of these
after my food. Except that one. I don't
like that one. It's jam. I don't like
Okay with you, boss.
Oh, I love sh kebabs. They're yummy.
Do you believe I would have approached
late at something earlier if my phone
was uh if my phone was charged? Do you believe me?
They believe me.
Hey, believe me, please. [ __ ] bleeding.
Do you believe me, Grezy? I would have
done it if my uh phone wasn't almost
about to die.
Be honest, Grezy. over again.
>> You believe me, don't you say? Yeah, right. selfish.
You know what?
Do you believe? Do you believe I would
have done it? Grey,
you need to answer me.
If my phone didn't die, do you reckon I
would have done some approaches earlier
at the mall?
I should be busy.
How do you know I'm with a greasy?
You know what I'm like? I'm out of
control sometimes, aren't I?
Look at that.
under the grill there.
You don't mind trust if you're gay. You gay. You can't might not my
Who is this
being the copycat?
You know that music. I'm being
I'm being a little
being a little copycat.
Look at that.
Look at that crazy
glue on a minute. No copycat. Copycat. D,
you Little copycat.
You little copycat.
Probably doesn't know what I'm talking
about, does he? Copycat.
Go there. You little copycat.
Look at that. You little copycat. [laughter]
They're gay. They don't like her.
They're gay. They're gay, aren't they?
[ __ ] gay, aren't they? They don't
like her. They're [ __ ] gay, aren't they? Copycat.
Sick of copycats.
I hate copycats. What's that?
A little copycat. Little copycat.
No. Oh yeah. [snorts]
Go to the grill now.
Love the letter.
What's wrong with the grill?
Put each other space. Thank you.
That was amazing.
You skip those Yeah. Yes. No.
is a little copycat.
Why is he a copycat?
>> Why is he such a little copycat?
Why do you think he's such a copycat?
Why do you Why do you have to put him
out with the crowd? Be unique. Be be
your own person. Be a copycat.
Why? Why be a copycat? Okay. No copycat. Don't copy Think
it's ready now.
You know copycat family copycats
and they bloody copy each other. One second. I thought
I like [ __ ] virgin.
[ __ ] [ __ ] bed. No bed, no money.
I'm not like some skin in a [ __ ] bed
with no bed. [ __ ] no money.
I look like some [ __ ] stupid little
no [ __ ] money in them.
Right. Ready for the finished product box.
There we go.
I didn't glue the back cuz I figured
that that was just enough. Yeah.
>> Yeah. I didn't rule it back to be
I'll be about
with the donuts.