Oh gosh,
them piggies showing down like a treat, mama.
Bit upset. Bit sad. Right, that f could
go on now since you got the the money in the thing.
Give me that.
All right, one sec.
Sick of these bloody Reddit mods banning
me. Joseph Farra.
I like your little picture when he comes up. Joseph,
sick of these bloody people dismissing
my bloody struggles. Had enough of it,
you know. I just I just got some breakfast,
Right. I I've got a bone to pick with Joseph.
I've had enough of this bollocks.
Here we go. I just have some tasty
piggies. Oh, they sure went down like a treat.
they keep dismissing my bloody
struggles. Indigo, I've had enough of it.
You know, I've had to [ __ ] put up
lady about that a couple of times, but
that's that's not the point.
They always dismiss my struggles and
I've had enough, you know,
[ __ ] telling me I'm going to meet
someone. When When will I meet someone?
You know, it's [ __ ] They keep
telling me I'm ready. I'll meet someone and stuff.
The dating apps don't bloody work. I've
had enough of it.
Seriously, had a [ __ ] laugh.
Now, I've been hearing since I was
bloody 14 years of age. You know, your
time will come. You'll meet someone.
Women aren't all the same. I've been
hearing it for [ __ ] years. You know,
isn't it time I'm shown different for a
change? I've had enough of this [ __ ]
I went to uh the dentist earlier to try
and book an appointment. Long story. And
guess what? That receptionist had the
same attitude as all of these other
women. Where are these bloody different
women? How many times do I have to keep
going out every week spending four 500
[ __ ] pounds, right?
How many times do I have to keep bloody
doing this? I've had enough.
How many more times do I have to keep
bloody doing this? I'm going to Thailand
in two weeks. [ __ ] you all.
You know, I've had enough of it now.
I don't know. Do
[ __ ] had enough of him. They're all
bloody stuck up.
Keep telling me I'm going to meet someone. D,
you know, we're getting old.
You know, we're getting bloody old. How
many How many times you have to keep
going out and spending money and stuff?
You know, I've had enough. I got a bone
to pick with Joseph Ferrar. Where were
these different women that we keep hearing of?
Now, the amount of times, right, I've
had to hear the skin virgin in the bed
sick. You don't know all women. And I've
had to go out and [ __ ] meet all of
these bloody [ __ ] you know. I've had
enough. I've had enough of it, mate.
Yeah, man. It's [ __ ] up.
Yeah, they've all got the same bloody
attitude. What the hell? What the hell
is bells? Well, guess what? I'll be out
tomorrow looking for that change
and I want a bloody change, you know,
from last time cuz I've had enough of it.
I'm sick of these [ __ ] Reddit mods as well. Simple white knights, you know.
Yeah, bro. It's [ __ ] ass, bro. It's [ __ ] pants. Really, man?
will be here today. I'm looking forward to that.
I'm looking forward to that little
dressing gown. I've been waiting ages for it.
But uh yeah, in all seriousness, bro, [ __ ] um
yeah, it it would always be the same
here. You know this. That's what Ant-Man
said. But no, he's just negative. He's
just [ __ ] negative, is he?
He's just [ __ ] negative.
These [ __ ] people on Reddit are bloody liars.
I said they ain't bloody interested.
You little liars.
They're all [ __ ] liars, aren't they?
Indigo. Bloody lying [ __ ] Yeah. No,
these bloody weekends are expensive.
Why do these people keep [ __ ]
dismissing my struggles? They don't seem
fased by it. They don't seem bothered by
it at all. Indigo, I'll show them what
these bloody women have done and they
don't seem Yeah. at all phased by it. They're
they don't seem that bothered. They're
not taken back by it. It's just quite
strange, isn't it?
[ __ ] stop dismissing my struggles. [ __ ] you. You know,
that should be my new name. Peter Belly Struggles. Yeah. Yeah, man.
Like I said, I'll be out tomorrow or Saturday.
Can't even be [ __ ] bro.
Really can't even be [ __ ]
There you go. Yeah. Yeah,
Oh, I didn't know he was the one snapped. Yeah. Heat.
Hello, Greg. I had a piggy breakfast.
I had lots of piggies this morning.
Yeah, I like a singer burger. I do like
a singer burger. That's my favorite.
But sometimes I'll just get a um 10 piece bucket
and have that without uh I don't like
KFC's chips. I don't like their wings either.
One second. My friends um my friends call me