[ __ ] hell, man.
Where is the Ferrar?
He's going quiet, is he?
First and for Hey,
this is for
I little purple avatar
and you can start talking and stuff. Oh man.
I'm waiting for Joseph Ferrar. Where's he gone?
No, I don't. I'm having curry for lunch today.
Yeah, curry. I like curry.
She broke up with someone.
Did they break up with her or did she
break up with them? Lovely.
That's a good thing though, isn't it,
Grezy? Nothing lasts forever.
Yeah, they deserve that.
Yeah, that's good.
Well, to be fair, she Was it a man? Was
it a man or a woman?
It was a man, wasn't it? Was it a man?
If it's a man, they she she If it was a
man, then yeah, she probably broke up
with him. If it's a woman, then it's
always a woman that breaks up with a man.
But if it's a man, then yeah, she
probably dumped him. That's what
normally happens. The men don't dump the
women. The women dumped the men. Yeah.
Well, karma hasn't got that [ __ ] back in
America yet, but um I'm sure it will do. Yeah.
I'm sick of the these people giving me
advice, Grezy. Right. They tell me to
use the bloody dating apps and I can't
even get a match, Grezy. And they said,
"Oh, go out and meet women. They're not
all they're not all the same." And then
when you go and try to speak to a woman,
all they say is that they've got bloody
boyfriends or they're not interested. Grievy,
year after year after [ __ ] year, you
know, they give you the same advice and
nothing ever changes.
I should be settled down now. You know,
I was thinking about this when I was
having my piggies.
When I was having my piggies earlier,
I like I should be settled down now. I
do. I I don't have the energy to come
out every day approaching Grezy. I'm 28
years of [ __ ] age, you know? I
shouldn't keep having to do this [ __ ]
I'm [ __ ] sick of it, you know?
I got the dentist tomorrow, Grevy.
Yeah. Managed to get an appointment.
I've had enough of it, Greavves. I've
had enough of it.
I've had enough of it, Grezy.
They say they're not all the bloody
same, but every time you go out, they
say the same thing. They've got the same mannerisms.
What's the chances, Grezy? They're all
the bloody same.
And that and that's my favorite word. Bloody.
That's why I use it a lot. I'm going to
[ __ ] had enough of it.
Having to keep going out spending money
just to hear about these [ __ ]
boyfriends don't exist. [ __ ] that. Yeah.
Think of it though, Grezy. It is It is
pretty [ __ ] up, is it?
you know, just to be able to get a date,
let alone a sex life, you have to go
through all of that [ __ ] approaching,
dealing with their [ __ ] dealing
with their games. I don't think it's
spoke about enough. Obviously, it is the
way it is, of course, and it's never
going to change. We get that, but I
don't think it's spoke about enough, Greasy,
cuz it isn't normal. It's the way it is,
but it's not normal, you know? That's
that is not [ __ ] normal, bro. I mean,
we can we can both agree on that. You
know, it's [ __ ] disgusting. The past
two times I went out, I made great
amounts of effort and ain't had a date.
I haven't had a date since April. It's bloody disgusting, you know?
It's bloody disgusting.
I don't I don't have the energy for it
anymore, bro. I ain't going out
approaching every day. I don't have the
energy for it.
It's like you have to get into a toxic
war zone just to be able to get a date
with someone just to get something so normal.
Do you agree with what I'm saying?
Right, Grevy? Obviously, it's never
going to change, but you know, it's okay
to talk about it once in a while. I'm
not pissed off. I'm not depressed. I
have to make jokes about it, bro.
Otherwise, if you don't laugh about it,
you cry. I'm not I'm not pissed off,
believe it or not. I'm I'm all right.
But it is [ __ ] up, you know. No wing
on my end, but you know, it is [ __ ]
It is ridiculous, isn't it?
Not to mention how many times you how
much you spend when you go out. It's
[ __ ] mental, bro. So anyways,
I'll be giving them the benefit of the
doubt again on Saturday. So
we'll see if there's any different women about.
Let's see if we can see what nonslegs is
finally talking about cuz he tried
saying that we don't know all women and
all women aren't the same. So okay,
we'll go out Saturday as well. See what
the score is.
But yeah, it is ridiculous. It is very very ridiculous.
This guy on Instagram was like, "Oh, he
looks Max." I said, "Bro, I look Max."
I've looked Max many times.
It doesn't um don't make a difference. Yeah.
Yeah, man. [ __ ] madness.
It's [ __ ] in it.
Yeah. I keep messing with people on
[ __ ] saying I've had enough. I'm at
my bloody witch end with it all. [ __ ]
just had enough.
I have been saying that to them. Just
had enough of it all.
You know, no one's bloody interested.
But seriously, bro, like it's it is
[ __ ] up really.
All it is is mind games and [ __ ] and
toxicness just to try and get a [ __ ]
date. I don't know why this is not spoke about more,
you know. And again, I'm not winging. I
don't I I know it's never going to
change and whatever, but it is [ __ ]
up, bro. It is [ __ ] up. There's a
difference between talking about it and
then being depressed about it. Like the
last time it was depressing, bro, for 2 weeks, right?
It was um
I was [ __ ] depressed, bro.
No, I'm all right, man.
Sleeping sorted out.
I still go out and have breakfast, whatnot. Um,
you know, it is what it is, bro. Only
time I stay in bed is cuz I'm generally
[ __ ] tired, bro.
That I think it's because like I said,
last time I went out, I got the 10
numbers and didn't get a date. I was
like, "Oh, yeah, there's no hope now."
Yeah, there's no hope now.
So, every time I go out, it's like, "Oh,
well, we're just going out cuz it's
something to do."
See what I mean? Ruy,
if you can look Max and get 10 numbers
um and not get a date, it doesn't look
good, does it?
used to be getting dates every [ __ ] week. So,
um since then, but it's just Yeah. Yeah.
Is what it is. It is [ __ ] up though.
It's crazy. I agree with you.
But people I I was saying to this woman,
well, this transgender in Scotland, Greasy,
how much longer is this [ __ ] going to
keep going on for?
Cuz you give you say the same [ __ ] every
year. Oh, you meet someone. Oh, no, no,
no. You're meeting the wrong people. But
how much longer is this going to go on
for? Just just a question
since we're talking about it, you know.
Just toxicness. Loads of money spent
just in order to get a date.
But people on Reddit, oh no, you you go
on dating apps, you get sex. They say,
"You go on dating apps and you get
[ __ ] sex. [ __ ] hell. [ __ ] [ __ ] sex, you know.
You go on dating apps, mate, and you get sex.
You know, I just want to find someone
now and have a baby, Grezy.
Don't give a [ __ ] about the [ __ ] I
just want to want huggles.
Huggles and nutrients. That's literally
all I want, you know.
But nope, that's too much to ask. Yeah.
What do you think, G? Do you think I'll
ever meet anyone else? Nah.
It's very, very unlikely, lad.
Do you remember that day? Yeah. When I
went out approaching all day, I started
in East London, went to central London,
West London, done the whole of Maiden
Head, done the whole of Reen, and then
come back at like 10:00 at night.
Oh, I was I was [ __ ] by the end of the
day, Gre. But people on Reddit say it happens,
you know, bloody. I've had a bloody
enough of it.
Bloody enough of it. I have. Everyone's
got the same bloody attitude. It's so bloody toxic.
And don't forget, Grievy.
All right, Grez. Let me ask you this
question, right? And I want you to be
honest. No taking a piss. Do you agree
with me that they dismiss my struggles?
because I'll show them stuff that women
have done and they don't seem phased by
it. They're like, "Oh, well, I mean, I'm
asking you an honest if if you agree,
you agree. If you don't, you don't." I I
feel like they do they do for the most
part dismiss my struggles
cuz they don't really have a an opinion
or a say on it. They they just don't
seem bothered. They don't seem shocked or that
they do because Well,
where is it? Here's the thing.
I need to go to different places. I've
been all over the country. Anyway, well,
that's this Scottish transgender who I
speak to who messaged me when the whole
Twitter thing was going on. She was
like, she was um
she was um she said, "Oh, well, women
are not going to give their numbers
because they feel pressured." But I was
like, "But it's not about people not
giving their number. That's not what the
whole thing is about. Why are you
talking about that?" I mean, that's not
what the the problem is, is it
Greavvesy? Cuz when was the last time we
went out and we didn't get numbers? It's
it will never happen. You can never go
out. Well, don't know about anyone else.
I can't go out and not get numbers. It's impossible.
You know, it would never happen. Never,
ever, ever happen.
So, that's not the what the problem is.
It's not about numbers. It's about when
you get their numbers, they lead your
ass on and play games. That's what the
that's what the main [ __ ] problem is,
that, you know. Yeah.
Oh, really? Indigo. Well, what about
Well, what about when I went approaching
in Brighton on the beach?
What about then? What about when I went
to Manchester 10 times?
What about when I went to Liverpool?
What about when I went to Wales three
times? What about when I went to
Sheffield three times? What about when I
went to Nottingham four times? Should we
go on or or not? Should we keep going? I
can go all day if you want, mate. I
don't give a [ __ ] You know,
we can keep going, mate. We keep [ __ ] going.
You know what I like?
Me and G are very similar.
It's not about London.
It's about the whole of [ __ ] England.
This duck up country.
What about Scotland?
But yeah, they do they dismiss your struggles because
they don't um
they don't seem to be phased by what
they do. Do you understand Greg?
It is dismissive because
they would be like, "Oh, what the [ __ ]
That's weird. Why are they giving their
number and then just be speechless?
That's what somebody that wouldn't
dismiss your struggles would would be
like. But they do they do dismiss them,
which is strange. It is weird, you know.
It's [ __ ] up, bro. All right.
Well, obviously got t.
Maybe I'll do a little dating video.
I don't know.
Where the [ __ ] is Joseph Ferrar?
I [ __ ] need him. Right.
I've had a bloody enough
these [ __ ] women Grey bloody stuck up had enough.
Well, it looks like you're never going
to be an uncley
to baby Peter.
You could be the baby's uncle.
You could have been the baby's uncle. Grey,
how do you feel about that, boss?
You could be his uncle.
What do you mean?
You can't say that about bumping.
Why? Why is a baby?
You could be his little uncle.
What's your problem? Why
did you say E to the Bubba?
But you don't mind like you But you like King. H.
So why do you like King then? H.
Yeah, they all should be fine.
And it's not that we need women. We no
one needs women. So we not want women.
It's not about wanting women. We don't
want women. We just need them because the nutrients.
Isn't that right, G? The nutrients. [snorts]
the nutrients and uh
it's the nutrients, isn't it? Grezy.
Yeah, it's the nutrients. Yep.
Oh gosh. I have a chicken curry for tea today. e.
Yeah, mommy's cooking me chicken curry. Can't wait.
Oh, [ __ ] sake. Remember Grey breicles.
I've never heard somebody call breasticles. [ __ ] breasticles. That's mad.
Will I beat someone Saturday then? Grevy
hopefully. Is it?
What do you think Greavvesy? Hopefully
I'll meet someone on Saturday. Fingers crossed. Hopefully you
need my vitamins.
So what if I if I can't find something
then greasy? How am I going to get my vitamins?
So am I just going to die then?
Can't believe I don't have a date.
[ __ ] fed up with this [ __ ]
I tried so hard the last two times I went out.
Crazy. [ __ ] had enough of it. Yeah.
Remember, Grezy, Peter B can't get
attached anymore cuz he's already found his mama. >> [laughter]
>> You [ __ ] [ __ ] mock me, don't you?
You [ __ ] love [ __ ] mocking me.
You mock me, don't you? You take the
piss out of me. I don't know why when
I'm the only one in here, but that provides content.
Sig not Peter Belly's mama. Do you remember Grezy?
Why did you take the piss out of me?
Where's Joseph for all?
I need to make some babies
so I can make more so I can get more
money from the government.
Yeah, I messaged people on Reddit saying,
"How do you get a bloody girlfriend?
Dating apps don't work." And then when
you approach them and none of them were bloody interested
and they don't reply back. I said,
"You've been lying to us for [ __ ] years.
I remember. Yeah. When I met USA,
right? Um and that all thing happened. I
was speaking to this guy on Reddit, bro.
And he said to me, this is what he said
to me, Grezy. He said to me that don't worry.
He said to me this. Yeah.
He said, "Don't worry, other girls will want you."
And sometimes I message him, but he
never opens my messages. And I say, "Oh,
you bloody liar. You said every you said
other women would want me." 3 years
later, you [ __ ] liar. I message him
and say, "We've got a bone. I've got a
bone to pick with you. You know, you
told me other people would want me
and I'm still single, you [ __ ] liar."
He's on Reddit.
You said that I'm good-looking
and other people would want me [ __ ] liar.
Other guys do it.
Watch out for the other guys.
Isn't that right? Griev the other guys
do it. Watch out for the other guys.
Yeah, you need to be careful of the other guys.
Is that right, Greasy? Other guys do it, do they? [laughter]
Look at the other guys. Other guys do
it. I was so tempted to jump on the
Weather Spoon's table, bro, and start
singing it. Everybody,
other guys are out there doing it. Yeah,
I'm a lunatic, can't I? Greasy,
there's this boss track suit greasy
and it's £278.
I was thinking of buying it, but I
thought maybe I shouldn't buy it. Um, obviously
you you wasn't with me, so obviously I
have to run things by you first, don't I?
So, I didn't buy it because obviously I
couldn't uh run it by you cuz uh you um
you wasn't [ __ ] uh you wasn't there.
So, you wasn't there. So, I couldn't uh
I couldn't run it by you, could I?
So nice with the trainers now.
278. It was
okay with you. Grievously boss.
okay with you, boss?
No, not okay with me, boss. No, that's [laughter]
Is that coming from my financial advisor? Yeah. [laughter] Oh, okay. >> [laughter]
>> Is that coming? Is Is that coming from
my Is that coming from my financial advisor? Squeezy. Yeah. Okay.
Maybe next month then,
Grezy. Maybe next month.
Okay with you, boss. See, I'm I'm
listening to you
this time, Greg. I'm listening to you. See? Okay, [ __ ]
Hi, Joker. No, I'm not okay. I'm a bit
sad. I'm a bit down. Um, I've not had
I've not got a date scheduled for this
week, so I'm a bit down. I've had enough
of it, Joker. You know, people have been
telling me for years that I'm going to
meet someone and it's a load of
bollocks. It's a load of fake aid. You
know, d apps, they don't work. I can't
even get a bloody match, you know. But
when I go out and try to speak to women
and stuff, they've all got bloody
boyfriends. They're not bloody
interested. I've had enough of it. And
you know, when you get the numbers and
stuff, they just lead you on and play
games. So, no, I'm not okay. I'm a bit downed
thinking, you know, people have been
giving me the same old advice for years,
you know, and it's just the same old
[ __ ] with these bloody women every
single time. Going out, spending my
money, not being able to get a date, not
being able to make a baby, not being
able to get my vitamins. I've had enough
of it all.
So, I'm chilling out today playing some
Franklin. I'm having a nice cubby cooked
for me shortly. I'm going to have a
sleep. I'm going to wake up tomorrow.
I'm going to go to the dentist. And then
I'm going to go back home. And then I'm
going to have a shower. And I'm going to
get into my clothes. And I'm going to go
to sleep. And I'm going to wake up. And
I'm going to go out. Okay, boss.
Grooy. Okay, boss.
Yeah, I'm going to go to the dentist tomorrow.
Oh, I can't have a bath. I love baths,
but we don't have a bath, unfortunately.
Oh, I love baths. I remember when USA um
when Chinese Izzy licked my bum,
you know, when USA Izzy licked my bum.
She's so lucky I had a bath before going.
I can't believe she licked my bum.
I was going to stop her, but it felt so lovely.
Chinese Izzy licked my bum,
but uh it felt so nice. I couldn't tell
her to stop. Weezy, she's so lucky I had
a bath, you know.
She's so lucky I had a bath before
meeting her because she would have been
licking a load of [ __ ] [laughter]
It's not even funny.
Then she sucked my toddy.
Nope. I haven't found love yet, that
boy. And I'm pretty pissed off about it.
No one's bloody interested.
Nope. No one's bloody interested. And
I've had enough of it.
You know, when it's when is it going to
be my turn to have a baby Peter?
[ __ ] had enough of it, mate. He still
messages me and asks me to go to Manchester.
No, that boy. I got five numbers uh last
Saturday and two replied and then they
stopped replying and I'm a bit pissed
off now. That's two big nights out I've
had and not even a single [ __ ] date.
And I'm and I'm pissed off about it that
boy because where were these people
where are these people getting the idea
that I'm going to meet someone? This has
been going on for bloody years now. the
same old [ __ ] you know, going on dating
apps, not getting a match, approaching a
woman, them saying that they've got
boyfriends or they're not bloody
interested or they give me their numbers
and they leave me on. [laughter]
I've had enough.
I've had enough. I'm going to come off
the bloody internet now.
I'm at my bloody wits end with it all. [laughter] I'm sad.
You know, I've had a bloody enough of it.
You know, these people on [ __ ] Reddit
telling me I'm going to bloody meet
someone and stuff. They've all got bloody boyfriends.
Yeah, that's my favorite word. Bloody,
[snorts] you know,
[ __ ] B. No, it's not funny.
It's not funny. It's so bad. I'm I'm
talking to this woman from India. Yeah.
Yep. I'm talking to some some woman from
India now. Grezy, I said she can make me
some curry cuz I'm a curry muncher.
Yep. I'm speaking to some women.
I said we're going to have some bubbies
and stuff. We're going to have some lovely babies. Um
she said and then she tried saying, "Oh,
I'm dating someone." I was like, "What?
You're cheating on me?" "No, you're all mine. Nobody else's.
You remember that one, Grezy? Nobody else's.
Yep. That's how I get my vitamins. Since
USA is left me, Joker, I have to get
vitamins from the curbies. Now,
you know, cuz obviously I don't get the
booby milk anymore. It [ __ ] sucks,
you know. Oh, I thought someone
messaging me there.
I've had enough of it.
I've had enough of it. I've had enough
of it. I've had enough of it.
I've had a bloody enough of it all.
Oh, I don't give a [ __ ] if she was
pegging or not. I just like the boobies.
I don't give a [ __ ] about that,
you know? I just need to be kept warm and stuff.
They're all [ __ ]
When are you actually going to [ __ ] meet someone?
They're just all stuck up [ __ ] So,
I've had enough of it.
I am going to go out Saturday cuz I said
I'm going to go out Saturday. But do I
want to? Not really. But
we're going to Anyways,
I really don't want to, bro.
But I'm going to make do with this
haircut. It still looks kind of fresh. So, yeah.
It is bad, man.
But how many more years you have to keep
dealing with this bollocks for joker?
I've had a bloody enough of it.
I was going to buy a boss track suit,
but Grevy said that I couldn't.
And Greavves is my financial advisor, so
I have to run it by him.
You know how it is.
Yeah. 278 great British pounds. N
I can't believe she licked my bum.
I can't believe Jinky has he licked my
bum. That's really strange.
Why would he lick someone's backside?
Grezy, that's a bit rude, isn't it?
Licking someone's backside.
Well, I want I want this bloody curry shortly.
My dressing gown come by the way, Grezy.
I forgot. Oh, I didn't show you it, did I?
>> Oh, I feel like a champion. Oh. Oh,
my dressing gown. C. Hey,
I'm a boxer now.
Bam, bam, bam.
Do you like me, little boxer?
Do you like my little dressing gown?
Keeps me warm. Oh gosh.
How's the beard? Does it look all right, Grezy?
I'll be going out on uh Saturday. I'll
wash my hair and brush the beard. Should
be all right. Is it?
I'm not getting a haircut this week. About that.
Too bloody cold.
Yeah, I got it from uh Timu if you want
to get yourself one.
There's black, gray, and navy. I got the black one.
Yeah, I got the black one.
My mommy bought me My mommy bought it
for me. Actually, I didn't buy it myself.
Why is this bloody remote on?
Oh, here it is.
Would it be so nice to wear this
dressing gown and be able to snuggle up to someone, you know?
I can't even find someone. I'm I'm
[ __ ] sick of it. Indigo, they've all
got bloody boyfriends.
I've got a bone to pick with a lot of
people on that Reddit, you know, cuz
they lied to me. They told me that if I
went out approaching and stuff, I would
have found someone. But it was all a
load of lies. All a load of bollocks.
Wasn't it greasy? It was all a load of bollocks.
I've had enough of these bastards. You know,
I want a word with him. He keeps running
away. He keeps running away. He ran away
when I put my approaching videos up. He
had nothing to say to them, did he?
About is how you're acting around women,
you silly goose.
[ __ ] had enough of it, mate.
Grey, is it going to be different this
Saturday when I go out? Please tell me
it's going to be different this Saturday.
Please tell me it's going to be
different this Saturday for [ __ ] sake.
I've had I've had enough of it, mate. You know,
you never know till you Hi, that's right.
This this this Saturday
might be different. All the other Saturdays, right?
Nothing ever happened. Nothing ever
changes. But this Saturday, you never
know. You never never know, mate.
It could be different.
What's the chance today? Could someone
calculate the odds up for me?
What What are the chances?
I'd say pretty slim, though.
What would you say, Greasy? Pretty slim.
I'd say pretty [ __ ] slim, lad.
What would you say?
[ __ ] sake, man.
Don't worry. I'm still going to Wales,
Grezy. I haven't forgot, lad. I haven't forgot.
Okay with you, boss.
I was watching some WWE Royal Rumbles yesterday, Grezy.
Yeah, if I was watching some um
Yeah, that old ones 2010.
Yeah, those were the goat WWE days, eh? Remember
them ones grooves you did like back in 2010, 2011.
Those were the good ones.
Yeah, I'm having a nice curry today. A
nice chicken curry.
Do you remember Groovy? Peter Belly
stuck in his ways.
Peeweee stuck in his ways.
I'm not stuck in my ways. I just need a new mama. That's all.
[ __ ] a load of bollocks.
I said to Antman, "Why are women cunts?"
And he says, "Because they say they've
got a boyfriend when nine times out of
10 they don't."
They say they've got boyfriends when
nine times out of 10 they don't.
doing it. Well, today I'm chilling. I'm
getting a nice curry cooked for me, so that's fun. Yep.
A nice lovely curry cooked.
So, I'm looking forward to that. A bit
peck. [snorts] So yeah,
do you watch Shagger Greavves? >> [snorts]
>> Well, you don't watch him at all. Do you
know who he is? Yeah.
Oh, nice. Nice. I last time I had Nando
was about a month ago, I think. I like
to be honest, Joke. I like Pepes.
Peppies is just as good. Yep. Yeah. Yeah. Bye-bye. Hello.
Nando is overrated though, Joker.
Yeah, but it's overrated. That's why I
don't really go there anymore.
Nah, it's overrated, lad.
GBK, now we're [ __ ] talking.
Indian Brick Lane, now we're [ __ ] talking, lad.
Do you remember Fraser Joker? Freze.
Do you remember when me and Freys done
cocaine greasy and we couldn't stop laughing? [laughter]
Do you remember?
Well, I need to be up early on Saturday
cuz I'll be approaching all day.
I can't believe I'm having to do this
[ __ ] all over again just to find a
candidate for baby Peter. I've had
enough of it.
Yeah, he did. That's why I doxed him.
Do you remember when he set me up, Greezy?
Do you remember all that? when he set me up. [laughter]
We use you remember
It was funny, isn't it? >> Yeah.
How much money did you save this month? Uh, Grezy,
I was able to save 800.
I done a lot this month as well.
I got the GS. I went out. Went to a restaurant. Yeah.
Yeah. I done good, bro.
Obviously, the football bet win the
football win helped. Oh, [ __ ]
Oh, gosh darn it, Grezy. You're so bad
with them bloody takeaways. What have I
told you about them?
Yep. I was just about I was going to buy
a tracksuit, but Grezy said, "You've
already done your monthly clothe money
this month." Yep. I had to run it by my financial advisor.
Oh, you're so bad, Grezy.
you and them bloody takeaways, you know.
Oh, I had sausages earlier. I I had
sausages, bacon, and egg
and mushroomies. I'm having a curry
soon. Gosh, I can't wait. Yeah.
So, if I didn't get the gms and that, I
would have been able to save over a
thousand. But obviously, Yep.
Virgin boy wants he's trying to get my
[ __ ] money stopped. Trying to get my
[ __ ] money stopped. What? For driving
more than you for wearing designer
clothes? That's not a crime.
It's not a [ __ ] crime, mate.
I can't believe some after shave. Yeah,
there something after shave. Some
deodorant come with my trainers.
Actual deodorant came in my trainers.
That's mad, bro.
But uh the deodorant is nice.
Yeah, the deodorant is nice though, man.
It's It's Lynx Cherry. It's so [ __ ] nice. Yeah,
I just want to be cuddled.
We just want to be cuddled.
I can't believe [ __ ] Chinese Izzy
still asked me to go to Manchester.
asking me to go to [ __ ] Manchester.
I can't believe she licks my butt.
That is insane. Imagine I had a curry
before going there. Reezy, imagine that.
Yeah, she sucked my toodger.
I don't think we had sex.
I just think she sucked my toger. Yeah,
I don't eat vagina. That's disgusting.
I don't eat uh vaginas. That's gross.
Isn't that gross, Greasy?
Yuck. Don't know where they been.
You don't know where them fies have been. You know,
the only time I would do that, right, is
if I was Hi, virgin.
Uh, the only time I would do that is if
the person was a virgin and I was with
them for a while. Um, or
they uh Oh, I was like married to them.
Other than that, I wouldn't do it, bro.
I could just use my finger.
I could pleasure them with my little finger. My finger.
Look my finger. I've done it a few times
before with my finger.
I've done it a few times before.
In the nightclubs,
this finger has done a lot of fingering. Yeah.
One, two fingers.
You don't need to eat vagina. That's [ __ ] gross.
It's just as good with a finger.
Which one in the toilet? There's been so many.
I had somebody crying over their ex
whilst I was fingering them. I said
you're bloody mad.
I said you're crying over your ex whilst
I'm fingerling you, you bloody mad head.
I am concentrating on myself, Joker, but
I need to have a baby soon. Unfortunately,
imagine I had a baby, Grezy, and there were triplets.
And imagine there were triplets, Grezy.
Oh, imagine little triplets. Oh, bless.
What would you think about that, Grezy?
Little three and me. Oh, bless. Grezy,
do you remember what what's special
about the month April? Grezy, do you
remember what's special about that month every year? >> [laughter]
>> Do you know?
Do you know, Grezy?
That's when I met my mama.
I met my mama on her birthday.
Gozy, I met my mama on her birthday.
How cute is that?
It'll be three years since I met my mama.
Yeah, Sig not Peter Belly's mama. I
wonder who that account is, Grezy, that
keeps coming in mocking me.
It ain't [ __ ] um It ain't Joker.
There's no way it's Joker.
It's not Joker.
Nah, it's not Joker.
No way. I don't know who it is, bro.
Someone that's been watching for a very long time.
[clears throat] Yeah.
My dressing gown. Yeah. Thank you. Gosh. Uhoh.
Know the truth.
I'm going to have some curry. I'm going
to watch some WWE
and I'm probably going to go sleepy.
Is that okay with you, boss?
It feels like a Sunday today.
Okay with you, boss.
I like curry.
So when I go to Wales next week, Greezy
and I do this video um with a chicken
ticker. Um am I allowed to do some
approaches? Is that okay with you, boss?
Is it okay if I stay overnight?
Okay with you, boss.
You know, cuz it is obviously quite a
long way, you know, just to have that
and then come all the way back.
Obviously, I have to run it by you
first. I haven't been to the West
Country for, you know, quite a long time. So,
just want to make sure that's okay with you.
Okay with you, boss.
All right with you, Captain. [laughter]
Okay with you, Captain. Yeah,
thank you, Captain. [laughter]
Okay. Yeah, I got to find this kebab place.
Right, let's see about the hotels now.
Actually, if I'm going to go uh
right, I'm going to come back later.
Yeah, and see about these hotel and
that. All right.