Ah, welcome back, Rickster.
Welcome back to uh the dark side. This
is where you originally joined, you
know. So, you're just coming back to to
where you was before,
you know. Um, so you you like it. You
like it down here, son. You'll never
have to grow up, you know, if you stick
with the BRBs, you know.
You know what I'm saying? Just just
stick with the brothers. We'll look
after you. You don't need to go on some
[ __ ] virgins channel, mate. We We'll
look after you here, you know.
We'll keep you safe, you know. And if
anyone tries to talk [ __ ] about you,
Rickster, you know, we got your back.
I've got your back. You've got my back.
I've got your back. You've got my back,
you know. And that's absolutely fine,
you know, to have each other's backs,
you know, and that's what's great about
it. I can forgive and I can forget when
you're back on this channel now and this
is where you you originally started, you
know, with your with your with your
little blue avatar and stuff. No idea
why the avatar is brown now, Rickster.
You know, it's that's a bit strange. I
don't know if you made a new account or
what the story was, Vicki, but you're
back now. So, you know,
yeah, come back to where you where you
belong. You belong here, you know, not
on that [ __ ] virgin channel in the
[ __ ] shitty council bed [ __ ] lads.
You're better than that, son. Welcome back, son. You know,
everyone can welcome you back now, Ricky.
back here now with us. You're safe,
you know. You can have loads of
sleepovers and stuff, you know, and
that's absolutely fine. Yeah, that's absolutely okay. Oh gosh.
You knife? Gosh.
No, Ricky can come back on this channel now. You know
Where the [ __ ] are you, Joseph?
We've gone live a few times today,
waiting for your arrival, and you've
just kept [ __ ] us over.
I don't know what what the problem is,
but if you
talk [ __ ] behind my back one more time,
Ricky, I'm coming. And if you don't
believe I'm coming, you can ask Trevor
Dawson what happened to him. You know, I
traveled 5 hours and he wouldn't come
out. Everyone remembers that I went to Middlesbrough.
That's when I was getting some [ __ ]
some [ __ ] and stuff, you know.
So yeah, that's that. Oh, she wick.
What did you do? Oh gosh. Oh,
What is that?
These [ __ ] bro. One sec.
I can't carry on doing that voice, bro.
I'm too tired, man.
No, it's too tired. Oh, hey.
[ __ ] hell, man.
Oh [ __ ] that curry was lush.
Oh man, it was nice. Gosh, [snorts] darn it. >> [snorts]
>> Where's Joseph?
When Joseph's not on YouTube, I start
getting worried something's happened to him.
>> Yeah, I'm I'm I'm starting to get worried now. [laughter] >> [laughter]
[sighs and gasps]
>> Start it.
Hey, I'm all right.
How are you? I just uh lady made me a
delicious curry. I'm currently in bed
now, chilling, feeling a bit sad and stuff,
but I'll be all right, I'm sure.
Yeah, that Rickar Millington uh is
backing us up now, which is good. So,
everyone should cut Rickstar Millington
some slack. You know, he's he's more
than welcome back on this channel. You
know, he's doing the right thing. And um yeah, congratulations.
Uh come back to the dark side, you know,
where you belong. We'll treat you good.
The brothers will treat you good on this
channel. You'll like it on this channel.
You'll never have to grow up.
Isn't that right, Rickstar Millington?
You know, the the brothers will look
after you and stuff.
You know, the brothers will look after you,
won't you? You look after Ricky
Millington, won't you? But if you snake
me one more time, I'm going to come to
Hull and beat you up.
I'm going to come there and beat you up, mate. Yep.
And trust me, I don't [ __ ] around. Cuz I
went to Middlesbrough. Remember I went
to Middlesborough and called out Trevor
Dawson? It took me bloody five hours to
get up there. And I'm not [ __ ] around.
Yeah, he's he's all right. Yeah.
Yep. Well, Rick Stars a brave. Yeah,
he's all right now.
But if he snakes me again, I'm going to
go to him. Punch him up. I'm not [ __ ] around.
Did you see my video to Joseph? Joseph Farra.
I don't know where he is today. Joseph Farah.
Yep, that's right. Joseph. A Batman no Batman
Batman you know Ricky Milling Greasy the
one that I was doing videos to. Well,
he's kind of defending me now. So he
he's one of the brothers, you know. He's
welcome back on this channel, you know.
He's welcome back to the dark side. But
I said any more of your [ __ ] I'll be
coming for you, mate. And if you don't
believe me, right, if you don't believe
me, I went to uh Middlesbrough before.
It took me about 5 hours to get there to
call out that Trevor Dawson. I'm sure
you remember that, don't you, Greasy?
Yep. So don't [ __ ] around, you know,
because I'll be up there quicker than
you could say [ __ ] Jack Robinson,
son. You're more than welcome back on
this channel. You know, you can be one
of the brothers, you know.
Oh gosh darn it, Grezy.
I had a match on a dating app and I
thought she was she was legit, but then
she unmatched me. Greavvesy,
I'm going out on Saturday. I need to I
need to meet somebody and have a baby quickly,
Grey. I need to meet somebody and have a baby ASAP,
you know? That's what I need to do
just for the fun of it, Grezy. Then they
can't [ __ ] back chat and stuff. Give
me grief, you know? So, yep. I'll be
I'll be looking for a candidate on
Saturday. Oh gosh. Yeah,
we doing that cuz I've had enough.
Had enough of these bloody women.
Yeah. Hopefully I will.
Hopefully I will pull. Hopefully. Oh gosh.
Oh gosh darn it.
Oh gosh darn it. Hopefully I will. Right.
But seriously, I do need to um find someone.
This is getting depressing now. Greedy.
If not, then I'm just going to have to
start going to Holland and Barrett.
I need to go to Holland and Barrett for
the [ __ ] vitamins. Is it?
If I can't pull this week, I'll just go
Holland and Barrett.
Get some multivitamins. Yeah,
not a problem. Yeah.
Yeah. Because obviously the vitamins.
Oh, that that curry was lovely. Greasy.
Oh gosh. It was a lovely chicken uh curry. Yep.
I don't know why you were so easy left
me. Why would you want to leave leave a
bubba without milk and vitamins? I don't
know. Why? Does that make you does that
make you feel clever? Does that make you feel hard?
You know, leaving the bubin,
you know, how cruel is that?
I don't know enough, you know.
I haven't took my medication today.
So that's why I'm a bit mad.
I got the dentist tomorrow
and um yeah,
I just want to find a new mama.
Would I ever find a new mama?
No one's bloody interested. Had enough of it, you know.
I've had a bloody enough of this [ __ ] Greasy.
So, yeah. The next person I'm meeting,
I'm going to try to get them pregnant on purpose. Greasy,
is that okay with you, boss?
Is that okay with you, boss? Obviously,
I have to run it by you first.
I've had enough of this [ __ ] You know,
why is it not okay with you?
You know, why not?
Why is that not okay with you? Grea, >> huh?
No, I'm not a new meds. Why?
Did you ever like the inbetweeners, Greavvesy?
Did you like the inbetweeners on uh
No, I'm just I'm just a hyper bunny.
Yeah, I'm full of energy. I'm full of
love. That's all.
If I stopped coming on YouTube, you
would as well, wouldn't you, Greavvesy?
I'm your favorite.
What? No, he never stop talking.
No, you're talking bollocks. One sec.
Did you used to watch the inbetweeners?
Did you used to watch them
or you you didn't like in Between Us?
You didn't like the in between. This is you crazy.
I've just been watching old WWE matches.
You can sit there all day and watch
these old WWE matches. They're quite um
they're quite entertaining, aren't they,
Greg? Like Big Daddy V and Yeah.
Yeah. I watch like really really old WWE videos
like the Royal Rumble Greasy. They're
quite entertaining, aren't they? Yep.
Nah, it's not real.
It's fun to watch, sir, isn't it?
Greasy. Fun to watch.
I want a new mama. >> [laughter]
>> Do you remember my body met for fights
and then I put the lost content up?
You liked when I put that video up,
didn't you, Grezy? You was there
straight away, weren't you? You was
probably having your little tea of
biscuits and bam, you got a notification. [laughter] Yeah.
No. Come back, G. You don't leave me.
No. Come back.
Can't leave us.
Greavves. E. You can't leave us. It's a bit rude.
Yeah. So, I'll be out Saturday.
I can't really be bothered to be honest,
but I did say
that I was going to, did I? So,
[ __ ] sake, man.
It's always the same [ __ ] Every time
you go out, Steven Howard, you approach
and then by the Monday you spent4500.
It's always the same old [ __ ] you know.
[ __ ] [ __ ] There's loads of things to do.
There's loads of things to do, man.
Loads and loads and loads of things to do. It's boring.
It's expensive. It's the same old [ __ ]
It makes you lose even more hope. Well,
there's loads of things. swimming,
working, making money, walks.
There's loads of things you can do.
Travel to a new place.
Go to a restaurant you've never tried before.
Loads of things you can do, you know.
People tell me I'm going to meet someone
on uh they still tell me I'm going to
meet someone Steven Howard on Reddit.
They say my time will come.
I've been hearing that since [ __ ]
since I was a nipper. Mad see women.
Yes or what? Ros. Yep.
No one's bloody well interested. Steven Howard.
No one's bloody well interested. Are they?
I mean, my hair still looks good. So, I
am going to go out on Saturday. But then
after that, I probably won't be out
probably for weeks to be fair.
Yeah, probably for weeks.
cuz that means I'd have to get my
haircut again. And I'm not just going to
I won't be in a rush to get my haircut again.
My hair looks all right. My beard looks
all right. I'll brush it
so it doesn't look too bad.
But then obviously the week after Oh,
no. But I said I'm going to go with my
sister the week after.
Oh, [ __ ] sake.
All these women have the same bloody
attitude. Steven Howard,
they they they sit there and say that
these bloody women aren't the same, but
they've all got the bloody same
attitude, the same mannerisms. Jesus Christ.
[ __ ] hell. Can we meet someone on
Saturday that's not all the bloody same?
Yeah, my beard and hair looks fine.
I washed my hair and obviously my beard. Send it.
That's the level. Bloody hell.
They're all the bloody same.
These women are all the bloody same. Steven Howard,
none of bloody interested. I'm sick of it.
I'm going to do a correct score on
Saturday. I'm going to put£10 on a correct score.
So yeah, man. [snorts]
Wish me luck. I reckon I'm going to do it, bro.
Yeah, because they're all the same. They're NPCs.
[snorts] They're non-playing characters.
Yeah, I'm going to do a correct score, lad.
Wish me luck.
Yeah, I'm going to put 10 pound on a correct score.
No, it's not, mate, cuz it's going to come in.
I bet you I get it, mate.
I'm going to do 2-1.
I'm going to do a double. I'm going to
do a double 2-1.
Getting a lot back, lady.
Yeah, my beard looks nice like this. Oh, there's nothing. [clears throat]
>> [clears throat]
>> All right, captain.
You all right, Captain?
All right, captain.
That's our Greek people. Oh man.
One second. I'm speaking to someone.
Yeah, one second.
A nod legs. He needs to get [ __ ]
laid. [ __ ] virgin. Where's Jo? Steven Howard
Sorry about this, bro. Yeah. >> [sighs]