No, it's [ __ ] bad, man. Bad, man.
Put a drink anywhere, man.
>> I've done about 50 approaches. I got two
numbers. I'm tired as [ __ ] It's my first drink.
My first drink, guys. It's impossible.
>> [ __ ] hot, isn't it? [clears throat]
>> Oh, it's [ __ ] impossible, mate. It's
time to do that. [ __ ] I love 50
sober, you [ __ ] I thought we was only
going to do about 10.
I need a chill out.
That's what I need to [ __ ] chill out, brother.
It's bad. It's getting worse. I swear
it's getting worse. Let's see if that
person had me on S.
It's generally getting worse, bro.
Really bad. It's bad, bro. It's bad.
>> I done 50 approaches sober just to get
two numbers. It's disgusting, bro. The
amount of attitude I have to deal with
today. This my first drink, by the way.
My third sip of drinks.
It's bad, bro.
It's impossible in this country, bro.
It's disgusting. It is disgusting.
It's impossible, mate. Yeah.
A lot of games, a lot of [ __ ] to be
had today, mate. Um, and it's only 5:00.
Seems later, 5, but it's fine.
It's so bad.
It's my first Guinness as well.
So bad. So bad.
You think to yourself, who what kind of
person are you to keep dealing with this
[ __ ] over and over again?
At least they can't water the old
Guinness out, can they? Oh, no. This [ __ ]
madness, bro. Madness.
It's bad. It's bad. It really is bad.
It's not even funny. It's weird.
>> Yeah, I done I think I done about 40
approaches so to get one number. The
rest of it was just suck up this
attitude and games just as it always
will be here.
It will never change. Never change. Uh who is
your one number?
That is [ __ ]
should be coming in a bit. Wait till I flipping [laughter]
[ __ ] elbow, man. Madness.
People battle a [ __ ] tourist crime.
They're not even accepting [ __ ] first
aid. It's a madness.
Not even accepting first aids, mate. [ __ ]
>> It's impossible in this country. I'm
telling you, it's possible in this country.
>> Oh, [ __ ] reserve.
What do you face so [ __ ] deserve?
[ __ ] had enough of this [ __ ] mate.
Same attitude, is it? Same attitude.
>> Same attitude, mate.
>> Oh, guess what? It took me 40 approaches
to get one number. Yep. You're not even
kidding. 40 approaches to get one bastard number.
Sober as well. My first drink. Mad.
>> This is mad.
They will never change. Never. Oh,
he's going home now, bro. [ __ ] two
numbers, one st. Might as well [ __ ] off it.
Yeah. Anyways, [snorts] I'll be gone.
I'm gone and I'll be I'll be back.
>> Yeah. Anyways, I'm gone. Yeah. [ __ ]
I'll be back later
when I'm done.
How about this [ __ ] brother?
>> Well, I'll be back live later.