We're at five. We're at fire. I'm [ __ ] screaming.
>> I'm steing [ __ ]
Steven. Steaming. Steaming. I'm [ __ ] I
got five. I got five. We're at five to
be 8:00 yet.
How we doing? Good. Yeah. I think I got five
until 8. Yes.
Yes. Until 8:00.
Oh, he left me. I'm with my boy, bro.
with my boy, dude.
I'm not [ __ ] boy. My brother,
mate, I'm fat. I'm going to be sleeping
tomorrow cuz I'm fat.
I'm actually [ __ ] [ __ ] up.
Hey, he just said, "Hey, I'm out here."
They did it, mate. I got five numbers,
but I've approached about 100 people
today, mate. Not even exaggerating. I'm [ __ ]
I'm I've approached like [ __ ] 50 people sober. I'm fat.
>> It's only a joke, mate.
I'm actually [ __ ] man.
[ __ ] It's not funny. It's not funny,
though. It's not funny. [laughter]
Three. Of course we are. Of course we
are. Three mates. You got [ __ ]
Hey J. I approached 50 people over. None
were bloody interested. They've all got
bloody boyfriends. Same old [ __ ] Same
old [ __ ] in this country. I've [ __ ]
[ __ ] had enough of it. [ __ ] had
enough of it now. Over.
Come here, bro.
High five, man. High five.
High five. We got them bastards, don't we, man?
>> Huh? Yeah. Finishes. It It finishes at a
Yeah, man. We We're [ __ ] bro. Anyway,
we're [ __ ] drunk in it. We're [ __ ]
in it. We're [ __ ] mate. We're drunk anyways.
We're done, bro. Done.
Oh, mate. I want them [ __ ] over there,
mate. I want them [ __ ] over there.
I want them [ __ ] over there. But people
that we approach are next. That's the problem.
That's the problem you got.
>> I told you, mate. We get into this place,
>> we'll [ __ ] clear the whole place out.
We'll clear the whole place out,
man. We'll clear the whole place out.
We're [ __ ] in it. Hey, how many
poaches did you see me do today?
>> I [ __ ] not [ __ ] man.
>> Not [ __ ] man.
>> I love it, man. You're my boy, man. For
how many months? How many months? Six
months. We saw each other six months,
bro. About six months. Yeah.
All the way, man.
>> [ __ ] love it, bro.
>> I've been through a lot. Listen, it's
not good. It's not good.
>> When when you approach,
>> it's not good. It's not good. I went
through a lot of [ __ ] today, bro. A lot
of [ __ ] Before you met me, I [ __ ]
walked [ __ ] how many miles [ __ ]
talking to them [ __ ] They weren't
having none of it, mate. Man, listen.
Listen. They weren't having it at all, bro.
It's [ __ ] hard. It's [ __ ] hard,
mate. I done 50 sober. You believe that [ __ ] >> Yeah.
>> I'm [ __ ] bro.
>> You know what I mean, bro? [ __ ] mad.
I'm [ __ ] drunk. Hey, we're drunk. I'm drunk.
We don't [ __ ] I've got five numbers
in it. Five numbers, one subject.
>> [ __ ] I [ __ ] 100 [ __ ] people.
You [ __ ] can. It's not [ __ ] good
when you have to approach [ __ ]
>> five out of 100.
>> Five out of [ __ ] 100. And how many
And how many's going to meet me? What?
None. Probably. Maybe one.
>> There you go. Yeah, but you was doing it drunk.
>> Yeah, but you do the street then. It's
over. Go on. You do the sleep sober.
Yeah, there you go. You done? No, but
like who's doing it in the bar and [ __ ]
mate. When you do it sober, they're
[ __ ] stuck up as [ __ ]
I had to go dentistry as well. My
[ __ ] mouth's [ __ ]
mate. Oh, look them. Oh, [ __ ]
When they dance is nice.
>> Yeah. When they go
I don't care.
You think they
>> hopefully [laughter] hopefully they
listen. They don't matter. It's [ __ ] Hey, what's up?
out the spoons as well. It
>> Yeah, those
>> We're rinsing it out. We're rinsing it
>> We're going to rinse the [ __ ] the
whole place out.
>> Going to rinse the whole [ __ ] place out.
>> We're going to [ __ ] rinse it.
>> What about Oh, there's got to be one you like.
>> There's got to be someone you like, man.
>> I can't see. Can you see anything?
What about over there? Huh?
>> Do you like any of them? Yeah. You want
to go for a ride? >> Yeah.
Yeah. [ __ ] it.
We need to get to SL before they keep
each other. You know what I mean? Yeah.
Oh, them three there. There. Oh, them
three there, bro. there.
>> Yeah. I don't want that Scottish woman see me.
>> I don't care about the other two. I
>> I don't care the other two. [ __ ] the
>> Yeah. [ __ ] that.
>> They're just [laughter]
love it, mate. Love it. But I don't want
her in me cuz Okay. the way out. As soon
as they leave, the whole place is
downstairs. The whole place is >> Yeah.
I need another beer.
>> I need another [ __ ] beer.
>> Yeah. [ __ ] that. They [ __ ]
We're getting on it, bro. We're getting
[ __ ] on it, son. Let's go, man.
>> I was hoping for this place to get full. You see?
>> It will do. It will do.
>> You think so? >> 100%.
>> But that's Yeah. Yeah. That's Scottish women.
>> I don't want to [ __ ] this up, bro.
>> Can I get another Corona, please, Captain?
Thank you, Captain. That's what we need
to do, mate. That's how you bank people.
You call them C. They're not there anymore.
>> They all there. Look, they are there.
The second one, idiot. They're there,
mate. I can You're more drunk than me. >> Drink.
>> Oh, I didn't drink. I didn't drink. I
>> Who do you like? Let's go. This [ __ ] you up.
>> Oh man,
thank you. Captain,
>> love you, man.
>> Where am I from? Where do you think
my heritage or area? Heritage or area?
>> Heritage or area, brother? >> Yeah. Okay.
>> Where do you think is >> where
like you count? >> Where? >> Arab.
>> I'm Turkish. >> Turkish.
>> Qua. You're Indian. Yeah.
>> Where are you from? India.
>> Oh, no. No. No. Brother. I'm quarter Turkish. Turkish.
>> Quarter. Less. Half. Less. less. But I
live in East London, bro. You live?
>> I live in southeast.
>> Southeast. Where?
>> Yeah. You're up the road from me, bro.
>> Up the road, bro. There you go.
>> Opposite side, bro. There you go, man.
I'm Turkey, bro. My mom's side. Little
bit. So, there's four. There's half.
There's quarter. Less than half. It's a
beard in it. You figured a beard in it.
Love you, man. Love you, man. >> [laughter] >> £6103.
It's still cheap though. [ __ ] a beer.
I'll buy you a bit. You sure?
>> I'm trying to look on the if I can
extend their money.
>> Do you want a beer?
>> Of course I do. >> Okay.
Okay. Hey, can I get another coin,
please, boss, for my friends?
>> I'm okay. I could anytime.
>> We go way back. We go way. I'll be [laughter]
>> No, you're not. How much you have? 3450.
>> Nah, you're [ __ ] Look, wait, hold on.
You go, boy.
You been scared.
>> No, you're saying it. Is that all you have?
>> It's pay me the rent.
>> How much? >> 1,200.
>> That's all you have to pay mortgage then.
>> Your [ __ ] Yeah. Your [ __ ] this part. Thank you.
>> You're [ __ ] then. Yeah. Really? I
didn't, bro. I didn't know it was that
bad. I didn't know. I'm [ __ ] but I'm
not that [ __ ] [laughter]
>> You understand what I'm saying, mate?
>> That's why I put in your 3K. Do you see
what I mean?
>> Yeah. Yeah. I didn't know it was that
bad. I thought you had a couple of thousand. Yeah.
>> Yeah. It's all right, man.
>> I'm your boy, bro. We're friends till the end.
>> We'll always be friends.
>> The [ __ ] end.
Yeah, that's why you don't get escorts
in it. Cuz the money [laughter] listens
at the end of the [ __ ] night after drinking.
>> Guaranteed you get laid. [ __ ] 100%
bro. I mean,
we need to get them [ __ ] over there. >> Yeah,
>> obviously. But listen, you can do that,
but at the end of the night, you get the escal.
It's like porn, mate. It's like [ __ ] porn.
No, but seriously, I know what you're saying.
>> Never tried. I never tried.
>> I know what you're saying. It makes
sense. People approach women.
>> And I do. I do as well. But if I don't
get laid the whole I'm getting escort, I'm [ __ ]
That's it. Yeah.
>> So, who you looking at? Captain. Yeah.
They don't want to start it.
>> Oh, come on. They come. the corn and day.
>> Oh, there you go. Captain,
I need to run it by captain first.
I don't give a [ __ ] about this Yankee
[ __ ] I'm going to do it, though.
How they gone, Captain? You
>> sure? Captain,
>> you're done. You're good. You're good.
You're good, mate.
>> Okay, listen. I'm going to go and
approach that one over there. >> Okay.
>> Okay with you, boss. >> Okay.
>> No, no, no. Listen. Listen. I need to
run it by you first. Is that okay with you, boss? >> Yeah.
>> Which one are you?
>> I'm doing one on the left, mate. Yeah.
Do you want to do this? Listen. On the
boat. on the [ __ ] net. Anyone you like to
matter. [ __ ] it.
>> You can go there and be nice and say how
you doing in the the cable car.
>> I'm [ __ ] here on the left.
>> I'm here on the
>> something nice.
>> I'm here.
>> Wait, wait.
>> No, I'm going to talk to her. Yeah, obviously.
>> Which one do you want to talk to?
>> You can just go together and say, "How
you doing the cable part?
It's a really nice line.
>> I'm going to hit on her on the left.
>> Okay. Okay.
>> You could Who want to
>> on the right? Don't worry.
>> On the left. On the left.
>> Be nice about the >> Yeah. What's the
Are you sure that Scottish country? >> Just
I know. I know. She wants a big guy. She
wants big guy to come out.
>> They were interested in you. They would
they would let me know you
dance. They would they would come and
say hi. Do you understand?
>> We're in person.
>> [ __ ] them. Should we do them?
>> Yeah. Okay.
Got her number. I got her number.
>> Come here.
>> I tell everyone I got her number. I'm on
YouTube live. Tell them.
I got her number. I got her [ __ ]
I got her number, by the way.
>> What? We on six. I'm on six now. Come
on. You need to keep up with me, bro. Come on.
>> I could ask for the blondie one for this one,
>> but I'm not
I [laughter] prefer I prefer snoring straight away.
>> I do as well, mate, to be fair, but it's
a bit too early. It's a bit too early for that.
>> Yeah, maybe an hour or two.
I got a [ __ ] number, didn't I? Six.
About six. See, I didn't care about the
ones behind. It's the other one. I don't
want a Scottish one. [ __ ]
>> Where is she from?
>> The one behind us.
>> Which one?
>> America. America. America. America.
>> Get up there.
How many How many months has it been?
Six months. Six months. It's been six
months since I've seen my friend. Six months.
It's a bit too early for that boogie and [ __ ]
>> We need to do the [ __ ] Yeah, man.
I got another bus. One second. Yeah. Oh yeah.
>> So I told you by the time they kicked us
out, we got three numbers.
We're clearing the whole place up.
>> We're clearing the whole place up. [laughter]
I love it.
>> He's not feeling up.
>> We'll give it until 9:45.
What time is it? >> 8:30.
It's open until 3. But the point is not feeling right.
>> Yeah, obviously. But it's 24-hour
transport, isn't it? [ __ ]
>> come here on a Saturday. It's full.
>> Will be full Friday as well.
>> Look, I just want to trust you. So, I'm
going to stay here.
>> Yeah. I love you.
>> Otherwise, I would have
>> Fridays and Saturdays are the best. I'm perfect.
>> I got you come or
you stay here. Stay here. Man,
>> I'm [ __ ] [ __ ] six numbers. I'm
[ __ ] I've approached about 100 women
today. 100 women. 100 women. doctor.
>> Hey, I I approached about [ __ ] 100
women today, man. [ __ ] ain't a joke,
bro. I swear to God, bro. I'm not even joking.
I am fat, fat, fat, [laughter] bloody interesting,
candy. I had to deal with a lot of
attitude today. Attitude problems,
people not being interested. I've dealt
with a lot of bad attitude today, bro. I
swear to God. [ __ ]
A lot of bad attitude. A lot of the same
[ __ ] It will never change. It will
Well, it will never change, will it?
And you'll never change.
Timmy Vega and you'll never change. So,
>> you all right, Captain?
Where's Captain? I think he for a smoke.
I think Captain has gone for a smoke.
You all right, Captain?
I bought my friend a drink cuz you're my boy. Yeah.
>> You all right, Captain?
Can't stop saying it. All right, Captain.
Anyways, I'm gone. I'll be back later.
[ __ ] I'm I'm done. Done, mate. [ __ ] done. Yeah.
Tuesday. I'll be still boy.