I'm [ __ ] [ __ ]
the [ __ ] up there. I'm [ __ ]
[ __ ] so fast.
Need some McDonald's. I need some
>> I don't know how many I got. [ __ ] a lot. Oh, [ __ ] Hey, bro.
I got about six numbers.
What a [ __ ] day I've had, mate. It
was so bad. I ain't doing this [ __ ] again.
I'm not doing this [ __ ] again, bro. [ __ ]
that. They're too stuck up in this
country in me, though. Too stuck up.
They're too stuck up, mate.
I'm out. No, I'm going back home. I'm
[ __ ] I'm sick of this [ __ ] I have a
boyfriend. I'm not interested. I'm going
I'm going to bed. I'm tired as [ __ ]
>> What time is it? Almost 11.
>> You should get [ __ ] with it.
I got to get escort.
I get an escort, mate. Oh yeah.
What the [ __ ] [ __ ]
I might as [ __ ] go get [ __ ] it.
I'm [ __ ] steaming this.
I'm a [ __ ] Like every single time.
Yeah. I go get escorted. I'm a [ __ ]
I'm a [ __ ] That's what I'm saying. I'll
just get an escort at the end of the
night. I'm a bastard.
I was just straight getting escort. I'm
straight. I'm a bastard. That's what I
was saying. I'm a proper [ __ ]
I got several kids.
>> Well, it will never change, will it? So,
you'll never change.
>> But it will never change, will it? Sorry,
>> but it would never change, would it?
I keep saying I'm [ __ ] tired. I've
been out since [ __ ] 2 p.m. Don't get
I'm going bed, mate. That's why I'm going.
I'm going bed. Get [ __ ]
I'm just going to say [laughter]
[ __ ] knacking, man. I'm tired. I'm
[ __ ] going home.
I need some piggies on me. I got it.
>> [ __ ] are jaded, bro. Oh, tired.
>> It will never change, will it? Indigo. Okay,
you'll never change. [laughter]
>> Anyway, if I'm gone, I bet you're going
to get like [ __ ] tired.
Hey, 14. I got I think I got like six numbers,
but it was so bad today. The same old
[ __ ] Not interested. I have a
boyfriend. Just the same old [ __ ] Never
changes, does it? But >> yeah,
it would never would never change, would it?
>> [clears throat]
>> Yeah, I'm going to an escort now, bro.
[ __ ] this. This is the same old [ __ ]
falling. People saying they're not
interested before you finish a sentence.
It's just the same old same old here. Never changes.
Nothing ever changes in this [ __ ] country. So,
>> anyways, I'm [ __ ] out of here, man.
I'm going to bang an escort and
go on get some McDonald's and [ __ ] go
to bed cuz I'm tired as [ __ ] I think I spent about60
60 70 maybe.
>> No, I never spend that much, bro.
Yeah. 60 70.
I'm [ __ ] tired as [ __ ] I'm [ __ ]
going to the brass house. I've been out
since 3 p.m. I went to the dentist
earlier and I had to put up with this
[ __ ] [ __ ] I've got a boyfriend.
[ __ ] stuck up people. Get the [ __ ]
out of here. I'm in Thailand next week,
>> so [ __ ] it all. [ __ ] all of you [ __ ]
>> Escort time, [ __ ] Then
McDonald's, then bed. Done. They're nakis.
They're the [ __ ] nakis.
>> Yeah, I've done some approach to sober
earlier. I done about 50 sober, bro.
Same [ __ ] I have a boyfriend, not
interested, stuck up. It's just the same
old [ __ ] is it? It's same old England. Never changes.
What's there left to say about
What's there to say about England? That
it never changes.
It will never change. It will never
Just like what Ant-Man said.
Just like when Ant-Man's friend,
it will never change. Even his friend
went to Thailand in the end.
But it would never change, would it? So,
but anyways, I'm gone. Going to bang
this escort and then come back when I
have my phone with all the McDonald's. So, yay.