Hey, I'm back now. Get in there, man.
Well, England's the same old England. That's nice.
Oh my god, I'm [ __ ] tired as [ __ ]
I put my t-shirt on that [ __ ] tired.
Really tired. Don't want to talk.
I am [ __ ]
I am really [ __ ]
Where's the co just disappeared.
I really [ __ ]
[ __ ] ain't even funny but not [ __ ] nap.
Not even a joke, man. Not even a joke.
I am tired of [ __ ]
Where's the [ __ ] Where the [ __ ] are they?
Where the [ __ ] is that thing you got?
Uh, yeah. England's the same old England.
I don't know how I used to go out until
7:00 in the morning, but do that these
days. It was so tiring, bro. Doing them
[ __ ] god knows how many approaches today.
It was a workout. I swear. Seriously.
resting [ __ ] in it.
It's just the taste of what England is
and will always be here. Good old England. [clears throat]
Good old [clears throat] depressing England matey.
What can we say about it then?
Oh, that looks [ __ ] wank. I'm tired.
Seriously, I am
I didn't sleep since I come back from
the [ __ ] uh dentist. Uh nope. Oh, I'm
asking you bastards.
But yeah, it's just the same old [ __ ] in it.
And I used to do this 7:00 in the
morning. I must I would have thought of
that yet. Now,
now I'm [ __ ] 28. Makes me tired as
[ __ ] bro. So tired.
It makes me tired. The fact that I can't
even believe I used to do that [ __ ]
I was a mad bastard. I'm so mad.
What a mad der
five, but that's not the point, bro.
ain't the point of that. That is [ __ ]
vile. And you know that's that's the
word for it to be fair. The word is vile
cuz that's what it is. It's vile, bro.
Let's get some food on. Oh, mate.
You bastard. Bastard [ __ ]
Oh, you [ __ ] Oh [ __ ]
Make it [ __ ]
put on me.
Excuse me. [clears throat]
Yeah. I don't know, bro. I'm [ __ ] uh
pissed off, bro. Not pissed off. Not
pissed off. Pissed off the wrong way. Disappointed. Trust me. Oh man.
[ __ ] I need a McDonald's, man.
What is that? It's dusty, bro.
Yeah. England. The same old England.
Will never change. Nice to know. Good loading. Um,
I've had enough of this bollocks, brother.
Where are these burgers?
Lost McDonald's. Yeah, I got one, bro.
[ __ ] the [ __ ] out of her,
bro. Today was so bad, bro. I'll talk to
you about in a bit, bro.
So bad. So bad, bro. This country
honestly will never change. But all all jokes aside, um,
this all food, I'm [ __ ] tired.
I ain't stopped, bro. Since the dentist,
I [ __ ] stayed away for this [ __ ]
bro. [ __ ] bastard.
I just gave the [ __ ] 80 pound, bro. I
just [ __ ] banged the [ __ ] out of her,
bro. After [ __ ]
bro. This country bad. You ain't never
finding anyone here, bro. For real. For
real. I swear to God, bro. You You
[ __ ] didn't get lucky back in
the day. You ain't meeting anyone now,
bro. That's facts.
Dude, I'm [ __ ] starving, lad. The
thing is, yeah. All right. I tell you
what I done. Yeah. One sec, bro.
Second, bro. I need to dry this bed off.
[ __ ] it ain't dry properly, bro.
[ __ ] still damp. Need to eat the food
and go to bed. I'm tired, bro. [ __ ]
Right, let me tell you what happened. Yeah. Listen,
that's sexy as
good to catch up with my friend again,
bro. It's been months.
So went out, bro. Want to get his ch.
I went out. Yeah. No, I went off the street,
bro. I went out. Yeah. Listen, 14
Maxwell. Yeah. I went out, bro. I swear
to God. I approached 40 people to get
one number. This was on the street
sober. All I was doing is getting the
same attitude, the same [ __ ] over
and over and over and over again. And at
the end of the day, bro, like I don't
deal with this [ __ ] much anymore. This
was like a oneoff where I just go out
and [ __ ] them about. And it's like, bro,
you really to be putting up with this
[ __ ] like you you got something wrong
here, bro. Anyone that wants to keep
putting up with this [ __ ] over and over
and over and over again. Then I ended up getting one.
the amount of walking I had to do to get
one of them numbers. It is impossible in
this country, bro. I swear to God. I
swear down. And then the other people
were just like playing games and just
pretending they had boyfriends. The same
old England. It will never change here.
It will never change. It will never ever
change in this country. [gasps]
Um and you know, there was one I was
speaking to from America. Yeah. And she
said she just moved here. She's here for
3 years. I thought, "Okay, we're on to
something now." And then um
I was like, "Oh, I'll be a tour guy."
No, no, we'll go for something
sometimes. She's I'll take your number.
No, I was like, "Let me let me take your
number." She was like, "Oh, I I'll take
your number." I know. Let me take your
number. And then she's like, "I've got
to go." So, it's just like at the end of
the day, mate, I don't want to see any
of you people complaining anymore. You
know, if I ever find out that any of you
people have complained about men, right,
on any kind of social media, I'm going
to go for you, bro. I swear to God, I'm
going to [ __ ] go for you because it's
like, what's the whole fade [ __ ] bro? I
don't get the whole farade. I don't get
the whole [ __ ] You know what I
mean? It's just like, and bear in mind,
bro, this, you know, is is mental. It
really, really, really is mental.
You know, it's it's [ __ ] You got
Antland's friend [ __ ] moving to
Thailand now because of this [ __ ]
Anyone that respects themsel would do
the right thing, bro, and leave. Anyone
that's got any kind of respect for
themsel, bro, you know, and and you
know, I might do a video on this. Their
attitude is disgusting, bro. A lot of
these people, bro, that I approached,
um, their attitude is vile, mate. And at
the end of the day, like if I went out
like approaching and you know, recording
this [ __ ] um, right, you you still
wouldn't believe it, bro. So, there's no
point me recording it, bro. It's bad. It
was bad, bad, bad, bad, bad. And the
only one that was actually okayish, I
believe she actually did have a
boyfriend. Um, and then it got to it got
to a point where it's like, bro, I'm in
it too deep now. Like, I'm going to
approach anyone and everyone until I get
a number. And we could have been there
all day, bro. So, this is why I don't
This is why I don't do this [ __ ] bro.
Because it's too toxic. It's toxic as
[ __ ] It's so boring. It's toxic now.
You know, people need to just grow the
[ __ ] up. I'm tired of this [ __ ] now. You
know what I mean, bro? Um,
it's just it's just boring. It is honestly boring.
I got an Irish number and then she I
think she gave me a fake number, but I
got another I got six numbers, but it's
not the point. It doesn't matter, bro. Like uh
I'm I'm fed up with their [ __ ] bro.
And and another thing is FY Maxwell, I
was speaking to this one from Amsterdam
and I was bigging up her country, you
know, cuz I like Dutch people, right?
I'll say it to anyone. Then we was
talking and stuff. She said that she's
visiting. She's like, "Oh, um, yeah.
Have you got any recommendations?" So, I
took time out of my day to give this
woman recommend [ __ ] dations, which
we could still class it as the [ __ ]
West, right? And then I was like, "Oh,
like, let's exchange numbers." So, when
I'm in Amsterdam again, and she said,
"Oh, I can't exchange numbers. I've got
a boyfriend." And but if we see each
other again, we'll go for a drink. I was
like, "Are you like are you being funny,
bro?" Like, at the end of the day, I
didn't say nothing. I had no occasions
cuz I'm I'm thinking to myself, bro, I'm
too old for this [ __ ] now, bro. And you
know, at the end of the day when I was
getting this bus back, right? I was
getting my the bus back home and I'm
thinking I'm sat there waiting for the
bus, bro. And then I've got onto the
bus, I'm thinking, how the [ __ ] did I
used to do this [ __ ] until 8:00 in the
morning every single week religiously? I
shall never know, mate. I shall never
ever know. You know, at at the end of
the day, you know, hope is a is is is a
is a thing. And but the thing is, you
tell any of these women about themsel,
you're a bully. Do you understand, bro?
You're a bully. I quote, "Yeah, which is
what Ricky Mill I I should do a video
talking about this whole thing, bro.
What happened last week, what happened
today?" Um, their attitude is
disgusting. And then when you tell some
of these people about themselves that
needing about themselves, apparently
you're a way bully, bro. No, that's the
right thing to do, you know, with some
of these people. You know, their
attitudes are vile, bro. I swear to God,
bro, you don't know the amount of people
that I had to deal with today. Um,
so you will bump into someone, have a
drink with them, but you won't give your
number because you've got a makeelieve
boyfriend. I mean, you live in a [ __ ]
dipping country for crying out [ __ ] loud.
So people that deal with this [ __ ]
relentlessly have got no pride. They got
no respect for themselves. It's obvious, isn't it?
And the thing is their the thing is with
these people, right? Yeah. Their [ __ ]
is not made of cement, you know?
You know, their their [ __ ] they seem
to think that their [ __ ] is made of
cement, bro. you know, and and when you
go to Thailand, when you move to
Thailand, you realize it's not a big
thing, you know, getting sex. You get
sex when you want sex and whatever, you
know, it's not a big thing. But these
women, they seem to think they are the
[ __ ] you know, and and their [ __ ] is
made of gold. And that's an unbiased
opinion. This is all unbiased. This
isn't, this isn't white knight. This
isn't simp. This is literally um an unbiased opinion. So
it will never change will it? I guess
that's the that's the moral of the story
because you got to ask yourself 40 who
whoever the [ __ ] you are lad uh you know
you got to ask yourself this question is
that really forget what people say to
you right right about you're going to
meet someone they say to you that you're
going to meet someone
right then they and they continuously go
with that right and that's what they go
with bro but we all know that dating
apps don't work we all know that when
you try to speak to people, they're
stuck up. So that put puts an end to
that fairy tale, you know, that that
that's the way I see it, bro. You know,
they are stuck up. They are entitled. A
lot of them I I dealt with. I didn't say
anything because I could be bothered,
bro. I was trying to go on to the next
one, the next one, and the next one, the
next one, the next one, bro. But yeah,
they they they really do have attitude problems.
Um that's that, bro. It's not for me to
tell them about themselves, you know.
Hopefully someone will do that
eventually, but uh in the future. But um
they really really really think they're
the [ __ ] You know, it's even when I
told you about the one that said about
that guy last week, no one said nothing.
They are literally all stuck up in
London. Yes. 90% of women in London are
stuck up. Yes, the [ __ ] they are, bro.
And at the end of the day, if if I was
if this was not an unbiased uh audience,
I would happily show you it every day.
But obviously, we've we've we've been
through that before. I will never
provide content on this channel ever
again. So, yes, all women in London from
London are stuck up. Yes. And if you was
not unbiased, I would prove it.
100 million% they are. And again, I am
unbiased. I'm not an incel. I'm not a
stimp. I'm not a white knight. Someone
that's gone out and says and say it how
I see it,
you know. So yeah, they're either stuck
up or they're full of [ __ ]
Um so they're either stuck up their own
ass or they're completely full of [ __ ]
Um you know that's that's that's what it
is. Some of them just play games like
that American one. I mean it's they're
all sort of they either game plays or
they're stuck up. So, I mean, which one
do you want?
And it's what it is, bro. Like, that's that. Um,
and it will never change. So, [snorts]
that's that, bro. It took me 40
approaches today to get one number. My
back is [ __ ] My feet are [ __ ] You
know, I went to the dentist earlier,
you know, mad.
It's not worth it, is it? It's literally
40 max. It's not worth it, is it? To get
a partner. It's not worth it.
Disrespecting yourself and continuously
dealing with their [ __ ] It's not
worth it, is it? Nah. [ __ ] it, bro. It
ain't worth it, is it? Nah, it's not
worth it. You know, it really, really
ain't worth it.
It took me 40 approaches sober, mate, to
get one number. Yes, it did. Yeah, it
did. And she was Indian. Yeah,
literally. Yeah, it was bad, bro. It was
bad, bad, bad, bad bad bad. I got six
numbers in the end, but it's bad, bad,
bad, bad, bad. You know, I dealt with a
lot of them, so I know exactly how
they're like, bro.
And it was bad. Their attitude of it's
bad, bro. Like, if it wasn't an unbiased
audience, I would record it.
We got some food coming in a bit as well.
So 40 sober. So yeah, you can imagine
how [ __ ] I am.
I met some women from Scotland.
None of them all right, mate. They're [ __ ] [ __ ]
Again, I'm biased. I'm I am unbiased by
the way. Uh lovely Big Mac Ramsey, if
that's okay with you, boss.
Yep. If that's okay with you, boss.
So, he wasn't here for me to run it by you first.
Bro, it was so bad today. Oh my god.
It is so so bad. I mean I mean I should
I'm not surprised but it it it gets
worse and worse and worse and worse and
worse and worse and worse doesn't it today? Saturday
some [ __ ] um >> [snorts]
>> Yeah, I'm really really drunk. I haven't
I hadn't slept, you know. I hadn't
rested since the dentist. Um,
yeah. I haven't rested since since the dentist last.
I'm really tired, lad.
3:00 in the morning griev never know, mate.
I never know how I used to do it, bro.
I'd love to know how I used to do it, mate.
I'd love I could barely do it [ __ ]
twice a month now, mate.
I'm too [ __ ] I'm so [ __ ] mate. My
feet are [ __ ] as well.
I wish I could laugh at it, mate, but it
ain't even funny. It's [ __ ] weird.
I ain't done any bets, mate. Oh, my
[ __ ] back is [ __ ] mate. Oh,
that's the approach that is
my bet. Bro, I haven't bet since thingy.
What is this bastard? My food.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] It's so [ __ ] bad, bro.
You know when I'm saying this, bro. You
know when I'm saying this stuff, you
know I'm serious and it is [ __ ] bad. So bad.
So so so bad.
It's really really bad. [ __ ] 40 to get one.
It really does make you think, you know,
how how people in this country still
think it's possible. You know what I
mean? Grezy, it took 40 approaches to
get one number. And like sober
approaches that sober approaches. You're
not just going to go out one day and
meet someone that's got a different
attitude. They've all got the same
Literally, they've all they've all got
the same [ __ ] attitude.
And that's not moaning. That's just
someone giving their opinion on what
they deal with, bro. People are allowed
to have an opinion, you know? That's that
they're just they're just all the same, is it?
I don't think I've gone on a session as long as
this in a while, bro.
Can't remember we don't think I have.
There was this American I was speaking
to Grezy. You got to laugh at this. I
know what you're like. They said that
they've just moved there and I thought,
"Oh, okay. Well, they seem all right.
We're going somewhere now. We're getting
somewhere now." Person doesn't seem
stuck up. Just about to walk into their
uh flat, right? So, I said, "Oh, uh
yeah." She, "Oh, I'll take your number."
I said, "No, no, hold on." I said, "Give
me your number." Bear in mind, these
were all sober. I said, "Give me your
number." They're like, "No, no, I'll
take your number." I said, "No, it's
it's for me to take your number." And
then they just walked in. And I'm
thinking, we're still dealing with these
games with these people over and over
and over and over again, you know? And
it sounds funny. It does sound funny,
you know, to you because it would sound
funny to anyone, but it's it's [ __ ]
weird, bro. I was saying the same [ __ ]
to my friend. It's weird. It's not
normal. It's weird. You know,
if I ever catch these people gezy
moaning about men, right, in in on
social media, I'm going to go for them, bro.
I guarantee you these are the same
people that moan about men on social
media as well. That's the thing.
Where the [ __ ] is this [ __ ]
with this food, bro? I'm [ __ ] starving, man. These people,
well, they're never going to get reality
check, are they? Cuz they're [ __ ]
simps. But you get
I'm [ __ ] ill, bro. A lot of them
didn't even say anything, Grezy, to be
uh to be honest with you. A lot of them
didn't even say anything. [clears throat]
Contradicts everything people say, doesn't it?
contradicts everything people say, bro.
Where the [ __ ] is this [ __ ] I'm [ __ ] hungry, bro.
That's [ __ ] somewhere [ __ ] completely different.
So yeah, we'll never change, will it?
I can't believe Ant-Man's friends in
Thailand. Now he actually lives in
Thailand. That's how you know it's [ __ ]
That's how you know the thing is all
[ __ ] up, bro.
You think I was laughing about this
earlier, Grezy? No.
No, mate. It ain't funny. It's [ __ ] weird, bro.
[ __ ] is creepy as [ __ ]
No, bro. It's weird.
It's so [ __ ] so [ __ ] weird.
I wish I could actually laugh about it.
It's depressing, bro.
It's not funny. It's depressing as [ __ ]
This guy is somewhere completely different, bro. Cool.
But I I [ __ ] her this time. We
Yeah, I [ __ ] her this time.
not just a [clears throat] [ __ ] It
was fun. I went on top. [clears throat]
Well, I got these numbers anyways, but
I'll message them tomorrow. And to [ __ ]
with them, basically absolutely to [ __ ]
with these [ __ ]
That's what I [ __ ] say, mate.
Bad is [ __ ] bad. It is, bro.
And I was getting like I was getting
like [ __ ] deja vu to be fairy.
I was like, [ __ ] we've been doing this
for years, bro. [ __ ] years, man.
It's It's not normal, but it's weird as [ __ ]
I don't know where this guy is with my food, man.
Somewhere completely different. Yep. Stop that.
We got [ __ ]
>> [clears throat]
>> Five or six. I don't know. [ __ ] tired.
What a [ __ ] day I've had.
[ __ ] having a [ __ ]
[ __ ] me. One sec in one sec. Oh my god,
man. What a [ __ ] day.
>> You need to stop [ __ ] laughing at
this [ __ ] as well, Goozy. It's [ __ ] weird.
Stop laughing at Laugh at everything.
I don't know why he keeps doing that. It
happened last time.
>> It's [ __ ] isn't it? Yeah.
>> Yeah, it happened. It happened a few
times. It happened a few times. [laughter]
>> I'm sorry, brother.
>> It's okay. It's happened. I don't know
why it happens.
It happens, bro. Yeah.
That's it. Yeah, man. >> 92.
>> Yeah. Thank you, Captain. [laughter]
>> That's getting all mad.
>> I got some nackies.
Oh, the chippies are fresh. Oh god.
I agree with you. You need to stop
laughing at the women [ __ ] though. It's
not funny, bro.
It's not funny, bro. It isn't funny,
bro. And you know. Yeah. Honestly, I
laugh at everything.
It's [ __ ] depressing.
We can see the westernity in their eyes.
It's bad, isn't it? It really is bad.
Yeah. I banged the escort with you and I came and Here
we go. I came in the escort boozy
wanted to come in something for a change.
See how much stamina stamina I had.
I'm so boo.
I can't go on that without using an
escort in the end.
I'm so naughty.
I'm so [ __ ] naughty. Like
Where is it? Will never change, would Huh?
Would it ever change? Really? No.
We never change it. I got some nuggets
as well. We
don't all right for you, boss.
I got some nuggets.
I play with you, boss.
These women are [ __ ] [ __ ] up with Yeah. [ __ ] up. [clears throat]
I thought I was immature. That's the
thing with I actually thought I was immature.
Not compared to these guns.
We don't ever change
and you'll never change.
That's what man said to me.
Talking about yourself, no self
projection on my channel.
Why do you think this women [ __ ] is
funny when it's not?
But as I said, these are the same people
that were murk
[ __ ] [ __ ] man.
cuz it's repeating. We don't have cell
projectors on my channel. [clears throat] [snorts]
This country is [ __ ] disgusting, man.
This country is [ __ ] vile. It is.
It's not a fat country.
Mr. to me. I've just come back from a
night out, mate. Too many
too many [ __ ] up [ __ ] in this [ __ ] country.
Too many stuck up [ __ ]
Why was he laughing at the [ __ ] uh delivery man?
My bed's falling me. Wooy. So tired.
I'm so tired. Ruy, I need a snooze.
I'll wait until it's been made.
Really? These women are really shut up.
Really? Why are they so [ __ ] shut up
in this country?
They even stop up when they play games.
They're full of [ __ ] And I always
thought I was immature.
Mr. B, how do you get women in this country?
You used to know. You used to tell me
how you get women in this country. How
do you get women in this country? Mr. B.
How do you get women in this country,
Mr. Bab? It's [ __ ] weird, is that some [ __ ]
You remember that I found that keeps
[ __ ] I'll [ __ ] paint myself. I'll
paint myself [ __ ] black next time I go out.
I'll paint myself [ __ ] black next time. Yeah.
You remember that comes in and says,
"Oh, can't win decent money. You can't
get women. This life is [ __ ] Yeah. That
account that keeps coming in mocking me.
You've seen it in it. Yeah. >> Yeah.
Yeah. is going to mock me.
I need to I need to get my bed by Grezy,
but the bed's damp. [laughter]
I have to wrap in the dryer to be
I need to go to bed, but the [ __ ] bed's damp.
It's [ __ ] damp, lad.
I sure did. Candy, man.
What a [ __ ] night I had, bro. I had
to approach f I had to approach 40 women
sober just to get one number. They're
all [ __ ] stuck up and full of [ __ ]
Yeah. Oh, [ __ ] bro. It's getting worse
and worse and worse and worse and worse
in this country, bro. It's bad. It's
[ __ ] bad, bro.
So much [ __ ] And I always used to
think I was [ __ ] I was the immature one.
I'm going to try Thailand next week
anyways, bro. So, this won't be my
problem no more.
It won't be my [ __ ] problem no more,
mate. Won't be my problem no more.
I got an escort. Yeah, I banged the [ __ ]
out of her, bro.
Got blow up and [ __ ] her and came inside her.
Reminds me of my uh baby fetish. Is that right, Grezy?
Reminds me of my baby fetish. I've had
enough of this [ __ ] mate.
I'm gone next week anyways, bro. [ __ ] this.
[ __ ] this game of soldiers.
I mean, bec
any longer, I'd literally be saying
like, "Yeah, [ __ ] this game of soldiers.
That might be a [ __ ] u too old of a
saying for you, lad.
[ __ ] this B with soldiers.
Mr. B might know the saying
if he's an old school [ __ ]
I'm having to make this I need to make
this beding greasy, but it's [ __ ] damp.
It should be dry now.
[ __ ] bed in sty.
You know what I mean by st? I'm tired. I
want to go to bed. I'm so tired.
I am so [ __ ] knacked.
Wait a minute, mate. Oh, it's not even
funny. I'm so tired. Music. So tired.
The [ __ ] bed was damn.
You know what I mean? You see
nasty hangover tomorrow for what? [ __ ] nothing.
Just a load of bollocks.
To be fair though, the Irish the Irish
people seem a lot more friendlier
than uh the people who were from that
were from Ireland to be fair. But either
way, it's just
I've had enough of it, mate. I know.
Is that all right, Grezy?
Sorry, I didn't go live that much in the
club. I was a bit busy
with my uh mate. One second.
Wait, this bed. I'm going to bed. I'm so tired.
I'm [ __ ] tired.
I ain't [ __ ] putting up with this
[ __ ] anymore, mate. entire M. Anybody
agrees that I've not been I haven't been
to [ __ ] bed since the dentist.
I've been up since 6:00 in the [ __ ] morning, mate. Tired.
So tired, mate.
I'm going to drop dead in a minute.
I'm so tired. I can't even do the
buttons up. That's how tired I am.
6:00 in a bastard morning. I've been up
frozing these pumps all day. Yeah,
but it's okay. I'll just wait.
You'll you'll wait. Yes. Till it's been made.
I don't think it's been made. That's okay.
I'll just wait.
You wait. Yes. Until it's been made.
[ __ ] kill you.
I'll just wait until it's been made. Yeah.
That's what you're doing, mate. We're
waiting for that GTA [ __ ] six.
But Grezy, can I can I ask you to do
something, bro? Yeah, cuz obviously like
you're a long-term viewer and that. Stop
laughing at the women [ __ ] bro.
Stop laughing at the women [ __ ] bro.
It's not funny, bro. It really isn't
funny. It's [ __ ] depressing, mate.
And you're sat there laughing at it.
It's [ __ ] depressing. I don't know
how you can sit there and laugh at it.
Why do you laugh at it, bro? It's
[ __ ] depressing, bro.
Just just come back from the brothel,
mate. I'm just going to go sleep now. I'm tired.
Don't know where my other pillow slip
went, to be fair. I've been up since
6:00 in the morning. I'm tired. Almost
24 hours and I done a lot of walking.
Approaching nonstop. [ __ ] I'm tired.
I'm going bed. [ __ ] this.
Yeah. Steen out, man. It was [ __ ]
depressing today, lad. It was really
bad, bro. It was so bad. I might do a
video on it tomorrow. Maybe not. I don't
know. But it was depressing. 40
approaches to get one number. Sober.
That was It was sober. It's so bad, bro.
It will never change in this country.
You can't even People are just so stuck
up. You can't even [ __ ] even say
anything to anyone.
They're so stuck up, mate. It's [ __ ]
Yeah. Oh, I'm home now. Greasy. Lovely.
I won't I won't be getting out of bed
today. Put that fan on. Put the fan on. Yep.
I got six numbers. Yeah, but it took me
40 approaches sober to get one.
Yeah, I got six at the end. That's not
the point. It took me [ __ ] 40 to get
one. This is This is depressing, bro.
I'm out. I'm out of here next week. I can't wait.
Thailand, here I come, [ __ ]
I'll be living a dream. I'm not putting
up with this [ __ ] again, mate. Make
believe and [ __ ] and games. I ain't
dealing with this [ __ ] again.
I've got more respect for myself, Grezy.
I've got more pride for myself. Any man
that's willing to put themsel through
that [ __ ] if they're not a virgin is
mad. Like obviously today was a one-off
but they're mad, bro. They're they're [ __ ] mad.
They are mad to put themselves through
that if they're not a virgin. That is
They're [ __ ] bro. It ain't It
seriously ain't worth it. It honestly
ain't worth it, bro.
stuck up. Same attitude, same mannerisms.
Trust me, I know, bro. I've dealt with I
I probably today approached about 100 people.
Probably about 100 people, mate. I'm not
even joking, bro. We went ham, bro,
since like 100 p.m.
And to be honest with you, they pretty
much are all the same.
So there's Peter Betty giving them the
beneficiary of the doubt again as Timmy
calls them and they're all the [ __ ]
same stuck up or full of [ __ ] That's
that's it. There's nothing really much
to say about that birdie, you know.
It is weird, isn't it? It is weird.
Definitely definitely not funny. It's
What's the word?
Oh, I got a Snapchat as well.
She said, "Oh, I'm not going to give my
number, but I can add you on Instagram."
I said, "I don't have Instagram." I
tried to get her a number. She's like,
"Uh." I said, "Can I get your uh
Snapchat?" She said, "No."
I said, "Oh, can you add me on
Snapchat?" She said, "Yeah." So, I got a
Snapchat as well. Almost forgot about that.
Yeah, they're just um yeah,
not [snorts] interested in this country
in it. like Ant-Man said, uh, pretty much. Um,
[snorts] that's in it. And uh
the madness, eh,
I'll tell you how many numbers I've got. One sec.
Oh, I I met someone from Scotland. Her
name was Morgan Grievy, by the way. Her
name was Morgan. Yeah.
What do you think of that? One second.
Yeah, it is six numbers. Yeah,
it is. Yeah.
could have been seven.
Should have been seven, but Oh, it
Thailand next week. Get the [ __ ] in.
Can't wait to leave.
I can't wait to get out of here. Stephen
Hard, it's going to be less.
No more this [ __ ] again.
I'm happy, bro.
Yeah, I can't wait, Dad.
They're so stuck up, bro, in this
country. It's unbelievable.
So stuck up.
I don't know if this is anywhere else
but London, but
so so stuck up.
Of course I have, bro.
Of course I have.
No, it will never get as bad as here, bro.
It will never get as bad as there. Cuz
there you can actually get relationships.
You can actually get laid. Uh-uh.
There's country women there,
but you can still get laid there.
No, no, no. Ant-Man tells me that it's
it's not as good there as it was 10
years ago, but it's still better than
here. Cuz over there, you can still get
30y old women.
You can still get like 30 year old women and stuff.
You can still get women, bro. You can
still get women over there. Even if it's
harder, you can't get women here. That's the thing.
You can't even get a conversation out of
a woman here. Yeah. Yep.
Tired as [ __ ] man. Tired as [ __ ]
It was a depressing day out, but it was
a day out nonetheless. But it was a depressing one. stuck up.
They're so stuck up here, bro. Stuck up.
How I used to go out until 8:00 in the
morning. I shall never know.
I used to go out every week, sometimes
twice a week, until 8:00 in the morning doing this,
just getting the same old [ __ ] over and
over, year in, year out, year in, year
Yeah, he had like 300 pound.
Yeah, he had £300. Yeah.
How do you find a woman in this country?
You can't, can you? Nope.
Why can't you just meet someone normal?
It'd be so nice just to meet someone normal. No attitude, no [ __ ]
no mate. Billy boyfriend. Just someone that's normal.
Just a normal woman.
Nope. Can't happen.
It can't happen, can it? No.
Can't meet anyone normal. [ __ ] it.
Well, at least I'm back in the nestic.
[ __ ] depressing, mate. So depressing. Uh,
I don't know what what
Thailand's nowhere near as bad as here, bro.
Thailand's nowhere near as bad as here.
It was impossible, bro.
Why am I home so early early? Cuz I'm
fed up. Fed up with the [ __ ] bro.
Gave up after six numbers. I'm tired.
I've been up since 6:00 in the morning
and I'm sick of the [ __ ] with women.
So, I thought [ __ ] it, get an escort and go home.
Got six numbers anyway. So,
I don't like staying out till late late anymore. No point.
I like to be home by a certain time nowadays.
Yeah, it's toxic, bro.
Toxic and negative.
So, yeah, man. I'm home now.
I like to be in by
I like to be leaving by home by 11. Yeah. You know,
the boyfriend [ __ ] gets old after a
while, bro. Very, very old.
It gets real old, lad. Yeah. Yo, Grezy,
what a [ __ ] day I've had.
Isn't it right, Grezy?
It's the person, mate.
Why do I like to be home earlier now,
is it cuz I'm getting older?
Is it to them getting older?
I [ __ ] this escort Grezy. I came
inside her. Is that cute? Grezy.
Yeah, I banged. I was on top with the
I'm going to sleep.