All right, captain. Oh, [ __ ] >> [snorts] >> Captain.
got a lost football bet.
Yeah, man. Oh, we got seven numbers. I
miscalculated. It was actually seven numbers.
Yeah, seven numbers.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
I'm sick of this [ __ ] brother.
Oh [ __ ] man. Let me Yeah, man.
[ __ ] hell, bro. [ __ ] hell. Yeah.
So, we got seven.
Eight. If you cross the one that was fake.
So, we almost we almost got to 10.
Almost. Al almost.
But I just I just don't have the energy
nowadays to be fair. I need to go on my
system next week. Then I won't be out
until probably mid December. So,
yep. It's bad, bro. It's really bad.
You're always on a like downward spiral
trying to date in this country.
really is bad. It really really is bad.
It sucks, man.
Well, it will never change, will it? So,
>> you'll never change. So,
>> that's that.
Somehow Antman went out every week. [ __ ] that.
Uh, I like the peace and quiet, bro.
Nothing really bad happened yesterday.
It was just their attitude.
just their attitude. The only one that
didn't The only people that didn't have
attitude were like people from like
third world countries, India. You'll
never get someone from India give you
attitude. Would never happen.
Um but no, it was really bad. It was
bad. It was bad to be fair. But that was
a one-off. I won't be doing that for a
long time. So,
it is bad. It really, really is bad.
But this is what you would be dealing
with every single day if you wanted to
find a partner. Not worth it. Just not
worth it. Honest to God, it's not worth
just to find someone. It's not It's not
worth it, bro. You know, man must be
must we really
have low selfworth to want to put up
with that every day, mate. [ __ ] that.
It's not normal.
So that's that. Anyways, we got seven
numbers. I'll text them at 11 cuz that's
my lucky number and I got this football
bet and that's that.
So still not going to go out today. Even
if it wins, it's not about money. I can
go out whenever I want. I've got money. But yeah, um
to be fair, I didn't even spend that
much drinking yesterday. It was the
escort and then the football bet. So
about £300 spent, I think. So
really, really bad.
Some of these people, they do need
telling about themsel, but I wasn't
there to do that, bro. I can't be
bothered doing that. I'm not I wanted to
go out and actually have fun. Like, some
of them do. Not all of them, obviously,
but some of them generally generally do
need telling about themsel,
but you tell them about yourself. You b
you tell them about themselves. You're a
bully. Oh, man. You're a [ __ ] bully,
are you? Really? Really? [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
I don't know, bro, why this is
the way it is. Oh, and everyone's skid
now as well, so not a lot of people go
out in London. The clubbing scene is
dying down bad, bad, bad, bad.
Hopefully, it picks up again in mid December. Um,
mid December. Yeah.
And the escorts have attitude as well.
It's just a [ __ ] country, isn't it?
Really, it really, really is.
You know, the only thing you do is is
make money and leave. That's it, bro.
Make money and go. That's the only thing
you do in this country.
Um, so that [snorts]
>> yeah, seven numbers.
One of them gave me a fake number, so it
would have been eight, but seven.
So I don't know what uh
what people's options are now to be honest.
It is strange.
You can get banned for going somewhere
speaking to people, but that doesn't
make any sense. I mean, if you if you
went say you went to like a supermarket,
right, and and you went every day and
you started talking to people and then
they decided to ban you, then it would
make sense cuz obviously it's a
supermarket, bro. People don't want to
be bothered. But a [ __ ] club, a
[ __ ] a [ __ ] pub. You know what I'm
saying, bro? Like, it's
it's very very strange. Very very backwards [ __ ] country.
Do you understand what I mean, Grievous?
If you went to like a
if you went to like a a supermarket and
you started approaching people every day
and they decided to ban you, then I'd be
like, "Okay, well, yeah, it's a grocery
store. People don't want to be
bothered." But so what? You're banning
somebody from a a pub or a club for
trying to change their marital status.
I just I don't understand this country,
bro. There's a few things I just don't
understand about this backwards country
and I don't think I ever will to be honest. So
yeah, Grey a lot of people with attitude
yesterday. A lot of people with attitude.
See, this is the thing. You know, you
said that you you you you want to
partner Grezy. Yeah. You want to find
someone, but it's not uh it's not a uh
it's not important. But this is what I'm
trying to say to you. This is what you
would be dealing with trying to date
this [ __ ] And you'd have to do it
every day as well. [ __ ] upon
[ __ ] upon [ __ ] upon [ __ ]
you know, just to find someone. Really?
Really, bro? Nah, it's not worth it.
Honestly, honestly, it's not worth it, bro.
It's not worth it. It really And like I
said, I went out yesterday because it
was a one-off and I don't approach it
sober before I met um my friend, but
bro, it's not worth it because it's
toxic. It's negative, you know. Um
then this is what you'd be dealing with.
Like I said, it's okay if you're a
virgin. um you know or you really really
want kids or something like that. But
other than that, you're any man that
would be willing to deal with that every
day, it's got something wrong with them, bro.
Games, [ __ ] attitude, that's all it is.
So, and if you do, if you are lucky
enough to find someone that's different,
they've got a boyfriend and they
generally do. So, just Yeah,
it's bad. It really is really, really,
really bad, bro.
But don't forget, I done a lot sober
before meeting my friend. I was out all
day, bro. When I come back, I think I
didn't even sleep. I didn't even sleep.
So, I had a [ __ ] long day, bro. And yeah,
I met I approached one in the Weather
Spoon. She said that she was turning 17.
Bro, I literally walked away.
Maybe she was, but maybe she wasn't. But
I just walked away. I'm not g. But
either way, it's just always going to be
the same here.
So, always going to be the same.
Like I said, we'll try again mid
December when it picks up a bit more.
I'll be going out next week starting. We'll see.
I haven't had a date in months, months,
and months and months and months and months.
[ __ ] upon [ __ ] upon [ __ ]
So, what you going to do anyways, VZ?
What you going to do?
People might be more nicer your way. I
don't know. But
yeah, they were really stuck up. I
remember the first one I approached, she
just nodded her head. Didn't even look
at me. It's just straight dismissive. [snorts] Um,
and then I'm thinking when I'm
approaching someone in a pub that it's
me and it's the way that I look. So, I'm
thinking, okay, well, the next guy that
does it is obviously going to get
somewhere. Nope. Another guy approaches,
right? And then he gets the same thing
and it goes back to the same thing. It's
like, wait, this is a cost of living.
We're in a cost of living crisis. Yeah.
You told that man yesterday that that's
I've known this guy for two years. Um,
you know, I met him two years summer and
bro, the guy's got £300 in his account.
You know, a lot of people are poor in
this country. Most people are poor in
this country. So, it's weird how they
would go out and spend money, that
amount of money, right, just to tell
everyone that they've got boyfriends.
And it is because I've seen people other
people speak to people and they get the
same [ __ ] And I'm thinking, wait, what? Crazy, bro.
Going out now is like a luxury, bro.
It's not like something you could just
go and do now for various different
reasons. Maybe you're saving money.
Maybe um you just can't afford it, whatever.
It's so expensive. It's [ __ ] expensive, bro.
But I met a Scottish woman, so
the Irish women weren't too bad to be fair. Um,
but it's just, yeah,
I think they actually do have a
boyfriend. Greavves. I believe them.
Their phone. That's the only That's the
only people that they're in a
relationship with is their [ __ ] phone. So
So that's that. But I don't know if it
would be possible now. Even if you did
approach every day on the street, I
don't know, bro. Back then it was
back then it was about seven and one,
eight and one. Now, like I told you, I
don't know about 50, bro, before I got
one number on the street. And usually
it's not like that. Usually it is about
1 in 10, one in seven. Um,
that is insane. I was going to stop
until I got number as well. I weren't
going to stop, bro. I was in it too deep.
And I wore my new trainers. I had to
wipe them. I'm going to put them away um
in a bit. So,
and I just got an escort at the end.
I actually [ __ ] her this time. She
said, "Oh, if you come in my mouth, I'm
going to bite your dick." I said, "Oh,
this time you got lucky." Did I I want
sex this time, you know? I want sex this
time. I told my friend whenever I go out
drinking, I always go always get an
escort at the end of the night. It's just straight.
you won't I won't go on a night out
unless I get an escort at the end of the
night. I was like, should I go home and
wank? I was like, nah. Sex is just just
feels way better, doesn't it? So,
so I just [ __ ] basically. Yeah.
Yeah. [ __ ] bro.
Hopefully this football bet comes in in it. Then
I'll save that money and put towards something.
They should put you off Greezy. I told
you it's serious. You don't understand
how serious it is. I don't need to
record it, bro. I don't need to show
people anything because whatever I show
it gets dismissed. So, who am I trying
to prove? I'm not here to encourage you
or discourage you. I'm just telling you
my experiences. And it was [ __ ] vile
yesterday. That's what it was. Vile.
That's the only way to put it. Like, you
might find it funny, bro, but I don't
find it funny, bro. I really don't. I
think it's [ __ ] [ __ ] disgusting,
to be honest.
Oh, frankly got hit.
Um, and then the games and the [ __ ]
and the being passive aggressive, you
know, it's mad.
And then then they'll say, "Oh, they're
not looking." Or t. You do realize when
we're doing these approaches, we don't
even have any expectations.
But but you can barely get a combo out
of someone. And when you do, they give
attitude. It's what? You're just going
to randomly meet someone then? Well, you
you you're just going to go out, right,
and randomly come across someone that's different?
Cuz when you give up, right, you get
none of this I have a boyfriend [ __ ]
none of this, all of the negative things
that come with it as well, you just
Yeah, you might be a bit bored, but
you're stable, bro.
So, it's better in my opinion. It's not
worth it. Definitely definitely not
I'm not a virgin either. So, if I was a
virgin, it would be a different story. But nah, they clearly
they clearly are all the same. You know,
I don't know how many times you're going
to have to keep giving these people the
benefit of the doubt over and over and
over and over and over and over and over
again. You know what I mean? It's
[ __ ] insane, bro.
Maybe when you're 40 it will change.
Maybe when you're in your 40s. But
it will never change, bro. It will never change.
So that's that.
Like I said, how I used to deal with it
every week. Well, to be fair, there was
a time where I used to have to hold
myself in like punching someone. Um,
obviously I couldn't do that, but you
know what I mean? Like that's it.
Maybe I'll do a video on this. I don't know.
I don't know what what I'm doing, bro.
Just get it. No, no, no.
I don't know what you you can do, right?
I want to get a curry today, but I don't
think I can be bothered going to the restaurant.
I might go go to a restaurant, but I
don't know if I'm going to be traveling
that far, bro. I can't be [ __ ] with
it. I'm annoyed. I want to But I can go
to another one, I guess, which is just good.
Order it in maybe. Um,
I've got a feeling that football bet
ain't going to come in. Hoping it does, but
just have this feeling.
Not a problem at all. Um,
and the thing is, Greg, a lot of these
people were uh
are are average looking people.
Um, this is the thing. A lot of them are
average looking people.
So, they're not even like, and some of
them are quite older as well, which
obviously lowers the SMV. So,
it's mad. Like, it's not even like
they're like models cuz you don't get
model looking people in in in the UK
really, bro. They're just like a below
average, average, slightly above average. Um people looking people, you know, Yep. £130 bet, boss. Yes, sir.
Okay with you, boss.
Is that okay with you, boss?
I thought why not? Seven numbers. Nice
football bet for our buzz and yeah,
see what happens in it.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro. Bloody grievy.
That's That's the only What? What puts
you off then?
Trying to find someone. What is it? My experiences.
My experiences put you off.
Like what? Like tell me like what part
of my experiences put you off.
And the thing is they never grow up in
their head either.
Yeah. But it's not about too much effort
either though Greavvesy. It's not just
about but it's too much effort because
even when you put the effort in, you
still don't get anything but [ __ ]
There's nothing wrong with effort.
There's nothing There's nothing wrong
with putting effort into something if
you would get something out of it. The
problem is is that it's too much effort
and all you deal with is [ __ ] and
you still don't get anywhere. It's
ridiculous. Would you join Okay. Okay.
Let me ask you this question, right?
Would you join a gym if you couldn't
gain muscle and it wouldn't benefit your
mental health? You wouldn't because
there's no gain. So, it's all just
effort, but there's no gain.
It wouldn't it wouldn't be bad if they
said, "Listen, right, you can approach
50 people and you'll get dates or a
relationship or sex." So, okay, well,
we'll put the effort in. But the problem
is is even when you put the effort in,
and it's toxic as well. It's [ __ ]
That's another thing. It's very, very
toxic. I don't mind if they're like 18,
19 and they're immature cuz that's what
people that age are, but we're talking
people older than me, bro. They never
grow up in their head
ever. They never ever grow up in their
head. I had one from Amsterdam. Oh, I
don't exchange numbers because I've got
a boyfriend. But yet you saying you're
saying about how you're going to see me
somewhere and have a drink. Like
they all say exactly the same stuff.
Like, and again, I'm not a s. I'm not an
incel. I'm not a white knight. I'm just somebody
hawking through experiences when I go
out, bro. That's I don't give a [ __ ]
People allowed to voice their [ __ ]
opinions on this [ __ ]
Maybe I'll see you around.
They say a lot of the same stuff for
people that are [ __ ] different
though, don't they, Greasy? They They
say a lot of the same things for women
that are apparently not all the [ __ ]
same. I would be very worried if
somebody started acting the way that I [ __ ] did.
They they just have this tendency to all
act the same. It's strange, isn't it?
You say you're not looking for someone
and keep it moving. I don't understand why, you know.
But remember, Greavvesy, we will never
stand up to ourselves cuz if we stand up
for ourselves, we're bullying. Isn't
that right, Greavves? We're bullying.
I approached someone yesterday and they literally
gave me a thumbs up. Yeah. How rude is that?
But if I said something back, I'm
bullying. You don't understand the
double standards here, bro. Yeah. She
literally just gave me a thumbs up.
Bit rude, isn't it? You know, you
understand. Now you understand the double standards. You know,
it's bad, isn't it? It really, really is bad.
So, at the end of the day, it gives you
like when I do tell people about
themselves, I don't think it's the wrong
thing. I think it's just me verbally
putting people in their place. What do
you think? Because these little simps
and these white knights inflate their
egos, making them act like [ __ ] And
then when they come across Peter Belly,
I just put them down to the level
they're at, bro.
You know, nothing more.
I think that's, you know, that's that's
the right thing. Everyone needs to meet
a Peter belly once in their life, don't they, Greasy? Yeah.
right, this woman turned around and said,
"Ah, this sounds so bad." It is [ __ ]
bad. Um, I wish I could say something
that would shine light and bright
design, but what but it is what it is,
right? I do hope you find someone soon.
Well, I won't find someone soon.
Um, I won't find someone soon,
but yeah, thanks for your message anyways. Yeah. So,
depends how bad you want someone grievy.
I don't want someone that bad to
disrespect myself every day. So that's
that. Occasionally I'll do it when I'm
bored out of my head. Like every couple
of months I'm just bored and I've got
nothing to do and we'll see if England's
the same old England.
But really, bro, nah, you get [ __ ] You know,
another thing they don't tell you on the [ __ ] internet.
Yeah, I think I got seven numbers.
eight if eight if that one wasn't
[ __ ] fake. But it doesn't matter anyways.
But anyways, if one of these numbers
comes of it, then it was worth it, you
know. But knowing my history, it's very
very very unlikely that anything is is
going to come from one of these numbers.
You know, if they do, then you know that's that.
But if they don't, I won't be repeating
that in a hurry anytime soon.
Hey, well, I need to go with my sister
um after that then when I've done them
plans. Um yeah, I I ain't repeating that anytime soon.
And then people tell me that I ain't got patience.
One second. But I'm going to message
this uh someone that's just messaged me. Hold on. Yeah. Someone. Right.
Let me message some of these numbers now. Otherwise,
That's one number.
What was that number then?
The [ __ ] was her number now?
A number, bro.
I just lost. No. One sec. No number.
What was that?
No, no, no, no. One second.
What's her number now? Hold on.
That's what it was.
I forgot the cunt's [ __ ] name.
I forgot the cunt's name. That what it was.
Right. I messaged three numbers so far.
I don't want to message
um all of them just yet. I forgot her
name, bro. This was so many of them.
So, how many replies do you think we're
going to get? I don't think we're going
to get any, bro.
What do you think, boss?
be nice, but I don't think so.
I just have a bad feeling, bro. I don't
know why. I just do.
So, what are you saying, Greavves? You
know, I'm never going to find someone in
this country. Is that what you're saying?
Is that what you're [ __ ] saying, mate? Huh?
Is that what you're [ __ ] saying? Huh?
Are you taking a piss out of me, mate?
Are you being serious?
I'm going to message that question.
Are you taking a piss out of me when
you're saying that?
Guess what the Scottish woman's name is? [ __ ] Morgan.
Of course it would be.
Yeah. It wouldn't be any other name,
would it? Out of the million and other ones. No,
of course not.
Right. One second.
So that's one, two, three, four. It messaged
And we've got three more left. Yeah.
You know that USA is thing uh Gregy that
was generally bro one in a million.
I was thinking about this. You know
there's some things in life that that is
one in a million. So obviously
approaching her and you know her giving
her number and whatever that was one in
a million just like subleting a house
once in a lifetime. It's not one in a
million. There's certain things in life
that's once in a lifetime.
So I've messaged
four numbers three to go.
Oh and I got that Snapchat as well.
Couple of numbers to text £130 bet.
What more could you want, Boozy? What
[ __ ] more could you want, eh? Yeah. [ __ ] sake.
One of these [ __ ] better get back to
me. You know, I've had a bloody enough of this.
I asked my friend how did he get on with them numbers. £370. Yeah. Yeah.£370 quid.
Bring this cross.
It's a nice return. Don't forget I won
one last week as well. So be nice to win again.
Hopefully the bastard wins again, bro. Yeah.
Hopefully these uh one of these numbers get back.
I don't know what more you can do,
Greaves. You go out approaching you
looks Max. What more could you do? What
more can you actually [ __ ] do?
It's just bad. And it's really bad.
Disgusting, mate. Disgusting.
But we're just going to have to treat it
as what it is now, [snorts]
you know, cuz it will never change. So
yeah, we'll just treat it how it is now, I guess.
It will never change, will it?
And you'll never change.
That's that. That's what Ant-Man said to
me. He said, "I'll never change." Rudy,
it's nice. I've got somewhat of a life
now, you know. Always on the go, always doing things.
It is nice.
Need to get a haircut next week as well.
That's an extra expense. Yay.
That's so fun, isn't it? Yep.
Do you like my football bet? Stephen Howard,
do you like it? Yeah.
So, I didn't even spend that much on the
drinking. It was the escort and the
[ __ ] obviously the football bet.
Yeah. And obviously the football bet in it. So
I don't know how much suspect cuz I was
I was just I just stuck the beer
yesterday as well.
Did you notice that?
Hopefully we get another first halfer.
Hopefully we get another first half a man. You know,
that will be a lovely site. >> [sighs] >> Yep.
Yep. Hopefully this [ __ ] comes in, bro.
after the [ __ ] after that Friday ad mate.
Now, do you believe I'm not scared to approach Grievy?
You always knew I weren't scared to
approach, didn't you, Grievy?
Just waste of [ __ ] energy, in it. Yep.
21 hours ago.
You think my bet's going to come in? Steven Howard
[ __ ] will recover nicely.
Well, yeah, that's a lovely bet. The
return is not that good, so it better
[ __ ] come in. It is good, but I was
hoping it was going to be like over I
thought I was hoping it was going to be like £400.
I was [ __ ] hoping it was going to be £400, lad. Yeah.
If you keep ignoring me, I'm going to
spam your your page. And then she
deleted all of her pictures. So I I
turned around and said, I'm just going
to message all your friends. I'm going
to message your little mates.
I'm going to message your little mates. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm going to message our little mates.
That's cute, isn't it, Grezy? Yeah.
Message our little mates.
Oh, she blocked me. She saw that
straight away, didn't she?
She saw that straight away when I said
about messaging her friends.
These people are proper [ __ ] bro.
Greasy. They're proper [ __ ]
Well, like I said, I made plans and
that's that with thingy and then I'm
done for a month and a half and [ __ ]
Yeah, I said I'm going to message her
friends and she blocked me straight
away. Grezy [ __ ] ignorers.
Bloody ignorers, aren't they? Grezy. Yeah.
Yeah. I don't know what I'm going to eat later. Yep. [ __ ] cowards.
They are cowards, mate. Yeah.
Well, that's me done anyways after next
week for a month and a half. So,
England's the same old England. Nothing changes there. Yay.
Good old England.
I feel hung over even though I stuck to beer.
These numbers haven't replied back yet. Maybe they're
Maybe they're busy.
Maybe. Just maybe they're busy. Okay. Uh,
I don't know why they they they on
Instagram message you and then they just
turn into complete ignoring [ __ ]
and they just turn into complete and
utter ignoring [ __ ]
I don't get it, bro. Steven Howard, I
don't get it.
And they turn into complete and not ignoring [ __ ]
Where's Joseph Farra?
Where the [ __ ] is Joseph Farah?
How much did I spend including this
about 300 lb escorts [ __ ]
I might do a video about dating.
Okay with you, Grezy boss.
Is that okay with you, boss? If I do a
video on dating, Greavvesy.
Okay with you, boss.
I'm going to have to run it by you first.
Yeah, I've got about £1,300 left.
I've already done a football bet. I've
got £1,300 left. I know. Like
no, it's like £1,500 left.
Hopefully that's enough for the month.
Is it Grezy? Should be. Should be enough
for the month.
I think that's enough for the month. Grezy, 1500.
Well, that was a big night out and I go
on two of them a month. So,
well, I'm staying local next time I go
out cuz I'm going out with my sister. I
normally go far, but she doesn't want to go far. So,
yeah. Would it have to be, would it?
It will have to be enough. Yeah. Yep.
Yeah, I spent £300 escorts and drinking
and obviously this football bet with it.
It's £300 for the weekend. That's £300
weekend. That is
and I bought the gums as well. So, I'm
not doing too bad am I Greavvesy?
Really? I'm not doing too bad am I? Nah,
the bet was 130, the escort was 80. Then the drinking
and obviously uh I [ __ ] her as well.
She sucked it and I [ __ ]
she sucked it. I just [ __ ] her.
So, if you come in my mouth, I'm going
to bite your dick. I said, "Lucky for
you, I'm not coming in anyone's mouth
today. I want sex." So, yeah.
Nope. You have to use a condom. Don't
call it a Johnny. That's so cringe.
I hate that word. It's a condom, not a
Johnny. That's a [ __ ] cringe word.
I'm not getting into it anyways. So, yeah,
bit [ __ ] basically.
I didn't realize I had that much uh
stamina to be honest, we
depressing, isn't it? Really depressing.
Uh, it's [ __ ] [ __ ]
You like my little dating videos, don't you, Greasy?
How much do you have to last you the
month now, Grezy?
Yes. So, I didn't even spend that much drinking,
but I um
I didn't spend that much drinking, but I
spent um went on the bet and the escort
and that. So,
if this football bat comes in, it will be lush.
If not, then it won't be as lush.
[snorts] It look greasy. I need to get
my haircut as well, so
we could be in some problems.
in it breezy.
But I don't do bad for somebody that
doesn't work to be honest. I can still
go out and kind of like hold things and
stuff like whatever. But yeah,
you know what I mean. So bad.
What do you think? Do you think this
football bet's coming in?
Do you think this football bet's coming in delayed?
I'm hoping the [ __ ] cunt's coming in.
My friend had 300 pound to his name.
Mad, isn't it?£300 to his name. [ __ ] me.
That is crazy and it grizzy. [groaning] Yeah.
The boyfriend [ __ ] gets old after a
while, ain't it, Grezy? Very, very, very old.
It gets old after a while, don't it, bro?
The boyfriend [ __ ] What do you think?
I'm hoping it comes in this first half
to be fair.
What do you think, Indigo? Do you think
this football bet's going to win?
Do you think it's winning this football
bet or what?
It's on my community post. Yep.
Saw my community post.
This [ __ ] comes in. I'm look smacking
one more time and I'm trying one more
time. Bro, you going to get [ __ ] after that. Yeah.
Look at my football bet.
But I done
[ __ ] better win, bro.
Yeah, I'm going to put my 370 in my little box.
I'm putting my 370 in my little box for
a rainy day. Yeah,
Joseph Ferrar's gone. When's he coming back? Yeah,
I was going to put 60 on a double both
scar no draw, but then I thought let me
just put the 130 on the [ __ ] Yeah. Yep.
Hopefully it hits it.
Hopefully it hits. [snorts]
None of these numbers have replied back
to me yet. That's Wian. [sighs]
Got a couple more to message.
It's not a lot to me, matey.
So, yeah. I'm gone anyways. I'll be back
later. So, I've got some numbers to
message and whatnot. So, a bit