No, no, no, no.
Oh, [ __ ] hell.
What a load of old bollocks. Yeah.
Where's this guy? He's been gone for
over a week, man. I've been waiting for
him. He's bloody gone.
Where the [ __ ] has he gone, man?
Where the [ __ ] have you gone, Captain?
Where have you gone, Captain?
>> [clears throat]
>> I'm waiting for this food, bro. Yeah.
Had a little burger earlier.
Yep. I had a little burger earlier.
It was lush.
It was lush. It was last.
That's what it was. Her
Well, this person's gone quiet.
Yeah, this person's gone quiet, matey.
That's a bit concerning.
Yeah, that's a bit concerning.
They've gone bloody quiet.
What can you say? Okay.
Good old Good old Good old
Good Old England.
That's what you say. You say good old England.
What it is?
So they're not available.
We'll give them the beneficiary of the
doubt as as Timmy likes to call it. You
know, you know old good Tim where we
talks about giving things the
beneficiary of the doubt, you know.
Yeah. beneficiary of the [ __ ] doubt.
E [ __ ] out, bro.
Maybe they're at work or something.
They seem all right, but you know, don't
they [ __ ] all seem all right?
What's that even mean, bro? Don't Don't
they all [ __ ] just seem all right,
you know? Oh, they all
think Joseph Fra's gone on holiday, I reckon.
Yep, I think he's gone on [ __ ] holiday.
Still still waiting for him, mate. He's gone. Yeah.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Oh, [ __ ] a
I can't bloody afford that. Are you bloody mad?
I can't bloody afford these bloody
restaurants. Silly goose. Ow, my little
back. Killing me. Ow.
You silly face.
You're such a silly case. You are
madness in it. >> [laughter]
>> That makes me laugh. I was watching this
podcast. Yeah, these guys walking around. [laughter]
He's walking about Liverpool. That's
what people said that I'm like and like you know Honey.
>> Yeah, man. [laughter]
It's funny, is it? Yeah. Bloody quiet.
I'm bloody quiet.
Thought we was vibing and stuff. No,
but that skin virgin needs to stop
[ __ ] projecting his skintess on me.
He is the biggest skin punt going, matey.
Nice free thumbs up from yourself, mate.
I don't know what it is with people in
this bloody community. I really don't. I
really don't know what it is with these people.
just chilling, bro.
I was speaking to someone on Snapchat. Um,
who I met in Oxford Circus,
but they've gone quiet, so
give them the benefit of the doubt.
Maybe they're at work or some [ __ ] I
mean, they were texting back and forth,
back and forth, and then they just went quiet.
It would never change, would it?
So, yeah, that's that. So,
be out again next week.
Yeah, she was. Yeah,
she's 20, by the way, but I don't give a
[ __ ] Old enough in it. She was all
right. Yeah. I don't know why she's gone quiet.
Maybe uh I don't know. But anyways, be
out next week anyway. Steven Howard,
that [ __ ] the skin rap face needs to
stop projecting his skintess onto me,
Steven. It's getting out of hand now,
lad. It's really really getting out of hand.
He really needs to stop projecting his
skimpness onto me. It's not good for
your mental health, mate. It really
ain't good for your [ __ ] mental health.
Yeah, I wash my hair. I not going to
come out the shower. I need to get a haircut. And
I need to get a haircut as well some point. Yeah,
I said I weren't going to go out next
week, but I planned it, so I am going
to. It wasn't about the money, bro. is
just [ __ ] losing that bet is [ __ ] annoying, bro.
Wasn't about the money at all, bro.
He needs to stop [ __ ] projecting his
skipness onto me,
but I'm only going to stay local this
time cuz that's what the plan was. So,
yeah, we'll stay local.
Yeah, out of them seven numbers, one
replied and obviously the Snapchat replied.
No, I'm not going out Thursday. Why am I
going to go out Thursday? I'm only going
out this week cuz I planned it with my thingy.
So, we had it planned. I'm not going out
Thursday. Why am I going out Thursday,
bro? I done enough. I went out last I
went out last week and the week before that.
Nah, bro. I'm not going out Thursday. I'm done.
I'm going out thingy because I've
planned it already. So,
why not? I'm not going that far. So,
nah, remember them days I' done for a
while now, bro. Matey,
I got an escort last week, an escort a
week before I went out drinking
approaching. What the [ __ ] bro?
Same people, same attitude.
How men put themselves through that, I I
I feel bad for them, bro. I really really do.
putting up with that [ __ ] just in order
to find someone. [ __ ] that, bro. Like I
said, it was a one-off for me, bro, cuz
I had nothing better to do. So, I
thought, let me let me see if we can
find someone that's not all the same,
that don't have attitude. And yeah,
um there is no woman out there that's
different. Believe you me, mate, I was
out for several hours on Friday. I was
out since 3:00 p.m., come back at 1:00
in the morning. So, believe you me, I've
done a lot of approaching, mate.
And I had a mind grain at the end of it
to be honest. It's so boring. You know,
all you do is meet people with the same attitude,
the same stuck upness, the same [ __ ]
Imagine you had to deal with that every
day. I think you'd end up going into I I
think you'd end up in a mental a mental
hospital, bro. I think you would
actually end up in a [ __ ] mental
hospital, a mental ward.
You actually would end up in a [ __ ]
mental wall, bro. It's It's bad. It
really really is really bad, bro.
Before I met my friend, I was out for
like 5 hours approaching, bro. It's bad
bad bad bad bad.
So, they're not worth it, bro. I
wouldn't be going out next week either
if it wasn't I wouldn't be going out this week.
Who can't afford to go out every week? Bomb,
you can't afford to go out every week.
Bomb, I was out last week. I was out the
week before. I'm going out this week.
That's three weeks in a row. That's
almost a month, mate. You keep going if you want.
Yeah, we can keep going if you want,
buddy. Not a problem.
Uh, do not talk about people that you
don't know. Thank you.
So, do not talk about people that you
don't know. Is that right, Steven Howard?
And I got an escort as well. I got an
escort last week.
And I got an escort the week before I
went out drinking. So yeah.
No, I had a backachche, bro. [ __ ] backachche.
No, to be honest with you, I had a
backachche, lad. I'm going to do a video
on dating, bro. I am going to do a video
on dating later. I just haven't got
around to doing it. I was out earlier.
So, just this needs to be addressed,
bro. Really, really needs to be
addressed. And bear in mind, bro, this
was a one-off.
Nope. No interest. I have no interest.
Dealing with stuck up women. They're all
the same. I'll be out on Saturday with
my sister. We've been planning this for
ages now, and we just haven't decided to
do it. And I weren't going to go, but
then I thought, [ __ ] it. We planned it
cuz after losing that football, I didn't
want to do anything. But yeah, [ __ ] it.
I'll go out, get my haircut, and I'll go
out. And that will be the third week in
a row. And we're at 24 numbers now and
not a single date.
Yeah, that's how it's always going to be
here, bro. So,
nah, no approaches. Not interested. That
was a oneoff, bro. That literally was a
one-off um on Friday, you know.
cuz I was out anyways. But
well, we'll see if this woman from
Snapchat meets me anyways. She seems all
right. But they all seem all right at
first, don't they?
They're all full of [ __ ] bro. Seriously.
One said that she's back in Russia when
she's not. I mean, you must really,
really, really, really
have no respect for yourself if you're
willing to put up with that [ __ ] every
[ __ ] you know, every day. You really
must have something wrong with you, bro.
What else am I going to do when you're
going to leave the country? Obviously,
bro, what else are you going to do?
You're going to leave the country.
You're going to give up. You're going to
save your dope. You're going to leave.
Well, what else are you going to do?
continue dealing with that disrespect.
Like, it's not normal, bro. That's why
people leave. Ant-Man's friends [ __ ]
in um in uh in um in Thailand.
Who is this Penny Bunny?
Is that somebody that was arguing with Timmy?
So yeah, that's what you can do. You're
going to have to leave. That's that's
that is it.
That's somebody that was arguing with
Timmy, wasn't it?
Can't even click on the account.
That's someone I was arguing with Timmy.
But yeah, that's what you're going to
have to do. You're going to have to leave.
Yeah. What's my plans? Nothing. I've
already been out. I was out for a couple
of hours. I went to KFC. Um went to
Sainsbury's. I've not long come back.
I'm just going to chill today. No plans
Is that the real Penny? I don't know who this is.
If you've been anywhere [ __ ] If
you've been anywhere near Timmy, I'm not
going anywhere [ __ ] near you. [ __ ] that.
Oh, online X. Uh,
I don't know. I can't go on the thing.
So, yeah, you're going to have to um,
bro, you just killed a vibe, bro. Just
just go away,
you know? Stop self projecting. Just
just go away, bro. You're just you're
just killing the vibe. You're boring
now. See, the the thing is with these
repeat these self-projecting repeaters,
Stephen, it's just boring now. They've
got no effect on us. They don't bully
us. They don't offend us. They're just
projecting. They just bore us, bro. They
just ruin the whole chat. That's all
they do. cuz how long have they been
saying the same projecting [ __ ] about
their own lives? It's boring.
So anyways, um right back on to you.
It doesn't even let me see if that's a real account.
I don't know who this is.
I know that Timmy doesn't like you, but yeah.
Nah, I'll never get with a woman from YouTube anyways.
No, I'm good, bro.
I don't believe they're real, man.
Hy, I don't believe this person's even real.
You know, you don't have to do something
every single day. You do realize that.
There is days where you want to chill.
I've been non-stop for the past 3 4 days.
Yeah. Oh, [ __ ] me, bro.
It's [ __ ] [ __ ] is it?
Anybody? I can't see. Um
Oh, it doesn't let me go on it. The account
Yeah, it's a fake account, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm having a um I'm having a lamb
stew today, Steven Howard. Okay with you, boss.
Is that okay with you, boss? Yeah. Yeah, man.
So, yeah. You You said, "What else are
you going to do?" You're going to have to leave.
That's that you're going to have to
leave. Well, what what do you want to
do? Do you want to keep do you want to
keep staying here trying all your life
get an attitude bullshitter people that
play games or just leave and actually
have a life somewhere else? You know
that's that's that
that's that it's you know it's always
going to be the same here. It's always
going to be the same here, bro. So what
what what are you going to do, bro?
Like I said, I wouldn't be going out
next week if it wasn't for um
obviously I planned this, you know, for
a very long time. So otherwise, I
wouldn't even be going out. I would just
I wouldn't bother. I would just stay in.
You get me, bro. I would just [ __ ]
just stay in me.
It's better than here though, bro. It's
dealing with stuck up bullshitting women,
you know. [gasps]
Yeah. It's better than over here, bro.
Of course, it's not perfect, but it's
better than here. Better than here, you know.
bullshitter is game players. That's all
you come across. I don't know how many
more years are you going to keep giving
these women the benefit of the doubt. I
don't know for how many more years are
you going to keep doing it?
People say they're not all the same.
They say one thing, but these women
prove another. So,
>> same attitude, same mannerism, same
games, same [ __ ]
Literally, they're it's just the same
[ __ ] for them. All
right. Starting it. So start it. Yep.
That's right. You know, Steven Howard,
what do you think of that? Eh,
seven numbers. Seven numbers.
Yeah, but it's cheap. But over there
Yeah, but over there it's dead cheap.
It's like if you go to a dentist to get
a fill in, it's like £20. You don't need
NHS. It's It's so cheap over there. It's
so so so so cheap. It might as well be
on the NHS.
If you have a problem with your tooth
fees, you go straight to the dentist.
You give them 20 pound, they give you a
fill in. Here it's like£60 for just a [ __ ] checkup.
No, bro. It's way better than here.
Trust me, it's no life here. It really,
really isn't a life here in England. The
women, the people, the weather, the
waiting around for things. It's [ __ ] bro.
There's no life here. There is no life.
There is no life. Yeah, bro. Um, you
don't need NHS. Everything is so cheap
over there. You can literally just go
and buy antibiotics dead cheap. So
[clears throat] yeah, yeah. So
that's that, man.
I'm having a lamb stew. Greavvesy. Okay
with you, boss.
Is that okay with you, boss? Oh.
Oh, I'm so tired, man. That was caught
with me the past couple of days.
[ __ ] dentist walking around, approaching,
dealing with bullshitters. H.
It will always be the same here, won't
it, Greavvesy? You know this. It would
always be the same here. You know this.
So, I don't know why you you asked this
stupid [ __ ] Grezy. It would always be
the same here. You know this. Yep.
I can't I can't believe it. Greavves. I
went out last week and the week before
and got an escort. I'm crazy, aren't I,
Greavesy? I'm [ __ ] crazy.
I'm out of control. I'm getting too
greedy, aren't I?
I'm getting too [ __ ] greedy.
It will always be the same. And a
burger, Grezy. I went to KFC. I got a burger. Yeah.
Uncle Bad Touch always wants to play.
Yeah, they're [ __ ] isn't it?
They're bullshiters, these women, aren't they, Greavvesy?
They're [ __ ] bullshiters, bro.
I can't be bothered with their games, their [ __ ]
You can only put up with it for so long.
Really? You've not been out for months.
Really? Nah. You're having a wank, aren't you?
You're having a [ __ ] wank.
No, you're having a wank. No way.
No, you're trying [ __ ] Yeah. prody,
you should go to Manchester, Grey.
Yeah, you should go to uh you should go to Manchester. That's mad.
What would happen if I went out
approaching today, Indigo? If I went to
central London and I started approaching,
what do what do you reckon the response would be? Huh?
No, but I'm saying what what would they say?
Cuz I'm trying to Yeah, but [ __ ] a
brass. [ __ ] off, Indigo. I'm trying to
find a bloody relationship.
And obviously people on Reddit tell me
that I need to keep trying.
Yeah, but but people on Reddit say you
need to keep trying to get a
relationship and stuff. Indie guy.
Yeah, that's true. But what about like
what about like a relationship and
stuff? Like meeting someone and getting
into a relationship?
Like what people on Reddit say?
What do you mean I don't get one in London? Why not? No.
I want this [ __ ] lamb stew. That's
what I [ __ ] want. I'm starving, mate.
Also, another thing, a lot of escorts
have attitude, Indigo.
A lot of escorts have attitude.
So, it it's about finding the right uh
escort as well.
Yeah, a lot of them have attitude.
Really do, bro. They really, really do.
And they also move around. So the one
that you've seen before will probably be
miles away now before they come back to London.
Yeah, a lot of them have attitude, bro.
The last one I went with had attitude.
It's just a [ __ ] country, bro. That's
all it is. It's just a just a [ __ ] country. That's so
don't know what's bloody wrong with me. Grieves.
Whoever's took it out of Peter belly. One sec. Virgin boy.
All right. Virgin boy.
No, I shouldn't have kept her
cuz uh I couldn't deal with her attitude anymore
and I weren't going to keep disrespect
to myself. Nah, no way, bro.
Even if she messages me now.
I'm waiting for this person on Snapchat
to message me back. We was talking all
last night, so maybe they're at work or
something, but I hope they do reply.
Now she was starting to be [ __ ]
She was starting to be [ __ ] So
that 19year-old, she was starting to be
[ __ ] and started calling me mate. And I
don't know how many times I had to say
I'm not your [ __ ] mate. I had to say
it a few times with so
Oh, I've already messages this person.
>> [clears throat]
>> Indigo. Why do people on Reddit say got
use dating apps?
Why do they tell people to go on these dating apps? Yeah.
What is it with these people telling me
to use bloody dating apps?
They say go on the apps for sex indigo.
They say use dating app for sex. Indigo,
what's your opinion on that?
Use use the apps.
They say go on Tinder. [laughter]
They say go on Tinder. Don't even get a
bloody match. [ __ ] liars.
[ __ ] bullshitted. Oh gosh. Where am
my little nestles now? So tired.
So tired. I want my little lamb stew. Oh. Oh gosh.
Oh gosh. So tired. Greasy.
Oh gosh. Do you think you can make it to
the um dentist, Greasy, on
you? You couldn't make it to the
dentist, could you?
I need to get another fill in. I think.
So, that's what happens when there's a
hole in your tooth. It [ __ ] up the nerve.
I need to get another one. I think
I do as well. Laney doesn't like them.
Lane, they scare Laney.
I like them as well.
Oh yeah, there's another one. I need
another filling, bro. I haven't had that many fillings.
It's like when you have a hole in your
tooth, it [ __ ] a nerve up in it. Yeah.
Yeah. Depends what pain. [snorts]
I like the foot pain in a wet world. No,
I didn't actually. The paranoitis that
was that pain was bad, bro.
It depends what kind of pain it is.
I like being ill. I like feeling ill.
I like feeling ill, man. Yeah.
Oh gosh. Squeezy. Oh gosh.
Oh, I'm so sleepy. Greasy. Oh gosh.
I'm going to go to your house, Grezy.
I'm going to visit you. I'm going to
bring King as well. [gasps]
Yep. I'm going to bring King. Oh gosh, Grizzy.
Losing that football bet was [ __ ] depressing, mate.
That was depressing, wasn't it, Steven?
Losing that bloody football bet.
[ __ ] hell, man.
So, if I get with this 20-year-old, is
that wrong? Grievy, if she meets me and
she's 20 and I'm 28, is that okay with
you, Greavvesy boss?
Grievy, okay with you, boss?
Is that okay with you, Greasy Boss?
Okay with you, boss.
I would still do it anyways. I don't
give a [ __ ] man.
I I would still do it, bro.
What a 20. Hold on. My 28. I would still
[ __ ] do. I don't give a [ __ ] mate.
They're out their [ __ ] They're out
their teams, aren't they? So, yeah.
20 and 28. Yeah.
I don't think that's that bad. No heat. [snorts]
Uh, someone's got bipolar.
Launch legs. I think you need to take your medication. medication, matey.
Why is it with people in this community
keep calling other people skint every day?
I think part of their disabilities is
getting themselves confused with other people.
It's very very weird. The stuff that
they come out with is is crazy. Like I
had someone say to me, Grezy, that you
[ __ ] you get universal credit on the
ETH and it's £420.
I'm thinking, what the [ __ ] This is
news to me. I didn't know that I got
money on the 8th of each month and it's £420.
Where the bloody hell do these people
get this stuff from? It's weird. It's so
random the stuff they come out with and
then you just know that they're just
talking about themselves because it's so
weird. Where the [ __ ] do they come out
with this [ __ ] from? They try to tell
you you can't afford trainers, you buy
trainers, you buy jeans, you can't go
out every week. This will be the third
week in a row. I mean, at some point
they've surely got to understand that
they're just talking about themselves.
And that's part of their disability, you know.
Yeah. And you're a virgin. Even though I
approved I've had sex. This is what I
mean with these people. They're they're they're classic
[ __ ] self projectors. [snorts]
They're proper proper self projectors on
here, man. Proper proper self projectors. Yeah. All >> [laughter] >> right.
right, I'll be back later. Yeah.