That took about a million
years. Oh, so I don't I don't even have
a day off to myself tomorrow. [ __ ]
hell. That is long, bro. That's what you
wanted, but it is long. It is long, bro.
I I'll put my good I'll put my new
passport to use tomorrow.
Yeah, it's going to be a [ __ ]
madness. A madness,
bro. Got this [ __ ] date to go on
tomorrow. [ __ ] sake. That's why you
always drink Thursdays. You see, because
when you drink Thursdays, you're
refreshed for Saturday. Well, almost
refreshed. Kind of a little bit.
Mostly. Yeah, you're mostly refreshed,
you see. Whereas if you drink Friday,
you're [ __ ] on Saturday still. So
that's um that's a problem you got.
Yeah. Yeah. It's going to be fun, bro.
I'm going to go and send
it. Got this woman to meet tomorrow.
I knew she like Peter Belly with the little
eyes. That would be getting a certain
virgin jealous. Especially when I hear
the voice. [ __ ] hell. That'll be
getting a certain virgin jealous, mate.
You want You don't want [ __ ] jealous
boot virgin to find out. [ __ ] hell,
man. But that was long. Well, I've got
two scheduled. That was long. That's And
that's what it is to get anywhere in
this country. It's [ __ ] up,
bro. It is
mad. And I think it was the first one I
done as well. The first one on the
street as well. It's mad. You see what
I'm saying? Like it it actually
contradicts itself, bro. I swear now.
Like you hit you, you know, you hit
these bars and these clubs, you send
send. You can't get nothing. And as soon
as you go outside and you approach on
the street, bam, you got a date again.
See, it's [ __ ] up. You see what I'm
saying? And I could have had a few probably
more. They mostly come see they
most they mostly come from the street.
These approaches actually come from the
street. It is
crazy. It actually is
mad. It's mad,
bro. You would have thought like you
look normal. You go to a bar, you get
something. You don't get nothing there.
You get chucked out of there. You do one
approach on the street and you get
something cuz [ __ ] It's a madness,
bro. It's a madness. I thought she
weren't even going to meet her. We We
spoke about it yesterday, but I didn't
think she really was going to. I thought
she was going to give her a number and
block me or
uh what trouble am I going to be getting myself
into with this woman? [ __ ] sake.
It was the first
We hug goodbye as well, man. Somebody
was just calling me. But um uh yeah, we hugged goodbye,
too. Hey, I got stuff to do tomorrow. I
can't be on here arguing with these little
clowns. Sorry, man. Honestly can't. Honestly
can't. I wanted to get a [ __ ] [ __ ]
today, but I can't do that because of um
I need to be prepared for tomorrow. I'm meeting
someone. So yeah, doing that. So
yeah, I just woke up today and I thought
I really fancied a
[ __ ] Like I really fancied one, but
yeah, I've got a person to meet so I can't
It is just so mad to me. It's so
mad. Like get nothing in a bar like an
actual club that's supposed to be
sociable, right? And then you get kicked
out from socialable talking to people.
What? They were just being dicks, right?
And as soon as
that as soon as you approach on the
street, you get it's [ __ ] madness,
bro. It like it sounds like it's it's
just mad to me. It should be the other
way around. You should just go you got
your sage on, you just go to a [ __ ]
club. You can't do
that. Nothing but street approaches
work. Literally nothing. Nothing, mate.
But the reason why we I'll tell Antman
about this as well. One sec.
He's going to expose. Uh, he's not
getting attention on my channel. I I
don't give these little clowns
attentions on my channel. Sorry,
buddy. Go seek attention somewhere else.
Go seek attention somewhere else cuz
you're on my channel,
buddy. Get a life. Get off of YouTube. Go get
laid. You little YouTube keyboard
warrior. I've got vids up.
Huh? Listen to me, rat face. You don't
[ __ ] tell me what I do and what I
don't do. You can put any chat you want
out there. I'm not bothered. YouTube's
your life. YouTube's not my life. You
shut the [ __ ] up and suck my dick. How
about that one? You little [ __ ] Get a
life. Get off YouTube.
Simple. All my All my chats with
Ant-Man, I literally don't care. Put
whatever you want up. I don't give a
[ __ ] You don't sit in your little
virgin bedsit, you little virgin, trying
to tell me I need to comply. Yeah, I am
doing something. I'm ignoring him. Stop
bringing him up. He wants attention and
he's not getting it. [ __ ] off and stop
bringing that on my channel. Bye-bye
now. Stop bringing it up. Yeah, it's
been years. He's
obsessed. You're obsessed. Get a life.
Go get lazy little virgin. Something
that I'll be doing again tomorrow. [ __ ]
off you freak. Yeah,
man. That's it, bro.
Um Oh yeah.
all my chaps of Antman. You don't do a
video on me trying to tell me I need to
comply. [ __ ] off you little virgin.
[ __ ] These people have got too much
time on their hands, bro. It is a madness.
Too much time on their hands. This is crazy,
bro. Get a life, mate. That's what you
need to do,
mate. Oh, waking up the same time. Oh.
Yeah. Oh, put the old feet up, man.
Pounding the old 80
sheets. Get life and get off your YouTube little
keyboard. Despise you find your creeper.
You have zero money.
Self-reflecting. I've got zero money.
What did this sound like to you? Stop
self-reflecting. And it's no good for
your mental health. Listen. What's the sound of
this? Yeah. What's the sound of this
anyways, bro? Yeah, you do live a very
lonely, bald, sad life. You're talking
about yourself. Think of it. You've been
on YouTube for years. Yeah. Projecting
your life onto other people every single
[ __ ] day of your life. And you, from
my understanding, have been doing it
since 2012. You do live a very lonely,
sad life for somebody in their late 30s,
potentially mid-4s. You're talking about yourself, mate.
It's not nice to talk about yourself
like that. It's no good for your mental
health coming on YouTube every day
calling people what you are. You're just
a sad little virgin with no money.
You're all the same on here. You're a
bunch of sad little
self-reflectors. Mate, if you had all of
these things, you wouldn't be on my
channel telling me I don't have these
things. Stop self-reflecting and go lose
your virginity, you little [ __ ] And
this is exactly why I'm coming off this
community because it's just the same
[ __ ] every day. Like you you can you can
only take it in small
doses. I got a date tomorrow uh Gary
with that American. I'm seeing her tomorrow.
Yep. Yeah. Speaking to her. Yes,
sir. Yes, sir.
Yeah, you got all these [ __ ] weirdos calling me,
bro. Yeah, I can't call on my WhatsApp
number. I'm going to change my number as
well. Turn my main number
out. I was, sir. Yeah, I
was. Yeah, man. I was [ __ ] drunk. I
was [ __ ] up my head, lad.
To be fair, I was [ __ ] out of my
head. That's why you drink on a Thursday,
Gary. That's why you drink on a Thursday, Gary.
Lad, that's why you drink on a Thursday,
right? Cuz of um you drink on a Thursday because
um you'll be [ __ ] set for the
Saturday. Yeah, I'm [ __ ] today, but
tomorrow I'll be
better. Stop calling me, you [ __ ]
[ __ ] Oh my [ __ ] god, bro. I'm
going to change my number. You [ __ ]
weirdos, bro. What's it? What's What's this free,
lad? Yeah, I would give a little Well, I
would. I'm changing my [ __ ] number,
dude. My WhatsApp number is different to
my um normal number. I'm just going to
change my normal number. [ __ ] off, you
weirdo. Stop calling me, you [ __ ]
Hello. Hello. [ __ ] off, man. You
stalking weirdos. Listen, Gary, after
today, bro, I'm leaving for a little bit.
I'm leaving for a couple of weeks, bro.
I'm going to try and make things work
with this woman and and um I'm I'm off
this [ __ ] for a couple of weeks, bro.
So, any rumors you hear, these people
are just [ __ ] weird
stalkers, you know? I'm going to change
my [ __ ] number, bro. Swear down. I'm
going to do a [ __ ] Morgan.
Yeah. I'm changing my number, bro.
Yeah, I have to call him up and change my
number. Yeah, [ __ ]
stalkers. Yeah, but guess what? But
guess what the thing is, Gary? Yeah.
Even when he was in London, he wouldn't
even let anyone know where he is.
They're [ __ ] Both of them are two
[ __ ] I could beat them both with
[ __ ] one hand, lad. I can beat them
both with one hand. How about that? You
know, I told the guy, "Stop calling me
and go suck your man." Right. What's
this free number? I'm going to change my
number now. One sec.
Three number, right? How to change a number. Oh
[ __ ] Change my number,
bro. Yeah, that's fine, bro. Yeah,
Jamie, if I look like you, I would do
the same, mate. Still a virgin. Yeah.
You ain't got a life, mate. If I look
like you, I'd probably spend all day
trying to ruin people's lives as well,
lad. Listen, mate. Look at the state of
you, mate. You're fat and ugly. You got
nothing in your life. That's why you're
on YouTube. You ain't got a wife. You
ain't got no kids. You ain't got no
money. Look at the state of you. You
ugly bastard. Anyways, how right my
number? One second, bro.
One sec. One sec. I'm going to change.