You're up.
>> [clears throat]
>> Just got some popcorn.
Good old popcorn.
Where the [ __ ] is Joseph Ferrar, man? Seriously,
waiting for that [ __ ]
Where the [ __ ] is he?
You never guess what this uh one on
Snapchat come out with. We are [ __ ]
full of [ __ ] mate.
is [ __ ] full of [ __ ]
[ __ ] this [ __ ] man.
Strange that though. It is strange.
We've heard it all before. I'm saying it You know,
so even when they come across by their
own words, people that are, you know,
different, they still make excuses.
So there you go. I've still never been
shown different, mate. You know, I I
would I would actually jump at the
chance to be honest with you.
Nice message, but they're [ __ ]
completely full of [ __ ]
No, you know what I mean, mate. It's [ __ ] [ __ ]
Someone last week on Instagram wants me
to do a video, so I'll do it when I'm ready.
But I don't understand it because they moan that
that all men are the same.
All the uh all the [ __ ] that they
go for are the same. Not all men are the
same. The [ __ ] that you go for are
the same. Big difference.
It is strange though. It is strange. I
just deleted them to be honest.
But there will winge that they can't
find anyone. madness.
I don't give a [ __ ] to be honest, mate.
I'm I'm I'm
more than happy just watching porn,
man. I don't give a [ __ ]
But even when normal people right?
Coming into their life, they're still
not interested. So, what what do these
people have to moan about? I just don't understand.
I don't think we'll ever know to be
honest with you. I don't think we'll
ever know. But that's just that, mate. Hear that?
[ __ ] are mad.
Doesn't bother me. It doesn't depress me, bro. Not really.
All right. But she's still full of [ __ ]
from what she's saying.
She said that you come across really
sweet. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. So,
obviously people don't have to give
people a chance, but
they're obviously going to moan in wings
that they can't find someone years down
the line. I've seen it all before. I've
heard it all before.
You know, I think every [ __ ] one has
to be all right. But even if you get a genuine person that
comes your way, you're still not
interested. So, I don't I don't
understand their problem. I seriously don't. Nope.
I got uh seven numbers. One replied,
then didn't reply. And I was speaking to
this one on Snapchat, and I I said to
them, I I'll read it out for you if you
want. I said to them,
"Do you wanna um
do you wanna
I said, oh, I said, do you want to hang
out on Thursday?" So, got to be
somewhere Saturday. They replied, "Uh,
hey, hope you're okay. I'm going to be
honest and say I'm not really interested
in getting to know or meeting anyone at
this moment in time." Strange. You seem
like a really nice guy, and although we
just met, my life is so busy with
education, work, and other personal
things. This is nothing personal towards
you. I just don't really have the time
to invest in new people. Thank you for
coming up to me that day. It was really
sweet. There's no hard feelings and all
the best to you. But the thing is is that
these are the same. Obviously, I can't I
I couldn't care less, bro. To be honest
with you, I don't expect any different.
The problem with this is that they're
going to moan and winge that they can't
find anyone, you know, be it tomorrow,
be it two years, 3 years, um, down the
line, they're going to moan and winge
that they can't find someone and all men
are [ __ ] And even when they come
across someone that's genuine, then
they're saying how they're not
interested. So, I mean, [ __ ] me, bro.
Like, I have to literally actively go
out and seek people and they're always
all the same. Whereas you have had
someone come up to you that is by your
own words genuine and you're not
interested. So I mean you don't really
have anything to moan about. You have
nothing to complain about really.
She seemed all right as well. She wasn't
stuck up or anything. But I I just don't
I just don't understand then bro. I
really don't. And again I don't give a
[ __ ] to be honest with you.
That's that's it, bro.
So trust me, Mr. B, these [ __ ]
when they say about them being
[ __ ] that that's the men that they
go for. You know, you've seen it in
their own words how I've come across.
So, you know, and they're still not
interested. So, at the end of the day,
that's that's on them, bro. That's their
loss. But they have no right to moan and
complain. I don't give a I can care
less. But you get what I mean, bro.
Um, so yeah, man. That's that
I might go outside there cuz I'm
planning my sister, but I don't know if
I can be bothered to be honest, bro.
It's not money. Money is not the
problem. I've actually lived quite a
good life recently and stuff. It's not
the problem, bro. It's just going to be
bothered with that [ __ ]
It's all right once in a while, you
know, trying to just have a laugh with
it and that, but [ __ ] dealing with
that [ __ ] constantly, mate. Yeah, [ __ ]
I'd rather sit there and watch porn on
my life, bro. But I swear to God, that's
actually how Yeah, literally, bro.
But it's mad how they don't even give
people the chance.
It is. It is crazy to be honest because
they always say they have bad
experiences with men and you know people
are creeps and then when when they
actually finally get the opportunity
they they they're not interested
and they come to them as well. I'm
pretty sure any man would be over the
moon if a normal woman come to them that
were different. I think the people
wouldn't pass up that opportunity. Um,
so you've actually got someone normal
cuz a lot of these white knights and
stuff and these simps, they won't even meet then.
You know, that's the thing. Someone
said, "Yeah, you think that all of these
women have got these options, but they
don't. They've got endless attention,
bro. I was actually listening to this
and it's actual facts." It is, to be
honest, it is. It's true to be honest.
But I mean they're still generalizing
people and then even when they're given
the chance they still pass it by. So
what are they moaning about really?
So they moan and winge. But at least
they didn't have attitude. That was good
to be honest. That was probably like the
best person I met. Yes. It was dreadful
on Friday, Mr. B mate. The [ __ ] I had to
put up with which is why I don't put up
with it obviously, bro. Um,
so I'll do a video about it.
She's still right, but it's just a shame
that like people write that stuff.
Yeah, it is a shame, bro. To be honest,
most people are stuck up though. So to
find someone that's not is nice.
So many uh stuck up people. I was
watching Alice in Wonderland porn.
Mr. B. Yeah,
Alice in Wonderland. I was watching some
really old school porn, bro.
Really old school porn.
I can't watch [ __ ] Johnny Sims and
[ __ ] bro. It's too It looks too fake. I
can't watch it. Obviously, all porns,
but I can't watch it
unless it's got like a story line to it,
bro. And I can't watch it. It's too
Looks too fake. [ __ ] I can't watch
that Johnny Sims. What?
He's full of [ __ ] But I'm not that
annoyed. I'm not annoyed at all. I don't
give a [ __ ] bro. What they do?
Cuz it's their loss. They're the ones
that's going to be moaning and winging
about men, not me. I don't give a [ __ ]
And I tried to come across as genuine as
I possibly could.
So basically when when these women right
sit there and generalize men when I I
like to think well that when I come and
I actually like approach I'm putting all
that [ __ ] to bed. I'm like proving them
that their theory is wrong, you know?
And every time I [ __ ] do and then
they're still not see when I when I say
Mr. When I say Mr. B, all women are the
same. That's because every single time
you go out, they have the same attitude.
They say the same things. They have the same mannerisms.
I don't have some [ __ ] random woman
coming and approaching me proving
actually [ __ ] different. You
understand? There's a there's a big difference. Oh well, that's that.
Just going to watch some WWE later. Okay.
See, this [ __ ] doesn't bother me anymore, guys. Cuz
it's like, if you can get 10 numbers
and not get a date, what what's really
going to surprise you after that? Come on, bro.
Calm the [ __ ] on, bro. Really? Nothing.
The [ __ ] man.
So, they're actually lucky to have
somebody actually go and approach them
and that's that's actually down to earth
and genuine and they're still
they're still uh
they're still not interested.
It's weird, bro. It is really really cuz they
cuz they say that men are weirdos and
creeps and stuff to test. So they when
someone you know it's weird. It is weird
and you've obviously come across that
way as well. So obviously when you first
meet someone you don't know what they're
going to do. And I'm always thinking
they're thinking I'm going to rob their
[ __ ] phone because we're in [ __ ]
Oxford circus. I'm thinking they're
thinking I'm going to rob their phone.
So you come across as genuine. You end
up genuine in the end and they still
[ __ ] you over. So
just really don't get it, bro.
Really don't get it. Strange.
I don't get why they go for people
people that beat them as well. Why they
go for like
why these people go for like women
abusers as well? Cuz if someone if a
woman gives me attitude, they're gone.
I'm like, "Adios."
And I don't have options. I'm not
putting up with that [ __ ] Why do you
think I [ __ ] that 19year-old off? But
they will stay with men that abuse them.
It's mad, is it? It is. It is [ __ ] mental, bro.
If someone gives me attitude and start
trying to take the piss, I'm leaving them. Bye. Cut contact.
It is strange, isn't it?
Very, very strange.
But she still didn't come across as stuck up,
which again is unusual cuz they're from
London. So usually they are stuck up.
But it's just a shame that they don't
because I'm sure in in a few years they
will be moaning about Ben. You know
strange is it? Yeah. Los
was talking last night as well,
but I deleted her cuz there's no point
staying in contact with someone that's
never going to meet you.
That is weird. That is weird.
Very very weird.
because I'm like the most I'm probably
the most genuine person that they'll
probably ever have approached them.
That's that's the most [ __ ] up thing
about it. Like not trying to be like
manipulative or anything, but I probably
[ __ ] know I am. So
what do these people really have to
complain about, man?
I shall never know.
But that's starting it.
Heard it all before, mate. Heard it all before.
I might have to get some popcorn, bro. [ __ ] >> Yeah.
moan and [ __ ]
moan and wind. Yeah.
Yes, I did.
Why are you talking about that? Anyways,
so I wasn't pissed off about Friday. I
was just thinking to myself like these
men are [ __ ] cray, bro.
If they're prepared to deal with this
[ __ ] every day in order to find someone,
they're [ __ ] mad. Anyone that deals
with this [ __ ] is mad.
That is mental, bro.
That is [ __ ] It didn't piss. It didn't
really piss me off,
but I It doesn't bother me cuz I I
always know it's going to be the same.
So, I play at my own risk.
So, that's it.
That's why it didn't piss me off. That's that Very strange.
Well, I never want children. I never
have wanted children. But yeah,
basically it it it goes like this,
right? It's not about that. It's about
the fact that
I would rather be by myself than have to
deal with what I have to deal with
Friday repeatedly. I'm not putting up
with that [ __ ] but I would rather be by
myself. Yeah, literally 100%. Yeah,
cuz if if it's to do
if it's it's either be alone or deal
with that [ __ ] Nah, I'm not dealing
with that [ __ ] So, if I have to be
alone, bro, then so be it. You know,
that's that's how it is. I'm not
bothered, bro. Um,
it doesn't it is what it is, bro. It's
not worth it. If you have to deal with
that [ __ ] just in hopes to find
someone, lad, I ain't doing it.
I'll travel the world by myself. It's
simple, bro. I don't care.
Cuz the thing is, esper, why should you
deal with games, [ __ ] lies, and
stuck up people just in order to find
someone? No thanks. No thanks.
I was just watching porn like an hour
ago. I wanked off like four times. I was
just watching some porn.
Yeah, I was speaking to some woman on
Snapchat, bro, who I approached in Oxford Circus.
Yeah, you never guess what they come out with.
See, it's like what Antman said, it's to
be expected. But I've never really not
been bothered about it since the 10 numbers.
Cuz I I
since the 10 numbers, bro,
since I got the 10 numbers right and I
didn't get a day, I was like, "Okay,
whatever happens, it's it's going to be
the same here now, ain't it?" So, I
accepted it from them to be fair, cuz it
is what it is. It's not going to change. So, ah,
you're boring. Bye-bye.
Self effect on channel.
So, here's the thing, Jasper. Right.
This is what this girl said to me on
Snapchat. Now, she wasn't stuck up or
anything. I met her in Oxford Circus,
right? Um, and we was talking. I didn't
get any bad vibes. And I tried to come
across as genuine as possible. Right.
Then they wrote, "Hey, hope you're okay.
I'm going to be honest and say that I'm
not really interested in getting to know
or meet anyone at this moment in time.
You seem like a really nice guy and
although we just met, my life is so busy
with education work and other things.
This is nothing personal to rude towards
you. I just don't really have the time
to invest in new people. Thank you for
coming up to me. It was really sweet.
There's no hard feelings." What I don't
understand is, bro, obviously this
doesn't bother me. I don't really care,
bro. At the end of the day, it's their
loss. But you have to understand, think
about this, Jasper, right? That
you are going out to try to find women
that are different and you can't find a
woman that's different. They've all got
attitudes or they pretend they've got
boyfriends, ret. Now, these women,
right, generalized men, right? They come
across weirdos, creeps, people that um
whatever. No, it's fine. But just hear
me out. They come across all of these
people that they can't get enough of,
right? [ __ ] No, no, no. Whatever.
So then they come across somebody that's
actually that's actually genuine that's
approached them that's actual the
probably the most genuine person they're
ever going to meet and they're not
interested. So at the end of the day,
bro, like there's there's no sympathy
for them. People shouldn't be able to
give them sympathy because at the end of
the day, right, it's like, yeah, okay,
they don't have to give you a chance and
I don't care, bro. But the thing is is
they're even writing on a paragraph that
you've come across in that way. So,
isn't that what they would want? Cuz
they say they want a nice guy and and
and I've approached them as well. I wish
I had someone approach me. So,
do you see what the problem is, bro? You
know what I'm saying? That's But again,
I don't care. I don't really, but you
get what I'm saying. Still something
that has to be said. They don't have to
do anything. They get approached and
like I said, bro, they're the I'm the
most genuine person they'll probably
ever meet in their life.
So, I'm not frustrated anymore. It
doesn't bother me, bro, cuz it will
always be the same. So, it doesn't it
doesn't frustrate me anymore.
You know, at the end of the day, I would
be more surprised if anything changed,
cuz it will never change. It doesn't
bother me, bro. It doesn't bother me.
But that doesn't bother me either. I'm
just saying it as a thing. Like they
they've had somebody approach them, come
up to them, right? So they've said that
you're genuine and you're nice. Okay. So
why don't they give you a chance then?
Nah, I was going to go out with my
sister on Saturday. I changed my mind
and I said earlier, okay, I'm going to
go out with you. But I just don't uh
I just don't want to, bro. Like, it's
not money. I have money. I can go out
every week. I've been out the past two
weeks. It's not money, but I'd rather
just sit in and watch WWE, bro. I can't
be bothered with this [ __ ] bro. I
swear to God, this [ __ ]
Like I said, Friday was a one-off. But yeah,
it is a shame though, bro, because
the thing is they don't have better.
They have endless attention. We used to
always say, "Oh yeah, they've got
options. They've got options. They've
got options." But you don't understand
is that the options that they've got are
just simps giving them attention.
Weirdos and creeps. They're the only
options. They don't have genuine options, bro.
Um, and I listened to that a video
someone said and they're actually right.
None of them are probably genuine
either. So, they've actually come across someone
it's it's it's bro it's it's it's hard
to try to explain this.
So, but they're not genuine options that
these people have. You understand?
They're weirdos simps and creeps and
[ __ ] that kind of [ __ ] So at the end
of the day, they're just as good as you
have no options really, but then they
get given a chance and then they're
still not interested. So I mean, how can
anyone give them sympathy at the end of the day?
I went out Friday and I dealt with the
same [ __ ] the [ __ ] the attitude,
the [ __ ] makebelieve boyfriends, the
mind games. That's all I basically dealt
with on Friday. Nothing different.
despite them all being the same. Yeah.
What do you mean? I was out, bro. I'm always out.
Won't be out for a while now. I just
want to chill. But I try and share.
it is strange though. It is. It is
strange. It is strange cuz you would
have thought that is what somebody would have wanted.
just the same as what I would have wanted. So, yeah, strange,
but yeah, it would always be the same here.
Yeah, they are losers on here, bro. They
just all they do on here is just project
their life onto other people.
That's all they do. They self project. Yeah,
they're just self-p projecting little
losers and they come up with the most randomest things.
I don't know where they get their their
information from. Apparently, I get
money every 8 I get money on the 8th of
each month and it's about £400. That's
news to me. I didn't know that.
I don't know where these people get
their information from. It's, as I said
before, they go off their own lives.
They seem to think everyone's got the
same life as them. For example,
I bought jeans, right? I said, "Should I
get trainers? Do I need trainers right
now?" Bam. Someone jumped on the
bandwagon saying, "Oh, you can't afford
trainers. Your skin." I thought, "Okay,
I'll just order the trainers then."
£210, gone. Went out the same week.
So, you know, you're constantly [ __ ]
telling these people that they don't
know people's lives and what people have
and what people don't have, but they
still self project. So, [ __ ] Who knows?
Yeah, bro. They're just self projectors.
That's all they That's what they are. Yeah. >> What?
Yeah. You're probably never ever going
to find anyone in this lifetime, Jasper.
And obviously, I don't want kids, so
there's no reason for me to disrespect
myself every day dealing with their [ __ ]
Cuz you don't realize how toxic this
whole dating thing is. I don't think you
understand the severity of it.
I'll explain it, bro, as um on a video
when I can't be bothered to do it.
Cuz I realized when I gave up,
I felt so much better, bro. I actually
changed as a person. That disproves how
toxic the whole [ __ ] thing was in the first place.
You I actually changed as a person like
after two weeks. Yeah, that's how bad it
is, bro. No one should have to deal with
that [ __ ] unless they want kids or
some [ __ ] Even sex isn't worth it. Even
just to get sex, it's not worth it. It's
not worth it, bro. It's depressing. It's
expensive. The amount of money I put
into it as well. I don't even get as
much money anymore, but I have had
money. So, you know, it's the money,
it's the [ __ ] it's the effort.
Um, it's just Yeah, it's not normal.
whatever normal is.
And at the end of the day, Jasper, these
people sit there and say that women
aren't all the same, all they like. But
best boy better believe that whenever
you go out,
um, all you'll meet is people that are bullshitters. So,
I mean, that's that's that. So, people
can say what they want.
There was one I was speaking to. I
approached her. She was from Amsterdam,
right? I was, "Oh, I've been to
Amsterdam." Yeah, I like the
Netherlands, Dutch people. This is
genuine, by the way. I wasn't even just
making this stuff up. Then they were
asking me for recommendations.
So, I gave them a couple of
recommendations and we were talking for
a little bit. They were with someone and
I was like, "Oh, uh, yeah, when I come
to Amsterdam, we're going to let's um
exchange numbers." She's like, "Oh, I I
I can't uh I have a boyfriend." And I
was thinking, "Oh, do you really?" You
know, and then um they said, "Oh, I
might see you later and we'll have a
drink." And I'm thinking, "What's the
need for that passive aggressive shit?"
I mean, I really really don't understand
it, bro. Just say you're not interested
and keep it moving, you know?
And they were like, "They must have been about 35.
They must have been about 35, like
average looking as well." Yeah. Yeah, bro.
Yo, of course the boyfriend excuse. It's
so boring, bro. It's so boring.
I was like sighing the the whole way
through, bro. Like, it's just so boring,
Uh, no. I just read out what she wrote.
Apparently, she's too busy to meet
anyone new and better t and stuff. So,
yeah. Boy excuse. There was another one
that said they were going back to Russia
tomorrow, which I don't believe it. I
mean, I could be wrong. I'm open for
being wrong, but I don't believe it.
What's the chances that you've met somebody
from Russia that's just gone back the
next day? It's just it's just all [ __ ]
But like I said, I didn't mind because
it was a oneoff, so I didn't have
anything better to do. So, yeah. Right.
It would always be the same old.
What do you expect, bro?
What What What do you expect? I I don't
expect anything different.
So, it will always be the same old
I've not had a date since uh April
and God knows how many numbers I've got
since April. Done. That's that.
It's weird, isn't it? Weird.
Very, very weird, bro.
That boyfriend [ __ ] And you know the
thing is a lot of these women
that's they need telling about themsel.
But the thing is, the thing is is that I
don't care to do it. I'm not interested
to do it. I don't care about it enough
to do it. But
the thing is these people, right, that
have a go at you for like putting a
woman in in a place or time, bro, all
you're doing is bringing them back down
to their level. You're not doing
anything but bringing them back to their
level that they should be at, but
they're not because of these white
knights and these [ __ ] simps.
So, but I they need telling about
themselves, but I want to be the one to
do it. I don't give a [ __ ] bro. If they
want to pretend they've got boyfriends
and think they're better than people,
it's not that's their life, bro. You
know, I'm not Unless they're saying
something to me, um,
then that's a different story. But what
I mean is generally they need telling
about themsel. A lot of them are really
bad, bro, on Friday. Like really bad. Um
um but I'm not it's not for me to do
that, bro. So
cuz I don't care.
Why would she string me along? Uh cuz
she's a westernized woman and that's all
they do is string people along. I mean,
what what do you expect? So,
yeah, that boyfriend thing is really,
really boring, bro. It gives you a
migraine at like the end of the [ __ ]
And I had no expectations. I didn't even
expect anything, but even just hearing
it is annoying.
It's boring. It wasn't annoying. It was
boring. That That's the word boring.
Boring, bro. [ __ ] boring as [ __ ]
What I don't understand, Jasper, is why
they go out if they're just going to
tell everyone they've got boyfriends.
That's why. And and what I mean by
everyone is I will see three or four
different people, approach the same
woman that I've approached in a bar, and
they get the same [ __ ] So, I'm
thinking, "Oh, yeah, these guys are
going to get somewhere obviously cuz
it's the way that I look or it's
something about me." So someone else is
going to get something in it. Nope.
Three, four different people get the same thing.
So this is the same old [ __ ] ain't it? So yeah.
No, I don't need to ask them if they've
got a boyfriend. They'll tell me within
the first message. If they generally
have a boyfriend,
they will walk away.
they will walk away or they'll say it straight away.
You know, if they're talking to you and
having to think, they don't have a
boyfriend. So, it's and I don't give a
[ __ ] anyways, bro. Like, you know what I
mean? So, that's that's that.
These things are not the problem. It's
not about these things are not the problem, bro.
Boyfriend or not getting numbers. This
isn't the problem. The problem is the leading on.
It's the toxicness that comes with it.
It's not about that. It is annoying. But
that one in Amsterdam annoyed me as well
cuz it's so obvious that she doesn't
have a boyfriend. You know what I mean,
bro? Like it's um
I don't know. That one kind of just
stood out because it's just it's
absolute [ __ ] It's absolute
Like same one with like when they study
abroad. They'll claim they're studying
abroad, right? But yet they they're in a relationship.
It is bollocks, bro. Absolute bollocks.
There was one I was speaking to and she
was from Greek, but she was from Greece.
Sorry. I And I generally think that she
did have a boyfriend because we was
talking and I don't know, she seemed genuine.
Um cuz I asked her who did you come with
cuz and she said so I mean
yeah I mean I believe that one but some
of most of them are full of [ __ ] I would
say but honest to God Mother's Life
7.5 of them are full of [ __ ]
7.5 of them were full of [ __ ] 100%.
I know. So, I think 2.5 is telling the
truth. Yeah, man.
Could be wrong, but
there's a lot of single people out
there. Loads and loads of single people out there.
Like I said, most I know a lot of people.
Most of people I know are single. Sorry. that started it. Yep.
Had to miss out. I answered some uh salted popcorn.
Heartbeat salted popcorn. Mm-
The point is it's
it's not worth it.
And there's people desperate to have
kids. That's the only way I can see it. on um
what the Snapchat.
Yeah, that's all they do. That's um
that's what they do. They lead people on.
That's all they do, bro.
There's some people greasy, they'll give
you their number. Yeah.
And when I say they ghost you,
they will ghost you, bro. And they won't
even block you. You will just never ever
hear from them again.
I remember I was in the shopping mall
where I where I was living at the time.
I think this must have been 6 months ago
and um I approached them. We're talking
they said about um how they um
we're talking they were playing games as usual. Um
then one day they just disappeared.
Greavvesy never heard from them again.
Never heard from them again.
It's all mind games with these people,
bro. It doesn't matter what age that they are. Yeah.
Grievy, are they interested in this
country or not?
They're are they interested in this
country or not? They're interested though.
Are they interested in this country? You
know what I'm saying?
Graves as watching Alice in Wonderland porn.
It was like Alice in Wonderland, but it
was a porner.
It was filmed in 1976.
Now the woman's all [ __ ] old.
Good old vintage B.
Good old [ __ ] vintage bomb. Virgin boy.
All these actors now are old. Is it crazy?
It's okay, Grezy. I'll just wait.
You remember what he said? Get out of
here now or I'll strangle you.
Oh, I'll strangle you. [laughter]
That's funny, isn't it? Yeah.
I'll strangle you.
That's funny as [ __ ] man.
Grieves, are you all right, Captain?
You all right, Captain?
We need to start saying that uh
more of them. Where's
Well, I'm going to pour myself a nice
cloak. Is that okay with you, Greasy Boss?
Okay with you, boss. There's
>> [clears throat]
>> Oh, where is he?
All right, captain. Right, captain.
Have you ever had Captain Morgan's
greens? I used to drink the white
Captain Morgans's. Yeah. And then the
next day it used to [ __ ] me, bro. Anxiety. Tired.
[snorts] [ __ ] hungry. Oh my god, bro.
I don't know how I used to drink it. I
used to drink the white one. That's the
strongest. I used to drink the white
one, bro. I was a crazy [ __ ] Now I just
tend to stick to beer if I do drink. No.
Yep. I never drink water.
Why would I drink water? It tastes like
nothing. The only time I used to drink
water is when I used to go to the gym.
Why would I drink water, bro? It tastes like nothing.
Who the [ __ ] Why would I do that?
It's all right. In the summer, I drink
water in the summer
and if I go to the gym, Greavesy.
Yeah. So does Coke. I drink Coke and tea.
That's the only thing I drink is Coke and tea.
Have you ever drunk Coke and had a wank?
It makes your dick burn for like 45 minutes. Yeah,
I used to piss in bottles. Me, Gregy.
Yeah, I used to piss in bottles.
My body don't need water.
I've been eating curry since the
umbilical cord got snipped. We How cute
is that? I've been drinking water since
the umbilical cord got snipped. Oh. Oh [ __ ]
Oh [ __ ] mate.
Nothing better than going to cinema and
having popcorn and coke.
Popcorn, Coke, and pick a mix.
If I go out approaching Saturday, will
this time be different?
Will it be different this time? So, okay.
So, how will I ever find anyone if it's
never going to be different then?
It's vile, isn't it? It's absolutely vile, bro.
So, how are you supposed to find someone in Grievy?
I'm joking. Uh, Greavvesy, I'm happy alone
just like you are.
Well, again, happy is not the right
word. It's more of a case of I'm not
going to disrespect myself in order to find someone,
especially when I don't have to. [ __ ]
that, bro. No way, bro.
No [ __ ] way.
That's ridiculous, mate. Yeah.
Yeah. If you didn't find someone years
ago, you're basically [ __ ] Yeah.
So, agree with you. Why do people on
Reddit keep saying that you'll find
someone and stuff then?
Are they just liars or what?
Cuz they say like, you know,
they say stuff like um
like uh your time will come and [ __ ]
That's what they say on um Reddit. Grezy, huh?
You like it when I go out drinking,
don't you, Grezy?
Don't you, boss?
Don't you like it when I go out drinking, boss?
Don't you like it, boss? Well,
Oh [ __ ] I don't watch Monty man anymore.
I haven't watch him for ages. I don't go
on anyone's channel, bro.
Nope. I don't watch Monty.
Now do the watch. Monty [sighs]
That boy excuse would do your heading,
wouldn't it, Greavves? It would do your bloody heading. Yeah,
you would think like these people
would actually give you a chance
considering they generalize all men.
Am I right, Gregy?
Like they say that they can't find good
men and stuff and they're creeps and
they're abusers and they're narcissists
and stuff and then when somebody finally
comes their way that approaches them,
they're not interested. So it's like who
can really give these people sympathy at
the end of the [ __ ] day? Think about it, bro.
We have to constantly go out and seek
for people that are different and no one
is. We can spend the rest of our life
and we'll never find anyone that's
different in the West, but they get
somebody that actually comes up to them that's genuine
and then they're still not interested. So it's
it's madness, isn't it? I mean,
you would have thought that's what they
would have wanted
considering when we see how we see how many people
and the thing is it's like they don't
really have options. They've got options
like I've said with their options are
desperate men that's never going to meet
them that are creeps and so their their
options is as good as none really.
They're not genuine people. They just
get endless attention. They're not real
proper options that they're getting,
believe it or not. They're just desperate people.
So they're basically the same as you really
think about it. cuz they don't have any.
You don't have any options, but they
don't have any genuine ones.
Think about it, bro. Serious. So,
they're [ __ ] basically the same that
like it's Oh, how do I say it? It's both
bad in different ways.
Yeah, they might be able to get sex with
like weirdos and Simpson [ __ ] but So,
that's it, bro.
Yeah, Jensen. It's weird, bro. But
these people that are messaging them,
you know, most of them won't even meet these women.
They're just online simps and they're
not genuine options.
You do realize that all of these
messages and the [ __ ] that these people get, you know,
it wasn't online dating. It was [ __ ]
Tik Tok that killed the game, bro. Even
3 years ago, it was somewhat decent.
Even 3 years ago, it was somewhat
It was still hard, but you still got success sometimes.
But now, no chance, mate. You can't even
get a date.
So, that's that.
I think it was Tik Tok that killed the game.
I think it was Tik Tok.
I think it was defo Tik Tok.
Dude, there's been a difference in 3
years, bro. An online date. Obviously,
Tik Tok's been going a few years, but
people been more on it now. So,
I think it's a few different things. Yeah.
So they actually get genuine people that um
will meet them and stuff and then
they're still not interested. It is
weird. It is very strange cuz I'm sure
these people want kids. I'm sure these
people want to meet someone, you know. Yeah,
that person on Snapchat basically is
another one not interested. Bob Bills.
Yeah, she wrote me a paragraph.
I'm going to do a video later on this
dating [ __ ] Anyways, cuz this guy on
Instagram says, "Where's your video?"
So, I said I'll do one later. I've been
meaning to do one, but I haven't. So,
we were just saying, Bob, well, I was
just saying how it's weird that these
women say that they can't find people.
They can't find genuine people cuz their
options are not genuine people, right?
They can't find anyone. But yet, when
someone approaches them,
in their own words, they tell you what you are.
you know, nice, sweet, all of the things
that you would think they want, but
somehow they're not interested.
It's a tricky one, isn't it, lad?
It's weird because she wrote as well
like, "You're sweet. Uh, thanks for
approaching me and talking to me and stuff." So,
it's like you're never going to come
across someone as genuine as me. So, why
would wouldn't you want that? I'm sure
these people want kids at some point.
I'm sure these or or I'm sure these
people would want to meet someone. So
why I just don't understand it. I just
And again, I'm not bothered. It doesn't
bother me, but I'm I'm
um just trying to see it from their
point of view.
It's just very very strange, isn't it?
You know, I do believe.
No, I don't believe in God.
I can't believe in something that I've never seen.
So, yeah, it is strange, Bob. It is strange cuz
we say all women are the same because
we've never been shown a different woman
despite our efforts. So, that's why
we're saying it. They say men are all
the same, but yet somebody will approach
them that's normal and genuine and
they're still not interested. So, it's like,
what the [ __ ] bro?
That's [ __ ] weird.
It doesn't matter whether I'm ready for
a relationship. It's the fact that they
generalize men. They say all men are the
same. They come across someone that's
genuine and decent and they're not interested. So,
and I don't and I was basically saying
that I don't understand how these women,
right, will go with these people that
beat them. They will go for these
[ __ ] I generally don't understand
it because if a woman gives me attitude,
I'm leaving. I'm gone. When that
19year-old started being a [ __ ] giving
me attitude, I [ __ ] her off.
But these women, Greasy, will stay with
people that beat them. Stay with people
that are [ __ ] choose these people.
They will generally choose these people,
which is mad because if someone gives me
attitude, I'm leaving, bro. And I'm
never coming back. And I've done it more
than once. So, it's strange, in it, bro.
They're very, very strange.
They go for people that like It's so
weird, isn't it?
It is. It is weird, bro. Very weird
why someone would choose toxic abusers.
It is strange, isn't it?
It is strange. Very strange.
[ __ ] me, bro. But yeah, Bob, that's how it is.
One of the numbers replied, stopped replying.
Well, I messaged them all again anyways
within a week. Um,
I'm starting it. Yeah,
I won't be putting myself through that
again for a very, very, very long time.
[ __ ] that, bro.
I think these men that do put themselves
through it need to really question their
dignity and their selfrespect at this point, bro. You know, mad.
They're [ __ ] bro. They are
And the thing is, Bob, yeah. How many more years?
Lovely bit of coke that went down there,
Gregy. How many more years, how many
more times do I have to go out and keep
giving these people the benefit of the doubt?
That's a question I'd love answered.
How many times or how long? How many different places,
you know, you have you have to go to,
you know, clearly.
It will never change, bro.
That's what I am, bro. That's what I am
doing. I don't care. I don't care about
it. Friday was a one-off, lad.
Friday was just a one-off, lad. I don't
care about it. I just done it cuz I
thought, "Fuck it." It there's nothing
bad to do about.
I had done sober approaches for very, very long.
So, I I didn't I just done it for the
sake of it. As ridiculous as that sounds,
it will never change, bro. It will never change.
It doesn't bother me, bro. I'm I'm I've
already got other aspirations. I just
done it as like a one-off.
That's why I'm not going out this week.
Well, I have planned with my sister. I'm
going to go out, but I don't really want
to go out.
Nah, it's not even that.
anymore because I know that it would
always be the same here.
So, there's not a thrill of it. It's
just I done it because
I don't know why I done it, but I defin
I definitely knew it were going to change.
Why do you think I wasn't pissed off
about it, bro? Because
what's there to be pissed off about? Why
do you think I wasn't pissed off the
whole time? I was bored of it. Yeah. I
was sighing a bit like
like a little Peterbelly sigh when they
say they have boyfriends. You just sigh
in it because it's just boring. But
yeah, it didn't piss me off, bro. Cuz I
didn't expect anything because I knew it
wasn't going to change cuz of obviously
the 10 numbers
and not getting a date. It's like it's
obvious it's never changing. So there
was nothing to really be pissed off about.
So that's why I wasn't pissed off. I
wasn't shocked, bro.
Doesn't shock me.
I'm not going out again, bro, for a very
long time, bro.
I'm not interested.
I will not be out again. Maybe eight
weeks, maybe. [snorts] So yeah,
for a long time, bro. A long time.
No point, matey. No point, matey.
Nope. No football bets, no drinking for
about 6 to 8 weeks. Nah.
Losing at 1:30 was depressing, bro. On
Saturday, even though I'm still up in that,
I'm still up. That's I'm not gambling anymore.
Who the [ __ ] is this?
[snorts] I'll just be like watching
videos and stuff.
130 on both teams to score,
but I'm still well up. I'm still well
up. So, I'll just be chilling, bro, and
saving to be fair. Um, that's it. Yeah.
Yeah, that vintage pool is addicting, bro.
Very, very addicting.
Bob bills. My friend said that they're
just not interested in this country
and I was trying to prove him wrong. I
said, "Oh yeah, you can't you can't
judge the whole country and stuff."
Yeah, he went Thailand. But I think he
might be on to something, bro.
I think he might be on to something
because if you go on dating apps,
nah, probably not to be honest.
I don't know when I'll be out again. Not
for a very long time.
Nah, not for a very long time, bro.
It's boring going out now. As you get
older, it gets boring.
It's boring as [ __ ] Yep.
It will never change.
So, I have to get used to watching porn now.
That'll be my life now. If I'm horny, I
just watch porn.
Yeah, I just watch porn. I used an
escort last week and the week before that.
You just watch porn all your life in it.
Well, dating apps don't work either and
approaching in bars don't work. So,
nothing works. So, that's that.
And believe it or not, cold approaching
has more chance of working than dating apps.
So dating apps don't work. Cold
approaching don't work. Approaching bars
I mean, for [ __ ] sake, even women in
pubs say they've got boyfriends. Bob,
it's not one thing that's the issue,
you know. It's not one method.
When I went to the pub with my friend, I
think about four people said they had boyfriends.
And this was in a pub, a busy pub. So,
it's not one thing, bro. That's the problem.
This is what people seem to think. So
when I called approach USA Izzy, that
was one that was one in a lifetime, bro.
Where they offered me their number and
hooked up with me. That was one in a
lifetime, bro. That would never happen
again on the street.
That will never happen again.
Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] about it, bro.
I The reason I've given up, bro, is
because [clears throat] it's not worth
dealing with their attitude, their
narcissistic [ __ ] ways, and the games
that they play. That's why I've given up
cuz it's just not worth it.
It ain't worth it, bro. It really really
ain't worth it to have to go through
that just to meet someone. Ain't worth it.
Unless you're a [ __ ] virgin or you
want kids. That's the only way I could
ever see it being worth it. It's not
worth it, bro.
And even if you get with one, they're
just nasty as well.
That USA was nasty, bro.
Yeah, maybe. Bro, I was thinking of New Year's.
Yeah, I was actually thinking that. I
was thinking that.
I was thinking that to be fair.
Yeah, I was thinking the same thing, bro.
Save your money till then.
It makes sense.
It does make [ __ ] sense to be fair.
Over that last week, the week before
that, still not a single date, Bob. Nope.
I don't care, bro.
I don't give a [ __ ]
Do you want me to read a message that
one on the Snapchat wrote to me? Uh, Bob,
I can read it to you if you want.
It's somebody I approached on Friday. We
was talking I was talking to her last
night. You want me to read it out? Yeah. One sec.
What do you mean they expect they expect
you to make the first move? Even when
you make the first move, they reject you.
What do you mean they expect you to to
to to make the first move?
When you when you make the first move,
they say they got a boyfriend or they're not interested.
What do you mean they expect you to make
the first move?
I'm Who's been making the first move for
the past 3 weeks, bro? When I've been going out.
When I've been going out, who's been
making the first move?
Me, bro. And they're not interested. It
hasn't been [ __ ] them.
So anyways, I'll read it out
because this is what I don't understand
with these people. Anyways, she wrote,
"Hey, hope you're okay. I'm going to be
honest and say that I'm not really
interested in getting to know getting to
know or meeting anyone at this moment in
time. You seem like a really nice guy,
and although we just met, my life is so
busy with education, work, and other
personal things. This is nothing
personal to ruled you. I just don't
really have the time to invest to meet
new people. Thanks for coming up to me
that day. It was really sweet. There's
no hard feelings and all the best to you.
So, this is what I'm saying with this is
that I don't care, bro, cuz I don't give
a [ __ ] But, I mean, obviously, we can
still wonder things. It's that they've
just said in their message, right, that
thank you for coming up to them. You're sweet. R.
So, surely to God, you've come across that, Raino.
So then they would give you a chance.
No, since most of these women think all
men are [ __ ] Yeah.
Why Why would they give you a chance?
You know, you're not ugly. There's
nothing wrong the way that you look. You
come across genuine.
I'm the most genuine person, Bob, that
they'll ever meet. And they're still not interested.
So they It's just madness, isn't it,
bro? But in a couple of years, they'll
moan and complain about all men. It's
weird, isn't it, bro? Weird. Weird,
weird, weird, weird.
[snorts] Excuse after excuse, [ __ ] after [ __ ]
But it's weird because you've obviously
come across that way because they've
wrote it. So you would have thought
that's what somebody would have wanted.
That's what you would want in a woman.
That's what I would want in a woman.
So, it's like it's strange
cuz Bob, we go out trying to meet
different women, but all of these women
are the same.
You know, we go out, right, trying to
find different people, genuine people,
but we can't find genuine people.
They're having a genuine person come up
to them speaking to them and they're
still not interested. That's what I'm
saying. It doesn't make sense. You know,
it doesn't make any sense at all
at all. At all, lad. And again, I don't
even care about it, but it's just an
example. It's just a figure of you know
what I mean? So
it is weird. Very weird.
It's always the same [ __ ]
It is local. It's central London.
And that girl lived in East London. Same
as me. She lives up the road from me. So,
it's always [ __ ] and games with
these people, Bob.
Always [ __ ] and games.
It's very rare you come across someone
that is actually even genuine. That's
that's how bad it is, bro. So,
what do you mean I asked for a date?
Yeah. I said to them, "Let's meet on t
on Thursday." I said, I no, I said to
them, "Do you want to hang out on
Thursday?" And then that's the [ __ ]
they come up with. So [snorts] yeah.
Yeah, that's the [ __ ] they come up with. Yeah, man.
I said to him, "Let's hang out." I
didn't so much ask for a date. So, yeah.
Yeah, Bob. It's weird, isn't it, lad? Weird.
Very, very weird.
Oh, [ __ ] me.
Imagine I was a virgin. Hey, Bob.
Okay. Well, what's the other alternative then?
Well, dating apps don't work. So, I
mean, you kind of have to approach.
It's either you approach or nothing.
You have to approach. There's no other
way. You're not going to meet anyone through friends.
You're not going to meet anyone on
dating apps. So, that's that's the only
that's the only thing you can do.
That's the only thing you can do.
unless you leave the country. So, so
put more effort into the approach. I've
put effort into the approach. I've done
different approaches multiple times.
It's not about It's not about me. It's about them.
They're not interested.
It's not about a pro effort or not
effort. They are just not interested.
That's that's that.
And it's not even about that either.
Again, it's not one thing. They play games.
So, I mean, it's them, bro. It's not me. It's them.
There's no more effort. Yeah. I'm still going, bro.
Oh, this Russian one said that she she
just messaged me just now saying I've
just arrived actually.
Speaking of the devil, she just replied back.
I'm going to message her saying, "Oh,
when you come back to London, we should
go on a date."
But it's not about more effort into
approach. I remember I approached
someone, they stuck their thumb up at me.
I approached someone
then they I said, "Oh, what's your
name?" They said straight away not
interested. The problem is is them.
And you'll know that as well because
it is it is generally generally it is them,
you know, especially in London. They're
just stuck up as [ __ ] One just put
their thumbs up. One put their thumb up
at me, bro, on Friday. Yeah.
Yeah. The problem is definitely
definitely definitely them.
Think about it. Someone that puts their
thumb up. Someone that says they're not
interested straight away. How long do
you think it takes to get to know someone?
No, I'm not going to play it. Call.
They're in [ __ ] Russia.
Okay, maybe they did go to Russia, but
that's not the point, bro. Even if
they're telling the truth, most of them
were full of [ __ ] anyways. So, [ __ ] them, bro.
That is strange, bro. it. [sighs] Yeah.
It's not about more effort. They're not interested.
It's It's not about you or effort or not effort.
No, I'm not going to Russia. No.
So yeah, they're just not interested in
this country. Bob Bills.
I can't get I can't even get any matches
on these bloody dating apps.
Let me message them
I'm kind of trolling when I'm saying this [ __ ]
I said to her cuz I'm kind of trolling.
I said, "Oh, nice. When you're back in
London, you should let me go. We You
You should let me know. We should go for some cocktails.
We could go for some cocktails
or duh, you can't find a slag. It's
England, bro. They're not interested in England.
Why do you think Yeah.
Um you uh
Why do you think Yeah. When you go on
these dating apps, you match with people in Thailand?
Have you noticed how you match with people and
um you match with people in Thailand.
You notice that
it's because they're just not interested in England.
So even when you're in England, you
still get matches in Thailand.
Yeah, I told her we should go for some cocktails.
And who cares if I can't find a slag? I
don't want a slag, bro. I don't give a
[ __ ] about it. Like I said, it was a one off. Nah,
not me, matey.
I never get embarrassed.
I got an Indian's number as well.
I got some good numbers on my phone, you know,
but none are bloody interested. Bloody, bloody.
I have so many numbers on my phone, bro.
No, I'm not doing that, bro. I already
done that Friday. I'm not doing it again.
I've got nothing left to prove. I don't
need to go out tomorrow and approach
sober. I done that Friday.
I approached about 50 sober. I'm not
doing it again, bro.
I don't need to do something that yields
the same result.
A sex offender. What are you What are
you talking about, you idiot?
Why am I going to go out and disrespect myself?
I'm not doing that, bro. I done that on
Friday for the lows. I'm not doing it again.
It's not ever going to be any different
here. So, I don't need to waste my time.
[ __ ] that, bro. [ __ ] that.
I approached about 50 people sober
Friday to get one number and one
Snapchat. You're going to get [ __ ]
bro. I'm not doing it again for a very,
very, very, very long time
to the point where I'm almost dying a
boredom. I'm not interested.
So yeah, man.
I don't want mental health problems,
bro. I'm good. I want to be stable.
I don't want to be I want to be stable.
I don't want mental health problems,
bro. I'm good. Jesus Christ. So yeah. Uh
yeah. Yeah, I did I I did think
something was up.
Yeah, bro. I did think something was up
to be fair. Too many stuck up [ __ ] in this country.
Yeah, that's that's the conclusion that
I come to. Yeah.
Yeah. Something is definitely up, man.
They're very stuck up and we're not
having the same conversation. So, you're
done. Bye-bye now.
I'm never going to get a girlfriend in
this country. So, why are you saying if
I got a girlfriend? I would never get a
girlfriend in this country.
Why? Why are you talking? If I got a girlfriend,
how and why would I get a girlfriend?
Have you got brain damage, bro?
Just You don't seem to process any of
the things that I tell you. Are you all
right, bro? No offense.
Just checking to make sure you're okay.
We've just spent the past 30, 40 minutes
me telling you my experiences and you've
just gone on and spoke about something completely different.
Are you okay, bro? You know,
is there something wrong with you or something?
I've literally told you I went out on
Friday and I approached 50 people to get
one number and one Snapchat. Bro, I
don't think I'm going to be getting a girlfriend. [laughter]
I don't think so, bro. You know,
bro, you can't even get a date. I don't
think you're going to be getting a girlfriend somehow.
By you, I mean me. It's figure speech.
Why would I go out approaching sober
tomorrow? Why the [ __ ] would I do that?
Just to get the same attitude problems,
the same make believe boyfriends, the
same mind games. Who on earth would want
to do that, bro? Unless they were
clearly just [ __ ] around. Nah, man.
I'm just going to chill, man. Watch some
movies. Go for some walks.
I don't know, man. Not sure.
It's the winter, is it? So,
I don't enough women's numbers on my
phone. I don't need to go out and speak
to any more people.
So, what you think? If I go out
tomorrow, it's all of a sudden not it's
all of a sudden going to change.
Really, really, really, broaching.
I'd be I'd be better off doing the
lottery, mate, cuz I'd have more chance
of actually winning the [ __ ] Euro
millions than it ever changing in this
country as far as the women go.
Yeah, I went out Friday cuz I had
nothing better to do and it was a
oneoff. I ain't doing that again, bro.
For a long time. I don't know when.
I have no reason to. I'm not
disrespecting myself. I like to be stable, bro.
Yeah, but I'm not going to go out every
day disrespecting myself. I'd rather be
by myself, bro. I'd rather be single.
I'm not going out every month hearing I
have a boyfriend hearing I'm not
interested dealing with mind games
and there's a chance not really cuz I've
been at this for 5 years and I've not
really had that much success
so not really
all that would happen is if you went out every day
the only thing that would happen is you
would just get numbers that lead you on.
I don't even think you'd get a date.
What do you think, Grezy?
If you went out every day, approach him. Nah,
you would just get led on.
And it would [ __ ] up your mental health
so bad you wouldn't even be able to keep doing it.
Nah, you would. It would it would [ __ ]
with your mental health so badly that
you wouldn't even be able to keep doing
it. That's why you'd have to take
breaks. And even if that never happened,
you would the only thing that would
happen is you would just get led on.
You're not going to meet someone that
gives you a chance. It's very, very,
very, very slim.
No chance of winning the lottery.
So, it's not worth my time. So yeah,
that's that. Yeah. Well, duh.
That's why I've given up.
That's why I've given up, bro.
Then there's no good women out there
anyways. So they would be good if they
were different, but they're not
different. They're all the same. So
that's why they're only good for sex.
They're all the same. They're all toxic.
So they're toxic. They're bullshiters.
They're narcissists. I'm not dealing
with their [ __ ] bro. Just to be with
one of them. No way, bro. I'd rather be by myself.
I'd rather be my [ __ ] self, bro, and watch porn. What's up?
But no, I don't I think if you
approached every day for a month, you
would just get led on.
What do you think, Grezy? What do you
reckon would happen if you went out
approaching every day for a month?
Nah, I don't think I still don't think
you would meet someone. No.
What do you think, Reevesy?
After big effort, bro, I've tried for 5
years. I've tried more than anyone in the world.
I've already tried more than everyone in
the world, bro. I don't need to go out again.
I don't need to go out again, mate.
I think this guy is trolling me, bro.
Bro, there's I don't need to make more
effort. I've already tried more than
anyone in the world. I would say I've
met more women than anyone in the world.
That's how bad it is. No, no, no. I'm
I'm actually really thinking that greasy.
I I think I generally have met more
women than well more than 80% of people
in the world.
Yeah, I'd say more than 80% of people. I
think I have
80%. It's got to be, bro.
If not more than anyone in the world.
So, I know this stuff, bro. I've been
dealing with this [ __ ] for years. So I
meant a stat.
Well, if you're genuine, why are you
saying I can decide after big effort?
I've tried more than anyone in the world
already. I don't need to go out again.
Isn't that right, Gregy?
I really want you, but I don't think you want me.
I want you, but I don't think you want me.
Yeah, I've already done that.
I've already tried every day. I don't
need to try again.
It's not about I I I won't quit
attitude. I don't want to deal with
their [ __ ] I'm not disrespecting myself. You know,
it's not about [ __ ] I won't quit. I'm
not dealing with their [ __ ]
Their [ __ ] is not worth me dealing with
their shitty games. So, that's what I
decided. That's my choice. See, the
thing is, Greasy, you've got to weigh up
the pros and you've got to weigh up the
cons with it with this thing.
And if the juice ain't worth the
squeeze, then the juice ain't worth the squeeze. Simple.
I would quit because I want to quit
because they're full of [ __ ] and there's
not much to gain by the end of it. So
it's it's that that's that. So
I'm not dealing with their [ __ ]
Only a loser would would would go around
every day [ __ ] approaching knowing
what they're like, you know? [ __ ] that, you know. So yeah, that's it.
You're always going to get that I have a boyfriend [ __ ]
so I can't be bothered with it
in it. Steven Howard.
I really want you.
You're addicted to it, lad. You say
that, but you're out most weekends. No,
I'm not out most weekends. I stop for 6
weeks. You're good of it, too. That's
the [ __ ] reckon it must be. You ain't
got the funds. Women want to do nothing
to get money. Uh, I do have the funds. I
can go out every week if I wanted to. I
spent about £1,500 in the past two
weeks. Yes, I have got the funds. I've
got more than enough money. Yes, I do.
But okay, bro. Believe whatever you
want. I'm not going to sit here and
argue with you. If you don't think I've
got the funds to go out, okay, I don't
have the funds to go out. Whatever.
Okay, bro. I'm completely skinned.
I mean, what the [ __ ] bro? Seriously?
Like, is that what you want to hear?
You know what I mean? It's like, what the [ __ ]
Why wouldn't I have the funds to go out?
I can go out every week if I want to.
I've been out the past two weeks. Oh, yeah.
But I mean, yeah, they want
millionaires. I mean, even if you have
loads and loads and loads and loads of money,
that's not even enough.
I remember I used to have thousands and
thousands and thousands and thousands
and thousands. It still never made a difference.
It doesn't make a difference unless
you're a millionaire.
Bit like what you used to. I used to
have thousands and thousands and
thousands and thousands and thousands, bro.
It wasn't even a joke. I had money
coming out my ass. I still got money. I
still got enough money. A lot of money. But
I can still do what I want. But yeah,
just lie and say you're a millionaire.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's as easy as that, isn't it? Yeah, bro.
Yeah. Cuz they're totally going to
believe that you're a millionaire. Yeah, bro.
but I'm not out most weekends at all.
I'm not out out most weekends. I went
out last week
cuz I said I was going to go out last
week and the week before that. I'm not
out most weekends, bro. That was the
first time in six weeks. I won't be
going out again until
mid December the earliest. So that's that.
I was going to go my sister Saturday. We
was going to go for a drink, but I just
can't be bothered, bro. I'd rather just
chill, you know, Greavves. I'd rather
just chill out,
you know, just nice chill out with a dressing gown.
Like [ __ ] going to the barbers, getting
your haircut, going out, dealing with
stuck up women, being hung over the next
day. I can't be annoyed with it, bro.
All right. I can't be asked, lad.
There's so much effort.
I think that's so toxic, you know. [clears throat]
That's starting it.
Well, it will never change, will it?
And you'll never change, Grezy. So,
you'll never change.
So yeah, I'm not going out disrespecting myself.
Why would I go out every week dealing
with their [ __ ] just for a very very
small chance to find someone? I'm not
doing it, bro. I'm not doing that [ __ ]
No way am I doing that. Just to get
[ __ ] over in the end anyways. even if
somebody was to get with me.
But no, I haven't seen King for a little
while. Maybe next week
just to get [ __ ] over in the end anyways.
[ __ ] just go Thailand. just go to
where they're actually interested,
you know. So,
even Ant-Man's friends in Thailand now
and he's good-looking. He's a
good-looking guy and even he went Thailand.
Yeah. Even he went Thailand.
That's mad how he went Thailand as well, isn't it? Country's dead.
The country is dead, bro.
You get You'll get banned from a bar for
speaking to people as well. The country is [ __ ]
The country is dead, bro.
The country is dead.
Nah, it's not nothing to do with luck.
I have been out multiple times since
April and I've not even got a date. It's
it's not luck anymore. It used to be
luck a couple of years ago, but
nah, it ain't luck, bro. It ain't luck.
Luck is you putting money on roulette
and winning or losing.
Luck is you putting a football bet on
and you might win or lose.
That's luck. You know, this with these
women has been going on for years.
It's nothing to It's not luck. They're
all stuck up. They've all got the same attitude.
No amount of luck is going to change
that. So, Thailand it is.
No, it's not locked, bro. It isn't lock.
no, no, not at all. I just think that they're just
stuck up with unrealistic expectations.
No. And there's a lot of people in the same position.
I was just born in the wrong times. Simple.
That's all it is.
I was born in the wrong time. Didn't
meet anyone when I was younger. So
that's where we're at. Nah,
they just they just got unrealistic
standards and they're stuck up.
It's not a And if he was born in the 1980s,
this wouldn't we wouldn't be having this
conversation. So it's that's what it is, bro.
But like I said, 3 years ago, you'd
actually get dates. Now you can't even
get a date, which I find is strange how
you can't even get a date.
But yet somehow people think that you're
going to suddenly meet someone when you
can't even get a date.
And I don't really want to deal with
them anymore as well, bro. It's just toxic.
They've got attitude problems. They're
toxic. I'd rather just not, bro. I'd
rather I'd rather not. So,
yeah, I tried Puff, bro. Yeah.
Few years back.
I don't like dating apps.
I'm on hinge, but nothing. Nope.
Did you? Lucky you, man. Lucky you. Yeah, lucky.
Lucky you, matey.
I can't even get a bloody match. Jesus Christ.
Maybe it's cuz I don't look fully white or something.
I don't know.
Maybe cuz I don't look fully white.
That's how shallow these [ __ ] be, bro.
Maybe because I'm not 6'2.
See, this is the thing, Bob. People will
tell you that women don't go for looks
and they're not [ __ ] superficial and
it's about personality, but it's [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] bro. because they go for
looks more than men do. And I'm not even joking.
And I've done a lot of social
experiments on this, bro. I've done a
lot of uh online social experiments on this.
So, I know basically what I'm talking
about, which is physical, but it's weird
cuz I'm not even ugly. But it is like a
physical thing with them. People try to
lie and say that it's not, but bro,
trust me, it is. It is. to start with it
and it's ethnicity as well. Like it's a few things. So
I can't remember. I ain't used puff for years.
So yeah, I ain't using it for years, bro.
But yeah, it is a physical thing with them, Bob.
It is physical. Um, like ethnicity and stuff.
Um, it is, bro. Even though people try
to deny it,
I don't know why they do cuz men admit
they're shallow and [ __ ]
It is weird.
You all right, Captain?
Joker. You all right, Captain?
I wasn't expecting you, bro.
Yep. Same [ __ ] bro. Same [ __ ]
Nope. My dad died when I was 11. >> [snorts]
>> Joker, I'm off Thailand, bro. I'm off Thailand. Joker.
No, he wasn't. He was white.
Murder will never change will it joker?
It will never change will it joker and
you will never change. So
that's that bro.
H would never change, would it?
Well, it will never change, will it? And
you'll never change. My mom's half Turkish.
Well, it will never change, will it?
And you will never change. So that's that
games. You will never change.
Joke. I almost shhat my underpants the other day.
Yeah, Greavves. I almost shhat my underpants.
It's not [ __ ] funny, bro. I had to
run my [ __ ] underpants. Yeah.
[snorts] Yeah. Yeah, I'm off the
Thailand Joker because the women just
aren't interested in this country.
They just aren't interested in this country, Joker.
That's what Ant-Man said.
Yeah, I realized they were just not
interested in England, Joker.
I get matches with people from Thailand.
Yeah, they ain't interested in this
country. Heat. Heat. Yep.
Now I'm off Thailand. No car. I'm gone, bro.
Oh, how much did you lose? 14 Maxwell.
Bro, people enjoy it. I don't give a
[ __ ] what people enjoy cuz I don't care,
man. These people are sat on YouTube
every day. They don't even leave their
house, bro. Me going out drinking and
getting rejected. I even get numbers,
bro. It's better than anything they can
ever do, lad.
These people are sat on YouTube skin
ain't got no life, bro. Can't even leave
their house, bro. You think I give a
[ __ ] what they think?
They're [ __ ] sat losers. Ain't got no
money, ain't got no life.
You know what I mean? [ __ ] them, bro.
Who cares what they think? You know,
you lost 600 pound today. Jesus Christ.
That's not good, bro.
Who cares what these people think, you know?
They even got a life these people on
here, bro. These haters.
[ __ ] them, bro. Who cares what they think?
I've won some good money the past two
week uh two months. I bought some nice garments,
bro. [ __ ] them. Who cares what they think?
Yeah, I've won some good money the past
two months. My trainers and jeans cost me £400.
Been spending money weekly, so Yeah.
Yeah. I'm speaking to my friend from uh Amsterdam, bro. Yeah,
we're talking from things from like 10
years ago. Grievesy, we remember everything. [laughter] >> [laughter]
>> No, I don't find it entertaining. I
don't give a [ __ ]
I think they're all [ __ ] Would
you go to Amsterdam, Greavvesy? Nope.
Just met a bunch of women that weren't
interested last week. Joker and the week
before that. Bang some escorts. That was it really.
I went to the dentist as well.
Depressed. No, I'm not depressed. I'm
just [ __ ] tired.
Not depressed at all, man. Just tired. I'm exhausted.
Yeah, I went to Amsterdam on my own.
Make myself God's gift to women. No thanks.
Yeah, I went out and stand by myself. I
remember that. I'm not depressed, bro.
I'm just tired. Why the [ __ ] would I be depressed? The [ __ ] Just tired. Yeah.
Where the [ __ ] is Joseph Bara?
I was a millionaire.
>> Yeah. Joseph Ferrar. Yeah. I call him Joseph Farra.
That's my little name for him.
He's a [ __ ] He's a proper He's proper
addicted to gambling.
Oh gosh, Roozy. I'm so tired.
Oh gosh, I wish King was here to snuggle me. Yep.
Yep. I won't be doing another bet for a
long time and I won't be going out
drinking for a long time. I get addicted
to the peace and quiet, Greavesy. You
see, you get addicted to the peace and quiet.
King's my Well, King's a dog that I know
that comes to see me sometimes.
I was laughing at the tenants, Grezy. I
was thinking about the old house I used
to sublet and it was funny, bro.
It was funny. Some of the things were really funny.
Do you remember when they woke me up at
4 in the morning talking, bro? They woke
the whole house up. That black guy, bro.
Oh my god, man.
It doesn't matter how much I made monthly, bro.
But just know that
it was funny.
It would never change, would it?
Yeah, bro. It was £300 a month. Yeah. [snorts]
Yeah. Yeah. £300 a month from I subleted
a four bedroomedroom house and I was
getting £300 a month. Yeah.
Yeah. Totally, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. That's what it was.£300.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Yeah. £300 for a four bedroomedroom house. Yeah. Yeah, man.
In in London next to a train station. Yeah.
Bro, stop asking stupid questions. Jesus Christ. Anyway,
this was funny.
No, I'm completely skinned.
No, I'm completely skinned, bro.
I've got about 50 p.
Yeah, I'm I'm probably going to starve
to be honest within the next week. Yeah,
I'm skint, bro.
Yeah, totally, man.
I'm going to be dying. I'll be outside motion soon.
Yeah, completely skint, bro.
Yeah, I'm completely completely skinn. 50p, bro.
Sucks to be me, man. What am I ever
going to do, you know? Yeah. Yeah, man.
I got 50 p, bro. Do you want to lend me some money?
See, if you ask stupid questions, you
get stupid answers.
You know, you're not talking to Timmy
Aldidge. You're talking to me, bro.
You know, you ask stupid questions,
you get stupid answers. Isn't that right, Grezy?
Uh, I can't buy my mini mugs. Well, duh.
I got 50p. Of course, I can't even
afford a can of Coke.
No, I can't even afford a can of Coke. So,
I'll never be scared, bro. I'm not stupid.
I got escorts twice the past two weeks.
Drunk, [ __ ] around, bro. All gums.
It was good, man. Good. No, I just want to chill.
Just have a little chill out, Joker. In
my little nestles now.
I'm getting too greedy, aren't I?
[sighs and gasps]
Yeah, too greedy.
By Joker, did you touch Isabelly's boobies?
Did you ch Did you touch Isabelly's boobies?
You know when someone asked me that,
Greavvesy? It's not even funny. It's just immature.
No, it's not funny. It's immature.
I wonder who that account is that keeps
coming on and [ __ ] with me. Bro,
[snorts] why are you in your 40s and a
keyboard warrior that ain't got a life?
Answer me that question and answer your question.
Bro, you people are on You're turn up.
You people are in no boat to talk about
anyone's life, bro. You are in your 40s,
sat on YouTube, no job, skin as [ __ ]
ain't got a life. Worry about fixing
your life first before talking about other people.
Fix your own lives before talking about other people.
Use them in your 40s. skin, no life, no
job, no nothing, bro. Like, fix your own
lives before talking about other people.
That's facts, bro. That is actual facts.
Actual actual facts, bro.
You need to fix your own jobless skin
lives before talking about other people.
That's another thing. Am
I lying though, Joker?
These people in their 40s sat skin on
YouTube ain't got a life, right? And
they try to talk about other people.
They ain't even got a life, bro. Look
what I've been doing in the past 3
weeks, bro. You've seen the [ __ ] I've
been up to. Have you [ __ ] You know,
I've been active, bro. active. These people
just [ __ ] on YouTube ain't got no life
every day. There no room to talk about anyone, man.
Yeah, Diddy. Good for him. He's another
keyboard warrior like you. No one cares, bro.
No one cares. He's another little weasel
like you, bro. He will never meet anyone.
Get with the times. Get with the times.
Give it a dime. Give her a dime. Give
her the dimes.
I went to the dentist on Friday. Joker. Uh, bye-bye.
Nope. It lost.
No, bro. They need to get a life. They
need to turn their life around before
they bounce off of other people's lives
cuz they ain't got a life.
So, [ __ ] off, bro.
They need to turn their own life around first
before judging others.
And no, it lost. A little football bet lost. Johnny £130 done. Oh no.
No, I had like a hole in my tooth,
so I had to get a fill in.
Oh, yeah. I had to get a fill in, bro.
Yeah, they gave me a filling, lad,
with the back of my mouth.
Yeah. Oh gosh,
I'm so cozy. I don't want to have a
haircut and go out drinking in the cold,
Grezy. I want to chill in with Franklin. Oh gosh, Oh,
this is lovely.
Just lying in bed. Oh, so nice. Yep.
I don't get the nutrients from USA
Izzy's boobs anymore, Joker.
So, I'm going to have to get vitamin tablets
cuz I used to get the
I used to get the vitamins and the
nutrients for my boobs. But when she
left me, I need to go to Holland and Barrett tomorrow.
I need to go hold in the B and get some vitamins. Crazy.
I don't need to budget. Joker,
I don't I don't need to budget. Oh gosh,
Grooves is my friend. Oh gosh.
I don't need to budget uh Joker
and they've all got boyfriends. Crazy.
Jo, I don't know why these women go out
if they're just going to tell everyone
they've got boyfriends.
Weird, isn't it? Yeah. Oh. Oh gosh.
See you tomorrow. Bye.