So I just have to order something.
Yeah, I bought the UGG bridge, bro. £165 it cost. Yay.
Yep. Bought him, bro.
Who's going to say ug booties? They're ugbs.
Virgin boy can't do that music, can he?
Nah, Virgin boy can't do that.
What? Why can't Virgin boy do that? Cuz
he's [ __ ] skinted in a [ __ ] skin thing. That's why. Because Greavvesy
because he's skinting skin flint.
Isn't that right, Greavvesy?
Imagine a skin flint. Right.
He's He's [ __ ] skin at that. He's
[ __ ] skin, man.
He's an absolute [ __ ] skin.
No, never, mate.
Skint and a [ __ ] skin flint.
Skin a [ __ ] skin flint.
Love that, mate.
Absolutely love that.
Does he? You owing people money now,
Grey. Oh, gosh darn it. What's wrong
with you, Grey?
Are you [ __ ] owing people money? Are you mate?
Oh gosh darn it.
You're like greasy. Oh god. Wrong of you.
What is wrong with our [ __ ] greasy?
What is wrong with you? Gravy. Oh,
what's wrong with you?
165 quid they just [ __ ] cost me, mate.
H. [clears throat]
Oh, gosh darn it.
Yeah, I'm going to watch a boxing match
uh boxing boxing match on Saturday.
So, yeah, that'll be fun.
Someone bought me a ticket.
Is that all right if I go to that greasy boss?
Okay with you, boss.
>> [clears throat]
>> Oh gosh darn it.
More fit than me. I'm not thick.
No, I thought you was talking about the [ __ ] virgin.
I thought he was talking about the bloody virgin.
He's [ __ ] mad. That [ __ ] virgin.
was a skin virgin at his mans.
That skin version's [ __ ] mad.
Proper proper virgin.
Anyways, I'll be back in a bit.