Yo, cuz it won. That's why
I'm not [ __ ] Good girl. Yeah.
Well, I messaged all them numbers again.
Followed up. Not a sausage.
Seems more and more hopeless every time you try.
Oh, when there was someone on a dating
app, they uh ignored and as soon as I
said something neg negative, they replied. Typical.
It never changes, does it? Never changes.
It will never change. Never. Same [ __ ]
There's always be the same old here.
Same old, same old, eh? never changes.
Oh god. Anyway, starting it
that is that Yeah.
and you'll never change.
Never change. Never
depressing in it, mate. Life in this
country is depressing as [ __ ]
What the [ __ ] What? All
right. Do you know what I done? [ __ ]
greasy. I [ __ ] ordered a [ __ ] Burger King.
They gave it [ __ ] cold. Tried to give
it cold. I said, "Send it [ __ ] back."
Then they then they said it's been
delivered and it hadn't been delivered. So, um,
yeah, I'm not I tried getting the money
back and they wouldn't give the £18
back. So, I thought, [ __ ] it. Can't be
asked. I'm not ordering food again.
My mom's ordered the food for me. I'm
not ordering food again, bro. [ __ ] that.
I'm not ordering food again here.
So, it's going to be restaurants
um or nothing really. That's that.
Anyway, saying something for one another.
Yeah, exactly. Because he's a white
knight. He's a s. Guess what? Uh, Greavvesy,
I just wrote um,
bear in mind, women aren't all the same.
So, I messaged this woman uh yesterday
at 11 uh sorry, 10:27 p.m. saying, "Hey,
what made you swipe?" Why? Right. We
should go to Nando sometime. Naturally,
they didn't reply.
So, I wrote at Oh, 7 5. I hate women,
man. Bam. Responded straight away. I
have a [ __ ] job, you psychopath, and
a life. Um because you're being a [ __ ]
I'm not in the mood of replying as a
means nothing. So it's actually bad
grieves. They actually try to justify
why they ignore normal nice messages but
reply to negative ones. They actually
just like try to justify and victimize
themsel instead of saying, "Well, I
replied to it because I wanted to reply
to it and I didn't want to reply to the
other one." Then I'll be, "Oh, well, at
least at least they're telling you
straight." They actually they're so
narcissistic that they try to justify
why they're being an ignoring [ __ ] and
then ignore to only negative messages.
But remember, Grezy, all women aren't the same.
I'm not so sure. I say that with a sad
face cuz we hear about these people not
being the same, but you have to admit,
Greavvesy, they have a lot of
similarities, don't they, for people
that aren't the same. I mean, would
would you agree with that? Would would
you agree with they do a lot of the same
things for people that are apparently
not all the same?
I mean, I'm I'm sure you could agree
with that. I mean, we don't we don't
agree on, you know, most things, but
and then she didn't even let me reply.
She said, "Because you're being a [ __ ]
and I'm not in a mood, me not replying
for a day means nothing. I've now come
on to him for the first time since
yesterday morning. Of course you did. So
as soon as a normal negative message got
sent, you you was just there straight away.
Isn't that a coincidence, Grezy? You are
going to die alone with the mentality
you have. Go have the day you deserve.
Yet she replied to that. I know.
Contradicted, isn't it? Um, oh, so you
Oh, so you should have rep Oh, so you
would have replied eventually. You'll
die alone as well. Who wants somebody
that only replies to negativity?
I mean, they're there straight away when
a negative message is sent, but when a
normal nice message is sent, bam,
they're nowhere to be seen.
Strange, isn't it, mate? You know,
none of them are innocent. They're
[ __ ] They're worse than men.
They're worse than men. They're [ __ ]
That's what they are, bro. They're
absolute [ __ ] And I believe I
believe different when I'm shown
different. And that's that. I'll believe
they're not all the same when I'm shown different.
Isn't that right, Grezy? You know.
Yeah. Yeah, the white nighting is is I
mean again if if a woman is getting
beaten up on the street for no reason
then I mean if someone intervenes I mean
it's a different story or um you know if
if someone robs someone you know there
is a there is a time and a place you
know to to inter intervene but yeah
they're just white knighting they're white knights
proper proper white knights and I don't
know why they do it I generally don't
know why they do it bro
it's embarrassing And I mean, they're
[ __ ] I know they're [ __ ] but
I don't really say anything about it
much anymore cuz
um I mean, what's there left to say, you know? So, yeah.
So, you can't stand white knights either. No,
I was watching Ed Matthews.
You watch Ed Matthews, is it Greasy? Yeah,
you watch Ed Matthews. Ed Matthews is uh Yeah, man.
No, I didn't see it.
Ed Matthews. Ed Matthews.
You know what's so mad is that even he
gets rejected by some people. Imagine
that. Someone that's got all that money,
that following still gets rejected by
some people. He gets like 40. Bro, this
guy gets like 40% of women.
Imagine that. Someone like him. All that
money. Well known. So what chance does a
normal person have? Just think about it
like that, Greavves. Think about it like
that. Yeah, this guy is, you know,
people know who he is and whatever and
he's just like an average looking guy
like he's well known. He's got money and bro
even he's getting rejected by 40% of
people which is less than half.
So what chance would a normal person actually have?
You know what I'm saying?
Would you agree with that? Grezy,
what what chance would a normal person
have really if you think about it?
You wouldn't have any chance if a guy
like him I've w I've watched this guy
walk around [ __ ] Liverpool
and he gets the same thing well by by by
60% of people and the guy's well known
and the guy's got money as well but the
money thing doesn't really it's all
about fame so what chance would someone like me
What chance would someone like me have, bro? None.
I messaged these numbers um earlier,
Greavvesy, like a Scottish one and like
a few of them saying, "Oh, you want to
do something on Friday?" No reply. So, I
can't go out now anyways, bro. I can't
afford to be wasting money at this
moment. I could do it, but I'd rather
put the money towards something else now. So,
Nah, that's why I need to go to that
boxing match, I
just not interested in this country, are they, Grezy? Nope.
Oh, you know that one that was lying
about her uh me being too old for her,
me not being Muslim. I caught her on
Reddit today, Greavves. messaged her saying um
so her um
I said to her, "Oh, remember when you
was lying, say you couldn't get with me
because I'm not Muslim?" No. And I said
to her, "Isn't it against your religion to lie?"
She uh she blocked me. "Isn't it against
your religion to lie?
I'm looking at my memories.
Nothing, bro. Just [ __ ] up a Burger King order.
Waiting for it again.
That's starting it.
We just chilling, bro.
So that's 20. Yep.
Tried bringing the food cold. Went back.
Said they delivered it. Didn't tried to
get the £18 back and couldn't get the
£18 back. So [ __ ] it. I don't care.
Can't be bothered, mate. I just I just
won't be ordering food again. Yeah,
just won't be ordering food again.
Yeah, I won't be ordering food again now. Um,
so that's that
cuz we're having the same problem where
they're going somewhere completely
different and I don't know how they're
going somewhere completely different
when the dress is [ __ ] right.
staying up somewhere completely different. So,
no more delivering food.
Yeah, no more.
So, yeah, no replies e.
It's disgusting, is it? Disgusting.
It's [ __ ] vile, bro.
All that money as well, bro. All the
money that's gone into that. [ __ ] hell, bro.
All the money I've spent going out and [ __ ] Bad. No hope.
No hope, man.
What do you think?
What are you going to do, Greasy, then
in the future? I bet I put you right off
in it. I bet I put you right off.
Ah, [ __ ] hell. But I Yeah.
What is it?
Is it still coming?
What are you going to do, Greasy? You're
[ __ ] in it.
I don't need to deal with them anyways.
I don't go out anymore, so I don't need
to deal with it. These white knights and [ __ ] Yeah,
I need to buy a new phone, bro. I need
to buy a new phone that's not blocked at some point.
It's still coming. Yeah, you're right. What's up?
Yeah, I need to buy a new fire at some point. Why? What?
These lot need to sort their [ __ ] out.
These people these these people need to
really sort their [ __ ] out. You either
get along or you Okay, I'm going to I
need to go downstairs and look at it.
You don't want the hugs? I'll give them
to someone else.
You don't want the Uggs, mate. I'll give
them to someone else.
I'll give him to USA is he?
That wouldn't be a bad idea, would it?
What do you think, Greezy? Give the UG
boots to USA is the uh
imagine that would be a lovely site. Oh, bless
like [ __ ] mate.
You're going to see my mood change in
about a week greasy for the better.
Obviously, it's still early days, bro.
But it will change. It will change very soon.
You will see when you give up dating,
you feel so much better.
So, so, so much better.
But you're not dealing with that [ __ ]
But apparently they're all different.
They're not all the same apparently.
But they're not all the same.
They just do a lot of the same stuff and
act the same way,
but they're not all the same.
Just have so many similarities.
They wouldn't or everyone would.
And you know the thing is speak speaking
the truth. Yeah. You know when I went
out on Saturday Yeah. I I approached
about 50 women sober, bro. And most of
them were complete [ __ ]
to be honest with you. Attitude
problems, full of [ __ ] act like they're
better than you.
But they're not all the same apparently.
Um, women aren't all the same. I don't
know how many more women you have to keep meeting.
I mean, I I generally don't know how
much more money you have to waste, how
much how many more you have to keep meeting.
I I don't think I'd ever know.
That's what makes me laugh is when they
say they're not all the same
and when they dismiss your struggles,
>> they just miss your struggles as well. >> Yeah.
So bad, bro. It
Where you going yours? Why?
Lady says she doesn't want the
Okay, I will give them to someone else.
I'll give him to next door. Huh?
Nothing. I said if you don't want the
URGs, I'll give them to next door.
Not a problem at all, mate.
Right. This bastard Burger King is coming out.
Why do they give the Coke's [ __ ]
wall? I don't understand.
They always give you the Coke's [ __ ] wall.
Yeah, I got a bacon double cheese XL
with extra bacon and extra cheese. Okay,
with you, boss.
I'll show you in a bit. Okay. Oh, lovely.
One second, bro.
Look at that. [ __ ] hell. Oh,
I forgot to tell you, G. I got three
pieces of chicken earlier, a fine middle
breast, and an egg. M M.
I love food.
Where the bloody hell was Joseph Ferrar?
It doesn't feel the same without Joseph.
I'm going to I'm going to read him with
going out, aren't I? Yep.
All that money wasted. Still don't have anyone,
but people already keep saying I'm going
to meet someone here.
Crazy. How are you supposed to meet someone?
No one's bloody interested.
You know what? It will do me good. You know,
it will do me a good state then.
It will do me good.
It's so toxic going out.
Who is it?
You reckon if I go out on Saturday, I'll
get a date? Would
you re approaching music?
Whereas if I go out on Saturday, is it
going to be any different? Cuz
I don't really
I don't really have money to be wasting and stuff.
So I need I'll need to know now if it
will be any different.
Is it all right if I go out or we'll do that after
it be different?
Groovy, but Antman said it would always
be the same. You know this.
Is Antman right or wrong? H
is that man right when he says it will
always be the same?
No, but he said to me it will always be
the same. You know this.
You know what he's referring to.
It's so nice eating now with my toothpaste.
Since I got a filling
since I got a fill in.
[ __ ] sick of people telling me I'm
going to meet someone
on Reddit telling me I'm going to meet someone.
What do you think the chances I'll meet
someone? Grezy, honestly.
Like what's your honest opinion on this
situation? No trolling, no [ __ ]
What's your opinion?
Oh no, I think I I think I dug myself in
it there when I said I want your opinion, Grimsy.
What's your opinion?
No, but like
what I'm saying with you, what's your opinion
on this situation? How is it ever going
to change? What do you What should we do with that?
Oh gosh, that burger went down like a tree.
What's your opinion? What What do you
think about it?
What's your opinion? How do you think
it's going to change? What What's the solution? Because cuz
every woman I keep meeting is the bloody
shame. They keep doing all the bloody
same things. They keep bullshitting,
pretending they've got boyfriends, acting narcissistic.
They're all being the same. Really?
You reckon if I give the Do you reckon
if I give the Ugg boots I bought lately
to USA Izzy? She might feed me again
if I buy if I can buy the UG boots.
What is he that I bought?
What do you think?
You reckon she'll be my mama again?
You reckon she'll be my mama? Huh?
Dark boots busy.
What do you think? You reckon she'll be
my mommy again? The 165 boots they're worth? No. Yeah, it's mine.
It's mine. Mhm.
Yeah, but they're £165 UG boots.
Squeezy. They're They're quite expensive.
They're expensive boots.
Mama, I got you some UG boots. Mama
said, "Yeah, I will get back with you if
you give me the boots.
I can't do that, bro. Um
I can't do that cuz of lady.
Who the [ __ ] is that?
There's a lady in it.
Ladies, the boots.
I'm drinking some Coca-Cola, Grezy.
That's what you do all day, don't you,
Grevy? You sit in bed,
you sit in bed getting really fat, don't you?
Don't you, boss?
Oh, you silly goose. s.
Oh, bless you.
Bless you then if you do that. Oh, bless.
I'd love to know where these different women are. Huh?
Virgin boy says they're not all the same.
They're not all the same. You don't know all women. Yeah.
They say you'll meet someone greasy.
Yeah, the weather is [ __ ] to be fair.
I'm at my bloody wits end.
then Belgian Punts were laughing at us.
Hey, you right, Slim?
Well, I've still not got a date
scheduled for this week and I'm at 24
numbers now, Slim. And none no one's bloody interested,
you know. Had enough of it. Interested?
Maybe if I went around the street
offering the Ugg boots, maybe somebody
would go on a date with me.
I've had a bloody enough slim.
Bad enough of it, Slim.
No, no one's bloody interested. Um, I
can put some of the combos up, Slim.
Um, I also spent a lot of money as well, bro. Uh,
they're just not interested in this country.
Yeah. 24 over the past about a month and
not a sausage.
Not an absolute sausage.
But they tell me on Reddit, Slim, that
I'm going to meet someone and stuff.
still telling me I'm going to meet
someone on Reddit, mate.
And uh I don't know what the problem is, Slim.
They've all got bloody boyfriends. I
done 50 approaches on Saturday, Slim,
and I only got one number and one
Snapchat. I've had a bloody enough of it.
I'm going to um I'm going to have to put
this I'm going to have to do a video on
this [ __ ] and show all of these numbers
because I've had a bloody enough of it.
I'm at my wit's end.
Yeah, I have actually. I have packed.
I've got some mug boots coming, LJ. And
they were more expensive than the ones
that you've got. They were £165.
You don't have £165.
You can't afford that kind of wonder, mate.
You skint, mate. You You're [ __ ]
skint, mate. You're [ __ ] skint.
You're [ __ ] skate.
Slim, where are you gone? Have you run away? So,
so this person gave me them their
number. They actually bracketed where I
actually met them and they still haven't replied.
Mate, we can't keep doing these four 500
pound weekends, matey. We can't keep
doing it. We We'd end up skin like Lord
J if we carry on, mate. It's not good.
No, but in all seriousness,
this is [ __ ] disgusting, bro.
But it will never change, will it? It
will never change. It will never change.
It would never change, would it?
So, they've typed their name.
Uh, it's not how much money I've spent
on them. It's how much money I've spent going out.
So, last week was £300 and the week
before that was £600.
So, and I didn't get nothing, mate. Not
even not even a date.
600. I think we're about £1,000 in now.
Maybe over. not a sausage.
And they've also put their name where
I've actually met them and nothing.
But don't worry, you'll meet someone.
You'll find someone. They tell you on
Reddit. You know, it would happen, mate.
I' had to bloody enough of this limb.
A lot. Yeah. I done 50 approaches to get
one number, lad.
Yeah, 50 approaches to get one number
and one Snapchat. It was really bad.
It's disgusting, bro. Really bad. I
messaged them all again today to see if
uh but nope.
Cuz I'm I'm I'm away Saturday, so I
didn't mind meeting on Friday. But nah, nothing. Absolutely nothing.
I don't know what the solution is, Slim.
I don't know why it's so hard. So So
yeah, it was bad, bro. Well, sober one.
There were sober ones. There were sober
ones. This was sober, but even still. Um, yeah.
I mean, Sim, I don't know why people are
still telling me I'm going to beat someone.
I mean, you get banned in places now for
even talking to someone. So, I mean, for
[ __ ] sake, bro. Like, it is never
going to change, isn't it? It's clear
it's never going to change, bro. It's
never going to [ __ ] change.
It's clearly never going to change, is it? Yeah,
>> this depression is [ __ ] it.
What am I supposed to do? Go out and
spend four or five four 500 every [ __ ] week?
Who can do that, bro?
Or for the rest of my life, you know?
It's not sustainable, bro. Not sustainable. you know. So, yeah.
I don't know where they have the idea
that you're going to meet someone, Slim.
I'd love to know where they get that idea from.
>> What? You You're going to go out one day, right?
And all of this [ __ ] is going to stop. Really?
Really, mate? Really?
I don't think so, bro. I really don't think so.
I think that's seven numbers, was it?
Yeah. Yeah, I lost my virginity a long time ago.
What did I tell you about self-p
projecting your virginity onto me? It's
not going to change the fact that you're a virgin.
I lost my virginity way before you.
Well, you're still a virgin. So,
no, I already lost my virginity, matey.
I put a porno up and you're still
arguing with a porno. So, that just goes
to show how simple you are. Anyways,
one, two, three, four, five, six. No.
Oh, yeah. There was one. Oh, [ __ ] Seven.
One second. No. No. One sec. One, two,
three, four. No, that's not Wait, wait, wait.
One, two. No. One, two, three.
There you go. That was a seven. Nothing.
We're over,000 pound in now. Nothing.
Not a single day.
Seems dodgy in it, bro. Seems dodgy.
I can't believe you're calling me a
virgin even though I prove that's I've
proved I've had sex.
The projection on this community is is
is bloody it's bloody unhealthy, mate. Yeah,
there was this uh woman called Lola as
Yeah, I haven't. Okay, bro. Whatever you
say. Go selfrelect. Go self project your
virginity on another channel. You borrow. Uh
yeah. I don't know what we're going to do, bro.
Where's the mat?
You have to go to Thailand, bro.
Did you ever go to Belgium? I met some Belgian lads
uh the other day.
They're from the They're from the Dut side.
Would you ever go to Belgium on a little trip? Gy Gravesy,
I'm talking to you. Graves e Gravesy
Graves I'm talking to you Graves. Oh gosh.
Why don't you go to Belgium? Oh gosh.
Have you ever been to Belgium, Steven Howard?
Have you ever been to Belgium?
Do you even know? Have you ever been to Belgiland?
I met a a couple of Belgium lads the
other day. They said they were from the Dutch side. Yeah. India.
Right. You laugh at Timmy Aldridge,
don't you? Greasy.
Why do you laugh at Timmy Aldridge?
Do you want me to do a uh video showing
uh these numbers?
These numbers, Greavves, I'll do a video
later showing uh the most recent numbers.
I think I'm going to title it, when is
this [ __ ] going to end? When is this
bloody when is this [ __ ] going to bloody end?
I think that's a good title, is it?
Oh, bless you then.
Bless you then, Grezy. Bless you.
What will be a laugh? What? My little video.
I don't think it's funny. I think it's bloody depressing
and it will never change. [ __ ]
Why do they keep banning me off [ __ ] Reddit, man? Yeah.
What do you think will happen if I go
out on Saturday, Steven Howard?
No, I ain't going out, bro. [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] that, bro. I ain't going out. I
ain't going out, bro. No way. [ __ ] that
It's the same old. Yeah.
So, I message that girl tenant.
I'll be like, "Maya, how are you, Maya?"
But then she's going to be like, she's
going to be like, "I want my £150."
Oh, that [ __ ] you, bro. I'll give the
Uggs to her.
No, I ain't talking to that [ __ ] bro.
No, I'm not going out, bro.
Well, I am going out cuz I need to go to the boxing.
But no, I wouldn't, bro, cuz that means
I need to get my haircut.
Pointless. Might as well chill in.
Is this the same old [ __ ]
What was that?
Yeah, I'll stay in a nest for like
I don't know, bro.
I don't know. We need to really figure
out a plan, bro. Seriously. All jokes
aside, something's got to give, bro.
This is just
Just the same.
>> This is just the same old [ __ ] Honestly,
it's just the same old [ __ ]
What? The out boots. The boots.
All right. Steven Howard, why does why
why does Reddit mods fear different opinions?
That's why anyone I speak to on Reddit,
I try to get them on Instagram quickly.
The Reddit mods are losers.
They fear different opinions. Steven
Howard, they're going mad. If anyone's
got a different opinion,
stay in the nesticles and watch some uh WWE
Yeah, these Reddit mods. Yeah,
it's all about power though, is it?
It's all about having that power. N. Oh gosh. Yeah.
So, how am I going to meet someone
anyway? Steven Howard,
you're never going to meet someone in
this country, matey. Never. No.
No, never happened. Never. Yeah.
lying to me about what?
You all right? Candy.
I messaged all of them numbers again um
today like a followup to see if I could
get like a date on Friday. Candy man and
not a sausage.
Not a bloody sausage.
Not a sniff of interest.
But Candyman, people on Reddit tell me
that I'm going to meet someone.
Yeah, I'm all packed. But they tell me
that I'm going to meet someone. Candy
man on Reddit. They tell me that I will meet someone.
That's what they tell me on Reddit. candy.
They say you have to keep trying and
stuff. I say I tried last week and I
tried a week before that and a week
before that and this you can't meet
anyone. I've had enough of it man.
No, for real, bro. It is it is [ __ ] Yeah. Sucks.
I'm bit sleepy. Yep.
Yeah. No, I'm awake, bro. I'm not going
to sleep. S I'm not going to sleep.
It's such a depressing country to live in. England,
you're always constantly like getting
[ __ ] from women. The weather's [ __ ] You
try to gamble to get a buzz. It's just a
horrible, horrible country. Like even in the summer,
it's bad, bro. It's really bad.
It is really [ __ ] bad, lad.
Yeah, it's really bad, bro. Yep.
They dismiss my struggles,
isn't it? People might dismiss my struggles.
[ __ ] these Reddit [ __ ] mods ban
people to feel powerful. It's pathetic, man.
banning just to feel powerful.
It's [ __ ] sad as [ __ ]
It is sad, bro.
I think the Reddit mods were bullied, to be honest.
I think they were bullied.
Let me message my friend from Canada. I
haven't heard from her for ages.
Wonder what happened to her.
It's not going to turn out bollocks.
You're not going to have the problems
that you have here there.
People are actually interested there.
They're just not interested in England.
They just wasn't interested in England.
They just aren't interested in this country.
It's not going to turn out bollocks.
Hold that [ __ ] virgin boy.
Hold that virgin boy mate.
Virgin boy will be going Thailand next. Steven Howard Yep.
Where's Greasy gone? Oh gosh.
Oh, he's a [ __ ] virgin. He's a
[ __ ] big virgin, ain't he, mate?
Oh, that's skin plonker. Yeah.
I'm unblocking this girl tenant.
I'm going to troll this [ __ ] bro. my uh
she's a [ __ ] slag, bro. Oh
yeah, I told her she's a [ __ ] bro.
This was months ago. She's going to try
and get that £150 out of me in it. She
ain't getting [ __ ] all, mate.
She can [ __ ] off, bro.
She was a [ __ ] Yeah. Mhm. My uh
We're going to do this 500 pound on the
both teams and score Steven Howard.
That would be lovely, wouldn't it?
That will be [ __ ] lovely.
I remember when they cleared the whole
house out. Yeah. And she was going to go
back to the house and and the [ __ ]
locks have been changed. I was dead, bro.
No, you would never you would never
forget. Yeah. The last day of the house.
You'll never forget it, bro. You'll
never forget the last day of that house.
It was jokes. They cleared the whole
house out, mate.
They weren't leaving anything. He bought
my TV, the washing machine. That whole
house got cleared out, boy.
His cousin was a bit loud though. A bit
loud. His cousin was a bit loud, man.
Bit loud, bro. Bit bit bit too much, you
know. Steven Howard.
[ __ ] hell. Yeah. The whole house
could clear now in it. Yeah. Yep.
this guy was like, "Oh yeah, you haven't
tried meeting you haven't tried meeting
women at your hobbies." That would be
exactly the same thing. Just because
you've got the same hobbies as someone,
it doesn't mean anything. Say you
approach somebody at the gym, right?
Let's just say for I've never done an
approach at the gym, but let's just say
you done a cold approach at the gym.
Yeah. Okay. They could still reject you
just cuz you've got the same [ __ ] Yep.
Just because they've got the same
hobbies, it doesn't mean they're going
to get with you.
No, it wasn't the one I cut from there. No.
What suicides are you? I'm 9 and a half 10.
Yeah, nine is the most common size. Yeah.
It will never change, will it?
I was watching uh Ed Matthew, Steven Howard.
One second, lad.
How much money do you have to last you
the month now, Steven Howard?
How much you got now to last you after that loss? >> Mhm. Yeah. Cash.
Cash bank account. Yeah.
So, what like £800? Maybe at 800. Yeah.
Yeah. So, how much is it exactly to last you?
So, how much exactly to last you then? 8 850.
Oh, another one calling me a virgin even
though I proved I've had sex.
Yeah, I think I've got I've got like £1,200 now.
I got 1,200 pound to last me. But
obviously I went out last week and the
week before that, bought some UGG boots. So, um,
yeah, I'm all right now anyway. So,
what knows, man.
I'm out Saturday.
Oh, I'm out Saturday. Huh?
[ __ ] me, bro.
How's that lasting you though? How's
that lasting you, man?£800
850. It's a bit tight, isn't it? Yeah,
you crazy bastard. Yeah.
What do you mean I can double that
within a month? What the money that I've got?
Yeah. But don't forget, I've I've I've
done a lot, bro, the past month. I went
out last week, spent a ton, got an
escort. Week before went out, spent a ton escort.
Week before that, um,
bought the trainers, bought the
jeans, bought the UG boots. So still it?
Yeah. You got your bills paid?
I need to pay my Franklin one.
You mean if I stayed in a month, I can
double the money that I have? Is that
what you mean?
I've got like 50. No, I got a 50 bill coming out.
So, I got a 30 bill, but that's at the
end of the month.
So, you said if I stay in, I can double
that money that I've got.
I am staying in, bro.
I've already gone out and [ __ ] I've
already gone out lots. I've already met
more than enough women, bro.
Going out again.
Yeah, very scared.
Yeah, very scared, bro.
Was he telling me that I could double it?
Steven Howard, was you telling me that I
can double it if I stay in a month? Yeah,
I've got about 20 pound, bro.
I get paid on the fifth.
Yeah, I get paid on the fifth.
I'm Steven Howard, so Yeah.
So, yeah. Do you reckon I'll be able to
double it up then, Steven Howard? Then I
should be able to double it up then, shouldn't I?
You've got 850 to last you a month, Steven Howard.
You've got 850 to last you a month. [ __ ] hell.
That's funny, bro.
Well, I'm not going out for a bit cuz
I've been out loads anyways. So, I'm on
a detox now.
I'm on a bloody detox.
Yeah, I'm on a detox. Like I said, I
went out last week, the week before, the
week before. [ __ ] that, bro. I'm not
doing it. If I had if one of them
messaged me back today, wanted to go on
a date, then I would have went out. But
I'm not doing it.
I'm not doing it, bro.
For that [ __ ] [ __ ] off.
I got the Yeah, I got the UGG boots. I
got my jeans. I got my trainers. So now
I'm just going to chill.
Save. Probably go out mid December. Yeah. Nah,
I'm chilling out, bro.
So what should I do? Just chit out now. Stephen Howard
What? So what? Just chill out until the
what? Just chill out until next month. Yeah.
One second, bro. I'm going to come back
live. I'm just talking to this person. Hold on.