Yo, I don't know why these people
[ __ ] talking. They're just going to
block you the next day. Same old Peter B.
Same old [ __ ]
How we doing, man?
Hi, Jasper. You right.
I was speaking to someone off Reddit
yesterday and then they disappeared.
Peter belly sign it. You know the Peter
Belly sign, mate. You know the pet side
that's the Peter belly sigh.
[sighs and gasps]
You like the Peter B.
Am I not on my way to the airport? Well,
I'm going on Saturday, so no [ __ ]
Anyways, you can [ __ ] off. You create
the same atmosphere on my channel. [ __ ]
off. Jasper, how we doing, man?
Anybody find someone in this country, Jasper?
It's the same [ __ ] with these people
every time. I'm bloody sick of it.
I'm [ __ ] sick of it, bro. I was
speaking to someone on Instagram
yesterday from Reddit and then they all
of a sudden blocked.
How many more people do you have to keep
bloody meeting? How much more money do
you have to keep [ __ ] spending,
Jasper? For [ __ ] sake. You know, it's
just a question, bro. It's just a question.
They keep saying that all women aren't
like that. All women aren't the same.
But [ __ ] how much more money do you
have to keep spending? How many more How
many more people do we have to keep
[ __ ] meeting? I just don't get it. I
seriously don't get it.
Same attitude, same [ __ ] same
mannerisms, same mind games. [ __ ] me,
bro. How many more people do you have to
keep bloody meeting?
Jesus Christ. We've got to be up to like
the 10,000 now, you know, Jasper. Yeah.
What do we do, eh?
Bro, I don't give a [ __ ] if it could be
worse or it could be better. I don't
give a [ __ ] about other people that are
worse than me. Other people that are
better than me. I said this to [ __ ]
ad man. I don't give a [ __ ] about people
that are worse than me. I'm not
interested. I'm not interested in people
that are [ __ ] better than me. [ __ ]
hell, bro. Jesus Christ. I'm I'm only worried about,
you know, no other [ __ ]
No other [ __ ]
What? You You want me to go out again
and spend another £600?
You want me to go out again and spend
another 600 [ __ ] pound? You know
what? Again, I've already done that like
three times in a [ __ ] row. [ __ ]
sod off about go out and spend another
600 [ __ ] pounds. I'm not doing that.
What? What do you think I am? [ __ ]
rich or something? I'm [ __ ] not.
Why are you comparing me to Maveli?
My situation is bad. My situation is
bad, bad, bad, bad, bad.
It's really, really bad, bro. Like, you
should have already met someone by now
that I'm 28 now. This is the age where
people should stop playing games. And
it's just the same old
Breezy. Like, I'm not even winging. I'm
just saying it how it is, bro. It is
literally the same old [ __ ] I'm I'm at
24 numbers now. Not a single day.
Not a single day. I followed up some
numbers yesterday as well. There were
some numbers from like two weeks ago.
Nothing. Not a sausage.
Where these people get the idea you're
going to meet someone? I shall never
[ __ ] know. I shall never know, mate. So yeah.
Yeah. Well, what if I what if I stay here, Greavvesy?
Well, what if I stay here? Then what?
>> Mhm. Or what what happens when I come
back here in 2 weeks? Then what
then? Okay. No, what happens? Yeah, but
obviously I'm going to have to come back.
So then it's going to be the same old
again with these women. The same old [ __ ]
as it will always be.
Do the boots came by the way.
Yes, but Jasper, it's the only thing
that you can do.
But it's the only thing that you can do.
You know, when you're here, that is the
only thing that you can do.
So that's why you need to leave wherever
that country might be. You know,
I spent a lot of I'm just going to show
everyone the Ugg boots. By the way, the
UGG boots come.
I bought them for my mama. Where's your 10,000 times? >> Oh, [laughter] boots.
Hello. The brand spanking new.
>> Do you like them? M. >> Yeah.
>> You should You should tell them. You
should tell [laughter] them. your little 165 quid.
I thought they cost 165 quid. Yeah.
£165 they cost me the Ugg boots.
Yeah. So, £200 jeans, £200 trainers, 165
UGG boots. Spent £300 last week. spent
£600 a week before that. It's getting
pretty hard to substain this lifestyle,
mate. You know,
it's [clears throat] getting uh it's getting um
it's getting pretty hard, matey,
just to think if you stayed in for like two months.
I'm watching a boxing match this week.
I don't lose [ __ ] hope. You know, if
you if you was this age and you didn't
try, right, or you tried a couple of
times, then yeah, there'd still be hope.
But the amount of women that I have met,
it's clear they're all the same. You
know, I'm I'm I'm different than [ __ ]
you know, most people my age. It's not
also the fact that you're 28. It's a
fact of how many people you've actually
met and no one can show you otherwise.
So, doesn't matter what anyone says
really. So, that's that
Yeah. No, I'm not meant to be in
Thailand. I meant to be in Thailand on
Saturday, which I've said multiple
multiple multiple multiple multiple
times. So, I don't know why you're on
here now saying, "Oh, are you you are
you not on your way to your airport? Are
you going to Thailand?" No, because I'm
going on Saturday and it's not Saturday. So, no.
So, I don't know why you coming here
making stuff up. Lord Jed the same
thing. Who said that we're going on
Thursday? I said I'm going on Saturday. But yeah,
and I'll be back in two weeks. Back to this [ __ ]
to someone on Instagram. Um, yesterday
Candyman from uh Reddit and then gone
like [ __ ] [ __ ] magic.
They were gone like [ __ ] [ __ ] magic.
The [snorts] next day, gone like slap magic, mate.
It's a [ __ ] madness, isn't it?
When will this [ __ ] ever change? Yeah.
Never change, mate. Never change.
It will never change.
Where's my [ __ ] controller, bro?
Imagine I was a big Tik Tocker and had
loads of followers.
I can't believe that's the world we live in now.
That's why it's so unhealthy, you know,
like Instagram and stuff. That's the
world we live in now.
It's a madness, isn't it?
Proper proper madness.
It's madness, isn't it, Candy man?
[ __ ] madness. Someone on Reddit told
me to not lose hope.
Huh? Not lose hope? Really? You're
telling someone like me to not lose hope? Wow. Absolutely. Wow.
Like I told you, bro, the only reason we
go out is we do it for the sake of it
now. Like we we actually just do it for
the sake of it.
Obviously, it's never going to change,
is it? So,
I could have actually booked another
holiday with all that money I've spent
the past two [ __ ] uh two months.
It's madness, isn't it?
Do you think if I go out today
approaching I might get a date wheezy?
If I go out drinking and approaching
today, do you think?
Re I get date for tomorrow or something. [clears throat]
Madness in it, bro. Madness.
Okay. So then what do I do when I come back then?
What do I do when I come back?
Yeah. Okay. But I'm going to have to
come back at some point, aren't I?
Yeah. But what about when I come? Yeah.
But I'm going to have to come back, aren't I?
Yeah, but what about Yeah,
but then what if I don't meet someone
and I come back Yeah.
Yeah. But then what if I don't?
It'll be the same.
Do you know what I find so mad is not
the fact that I haven't found anyone,
Greavvesy. It's not about the fact that
I haven't found anyone. It's the fact
that you haven't even got a date since
April. A [ __ ] date. Like, not even
like an actual date, bro.
24 numbers in and not a single date.
Over £1,000 spent. Not a single date.
But they still tell you you're going to meet someone.
You know what I'm saying? They still
tell you that you you're going to bloody
meet someone and stuff, mate.
H. Bye-bye, [ __ ]
No spastics on my channel.
But they still tell you that you're
going to meet someone, Grezy.
Am I wrong in saying that there's no
hope here? Am I actually wrong in saying
that there is no hope here?
Am I wrong in actually saying that?
I don't think I am.
I don't think I [ __ ] bro. No,
they've all got the same attitude. Oh,
have you seen that account, Greasy?
Have you seen that account, Grezy? Um, Autumn Rose,
I said, "Filters."
She said, "They wouldn't even help you,
mate." I said, "I'm not your mate."
And they clearly haven't helped you,
have they? He was like, "Well, you
clearly think they have done something
to point it out, hun. This stupid [ __ ]
mate. What is it with these women
calling people mate? It sounds horrible.
It sounds really, really horrible. What
is it with these women calling people mate?
This sounds so vile, bro. It sounds It
sounds vile. Anyone saying it to be honest, you know? Don't know.
Don't care to be honest.
So, it's what I was saying to man
earlier. He says, "Oh, it clearly does
bother you about these streamers." He
says, "No, it doesn't. I don't care
who's better than me, who's not better
than me, who's got more money than me,
who's got less money than me."
You know, I don't really care to be
honest. I've lived I've lived the life.
I've lived a good life. I'm still living
a okay life is. I don't give a [ __ ]
about you know, you know. So yeah,
so yeah, it's madness. It is a madness.
It's impossible to [ __ ] get a date in
this [ __ ] country,
not interested in this country.
But it's not even the fact that they're
not interested. It's the fact that they
play games. It's like you'll never come
up to someone and they just straight be
honest. Never. You'll never get honesty.
So, it's not even really that, is it
really? play games, lead people on.
They do what they do best and that's
what they always do. Doesn't matter how
doesn't matter how old they are, you know.
So, I followed up. I even said to one
greasy that I I'll, you know, I'll come
to Manchester next week. Nothing. Not a sausage,
which it wasn't it wouldn't even been
easy if I had to go up there to be
honest. That is [ __ ] bad, bro. really really bad.
I'd believe it if you was at least
getting dates, but you can't even get
dates. There is generally no hope here.
Really is no hope.
23rd, it's got to be about 23rd number
now. Nothing. And that's got to be
within a month, to be honest.
Uh, yes. And it won't be to prove the
hate is wrong. It will just be because
I'm doing it. I don't need to prove the
I quote haters wrong. Because even when
you prove the hat is wrong, they still talk [ __ ]
I've shown more money than them. They
still talk [ __ ] I've shown me having
sex, they still talk [ __ ] So no matter
what you prove to these people, they're
always going to chat [ __ ] anyways.
So there's no proving people wrong
because even when you get proven wrong,
you still talk [ __ ]
You know, I have I have people on here
call me a [ __ ] virgin when I've had
my dick shoved down a woman's mouth.
Um, when I've been next to women in bed
and they still call me a virgin, I'm
thinking, "What the fuck?" Not that it
bothers me, but it's like, "What the
fuck?" So, whatever you prove to these
people, they just c that [ __ ] anyways, basically. So,
uh, it's a [ __ ] community. It's full
of low lives.
low lives that ain't got a life that
just sitting all day self projecting
basically. Yeah, most these people don't
leave the house. So,
but yeah, it's a shame about the women
thing, Codine. I'm uh 23 numbers in and
not a single date.
Not a single date.
Madness. Absolute madness.
It's some madness, bro.
Nope. I never said I was going to Thailand today.
I said I was going Saturday.
Can't believe I'm have to [ __ ]
cross the [ __ ] pond just to find
someone. It's a madness. It is a
What is it with these women, Cody? I
really don't understand it.
They've all got the same attitude.
Look, I even followed up and still none.
It's It is mental, bro. Really is.
I'm not sure, bro. What's >> [snorts]
>> I don't know. And it's like they'll
speak to you normal one day grieving and
the next day they switch
because they can only keep the fakeness
up for so long cuz that's what it is
with these women. They're fake fake and phony, bro.
I It's I'm not going to Thailand
tomorrow. Do you just make stuff up as
you go along?
Do you people just make stuff up as you go along?
I think I think you're just making stuff
up now. Firstly, you're saying I'm going to Thailand
today. I didn't Oh, it's Thursday today.
I thought it was Well, I think it was
Wednesday. And now you're saying I'm
going tomorrow. You just making stuff up
now. I think I think they're just making
stuff up now, Grezy.
You know, they're just making stuff up.
You know, that's what they're doing.
They're just just they're just just
making up the dates now. Rey,
guess what? I won't be here when I'm in
Thailand. I'm getting briefed.
I'm not going to be hearing that.
Nah, bro. It's uh Saturday.
I've had a bloody enough, you know, dog.
I've had a bloody enough. I didn't get
any dates from last week and the week
before that, dog. When is it ever going
to bloody change?
My friend in Australia said, "I think
you've collected enough data now to know
that it's never going to change." Yeah.
Yeah. Well, it won't, would it?
and the amount of money that's uh
No, I'm going to Thailand.
I'm going to Bangkok, Thailand. Yep.
Where's my um Where's my emot? Where's my remote?
Greasy, I lost my remote.
That's that is it. I got a nose bleed.
What the [ __ ]
I haven't had a nose bleed in ages.
Never you mind what airport that is.
That's for me to know you to never find out.
I know what you're trying to do.
I'm not telling you what time I'm
staying in. Bro, these little games are
not going to work. You're talking to me,
not Monty Man or Timmy. Remember that.
Yeah, I'm not telling you.
I am not telling you.
You'll see the videos when they're up. So,
so why do a lot of these women say mate
as well? It doesn't sound good. It's
horrible. It's horrible when even when a
man says it for [ __ ] sake.
They've all got the same attitude.
The same attitude.
But they're not all the same cuz you
haven't met women.
Doesn't matter how much cash I'm taking.
Never you mind.
Never you mind, matey. Yeah.
Yeah. That's fine, bro. That's fine.
If I saved the money, yeah, the past
month and a half and I didn't go out,
I'll probably be able to do it again.
Just like betting on the football and whatever.
You don't need to know. Stop asking me
questions, bro. You're going to see me
when I'm there. That's it.
You're going to see me when I'm there.
Going to a restaurant today.
No, I didn't. I've never put flights up.
Never. Hey, Bo. Are you on YouTube
again? No life.
If you comment for the first time, I'm
going to have to ban you, son.
Cuz you should be out with your mates,
not sat on YouTube typing to me. I'm
going to have to ban you. I'm going to
Something smells fishy. It's probably
your mommy's [ __ ]
It's probably your mama's your mama's
[ __ ] that smells fishy, mate. Nothing
fishy from this side, mate.
No, nothing fishy from this side, mate.
It's probably probably your mama's [ __ ]
Probably your mommy's [ __ ] Yeah,
I know. I'm going to have to ban you.
Why are you not out with your mates?
You're sat on YouTube. I'm going to have
to time you out. I don't want to see you
sat on YouTube. No life. So, we had to I
had to time him out, bro. I had to time
him out. I want to know why he's sat on
YouTube and he's not out with his mates.
Triggered. Oh, man. You need to think of
some new words, bro. In all seriousness, triggered.
Stop repeating you [ __ ] spastics.
When are you spastics going to come out
with some new sayings?
That twiggarded thing is so boring.
Hell, you bunch of spastics. Think of
some better comebacks.
Jesus Christ. Oh gosh darn it.
Oh gosh darn it, mate. You know.
Yeah. I don't lie. I don't lie at all.
Never you mind. You're going to see me
when I'm there. Don't you worry about
that. If I'm not there, right, Saturday,
then you can give me grief, can't you?
You don't need to worry.
I mean, think about it. Do you really
think somebody's going to tell you the
exact time and date that they're going
for you little low-life grasses that
don't leave your house to try and [ __ ]
the whole trip up? Come on now, man.
Come on. [laughter]
Like look at the [ __ ] that you're
asking. Do you think people are really
really that stupid?
Seriously, you little lowife grasses to
try and [ __ ] the whole trip up.
Isn't that right, Grevy?
Oh, I got banned. Um,
I got banned from Hinge to be fair.
Grieves. Yeah, I got banned from Hinge. Yeah.
Madness in it. It'll never change it,
will it? It will never change.
Oh, it's there. Yeah, it will never
change, will it?
Sucks, is it, bro?
It does suck. clown at Grezy.
I can't believe I've not had a date the
past the past month.
Greasy, can you believe it? I can't
believe it, mate.
I really really can't believe it. Madness. Absolute madness.
Isn't dates where you actually get to
know someone? I fault. But no.
Why did Ant-Man say to me, "It would
always be the same there. You know this." Nah.
It would always be the same there. You
know this. How
How will it always be the same here? Greavesy.
He's lying, isn't it?
It would always be the same day. You know this. Nah.
Planning to go to a restaurant today, Grezy,
but I'm a bit poor.
I'm a bit poor, lad. So
Good guy, bro.
I might just go to a restaurant, bro. Yeah,
don't forget I lost that £18, didn't I?
I lost that [ __ ] £18.
So, did I get back?
If you remember inbound Yeah.
Why? It's peanuts to me. Why be peanuts
to me? I'm not rich.
I'm not rich at all.
Yeah. So, I won't be ordering again.
I won't be ordering again, matey. No way.
No way am I ordering again. Nope.
600 weekend out. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
And I could have been [ __ ] a couple of
times because of it as well. Yeah.
I could have been [ __ ] a couple of
times because of it.
If I didn't get lucky, mate. So,
it's happened a couple of times.
You'd have £1,000. You go out Friday. By
the Sunday, you've got like400 pound
left. 350. Don't know where the [ __ ]
money goes to be honest. No, bro.
Just think about it. If I didn't do them
weekends and stuff, I'd probably be able
to afford another holiday. in it.
I'd probably be able to afford another [ __ ] holiday.
That's the bad thing about it. Yeah. Sir,
>> why would it never change here, Doug?
The women are just so stuck up.
Why is it so [ __ ] bad here, man?
Why is it so bad here?
>> [clears throat]
>> Oh, my attitude stinks. Oh, really? H really
interesting. Well, thank for that.
Oh, really? Is that what it's been all along?
well, you learn something new every day.
Thanks for that, man.
Oh, thank you, bro. Thanks for that.
Oh, thanks for that.
Yeah. Interesting. Interesting.
So, when I've approached someone and
they've said straight away they have a
boyfriend and they're not interested and
they've led me on, that was my attitude. Oh,
wow. Thank you for that, man.
Thanks for the Thanks for the um constructive criticism.
Yeah, of course you haven't.
You never had any problems with women.
I'm sure you haven't, buddy. I'm sure
you haven't. I would say if I've had
problems I would say a lot of people have.
I mean, I would say probably 80% of
people have if I have Greavvesy. I mean,
that's that's that's fair to say, isn't
it? I'm not saying everyone, but I'm
saying I would say 75 80% of people if
I'm struggling, they're struggling.
Would that not be fair, Grezy?
Would that not be a uh
fair uh fair point?
I might get my haircut today actually.
Yeah, but a lot of people are single. Greasy.
But there are a lot of people that are single. So,
there are a lot of people that are uh
that are single.
It isn't growing though. It isn't growing.
It isn't growing at all.
No. No. No. No. No. No. No. No way. No. Nowhere.
If I'm struggling, 80% of people are struggling.
So, and it also depends on your
circumstances as well. I feel like it
depends on your circumstances.
So, doesn't really matter anyways, does
it? It's not going to change my
situation. So, that's that.
Cuz most people I know are single.
That's That's what I don't understand.
Most people I know are single.
I know some people in relationships, but
majority of the people I know are single.
So, whatever the reason is, they're single. So,
yeah, you do struggle with women. You do
struggle. If I struggle, you would struggle. Simple.
So, that's that.
Yeah. You drive, you have your own
house. That That's what most people
have. That's that's not something to
brag about, you know? Most people work
and whatnot. So, I mean, that's not a brag.
That isn't a brag. So,
you know what? I might do an approach
today. I might do some approaches when I
go for this uh restaurant.
Uh, well, I mean, I put the evidence up
there, so I mean, it's not about being
right or being wrong. I mean, I've put
the evidence up there.
So, I mean, that just got dismissed as
it always will.
Dismissing people's struggles.
That's what people do best.
Is that right, Candy Man?
I mean, why am I why am I having this
argument? I've literally shown my
experiences. There's no argument to
have. So, yeah, that's that. So, it's
what it is.
So, I might do some approaches today.
Grievy, is that okay with you, boss?
I'll go for the meal.
I'll go for the meal, but I want to do
like couple of approaches. Is that okay
with you, boss?
I have to run it by you first.
Think about getting a girlfriend.
Have I don't need a job, mate. I've got
money. I don't need a job.
I don't need a job. And even if you have
a job. Anyways, we're having the same
argument. We're not going to get into
this silly conversation again. Anyways, [snorts]
um Jake Jax FY said your experiences
aren't a reflection of society and
doesn't make it true. What? He said that
directly to me.
So he said that so wait, he said it
directly to me
or someone else.
Well, he said he's saying it directly to me.
Well, well, considering a lot of people
are going to Thailand, a lot of people
are struggling, it's a known fact that
it's harder in the West. It kind of does.
I mean, it kind of does considering a
lot of people are going to Thailand now
and a lot of people struggle in the
West. Everyone struggles whether they
get someone or not. So, it is 100% a
reflection of society and it 100% does
make it true. Get the guy over here,
bro. I'll have a debate with him. He can
join the Streamyards.
It's a known fact that people leave the
West to find someone.
100%. It's a reflection of society. 1 million%.
So, I mean, get him on here. 100% it does.
1 million% it does. And even if it
doesn't, it doesn't matter. There's my
videos show what happens when you're
starting a conversation with someone very normally.
That that that says everything. You
know, I've got screenshots where people
have led me on, played games. It's
evidence. You can't argue with black and
white evidence. Whether it goes for the
rest of the society or it doesn't, it's
black and white evidence. You can't
argue with black and white evidence. But
people seem to still think that they can
argue with black and white evidence.
Listen, listen, listen, listen. It's not
a debate with me. It's not a debate.
It's actual evidence. You can't argue
with black and white evidence. Say you
went say you went Okay. Right. Say you
you got arrested for murder, right? And
you went to court, right? And they
showed you you stabbing someone in the
heart 10 million times and you're still
saying, "Nope, nope. It's not a
reflection of society. Nope. Nope. Nope.
Nope. Nope. The judge would laugh at
you. The judge would be like, "Well,
you've clearly murdered someone here. We
We can see it in black and white
evidence, CCT evidence, and guess what?
Your ass is going to prison. You can't
argue with black and white evidence.
Whether you want to keep dismissing it
and pretending it never happened, bro,
that's on you. But the evidence is
there. It's not about someone being
right or being wrong or thinking they're
always right or thinking they're always
wrong. When the evidence is there, you
can't argue with it. And I have shown
evidence multiple multiple multiple
multiple multiple times, you know? So,
it's that's that. And that's all you're
going to get out of me, bro. Simple.
It's ridiculous, bro. Ridiculous.
Um, so you can't argue with black and
white evidence. I mean, there's
conversations out there where people
have led me on. There's videos where
I've tried to start a conversation with
people and they've said straight away
they're not interested. So, anything
else is irrelevant.
You know what I'm trying to say?
That's a valid [ __ ] point. So, if you
get this guy on this channel, I'll be
more than happy to show him these
videos. I'll be more than happy to show
Okay, whatever. I'm a job, bro. You're
not going to put me down, right? Your
little self-reflecting is not going to
put me down. So, there's no point
self-reflecting cuz it's not going to
put me down.
You know, a little simp like you is not
going to put me down. So, there's no
point even trying. Yeah. Why aren't you
at work now? You're calling people
jobless. Why are you not at work?
Because you don't have a job yourself.
You might want to get yourself a job
before [ __ ] um before um you know
talking about other people.
You're you're on YouTube telling people
to get a job. The irony, bro. You're on
YouTube telling people to get a job. The
irony. Yeah. The irony. You've been sat
on this live stream for about half hour
telling someone to get a job whilst not
a job yourself. That's called self projecting.
Yeah, simple. Yeah, record what I say
and just send it his way. I I'll end up
going on [ __ ] Tik Tok.
Yeah, of course you do, buddy. Of course
you do. And also, I've worked to live by
myself before. You know, again, this is
all sing because Greavesy, the thing is
I have shown evidence. I have abs I have
shown evidence of what I've been through
and these people are still having none
of it. That's why I don't argue with
them. They're simps. Just like this
Doug, he's probably a virgin. Never been
with a woman. You know, there's no point
with these virgins arguing with them.
You know, there's there's no point. Like
I said, you can show these virgins black
and white evidence and they'll still
still lick women's asses. It's autism.
There's there's no point with them.
There is no point. If they want to keep
defending women and be virgins all their
life, that's them. I'm not interested,
bro. I don't care. You know, you know,
you want to you you you want a debate.
Okay, come on in the hangouts right now
and have a debate. It's not about a
debate. You've pro you've been proven
wrong multiple multiple multiple times.
You know, it's not about that you've
been proven wrong. It's not about me
being right. It's you have been proven
wrong and you're more than happy to sit
there, be a virgin. Women don't like you
and and suck up to them. This is what I
mean, Greasy. They they they've got
autism, these people. They don't get
women. Women don't like them and they
still defend them and they don't Women
don't like them. It's it's autism, bro.
I'm telling you, it is autism.
Yeah. And I know what you are. S virgins
that's never been with a woman. It's
[ __ ] obvious. It's [ __ ] obvious.
What did I say, Greasy, on the on the
start of that video? That I am an
impartial person. Not an incel, not a
white knight, not a s. I am an impartial
party. Yeah. I'm not biased. And if you
watch that video, you would have seen
exactly what I have said. Yeah. And I'm
sharing my experiences and I'm sharing my experiences. You know,
they are [ __ ] They are all the
same. They've got attitude problems.
I've proved it multiple multiple
multiple multiple times. The only people
that say otherwise are people that don't
get women with autism. They're the only
people that say otherwise. He's like
this Doug. He's a virgin on benefits. No
job. Never been with a woman. No job.
Nothing going for him. And he's
projecting that onto me. You know,
licking women's asses, but still a
virgin. The last thing I would be doing
is licking women's asses if I was a virgin.
Yeah. So, you start work at 2:00. You
don't start work at 2:00, mate. Shut up.
You're a jobless bum on benefits. Shut
up. You're a jobless bum. Stop self-p
projecting your [ __ ] weirdo skin life onto me,
you [ __ ] bum. Go and get a job. Go
and get some money. Go and get a job,
you loser. Stop [ __ ] coming on
YouTube telling people to get a job when
you ain't got a job yourself. Go and get
a job, you lazy skin bum virgin.
Go and get a [ __ ] job and get off of YouTube.
That's me saying to these to these
people, this for a [ __ ] change, bro.
[ __ ] get off of YouTube, get laid,
and go and get yourself a [ __ ] job
about you [ __ ] start at 2 p.m. Do you
Do you actually think 90% of the people
in this community work? Bro, 90% of this
community does not work. I tell you that
right now. Right here, right now. 90% of
this community does not work.
Yeah, of course you are, mate. [laughter]
Yeah, of course you are. Yeah, of course
you are, mate. Like I said, go and get a
job. Go and get a job and go and get
some money before telling other people
to get a job, you bum. Yeah.
Well, £800 a week. [laughter]
Yeah. Okay, bro. Like I said, go and get
yourself a job. Go get a lady. Go get some money. Yeah,
these simps are [ __ ] mad. These and
and the thing is I keep saying I'm
unbiased. I've got no reason to lie. I'm
not a virgin. I don't need to lie.
They are [ __ ] They are [ __ ]
Women, they are. Like, you want me to
lie and say they're not? I don't give a
[ __ ] I'm just saying, bro. you know.
Anyways, go get a job.
Just using cards.
Now you've got serious issues, bro. Look
at you sat on YouTube pretending that
you work. Like, it's [ __ ] sad as you know?
But wait, you you said that you don't
think I'm a virgin. Wait, wait, wait.
You You don't think I'm a virgin? So,
you don't think I'm a virgin? Really? [laughter]
Wait, you don't think I'm a virgin? Oh, really?
I mean, wouldn't you know that I'm not a
virgin because I put a poo out there?
This is what I mean with you little
self-projected [ __ ] You said that
you don't think Well, no. I don't think
somebody would think someone's a virgin
if they prove they've had sex.
You need to get a job and go get laid.
You know, you need to get off of YouTube
and go get laid. Seriously,
get off of YouTube, you [ __ ] bum. Anyways,
I'm banning you now. Bye-bye, [ __ ]
So, what will happen if I go approach
him today, Damian?
You think there'll be that change or what? Huh?
Do you think there'll be that change or what?
Yeah, but what do you what do you think would happen?
about this, bro. I really hate talking
about this. It's so depressing.
[ __ ] hate talking about this. It's so depressing, bro. Yeah,
attitude problems. Same [ __ ]
So, yeah, get that Tik Tok. I'm going to
go on Tik Tok and uh I'm going to I'm
going to stick on that guy, bro.
It doesn't matter about society. Just
just just just just just read what
you're watching, bro. Just just just
listen to what you're watching. some
normal person that's decent looking is
trying to start a conversation with
someone and they're saying straight away
they're not interested. [ __ ] other
people. [ __ ] the rest of society. We
don't care about the rest of society.
Yeah. It's like and I'm more than happy
showing my other channel if you want to
see my other channel. I've got another
channel remember with all these
approaches on. So you try and tell me
something. You can't tell me nothing.
So yeah, I'll tell him about himself and
I'll show him as well, you know.
Need to go to this [ __ ] boxing match
as well. [ __ ] sake. Bad. Bad. Yep.
to go into this restaurant today maybe
but like I said I have to run it by greasy first with Boss.
Okay with you, boss.
Clear. Lower deck.
I have to run it by you first. Greasy.
You know what? I'm like, huh?
Is that okay with you greasy boss?
If I go, boss,
I might do some approaches. [ __ ] it. It
will you be looking to Will you be
looking forward to the nice video, Grezy?
It's a nice little video.
bit hairy I am, bro.
Yeah, I might just go out do some few
approaches and then get some food.
Yeah, I need to wash my hair that well. Yeah.
No, no, no, no. At least I brush my beard.
My little beard, Grezy.
get a haircut on um we get a haircut tomorrow. Yeah.
Oh yeah, he's brushing. Needs brushing, bro.
He's brushing there.
You don't believe I'll do the
approaches, do you, Greasy?
You don't believe it, do you?
I [ __ ] will, mate. If I say I'm going
to do it, I [ __ ] will do it.
Yeah, it might be different. Might it Greavesy?
Might be different. Hey, Greavvesy.
But I might get I might get [ __ ]
tempted to go and drink and that bro
cuz it's right by [ __ ]
thingy in it.
right by like all the bars and [ __ ] but
I'll be doing that, bro.
Can't be doing them things, matey.
No, I can't be drinking, bro. Yep.
That's it's dangerous squeezy when I go
out but very dangerous.
It's expensive as well.
We could be in a bit of bothersy.
You know, we could be in a bit of [ __ ] bother.
Is that cute, Grezy? You know, >> yeah,
it will be [ __ ] up in it, Grezy. We
will be [ __ ] up. Yeah.
Nah, but I'm not going to go out
drinking. [ __ ] that.
I'll go I'll go for some food and do
some approaches. That's it.
I'm not drinking, bro. [ __ ] that.
I will do some appro I will do some approaches though. [ __ ] it.
Hopefully there'll be a change. H.
You reckon there'll be a change, Greavvesy?
A little change?
No. Yeah. No.
It's such a depressing cycle in this
country, in it, indigo.
It's such a depressing cycle.
You go out, you approach, you become
depressed, and it never ends. The cycle
just never ever [ __ ] ends.
It's so bad, bro.
It's never ever ending.
I don't think I'm going to go out today,
bro. I don't think so actually cuz the
thing is it's just it's always going to
be the same old [ __ ]
you know, and then you just end up
feeling worse. I don't want to end up
I just I don't want to end up feeling
worse, bro. That's the thing. Yeah.
You know what I mean? Don't you, Grezy? >> Yeah.
You just end up feeling worse.
I don't think it's a good idea, bro.
Trust me, it ain't a good idea, bro.
There's actually a pub though. There is
a pub right next to the station, but
simply no point.
No one's bloody interested. you know.
Yeah, I have
[ __ ] sake, man.
What do I do today?
What do I do? Stop.
No. No, no, no, no, no.
starting up. So, [snorts]
easy. I need to be good.
That's what I need to be, man.
I need to be a good goose. Crazy. Yeah,
good old bed. Edens.
Do you think Greavves?
I could go out today, but the thing is that
Christmas is a bastard, bro. Every time.
Every time. Is it, bro?
I could go out today,
but the thing is, yeah,
I could go out drinking today, Grims, but
I don't know.
It's tempting, bro. See, I'm a crazy
[ __ ] I am a crazy [ __ ] bro. You know
what I'm saying? This is what I mean.
Grieves. I don't know why I feel like it
today, you know.
I think it's cuz the weather's not too bad.
Just go get a meal and just get on the piss straight.
I'm [ __ ] mad. You know, I am [ __ ]
It's expensive nowadays doing these
things though, bro.
I'm not [ __ ] rich, you know?
That's the thing.
A rich matey.
But if I drink Guinness, right,
I can't water Guinness down in it. Huh?
when are you going to wear your Uggs? >> Yeah.
>> Oh, might just wear the black I might
just wear the coat with a black t-shirt,
the jeans and the trainers and it Yeah.
Okay with you, boss.
So, you sure it's okay? So, you sure
it's okay if I go out, boss?
>> Okay, boss.
Ny's gave me the heads up, so I guess
we're kind of having to go out now,
aren't we, Roozy? [laughter]
I'm [ __ ] terrible. I am [ __ ] terrible, you know.
Very, very, very [ __ ] terrible, mate. You know? Yeah.
Oh, let's put that there.
So obviously we'll start with the meal.
We'll do a protein and we'll do the meal and then
go from there in it. [laughter]
Okay with you boss. Yeah.
>> Yeah. Get that [ __ ] uh
get that s get that [ __ ] s on this channel, mate.
So, what I'll do is I'll probably I'll
probably go approach and go for a meal and then um yeah,
see hopefully it will be different today.
Hopefully it will be different today. I
am candy man. Wish me luck, lad.
Hopefully it will be different. Fingers
crossed. No boyfriends today.
Fingers crossed. Eandy man, you'll be
rooting for me.
beard though. The beard's quite long, isn't it?
Well, I guess we'll just watch it. But yeah,
fingers crossed it'll be different today,
you know. No [ __ ] Tandy, man. No
Don't get any of that [ __ ] today.
Whoa. [ __ ] I'm trying a different area
this time. So, going right by the uh cubby houses.
Yeah. Going right by the [ __ ] cubby houses.
No, no, no, no, no.
Is that all right with you, Grezy?
Is that okay with you, boss?
No, no, no, no, no.
I ain't been out on a Thursday for
[ __ ] ages, man. Absolutely [ __ ] ages.
Grey [ __ ] ages.
Shut up little things.
Do you think it's possible I won't get
one number today?
one number? I don't I don't think so,
mate. I don't think it's possible. What
do you think [snorts]
to knock that one number? I don't think
it's possible, do you?
Nah, I don't think it's possible, bro. I
always get a number.
Can I actually be asked going out?
That's a silly question, isn't it,
Greasy? Of course I can, mate.
No, I don't think it's possible, bro.
You'll get you'll get numbers.
>> Yeah, Christmas shopping. [ __ ]
Christmas. It's [ __ ] expensive. And it [ __ ]
get it literally mate [ __ ] everything
up, doesn't it? This Christmas [ __ ] thing.
So, I'll try a different area this time
and see uh see what the see what the
score is. Ezy,
see what the score is. Yeah. Right.
It needs to be brushed down a little
bit. Should be all right. Yeah.
Right. Uh should we wear
trying to think what I could wear?
Yeah, I think the black top.
Oh, maybe I'll wear the teddy bear top.
Got some stonies here. I'm trying to think. Wear this again.
No, I want to wear the coat. I want to
wear the coat to be fair.
Yeah, I want to wear the coat
with a t-shirt, right?
Hopefully it's bloody different today,
Ruby, cuz I've had a bloody enough. And
yeah, I did say it. I said bloody.
That's the only word I know.
Well, I'm bloody hoping it changes. I'm
bloody sick of the [ __ ] boyfriend
[ __ ] and whatnot. I've had enough of it.
Hopefully, it bloody will change. I've
got some face moisturizer as well. So,
yeah, I've got some face moisturizer. Um,
all right. We'll be shooting boot
cuz what else are you going to [ __ ]
do is [ __ ] sit in one second.
Right. Got the bug t-shirt, got the
jeans, and the trainers are coming along as well.
Oh, I didn't show you, did I, Grezy? I
got Superman socks.
Yeah, I got Superman socks.
that ones are dirty.
Is that okay with you, boss?
Is that okay with you, captain?
Is that okay with you, captain? Now
before um I was you know thinking of
going out uh today Greavvesy I did
contact the manager again obviously
because of Virgin Boy and obviously you
know we want Virgin boy to come out with
us and stuff. Um again um it's a
strictly no Skint virgin policy. No
Skint virgins and bedsits allowed.
Again I don't make the rules. I'm I'm
not saying anything mate. I'm I'm uh
again I'm not I'm not I'm not involved
with this. It's a no skin virgin policy.
No. Again, I'm not you know involved in
any just silliness.
Oh yeah, I've got that that and I've got
that as well.
Yeah, bro. Don't you worry. I will be. Mhm.
Right. What else? Yeah,
obviously the train is in it.
You have to have the old savage on a be.
You have to have the old savage on a B.
Clear lower deck, Grezy. Clear lower deck. Zippy.
Right. And I've got the trailers as well. So,
no. Gosh darn it, Candy. You're being so so so
negative. I don't know what it is with
you. Tell him, Breezy. Tell him he's being negative.
That's what he's being. He You're so
negative. You are.
I know. He's He's being so blooming
negative. I don't know what this guy's
[ __ ] problem is.
Oh, gosh darn it. You're being so
so so so so
negative. Negative. Negative. Negative.
Isn't that right?
He He's being so bloody negative. I
don't know why you're being so What is
your problem, mate? What is your [ __ ] problem?
Well, I'm just having a shower here. Be
back in 10 minutes.
Oh, I didn't even get my underpants.
>> Oh, god darn it. Didn't get my
underpants. What underpants should I
wear? The chucky ones.
The Chucky ones. No, let's be serious.
Let's absolutely be serious.
Let's actually be serious here. Right. Yeah.
Oh [ __ ] man.
I bought some washing stuff as well,
Greasy. That's I'll be invoicing you.
I'll be [ __ ] invoicing you.
I'll be [ __ ] invoicing you. I will
be, mate. I [ __ ] will be.
Oh, I got my little gorilla powder as
well. Oh, gosh darn it.
just come out the bloody shower. Oh,
you're all right, mate. Oh, [ __ ]
Now, this is this is basically a uh
uh this is basically a um
this is basically an area where there's
like loads and loads and loads of Americans. So,
yeah, we're basically going to l Yankee Land.
Yeah, we're basically heading to Yankee Land.
Greasy. Um so, yeah. Don't know if
that's okay with you, Bob. >> Yeah.
Yeah. One second.
Quees, are you trolling me? When I'm
saying when I'm saying the West is
finished and you're saying it back to
me, you're not trolling me, are you?
Oh, no. You can't be saying that
actually because uh what is it? Because
there's nurseries that are still open.
other people that probably met people
years ago. That means that there is that
that somehow means that there's still a chance
even because other people who met years
ago met someone.
So that's completely comparable to my situation
apparently. [snorts] Apparently that's
completely comparable to my situation
now having to find someone when I was
younger. That's that's completely the
same thing, you know. Madness, bro. Madness.
I need to brush my furry beard
cuz it's quite furry. Greasy.
It is quite furry, isn't it?
[gasps and sighs]
Should be all right. I'll brush it down and that. Yeah, man.
Well, we'll see today, won't we, bro?
badness. I ain't done it in this area
for ages to be fair. Yeah, man.
Obviously, like I said, we always have
to run these things uh by you first.
Obviously, that's the whole uh okay with
you, boss. That's that's that's what
happens. You see, that's what [ __ ]
happens, mate. I'm [ __ ] telling you, you know. Okay.
So, I'm taking [ __ ] Reddit's advice
once again, Greavvesy. Once a [ __ ]
again. Taking that [ __ ] advice. Would
this be the day where this [ __ ] where
this [ __ ] changes, Grezy? Would it Will
it be the day where this [ __ ] changes?
I've had a bloody enough of it, Rezy. A
bloody enough. You know, I'm at my
[ __ ] wits end with it all.
I'm at my wits end with the [ __ ] lot
of it to be fair.
Why is my beard so like that, bro?
Bit long in it. Oh well,
it's not too bad, is it?
I got out on thingy as well, so it's fine.
So, what curry we getting today, Grey?
What curry are we getting today, son? What curry?
Don't stop being the old gosh darn it.
We don't It won't [snorts]
a serious beard actually that bad.
The beard's not that bad, is it?
What do you think, Greavves? Is it okay
to go sending it in with this beard? I
think it's all right, is it?
Is the beard actually all right? I'm
going to brush it, obviously.
Oh, it's too long.
Yeah, but I'm not going to [ __ ] go
and get a [ __ ] haircut, bro. That's [ __ ] long.
Yeah, but I'm not going to go and get a
haircut. It's That's [ __ ] bro.
That's [ __ ] And it takes up a lot
of the day. So,
Oh [ __ ] almost showed my testicles there.
It's not that bad, is it?
We can brush it maybe.
Why does it go so long like that? I
don't know why.
I mean, it doesn't make a difference
anyway, does it? Even when you look max,
you still don't get anything. Let me dry
it. It should be all right, shouldn't it?
It's a bit long. Yeah.
I think it's got one more approaching in
it. What do you think, Greavesy?
See if I can brush it or something.
That'll be the next bloody excuse. We'll
be the next [ __ ] excuse, would it?
No, I think that's all right. No.
How's that, Grezy? A bit better.
That was not greasy.
That a bit better, boss.
This should dry a little bit.
That's a bit better. It
going to have to do, mate.
But I have to do
rebrush it and add some stuff to it. It
should be all right.
We don't really want to go to the
barbers, bro. It's long. Yeah.
So, good evening. Estimate how many numbers today?
Estimate. We use a estimate. Estimate
estimate. Estimate estimate. Estimate. Eh, [snorts]
that's okay with me, boss. Is that okay
with you, boss?
That's okay with me, boss. Yeah. Right.
Always looking for that change because
if you know me, I'm always looking for that change.
Doesn't matter how much money
we have to spend,
we'll always always be looking for that change.
We always be looking for that change.
You said it would never change, but uh
I think you just being negative.
You just be a negative Nancy you look
bit look a bit better now. Yeah.
Yeah. should do.
Does it [ __ ] matter anyways? I mean,
even if you Oh [ __ ] Oh, I sprayed the
wrong [ __ ] one on my bloody armpit
screen. Oh gosh darn it.
I almost sprayed the wrong [ __ ] one.
Oh gosh darn it.
Some people like might like like the beard look.
Is that right, Grezy? Some people might
like the beard look. Hey
all fuzzy again.
goes all fuzzy again the bit.
Maybe because it's wet or something.
You just brush the [ __ ] up.
Yeah, I'm angry.
Oh, how do I look, Grezy?
My hair is drying. But
do I look okay, boss? Oh man.
Yeah, the beard's a bit long. I'll
definitely have to get that trimmed. one thing.
I trimmed on [ __ ] um thing.
One second, bro. >> [snorts]
>> That bit is a bit too long, isn't it?
It is a little bit long.
Just a tiny bit. People
might like the beard look though,
Greezy. You never know. Some people
might like the beard look.
Maybe just a little bit there.
I like when my hair dries naturally, you
know. I don't know why. I just kind of do.
Okay with you, Greensy Bot. Okay,
you don't [ __ ] about
like what Steven Edward says. You don't
give a [ __ ] about us.
You're a meanie.
[ __ ] [ __ ] new one.
Yeah, man. [snorts] How's that, Grezy?
Is that all right?
Is that all right, Grey?
I'm getting a bit hungry now.
getting we bit hungry, bro.
What a I'm going to I'm going to come
back with you later, obviously. Not
going just now. And I'll be like, "What
a [ __ ] day I've had."
That's what Yeah. The beard's not too
bad, is it?
I'll be saying, "What a [ __ ] day I've had."
Okay. with you, boss. Yeah,
we use that [ __ ] everywhere.
Everywhere. Everywhere. You know.
How's that, wheezy, boss?
How's that, eh?
Okay with you, boss.
Obviously, I've got some nice jeans and
trainers, so they should be doing uh
they they should be doing a lot of work. Really, mate.
Hopefully I don't get in it too deep
today, bro. Hopefully, we're not too
deep in it where we have to send and
send and send. We're just about to go
out for a meal, man, and get on the drink.
Oh, get on the Guinnesses. Hey. Yeah,
man. My beard's a little bit long, but
I've brushed it. It should be all right.
Put some lotion on my face and that. And
yeah, man. I'm going to go to a
different area this time. I've been to
this air. I've been to this area for a
long time, but it's where all the curry
houses are. So, we'll just uh see see
what it is, man.
Yeah. Yeah, I just come out the shower. So
hopefully we'll find that uh change today, Bob.
Not very likely, but you know, we still
we still go out, mate. We still go out.
It's fine. It's no problem.
You know, so
just spray some sage on me. Oh, I'm
addicted to bloody savage.
I'm addicted to this bloody savage. Oh,
you could just smell Weezy. Oh,
if you can just smell it, Grezy.
I will do, mate. I will do. I will do.
Hopefully, we don't get that bloody
boyfriend [ __ ] today. Isn't that right, Grezy?
Got my little trainers up. What do you
think? The beard look all right? I'm
going to brush it a few more times.
Should be all right. It's winter, so
not stopping up at the barbers. [ __ ] that.
That's long. But got my little trainers. So
look, still looking fresh.
Fresh cool trainers. Freshy cool M.
Just keep just making friends, guys.
Just making friends. Oh,
you know what I'm saying? So,
got some lotion for my face as well. I
need to put some face lotion on.
Hopefully, there's not none of this
bloody boyfriend [ __ ] today.
Bloody hell. I'll be giving you I'll be
giving you a review by the end of the
night. At the end of the night, I will
be giving you a review.
Just going to leave it like this.
Just going to leave it like this, bro.
I'm going to wear my coat and my trainers. So,
do you think of the beard?
No, I'm not packed up because I'm going
on Saturday again. You're just making up
the [ __ ] dates. You're just making up
the dates at this point.
Yeah, I'm just going to leave my hair
like this. Well, it's going to dry
obviously and then put my coat on and
just go and see what the score is basically.
Can't believe I'm [ __ ] doing this again.
I actually can't believe I'm doing this
[ __ ] again, brother. You know,
not me, mate.
You like it? Yeah. I'm going to need to
brush it a little bit, bro, cuz uh it's
a bit long and I don't really want to go
barbers today. So, I'm going to add some lotion
and my face lotion. Yeah, I'm going for
a curry. Um
going to do some approaches. Going for
some curry, then get on the piss.
Got my Superman socks on as well. Yep.
So, that's what we're going with, man.
Brush that a bit more.
Should be all right. Where's the
Don't worry. Video is coming up for you,
Grey of the lovely curry.
Don't worry, matey. It's coming up for you. So, yeah.
Oh, I can't can't not do that. So, we're
going to send it sober.
Gonna get some food then just get on a
drink basically. So yeah,
Superman. Superman. Superman.
No, I don't lie to please. No names on
the screen. I I don't need to do that.
Like I said, if you believe me, you
believe me. If you don't, you don't.
So that's that's that, man. That's
[ __ ] That's straight that it
superman. Superman Superman sucks. You know
the only bad thing with black ginger is
when the white goes on it. You can
actually see it goes everywhere, bro. Goes everywhere.
It's sh lad. Sh. Yeah.
But yeah, you think what you want, bro.
That's on you in it.
Nah, black jeans are the best. Deleted.
Black jeans for sure. [snorts]
What's the time one in it? I'm not
leaving just yet.
Hopefully we'll find that change today, Mike.
[ __ ] hell. Spend the money again.
Hopefully we'll find that change. E
hopefully we'll find that change.
Haven't been out on a Thursday in ages, so yeah, absolutely. One sec.
No, I'm going a different location this time, bro. Worth nice.
you know, going to going to a different place.
Yeah, pretty much.
Pretty much, bro. Yeah.
Got some lotion I need to put on my face. What's up,
I need to put my hair like that.
This is I think you're going to be
getting the wrong idea when you see this.
Yeah, don't get any wrong ideas now, you sick [ __ ]
Greavves probably don't understand it
cuz he's a bit He's
a bit um
he's a bit too young to understand.
Oh, that lotion is nice, bro.
That lotion is sick. I'm going to put
some more on when I go out.
Yeah, that's nice. That lotion.
Nice. That lotion.
Look at that.
It helps your face, man. It is good.
That lotion, eh?
I had to sleep on my little blankie.
My little [ __ ] blankie, bro.
Oh, thank you, Autumn. Thank you. You're
so kind of you.
You're sarcasm, eh?
You're sarcasm. Well, let me tell you
something. If I don't pull today, I'll
be coming at you with a bloody axe. I'm
making you tempted to go out. Well, come
in and come out and come and join the
fun. You know, you're more than help.
You're more than welcome to come out
with me today if you want, buddy. You
know, why not come and join the fun, you
know? No one's stopping you, you know.
Why not? Come out enjoying the fun, you
know? That's what life's all about,
you know? I'm going out, bro. [ __ ]
I went out last week, week before, spent
a load of money, and now I'm just going
out today. So,
Afghan P. Yeah.
It's not nice to call me Afghan Pete, is
it? Afghan Pete. I think I look all
right. What do you think, Autumn? Do you
think the beard looks all right? It's a
little bit long, but
working with it, you know?
I mean, it doesn't really matter anyways
cuz you're still going to get the same
[ __ ] So, does it really matter anyways? Uh, yeah, man.
Oh, you sure? Thank you. That means a lot.
You know, why don't you come out with me
today? Join the fun. You know, you're
more than welcome to,
you know, why not?
You're more than welcome to come out
today and and join the part if you want.
I've been out on a Thursday since
[ __ ] months ago.
Hey, don't say that, Candy. We still got
time. We still got time.
You're just being negative, Autumn. This
This Candy man, he's just being
negative, isn't he? He's just being
Candy. You're just being negative. Stop
being a negative Nancy.
You know, tell him. Tell him he's being negative.
He's being negative.
I I'm wearing 200 pound jeans.
Well, they they're they're just being
they're just being jealous,
Tim. They're just they're just being
jealous. That's what they're doing.
They're just jealous. I don't know what it is.
Nah, don't be a He's being jealous. He's being negative.
You know, I I think he needs a timeout.
I mean, why why would he possibly think
that all I mean I'm 23 numbers in, over
a,000 pounds spent and I've not even got
a single date, you know? Not even got a
you know. But why would he think that,
you know, it will be the same this time?
I shall never know, you know. I shall
never ever ever ever know.
But that's why he thinks so, you know.
We'll be out anyways, bro. We'll be out
here. You know, some people like the beard look.
Some people like the beard look, you
know. So, we'll see. We'll see what the score is.
Yeah, I know, man.
Story of your life. You're still a virgin.
I mean, that's the story of your life,
though, is it, lad? You're a virgin, so
you're worse than me. Is that right, Autumn?
Did I? Yeah. They hate me, bro. They
hate you as well. To show.
Yeah, I will, bro. I will. Yeah, no worries, man.
They hate you as well.
And they hate Mike, you know. That's that's that.
You're gay. Really?
Really? Are you?
You're You're gay.
Okay. Well, I'll be live later if
there's any Wi-Fi. So, you'll see, won't you?
No. No. No.
Oh, they hate you as well, kindly man.
You would never pull even if your life
depended on it.
You know, you're not going to you're not
going to [ __ ] put us off the madness today.
You're not going to put you're not going
to put us off the madness. So, there's
no point even trying, mate. Nah,
it's not what I say, it's what I know.
When was the last time you've been with
a woman? Come out with me today, bro.
I'll buy I'll buy all your drinks. I'll
buy all your drinks if you want.
I'll buy all your drinks. Courtesy of Peter Bennett.
That's an offer you can't refuse, right?
They hate you as well. Just like they
hate 80% of men, they don't like you
either. So, yeah. It's not what I say,
it's what I know. So, yeah.
Yeah. Okay, bro. Whatever. Yeah, man.
Yeah, man. Whatever.
No, no, no, no,
no, no, no.
Oh, you a liar. [clears throat]
Yeah, it's all about being positive. Of course, man.
Obviously, [snorts] man. Cuz the last
few times we went out, we was just like so negative.
We were just like so negative, weren't
we, bro? So negative.
Get ready for it. No, I don't want to
get ready for it. Maybe I don't want to
get ready for that. Yeah,
that's what you would get if you
approach women. They wouldn't even say
that to you. They'd be like, "Get the
[ __ ] away from me, you ugly cunt."
That's what they'd say to you. That's
what they'd say to you, mate.
Look at this bloody hair, bro.
Bloody hair, man.
My hair is all funky. Sure.
If you come meet me, I'll Yeah, man. If
you come and meet me, I'll happily buy
your drinks, bro. If you want. Happily,
bro. I'll happily buy your drinks.
All right. Don't be a [ __ ] white knight now.
They feel comfortable around me. Don't
be a [ __ ] simp white white night now.
Jesus bloody Christ.
Don't. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. All right.
All right. Calm it. Calm it. Stop it.
Don't be a bloody white knight now.
Don't be a little s, you know.
Don't be a little s matey. Yeah, mom.
Never. Never in my life have I ever singed.
Simp doesn't get you laid. White
nighting don't get you women. And you
know the thing is these white knights
would never have the these white knights
would never have the balls to ever do it
in person. Never. Look, did you see that
that video? I mean, Weather Spoons, you
see them three guys? They said nothing,
bro. They knew they couldn't say
anything. They literally knew they
wouldn't be able to say anything.
They knew they wouldn't be able to say
anything, bro. I would have broke their
[ __ ] jaw just from one punch.
So, they whiten on the internet, but in
real life, they could never white, bro.
Just like today, you'll see.
That's that, isn't it? So,
yeah. And I didn't calm down and I
continued. Yeah. And I continued and I
told the security guard to get the [ __ ]
away from me.
Yeah. Yeah. And I told Yeah. And I continued.
So, yeah. If I was a [ __ ] he would
have done more than tell me, bro. He
would have done more than told me. If I
was a [ __ ] he would have more than
told me, bro. Trust. So
yeah, he would have more than told me,
bro. He would have more than told me. Believe that.
I will never ever sing.
These people that simp. Yeah, I feel
sorry for them.
They're [ __ ] virgins.
They're absolute virgins, bro. Absolute virgins.
You like the beard? The beard's nice.
Do you like the beard, Autumn? Did you
actually like my little beard? He calls.
It looks all right, bro.
Need to do my hair a little bit more.
Just nice. The beard me. I like the beard. Me. Yeah.
[ __ ] beard, man. Beard beard. I'm
going to go in a bit anyways.
Need to go get some food. [ __ ] hell.
Need to go to the dentist next week.
Yeah. So, that's all we need to do.
a being stuck. Did you really
This is my boat.
I need to buy a new one next year.
But they do good for the money. They do
last quite a while as well to be fair.
>> I love this coat, man. Got a Hilfiger
coat on as well. Yeah, man.
Got the trainers on as well.
Don't worry. nice traders and things
will make up for the uh you know
it will make up for the um
slightly long beard. I'll show you what
I'm wearing. Oh, in one second.
I was speaking to some woman yesterday
and then she uh she disappeared.
Bro, of course it's going to be the same
old story, bro. It will never change.
I know this. You know that. But what
else is there to do, man?
Oh, [ __ ] Yeah. And then she just disappeared.
You don't need to tell me, bro.
We know it will never change. [ __ ] sake. Right. Anyways, so look,
look at that, man.
Look at these fresh trainers.
Maybe if you had a life, you wouldn't be
invested, would you, Mike?
If you had a life,
if you had somewhat of a life, lad.
If you had somewhat of a bloody life,
you wouldn't be invested, would you?
I still think I look cute.
I don't know if I should add some lotion
to my hair, lad. Yeah.
One second, man.
I don't remember to like try curl my
hair a little bit. Maybe
change the socks.
No, I don't. No, I'm not changing the socks. One second.
I'm not getting a haircut.
Why am I going to get a haircut? It's
not going to make no difference. Even if
I get a haircut, I'm not getting a haircut.
Doesn't make a difference anyways.
Whether you get a haircut, whether you
don't get a haircut, I'm not getting a haircut. So, yeah.
Do you think of the curls? Oh, my curly hair.
Yeah, my curly hair. We'll get a
haircut, bro. [ __ ] that.
I was going to put some Gorilla powder
on my hair, but
Well, I guess we could do Yeah, add some
product on my hair.
The [ __ ] am I going to get a haircut,
bro? The [ __ ] is the point of that?
just to get the same [ __ ] Oh [ __ ]
This is what you do with this powder.
You sprinkle it on your hair
and then you do this.
Then close up your hair.
What do you think of that? Ooh,
cold your hair up.
But you never know anything like that
before, have you?
Why do they always come on my bloody channel?
Why do people always
come on my bloody channel? Whereas,
why do people always come on my channel?
Is that where like the content is or something?
something? They always seem to end up on
my bloody channel. You know,
always come on my bloody channel.
Always come on my bloody channel. I
don't know why.
I just comb my hair up a little bit.
Do you like my little hair, Bob?
Do you like my little hair? Do you like
how my little hair's looking?
Do I'm going in,
Grezy. I'm going in.
You like that, Grezy? I'm going in the deep end.
That's what it basically means. You're
going in. That's what Yeah. When I As
soon as I leave that door, mate,
anything can happen.
I'm going in.
What do you think, Bob? Do you think we
we look Do you reckon we look okay going out? Nah,
I'm going for this. And it doesn't
really matter anyways, does it? You're
still going to get the same [ __ ] So,
you're still going to get the same [ __ ] mate.
So, it doesn't matter, does it?
My hair just looks so long, bro.
It should be all right now, is it?
But it doesn't matter cuz even if you
get a haircut, you're still going to get
the same [ __ ] aren't you? up.
You're still going to get the same old in it.
You'll still get the same old [ __ ] in it.
What do you think, Grezy?
Do you think it looks all right?
I think it does.
Yeah, but what about all the other times
that I went out with the comovers and
they all said they had boyfriends, Bob Bills?
What about all those times
and then they said that they had
boyfriends? What about all them times,
Bob? When I got the 10 numbers?
Nah, [ __ ] that, bro. I'm I'm
What do you think, Grezy? Do you think
this looks all right? Just little look.
I don't trust you cuz I looked Max
before and I got 10 numbers and I didn't
even get a date.
So, no, I don't trust you.
I don't trust you at all.
I don't trust you.
I don't trust you at all because the
last time I went out I looked smack and
I didn't get anything.
No, seriously. Goes, is this all right?
Yeah. You like this?
Joe, this is all right going out like this.
Let me ask Antman. I'll run it by Ant-Man first. Oh.
and man just said enjoy. Just let me
know how it goes and [ __ ] I will do captain.
I like it when you say it as well, captain.
Yeah, there's no point making an effort
anyways. It will never change, will it? Yeah,
it will never change, will it?
Well, it will never change, will it?
Right, Greasy. I'm going to charge my
phone up a little bit now. Um, I'll be
making my way. Obviously, I need to go
to the restaurant first. Um, and yeah, I will A
see you. Well, I'll actually be I'll actually uh
I'll be live later. I'm definitely going
to be back later. You never know until you try.
You know, buddy, you know, you'll never
know until you try. You just never know
You never know until you try, mate.
That's it. So, I'll do a a video for you
at the restaurant and then yeah, I'll be
live later. Okay with you, boss.
So, yeah. And uh that'll be me, bro.
100% be me. So, yeah, man. I'll ab
[ __ ] see you. So yeah, see you later.
And the food video is going to come up as well.