Captain,
you calm down. Hey, Greasy, you calm
Oh, man. These cocktails are absolutely lush.
These cocktails are lush.
You right, captain.
Sorry about that, Captain.
Out here, man. On the cocktails. We're
at two numbers, one Snapchat, and my third drink.
We're going to send it like a
[ __ ] today, bro. Oh, yeah. We
did. We did, didn't it?
Goodness, bro. [ __ ] madness.
Waiting for places to get busy. I'm a
bit licky now, bro. Licky. Yeah, bro.
Get a bit busy. These
cocktails have got ramen in them. So
I'll be I got I had a vindaloo before this. >> Yes.
Hey, I've recorded some approaches, by
the way. So, I'll be uploading them.
I'll be uploading them later.
I'm [ __ ] bro. I swear I'm actually
just like in my head. You don't
understand, bro. I'm back.
>> They look all right, but [ __ ] off.
It's not really feasible, is it?
Bro, that that just hits you straight in
your head, bro.
That hits you straight in your [ __ ] head.
talking to this one. Oh, I was like,
"Can I get your number?" So, I'll give
you my snap. I learn the number. I said,
"Okay, I'll give you my Snapchat. I'll
download it next day just for you.
This is [ __ ] madness, bro. I ain't
been drinking it in ages.
I don't really go this area.
This makes you [ __ ] bro. I got
a feel it's going to be a good night though.
Hopefully this time
hopefully this time we'll actually get it.
I done some approaches as well. I'll
upload it tomorrow. I don't give a [ __ ] mate.
We're at two numbers on one Snapchat.
[ __ ] This is our third drink. We ain't
This is like sober protest. We ain't
done that many drunk to be fair.
I'm [ __ ] steaming, bro.
They put rub in these [ __ ] cocktails.
I'm going to be [ __ ] tomorrow.
I am going to be so [ __ ] tomorrow.
No, it's not even funny. Like tomorrow
I'm going to be so [ __ ] up.
That's [ __ ] white rum, bro. That is
[ __ ] white rum.
That ain't no dark rum. I'm telling you
straight. That is That is white rum, lad.
That is white rum, bro.
Brother, that is white rum.
That is white.
Hey, Grezy. Hey. Hey,
so I done some approaches. Uh, I
recorded me doing some approaches.
Paused it, resumed it. I'm going to
upload it later on. And not a lot not
long had a vindaloo. Now I'm drinking.
So I've got some I got two numbers on
one Snapchat. They're all [ __ ] sober,
mate. These this video was coming up.
[laughter] Look at you. You was waiting
for it. Nothing lasts forever, was it, Grezy? [ __ ]
I'm [ __ ] I'm going to be going on
this plane [ __ ] I literally am greasy.
Greasy loves the content. It loves it.
>> Two [ __ ] numbers.
Two numbers and one Snapchat. [snorts]
This is a [ __ ] [ __ ] area, bro.
They're all [ __ ] here, bro. All [ __ ] here.
They're all [ __ ] here, lad. Okay,
so we're two numbers, one Snapchat.
We're two numbers, one Snapchat.
Two numbers, one Snapchat. [ __ ] hell.
I ain't been to this area in like a year
and a half drinking. So, I thought I'd
try this over here this time.
Looking at them [ __ ] over there, but not really.
Anyway, approaching video going up
there. It's coming up. The video is Bro,
I'm telling you, this is white.
This is white rum.
I'm telling you 100%. This is white rum, bro.
This is white rum, brother. Two numbers.
I don't know if one of them is real. I
think one of them is
a number on video as well. So, I'm going
to be putting that up.
>> Oh, guess what, Greavves? Let me let me
tell you this, boss. You're not going to
believe this, right? Be easy. So,
I was talking to this Australian, right?
Not even joking. I was talking to this Australian
and we're talking and yeah, we was
talking for about 10 minutes and I was
like, "Oh, can I get your number?"
And uh, guess what her name was?
Her name was Anatasha.
The same name as the other Australian I
approached in a similar place. Isn't
that mad? She had exactly the same name
as the last one. I never found the same
place. Oh gosh. You know what I'm
saying? You would never You would never
believe something like this, mate. You
would never believe it if you were told
it, would you? Would you, mate? She had
the same [ __ ] name.
Of course you would, [ __ ]
Of course you [ __ ] would.
I'm [ __ ] mad, May. I'm going to get
some more cocktails after these.
Now, I know I said I was only going to
stick to the beer. That's what the plan
was, only sticking to the beer. But I
think it's going to be cocktails. It's
going to be a cocktailer. Okay. With
you, Greasy Boss. If I get some more cocktails,
>> obviously again, I've got to run it by you first.
Slam the Venu.
>> [clears throat]
>> You all right, Captain? Good, man.
Yeah, I'm like, yeah, straight.
[laughter] See, I'm mad. I'm [ __ ]
mad. You don't get me. I'm bad enough sober.
Hey, listen. Listen. You are born alone.
You die alone. Yeah. So, you can enjoy a
night out by yourself.
You can enjoy these nights out by ASL.
Nothing lasts forever. Greasy.
So, I was thinking of giving the UGG
boots to USA, is it? I was thinking of
getting the getting the spliff putting
putting the spliff in the Ugg boot box
and sending them to [ __ ] America. If
you want me to hand them to you
personally, if that's what will if
that's what will make me get my mama
back, that's fine. That's okay, you know.
How [ __ ] hard you the boots? You want
the boots here? I'll give you that no
mug boots are expensive.
These cartels are mad. They're getting
you licky, bro. I swear down.
Some approaching videos coming up as
well, so be patient.
Bey, can I get some more cocktails or
can I not? You never heard of UG boots?
They're famous boots, bro. From Australia.
Yeah, they're they they they've been
going [ __ ] years, mate. They've been
going years. Ugg boots.
You don't know about Ugg boots?
Don't know about Uggs?
Yeah, they're old school, bro.
USA will know what they're like. Don't
tell her. Nothing last forever. Greasy.
Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
Grezy, am I allowed?
Oh, it hasn't. Okay. So, I can get some more, right?
Yeah, she's I'll give her I'll give her
the I'll give her the cocktails.
I'll give her the cocktails. If she
wants the cocktails, I'll give her.
If you want the cocktails, I'll give you that, mate.
Yeah, I was chatting up this Indian
thing. I got a snap in it. She said she
wouldn't give her a number. It's quite
just on Snapchat. Two numbers. one [ __ ] Snapchat.
>> Yeah, she was all right. Australian, but
she had the same name as the person that
I approached last time.
I am [ __ ] bro.
Luigi, you sure it's okay to get some
more? I want to get some more, bro.
I'm [ __ ] lied, bro.
They must have put some mad white rum in
this [ __ ] bro.
They must have put some white rum in this [ __ ]
It's okay. Thank you, Captain.
I am [ __ ] bro.
No, I don't think you understand. I am actually [ __ ]
Two for £16. They are
two for £16.
Two for 16 quid.
So yeah, it took me four approaches to
get one number, which ain't the worst.
I got her number. One sec.
The other one don't have WhatsApp.
No, Grezy. It's pretty [ __ ] bad,
mate. It is pretty [ __ ] bad, mate. It
is bad. They're not interested in this country.
I'll sign up to South African.
We need We are going to get another
three numbers. Don't worry about that,
boss. 100%, mate. We're talking about me here, bro.
And these were sober. These ones were
sober. Except the Snapchat,
bro. We're getting We're getting We're
getting it in, bro. Trust me,
I need to go soon. I'll be back later.
them cocktails, bro. Oh my god, they're
mad, bro. They're putting some white rum
in that [ __ ]
They're putting some white rum in that
[ __ ] brother. I swear that is strong as
[ __ ] Almost broke the [ __ ] bench,
bro. That is strong [ __ ] My god.
Where do you go toilet?
>> Mother, where where's the toilets?
Look how drunk I am.
What the [ __ ] are they putting that [ __ ] bro?
Wake up some mad
That's Ant-Man's favorite right there.
That's his favorite.
[ __ ] yeah. I am [ __ ] leopard, mate.
Not a big dodge. [laughter]
>> What did the piss in the stink?
>> No, bro. Oh, nice.
Snapchat two numbers. One of them is
from Spain. One of them is from Spain
and she goes back in a couple of days.
Is weed legal? Is weed legal though?
I mean, not technically, I was saying to
her, but they're not going to do something, but then
[ __ ] hell, bro. I'm stealing as [ __ ]
I'm so drunk, bro.
take a picture of myself on the [ __ ]
booth in it.
I need to go soon, boss.
She wants that car. All right, Captain.
You all right, Captain? >> [laughter]
>> Oh my god, bro. These cocktails are mad.
They are mad. There's some Japanese ones over there.
Don't really like Japanese ones.
Right. When it gets to 70%, I need a
buff and I'll be a
them cocktails are mad. Not at the
minute. Not really.
There's like a group of six people, but
not really, bro. Not really any good.
>> Yeah, it's a bit early. We need to wait a week.
We'll get busier. Don't worry.
get a bit busy busier
>> when it's on 70%. I need to turn my phone off.
But I'm going to get some more cocktails.
>> Finish some work.
>> Oh, no self protection on my channel.
No self protection on my channel, mate.
I met some woman. She her birthday was
October 16th which is the same birthday as Monty's.
Yeah, they all finished at work, so I
need to wait. Anyways, I'm on 70%. I'm
going to go. I'll be back later. 100%
later. I'm coming back.
Some more session.