up there, son. I'm [ __ ] back now. I'm
[ __ ] steaming. Steaming as [ __ ]
mate. I was about to say to the guy
here, do you want to do it dirty, bro?
Go around the corner if you want to do
it dirty, bro. If you want to do it
dirty, we'll go around the corner, bro.
Away from the train station. One of Peter Bell.
One of Sorry, one of Peter Belly's uppercuts.
You be fitness, bro. For real. For real.
laughing off on the [ __ ] train, bro.
He would have been a [ __ ]
Guy would have got his head, mate. He
knows he would have got his head. He
knows he would have got [ __ ] up real
life, bro. Yeah. She stops running up
her mouth, mate. Leave her to her, bro.
>> Oh, and leave it. Leave it. Oh, and
leave it. Leave it, Angela. Leave it,
Angela. You got [ __ ] up, bro. >> Yeah.
No little, bro. Listen to me. No.
No. Little [ __ ] Yeah. From Ireland,
from all mixed race islanders ain't
going to stop nothing, bro. You're not
[ __ ] up. Real life.
[ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah.
Do you see him crying? He's like, "And
leave it. Leave it."
And leave it. Yeah. You knew to leave
it, bro. You You're going to told about
yourself even more. Shut up. You ain't
about that in life, bro.
Yeah. I'm You know what? Another thing
is I'm sick of these. I can't think
about it, bro. They're not No, bro.
>> They're not about that life. Trust me,
they're not about that life. Yeah.
believe it and remember
I'll [ __ ] die, bro. Just
nothing. Nothing lasts forever.
Bye. You're a weirdo. Bye-bye now.
Thought that was LT there cuz he's the
only one that calls me off private.
Yep. The [ __ ] am I, bro?
Did you see this Irish guy? This little
mix race thing. Yeah. The guy I thought
the guy was from from London to be fair.
I had to mute the mic. I was like,
really? Is that what we're really going
to go down, bro? We've got one uppercut,
you're done. It is over. Trust me, bro.
Yeah. She wants to run up her [ __ ]
mouth. Her bloke had to tell her about
herself numerous times and
Yeah, bro. I muted my mic and I told him
about himself. Really, bro? Really?
Really? I shot myself. I was stood right
next to him and I muted the mic and I
said, "Oh yeah, really?" She's running
up her mouth. You never shattered myself
from anyone in my life. Never have.
Never [ __ ] will. Yeah. Never have.
Never [ __ ] will [ __ ] myself from any
[ __ ] Yeah. We knew that from two weeks
ago. Yeah. He was going to do what? He
done nothing, bro. The guy done nothing.
I said she was running up her mouth. Her
bloke had told her numerous times to
shut her mouth. Bro, no one is doing
nothing to me ever. Believe you me, bro.
That is never happening.
Yeah, I shut it. Okay, bro. I shut it.
Okay, bro. Yeah, whatever you say, man.
You know, I'm not even going to block
it. I told the [ __ ] about her [ __ ]
self. I told the [ __ ] I told her about
her [ __ ] self and her bloke was
telling her to stop her [ __ ] How many
times? Okay, bro. You keep telling
yourself that. Yeah. No one's scared of
some little batty man little mixed race
[ __ ] for mining. Bro, one of my
uppercuts, he would have got banged out,
bro. He would have got he would have got
his nose broken, bro. Okay, I'm scared,
bro. Okay, whatever you say, bro.
Whatever you say. Yeah, because everyone
was getting involved. I'm not scared of
anyone, bro. The guy is not about that
to life. Did he come in my face? Did he
touch me? No. No. No. He knew his place.
He would have got knocked out the [ __ ]
out, bro. So, yeah. Anyways,
yeah, he told me he would take me off
the train and he done nothing. Yeah.
Yeah. He said that he Yeah. He done
absolutely nothing about it. Yeah. He
told me, but he never done nothing cuz
he went nowhere near my personal space
cuz he would have got his ass knocked
the [ __ ] out. Yeah. And he done
absolutely nothing about it. And I muted
my mic and I said, "Oh, really, really?"
Yeah, yeah, yeah. She's running up her
[ __ ] mouth, bro. The guy done
nothing. Actions speak louder than
words. Yeah. If you went anywhere near
my personal space, I would have knocked
every one of his teeth out. I would have
knocked every single one of his teeth
out. Shut the [ __ ] up. You're a
keyboard. You're not about that life. I
would have uppercuted him and busted his
teeth down his throat if he went
anywhere near my personal space, bro.
That's And that's and that's an absolute
[ __ ] thing right there.
shouted it from him, bro. He was talking
[ __ ] and he he stood nowhere near me. I
was telling the woman about herself. I
was arguing with like three or four
people at the same time. If he went near
me, he would have got his head smashed
in. Trust me, the Irish are not about
nothing. And the guy was actually Irish.
I didn't even know that to be honest
until [snorts] I started talking about
him. I would have kicked that cunt's ass
back to Ireland where we come from
because the Irish are [ __ ] weak. [ __ ]
the Irish, bro. [ __ ] the Irish. I would
have just banged him once straight in
his mouth. If he went literally near my
personal space, I would have banged him
out once and that would be it. There'd
be no coming back, bro.
Straight. And I wasn't arguing with him.
I was arguing with that stupid [ __ ]
Yeah. There was like four or five people
on me and I was arguing by my [ __ ]
self. The guy wouldn't argue with anyone
out the train, but he got [ __ ] up,
brother. Yeah. He got he got he got off
Yeah. at Ilford. He got off at Ilford. I
would have baded him up, bro. You really
really don't understand. You really
don't understand. Like, you should have
You should have learned this [ __ ] from last week.
But still, you don't learn. So, what can
we say? Why the [ __ ] I ended up this
here, bro? Yeah. [snorts] He said, but
he never done nothing, bro. Was he in my
face? Was he in my personal space? No,
he wasn't. Yeah.
Yeah. I was arguing with about three
people by myself. I was by my [ __ ]
self. By myself.
Yeah. You think that guy went anywhere
near my personal space? No, bro. And he
was mixed race as well. I didn't even
know he was mixed race. He was Irish as
well, bro. He would have got his ass whooped.
Yeah. And no doubt LT would have had
something to say about that as well, to be fair.
Bro, I don't even know who the [ __ ] that guy was.
I sounded shook. Okay, bro. Whatever you
say. I sounded shook. You know what?
It's always excuses with you people.
Every single time. Every single time,
bro. It's excuses with you people. I
don't know what it is with you. You
little mongos on this community. I seriously don't.
I'm [ __ ] I I'm led as [ __ ] but you
make these mad excuses time and time and
time and time and time again. I don't
know what the [ __ ] it is with you
people, man. Seriously,
trust me. If anyone stepped in my
personal space, they would know about it, bro.
You know what I mean? Trust me, they
they would have known about it, bro.
They would have known about it, bro. If
they stepped in my personal space, he
would have got knocked out. Yeah.
Simple. Yeah. I told her to tell her to
shut her mouth and [ __ ] wind her
[ __ ] neck in. Yeah. And her partner
had to told her multiple times to
[ __ ] stop, stop, stop. How many times
did her partner need to tell her
multiple times to stop, stop, stop? It
was like about five of the [ __ ] on me,
mate. I'm not scared of no one, bro. I'm
not scared of no [ __ ] Never have been,
never [ __ ] will be. Don't care if
they're black, white, [ __ ] mixed
race, India, Pakistan. I don't give a [ __ ] Simple.
So that's that.
I said sorry to him. Okay, bro. You keep
telling yourself that, man. I said sorry
to him. [laughter]
Oh, really, bro? Really? Really? Really?
Yeah. Okay, bro. He said he was going to
take me off the off the train. Did he do
anything to me? Did he step anywhere
near me? No, he never, bro. He done
nothing. I was too busy arguing with the
[ __ ] woman that wouldn't keep her
mouth shut. He literally said and he
done nothing. Otherwise, you would have
heard about it. And I was too busy
telling her to [ __ ] shut up.
You know what I mean? If he went
anywhere near me, I would have busted
his teeth down his throat, bro. And I
would have [ __ ] him back to Ireland
where he [ __ ] come from. That's what
I would have done. Yeah.
I would have busted his teeth down his
throat, bro. and sell him back to where
he the guy was black and white. He was
mixed race and you even know what that
means. If he went anywhere near me, I
would have battered him up, bro. Yeah,
you've seen all of the times that I have
stuck it on people. He was going to do
this, but he never he never went
anywhere near me. I was arguing with
about three different people at once. He
went absolutely nowhere near me. Yeah.
Actions speak louder than words, bro. Do
you see me saying sorry? No. It will
never happen, bro. Yeah. Simple.
He chatted [ __ ] He wanted to get
involved. I was continuingly telling the
[ __ ] about herself while her partner
was telling her to shut the [ __ ] up. You
know what I mean?
You know what I mean? That's it, bro.
Because I was too busy arguing with
three different [ __ ] people.
And [ __ ] what he said. Why didn't he do
something, bro? He heard me on the train
saying [ __ ] [ __ ] women, [ __ ]
And he done nothing. So [ __ ] what he
says, bro. It doesn't matter what he
says. He done nothing. It doesn't matter
what he says. He done nothing. So what,
bro? What what what what what
you know what I mean? What what what
bro? He he literally said and I was
talking about [ __ ] women and he never
went near my personal space, bro. He
done nothing to me at all cuz he would
have got his teeth smashed out. You
don't understand, bro. This is real
life. Yeah. This is not shitty island.
This is not shitty [ __ ] He would
have got his teeth smashed in in front
of his girl. Yeah. I'm trying to argue
with about three different people at
once. Yeah. Three. Yeah. Three different
people. You know what I mean? Yeah. He
gave me the warning, bro. Yeah. Okay.
You keep telling yourself that, bro. You
keep telling yourself that. Okay. Yeah.
I shut it. Okay, bro. He gave he gave
but he never done anything. People that
are about stuff don't do anything. They
do [ __ ] bro. He never gave me no
warning, bro. I was keep telling her
about herself. She's a [ __ ] loser. I
kept I kept running my mouth, bro. I
kept running my mouth. And the guy was
mixed as well. Funny enough, L2 should
know about this as well. What did you
want me to do? Argue with a 100
different people. Bro, there was no
warning. I continued. I carried on. I
didn't get off the sp. I carried on.
Yeah, bro. What? What? Okay. What What
did you want me to say? Well, I'm
already arguing with one person. He
would have got his [ __ ] Irish [ __ ]
mug teeth smashed out. I would have
[ __ ] the [ __ ] back to Ireland where we come from.
Yeah. Anyways, bro, no one's scared of
no one. People that People talk and they
don't do [ __ ] Yeah. He knew if he come
to me, he would have got his face
smashed in, bro. Yeah. Stop [ __ ]
talking [ __ ] Yeah. I was arguing
with a woman on a trade. He wanted to
make a sly comment. Yeah. He ain't about
that life. People that are about [ __ ]
don't talk and they actually do. Yeah.
He got off the [ __ ] She got off the
train. I told her about herself. I told
her about herself. Yeah. And he done
nothing cuz if he stood near me, I would
have batted his teeth out, bro. Straight
and [ __ ] him back to Ireland, bro. You
know that [ __ ] He said this, he said
that. But what did he do, bro? What did
he do? What did the man do, bro? What
did the man do? Nothing. So, shut the
[ __ ] up. Yeah. What did he do? Did he go
anywhere near me? Did he make me say
sorry? The guy done nada. He It was all
words. Words. Words. Words. But the guy
weren't about nothing, bro. Cuz if the
guy was about anything, he would have
went up to me. He would have grabbed me
and I would have [ __ ] smashed his
teeth down his [ __ ] throat. Like, you
don't you don't know me, bro. Yeah. You
don't know me. Yeah. This, that, and the
other. But he didn't do nothing. It was
all words. Shut up. You're not about
that life, bro.
Yeah. Yeah. He is not about nothing. The
stupid little [ __ ] half car [ __ ] from
Ireland. Yeah. And tell tell LT I said
that dirty little half car [ __ ] that
done nothing. Little dirty mix race [ __ ]
that didn't do nothing. Bro, that little
half car [ __ ] could only run his mouth.
Yeah. And knowing knowing damn well that
people on the [ __ ] train that little
half car [ __ ] didn't do nothing, bro. I
would have banged it back to Ireland
where we come from. That little [ __ ]
half car [ __ ] And he lives in as well.
He say he lived in. Bro, the guy's not
about that life. Stop talking. Stop
talking and do something, bro.
You little dirty half car [ __ ] Did you
go anywhere near my Did you go near my personal space?
making me say sorry. I didn't say sorry
to no one, mate. No, I definitely
definitely didn't. No, I definitely
didn't, bro. No, I definitely didn't.
I said sorry. I said sorry. No, I
didn't, mate. Anybody can go back on
that video. I didn't say no sorry to
some half cast [ __ ] from Ireland, bro.
Are you mad, brother? No way, bro. No way.
I said sorry to some half cast little
Irish [ __ ] that's full of words. Get out
of here, man. You're full of [ __ ]
[ __ ] out of here, man. The Irish are
weak. The Irish suck dick every time.
Irish people absolutely suck dick. [ __ ]
the Irish. And I've got Irish in me as well, bro.
It ain't about that life, bro. Stop it,
man. [ __ ] me. You're boring now, man. Yeah,
you're [ __ ] You're actually [ __ ]
[ __ ] the Irish. They're all [ __ ]
Yeah, that's what they are. [ __ ] the Irish, bro.
I said sorry. What the [ __ ] I said
sorry, too. Yeah, you might want to go
back on that video. Man's never said
sorry to no one in my life, bro. Never
in a million [ __ ] years. And guess
what? You're full of excuses every
single time. [clears throat] Every
Every single time. Yeah, you're full of
[ __ ] excuses every time. Yeah, he
said. But what did he do? He done
nothing. He done nothing. So it's all
words, bro. Yeah. And you can tell LT
this. I muted cuz I was arguing with
about five people. Yeah,
bro. He would have got his face smashed
in. It's all talk. He wanted to look big.
I muted cuz I was arguing with with like
three different people.
Look at that. Three different people. Yeah.
I have never I didn't say sorry to him.
Are you mad, bro? I said sorry to him.
Are you [ __ ] mad? Are you mad? I said
sorry to him, bro. Really? Really? Okay, bro.
Are you I said sorry to him. I said
sorry to him. Are you mad, bro? You're
just making [ __ ] up at this point, bro.
Stop it. You're making stuff up.
Yeah, I'm like call Irish and Irish are
[ __ ] bro. They ain't about that life.
Then he tried licking my ass at the end
as well. I told her I told him tell her
to shut her mouth up. Yeah, if you
actually watch the video properly, I
said tell her to shut up. You are the
[ __ ] loser. Oh, stop it. Oh, and stop
it. Annie. Oh, Annie, stop it. That's
what he said, bro. You're not about that
life, bro. You'll get a [ __ ] up real
life, bro. And trust me, the next time I
go out, when someone wants to try
something, you will see real life, bro.
You will receive real life, and you will
not be able to make excuses like you
keep on making.
I'm like, yeah, quarter. Yeah. Well, I
think I'm less than quarter, but it
doesn't matter, bro. Still, [ __ ] the
[ __ ] the Irish. They all suck dick.
Simple. Yeah, they're all [ __ ]
You Hey, you an idiot. I'm a [ __ ]
Okay, bro. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. You keep
telling yourself that. Okay, bro. Yeah.
Good for you, man. Good for you. Good
for you. Good for you. I got a banging
headache, bro. Banging headache. I need
to put some videos up as well, to be fair. [sighs]
I'm [ __ ] mate. I am [ __ ] [ __ ] I
am actually steaming, bro.
Steaming to [ __ ] We got these old
[ __ ] chatting [ __ ] He said, but he
didn't do nothing, bro. He didn't do
anything. You're full of [ __ ] Who cares
about any of you, bro? Even when
someone's live, you talk absolute [ __ ]
time and time. I think I got two numbers
on the one, but you talk [ __ ] every time.
I'm [ __ ] bro. No, I am seriously seriously [ __ ]
Yeah, bully [snorts] out my own yard. [laughter]
Yeah. Okay, bro. You keep telling
yourself that, brother. You keep telling
yourself that. See you later, bud.
I didn't have this energy on the train.
I told the woman about herself in front
of a bloke. Okay, bro. I didn't have
that energy on the train. Okay, you keep
telling yourself that. Yeah. Okay, bro.
You keep telling yourself
Okay, bro. I didn't have this energy on
the train. Okay, bro. Whatever. Yeah,
man. And you keep telling yourself that.
Okay. Okay, bro. Good for you, man.
Stephen, bro, them ciles get you [ __ ]
Steven Howard, man. Okay, bro. Whatever you say.
I need to put some videos up, bro,
before I completely get [ __ ] out of
it, man. Seriously. Yeah. So yeah.
Oh, I'm [ __ ] steaming, bro.
Someone's called me.
>> One second, bro. Chill. Chill. Chill.
Listen, bro. Chill. Chill. Chill. Bro, I
am [ __ ] I am actually [ __ ] bro.
I'm actually [ __ ] bro. I'm sting as
[ __ ] man. I need to put some videos up.
I need to I need to put some videos up, bro.
>> I need to put some videos up, bro.
I am actually [ __ ] bro. I am [snorts]
steaming as [ __ ] man. really bad.
It was really bad today. Anyways, I got
I got like three numbers on one
Snapchat. It's bad, bro.
I'm trying to see.
One second. One. Chill. Chill. Chill.
I'm putting it up. I'm putting up. I'm
I'm putting it up, bro.
I'm putting it up, bro. Just chill. [laughter]
I love this [ __ ] bro. Hey, brother.
I'm uploading a video. So, just just wait here.
I am [ __ ] levered, bro. You think
it's a joke? I think it was funny, but
I'll be [ __ ] Chill.
Got to be that old age if he
will never change in his country. It
will never change.
These people in here, they make up mad
excuses every time, bro. Yeah. They They
just sit there and constantly constantly make excuses.
Constantly make excuses.
Oh, I love it. I love how they picked up
on that when I'm arguing like three
people at once.
I don't know who he is, but I didn't
even know he was with Irish until I was
coming up speaking to him. I didn't even
[ __ ] I was arguing with one person. One
person's getting involved.
Uh, no. Baz, they all had boyfriends.
Not interested. Same.
Uh, one second now. My jeans.
Uh, no. I got one Snapchat and two
numbers. One number if you're classing
them to 100% be real. Same old, is it,
Daz? Same old.
Same old. I've got a video coming up,
lads. Uh yeah, I've got a video coming
up. I've just up I'm uploading it right
now. It's going to be six minutes, so
you be the judge. I'm [ __ ] steaming
bass. I'm [ __ ] bro. I'm [ __ ] That's [ __ ]
Yeah, they're just not They're just not
interested in this country. Baz starting it.
I'm like spinning, bro.
Yeah, they all do that. They stick their
nose in, but they're not about that
life, bro. When someone sticks it on
them, they're not they're not about it,
bro. They they
until someone sticks it back on them,
they're not about that life, bro.
I don't know why I even went out today,
bro. I don't even know why I even bothered.
I mean, it's not about the money. I
don't care about spend 100 pound,
whatever, but it's like I don't even
know why I went out.
Same [ __ ] in it. I am [ __ ] sick. And
I'm [ __ ] bro. I am actually [ __ ]
Like seems [ __ ] I [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah,
it's them cocktails. They have some
[ __ ] They have some mad mad [ __ ] in
it, bro. I need to be sick, bro.
Oh, bro. I'm [ __ ] stealing, bro.
I am going to be sick. I am going to be
[ __ ] sick. I am going to be sick, man.
Seriously, bro. I'm going to be sick.
I'm actually going to be sick everywhere, bro. [snorts] Yeah. One sec.
This is serious.
I [ __ ] bro. I'm [ __ ] I'm [ __ ]
Oh my goodness, bro.
them [ __ ] cocktails
had some had some white rum in it, bro.
That was right rum. That was right, R.
That was right, [ __ ] I'm
telling you, bro.
That was a Hey, that a B. That was right wrong, bro. [clears throat]
That was right, Rob, bro. I'll tell you
I was right.
That was right. Telling you, bro. I'm tell
I'm telling you that was right. That was
That was right, Romano.
Oh my [snorts] [ __ ] god, brother.
I'm [ __ ] bro. I am actually [ __ ]
Of course kick me out, bro. You mad.
These people, they make up excuses. [snorts]
They make up excuses time and time and
time and time again.
They They make up excuses, mate.
>> Um, that's that. Chill.
Chill out, bro. Good chill. I
I'm [ __ ] bro.
This [ __ ] Yeah,
just chill, bro. Just chill. Chill,
please. I'm really [ __ ] bumped.
>> [clears throat]
>> I got like three numbers on one Snapchat
or two numbers on one Snapchat.
I'm [ __ ] dizzy, bro.
It's not all right. It's not an all good
night, bro. I've got some I'
uploading a video, mate. I'm uploading a video.
I'm uploading a video, bro. It's coming, man.
There's nothing done about this [ __ ] brother. [snorts]
It was bad, bro. [snorts]
Stop that. People not interested. Same old [ __ ]
One second, bro. Just chilling out,
please. I'm [ __ ] steaming, mate.
What do you think, Stephen? Give us a young boots. >> [snorts]
>> What do you think, Buff? Yeah.
What do you think? Give USA.
Oh my god. Sick of myself, man.
I'm stupid, bro.
There was this guy. Well, I'll tell you
about this. Let me just make this better.
This is why I hate Liverpool Street.
It's full of stuffed up. It's full of
stuck up, snobby people that think
they're better than people. And I'll
tell you a story. I'll tell you a story.
One second. Let me make this bed, bro.
[snorts] It's all right, bro. You're
good at that.
Let me make this bed, bro. >> [snorts]
>> Um, okay.
Let me make this bed, bro. I'm a bit [ __ ]
I wasn't scared of no one on no train,
bro. You mad? I wasn't scared of any
color. These people need to sit there
and make up excuses every time, bro.
Yeah, he wasn't going to. Yeah,
they say that Irish, but B, trust me,
I'm stronger than the [ __ ] Irish,
mate. And you will know that, bro. You
will know about Peter Belly strength.
Yeah, Peter Belly is because Let me say something. Yeah.
Not to be Timmy, bro, but Oh, well that
that would be it, bro. That that that
would be it, lad. Yeah. Just a little
straight straight in their head. That's
done, bro. That's it. Yeah. Nothing else.
Yeah, bro. I'm a hard [ __ ] bro. I'm a
[ __ ] hard [ __ ]
Yeah. Yeah, bro. The guy was chatting
[ __ ] I was too busy arguing with a [ __ ]
that was in front of me. It would have
got no the guy [ __ ] I was arguing with
her and her [ __ ] husband. He come
near me, bro. Would have been straight
in your face, bro. It would have been
like this. Like straight bam, bro. Trust
me, you don't know me, bro. Trust me,
you don't know me, bro. Yeah. And if you
carried on, I would have said, "Do you
want to do you want to do do you want to
do it dirty, bro?" Yeah. If you want to
do it dirty, bro, we'll go over there.
Come. That's what I would have said to
him. If you want to do it dirty,
if you want to do it dirty, bro, we'll
go over there, bro. Straight. Yeah. No,
you wouldn't have known, Buff. You would
have known, buff, trust me. Yeah.
If you want to do it dirty, buff. Yeah.
No, Mr. B. I'm not having it anymore,
bro. I'm not having it anymore. You want
to do it dirty, bro? You want to do it
dirty, bro? Yeah, she was shouting
[ __ ] [ __ ] Her [ __ ] e her [ __ ]
husband was telling her to shut the [ __ ]
up. Yeah, [ __ ] [snorts] pack it in.
Leave it. Leave it. Yeah. Time and time
again, bro. We heard about Leave it.
Leave it. Leave it. Yeah, bro. The guy
next to me can say what he wants. Is
anyone in my personal space, bro? Is
anyone in my personal space, Mr. Me? No,
they're not, bro. No, they're not. Cuz
we would have done it dirty, bro. Yeah,
dirty, bro. Trust me. dirty. Yeah. I
don't care where they're from, bro. Yeah. Scotland,
[ __ ] Ireland, wherever the [ __ ] they
were. If you want to do it dirty, bro,
we'll do it dirty, bro. We We'll [ __ ]
do it real real life, bro. Yeah. Trust
me, Mr. B. Mr. B. Listen to me, bro.
Yeah. I'll [ __ ] you up. Real life, bro.
Yeah. Real life, bro. Trust me. No. No.
No. No. Mr. B, you will get [ __ ] up
real life, bro. Yeah. Trust me. It's not
a joke. The video is is it's it's 4
minutes remaining approaches. This is
the approaches that I've done. Yeah. You
you'll get [ __ ] up real life, bro.
You'll get [ __ ] up real life, brother.
Yeah, Mr. B. I'm not scared of no Irish.
Yeah. I'm a man's man, bro. Yeah.
Straight. Put straight my chest out.
Dumb, brother. You understand, Mr. B?
I will [ __ ] you up, bro. Yeah. I will
[ __ ] you up real life, bro. Yeah,
it ain't a joke, bro. You think
everything is funny, bro. Yeah.
You think everything is funny, bro.
Every time you laugh at this [ __ ] Look Look,
just stop. Stop. Stop it. I got I got some boots.
Look, Mr. Be
I was thinking of getting these.
I was thinking I'm thinking of giving
these I was thinking I'm thinking of
giving these away [gasps]
bro. I was thinking of giving these to USA. Look
brand spanking new hugs. I paid for them
bro. My own money
straight. Bam. They're not fake. They
got no certificate on them. They're not
fake. Mr. B 100%. They're real, bro.
They're [ __ ] all authentic. Yeah,
they're all they're all they're all
they're all authentic, brother. Yeah.
But you know what? [ __ ] you. You're not
having it. Yeah. You're not having my
You're not having my Ugg boots. You're
not having my Ugg boots. You can get
[ __ ] They're mine. They're mine. I
bought them £165. Yeah. £165.
£165. They cost me. Yep. Yes, they did.
Now I've had to deal with these little
snobby [ __ ] today, mate. Yeah. It's why
I avoid going to Liverpool Street, cuz I
don't like dealing with them. I don't
like [ __ ] dealing with these sloppy ass [ __ ]
But I went to Liverpool Street. I had to
deal with them.
No. Listen, listen. Hold on. When you're
sober, we'll have a we'll have a debate
about this. Yeah. Yeah. He weren't
having it cuz he knew. He knew he'd get
his ass whooped on a debate. In a debate
on a debate in a debate.
You're not [ __ ] mate.
You are [ __ ]
Yeah, you're not more intelligent than
Peter, mate. You might be more intelligent than
let me tell you something. You're not
more intelligent than me.
You're not more intelligent than me.
Hey, you are not more turning than [ __ ] me. Yeah.
Was I scared on the train, Stephen
Howard? Was I scared on the train? Did I
seem scared on the train to you? No, I'm
not scared. No,
these people make up stuff. Yeah,
these people make up [ __ ]
Told her about her [ __ ] self, bro.
Even a man couldn't say nothing. The
These people are full of [ __ ] every
time, bro. Yeah.
Do you know what, brother? I'd love I'd
love I'd love someone, bro. I'd love
someone to come for me, bro. I would
love someone to come for me cuz I would
give them a good old [ __ ] hiding,
bro. A good oldfashioned hiding.
You know what I would give them? I would
give them a good oldfashioned hiding,
bro. Good oldfashioned hiding. No
knives, no [ __ ] none of that, bro.
A good old A good old [ __ ] walop in
there, [ __ ] Yeah, just like I said on
the train, bro. You saw me saying what I
said on the train. A good old [ __ ]
wallet, bro. A good oldfashioned [ __ ]
Yeah, that's what I'd give them, bro.
Yeah, a good old [ __ ] good oldfashioned
one, bro. These people make up excuses.
Excuses, but I'm by myself. I'm arguing
with people. I'm arguing with people on
the train by myself, brother. Yeah,
there about four people. Anyone come
near me or touch me, bam, they're
getting straight banged in their jaw,
bro. Simple. What? What are you saying?
You still making up these excuses?
every time. Like
I'm sick of this [ __ ] bro. It's I went
out today, bro. Steen All
same old [ __ ] I have a boyfriend.
I'm like I'm sick of this politics now,
bro. I am so sick of this [ __ ]
with this with this [ __ ] in this country
time and time and time and time and time again.
[ __ ] enough of it, babe. Yeah,
I need to make this bed and I'm drunk.
Don't know how I'm going to make this bed.
By the way,
the thing is, bro, it's it's
it's not funny, bro. Like, you might
think this stuff is funny, but none of
it is funny, bro. You might like the
content and whatnot, but bro, it's not
funny. None of it is funny. It's depressing.
It really really is depressing, bro.
Man to man, it ain't funny. It's
depressing. I take some pills cuz I'm But
but honestly, bro, it's not funny. It
really really ain't funny, bro. This
situation is [ __ ] depressing as [ __ ]
Like, all all jokes aside, you can't
even speak to someone
hour without hearing, "I've got a
boyfriend. I'm not [ __ ] interested."
It's the same old [ __ ] The video is uploading now.
I You watch that video, mate. Yeah.
You watch that [ __ ] video, mate.
Yeah. I'll give them [ __ ] Irish [ __ ]
what for, mate. Yeah. And I'm I'm cool.
I'm like [ __ ] 25% Irish, if not less.
Trust me, ain't nothing to be scared of,
mate. Trust me. I'm a [ __ ] [ __ ] I'm
not violent. I don't believe in
violence. I'm not going to have someone
have their mouth. Of course, I'm not
going to have that, you know.
[ __ ] that [ __ ]
Anyways, video is up now. So, enjoy laughing.
I would rather someone laugh at
a how depressing I see is, but joke.
I don't know why this is so
why this is so hard in this country,
bro. Trying to meet someone. It's
[ __ ] depressing, bro.
I was I was speaking to this guy. I'll
tell you about this when I've made this bed, right?
I'll tell you about this made. But I'm
gonna message these friends because we
got I've got their I got their socials
and stuff. I know their names. And one
second, let me make this bread. And I
said to him, "Listen, I listen listen.
It's not what I'm perceiving. It's my
experiences. I'm more than happy to have
this electro conversation with you, bro.
Like I You don't think I'm intelligent?"
Yeah. Because your parents are rich and
ta bro. Trust me, you would get [ __ ]
in the park. You wouldn't lose. You
won't win the argument against me, bro.
Yeah, we're cold, lad. Cold. So, at the
end of the day, mate, you
you're not going to win against me, bro.
I'm very intelligent, bro. As much as
you think I'm not. I mean, I'm
intelligent. No, I'm not claiming I'm
the smartest person in the world. I'm
not going to claim that. I don't claim
that. But trust me, I am very, very intellectual. electrol.
Trust me, bro. Yeah. And the guy went, I
said, "Listen, give me a Snapchat. We'll
have this debate. I'm so confident. Even
though this guy is a stuck up snob, I'll
beat you in it, bro. Any day of the
week." Um, and he weren't having it,
mate. He was, "Oh, no, no, no." I was
like, "No, no, no, no. Come on. Come on,
man. Come on. You starting this now.
Let's have this combo. Come on. Me and
you straight." Yeah. You won't have
enough of it. Little snob. Little stuck
up. Snobby little [ __ ] That's why I
don't go to uh Liverpool Street much
because I will stuck up. But I thought
today we'll go for
and yeah, it will never change, will it?
They were cold as [ __ ] man. Cold as
Hope you like him. Um, don't say I don't
provide content on this channel.
I am tired. I am very tired. I feel like
I'm going to die, bro.
But I don't know. It's uh it's one of
them. He didn't want to talk. So,
what do you do?
Will never change.
You'll never change.
Same old. same love.
I just thought, "Fuck it, man. [ __ ] it."
[ __ ] cocktails. [ __ ] me up.
I don't like snobby people, but I think
they're better than everyone.
Keep it real with me, though. I'm from
London, bro. Like I can't stop scure
you can't either.
I made this bed [ __ ] stink out my [ __ ] head.
No, it's not about the money that you
spend. It's about how hung over you
actually end up,
which is how hung over I am.
I'm so so I'm so tired. So tired. Farts. So
I fall asleep. Don't judge a boy, bro. tired.
I was speaking to a we a wey bit.
I am Steven.
Oh my god, brother. I am [ __ ]
I'm so tired.
I am so tired.
I am so [ __ ] [snorts]
Bro, I need to leave. I'm tired, bro.
I'm so tired. Yep.
I'm gone. I'll be back tomorrow. I'm tired. Bye.