Back. I'm back. I kind of feel a bit
better now, man. But I'm still [ __ ] a
bit steaming to be fair.
But I am [ __ ]
as [ __ ] bro. really bad. [ __ ] that.
I've had to sick about a million times, bro.
[ __ ] so [ __ ]
I was scared of him right now. Should be good.
Just watched a bit of porn madness.
Yep. A bit of porn.
[ __ ] bro. I'm [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah,
I'm so tired as [ __ ] I'm tired as [ __ ] bro.
This is why I don't drink spirits, cuz I
end up [ __ ] like mad. Yeah.
Oh my god, bro. I'm [ __ ]
Yeah, I stood my ground, bro. I'm not
scared of no [ __ ] I don't know why that
guy was making excuses.
I'm not scared of no [ __ ] bro. I was
arguing with like three people at once,
bro. I'm not scared of no [ __ ] You know
what I'm going to do next time, bro? I'm
just going to knock some guy out, bro.
That's what I'm going to do next time to
shut all of these [ __ ] up. I'm
literally just going to knock some poor
[ __ ] out, bro. From Ireland. Um,
yeah. Like, literally some guy from
Ireland. Next guy I meet from Ireland,
I'm just going to knock him out, bro.
Simple. Cuz you people in here just
seems to make loads of excuses, man. It's bad.
Yeah, man. Did you like my uh
Did you like my um sober sober approaches?
So, I take it I'm never going to beat
anyone. So, I go Thailand on Saturday then.
Steven Howard, I guess it's what it's
come to, isn't it?
I guess that's how it how it is, huh?
It will never change.
I guess that's where we're at.
Ballsy. What do you mean ballsy, bro?
Well, you got to understand, I've been
doing this for years. It doesn't praise
me, brother. I could approach anyone. It
doesn't bother me.
I'm going Thailand on a weekend, Terry,
mate. I'm [ __ ] going Thailand.
Yeah. It doesn't matter if all them guys
are around. I'm not scared of talking to
anyone, bro. You know me, bro. I've been
doing this for years.
Why would I be scared? I'm not scared of
any. This was sober. I'm not scared of anyone, lad.
I'm not scared.
Why would I be scared, bro? It's nothing
to me, bro. Talking to people today.
This is what happens when you go to a
really snobby area like Liverpool Street.
They are absolute [ __ ] I mean,
like just the people, bro. Like, the
people there were [ __ ] bro.
They are [ __ ] in in Liverpool Street.
That's why I don't normally go out
there, bro. I I just went out there
today and they're just full of
[ __ ] Absolute [ __ ]
Snobby ass [ __ ] people
that think they're better than people
cuz they got more money than people.
It's worse than actual central, bro.
They are actual worse than central
London. I was talking to this Indian dude, right?
Indian heritage, right? And he One
second, bro. I've got a headache as
[ __ ] bro. This guy was trying to talk
to me like he knew more than me. I said,
"Listen, brother." Yeah, stop trying to
sound more intelligent than you are, cuz
you're not right. And I met their
friends and stuff and I was like, "No,
we're talking. We're having this
conversation and he was trying to really
be smart proper." Like, I've never met
such a smart ass in my life. I said,
"Listen, give me your Snapchat. Give me
Instagram. We'll have this we'll have
this conversation sober tomorrow and
I'll I'll absolutely destroy you in the
argument, bro. You're not more
intelligent than me, mate. Trust me,
you're really not. And I don't I don't
claim to be a smart ass. I don't claim
to be intelligent, but mate, if I need
to be, I will be. That's it.
Then he just went off. So yeah,
Liverpool Street is a bad area for
snobby ass people. It was really bad to
be fair. I don't really go out drinking there. So
yeah, Steven, I guess they're not
interested. One Snapchat and two numbers
that are real and I got another two
numbers. I don't know if they're real or not, but
really bad area in it.
I mean, welcome to England, bro. It will
never change. I mean, what can we say?
What's what are we saying? That's not
already been said. It will never change.
It will never change. So that's bad, bro.
>> It's Saturday, so
I'm so [ __ ] bro. Like, you don't understand.
I'll put my food video up in a bit.
Yes, even I would say it is [ __ ]
It is a [ __ ] up madness.
If I had the answers, mate, I would know.
I don't know why it's so hard in this
country to find someone.
I don't know what the problem is. Like I
was speaking to this dude, right? And he
seemed uh similar heritage to me, but he
was Dutch heritage. A lot of Turkish
people are Dutch. And he said that he
went on a date, right? He's waiting for
this woman to go on a date with and she
come and she was [ __ ] stinking, bro.
She was fat. She was like a three out of
10. Now the thing is is that I can't
even get that on a date now. I can't get nothing.
Whereas he could that's all he could
get. This is what I'm trying to say.
It's really bad, bro. Like, it's You
have no hope in the There's no chance in this country.
I don't think there is to be fair. I
mean, I have one Snapchat and
yeah, the problem is me. I mean, my
videos show otherwise, so I mean, we're
not going to get into this conversation.
I mean, my videos say otherwise,
so. And this woman was big and fat, bro.
And this guy was decent looking as well.
So people that are better looking than
well, people that are look lookers to
me, bro, they're getting these fat ugly women.
No, the the women are the problem is
definitely these women in this country.
It is 100% the women in this country
because when you go to Asia, you're not
going to have any of these problems.
You're not going to have none of these
problems that you're having here.
The problem is the women in this country.
Um, so it's definitely these women. You
know, you go to anywhere in Asia, you're
not going to have these problems for as
long as you have them.
Uh, Thailand especially. So, I mean,
it's people that actually want relationships.
No, the problem is definitely women in
this country. They're stuck up there.
So, [snorts] so this guy has got like a
man bun and he's like, I don't know,
normal, decent looking and he's on a and
he's on a date with this big fat ugly
woman that's got a kid. Oh,
I'm like, what the [ __ ] bro?
So, this guy's decent looking, right?
He's on and this guy that was Indian
heritage, he really thought he was smart, bro.
He really really thought he was smart,
but he knew I would have smashed him in
the argument any day of the week. That's
why he walked off.
So that's that basically.
You'll never have any of these problems
in another country.
You will never have any of these
problems in another country, mate. Only England.
So it will never change. So,
you'll never have these problems here.
Uh, you'll never have these problems in another country.
If you was in another country, you
wouldn't be dealing with this. Any
country, it would be even if it was like
[ __ ] I reckon even if you was in
America, right? You wouldn't be dealing
with this [ __ ] for as long as you dealt
with it for.
No way. No [ __ ] way, bro. Even if you
were somewhere like America or
like Austria, I reckon 100%, mate, you
wouldn't be dealing with this for as
long as you you would have here.
They're stuck up [ __ ] in this
country. That's what it is. It's not
you. It's not me. It's not the [ __ ]
stealing of the [ __ ] war, lad.
You know, it's it they are stuck up
[ __ ] in this country. That's
literally what the problem is. And I
don't give a [ __ ] either. I don't care.
Like, I'm not even sat in it, bro. I
don't give a [ __ ] I know what it is. I don't care.
It will never change, will it? So, I
don't I don't give a [ __ ] I'm just
saying it is what it is.
Uh I don't know why he Yeah, she's some
fat ugly. She's a fat Cuz he said he's
waiting for the state. I was talking to
him. I got his number. I said, "Oh, when
I'm in Reading, we'll go for a night out
and that." And he's saying, "Oh, he's
got a date and that in it." So, I'm
thinking, "Oh, damn." Okay. So, the day
laps are working for him, right? So,
then this [ __ ] big fat woman comes
who's got a kid. I was thinking, "Oh,
damn." So, that's what you look like to
even get something like that.
Let's just say the P, let's just say the
guy's a point looking at me. It's
[ __ ] madness, bro. So
I don't give a [ __ ] anyways me but I
don't care. It will never change. So
that's that in it. So
that's that. Get used to it or leave.
That is it.
And it's not even about that. It's not
even about women. It's just the whole
thing is toxic.
That's the the That's the whole thing.
The whole thing is toxic. It's not about
one thing, mate.
You got some woman on the train running
up her mouth. I had to tell her about
herself multiple times to the point
where her [ __ ] husband or whoever the
[ __ ] it was was like, "Leave it. Leave
it." You had to say to her, "How many
times did he have to tell her to leave it?"
[ __ ] mad country. It is. It's just
full of [ __ ]
Well, we're not even just talking about
women. The country is full of [ __ ] Period.
I was like, you are a loser. Yeah. Go
sort yourself out, mate. I mean, I stood
my [ __ ] ground, mate.
Yeah. He mugged me off, didn't he? Yeah.
Really? Did he? Yeah. Yeah. Oh, did he?
Yeah. Really, man? I mean, you
constantly make excuses, don't you? He
mugged me off by chatting [ __ ] when I
was arguing with like two other
different people. Yeah. Okay, bro. Well,
bro, if he really mugged me off, then he
would have actually done something and
he would have got his teeth smashed in.
So, and he would have knew what time it was.
Mugged me off when I was already arguing
with two people. Really, bro? Yeah.
Okay. You're full of excuses. You are,
mate. You're constantly constantly full
of excuses. Why is he saying not doing,
bro? Like, we're we're like adults now.
No, it wasn't funny. There's nothing
funny about any of it. How many times
did I have to tell her to wind her
[ __ ] neck in? And that was her
partner as well. Bear in mind, that was
her partner. So, I'm arguing with like
two people. Some other guys getting
involved. And if you would have went
anywhere near me, he would have got his
teeth smashed out. Same as the bouncer.
Same as them four people. It's simple, bro.
And it ain't a good thing either. This
is why I don't go out. This is gen This
is generally why I don't go out, lad.
This is why I generally don't go out.
What energy did you want me to have? I
was telling a woman about herself and
her husband was trying to get involved.
What? What did you want me to do, bro?
Did I [ __ ] myself? Did he come in my
personal space, Terry? Did he come to my
area and I not show up? No, he never.
What did you want me to do, bro? He
never come in my face. He's a wobbler,
bro. Yeah, just like you. You're a
wobbler. You're not about that life.
I told a woman about herself. Her
husband kept getting involved. This guy
said some whatever. Okay. What What did
you want me to do, bro?
He said he would take Well, why didn't
he then? Yeah. She got off the train cuz
it was her stop. Yeah. He was like, "Oh,
I've had enough of you." Okay, cool. So,
why didn't he do anything then? Okay.
Why didn't he do anything then?
He said, "Why didn't he do anything
then?" I was arguing with the woman, so
why didn't he do anything then? I had
exactly the same energy then as I have
now. Simple. That's it.
Yeah. Why didn't he do anything then,
bro? What the [ __ ]
And how many times did I tell him to
tell her to shut her mouth? How many
times did I say it? You're full of
excuses, bro. You are actually full of excuses.
Seriously, you really [ __ ] are.
You're full of mad excuses every time,
bro. What he said. If he was really
about anything, why didn't you do
anything, bro? Why didn't Cuz I was
arguing with the woman. I was telling
her to shut her mouth several times. Yeah.
Why didn't he do anything? Why didn't he
Why did he spoke speak and not do? He
would have got hurt, bro. And this was
like some mixed race guy and he was
Irish like you know them kind of
hoodlams, bro. The guy would have got
himself hurt, bro. Really? And why do
you care? You make excuses anyways.
So what what what what do you want, bro?
You make you constantly make excuses
for everyone I stick on. So why do you
care, bro? Why do you care?
He said, but did he did he do anything?
Was he in my face, Terry? Yeah, he said.
But did he do anything?
But did he do anything? No, he never. So shush,
you know, and bro, you you're constantly
you constantly make excuses. So why why
does it matter what I do and what I don't do? So
>> yeah, why does it why does it matter?
Why did I move my life? Cuz I was
[ __ ] arguing with someone, you
[ __ ] idiot. What do you do? Do you
think the guy come in my face, bro? It
would never happen.
It would never happen, Terry. It would
never ever happen.
[ __ ] I was sick a million times, bro.
What do you mean? Why did I mute the
live? cuz I was telling that [ __ ] about herself.
Did you hear her husband that's enough
now? That's enough now. Did you Did you
[ __ ] hear her, mate? Did you hear her
husband telling her that's enough now?
That's enough now. Shut up your [ __ ]
mouth, bro. You only had one person on
the train [ __ ] defend you. You know
what, Timmy? Next time I'm going to I'm
really going to knock someone out, bro.
And you're still going to make excuses.
You're still going to make excuses.
You're still going to make excuses,
mate. Like every time you always do.
[ __ ] madness, man. You're [ __ ]
full of [ __ ]
Yeah, I'm all talk. You're all talk. I
went to your area last time and you
don't [ __ ] all, mate. So what? You all
[ __ ] talk. You will
you'll always be all talk.
But no, all seriousness, Livermore
Street is full of stuck up people. It's
worse than central London.
To be honest, it never even got busy in the end.
All stuck up women, [ __ ] Even the
people that aren't women, they're just [ __ ]
Really, Terry, man, you love me. Really, mate?
You and your [ __ ] boyfriend, eh? You
and your boyfriend out. Yeah.
Well, it will never change, will it?
You'll never change, will you, Terry, sir?
It will never I don't know why it was so
quiet to be fair. I mean it is Thursday.
It was [ __ ] dead.
It's [ __ ] dead, mate.
[ __ ] dead, bro. [ __ ] Then it
started raining as well.
Oh well, I'm going to have a nasty
hangover tomorrow. Yay. Yay.
It's so bad, bro. had these [ __ ] cocktails.
It's [ __ ] It's not funny, bro. It's [ __ ] serious. Yeah.
I don't know why it's so difficult,
Steven Howard. Bro, it's [ __ ] hard
trying to date in this country, you
know? I wouldn't mind getting dates and
[ __ ] them up. I would be like, I
don't give a [ __ ] lad.
B, I don't give a [ __ ] I know it will
never change, Terry. It will never
change. Do you think I give a [ __ ] if
these two numbers on one Snapchat don't
reply? I don't give a [ __ ] It will never change.
I mean, I'm not expecting them to reply.
I mean, I would be more surprised if
they do anything different. It will
never change. Like, I don't give a [ __ ]
bro. I don't care. That's what I'm
saying. I generally don't give a [ __ ]
I'll say the same [ __ ] tomorrow, bro,
when I'm awake. I don't care. It will never change.
So, I don't I don't give a [ __ ] I'm
leaving anyways. Why would I give a
[ __ ] I'm leaving, bro. I don't care. I
do this [ __ ] for the shits and giggles.
It will never ever ever change. So
that's starting it.
Banging headache, man. Banging headache.
And when you drink the tea, it makes it
worse. It makes you just want to be sick.
What do you want me to do? Cry about it.
I'm not crying about it, bro. I I know
it will never change.
What do you want, bro?
It will never change, will it? It's like
what Ant-Man said. It's like what Antman
said, Terry. Well, it would never
change, will it?
Get used to it or leave in it. That's
that. And I'm leaving. [ __ ] that. I'm
[ __ ] leaving, mate.
I spent £100 today. Yeah.
I'm [ __ ] tired, bro.
I don't think you can find someone. I
don't think you can.
Unless you've got like loads of
Instagram followers and you're famous. I
don't think you can find someone in this country, bro.
I don't think you can find someone unless [ __ ]
you're rich and famous.
From what I've seen from these Tik
Tockers, to be fair.
I don't think Oh, well, I don't think
you're going to find someone. I don't
think you can. Yeah.
[snorts] I don't know what you're going
to do, man.
I'm leaving. Huh?
For the uh Yeah, clear.
Cleared out a lot of things, bro.
Bro, that's a madness. I need to put my
food video up to be fair.
Yeah, one Snapchat and two numbers.
One was from India to be fair,
which is why they spoke back in the first place.
I don't think you're going to find
someone here, bro. I I really really don't. No.
And Liverpool Street was the worst area
as well. They're [ __ ] all stuck up.
They're all [ __ ] [ __ ]
And I mean the people I mean generally
the people are [ __ ] [ __ ] Um yeah. Yeah.
I am [ __ ]
Anyways, I'll be back tomorrow. Anyways,
I'll see you later, bro. I'm [ __ ]
going to sleep. I'm tired.