[ __ ] it up.
>> You don't mix your drink
sick about a million times. [ __ ] madness, bro. Oh maybe.
Oh bloody matey. Oh. Oh, [ __ ]
This was hard, bro.
I'm going to cook this bloody bacon when
it comes. I'm [ __ ] starving.
[ __ ] starving. I am
going mix your [ __ ] drinks. Yeah, I
remember why I don't now.
[snorts] I remember I [ __ ] don't to be fair.
Yeah. One Snapchat, one [ __ ]
number. Two numbers.
Yeah, it's [ __ ] hectic, bro.
Oh my god.
So tired, man.
Well, yesterday was a complete waste of time.
It's as if we almost never went out.
And yep, that's that's that. Well, well,
well off tomorrow anyways, so that's
going to be lash.
At least I've got a day to recover. It
will be lash. Absolutely lush.
That's how you know the
the the scene is dying. The um
the the the the club scene cuz it was
dead yesterday, bro. And even though
it's Thursdays, Thursdays are normally
busy. So unless you go right right into
Central, no [ __ ] really goes out.
you ain't got the money or they're
saving for [ __ ] Christmas or
something along the lines of that, you Yeah.
Come on, man. I need some food.
Need some greasy crispy bacon, bro.
That's what I need.
people think I don't take I don't take
offense to it now you know so you know
when people ask me if I took cocaine
it's because basically when I'm bad enough sober
I'm outgone enough sober when I drink
it's just like I'm completely crazy
aren't I so
that's why people think I take cocaine That's mad.
That is madness.
Go up. There we go.
This guy told me that he lives in China
with his wife. That's [ __ ] mad.
And the other one said they live in Bristol.
Madness, bro. [ __ ] Bristol. I met
some people yesterday. Good old Bristol.
Good old Grizzle.
Good old Rizzle.
How we doing, man?
I'm [ __ ] hung over as [ __ ] I was
violently sick. Yep.
I'm just going to have some bacon in a
bit. And yeah, I got
two real numbers of one Snapchat.
I know it it was dead, man. I don't
know. People don't have money anymore to
to go out. I don't know what it is. It
was kind of dead to be fair. [ __ ] But um
yeah, I mean, most people weren't
interested. I mean, it's it's what you
expect now, is it? It's England. I mean,
what's more to say about it?
Now I'm just going to have a load of bacon. Yep.
Oh my god, I'm tired. I'm going tomorrow
as well, so it gives me a day to recover.
Oh, bro. I thought I was going to die,
man. Never mix uh Never mix um spirits.
Never mix spirits.
That's all I'm saying, boy.
[snorts] That's all I'm saying, boy.
Yeah, I had like these cocktails and
[ __ ] man. [ __ ] Absolutely mad. No,
just feel [ __ ] I feel dead, bro.
There's a lot of stuck up people in Liverpool Street.
There was these three guys I met and
they were intolerable.
Like well not all of them. Two of them were so
so intolerable, bro. Like they was just
so like I can't explain it. Like full of themselves.
Two of them. The other two was all right
to be fair, but they were so like I
can't explain it, bro.
Just full of themselves.
Like it's Yeah.
They think they're better than everyone
because their parents are [ __ ] rich
or some [ __ ]
Yeah. Like really really uh
stuck up. That's the most westernized
place you could ever go to is is
Liverpool Street, bro. Proper, proper.
So that's that. Yeah. >> [snorts]
>> Yep. Get used to it or
I'm I said to him that we would have
this debate as well
and uh he was like
could you imagine like Timmy trying to
win a debate against these people? Never
happened. Where did they go? Oxford Uni.
That explains why they're so stuck up.
You heard of that? Oxford Uni? Yeah.
And there was this guy, right? He had a man bun
and uh I thought he was Turkish. Like I
thought he had like a similar heritage
to me. And then he said he's got this match on.
So the guy is like I don't know
average above average guy. He said that
he's got a date. And I'm thinking, "Oh,
the date's coming." Like, she's going to
look good in it. Obviously, the [ __ ]
was humongous, bro. And she was a single mom.
So, I mean, what? I couldn't believe
what I was seeing, bro. [ __ ] hell. Yep.
I couldn't believe what I was seeing. It's mad.
Yeah, just uh disagree. But me
guy commented on my video, right? And he
said, "Except that you're he spelled
accept wrong. Except that your life's
your life's loser." Now, the thing is,
right, A, you can't even spell except
right. And B, right, nobody on this
community can call anybody a loser.
These people here are living their worst
life. Like a rich and famous person can
can say something. These people in this
community can't say anything about
anyone. They're living their worst life.
Like they don't even they don't even
leave the house,
you know? And I said, "Bro, you can't
even spell properly, you [ __ ] alcoholic."
Probably an alcoholic to be fair. And
I'm thinking they can't tell anyone
about any anything. They can't tell
anyone about anyone, you know,
anyone anyone's life. You know what I'm saying? So
yeah, bye-bye. We don't have mongos on my channel.
You know the drill, delay. Don't know
why you waste your time.
Stop self projecting.
What? Did I hit a nerve or something?
Come on, bro. Like, no one on here can
call anyone a loser. These people are
living their worst life.
Like, their worst worst life, bro. I
mean, they they they don't even leave
the house, these people. That's how bad
their life is.
Sat there trying to judge people that
they don't [ __ ] know. Like, it's it's
it's insane, bro. How can anyone on here
try to call anyone a loser? It's mad.
How can the How can the biggest losers
ever try to call another person a loser?
I mean, it's
there's not even room for criticism when
these people are living their [ __ ]
worst life, you know? Musty beard. [snorts]
These people are [ __ ] weirdos. I'd
say most of these are virgins on here,
you know, on this community, bro. I
notic you say most of these are virgins on here.
I reckon so. I reckon so
I reckon they are virgins.
See, the dating [ __ ] it doesn't bother
me even though I've had [ __ ] spirits.
So now I'm going to be [ __ ] depressed
cuz that it really doesn't bother me
because you would be more you would
expect this. You would you would be more
surprised if something else happened.
You'd be more surprised if something different happened.
You understand? You'd be more surprised.
So it's not even like you can't even be
surprised at it. It's just same old isn't it?
What's what's left to say, man?
Like I'm dying,
bro. I feel like I'm dying, bro. So yeah,
making [snorts] an account of someone's
bed. How old are you, bro? In your 40s.
Got to be in your 40s. One second.
You go, man. Sorry about that. [ __ ]
just got my Instagram message.
Snap's all right to be fair. Snapchat's good. Um, Snapchat is
Let me listen my Right.
Oh no, I got another one, didn't I? Oh
[ __ ] I forgot about that one.
Okay, I got two real numbers and one Snapchat.
I got some other numbers, but I don't
think they were real.
No, I did. I got two. I got uh No, no, I
didn't get another number.
Remember that actually.
She was Tai. I was like, should I really
approach Tai? I'm not really into Tai. So, realistically,
you have two options
as far as this goes.
You either [snorts] try every single day
and put up with the [ __ ] and have to
be really really really really stubborn
or you leave which is what I'm doing. I
mean that's the only two options that you've got. Um
so that's that's that in it.
Those are your two options. There's not
even there's not even a third one. Sorry, brother. Candy,
I already knew the results.
I mean, my approaches show otherwise,
Mike. I mean, my approaches prove my point.
So, I mean, my approaches
kind of show that it's them, but we
won't get into that. I mean, we're not
talking about who's at fault. My videos
prove my point, so whatever you're
saying doesn't really make any sense.
But anyways, just playing some GTA.
I mean, I've literally done approaches normally
and shown what happens when you try to
speak to someone. That's the end of
that. It's that's that's the end of
that, bro. There's no right and there's no wrong, you know.
So anyways, we're not going to keep
going around like you you people in here must have
you must be the only people
that will be proven wrong and still
think that you're right. And and you
might think that I'm that I'm just
saying that, but you are the only people
on here, right, to be shown black and
white evidence like the black and white
TV pictures in the in the 50s and you
still think you're right. It's it's it's
madness, mate. It's madness. It's
absolutely madness. And now you're
making up excuses that women don't want
to be approached. Well, dating apps
don't work. So, I mean, you don't have
any thing. And another thing, Candy man,
you were saying that women hate me. They
[ __ ] hate you as well, you [ __ ]
loser. Where's your woman? They hate
your guts as well, you loser. Just like
they hate 80% of other people. You know
what I mean? I was like, they [ __ ]
hate you as well. You [ __ ] loser. Little singleton.
Little [ __ ] You will not come on the
panel and say anything. You little
[ __ ] Yeah, it's like exactly what I
was saying to the trade yesterday, bro.
They hate you as well, you single
[ __ ] You're probably still a virgin,
mate. You little [ __ ] [ __ ] Get off
of YouTube. Go get laid. Women hate you
as much as they hate me, you [ __ ]
You've never been with a woman, mate.
You probably never seen a woman naked. So, yeah.
And yeah, it is London's fault. I mean,
people in people in London are stuck up.
And we're not even talking about women.
I met some people yesterday and it's
complete [ __ ] in London. So, it is
London's fault. Yeah, cuz it's full of
[ __ ] London is full of [ __ ]
bro. We're not even talking about the
women. It's London's fault. Yes, it's
full of [ __ ] It's a [ __ ] place, you know?
I mean, London is full of [ __ ]
This is a guy who has had more women
than you, you little gay lord. This is a
This is a guy that's had more women than
you, and you're still a virgin.
I mean, you're the guy that's still a
virgin, and you're telling me about
women hating me. [ __ ] out of here, mate.
Dusty, get a life. We know it's you
behind that account.
You're so much of a [ __ ] that you you
just gave it away, bro.
And they hate you as well. Women hate
you as well because you're ugly. Yeah, I
know. Women hate you as well, Dusty. You
look low life. Exactly, bro. They hate
you as well, Dusty. You look low life.
Dusty showers. I told you this, bro.
I've known it all along. Listen,
Greavesy. I've known all along that this
candyman is Dusty Showers. How many
times have I said this, bro? It's the
same little virgin that ain't got a life.
It's the same ugly little low life that
ain't got no life. I'm not going to give
myself a headache. Yeah, bro. Your right
hand doesn't count.
Your right hand doesn't count. And let
me tell you something, bro. I'm more I'm
way better looking than you will ever
be. And I've had more women than you
will ever be. Dusty show bizy little
manta. Yeah, you are. Go [ __ ] suck up
your mom, you little single virgin. Get
the [ __ ] out of here, bro. I knew it was
you. You're so disabled that you can't
even Let me tell you something, Grezy.
Yeah. You know, I've gone on Monty's a
couple of times behind fake accounts.
You didn't know that, did you? Yeah.
This guy is so disabled that he gives it
away that it's him. He's so much of a
[ __ ] disabled low IQ that he gives
away that it's him. That's how disabled
he is. Like they give it away. That's
how disabled they are. But bro, you
never caught me, did you, on Monty's,
did you? You never caught me on Monty's,
did you? No. But this little single
virgin m that women hate, we can we can
literally spot him a mile off.
Don't [ __ ] try and come on my channel
trolling me, you little spaz. You little
[ __ ] ma, little virgin. Don't [ __ ]
come on my [ __ ] bro. Yeah. With your
behind your little gay account, you
little gay lord. Yeah. And try and troll
me. And I told you this as well months
ago, Grezy. I told you this months ago, bro.
Yeah. That it was him. Yeah. You [ __ ]
little [ __ ] little [ __ ] Yeah. My
manta, bro. Listen, listen, listen,
listen, bro. Do you want me to meet you today, bro?
Yeah. Before I go. Okay, bro. Do you
want me to meet you today? Yeah. Do you
want do you want me to meet you today or
not? Listen, bro. I'm I'm free today.
Yeah, you little [ __ ] Right. Let me
smack your ugly face in, bro. I'm being
serious. No [ __ ] now. No [ __ ]
No, no, no, no. Listen, listen to me. Do
you want me to come and meet you today
and smash your ugly face in, you little
keyboard warrior? Do you want Do you
want me to come and meet you today or
you just going to keep typing [ __ ]
You [ __ ] little single [ __ ] little
virgin. That's what I thought, you
little [ __ ] Cuz you know, bro, you
[ __ ] know. Yeah, you know. You're a
little [ __ ] I can say whatever I want
to you, bro, and you're not going to say
nothing back. Cuz Dusty Showbiz is a
singleton [ __ ] That's scared of me, bro.
I mean, why not, bro? I had nothing bad
to do. So, do you want to meet today or
not, bro? So, do you want to meet today or not?
Tanny. Tanned, do you want to meet today
or not? Exactly. Own me, bro. You little
bongos don't own no one. You're sat at
home in your 40s. No money, no life.
Bro, you own yourselves, you little
[ __ ] bro. You own yourselves. Life
owns you every day. You wake up ugly,
alone, no money, can't leave your house.
Bro, life owns you. Again, you must you
must this your disabilities must get you
confused. You fat ugly little [ __ ]
low lives don't own [ __ ] How long have
you had me on here running up my mouth
about you and you done absolutely [ __ ] all, bro?
Yeah, man. Simple, bro. Okay, whatever
you think. But guess what, bro? You're
not going to meet me ever. How am I
lying when I told you that I'm going
tomorrow, you little [ __ ] Why are you
making new accounts? You shouldn't you
be at work, you little jobless mong. You
own me, bro. I'll meet you today and
I'll slap you across your face. Bro,
listen. How about How about I own you in
real life today, bro? How about I meet
you today? How about I meet you today
and I own you in real life? Not behind
the keyboard? How about that one? How
about I come and slap the [ __ ] out of
you today? Are you going to keep making
excuses? Oh, you're going to just keep
making excuse after excuse after excuse.
How about I come and own you and back
slap you across your ugly face today?
So, you don't want it then. So, stop
talking [ __ ] There's no point being a
keyboard warrior. Listen, bro. You're
older than me being a keyboard warrior.
Take that L. Take that L, you keyboard
warrior, bro. If you can't even come on
a panel, you're so disabled. You
probably be slurring your words cuz
you're a [ __ ] [ __ ] I mean, bro,
you've got so much anxiety, you can't
even join the hangouts, lad.
You're a little keyboard warrior, little
[ __ ] scared to join the panel when
you're running up your mouth. You know,
at least with the other ones like Reeves
and whatever. Well, the guy's not on my
[ __ ] hating. Yeah. You're hating, but
you're scared to join a panel. What
could you possibly own, brother? What
could you possibly own? You're terrified
to join a panel. You sit there behind
the [ __ ] keyboard, bro. Stop it, bro.
It's too early for this. Just [ __ ]
stop it. You're scared to join a panel.
I can't take you serious, bro. If you've
got if you've got if you got Oh, you'll
join a panel. One second. Otherwise, I I
can't take you serious. I can't take
someone serious that's scared to join a
panel. I [ __ ] can't, mate. I [ __ ] can't.
I really can't, mate. Well, we'll put
the link up for you anyways if you want to join.
Dusty showers, you made another account.
You made another account. You made
another account, bro. Calling me a
bunter. I'm better looking than you will
ever be. You single virgin.
Bro, I'm better looking than you will
ever be. You are the m. Stop looking in
the mirror, you little scaredy-cat. Grab
a pair of balls and [ __ ] join the
panel for a [ __ ] change. One second.
Let's see if the [ __ ] is brave enough
to join a panel. Come on.
Come on, Dusty. Come on, Dusty.
Come on, Dusty. The anxietyridden
bastard. Scared of panels. Come on. Come
on. Come on. Let's arrange to beat
today. Come on. What are you scared of?
What are you scared of? Scared of a
[ __ ] panel, you [ __ ] ugly loser,
bro. You've never been with a woman.
Women hate you more than they will ever
hate me, bro. Yeah. Women hate your
guts. You're sat there alone in your
40s. No life, repeating yourself. Little
[ __ ] I knew it was you straight away
cuz you're so disabled. You don't own
me, bro. Own me. You can't even join the
panel, bro. You can't even join the
panel. You [ __ ] m you ugly bastard
behind the keyboard, bro. Triggered,
you're the one typing to me, bro. Come
on the hangouts and I will own you, ugly
bun. Come on, and I'll come and slap you
up today. I will come today and slap the
[ __ ] out of you. Come and join the
panel, bro. What's What are you waiting
for? What are you waiting for? Dusty,
the little spacker that has to make
different accounts cuz he got bullied
off of the other one. Come on. Come on,
you little [ __ ] Let me come and meet
you today. I'm serious, bro. I'm deadly
serious. Let's go. Let me smack your
teeth down your throat before I go
[ __ ] you know, to Thailand, bro. Let
me smack your teeth down your throat,
bro. And I will violate you worse than
anyone has ever violated me. Come on,
bro. Come on. Please don't be scared.
It's Friday today.
It's not a problem, bro. Come on.
Come on. So, you're not [ __ ] doing this.
So, what's the point of it, bro? You're
not that. Look, look, bro. The link is
there. Yeah. Let's meet up today. You,
you know, you're big enough to [ __ ]
make different accounts and whatever,
but you're never going to join a panel.
It's embarrassing, bro. It's embarrassing.
You know what I mean?
Ew, a simp. Ew, a white knight. So
you're not Yeah, you're embarrassed as
well, bro. In your 40s being a keyboard
warrior, but in real life, you know,
you'd get slapped the [ __ ] out of, bro.
You wouldn't even look at someone the
wrong way in real life. You're behind
the keyboard in your 40s.
What a [ __ ] loser. This is what makes
me laugh, bro. You people Yeah. This is
the maddest thing about this [ __ ] is you
little monties, you little spackers are
older than me. You're older than me,
bro. Older than me. And I would consider
myself as getting old and you're on here
being a keyboard warrior. Spaz, but
you're scared to join a pedal. What
could you possibly own, bro? What could
you own when you're so much of a [ __ ]
you're so disabled that I knew it was
you straight away. You're so It's your
disabilities. And then you're scared to
join a panel, right? You're scared to
join a panel, but you're saying that you
own me in in what universe, bro? Bro,
stop it. It's embarrassing. Now, look,
the panel, the link's there. Join if you
want. So, are you joining the panel or not?
Dusty the little [ __ ] You scared to
join the panel, Dusty Showbiz, the
[ __ ] that's join. Bro, you're calling
people triggered, but you're typing away
to me, bro. Yeah.
Listen, [ __ ] boy. Are you going to
join the panel? [ __ ] boy. [ __ ] boy.
Listen, bro. You're talking about how
you own people. Your mom is a dirty
little slag and she got banged by a
bunch of [ __ ] and you're going to do
nothing. And I'm prepared to travel to you today.
Exactly. You're a little [ __ ] now. Run
away like you you know what you're good
at, bro. Yeah. Yo, an absolute monty
little [ __ ] Go running away, bro.
Like you always do, you little [ __ ]
Some old wrinkly man, bro, in his 40s.
Some old wrinkly fat [ __ ] in his 40s
trying to tell me that he owns me,
brother. I will travel anywhere to you
today and I will slap the [ __ ] out of
you, bro. And that is a promise. That's
why you won't join the hangouts, bro.
You're too much of a spaz. Like I said
earlier, you you you'll join and you'll
be slamming your words like that because
you Okay, if you own me, join the panel
then. If you own me, join a panel and
I'll bully you and I'll come to you and
I'll slap you up today. Simple. If you
own me, why are you scared to join a panel?
Why are you so disabled that you can't
join a panel then? Well, you don't owe
me, bro. You would get slapped up in
real life. I would punch your ugly
virgin face. from one side to the other,
lad. I would punch that [ __ ] ugly
face of yours from one. So, you're not
joining a panel then. So, you're all of
this. You're all of this. Yeah, but
you're not joining a panel. You're such
a big man, but you can't join the panel.
Make it make sense, bro. Make it make
sense. All of these other people like
crime and that, they can actually join a
panel. Yeah, exactly, bro. Man, yeah,
[ __ ] off, you little ugly bastard. Yeah,
you are the big nose. I'm better looking
than you will ever be, you little
[ __ ] We Why don't you show your face?
Show your big belly and your fat ugly
face. Show everyone what you look like.
Come on. Let's compare my looks to your
looks. You're [ __ ] the fat ugly
bastard. Just like everyone on here,
bro. Every single person on here that
has tried talking about my looks before
has all been fat and ugly. Trust me,
mate. No one cares what you fat, ugly
little skit low lives have to say about
any [ __ ] Trust me, bro. It's been like
three times now. And you people always
are fat and ugly looking. We don't care
about your projection, bro. We will show
our face. We will show our face. We're
not insecure fat, ugly bastards like
you. Now, if I was on a if I was on a
panel, bro, look, look, look, listen.
I'll do it right here, right now. Yeah.
Beard's a bit long. Listen, bro. I need
to get a haircut to be fair later.
There's a bit, bro. I can show my face
and I'm like scruffy right now, bro. I'm
not insecure about what I look like. I'm
not insecure about my nose. Do you know
why? Let me tell you something, brother.
It's because A, no one could ever make
me insecure. B, we've all seen what you
people that talk [ __ ] about people's
looks look like over and over and over
and over and over again. Yeah. Fat,
ugly, big bellied. Bro, no one cares
about you people. I look like an im. You
can't even spell immigrant. You [ __ ]
You can't You can't even spell
immigrant. You need to go back to
school, mate. Sort your ugly looks out
when you're [ __ ] whilst you're at it.
So, anyways, this is me and I and I need
to get a [ __ ] haircut. You can't show
your face cuz you're fat and ugly. Just
like all of these people that come in
here and try to talk about people's
looks. They all are fat and ugly. Bomb
Pat Mustard. Uh, I'll give you another
example. Does anybody remember Gay Cat?
Yeah. When she was talking [ __ ] about
Kayle's looks and then she turned her
camera on by accident. Nothing you fat
ugly little bastards say would ever
affect me. I will never stop showing my
face because let me tell you one thing I
know. I'm not saying I'm ugly. I'm not
saying I'm not ugly. I'm not saying that
I'm good-look. But I know one
[ __ ] thing that I'm better
looking than you and you can't show your
face. That's why you hide behind the
keyboard. So, I mean, look, this person
that's apparently all of these things
can show their face. You can't. Speaks
volume, doesn't it? And I know what
you're saying. You're going to make up
all of these excuses how you don't want
to get doxed and no no no no.
Because you know you're fat and ugly.
You know you're a fat ugly bastard.
That's what it is, lad.
So that's that.
Yeah, I a [ __ ] Bro, why are you
changing the subject? Why are you making
stuff up and changing the subject?
You [ __ ] little batty man. Bro,
you're calling me a batty man, bro. I
will travel to you today and you can
call me a batty man to my face. You
still keep ignoring me. You keep
ignoring me, ignoring me, ignoring me.
Ignore me. Ignore me. You little single
[ __ ] virgin. I'm I'm chatting [ __ ]
about you and I'm wanting to meet you
and you're just hiding behind the
keyboard. You [ __ ] loser. You don't
[ __ ] own me. The day some little
[ __ ] keyboard owns me, bro. That's
scared to join a panel. Like you, right?
Like I said, you can't even join a
panel. Like, get the [ __ ] on my level, bro.
The link is up. Okay, I'll put it up
again. One second.
You'll find my address. Okay. And you'll
Okay. And what will you do? Send me a
pizza. Please don't. Bro, please don't.
Please don't. Please don't. Please
don't. Please don't. Please don't.
Please don't get my address. Please
don't get my address. Oh, don't don't
get my address, mate, cuz you're going
to send me a pizza,
man. Give it the [ __ ] up, bro. It's
embarrassing now. Just stop it.
I can't take you serious. I can't take
someone that's scared to join the panel
serious. I I can't take these kind of people serious.
Like I said, it's obvious with you
people on here. You haters any well or
you haters? You're very fat, very ugly,
very skinn, been bullied your whole life
and you come in here trying to bring
other people down with you. You are all
the same. All you end up looking the
same as well.
You're boring, mate. Boring.
So, you're not going to join a panel
now. So, you're a keyboard warrior.
Yeah. A keyboard warrior can never own
someone like me, bro. Just stop it.
Like it's embarrassing now.
Why are you making another account to
come on someone's live stream? Do you
not know how sad that is?
Yeah. So Dusty Showbiz, you're not going
to meet me then. No, you're not going to
join the panel. So just a keyboard
warrior. So you're just a little m
keyboard warrior then, aren't you? With disabilities.
You're just a disabled little mun with
[ __ ] disabilities ain't got a life.
Yeah, bro. It's so funny cuz people like
you, bro. You You wouldn't even You
wouldn't even look at someone the wrong
way. That's what makes me laugh if you
fat ugly people. Yeah.
Yeah. They hate you as well. Yep. I
know. But they hate you more because
I've actually been with women. You've
never been with a woman. Women hate your
guts. That's why you're a single virgin.
They hate you as well. That's why you're
single. And you ain't got a woman. And
I've had women. And Peter Bell has had
women. But Dusty Showiz can't get none
because he's too ugly.
Women also hate you. And it's not
whatever I say, it's what I know. They
hate you as well. Come up here right now
and show us your woman. Come on. Come up
here right now and show us your
girlfriend. Women hate you. You little single virgin.
No, no, no. The disabled bus pass. No, I
don't. Dusty showers. Women hate you.
They keep you single. You're a little m
virgin. You're in your 40s and you're
still a virgin. If that doesn't tell me
that women hate you, I don't know what
does. You're a little keyboard warrior.
You've never seen a woman naked. You've
never [ __ ] a woman. You're too scared
to join a panel. Take that L, bro. I saw
you. You don't owe it. You don't own anyone.
Yeah. Yeah. My family hate me, do they?
Really? I mean, I see my sisters all the
time. See my mom again. We're not like
you disabled Chroers. We're not disabled
like you. We're not all 40year-old
virgins like you. Scared to join a
panel. See, I don't I don't need to
block people because you're a little
virgin. You're a little manta. You're a
little bully victim. I can say whatever
I want and you will never meet me
because you know what's good for you. Do
you think anyone can say that to me?
Your mom's a [ __ ] She sucks [ __ ]
You're a [ __ ] and you will never meet
me and you can never beat me. You're a
[ __ ] You're a keyboard warrior.
You're a virgin. You're single. All
women hate you. You're fat and ugly. You
can't join a panel. No one can ever say
that about me like I say that about you.
How does it feel? Take that L, loser
boy. Take the L that you can only keep
writing behind the keyboard because you
know what's good for you. Because you
know what is good for you. You know what
is good for you little boy. Yeah. You
know if you are a man join a panel and
we'll meet today. Simple. I will travel
anywhere to meet you today bro. Exactly.
So I mean Yeah.
I'm a bacon.
What? What? I'm What? You're calling me an aunt?
You're calling me an aunt? Wait, hold
on, hold on, hold on. Wait. You're
calling me an aunt.
You're You can't even spell properly for
[ __ ] sake. Right. You're calling me a n.
So that's what you're calling me. Wait
for this question. Well, what are you
going to do to a non What are you going
to do to a dirty bacon? What the [ __ ]
are you going to do about it, Dusty? If
you can't even join a panel because your
anxiety is that bad, you little loner.
You disabled loner. What are you going
to do to a dirty bacon? And I'm I'm a
dirt. If you're saying that I'm a bacon,
I can be the dirtiest out of date
stinking bacon and you're going to do
nothing about it. But type behind your
little keyboard cuz you're a good boy
and you're scared to join panels as
well. Isn't that right? Isn't that
right, son? You know what's good for you
though. You're a smart boy. Because you
know if you join a panel and you tell me
where you are, I'm going to beat you
today. I will meet you and I'll [ __ ] you
up. Simple. It's it's straight. But you
know better because you're a good boy.
Aren't you good boy? Goody two shoes.
Yeah, mate. I'm not talking about you.
I'm talking about this dusty showbiz. So
stop changing the rules. I will travel
anywhere to you. I will do what I
[ __ ] want. You disabled little [ __ ]
I will [ __ ] do what I want when I
want. You [ __ ] disabled little fat
[ __ ] I will do what I want when I want.
I [ __ ] tell you when I want. You fat
ugly [ __ ] I will do what I want and say
what I want. Are you going to meet me?
You [ __ ] dirty, stinky, disabled mun.
You can't even troll properly. I
fathomed you out straight away, you
[ __ ] [ __ ] right? I fathomed you
out straight away because of your
disabilities, disabled little dusty. You
know what I mean, bro? Yeah. [ __ ] out of
here, man. [ __ ] out of here. I will
[ __ ] tell you where to join when I
want, you fat, ugly bastard, and I'll
meet you anywhere you want.
Uh, I'm pretty sure everyone knows what
the side means, mate. I'm pretty sure
everyone knows that.
Jesus Christ. So, you're not going to
join a panel? Dusty Showers, you're a
little [ __ ] I mean, it does tell you,
right? If someone's that age sat on
YouTube having to troll people, what do
they have in their life? Think about it,
man. Like, and then the fact they've had
to make another account. It just goes to
show, bro. Your life is your life is
already ruined and you're in your 40s.
You're in your 40s, mate. A loner on
YouTube trolling. Look at your life.
Look at your [ __ ] life. Having to
make [ __ ] fake accounts to try to
troll people. Imagine being that much of
a [ __ ] And you're and you're past
your 30s. You're past your 30s.
You're alone on YouTube, Mr. Lonely,
trolling behind fake accounts and you're
older than me. Imagine being that much
of a [ __ ] loser. And again, I know
the thing is like, you know, I don't
have a friend in the world. Again,
projecting, mate. Everyone's seen my
friends. Everyone's seen my friends. But
let me tell you something, mate. If you
had friends, you wouldn't be sat on
YouTube alone trolling like a spastnic
every day. You wouldn't be sat on
YouTube, mate, trolling like a [ __ ]
disabled [ __ ] if you you've got
nobody, mate. You got no friends, no
misses, nobody. And everything that I
say about you is right. And you are the
ma. Stop calling yourself a m.
Yeah. Yeah. You run away like the
keyboard warrior, you ma. You [ __ ]
[ __ ] Don't make another account and
I'll figure you out again within 5
minutes because again, low IQ,
disabilities. You can't even spell
properly, bro. You literally can't even spell properly
because you're you're a [ __ ] [ __ ]
talking about friends. Where's your
friends, mate? When you're sat on
YouTube trolling people because you're a
[ __ ] lowife little bully victim. We
We Candy Man, right? Is one of them
people that got bullied in school. An
absolute bully victim. That's why he
comes on YouTube every single day. Give
me this. Because he's an absolute bully
victim. Every Do you know what? Yeah.
Every time this guy tries to leave his
house, he probably gets slapped across
his face for being so ugly. This is why
he does this. He's got no friends, no
women, no life. Just a keyboard warrior.
Just a keyboard warrior. He has got
downs, bro. He types like a [ __ ] He
types like a bongo. Because he is a
little bongo. He's a little bully
victim. Trust me, someone. Yeah, there's
no there's no content on your channel.
There's no videos.
Just an absolute bully victim. That's
all you are. Like you people in here
don't bother no one because it's
deeprooted bullying with you people that
you've experienced when you was younger.
Absolute bully victims. And everything
I'm saying is the truth. That's why
you're saying about L J because you're
an absolute bully victim. I know, bro.
I'm I I'm I'm very intelligent when it
comes to working you people out. An
absolute only an absolute bully victim
in his 40s would come on YouTube every
day trying to troll. Only a bully victim
would do that, you know, and that's
true. I mean, I'm not wrong about these people, man.
But he's so much of a [ __ ] that he
gives himself away. That's what makes it
funny. He's so disabled, he can't even
type properly. [ __ ] bongo. [ __ ] [ __ ] Absolute [ __ ]
Talking about people that's not 30, bro.
You're you're in your 40s.
You're in your [ __ ] 40s. What the [ __ ] bro?
So you're scared to join a panel? Yeah.
It's typical with you keyboard warriors. Imagine
being a keyboard at your age. You know,
people done this [ __ ] when they were
like [ __ ] 11, man. You get a grip.
You know, [ __ ] women will always hate
you more than they ever hated me, Mr.
Singleton. That's why you can't show
your woman because she doesn't exist.
There's not even any content on your
channel. No content at all. Why is there
no content on your channel? I don't
understand. You would have thought
there'd be content on someone's channel
if they're on YouTube every [ __ ] day.
Not even any content.
It's a madness, you know.
No, he is a [ __ ] He is a proper proper [ __ ]
I [ __ ] caught the [ __ ] a mile I
spotted him a mile off, mate. I spotted
that [ __ ] [ __ ] a mile off.
It's too easy. But guess what? No one
ever spotted me. No, no one ever spotted
my cup of accounts.
Oh [ __ ] One sec.
Right, I'm going to cook some bacon now anyways.
But yeah, you really need to sort your
life out, mate. You're in your [ __ ]
40s sat on YouTube trolling. It's pathetic.
It's absolutely pathetic.
Look at what I done yesterday. I went
out, done my own thing, ate some food. I
mean, what was you doing? Sat on
YouTube. It's like it's it's it's that's
what it is. And then you got a and then
you got another comment, right? I can't
even type saying you need to accept that
you're one of life's losers. Now, the
thing is is that nobody on here could
call anyone a loser.
But believe it or not, I probably got a
better life than most people on here in
terms of having a life. It doesn't all
need to be about money. These people
don't even leave their house. These
people on here, I mean, these people on
here can't call anyone a loser, baby.
They really really really know in no
place to talk about anyone, mate. Yeah,
because look at their lives on YouTube
at their age doing what they're doing.
But they say they're not disabled,
you know. They say they say that they're not.
I don't know. They say that they're not
the They say that they're not disabled,
but why the [ __ ] else here would people
be on YouTube repeating the same [ __ ]
every [ __ ] day if they weren't disabled?
You know, no offense. I mean, no offense. Seriously.
You know, they they they do all of this
because it's past trauma. It's it's
bullying. These people have been
bullied, bro. That's what they have
been. They've been bullied, bro. Yeah.
Been bullied their whole life.
You still there, Mike?
And you know, you're talking about
London, bro. We're not We're not talking
about women. We're talking about the
whole of London. Yeah. The whole of
London. Yeah. It's full of [ __ ]
Most people in London are [ __ ] Man
and women. Yeah. They are [ __ ]
And I know that cuz I've got more life
experience than you.
I dealt with some snobby [ __ ] yesterday.
They think they're better than you cuz
their parents are rich.
You know, I'm going to actually message
that guy as well. I would love to
message that guy cuz I got him on
Instagram as well. I said, "Listen, you
know your friend, I would love to have
that debate with him." You know, I would
love to have that debate with him.
just because like
you know and and I have heard to be fair
you know about the university just
because you know your parents might have
more money you know it doesn't mean
you're better than someone you know what
I mean but I was going to tell him as
well I love to have this debate with he
didn't want to have it with me yesterday
I said okay we'll have it when we're
sober then he was they were proper [ __ ]
Bro, like there was two there was four
of them. Two of them was all right. And
the other two guys, they you can just
tell that they were so up their own ass.
Like [ __ ] was always almost coming out
of it. And it it is insane. They're so
stuck up. The worst area.
The worst area to uh to uh No, they
weren't women, they were men.
So yes, it is London. It's 100% London.
And it's not and it's not a gender thing. Yeah,
that's that starting it. Look at these
bacons now. So,
no, it was these um
proper proper um
proper up their own ass.
It was weird, bro. Really very weird.
They don't have money, but their parents
have money. So, they think that they're
better than people
because they've got more because their
parents have got more money than than you No. Okay. Yeah.
Yeah. And I was like, and you could tell
that the guy was intelligent, but he was
thinking that he was more intelligent
than he actually was. And we all hate
them kind of people. I hate them. You
hate them. [ __ ] You can just tell the
vibe that he was giving off. It's just like
the other two was all right. Um
the brother lives in China. They were
all right, but uh it's the worst uh it's
the worst area for sucker people. Liverpool Street,
which makes me mad because they can't
even afford to [ __ ] go out drinking
most people. They didn't do this, bro.
It was dead. Dead as [ __ ] to be fair.
They're all slobians think they're
better than people. I've never
understood it being from London myself.
I've never I've never understood it.
Really never have. Um never never never
ever ever have. You know, I I never had
a bad childhood.
And I don't think I'm better than any
any person randomly because I'm from
London, but they do, you know.
And I was trying to I was experiencing
then he like counter wrapped what I was
saying and [ __ ] You going to stay with
you? He was a smart ass bro. >> Yeah.
I don't like people like that, bro.
I don't like people like that, bro. Hey,
I don't know.
Maybe because of my uh language, it goes like,
"Yeah, I got two numbers on one Snapchat."
But I've one number, one Snapchat. Still
early, but who knows? E.
Yeah, it was really bad. Hope you watch
the videos, man. Same [ __ ] in it. That's
that, man. Yeah. Yeah. I was being sick
earlier, bro. Bad, bad, bad. I thought I
was going to die, but in England's the
same old England. I always say it will never change.
It will never happen.
Set you settle down. You can't even get
a conversation out of someone, Jasper. I
don't think you're going to be settling
down anytime soon, mate. You can bet you
can barely get a conversation out of someone.
I don't I don't think uh I don't think
I'm going to be settling down
in this country.
You can pray all you want, mate, but I
don't think it will Well, it will never
change. It will have changed. That's not
what we think. You're going to pray for me.
Thanks, man. But it's not going to happen.
This is how bad it was, right? Dasp. But
there was this guy with a man bun and um
this is how bad it is. He was similar.
He looked similar heritage to me and I
went over and spoke to him and I said to
him, uh I said to him, Jasper, um uh oh,
what heritage are you? He said that he's
Dutch and similar similar to me. And he
was waiting for his hinge date. All of
these people get dates on Hinge. I don't
get any dates. So went on a Hinge date.
Went on a Hinge date and uh basically um
it was a Hins date
and um she was fat as [ __ ] bro. And she
was a single mom. So that tells you a
lot about the game. That in itself tells
you a lot about the game.
Yeah, she was really She was quite big.
I don't think Oh, she's going to be some
decent, isn't it? [ __ ] No.
So, uh, yeah, man. Yeah, I know.
Obviously, but I'm just saying that's
that's the game that we're in, bro. It's dead here.
I got a lot of I have a boyfriend
yesterday, Jasper. A lot of it.
It makes you [ __ ] wonder why you even
go out, mate.
Bro, mess you up.
Oh, lucky you, man. Lucky you. >> Yeah.
>> So, I think that's 26 numbers in now.
26. Not a date. Jasper, get the numbers
up now. We might have got a date before
he went, but
it will never change, will it?
Yeah. Did you like the uh Did you like the approaches?
Hope you like the approaches, boss.
Yeah, we'll never change, but I never change.
I'm funny. Why that [ __ ]
is that first [ __ ] 11. >> So,
you wouldn't be able to. I've been doing
it for years, mate. I'm used to it.
I've been doing it for [ __ ] very long time.
>> Yeah. Completely raw. Completely sober. [snorts] >> Yep.
>> That's me. That's me, Captain.
>> You know, I find them harder to do in
the actual bar. Like, I find them harder
to do in a bar. like I still do
obviously but I think so miss well
[snorts] you know
>> I done a lot yesterday a lot of approaches
no one's bloody interested in this country
it's called jealousy Jasper the thing is
with these people right let me tell you
something with these people
right let me tell you something about
these people right like They sit in all
day. They haven't got a life. They
haven't got no life. They've got no
money. They were probably bullied, you
know, in school. And that's why they
hate on anyone that like got a better
life than them or has a life. Um, that's
what it is. They're just fat ugly people
that's that that ain't got a life. Like
[snorts] I'll give you an example,
right? Somebody commented on that video
saying, "Except PJ that you're one of
life's losers." Now, he didn't even
spell except right. I said, "You spelled
accept uh wrong." And wait, no one on
here can call anyone a loser, mate. I
mean, I'm a loser probably compared to
people that are traveling the world and
doing better things with their life, but
I mean, someone on here trying to call
someone else a loser. I don't think so,
bro. So, I think he was just jealous
that I went out approaching and they're
sat indoors, no life, no money, scared
the house. It's all it comes to they
they hate I think they're depressed
people that hate anyone that's got um
that's better looking than them and
younger than them. That's what I believe
personally. Yeah. I mean I've got some
fat old I've got some fat man called
Jamie Thompson stalking me every day. He
still stalks me, you know.
I mean he still [ __ ] stalks me.
But I think it was a bad move yesterday
going Liverpool Street. It's because I
hadn't been there in so long. I thought,
let me try there and it was dead, man.
Yeah, they can't.
And I didn't think I was going to get a
date or anything. I know it will never
change. It will never change. It will
That's why I'm not off.
Yeah, he is in the [ __ ] side. Well,
>> yeah, it was just the same old [ __ ]
Not interested in this country, lad.
No. Did you What's my approaches all?
No, I didn't get nothing. Not
interested. I got two numbers and
and one snap.
Yeah. Well, actually it was it was
No, no, no. It was actually um
uh I think it was three I did. Yeah, I
think three of them
two WhatsApp ones and one that I think
as well and another one. So I think yeah
I think one of them are fake. So
yeah I think one of them are definitely fake
but two of them definitely wasn't. So
that's really terrible to be honest.
Yeah I'm still going.
Oh [ __ ] So yeah, same old. Mhm.
Yeah, I'm having roam slam. Yeah. [clears throat] >> Yeah.
I got the dentist on the 19.
Yeah, the sensitivity gone down. I think
it's when they do do it the feeling that
it it takes a while for it to
this one seems to resolve. Yeah.
M [clears throat]
no, I bought a pair of UGs because I was
buying to buy my mom a pair of
I didn't buy them for me. I bought for my mom.
You know what makes me laugh is when
they come on here and people think that
they think everyone's got the same life as them. No, December. Next month.
Four people skip because they're skin. No. December. You hope. Oh
yeah. Hopefully it's not rain.
Hopefully it's not raining tomorrow.
So you can wear your little Uggs.
Everyone will be well. J.
Is that right, Grey?
that they were trying to say that I was
scared of that guy on the train. Yeah,
that Irish mix guy. Oh, he he was saying
that he wants to do this, he Well, I was
arguing with like three, four people.
Grezy, I was arguing with like three or
four people. If the guy come in my
personal space or he tried piping up to
me, he would he would have knew what
what time it was, bro.
I would have just said to him, "Grevy,
do you want to do it dirty in it?" Yeah.
Did you Did you see the the thing on the
train? She was arguing. She said some I
said, "You are a loser. Look at you
talking about people that you don't even
know." How many times did a [ __ ] man
had to tell her to whine her [ __ ] neck and
it's mad? He had to tell her several
times, bro. He was like, "Leave it. Leave it."
Yeah, bro. Madness. Cuz
the live's still up there. Should be.
Yeah, if it's still up there, bro.
I never said that.
I know. That's Yeah,
they're sad just they're low lives.
They're low lives, bro. What do you
expect from people that that ain't got life? They're sados. Idiots.
Have you seen that? Um,
that's Have you seen that Red Star
account? That Red Star account has been
stalking me for like 3 years, bro.
Four years. Four years been stalking me
every single day. And guess what? He
doesn't get paid a penny for it.
You are [ __ ]
Stop talking about yourself. It's not
nice first thing in the morning. It's
not nice to talk about yourself like that. Yeah.
Come back when you learn some banners.
Yeah. They're low lives, bro. They're low lives.
Yeah. There was this account earlier,
right? I said I said, "Listen, you've
been being a keyboard war for ages. Join
the panel and I'll meet you today. I'll
go wherever you are today and I'll meet
you and you won't have none of it." And
he claims he owns me. But how can you
own someone when you're scared to join a
panel? Imag scared to join a panel.
A [ __ ] panel. And you're telling me
that you owe me? Have a word with
yourself. Just embarrassing. Really embarrassing.
I sh my teeth out. Yeah.
Yeah, they are obsessed to be fair, bro.
And they never stop either. It's weird. Hey,
you got some liver. Are you all right?
You sure? Yeah. >> [gasps]
>> And they can't even think of different
insults. It's the same. It's the same
insults every time. It's the same repeating things.
Like this dusty show. Oh, big nose. I
was like, "Bro, you're still talking
about my bloody donkey. Boring, bro.
Think of some new comebacks. It's
boring, you know.
Think of some original stuff.
They can't even think of their own
bloody comebacks, you know. Bloody
bunch of [ __ ] >> Yeah,
>> bunch of [ __ ] I'd say.
But yeah, it was really bad. I woke up
sick everywhere, bro. It was bad. I woke
up with a bumping headache cuz I mixed
the spirits. I didn't even realize I was
having cocktails and where there's a happy hour.
Yeah, they're just boring. They're just
boring little low lines, aren't they? I
mean, that's what they are. They're
clearly jealous of something.
I had a drink called Old Dirty Bastard.
Yeah, there's a drink called
Old Dirty Bastard. Oh, mate.
Yeah, it was a drink called Old Dirty B.
Old dirty bastard.
Yeah. And that's how you get This is But
this is why I like to stick to beer. I
try to stick to beer if I can.
I do try to stick to beer because
whenever you get spirits, you're [ __ ]
the next day.
This I was having Oh, bro.
Oh my god. Bro,
you don't understand, brother. You don't understand. Seriously. Yeah.
I don't know why they come here every
day calling people skint. They must be
talking about themselves. Jasper
must be talking about their own lives. Is it? So yeah,
still not a step closer to getting a date, Jasper. So
the only maddest thing is you can't even
trust women. They're all liars as well.
That's another thing. I I I noticed that
as I got older, right?
as I get as I got older that I'm like uh
you can't even trust them. Um
they're just liars. Like I can't now
when I when I speak to one I auto
automatically think oh a liar cuz uh
that's how I've um I've called them out
lying and and [ __ ]
Yeah. They're just bitter old men.
That's what they are. Bitter old men
that have got no life.
That's what they are, bro. But I I mean
I can't even trust them.
Like that's how bad it is, you know, cuz
I've caught them out on lies multiple
multiple multiple multiple multiple multiple times.
Um if a woman says that she doesn't date
only she will only date a Muslim, she's
lying. If she says she only dates people
that older than her, she's lying.
Everything she they say is lies.
It's just lies.
with them. So, um,
no, do you know what it was? It used to,
to be honest, it used to, it used to
piss me off, you know, especially like
the next day, right? Um,
um, when obviously I've mixed like the
spirits and that and then I'd get the
numbers and I wouldn't get anything. It
used to for a long for years it did for
years and years and years and years and
years. Um, it did piss me off like
badly. But now it's like I just it is
never going to change, is it? So that's
that's it. I think when I look Max right
and I got them 10 numbers and I didn't
even get a date, I knew then like it's
impossible. It's I mean even though I've
been trying for years and years and
years, I mean that in itself like yeah,
there's no finding anyone in this
country. And if you you know and when
you do go out you're playing it at your own risk.
So you got no one to blame but yourself
really cuz you know that it will never change.
So it's and it and it will never change.
So that's why there's nothing, you know
what I mean?
I' I've definitely learned that all
women are the same despite people saying
that they're not the same. I mean that
nonslegs, I used to meet him and I used
to always say to him before I had
experiences that these women are are the
same. They're the same. they're the
same. And he would barefaced look at me
with them virgin blue skin eyes and tell
me that they're not all the same. You
haven't met all women. Now I have met
thousands and thousands and thousands
and thousands and thousands of women.
Um, more than he would ever. And they
are pretty much all the same to be
honest with you. I mean,
but he says that they're not all the
same. So, but they prove that they are
all the same. say the same stuff, have
the same mannerisms. I mean, they all
watch Tik Tok. They're all on Tik Tok.
They're all on Instagram,
you know? It's it's took over their
lives. So, I mean, they really are all
the same. Just because they might look
different, it doesn't mean they are
different them or they are the same.
That's what I'm saying.
I mean, how how many more years do we
have to keep trying, Jasper? I mean,
we've been trying for 5 years. We've had no success.
I mean, how many more years and how many
more people do you have to keep meeting?
So, I mean, it's not it's all it's it's
not when you go out. This is all that
will happen. When you go out, they
either say they have a boyfriend,
they either say they're not interested,
they either give you attitude, or they
give you their number, and they lead you on.
The end. There's literally nothing else
that happens. There's literally nothing
else that happens.
That's literally, it's always one of
them three things will happen. Nothing
else. And now you can't even get a date,
which is crazy why you can't even get a date nowadays. Yeah,
I mean that's all that ever happens.
You try to give them the benefit of the
doubt time and time and time and time
and time and time and time and time
again. Um, and they all prove they're
the same. So [snorts] that's that's
that's it in it. What do you what should
we say, bro? Hey,
and now it's not helping now cuz a lot
of people don't have money. So, and much
much less people are going to be going
out because their skin.
Liverpool Street was empty yesterday.
Pretty much empty. And it and it should
have been busier. It should have been
like in that bar, right? Realistically,
there should have been about
30 people maybe. There was like not many at all. Hello.
>> I don't make plans.
I don't make plans, matey.
I wish I could just find someone that's
not full of [ __ ]
Yeah, it'll be good. But the women will
still never be interested. So
there's a few things that if there was
if the people weren't listen this
country would be perfect if
the women were better, the weather was
better, the people weren't such
[ __ ] and you didn't have to wait
around for things. If you took away the people
and the weather, the country would be
fine. You know,
it's more the people that uh
Well, duh. But you're I know I'm never
going to meet anyone. I mean, that's
just it's never going to happen because
it will it would have happened by now,
but I don't I don't care anyway. So, I
mean, it will never change and it will
never happen. So, that's that. So, I've
accepted it now.
You know, I know very much if I speak to
somebody one day, they're gone tomorrow.
It's just so predictable. Now, I can
predict it more than Antman can predict
it. Like, I know if say for example, I'm
speaking to someone on on Instagram, I
know the next day it's a it's going to
be a completely different person.
Yep. I've been to Scotland twice. I've
been to Wales three times. [snorts]
I have been to Scotilland. Yes.
tried to pull there, didn't pull. End up
getting an escort.
Yeah, bro. I've been everywhere. I've
been all over England,
Scotland. I've been to Wales. Yeah. [clears throat]
And the thing is, every time you go out,
it's so toxic.
As I've noticed, it's always toxicness.
For the most part, it's very toxic. Um,
I feel like you've got more chance in
real life. I mean, you've got Well,
nowadays it probably it would always be
real life. Yeah. Because I don't get
anywhere on dating apps. I've never
really met anyone from online. So, it'd
have to be real life. Yeah. It's still,
but you'd have to go out every single
day trying to meet someone and it just
wouldn't be worth it. And it's so toxic
as well when you're trying to date. It's
so toxic. Their attitude, their lies,
the bullshitting, then you got [ __ ]
on the train, you know, it's all toxic.
That's why it's better just to walk away
from it. That's But you, you know, real
life, definitely 100%. Um I mean, if I
had an approach, I'd still be a virgin
if you didn't want to count escorts.
But um I mean, I don't know how these
dating apps work for people, but they
don't work for me. So, I don't know how
they're doing it.
cuz I can't even get a date. So, so yeah,
I don't I don't know, bro. Um,
and it's very toxic as well. Um, it is
toxic. It's like when I was on the train
yesterday doing live stream, this woman
thought she could start running up her
mouth. I ran my mouth back up to her.
Yeah. And not running it. I said, "Yeah,
you are the loser." Talking about people
that you don't even know. Like, get a
grip. And I kept answering back and her
man was telling her numerous times,
"Leave it. Leave it." And then this
other guy tries to get involved as well,
trying to say, "Oh, he's had enough for
me. He's going to throw me off the
train." I said, "Oh, yeah. Really,
really?" And if he went anywhere near my
personal space, I would have knocked him
out, bro. I would have knocked the [ __ ]
flying, bro. Seriously? Yeah, I would
have. No, no, no. For real, I would have, bro.
So, just from that, that would that
turned into that. So, it's toxic. It
doesn't even matter, bro, who would have
won, who wouldn't have won. It's toxic.
The whole thing is is toxic, bro. All of
it is toxic. Even if you beat me, it
doesn't matter. I beat him or whatever
it is. The whole thing is toxic.
It's not about who will win or it's the
it's the whole point of what the [ __ ]
you know? He might have beat me, but I I
would have stood my ground. If he come
if he if he went in my personal space,
bro, and he kept running up his mouth, I
would have done something, bro. I would
have, of course, I would have defended
myself. And it's like, and this is all
from trying to date and going out
drinking. It's toxic.
Like, this is what I'm trying to say.
But obviously, if you go out for a meal,
it's not toxic. It's not. Obviously, you
go out, you go out for a meal, but when
it's through women and drinking, it's always toxic.
No, it's toxic because of the women's attitude.
It's toxic because of like Okay, so it's
toxic because of their attitude, their
lies, their [ __ ] And then it and
then when [clears throat] you try to get
into a place, the bouncer discriminates
against you. And I mean, you're I got
banned from a place for approaching
people in a It was a It was a club. Yep.
It was a club. And they banned me uh for
talking to people, approaching people. Yep.
Not even joking, bro. Yeah.
And I didn't even have an argument either.
So, and obviously the women's attitude
and that [ __ ] and any alcohol, it's
just toxic. It's hard to explain it. Um,
and obviously things can escalate as
well. So, that's why sometimes I just
like there's no point.
Yeah. And they didn't complain about me.
They said, "Oh, they complained about
you." I said, "They didn't complain
about me. No one has ever complained
about me unless they've argued with me."
So that never happened. Um, so I'm
thinking, "Hold on. You've got a bar
here. You've got like" And then I I
think I approached like four people and
I said, "Hold on a minute. I'm a single
guy. I'm allowed to speak to me if I
want to." They didn't complain about
anyone because no one argued. Stop
making up [ __ ] Like how many other
places have you gone approaching in and
how many have you got banned from? None.
So stop talking [ __ ] Yeah.
And they're just, you know what I'm
saying? So you're not allowed to speak
to people in a in a in a in a social
environment apparently. So I like whatever.
Think of all of the people that you
approach on the street, how much police
is around. No one ever complains. I've
not really had that that bad ones to be honest.
Yeah. Yeah, it was. I think Yeah.
Her her man was like, "Leave it. Leave it."
He couldn't even defend her, bro. He had
There had to be another guy defending
her. Well, not defending her, but trying
to like run his mouth up.
I'd love to beat an Irish person up, you
know, cuz they say that they've got this
this reputation for being, I quote,
strong, right? I would love to fight one
of them, bro. I would love to fight one of them.
I don't watch Andrew uh Tate. I've heard about him.
I've heard about the dude, but
and there was one I was speaking to from
Australia. Yeah, she was Sri Lankan heritage
and um she was talking, we was talking
for like a good 5 10 minutes. She seemed
all right to be honest. Um guess what,
Greavvesy? She had exactly the same name
as another Australian that I met about a
year and a half ago who played games,
made up lies and play games. She had
exactly the same name and she was from
exactly the same place. I mean, if that
doesn't tell you that it's never going to change
and she looked all right as well, but
she said that she's been seeing someone
for a month. So, I messaged her and that
and she didn't reply. So,
Yep. It just never It just will never
change, will it? Yeah. Normally I go to
like Leicester Square, Tottenham Court
Road, but I thought I go Liverpool
Street this time.
And it is [ __ ] dead. Absolutely dead.
It's going to get to a point where no
one goes out drinking even in central
London. It will get to that point. You know,
people are going to become so skinn
that's the only place now you'll find
people really drinking. and Liverpool
Street as well should have been good, but no.
And trust me, Thursdays are the new
Friday. Trust me, in London, Thursdays
are supposed to be banging.
So, that's the only um
place you're going to see it now. So,
I starting it.
So, yeah. I just think I just think some
people are meant to be single. Jasper,
just like me, I think some people are
just meant to be single.
That and the fact that if you ain't got
loads of Instagram followers and you're
not rich, no one's interested.
Seems that way. I mean, let me tell you
something. I was saying this to Ant-Man,
right? You watch these big Tik Tockers,
right? And they only get about
they get about 40% of women. 30 40% of
women. They get they don't get every
single woman. and they're big Tik
Tockers. They, you know, they've got
many a millions in the bank, right? So,
what chance do I have if they're only
getting 40% of women and they're [ __ ]
loads of followers and they still have
to deal with it? Eh, I have no chance, bro.
That's the way you really got her.
And then it will get to a stage where
they can't even get anyone. So, this is
what's going to happen.
You believe I'll find someone even
though I've approached about 10,000
women in a in a space of 5 years.
You still think that I'll find someone
even though I haven't had a date since April
and I've had many many numbers and I've
approached loads and loads of people and
I can't even get a date. You still
somehow think that I'm gonna find someone?
I don't know, man. It doesn't seem likely.
Let's ask Grezy what he thinks.
I mean, it you can't even get a date. I
mean, most states don't even go
anywhere. Most states are just
establishing whether you you um uh like
someone or not.
Um, and if you can't even get a date, I mean,
it's I don't think so, bro. If you told
me this about 3 years ago, I believe
you. But you could actually get dates
and stuff, but
I don't think you're going to meet
someone. Just the fact that you can't
even get a date,
you know, when you've gone out and
looks, Max, I I don't think so, bro.
I really don't think so.
And I don't want to deal with toxic [ __ ]
just to find someone. That's what I'm
saying. This is the the problem as well,
Greavvesy. I don't want to have to go
out every day dealing with attitude,
dealing with lies and games and
[ __ ] I don't want to deal with that
that. It's not worth it to find someone.
It ain't worth it.
It really, really isn't worth it, bro.
But then again, I'm used to it anyway.
So, I don't think it would even affect
me now. So, but still, like you It's not
worth it, man.
Leave it. Leave it. That's what he was
saying, mate. Leave it. Leave it.
But yeah, I don't know approaching video
cuz my friend wanted to see some sober
approaches. So, yeah.
I don't know what the problem is, man. Yeah. So, yeah,
it will work out in the end.
I'm not so sure.
It's not looking great, is it?
I'm not so sure. It's not looking great, is it? I'm honest.
We're going I thought it
Welcome, Miss S.
I love you, man.
No one's bloody interested.
I'm speaking to this Indian one. Second, bro.
Oh yeah, I've got that other one detect on that.
[ __ ] hell, man.
At the wall. At the wall.
What's his name, mate?
No, that's a good approach ending video. So,
your belly's got some [ __ ] bollocks
on it. Hey,
have you ever have you ever watched
South Park and saw uh Sam's dad's
bollocks? That's is that's my size of my bollocks. Yeah.
Yeah. Ray Marsh.
can't even bloody meet someone.
won't even bloody meet someone
had a bloody enough of it. I have
it will never change, will it? It will
never change. But
it will never change, will it?
It will never change.
change. Will it
ever change? Will it mate?
I need to get a haircut, bro.
Oh, yeah. [ __ ] dream, bro.
That's why I need a little trim. better.
Get my haircut tomorrow.
Yeah, I got my little haircut tomorrow
and um yeah.
Oh [ __ ] bro. P
One second, bro. Hey, man. Did you like
the approaching video?
Hope you liked it, Indigo.
Hey, do you like the approaching videos?
Hope you liked it. Uh, Captain
Oh, I need to get my haircut, man.
That's right. Yeah.
Yeah, I tried tried and uh
tried and failed, bro.
I started it.
What do you expect? Really, eh?
I do remember Ant-Man. Well, it will
never change, will it?
And you'll never change. So,
Yep. They've all got bloody boyfriends. You go.
We've all got bloody boyfriends. Yeah.
I will do, mate. I will do.
It's got to be better than this [ __ ] brother. Yeah,
they're just not interested in this country. Indigo
I got a roast dinner today.
Yep. Roast dinner. Yeah.
Where the [ __ ] is um
um you know, Joseph Ferrar? Yeah.
She loves my videos.
Kind of cringe, bro. To be fair.
That dusty showers. He needs a [ __ ]
life, mate. He's a [ __ ] life. Yeah.
Does he What's his What's his What's his Instagram?
Did you like that little train thing, Grezy?
Lex. Okay, let me have a look. Right.
I got him. Yeah, I got him. One sec.
Yeah, I got heated on the train. Grezy
him saying, "Yo, are you the white knight?"
Yeah, I just messaged him.
Is he from Oh, he's from England. Okay.
I would love to meet him for a [ __ ]
debate like a like a podcast. Yeah, I
just messaged him. You'd love to see
that, wouldn't you, Grezy?
You'd love to see that, wouldn't you,
mate? Yeah, I I'd glad. It's like this
snobby [ __ ] um guy yesterday that
goes to Oxford Uni. He thought he was
more intelligent than me by the way he
was like he come across like he was up
his own ass. I said I'd love to have a
debate with you. I'd love to, you know,
love to, mate. Yep. Yeah,
I messaged him anyways.
What would you do if there was a video
of me beating the white knight up? Huh?
Do you want a pilot or do you want to do
it? Do you want to do it dirty greasy? Huh?
I do want to do it, but you want to do it bad.
I do want to do it bad. Greasy. Come on. So yeah.
Yeah. I'm just saying Gre I can't trust
women anymore. They're full of [ __ ] in it.
They're full of [ __ ] women, aren't they, bro?
They still make excuses though. Yeah. Anyways,
I'll be back later.