[ __ ] hell, mate. How about
I rush? [ __ ] and I'm swinging this [ __ ] cereal. M.
You can't beat some nice cornflakes with sugar.
It's all over it.
[ __ ] fart, mate.
It's good virgin.
That blooming pon.
You like captain.
I had a roast dinner. A nice roast
dinner. But now I'm having some corn
flakes. They're very refreshing.
I woke up with a bad hangover. I was
sick. I had a mad headache.
No more run for me. No more cocktails
for me, matey.
Yeah. One number replied, by the way,
he needs to get laid. He's a new stupid duty.
I think he needs to lose that V card.
I just think he needs to
I think he needs to lose his virginity
to be honest.
I've been saying it for years. He needs
to finally lose his virginity.
Yeah, one number replied back and it
wasn't the Spanish one,
it was another one.
But yeah, one number replied,
we were talking for a little bit. But
Snapchat didn't reply.
See, it's so mad how you can get like
two, three numbers and one replies and
you can get 10 numbers and no reply.
It's weird, isn't it?
It's just random. You know, you can't
you [clears throat] can't predict it, you know. Nope.
No, not at all.
I didn't [ __ ] up at all, bro. What the
[ __ ] I got their number. I [ __ ] text
them. They didn't reply. [ __ ] Do you
want me to do, bro? You know,
I didn't [ __ ] up at all.
They didn't reply. So, um, yeah.
Did you see the argument with me on the
train? You see how these people in here
try to twist things saying I shot myself?
I shot myself. Really, bro?
I shot myself. Are you [ __ ] mad? No, bro.
By the way, you know that candy man is
that dusty showbiz. He's a little
[ __ ] I was arguing with him earlier.
The little [ __ ] The little mongrel.
I knew it was him. I said it from the
start. It was him. He's a little
mongrel. That little candy man. I told
him to join the hangouts today. I'll
come and slap him up, bro. He wouldn't
do it. He wouldn't join the panel.
Despite talking [ __ ] Despite talking
[ __ ] [ __ ] Oh the [ __ ] I said come
join the hangout. I'll mash you up, bro.
I I knew it was him anyways, bro. I said
it from the I said it from day one. It's
him. He's so obvious.
You know that guy was mixed race. You
know that Irish guy? He didn't look like
a typical Irish person. He looked like a
typical road man.
Yeah. And he wasn't the one that was
with her. He was just someone else. The
man that was with her was telling her to stop.
Imagine that. The man that she was with
was actually telling her to stop and not
me. How mad is that?
Wherever the [ __ ] Burkeman's Yeah,
it's one of them, mate. Is it? It's one of them.
But I w scared him at all. I'm not
scared of no one, bro. I really, really
is. I really, really aren't
scared of anyone, bro. Honestly. Yeah.
Yeah. He was Yeah, he was mixed race.
If he was going to do something, he
would have done something. Why is he talking?
I'm saying, bro, just a little wobbler.
Waffler. Sorry, not waffler. Waffler.
Ah. Did you like it, Grezy? Virgin boy
could never do them approaches, could
he? H not Virgin boy.
Virgin boy can never do that.
That [ __ ] Virgin boy, mate. That
[ __ ] Virgin boy.
Could you imagine Virgin boy doing it? [ __ ] hell.
Could you imagine a Skint Virgin doing
it? Stephen Howard walking around with
his skint outfit. [ __ ] virgin.
Could you imagine?
Yeah, I met some guy uh yesterday.
Grezy, he's uh he's he's he's he's mixed
race, but his brother's white. Yeah.
Yeah. His brother's brother's white.
Have you heard? You You've heard of
stuff like that before, is it? Just half
brothers. But he was really really like
snobby cuz they go to like well he goes
to Oxford Jun.
You know Oxford Jun, right?
You know Oxford Junior.
Have you heard about that uni? Oxford Uni
had a ro pigs and blankets mass gravy. I
just had some corn flakes now.
They're very refreshing.
Add pigs and blankets. Some lamb.
Thanks for the food, captain.
I gobbled it all up, didn't I? No, I
gobbled it all up, bro. Cuz well, I
don't smoke. I've got clear airways. So
what I do is I was just like scoffing
it, yumming it cuz I've got clear
airways, you know. Oh, it is getting a
bit long now, isn't it? The beard. >> Yeah.
Hope you like the approaching video, Grezy.
So that's how it is in this country.
Did you write a little pause?
Yeah. It will never change, mate. Never change.
It will never change.
It will never change, will it?
And you'll never change.
You like my hair like this, Greasy. It's very fluffy.
Oh, that guy's um replied back. I met a
couple of guys yesterday as well.
What did he write? He wrote,
"Hello, mate. Sorry for the late
response. Been hanging out my ass all
day. Day went well though, man. I'll
definitely be seeing her again.
You out again tonight? Haha. Nah, bro. I'm still
I'm still lagging.
I made a new friend. Gravesy.
Is that cute? Uh, I messaged him, man. I
commented on one of these uh I commented
on one of these [ __ ] uh
he comment I commented on one of these um
uh pictures, but he didn't reply.
See, I don't take offense now when
people say, "Oh, you on cocaine and
that." the the reason they think I'm on
cocaine is because I'm so outgoing,
Greavesy. You know, I'm bad enough
bloody sober. So, when I've had a drink,
you know, you can imagine uh you know,
it's like that's obviously that's why
people think I'm on cocaine
cuz that's how people act when they're
on like cocaine and that. So, I don't
even take offense to it now. You know, I
can see why to be fair.
People are not as bad as me. So,
you know, if I've had a drink, then
okay. Yeah. I mean, if they think that,
that's obviously because of that. But if
I'm sober, then let's try to [ __ ]
violate to be honest.
One second, bro. One sec.
Yeah, I made a new friend, Grezy.
Yeah, I made a new friend.
Do you like that, Greasy? When I go out making friends? Yeah. Oh,
did you know that I'm from Bristol, Greavesy?
Did you know that I'm originally from Bristol?
Did Did Did you know that?
Yeah, I was born in Bristol.
Did you know that?
Oh, is that what you said? Did you tell
him about my experiences and stuff?
>> Yeah, he was. Yeah, they just miss
people's struggles in it.
Have you heard about Oxford Uni? Greavvesy.
See, this guy's replying back. Why can't
it be a woman that's replying back like this?
Yeah, those those cocktails were punchy,
weren't they? They were, mate. They were strong.
Yeah, those cocktails were punchy,
weren't they? I'm just on the bus to
town. Can't be [ __ ] though. Really?
I'd go meet him, but he's in [ __ ]
Reden. I [ __ ] go there, bro.
Yeah, that's mad.
I can't go [ __ ] reading, bro. I need
I can't go running, bro. So yeah.
Yeah. This Jamie Thompson guy is a
weirdo, bro. He stalks me everywhere I
go. I think he's jealous of me or something.
Constantly emailing me, constantly
trying to call me. I think he's jealous
of me or something, bro. He's got this
weird obsession. He doesn't leave me alone.
I think he's jealous or something, bro. Very weird.
This guy commented on my um video uh
earlier, Stephen, I was saying, PJ,
except that you're one of life's losers.
And I'm thinking firstly, you can't even
spell except right. And bro, you're just
hating because I've done a video doing
something that you could never do. You
could never go out and approach women
sober at the train station. So that's
why you got these fat, ugly haters.
I mean, no one on this community can
call anyone a [ __ ] loser.
Please, bro. [ __ ] please. These
people on here trying to call me a
loser. Are you mad? No.
back saying, "Oh, yeah. Can't go wrong
with a Guinness boy." Yeah. Out in Reading.
So, I can't I can't go, bro. That's too far.
That's too far, bro.
Let's go all the way there. I want to
meet this guy, bro, and got the piss,
but I can't. I [ __ ]
can't go wrong with a Guinness. That's
an old school.
Why can't women be like this, bro? Should
I go to Reading and meet this guy? No, bro.
I met this guy um from Red and Bob. We
got on the drink together and he had a
date, right? Bear in mind, this guy's
probably a little bit better looking
than me. He looked the same heritage as me, right? And uh
and I went up to him, the bar, I was
like, "Oh, you you Turkish and that is
in it." And he was was talking and that
he says he's got Dutch heritage. He's
from Reen and he said that he was
waiting for the date in it. So he's got
a date from him. So I'm thinking, "Oh,
[ __ ] another someone's got a date. I
don't have a date." So he was waiting
for his date. Obviously I was around the bar. Um
yeah, let's just self project him, bro.
She's a fat ugly [ __ ] And then some
Irish guy tried like Yeah, it was some
fat ugly [ __ ] I said, "You're the
[ __ ] loser. Shut your [ __ ] mouth."
But people on YouTube try to twist
things. Then he said that he's out
tonight and reading this guy. Anyways,
his date come. His date come,
right? His date came
and she was [ __ ] fat, bro. Fat single
mom. And I'm thinking, what?
She was a fat single mom, bro. He was
happy with that, though. And he he was
happy with that.
I'm thinking, what the [ __ ] has the
world come to? I can't even get a date.
This guy is looking better than me
tonight. He's got a date and she's a
fat, ugly single mom. What the [ __ ]
bro? I was like, nah, nah.
It's like, but he's obviously from
Reading, isn't he? So, maybe it's a bit,
but he's a cool guy, man. He He's out
tonight in Reading. I'm quite tempted to
join him, but I'm not going Reading,
bro. That's long.
That is long. Um,
yeah, that guy on the train. And And you
know, the thing is, Hermes just said,
"Leave it. Leave it. Yeah. She was like,
"Leave it. Leave it." And she listened.
I said, "Shut up, man." That's what I
said. I told her she was some old woman
with glasses. I said, "You are the loser."
Yeah, you loser. That's what I [ __ ]
answered [ __ ] back. Damn right I did, [ __ ] [ __ ]
And then the eyes. I was like, "Oh, I
want to throw you off this train." I was
like, "Oh, do you?" And he weren't even
with her. I was like, "Oh, yeah. Yeah."
Well, he's lucky he didn't go in my
personal space, mate, cuz he would have
been getting knocked the [ __ ] out.
This is the [ __ ] that you deal with
every time you go out drinking, bro.
It's so toxic. This is why I don't like [ __ ]
I met some posh [ __ ] um yesterday, Bob.
Really really posh [ __ ] Yeah, they go
to Oxford Uni. [ __ ] horrible [ __ ]
They were. No, to be fair, they were all
right, but they were very, very up their
own ass. I was in Liverpool Street and
and and the clubbing scene is dead, bro.
It was a Thursday. Don't forget,
Thursdays are good
because, bro, them entitled [ __ ]
That's what they are. They're entitled
[ __ ] It's England. I mean, what do
you expect? They're all entitled
[ __ ] It's a country full of
[ __ ] I mean, what the what do you
expect? They go to Oxford Uni, right?
And the guy was mixed raced, right? And
his brother was white. So the half
brothers and he come from China cuz he
lives in China. And then there was
another white guy who was friends with
the white guy and he lives in Bristol.
And I'm thinking, how the [ __ ] have they
all ended up here?
Yeah. She heard me talking about women.
Cuz I was live talking about women. Yeah.
Yeah, of course you did, bro. Obviously,
I was live talking about it, weren't I? So,
I was like, "Stop it. Stop it." Yeah. So,
I'm going to write back to this guy.
Yeah, this guy's all right. I would I
would go and meet him, but I'm not going
reading him, bro. [ __ ] that. Do you
remember reading e Bob? We have some
memories there, don't we? Do you
remember? Uh what was it? Uh Sandhurst. yeah.
You remember you remember reading, don't you, Bob? Yeah.
Yeah. She She run up her mouth when I
told her about herself back. Imagine
that, bro. It was a packed train as
well. It was a train full of [ __ ] mate. Yeah. >> Yeah.
I don't care because I've been doing it
for years, mate. Why would I give a
[ __ ] Why would I care?
I don't give a monkeys. [ __ ]
Yep. But people on Reddit say that
you're going to meet someone, Bob. They
say you're going to meet someone.
people on bloody Reddit.
So what is that? What you told him,
Greavvesy, to stop dismissing my struggles.
I don't give a [ __ ] if they hear me approach.
I don't give a monkeys. [ __ ]
Isn't that right, Greasy? I don't give a [ __ ]
Not for me. I don't give a [ __ ] bro.
I honestly don't care.
But yeah, one number. I got two numbers.
Well, I got four numbers, but I think
one of them are fake. Three numbers on one Snapchat.
Liverpool Street was dead, bro. I
thought it was going to be better.
No, I'm not going now, bro.
I'm hung over as [ __ ] He says,
he said, "Yeah, bit of a mission for
right now, bro. Let's sort something
soon, though." I like, "Thank you, Captain."
Yeah. One replied,
uh, an Indonesian.
The Snapchat didn't reply, which is strange. Um,
she's from India.
I got two numbers. the Spanish one. I
got an Australian one, but she don't have WhatsApp,
so I'm not sure if that was her number,
but she said she was seeing someone
anyways. Yeah. So, I got two WhatsApps
and one Snapchat and only one number replied, so
someone at the bar,
I think she was Indonesia. I don't [ __ ] know. Yeah.
Do you think Redden has a different
accent than me, Bob?
Rein has a different accent than me, is it?
Yeah, they doing it.
What do you think, Bob? Do you think
they've It's not actually called
reading. It's called reading.
It's not reading. It's reading, actually.
cuz it's about reading. So that's what
it actually is.
Yeah, it's actually reading.
Yeah. Where's Ricky? Where's Rickster?
He's gone awfully quiet.
Yeah, he's gone awfully quiet. Bloody.
I've got a friend that lives in Brack.
Yeah, it's Burkshire. Yeah,
it's a near phrase. It's kind of near phrase. Yeah.
Is that another message? Oh,
yep. She's replied back.
Oh, is that where she lives?
He was a pretty good [ __ ] No, he's
Dutch heritage. He just sounds like me.
He sounds westernized like me.
She's asked me, "Do I like the tacos?"
What kind of question is that?
Do I like tacos?
Bit weird, isn't it?
But yeah, Liverpool Street's dead. Bob,
Thursdays are the day to go out and it
was just empty really.
I guess people are skint nowadays.
It will hit central London. It will hit
central London in the end. In the end,
it will hit central London. No
tacos. I'm just going to say yeah, I did.
I bought Laney some Uggs, Bob. I was
going to give MCUSA. Is he? I did go to
Shordage, you idiot. It's the same
thing. Liverpool Street. Shortage. It was dead.
I did go there.
It's dead. No one No, no one was out really.
Yeah. Near like the kebab shop and that
going towards Fington. It's dead. It was
dead, bro. Went to a couple of bars.
Dead. Dead. Dead. Dead. Dead. Dead.
It was dead, bro. And I got the last train back.
Shortage is basically Liverpool Street.
It's like 5 10 minutes away. It's the same thing.
It was dead. It was dead. Dead. Dead.
Dead. Dead. I made the wrong mood to be honest.
Yes. And I went there. It was dead.
Yes. It's like a 10 15 minute walk. It was dead.
Yeah, it was dead.
Some [ __ ] balls.
London is is proper active.
No, even if it wasn't pissing down, I I
still think people would have went out.
No, I still don't think people would
have went out to be honest. It's dead.
Liverpool Street is dead. The only place
you're going to get people out is like
[ __ ] central London, Leadeds, um, Newcastle,
like it the only places you're going to
get people out, bro. In London, it's
central. There's no other place where
it's going to be busy.
Trust me. Trust me. There's in
Stratford's dead. Every single time I
try to go out in Stratford, I end up
going Central cuz it's so dead.
I always say I'm going to, but it's so
dead. I mean, Liverpool Street's dead.
And that used to be good. It is. No, it
is dead. Liverpool Street is dead. I got
the last train back. It was dead. And
it's the worst place for stuck up people.
It was the worst place for stuck up people, bro.
Nah, [ __ ] that, bro. I'm done. I'm done.
I'm done with this country, bro.
Nah, I'll go to Rein to meet that guy
and have a drink, but nah, bro. That's
me. You get to You get to reading on the
[ __ ] um on the Elizabeth line. I'm
not going up north again. [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] that [ __ ]
No, bro. [ __ ] that.
But all I'm saying is Liverpool Street
is dead. If you go somewhere like Leads,
it's rammed out. It's never dead. It is
rammed. Rammed out. It's like Newcastle.
I was going to I think he did to be
honest. He said that he ended up back in
Brixton with her.
I reckon he did. Red's not that bad
though. You get on the Lizzy line.
It's getting back though, ain't it?
The thing is getting back, isn't it?
Yeah. What do you know about elephant
castle bump? Elephant and castle bump.
What what's what's the expectant castle Bob? Huh?
By Greavvesy. Who is this account? Bob,
he keeps mocking me. This this Bob
account. Is it you, Greavvesy?
No, there's no history.
Nah, there's no history at all.
Is there a grey?
Nah, there's no history there.
I used to work in elephant castle a lot.
Why? It's all I did was have a one night
stand there and that's it. Yeah.
Where the [ __ ] hell is that?
Did you see them women? They said they
were waiting on their boyfriend.
Why do they lie so much? What's with the bloody lies?
There was this Aussie I was talking to, right?
She looked stuck up as [ __ ] like
Indian. So, I went over and approached
her and she uh she's from um
she was from Australia.
She stopped and spoke, said that she's
Sri Lankan heritage. Uh um
and yeah, we're talking the [ __ ] She
said she's here through uh mid December
and she said that she's seeing some
she's been seeing someone for a month. I
said, "Oh, okay. Oh, let me just take
your number anyways."
Got her number. I didn't reply. What's that?
>> So, her name was Anatia. Anatasia.
The same name as the other Australian in Liverpool Street.
You just can't make this [ __ ] up, can you?
And she was from Sydney as well. Yeah. Okay.
People on Reddit say you'll meet someone like that.
People say you'll meet someone, Bob.
They say you need to be confident. Well,
let me tell you that. Uh not a lot of
people have been able to do what I done.
Think about like this, Bob. Yeah. This
Ed Matthews gets rejected by 60% of
women. So, he gets 40% of women, right?
This is cuz he he's been rejected as
well. He's got attitude. People that
have given attitude, right? So, let's
say he gets 40% of women. Let's say he
gets slightly less than half, right? And
he's got loads of money and he's got
loads and loads and loads of followers.
That's him. Yeah. So, what chance does a
normal person have?
No. Uh, what chance does a normal person have? None.
You know who he looks like a bit that uh
Ed Knuckles? He looks like um you know TGF, bro.
He looks like that Jay from [ __ ] uh TGF.
Hey, I swear they look they look alike,
bro. You know how some people look
alike? I think they look they they look
like each other, don't they? Just got different accents. >> Yeah.
Yeah, they look similar, bro.
Looney Club. What the [ __ ] are you talking about?
Oh, no. He's not pretending to [ __ ]
meet people again, is he?
No. No. No. But their face. But their
face is the same, bro.
TGF and No. No. But they got the same face, bro.
He looks like that Jay from [ __ ] TGF.
I swear, bro. Like the nose and the
beard and that.
It's like Cal Freezy. He looks like
Martin Stew look alikes. Martin Stew and
Cal Freezy look alikes. Identical, bro. Identical.
They are so identical, bro. Like, it's
not even funny. Anyone would think
they're twins. But that No, but they've
got the same face, though.
Same face, same beard. They look Bro,
they got the same face.
I don't know. He gives me TGF vibes.
So if he's getting rejected by 60% of
women, he's only getting 40% of women.
What chance does a normal person have? None. So
I don't know him, bro.
So, what are the options here, Bob? You
got to leave a
toxic as well because say that thing on
the train carried on, bro, I could have
got hurt or that guy could have
seriously got hurt. You know, it's
toxic. It is toxic
cuz what it is is right. You'll go out
right, you drink, you'll have to deal
with women's [ __ ] that puts you in a
bad mood. Then you have to deal with
bounces that discriminate, for example.
Then another [ __ ] that gets involved
and then it escalates. That's how it
escalates, bro. It could end really bad
one day. You know that? Really bad.
Really bad. It's toxic.
That's the right word for it. It is toxic.
It escalates as well, you know.
It does escalate, lad.
Can you imagine the virgin boy going
around Liverpool Street? Liverpool
Street approaching Bob.
that [ __ ] blinking virgin, you know? Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] hell. I'm knackered, bro.
I'm so tired, Bob. I was drinking
[ __ ] cocktails with Ray and nephew in
them. Oh, bro, I was [ __ ] I didn't
think I was going to see the next day.
God, he's such a virgin, isn't he? He's
such a [ __ ] virgin.
He's such a bloody virgin, that one, you know. Nah,
nah. I forced myself to be sick on the
toilet. I woke up with a banging
headache, bro. Banging headache. That's
why I usually stick to Guinness. I
usually stick to Guinness, but it was a
happy hour in the cocktail, so I
thought, "Fuck it."
Oh mate. Oh mate.
[ __ ] hell, bro. I thought I was going
to die, bro. Yeah.
She don't want to know you. She don't
want to know you. She don't want to know you,
Bob. So, why does Ant-Man say that
they're not interested in this country?
Why does he say that? Like, why would he
even give him that idea?
Why would he even say something like that, you know?
Why? What? Why does he say that, Bob?
That they're not interested
in this country.
He's kind of right though, is he?
They were laughing at you, mocking you
when you was traveling around the country.
When you were traveling around the
country, they were laughing at you. They
were mocking you.
They were mocking y
[laughter] that's a bad thing to say in it.
Antman a troll.
Good for him. No one cares about that virgin.
He's not getting attention on my
channel. You need to go get laid. [ __ ] virgin.
They are laughing at you.
They were mocking you. It's the same
[ __ ] just different characters. It's
like he said it's like watching Jaw,
right? But different people being ate
you. He said, "Yeah, it's it's like
watching Jaw the movie, right? And just
different people being eaten.
Same [ __ ] just different characters." Yeah.
Ad man says unless you've got loads of followers
or you got like millions of pounds or
you're a big YouTuber, they're not interested.
Is that true, Bob?
Is that true?
I like beer on Sunday.
And there was only one that replied, remember? So yeah,
I'm still talking to them.
I bear this so long. My bed.
What could be true? Huh?
What could be true, lad?
And yeah, the jaw film. That's what
we're talking about. I just need to get filmed tomorrow. Um, yeah.
What What about the Tik Tok thing?
Yeah, they're not interested unless
you're a big YouTuber
or you got loads of Tik Tok followers.
Because as soon as they look you up,
they're going to want you. That's what
he said. He says, right, if if someone
approaches them, right, as soon as they
type their name and they see their
YouTube and their Tik Tok, they're going
to want them. They're going to want to
be with them.
That's what he said. And if you're not
that, then you've got no chance.
That's why a lot of people go Asia.
Yeah, they will want to be with you
as soon as they see. And obviously if
you're not that then
they're just not interested. So Grezy, look.
I'm so silly, aren't I? Greasy.
I'm so silly, aren't I? Look,
imagine going out like that, Grezy.
Can you imagine,
Grezy? Imagine going out like that. >> [laughter]
>> I'm so silly, don't I?
So, how are you supposed to find someone
here then, Bob?
If you're not like a famous Tik Tocker
or a big YouTuber,
I can't help it that I weren't a big
YouTuber or I'm not a millionaire, but
that doesn't mean I shouldn't be able to find love.
You know, this social media bollocks has
[ __ ] everything up.
Or a drug dealer. Or or if you're you
could be a drug dealer.
Drug dealer, big YouTuber, Tik Tok, a
millionaire. Basically, if you're not
any of them things, you're [ __ ] Not listen. Yeah.
So, what could you do, Bob?
And the only thing is after a couple of
approaches, it gets very tiring as well.
It gets really tiring. So, it's hard to
keep up because you get tired after
about the seventh one
cuz it's a lot of energy. So,
you pretty much
pretty much [ __ ] really.
Why did you delete your comment from my channel, Bob? >> [snorts]
>> No. People on Reddit say there's still hope.
Nah, people on Reddit say there's
there's still hope, lad. Yep.
No, we're not. We're not.
We're not going to be single forever.
How can we be sing? We're going to meet someone eventually.
to say anyways. Bob,
what would happen if I went out
approaching today? Bob Yep.
I'm tired, bro.
That's what they say in it. You'll meet someone. Bob, I'm tired.
I'm [ __ ] knackered, bro. I am absolutely knackered. Oh. Oh,
I'm so tired, bro.
So, what are we going to do then, Bob?
about the situation.
Lady lied to us. Yep. Nope. No. Whatever.
And then when you and then they tell you to try
and then when they when you try, Bob,
they say you're trying too hard.
So which one is it?
So unless you're a Tik Tocker, they're
not interested basically,
Bob. It's mad, isn't it? Unless you got
loads of followers,
they're not bloody interested. Yeah. Madness, it
[sighs and gasps] Yeah.
What would you do, Bob?
What would you do? Huh? Mhm.
No, it's not low iron. I'm [ __ ] hung over.
You're [ __ ] [ __ ]
I'm [ __ ] hung over, mate.
Hopefully I'll get a date next week in it, Bob.
Hopefully I'll get a date next week out
of one of them numbers. Oh,
why hasn't this Indian replied on Snapchat replied with. Yeah.
I'll give her a little bell, Bob. I'll
give her a little bell.
All right. Don't call me a [ __ ] Oh,
do you want to see the family? Do you
want to see the um intuition family I
met yesterday? Bob,
I'll show you the family if you want. Yeah.
So, on the right
is the guy I met and on the left is a
guy I met. They're half brothers.
How mad is that?
How [ __ ] mad is that, eh?
Yep. That's the family. What a lovely
What a lovely family. Eh,
I think Greavves is under that Bob account. Yep.
Yeah. It's a race thing with LT.
What is that? Yeah.
Yep. He switched just cuz that bouncer
wasn't about anything. But if the
bouncer was white, it'd be no problem.
If the bouncer was white, it'd be
absolutely no problem, mate.
Isn't that right, Bob?
No, she was white.
The Irish guy was He looked like a He
looked a hoodlm,
but he was just Irish.
He wouldn't have won against Peter
Belly, mate. Trust me.
Trust me, he wouldn't have.
Peter Bell is big and strong, isn't he?
He said, "I've had enough of you, too."
That's what he said. [laughter]
Mad didn't it, Bob?
Everyone was looking, you know. Everyone
was [ __ ] looking. Yeah,
>> you know, don't you, Bob? I had some
piggies this morning,
but I still prefer the milk from USA.
Then I'd be even stronger.
I I'd be even stronger with the milk,
you know, but obviously I don't get the
milk anymore. So
yeah, loveish I don't get a milk
anymore. What do I, Bob? H.
No, I don't get the milk anymore. Oh,
that's sad, is it, Bob?
P and B can't get attached anymore. Bob,
he's already found his mama.
I was telling her about herself, though.
I was answering her back. I was telling
I was answering her back, bro.
her she's the [ __ ] loser. You're the
one sat on the train mouthing off to
people that you don't know. You are the loser.
I was telling her about herself back.
I [ __ ] told her about herself back,
mate. Don't worry about that. Some fat
ugly woman, bro. Some fat ugly white scenes, bro. Yeah.
I'm in bed. I'm [ __ ] hung over.
I'm [ __ ] hung over. [ __ ]
So, what would have happened that day
when LT broke in, Bob? And if I was there,
would I be alive today?
Bob, if I was in the house that day. Huh?
Yeah. What? What if they killed me?
Greavves. I wouldn't be here today, you
know, if I was in the house that day. I
don't think you understand how serious this is.
I don't think you understand how serious this is. this is, you know.
Nothing lasts forever. Greasy,
isn't that right, Grezy?
That candy man is Dusty Showbiz. He's a
loser. He's like, "Oh, women hate you."
I said, "Yeah, they hate you as well."
And he's like, "Whatever you say." I
said, "Yeah, it is what I [ __ ] say."
This is why I don't like getting getting
into it with these people cuz I want to
hurt them, bro. I want to get my hands
on them. If you can't get your hands on
these little weasels, then there's no
point arguing with them, you know?
I want to get my You want to get your
hands on these [ __ ] little weasels,
you know what I mean? And you can't.
I said they hate you as well, mate.
That's why you're single. You little
[ __ ] Then he started coming on with a
month of [ __ ]
Yeah. I said, "You're a little [ __ ]
mate. You can't even join a panel. Stop
it. You don't own anyone when you can't
join a panel." Yeah.
You can't type [ __ ] if you're not going
to meet anyone and join a panel, bro.
It's It's obvious, isn't it?
You [ __ ] fat bastard.
Still talking about my nose. But get
better. Get better comebacks. You
repeating little low life. Get some
better comebacks. It's boring now, mate.
That all you got is a nose. [ __ ]
hell, man. How many times have you heard
the same [ __ ] nose joke?
Same jokes, same insults. Very boring, bro.
message is the Oxford guy saying I
really like you. I said, "I really like you, Adam.
Found a new dada."
Bob, I found a new daddy.
Is that cute, Bob? Oh gosh.
At least I got some milk from Sig
though. Ain't it Bob?
At least Sid gave me some milk.
I was sucking on her boobies the whole time.
So, at least I got my milk, isn't it, Bob?
Yeah. At least I got some milk, isn't it?
Oh no, here it comes. Greasy,
Oh, wait for it.
It's coming, bro. Yeah,
it's coming, Grezy. [laughter]
Yeah, I messaged him mix race Adam.
He was a post [ __ ]
I said to him, "When did you last get a
blowjob?" He said last week.
You last You got people younger than me
getting [ __ ] laid. [ __ ] hell.
You got people younger than you getting
laid, Bob. [ __ ] hell, man.
See Grezy, it's the same person behind
these accounts. I think this is Grezy.
Signal Peter Belly's mama. Yeah, it's
See, it's this Bob account is greasy,
isn't it? It's got to be cuz it keeps
coming and mocking me wherever I go.
It's there whenever I come on YouTube.
It's you in it, Grezy.
Yeah, I think it's I think it's you in
it. It's got to be
Sig not Peter Belly's mama.
Yeah, he abandoned you.
Yeah, but I still got milk.
Yeah, but I still got milk from her
though. So that's the main thing is it
bo at least I still got milk from her
like at during the time I was uh
abandoned. At least I was still getting
milk in it, Bob.
Yeah, at least I was still getting some milk
in there, Bob. >> [snorts]
>> Oh, this person on WhatsApp's being an ignor.
Yep, she's being ignoring now.
Same old, isn't it? Same old.
Hey, hey, Billy Dundee.
You tell me, bro.
Yeah, it would always be the same [ __ ]
It would always be the same [ __ ] here.
It would always be the same old
There will always be the same old here.
I've got 26 numbers in the past four
times I've gone out. Not a single date. So yeah,
guess they're not interested in this country. Sluggy. Nah,
not pissing me off.
Just the same old [ __ ] Alton. It's to be expected.
It's to be expected. It will never
change. Not pissing me off. Yeah.
Okay, bro. You're kind of ruining the chat.
We don't want your self projection on my channel, bro.
Like, go back to being a low life somewhere else.
Yeah, but it's not about that though, is
it, Autumn? It's not about people giving
up on relationships.
It's about people playing games and
people leading people on and not being
honest. So, I mean, it's not one thing.
You do realize that. Uh,
bro, stop it. It's boring. Really,
really, really, really is boring.
Oh, it's boring.
Go self-reflect somewhere else. We said
the same thing to Candyman [ __ ]
earlier, bro. It's boring.
It's boring. Stop it.
It is so boring. Stop [ __ ] up the
chat with yourself [ __ ] It bores everyone. Bye-bye now.
Yeah. So that's Oh, I assume you watch
my approaches then, Autumn. Yep.
Take you watch the approach today.
I put a new one up yesterday.
No, there's another one I pull up on the channel.
There's another one I pull up uh yesterday. Yeah,
I had someone on my channel say that you
need to accept your life loser, but he
spelled accept wrong and he's from this
community and he's calling me a loser
from this community.
That's funny, bro.
Yeah, have a look, man. It's uh 7
minutes long, but
I think it's a good video.
I got go
to this thing.
So hung over.
My toothies are okay now. Steven Howard.
I thought I needed a filling on on the
other side, but I don't think I do. I
think it resolved itself.
I like the dentist.
What would you do if I told you I wasn't
going to Thailand tomorrow, Greasy?
How How would you feel about that?
What would your opinion on that be?
If I told you I wasn't going
and there was all a load of lies.
What would you say about that, Grezy?
What would you do if I told you I was lying?
Where is he? [sighs]
Well, what do you think? What do you
think? What do you think the option is?
You tell me what what you think the option is.
I've not got the bollocks. Why would I
not have the bollocks, bro? I'm not
scared of anything. What would I have to
be scared of?
I'm not scared of flying. I've already
been on a plane. What would I be scared of, bro?
Well, what what is the only option then?
What's the option, Grezy?
I'm asking you what the option is.
We're going to wait for Autumn to come
back. It's okay. I'll just wait.
I'll just wait until she comes back.
Yeah. Why? Why you Why do you think Asia
is the only option then? Uh,
no. I'm not scared of flying. I've
already been on a plane.
But you still tell me I'm scared of flying.
See, I mean, it's it's the same as you
you saying I'm a virgin and I proved
I've had sex.
I'm scared of flying, but I've already
been on a plane.
How does that work by myself?
I mean, I don't know how that works, but
Yep. [clears throat]
I'm scared of flying, but I've been on a
plane by myself.
That makes sense.
That makes That makes sense, doesn't it?
Yeah, that makes a lot of sense.
Just like people are virgin.
Uh, no. I didn't book a flight back. I
booked No, no, no, no, no. The reason I
didn't book a flight back is because I
didn't know if I was going to like it or
not. I didn't know if I was going to be
scared or not. I didn't book the flight
and then not go on the flight.
So, I mean, I didn't book it and not go
on it. I booked the train in case I
didn't like the flying.
That's what happened. I didn't book a
flight and then go on the flight. So,
no. If I was scared of flying, I
wouldn't have been on the plane in the
first place. I wouldn't have got on the
plane in the first place if I was scared of flying.
So, yeah, you're talking [ __ ] But
you're always going to talk [ __ ] Like,
you call me a virgin, I prove I've had
sex. I mean, it's the same [ __ ] with you
people, bro. No one's asked anymore.
Even when you're proven wrong, you still
make up [ __ ] So, whatever.
You're always constantly making up [ __ ]
and that's what you do on here. So yeah.
Yeah, LT says a lot of things.
Just like you people in this community
say a lot of things.
Yeah, you people say a lot of things on here. You know,
no, I'm just saying things that you
people lie about. It
Oh, [ __ ] me, bro.
What the [ __ ] is that? Thunder or some
Where's Autumn? She's disappeared. Come back.
Come back. A Tim, where have you gone?
It's been It's been seven minutes. Come back.
No, I don't want I don't need anyone to
validate my feelings.
No, I really, really don't, mate. I
mean, I put cold approaches on my channel
and I don't disable the comments and I
don't delete comments. Believe you me, I
don't want anyone to validate my feelings. So,
I really don't unlike Virgin Boy. Have
you seen Virgin Boy Greavesy? He will
delete comments that disagrees with him.
He will delete people that dislike uh
put thumbs down and he'll delete people
that uh get thumbs up on their comments.
He's scared of likes and different
comments and [ __ ] is a proper proper
autistic virgin. I don't know if you've noticed that,
right? I don't know if you've noticed
with that virgin that uh anyone that
disagrees, they get blocked. Like proper
like disagrees, they get blocked. And if
things get thumbs up, he disables them.
And if someone said something about me
and it got thumbs up, he'll ban them.
He's literally scared of dislikes.
He's scared of dislikes. Me, I don't
give a [ __ ] about dislikes.
Nope. I don't I don't give a [ __ ]
I really don't, mate. I'm ask.
Yeah. He's got a thing with likes and
dislikes. Have you noticed that, Steven Howard?
He's got this thing with likes and
dislikes. And if something gets like uh
if something gets thumbs up, he will say
that I made accounts to do it. He's got
this really up bad obsession with uh
my own mom wants me dead, bro. Are you okay?
My own mom wants me dead.
Does your mom want you dead, bro?
Because that sounds like serious
projection right there. Your own mom
wants you dead.
That's definitely projection.
Where the [ __ ] do you people come out
with these silly comments? I shall never ever know.
Must be projection.
Must must must be projection where you
come out with these random silly things.
My mom hates me.
Bro, just just stop it. It's it's
embarrassing now. Just just just just
stop it. [ __ ] back to law J where you
come from you little sad act and stop
embarrassing yourself. See I don't need
to block comments
like you're you're just embarrassing
yourself. Just just stop it. Really stop
it. Stop stop projecting. It's embarrassing.
Take a chill pill.
Where do these people come out with
these things? I shall never [ __ ] know.
They go by their own life.
Just like when they call people skin, their skin,
it's just that they they bounce off
their own lives and think everyone has
the same life as them. Oh,
my mom hates me.
You said my mom hates me.
My mom, I think this guy's done his bollocks in.
I think this slim cognito's done his bollocks in.
It's okay, bro. Just admit it. You've
done your balls in. This is how people
normally act when they've when they've
done their balls in. Telling me my mom
hates me. What the [ __ ]
bro? Are you okay, man? bullied me.
Bro, are you okay?
I know you've done your money in right,
but you know, you don't need to take out
on me that you've lost your money gambling. Stop it.
Please stop it.
Stop being a keyboard warrior for one
day. We know you done your balls in, but
just stop it.
Just stop it.
Bored, alone, bored, and depressed.
Bored. I've got more money than you. I'm
not depressed. I'm [ __ ] hung hung over.
Yesterday I done more than what you done
in a year. You are alone. That's why you
go on LJ's channel because you're Mr. Lonely.
Mr. Loner again. It's your life you're
talking about. I was out yesterday
having a laugh, making new friends. No,
bro. That's your life, not mine. Again,
you're only going off your own life.
Your mom hates you. Bored, depressed,
skinned. It's your life.
And you try to counter out counteract it
by saying that someone else's life, bro.
That's your life. Yeah. What are you
really doing tomorrow? I can tell you
what I'm doing tomorrow. I can actually
tell you what I'm doing tomorrow.
Going to see a boxing match. Going for
some drinks. No, bro. That's your life.
That is literally your life.
Now go back to LJ's channel and go suck his dick
and go suck his dick and stop coming
back on this channel, you [ __ ] weirdo. What? What?
Yeah, I was out yesterday again. Not
everyone's got your life. This is what I
keep trying to explain, bro. We're not
all skin bed bound like you. I don't
know how many times people have to say
to these people on here, we're not all
skint bed bound like you. I know your
disabilities, right? Doesn't let you
acknowledge that, but we're not all
skint bound like you. Like, seriously,
we're not. I I don't know why you think
everyone's got the same life as you. Uh, stop it.
I'm disabled. Really, bro? Why don't you
come and say it to my face, bro? Why
don't you come and say all of this stuff
to my face, bro? You're on the biggest
disabled, bro. You're on L's channel
sucking his dick every day. What life do
you have on that guy's channel sucking
his dick? Somebody that can't even
spell. And you're making fun out of
disabled people. You're on a farey
freak's channel sucking his dick, right?
And he can't even spell. And you're
sucking his dick every day. And you're
coming on here calling me disabled.
You're the one going on LJ's channel
sucking up his dick cuz you ain't got no
life. Cuz we all know anyone that goes
on LJ's channel has got no life. We We
know that. Anyone that goes on that
channel has got no life, bro. All it is
is a bunch of fat ugly people that talk
about themselves. This is why I don't go
on it. This is why Steven Howard doesn't
go on it. And this is why And this is
why And this is why Greavvesy doesn't go
on it. Because there's a bunch of fat,
ugly people like you, Slim, that ain't
got no life. They're the only people
that go on that channel. No one else
goes on it. Literally, nobody else goes
Same pe same people, same repeating, you know.
Yeah, I know, bro. That's what I just said.
But he calls me disabled. Yeah, he's on
an autistic guy's channel all day, every day.
It's torment, bro. Yeah, every day for
me is torture. I've got more money than
you. I'm better looking than you. I've
got more of a life than you. I know,
bro. It's so hectic being me. What am I
going to do, bro?
What the [ __ ] am I going to do? Being
better looking than you, younger than
you, I've got more money than you. What
am I possibly going to do? It is It is
torture being me every single day, mate.
You know? Yeah. It's so bad, bro. It's so bad.
But yeah, he's on L J's all the time
because he ain't got a life. He ain't
got a life. You see him on L J's all the
time sucking his dick. He's a low life.
He's just like Dusty Showers. They're
all little They're all little low lives.
Yeah, bro. Fat ugly people that ain't
got a life.
Yeah, that's the only people that come
on LJ's channel, bro. Have you actually
Have you actually seen the content on that channel?
It's just the same repeating people.
Have you seen it? It's the same little
mongos that put up the same pictures
that repeat the same [ __ ]
Yeah. Lolian skin again. Self projecting
skin. I'm skin. Okay, bro. Yeah. Okay.
Self projecting again.
Self projecting again. Do you remember
the last person that said I was skinn
and I couldn't afford a pair of
trainers? Don't make me embarrass you again.
Don't make me embarrass you again. I
know, bro. They're so disabled. They
come out with the same self-p projecting comebacks.
You know, they come out with the same
self-p projecting comebacks. It's just
like that Dusty Showers.
It's the same repeating. That's why it's
boring. They're just repeating little
bastards. They've got no different
insults. It's just the same self-p
projection, same skinned people calling
other people's skin. It's boring as
[ __ ] So, that's why I don't go on that
channel. It's the same self-proeding
repeating people that talk about their
own lives. It's boring as [ __ ] you know.
And again, you just for example right
now, right, you're calling me ski. You
must be talking about yourself. You
don't know how much money I have. I
bought my mom a pair of Ugg boots. Spent
over £100 yesterday. Got designer
clothes I bought recently. Why would I
be skinned, bro? The only one that skin is you.
Their disabilities, right, get
it gets them confused with other people.
It gets them confused with other people,
their disabilities, think that
everyone's got the same life as them.
Just like this Slim Cognito. Another
little sad act.
Another [ __ ] sad act.
You, Bro, you troll. You can't troll.
Bro, you little spastics can't troll
nothing. You can't even join a panel.
You can't even join a panel, bro. You do
not troll anybody. You can't even join a
panel. You do not troll anybody, bro.
Someone that is scared to join a panel
cannot troll anyone. You know, that's
that's facts. And I'm And you're saying
that I only have you to talk to,
brother. We've all seen you and Lord
Jay's 24/7. What life do you have when
you're on some spastics channel 24/7?
Who have you got to talk to? Again,
self-p projecting time and time and time
and time and time and time again. Trust
me, I've got more friends than you will
ever have. I've got a bit more of a life
than you will ever have. I come on here
because it's [ __ ] it's just fun. It's
just fun and addicting to go live. I
don't have anyone else to talk to
really. I made some new friends yesterday, actually.
I've got friends. No, that's you and
Lord Jay again. Self- projecting.
This is what you like to do. You and L J
like to self-project. That's what you
do. That's all your life consists of.
Think about this. Right. This is also
what L J does as well. He calls people
skin, but he begs people for drinks in Weather Spoons.
That doesn't that doesn't add up, does
it? Hold on. Tone this down, bro. The
guy says that he's got all this money,
right? But he begs for drinks and Weather Spoons.
That doesn't really make a lot of sense,
does it? I mean, if someone has all this
money, they wouldn't swallow their
pride, you know, to to to do something
like that. It's always lies with these
people. I don't know why they don't just
be honest like I'm honest.
Guy sits there and and says that he he
owns six properties. Six properties.
Six properties, bro. Really?
Really? You You own You own six properties? Yeah. Six properties,
brother. Stop it. Stop the lies now.
It's embarrassing. You know, a property
in Belfos would be the equivalent of
probably about £5. You do realize that?
These the the lies, bro. They're
absolute lies. The guy is on benefits.
He made me hide behind my mom. I was in
front of my mom, actually, and he had
several chances to hit me. I was in
front of my mom, not behind my mom.
[ __ ] Again, like I said, you mongos
come here and you like twisting things
because you're [ __ ] disabled. No, I
was in front of my mom. If you watch the
video properly, you Scottish [ __ ] alcoholic
mate. L I spoke about his kids and he
done nothing about it. We're not going
to get into the same balling repeating
[ __ ] again cuz we don't do this on this
channel. We don't go over the same thing
over and over and over and over and over
again. We don't go over the same [ __ ]
over and over again. This isn't a
repeating channel. But for your
information, I was very much in front of
my mom. Yeah. But anyways, bro, listen.
I will give you the same offer as I gave
that dusty showbiz. Come on in the panel
and let's arrange a meet up.
Come on. Come on the panel. I'll put a
link up. Come in the pang that. Yeah.
Come on. Exactly. You're a little
keyboard warrior. Trust me. You You LJ
and you other little spastics troll
yourselves. You're sat on YouTube all
day lonely and skint bro. Life is
trolling you, bro. Yeah. Trolling you.
Seriously, you people are fat, ugly
little low lives, bro. Life has been
trolled you. Anything that you think
that you do on the internet, bro. Trust
me, you just don't do it. You're all sat
on YouTube all Mr. Lonely, no money,
depressed. Bro, life has been trolling
you since you have come out of your
mom's vagina. It's It's that bad, bro.
Yeah, it's that bad, bro. Life has been
trolling you. You ain't even got a life.
This is why I don't understand these.
They haven't even got a life, bro. Not
even a life. [ __ ] friends. [ __ ] women.
They ain't even got a life. That's bad,
bro. Go on. You have to admit that's
You have to admit that's bad when you
don't even have a [ __ ] life. Jesus Christ. Ah,
imagine that. Not even alive
or disabled. You are disabled.
Oh, so you're dusty as well. So, bro,
you got you got about a million and one accounts.
What a low life. It shows that you're
some bro, you're another red star in the making.
You're on another account, you disabled
little low life. You're on another
account, you little low life. You just
got, bro, this guy's a bully victim. I'm
telling you straight, he's a bully
victim. Same as that [ __ ] red star.
Did you see, bro? Abuse, bro. Life has
been abusing you little weirdos. Like
I've told you millions of times, your
skin alone and ugly. Whatever you think
that you do on the internet, you just
don't do it. You're fat, ugly loners.
You've got nothing. No matter what you
try to say about other people, you are
sat on YouTube every day with nothing.
Absolutely nothing. And you want to keep
denying it all you want. Bro, like I
said, you can't even join a panel.
You can't even join a panel. You can't
be took seriously. You know,
you can't even join a panel. Who could
you possibly be bullying?
Do you think a Do you reckon I could go
on a community and somebody would make
me so scared to join a panel? Bro, that
could never be me. That is you.
You sad little bastard.
Sad little trolling bastard in his 40s.
He's another red star. He's a red star
in the making. Fat, ugly, no money, no
life. You know it, bro. You know it.
He's another red star. Another bully victim.
Tries to leave his house. Gets beat up
for being so ugly. comes back on the
internet, self- projects. He's another
red star. He's another bully victim. I'm
telling you, bro, they're all the same
on here. Fat, ugly, depressed people.
They're all the same on here. If you go
on Lord JS, you will see exactly the
same thing. Bunch of losers that don't
leave their house.
Fat, ugly, single, no money. Bro,
they're all the same on here. All the
same little retards. And it goes to show
Yeah. that they have to come on here
every single day trying to troll people
because they have nothing. They have
nobody. This is why they come on these
little accounts because their lives are
nothing. They're nobodyies. Bully
victims. That's what they are. They're
absolute bully victims. This is why they
do this in real life, bro. This is what
I'm saying. Nowadays, community bully
me, do they? Do they really? I mean, I
wouldn't call it bullying to be honest.
I mean, they all talk about themselves.
I mean, people talking about themselves
is not bullying. I mean, they know where
I live. If everyone if anyone wants to
step to me, they're more than welcome.
Cuz let me tell you something, mate. I
don't even go on that channel. Why would
I go on that channel? A bunch of people
that talk about themselves. Is that the
new bullying? So because you people call
yourself skin, you call yourself a m.
You you you call yourself all of these
things, that's bullying me because
you're talking about yourselves.
So you talking about yourselves in your
own life is bullying me. Well, you learn
something new every [ __ ] day. Yeah.
Red Star owns me. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. He's scared to meet me.
Can't even show where he is. But yeah,
he owns me. again. You learn something
new every day. Yeah. With these fat,
ugly, chubby fingers. Another Pat
mustard. Like I said, you are all the
same on here. Old, fat, and ugly with no
life. And every time I say this, it hits
a nerve because I'm right what I'm saying.
You know, you're fat, ugly, disabled,
and you ain't got no life. Let me ask
you this question. When you're behind
all of these accounts trying to troll
people, where's your money? Where's your
girlfriend? She doesn't exist. Right,
let's let's get in it right now. Yeah,
come on. Let's let's really talk about
this. When you're sat on YouTube every
day, where's your girlfriend? Where's
your money? This is what I'm wanting to
know about these people, right, that are
trying to criticize other people. You're
sat on YouTube every day self-projecting
because you're fat, ugly losers. And
that's why I can get a reaction out of
you because I know exactly what you
morons are. fat, ugly, depressed, hate
yourselves. That's why you come on here
trying to bring other people down to
your depressed, ugly level. Half of you
people are [ __ ] alcoholics as well.
You can't even spell properly.
I've never had a girlfriend. Yes, I have
had a girlfriend. Again, where's your
girlfriend? Listen, where's your
girlfriend? Where's your money? Again,
self-p projection. Again, self-p
projection. You've never had a
girlfriend. You've never had sex. You've
got no money, bro. You're not going to
win with me. You can type a million
times, you know, however the [ __ ] you
want. But the thing is, bro, you've
never even seen a woman naked, bro.
You're still a virgin. Like, get them
laughing emojis back onto yourself, bro.
You don't even have a girlfriend. You've
got no money. You got no life. You're on
YouTube behind fake accounts because
you're a nobody. You can't even join a
panel cuz you're a nobody. Am I lying,
bro? Am I literally lying? When When I
Okay. When I'm telling you right now
that you're so scared you can't join a
panel. Am I lying? Because you call me a
liar. Okay. Let me put it up right now,
bro. Yeah. So, if I put this link up and
you can't join because you're petrified
cuz I own you. Am I lying? Are Are you
Are you actually going to join, bro? You
and your little virgin crew nothing.
You've been bullied. You've been bullied
all your lives. Yeah.
Listen. Anyways, so you're not going to
join the hangout then, you little bully
victim. You're going to keep letting me
ripping you apart and you're never going
to meet me. But you said you own me. How
can you own me when you can't even meet
me? How can you own me when you can't
even meet me? You absolute [ __ ]
You're so scared you can't even meet me.
You [ __ ] loser. Skint fat ugly loser.
That's all you are. You non-slegs red
star, you're all the same ugly skin
losers. And that's why I get a reaction
out of you because it's the truth. You
are ugly single. Nobody losers.
No life but YouTube. We have seen this
account on L J's multiple times because
you're all on benefits. You've got no
life. You have got nothing.
Big ugly losers. And that's why when I'm
right when I'm saying this stuff, it's
the truth. big ugly skin losers that's
got nothing but YouTube. Everyone has
seen your account all over Lord J's
multiple times because you are a lonely
[ __ ] with no money, no life, can't
leave your house cuz you've got anxiety.
Like I've told you multiple times, bro,
you probably tried to leave your house
and you get bullied every time you try
to step out the front door. You're a
[ __ ] [ __ ] Now listen, when you got
a pair of balls and you actually want to
join the hangouts, come back to me, [ __ ] [ __ ]
bro. Do you know what I mean? This is so
annoying with these people. I would love
to get my hands on these people, bro. I
would freely love to get my hands on one
of these mongos
cuz I would do some serious serious
serious damage. They're all losers.
They're life. They're low lives, bro.
How many times have you seen these
accounts, bro? Yeah. No, I didn't see
your post. I'm not interested.
And I don't know why you're coming on
that account. I don't know why you're
coming on that account when your
account's not even blocked. But anyways,
that's the thing. But I would love to
get my hands on one of these people.
They're fat, ugly, lonely people that
ain't got a life. Have you noticed
something with these people? Yeah.
What triggers them is when you actually
have a life. Have you noticed that,
Stephen? Now, look at what I done
yesterday. Yeah. Went out approaching.
Well, [ __ ] shits and giggles or
whatever. And it seems to have triggered
these people. It seems whenever you've
got a life, something they don't have,
they seem to not like it. I'm not sure
if I'm the only one that's picked up on
that. Whatever the [ __ ] it is you're
doing, don't forget these people are sad, alone,
sat in. Uh,
yeah, you can be at the boxing all you
want. I'm not bothered. You're going to
be at the boxing? Yeah, that's fine,
bro. I'm not bothered. It's in
Tottenham. You're more than welcome to come.
I don't know why you're blocked. You're
coming to the boxing. That's completely fine.
That's completely fine. It's in
Tottenham. I'll still be going.
I mean, what's what's your point?
What's your point, bro? What is your
point? And I'm not even going alone either. So, that's that.
So yeah, that's you're more than welcome
to. I'll be going tomorrow. So
I got bought tickets. That's not a problem.
What's his channel?
I don't even
Yeah, that's fine, bro. Then you'll see
me tomorrow then, won't you? Not a problem.
I think he's been posting about me as well.
Yeah. Watch the channel. [snorts]
The thing is, Smokey, I'm not scared of
people like you.
You're scared of people. I'm not scared
of people like you. Don't forget
I'm I'm I'm not scared of anyone. I
never said you're scared of me. I'm just
saying I'm not scared of you and I'm not
scared of LT.
So, I don't know why you're telling me,
bro. But anyways, watch this channel.
Anyways, bro, I don't want anyone to be
scared of me. I'm not the one here making threats,
you know? I'm not scared of you or LT,
bro. So, I don't know why you're telling
me where you're going. That's That's
good for you, bro. That's really good for you.
That is really good for you, bro. you're
more than welcome to go.
And you know what I tell you why I fell
out with um LT is because of the whole race thing.
The race thing became really really
weird. I mean that's why I don't speak
to him anymore because of the whole race
thing. He's clearly got some ego with
his race. So I was like, "Nah, I'm not
I'm not I'm not dealing with this no
more, bro. It's too weird."
I actually thought he was like, "All
right." And he just had like a bit of a
temper maybe. But then as soon as that
bouncer thing, I was like, "No, this is
weird, bro. It's clearly clearly a race
thing." And then that's why I don't I
don't talk to uh I don't talk to the
dude anymore. I don't know if you do,
but that's on you. You talk to you want. So yeah,
he's not a normal He's a normal guy.
He's not He's a normal guy, mate. About
to kiss these teeth at me. I stood my
ground, right? And he was being a [ __ ]
And I stood my ground. And the only
reason he stood up for that guy is cuz
the guy was black. Not because he was a
bouncer and he couldn't do this and he
couldn't do that. Because me and you
both know bouncers can do stuff. It was
because the guy was black. Yes, it was
because the guy was black. If the guy
was white, if the guy was white, right?
If he was white, then there'd be no
issues. There'd be no problem.
So, I don't really think that's normal.
But if that's normal in your book, then
So, bro, it's not it's not normal. It's
it's really really really not normal.
You defended a guy because he was black,
not because he was a bouncer.
So, no, that isn't normal, bro.
That ain't normal at all. That isn't
normal at all. At all.
And I was like, "Okay, what about them
two white guys then?" Then I told them
about themselves. What was the excuse
for them? What was the excuse for them
then? What about the white knights in
the Weather Spoons? They were white.
They knew not to go there with me. Well,
but he said nothing about that because
they weren't black.
Am I lying? What I'm saying, Grezy?
Let's all have an unbiased Let's have an
unbiased opinion on this.
Let's have a completely unbiased opinion
on this. I think it's pretty much a
[ __ ] waste thing. Uh, it's pretty
much a a race thing. It seems that way.
No, really doesn't seem that way, bro.
No. Really? Come on, man.
Then from then I was like, "No, this is
weird, bro. This is weird." You say
people don't stick up to men, people
stick up to they they stick it on them.
They stand up for themselves. It's an
excuse. Oh, the guy's at work. Okay,
then another guy. There's another
excuse. And another excuse. And you're
just full of excuses. So what the [ __ ]
bro? You know.
So yeah, it's too weird. Way too weird.
So that's that's not normal in my opinion.
It weren't cuz the guy was about to.
It's cuz the guy was black.
So you're saying that it's not a race thing?
I mean, it seems that it is a race thing, though.
It seems that it is a race thing though.
How is it not a race thing?
You know what I'm saying? It is a race
thing, bro. Of course it's a [ __ ]
race thing. You know, he even told me if
I went for that Charles in America.
Yeah. And I beat him. He would get me,
bro. He said that he would get me again
because the guy was black.
Because the guy was black.
Do you understand? It's not anything
else other than race. How the [ __ ] do
you not see that?
Even if I went out right now and beat up
a woman, he wouldn't care. He wouldn't
do anything about it. But as soon as
it's a black person,
all hell breaks loose.
What's your opinion on it, Greavvesy?
Cuz Greavves is not a yes man. He will
he we disagree with most things.
The only thing we really agree on is narcissists. So,
because they are [ __ ] [ __ ] but we
don't really agree on anything else.
No, it's definitely definitely a race
thing, bro. It is. Of course, it's a race thing.
And you're just licking his ass smoking
me because you're scared of him.
Because you know that if he calls you
out, you're [ __ ]
You know, you know deep down Smoky,
you've wrote comments before. I'm not I
don't give a [ __ ] I'm not [ __ ] sting.
The only reason you're sticking up for
him is because you know if he calls you
out, you're [ __ ] That's what it is. So,
because if you was disagreeing with him
and you was talking [ __ ] about him, he
would call you out. No.
So, how you know I mean
I'm not scared of no one, mate. I
defended myself on that train yesterday
and it was a packed out train. Yeah, it
was a packed out [ __ ] train.
This Jamie Thompson really needs to get
a life, bro. What the [ __ ] is he doing?
This Jamie Thompson is really weird.
Well, he does.
I stuck on a bouncer cuz he started on
me and apparently he can't do anything
because he's at work. And then uh it's a race thing.
It's a race thing, bro. Of course it's a race thing. So
that's why I stopped talking to the guy.
That's the end, bro.
Yeah, that's the end. That's the only
problem I have, I think. That's the only
problem I really have, I think. Yeah.
I mean, I didn't even want to go to the
boxing. It just got paid for me to go.
Even though I couldn't be bothered.
I didn't really want to go cuz my other
sister's going. I don't really talk to
my other sister. So,
I talked to my other one and obviously
my mom obviously, but I don't speak to
my other sister cuz yeah, some people
are just better off not talking and I've
got my reasons in it, but I thought,
"Fuck it. I'll go anyways. Simple.
So that's that to be fair. Here we go.
What do you want to see? A fight in a in
a box. Do you want to see a fight in the
boxing uh boxing match?
I'm going to be absolutely [ __ ] in it.
Nah, not even. We're not all like you, Dusty Showers.
Bro, I'm not scared.
I'm not [ __ ] scared. We're not all
like you, Dusty Showers.
What is there even? I didn't even know
there was a [ __ ] arena in [ __ ] um
in the O2 to be in Tottenham. I didn't
know there was a arena in the in Tottenham.
I didn't even know. I thought there was
only O2 in Wembley. That's why I went to
watch WWE when I was a kid.
Yeah. And guess what? Life owns all of
you people. [ __ ] middle-aged [ __ ]
fat ugly people that ain't got no money
and no life. So guess what? Life owns
you. And that's real life, bro. That's
real life and not just a chat. Yeah.
And life owns you. And that's not even a chat. The stadium. Yeah.
Any reply yet? No.
No, no, no, no.
>> [clears throat]
>> Yeah, cuz you're an addict, fella.
You're an addict, fella.
Yeah, you an addict, fella. That's why Really?
How much do you get a month?
Loads of money, eh?
I'm going to make a cup of [ __ ] in a
minute. So, what are you going to are
you going to meet in the boxing? Yeah.
Yeah. Why don't you go meet?
You get more than 10k a month. Really?
More than 10? [laughter]
You get more than 10k a month of your
own money. Really 10k.
I think you're a bit of a fantasist, mate.
I haven't spoke to Monty in ages, have
I, Grezy? Do you think he still
remembers who I am? I don't go any channel, bro.
10k a month. Really, bro? Yeah.
Something tells me you're telling Porcupies, bro.
So, you get £10,000 every month.
I don't think so, bro. That's ridiculous.
10 grand every month,
brother. Come on.
10 grand every month.
10K, bro. I I don't know if I believe
that, man. Not trying to be a hater, but
I used to get 3k a month when I used to
sublet the house.
I have to do nothing.
Get less now, but it's all [ __ ] money
and [ __ ] [snorts]
Not a problem, is it?
I didn't b your main channel.
[ __ ] 10k a month. Yeah.
You know, we don't we don't think it's
millions, but I mean, it's a lot of
money a month. What? Again, 10 grand a
I mean, it's a lot of money to get above visit, mate.
I mean, even [ __ ] qualified people
with trades don't even get that amount.
No one said 10k is millions, bro. But
you're saying that you get 10k every month? Really?
Bro, if I if you got 10K every month, I
don't think you would be on here somehow.
I really don't think you would be on here.
If you got 10K every month
cuz you don't provide content, there's
no videos on your channel. You don't
make money from YouTube. You have no
reason to [ __ ]
You're wanting more than me,
but you say you get 10K a month. Cuz
why would somebody with all that money
be sat on YouTube every day, all day,
every day? It just doesn't make sense, does it? Madness.
Give it a whirl.
Entertainment. I don't think it's
entertainment. I think it's a load of bollocks.
Uh, I might not even go out tomorrow to be honest.
I might find a film in the cinema to watch.
Let me see. H one sec.
One sec. I'm trying to look up something.
Going for Go for a P. What?
One second. I'm trying to look.
Just [ __ ] off somewhere, bro.
What if I go and get that chicken dollar
kebab instead? Greasy in Wales. Would
that be then? Would that be uh
Would that be okay with you, boss, if I
do that uh chicken tickadona video I was
telling you about? Would that then be
okay with you, boss? Mhm.
He usually loves the content, isn't it?
Smokey, do you want to go for a pint or
do you want to do it dirty?
Do you want to go for a pint or you want
to do it dirty?
It's up to you. Do you want to go for a
pint or do you want to do it dirty?
It's up to you, B. Mhm.
I don't want to see my other sister, bro.
I can't go to the hippodrome. You know I'm banned.
You know I'm banned, matey. No,
I can't go in hyper. remember
go to a bookies but can't uh
yeah we need to do it me and you
tomorrow we got to do it bad bro let's
yeah let's do it bad in it would you
prefer grievios to have a pint or do it
bad or do it dirty H.
No, I don't want to go cuz my sister's going, bro.
Don't speak to my other sister.
I'm not even using that as an excuse.
I'm actually being serious.
And I'm not scared. Why would I be
scared, bro? You're not going to see me
anyways. And also, I'll be with
four different people.
So, think about that. I would be with
four different people,
so I wouldn't be scared anyways. But
I was thinking about it to be honest, bro.
I'd rather go and do my own thing to be fair.
Yeah, I'm petrified. Okay, dustic. You
can't even join a panel.
I mean, you can't even join a panel.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Okay, you can't
even join a panel. Bye-bye. Low life.
These people that come on here and
troll, bro, they've really got something
going on in their life in it, bro.
You know, I mean, I'm sure there's
people that come on here just for a
laugh and they just type in it. But I'm
talking about the people that actually
continuously try [ __ ] with people on here. Bro,
I'm not worried about you LC, bro. I'm
not worried about you, RLT.
I know I won't see you. It's That's not the reason.
So, you just twist things every time.
This is what I mean with these people.
They twist things time and time and time
and time again. They twist things, bro.
I'm sick of people and they twisting
things all the time,
bro. I'm going to be with four people.
You're not going to see me, bro.
Why would I be scared when I'm with
other people? You You just twist things
all the time, bro. What do I mean with people here?
I'm not worried about you or LT.
Seriously, I'm not.
Not one little bit. You just twist
things every time, bro. [ __ ] annoying.
My mom can't go cuz she's looking after
the baby. Yeah, the ticket was £45.
I'm pretty sure my sister can go without £45.
I'd rather do my own thing and I don't
want to see my other sister again to be honest.
I don't want to see her again, bro. To be honest,
I speak to one sister and my mom. That's that.
Yes. So, what, bro? I'm not worried
about that. I think may No, maybe if it
was front row seat. Okay. If it's a
front row seat or like third, then I'll
go. But I'm not going to go somewhere to
sit all the way at the back. Okay. Do
you know what? Yeah. If it's like first,
second, third, fourth, fifth, sixth,
7th, 8th, something like that. Okay. And
then I'll go. But if not, I'm not going
to sit all the way at the back. I don't
really want to be there anyways.
If it's like the 15th seat. Yeah.
Bro, it's not about them having me on. I
still wouldn't go either way.
You never watch WWE Live, Smokey. I I
watch WWE Live and
the first ticket was like £400 and it
was quite a bit at the back.
And the second one, it was almost front
row and that was like £65.
Yeah, I used to watch it when I was younger.
Yeah, it's fake. But they get hurt.
They definitely get hurt though.
They definitely get hurt.
So why so why did she book the ticket if
it's all the way at the back?
So what's the point of book? So what's
the point of going if it's all the way
out the back then? You might as well
just watch it on TV now.
You would have thought.
Yeah. I don't give a [ __ ] if they're
going or they're not going.
I'm not scared of them, bro. I'm not
[ __ ] scared of them.
I ain't scared of them at all.
I'm really not scared of them at all.
So, it doesn't really matter.
I was thinking whether to go or not.
Anyways, I'm not really into boxing. You
know that I'm not into boxing.
See, this is what I mean. You twist
things every time.
You twist things every time.
Yeah. I spent £100 yesterday. grievy on drinking.
Drinking and food.
Drinking and [ __ ] food, bro.
It weren't that bad then, was it?
Drinking and food. 100 pound. At least
it was them [ __ ] 600 weekends. I
can't be doing them anymore, mate.
No, I was debating whether to go or not. Anyways,
for [ __ ] sake, I don't why, bro. I'm
not interested. I'm not the one that
bought the [ __ ] £45 ticket anyways.
I don't care about this, bro. No one's
going to care about £45, are they? Come on.
Let me ask her
how far we back actually. Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] hell.
I am [ __ ] bro.
How would you be in an arena, Greasy?
Would you get anxiety
going to like a stadium? I wouldn't.
No. Would you?
People go go and watch [ __ ] football matches.
Yeah. That's like Dusty Showers. He's so
easy to spot. It's so predictable.
We know it's you. We know it's you. We
know it's you. Dusty Showers. You little low life.
It's mad, isn't it? Nah.
What about if he was in the front seat?
You reckon it would be a bit better?
This guy's This guy's a Man United fan,
right? And he drove all the way to
Manchester to watch the match.
He drove all the way to Manchester
and he sat at the arena. [ __ ] that, bro.
Nah, [ __ ] that. [ __ ] that. And then they
lost as well. They lost as well.
He's a West Ham fan. No, he was a West
Ham fan. Sorry.
Your main's not blocked. Yeah.
You'll get anxiety, wouldn't you, Grezy?
You'd get anxiety, wouldn't you?
Try seeing a new year in in London,
mate. I've done that before. I saw the
new year in Oh, mate. You get stuck.
I've actually seen the new year and I
don't know if you remember a couple of years ago.
Bless you. Then if you have anxiety then grievy bless
I remember when I when I done that Uber
Eats job bro that was I can't believe I
done that you know
I can't believe I actually done that all
around central London [ __ ] hell
I'm mad in it Greasy for doing
That was mad. That was long, bro.
I used to come back. My eyes hanging out
my [ __ ] head. Yep.
Let me know. Let me know.
I think you've got so much anxiety,
Grezy, that I don't even think you'd be
able to even go to a bar with your Greavesy Nah.
Bless you then. Bless you then. Greasy.
I fancy a McDonald's. Greasy.
I can go to bars and stuff.
What do you think of my approaches,
Grezy? Do you reckon you could go out
and do that?
Do you actually think you could go out
Yeah, gay boss. Isn't that right,
Greensy? Nothing lasts forever. Oh gosh.
Do you reckon you could do the
approaches that I don't? Nah.
Not that not that you'd want, but
do you reckon you could do it?
I had a roast dinner though. I shouldn't
be ordering food. I had a roast dinner.
No, I don't think I'm going to do
anything tomorrow, to be honest.
I think I'm just going to stay in bed.
Well, I might go cinema. There's uh this
film looks good. I need to see the trailer.
No, I'll probably just stay in bed to be fair.
I don't really want to go to the boxing, man.
The ticket was only £45.
I don't even really want to drink
tomorrow either, to be honest.
Um, so I might go cinema if I do
anything at all.
Did you like the approaches, Greasy?
They were lushing it. I'm a crazy
bastard, aren't I? Yeah.
Why' you ask, Joel to uh Thompson? Why'
you ask, lad? Yeah. [ __ ] man.
I'm so [ __ ]
I'm so tired, Beezy.
I'm so sleepy, aren't I?
Oh gosh. Do you like that one, Grezy? Yep.
Where's Joseph Ferrar?
He's gone missing, isn't he?
Maybe he died.
I'm watching Ed Matthews.
I like the content. I think it's lush.
What's happened to that Joe, man? Maybe
he died, isn't it? Joseph,
[snorts] that's quite uh that's quite concerning.
But you know if I don't you know if I
don't go tomorrow Greavves I'll be in the doghouse.
You don't know what I mean by that do
you? I would literally be in the doghouse.
I will be in the doghouse mate
if I don't go to uh
I'll get in the neck. Get in the neck mate. Yeah.
You know what that means? Oh gosh.
Oh gosh. Easy. What did you order for
the chin chang?
What did you order? Oh gosh. Yeah.
When am I going to use my willie again?
Greavves on a woman.
When am I going to get to use my willie again?
I don't know why God gave me a willie if
I can't use it.
What's the point of me? I can't even
order from Just Eat.
I can't even order, can I? Cuz of the
problem that I had
where they keep ending up somewhere
completely different. So, I can't even order food
from there. It'd have to be a different
company. They keep ending up somewhere completely different.
So, I can't even order food. Well, I can
do it directly from the on the telephone.
I quite fancy a Chinese, you know, bro.
No, I'm not going to I'm not going to
have it. I need to chill.
You're tempting me. I want a I want a
nice cow man and chicken balls. Oh gosh.
Why was I born with a willie if I can't
use it? Grievy,
what's the point being born with
something that you can't even use?
What did you think of the Spanish issue? >> [snorts]
>> Oh gosh, I really want to I want to beef Charmine.
All right, she's replied back saying
haha. Well, let's see.
No, she didn't reply. But this other one replied
saying she might meet.
So, I'm not going to reply back to her.
I'll hit her up in a couple of days.
This is so long, bro.
She didn't say she might. No, she didn't say that.
At least we got a [ __ ] reply, ain't it?
At least we got a reply. Yeah,
I need to do some international videos,
Greezy. Bro, I really need to start like really um
doing some international
like mad like these Tik Tockers. I want
to be like these Tik Tockers, you know.
I want to do some international content.
I need to work and earn some money first, bro.
For a couple of months. I have to work
and save like a month. I mean,
yeah, I might start working, bro, in December.
Save, do Christmas, and then obviously
January, February, you save. So, you
have two months of saving money.
Hardcore, just saving money, bro. And
then just do some mad content like March.
I need to save up some serious money,
bro. If I'm wanting to do that, you
know, everyone starts somewhere, you know.
It'll be good content. It'll be good
I want to do what these Tik Tockers are doing, bro.
I want to be like them.
Is that cute? I want to be like
What was Q Greaves that I want to be like them?
Well, do you think 28 is too old to be
doing it? Nah. Nah,
that's not too old, is it?
But I'd have to seriously give up dating
here. I'd have to give up dating here if
I wanted to move forward. I really have to, bro.
You know, I I really I'd really have to give up
with the women here if I'm willing to do
stuff like that, bro. Because if I
didn't go out the past month and a half,
I'd be loaded.
I would actually be loaded. It's not
even a joke. I'd be loaded, bro.
I'll be loaded, bro. Yeah.
So, what would you do if I start
traveling and doing like Tik Tok
content? Grezy, would you like that?
Would you like that? Grezy.
Grezy is my biggest troll, you know.
It'll be lush content.
Get what? Getting in trouble. Yeah, but
what if I end up like [ __ ] Fatali in
[ __ ] Thailand prison?
He's looking at 5 years. He is.
He's looking at five years.
It can happen. No.
What about me and L J fighting Greavesy?
Would that be lust content?
Would that be last content?
>> Would you like that? Yeah. Heat. Yep.
One sec. I'll be back.