Oh,
[ __ ] mad. Oh,
that skinned virgin boy is [ __ ] nuts.
He's [ __ ] mad.
Sorry, bro. It's just something that I
say, you know.
I could do with another restaurant today, mate. All right, Captain.
All right, Captain C.
All right, Captain C. [laughter] [snorts]
Just made myself a little cuper and I
should Oh gosh. Got the dentist in a in
a couple of days.
But wow. Trust me to get a thumbs up.
What time I flying? Uh, well, I'm not.
It was all a load of lies.
Can I ask you a question? Why do you
people make up stuff as well? When I
said I was going today, you asked me for
the past four days, when are you going?
When are you going? And I literally said Saturday.
Well, why do you make stuff up as well?
Like when when people didn't even say that day.
You're so invested, isn't it? It's mad.
You're so interested in other people's
um lives. Is what it is, I guess, isn't it?
Like I'll say for example I'm going
somewhere next Thursday and you would
ask every day until Thursday am I going
today am I going today am I going today
yeah I know but people's asking me
yesterday am I going or the day before
am I going the day before am I going so yeah
you ask same thing every day supposed to
be going to this boxing today can't be [ __ ]
So, I'm just going to give half the
money back for the ticket. I can't be
bothered, bro. That means get my
haircut. I can't be bothered today, bro.
I'm tired as [ __ ] I need to chill out, bro.
Honestly, I need to chill out, bro.
Honestly, I'm [ __ ] tired as [ __ ] [snorts]
I'm tired, bro.
And I need to get my haircut and I can't
be bothered. Can't be annoyed with all
that. So, mad.
Yeah, but they Yeah, but they lie on
here as well. But these people here do
nothing but lie. Like Lying that he's
got six properties. He doesn't have six
properties. The guy skin,
you know. It's so obvious that he
skinted. I mean, bro, it's just It was
funny, isn't it?
It is. But I am actually going to go
though. This time I'm not going to say
when I'm going and you just seen me
there. I mean, all these people do is
lie on here. So, I thought I would have
fitted in with one little lie.
Someone saying that they've got six
properties. Really, bro? Really? Really?
Come on. Just Just admit that you want benefits.
I'm I'm being real. I get like £1,100 a
month, but obviously I make money other
ways and [ __ ] and I've won some money
and stuff. I don't know why people need
to lie about what they get, but
I don't know why they need to lie. Just
just say what you get, bro. That's how
much I get.
Well, it hasn't been for the past 3
months, but I mean, technically, one
payment is what I get, but obviously I
get more as in I do other stuff for money,
you know? Obviously, I've won on the
roulette. I've won some football bets,
so it hasn't been that for a long time.
But if I wasn't to anything, that's how
much I'd get. This is what you need to
do, man. Stop lying.
That's what people need to do. They need
to stop lying, bro.
I showed me doing approaches the other
day and got rejected because I simply
don't care. Don't know why people need
to lie. I don't get it. [snorts]
So yeah, only one of the numbers replied back. Oh well,
[sighs and gasps]
I don't care.
Don't care, bro. It doesn't bother me.
That's what I said to you. It doesn't bother me.
I think it would bother me more if
something if it happened. I'd be way
more surprised if something else
happened to be honest.
But think about these lies, bro. Six
properties. How can someone randomly own
six properties, bro? That doesn't even
make any sense. And also, even if you
did own property, it wouldn't even be
worth anything in Belfast.
That doesn't even make sense. It's like
me, right, going to Liverpool, right?
Saying that I own property. What? What's
the property worth, bro? £1, man.
Have a word for yourself.
But yeah, I'm not going today to the box. Anyways,
no, I can't be asked, bro. I want to
chill today. I do want to chill. So,
cuz then by the unless it was like front
row tickets or something and someone's
paid a lot of money, then I'm going, but
I'm not going. Then obviously I would go obviously, bro.
Like I said, I don't really want to see
my other sister ei.
And by the time it finishes and then
drinking and [ __ ] all that, can't be bothered.
I learned the hard way as well. I need
to really stick to the beer when I go
out again. No, like really need to stick
to the beer, bro.
Nothing else but beer. Nothing else but
beer, bro. I learned the hard way.
Yeah, I was going to go reading
yesterday to meet this uh to meet this
dude, bro. Was going to get on it, but
uh it was bit short notice, so
could actually try and meet him today to
be honest. He's a cool dude, but
I can't be bothered, bro. It's long. It
is actually long, bro.
I need a nice detox, bro. A nice detox.
And then it's probably going to start
[ __ ] raining as well. Then it's
probably going to start raining later as well, so
can't be having all that, man.
This person on Reddit says
if I meet them, they'll meet me. And
then but then they said they wouldn't
have sex until we're married. But then
they said that we could get married very quickly.
And I went on another account and I used
another guy and asked her the same thing
and she said the same thing. So I guess
she's genuine this one. But I mean, you
know, you go there, get married, have sex. You know,
why not? We're speaking about having
babies and stuff. Seriously, bro.
Well, I'm in England.
I'm in shitty England.
I was only lying about going to
Thailand. Jesus Christ.
Bro, listen. Let me tell you something,
right? If I was actually going to go,
you wouldn't know I was going.
You would You wouldn't know I was going.
You wouldn't You wouldn't know. If I was
really going, bro, do you think I would
actually tell you I'm going? The only
thing you would see is videos when I come back.
That's the only thing you would see. You
wouldn't even know that I was going.
That's how bad it is, you know.
You'd only see videos when I'm back.
You'd hear all about it when I come back.
Because think about it, bro. These
people Did you Did you Did you hear what
they were asking? Flight details, the
day and that so they could try to ruin the trip. You know,
my back is hurting me, bro.
One second. Someone's voice me. I'll be right back. Yeah.
Wait, what time does it finish?
What time does this boxing finish?
Freaking ant was saying it's like early
hours in the morning,
but then my sister said that it was 10:00.
What time does this match actually
finish? One second. Yeah.
So, it's not So, it starts at 9:35 p.m.,
which means it's not going to end until
early hours in the morning.
Bro, we're not I'm not doing that.
What the [ __ ] One second.
No, I'm not betting on the football today
to be fair. I could do, but I'm not.
Wait one second.
What time does it
What time does it finish?
So it'll be like 11. So then what? By
the time you get back. I'm not doing
that, bro. No, that's long, bro. I'm
just chilling. I'm going to stay in bed
today. I'm tired.
Is that cute? Greasy. I'm tired. Oh, bless.
I said to my mom, "You can tell my
sister I'm not going in it. I'm not
saying nothing, man. I don't want to get
in the neck." Grezy, I don't want to be
in the doghouse.
Isn't that right, Captain?
Grievy. Isn't that right, Captain?
We're in a bloody doghouse. An app Lincoln virgin.
Oh, I forgot to tell you, Grezy. Uh, I
got a KFC uh last night. I I ordered it from Deliveroo,
bro. It I got a four piece meal. It was
£12 something. That's a bargain.
Definitely be do using Deliveroo in the
future cuz I can't use Just eat in it
because they end up somewhere completely [ __ ] different.
£12 for a four piece meal delivery. That
That wasn't that bad to be fair.
It's normally like £20 or some [ __ ]
whenever I used to go and just eat.
But yeah, I just use Deliveroo. It was easy.
That's what I'm going to use from now
on. Yeah, I got four pieces of chicken.
I was a bit hungry. Grezy,
who's that Bob account that keeps
mocking me? Grievesy, is it you? Be
honest. I won't be I won't be annoyed if
it's you. If you just tell me
is that account you
think that counts you, mate.
But it's mocking me though, isn't it, Greavesy?
cuz it's been around for a long long
time and it seems to know so much.
Peter belly doesn't know where to turn to.
Peter belly doesn't know where to turn.
Yeah, he doesn't know where to turn.
No, I don't think it's it's definitely
not Joker. See, me and LT used to think
it was Joker, but it's not Joker.
This Jamie Thompson needs to get a life,
man. He keeps giving my number out, and
I keep getting these calls. He's a
[ __ ] weirdo, bro. Have you seen him?
That fat [ __ ] Jamie Thompson?
He's a [ __ ] stalker. He ain't got no
wife. He ain't got nothing. He's a
stalker. He's a little low life. Just like Dusty.
Nothing but a low life.
That's all, bro.
Me today, I'm chilling.
Well, hold on a minute. There might be
something in the cinema. One sec.
There might be something in the pictures.
What the hell is Joseph Ferrar?
Is that okay if I don't go to the boxing
today? Greasy boss.
But I can't be asked, bro.
To be honest, I only went out Thursday
cuz I knew I didn't have to get my haircut.
I knew I didn't have to get my hair I
could have got away with going out one
more time. When it's to do with like
getting your haircut, I just can't be bothered. You know,
you just can't be bothered, mate. Really?
I can't be bothered, bro.
I can't be asked.
Yeah. Well, I'm going to give them the
money back, aren't I? Well, I'm going to
have to give them the money back. Is it? That's that.
Yeah. If If you If you give them the
money back, then they have nothing on
you, is it?
Yeah, but if you give the money back,
then that's you're you're squaring it. That's that
you're allowed to change your mind. You
know what I'm saying, G? You're allowed
to change your mind if you give the
money back. I'm going to give half the
money back. They were £45. I'll give £25.
So, I'm sure they can live with [ __ ] 20.
No, she said, "Oh, do you want to go? Do
you want to go?" And I just thought,
"Yeah, [ __ ] it." And now I don't want to go. So that's that.
Yeah. I can't be asked, bro.
See, I would go to the Hippodrome and
try and win some money, Goozy. But the
thing is, what if I hit a jackpot?
They're not going to pay me out. So, I
could only win basically below
I could only win below like 500 and keep
going back and back and back and back
and back, but I can't What if it hits a
jackpot and you win like six grand and
they don't pay you out? So,
yeah, it's not uh it's not feasible, is
it? For another five years. So yeah,
if you hit if you hit a jackpot, right?
So you won like a jackpot then you they
wouldn't pay you. So
can't be doing them things anymore. Has
to be online if I were to go but it has
to be online. >> [snorts]
>> Yeah, this woman said if we marry we can
have babies. Grezy,
she says, "Oh, yeah. If we get married,
we can." She says she won't have sex
before marriage, but she's willing to
marry and stuff.
Is that fair, Grezy?
I mean, I don't believe in marriage and
I don't not believe in marriage.
Now, I made another account to see if
she'd give me a different answer, but
she gave the same answer. So, I guess
they're genuine, though.
I don't trust women. They lie all the
time. So, you have to
>> have to um see for yourself, you know.
>> Why is that greasy? I can get married.
And then we can have some lovely sexy.
At least she doesn't want you to be a
Muslim. I mean, I don't think that's
that bad. If someone says, "Oh, we can't
have sex until marriage." I don't think
that's bad considering a lot of people get married.
I don't think that's the worst thing.
It's when they say they won't get with
you cuz you're not a Muslim.
I mean, that could just be a belief. You
know, I won't have sex until marriage.
And they're Muslim as well, obviously.
So, I don't think that's the worst
thing, bro. To be honest,
I don't think that's bad at all if
somebody won't have sex until marriage.
And they're they are Muslim, you know?
They're Muslim as well. So, I don't see
a problem with that to be honest.
She said that we can kiss and stuff, but
we can't do anything until marriage. And
obviously, they would marry early as
well. So soon as you can get married,
they probably would marry you. So
but when they try to say,
"Oh, oh, you need to be a Muslim." They
they won't get with you cuz you're
Muslim. That's wrong. That's [ __ ]
That person was just coming up with 101 different excuses.
But I think this person's legit.
Yeah, I wouldn't mind getting married.
There's nothing wrong with getting married
before having sex. What's What's wrong
with that? Nothing's wrong with that at all.
Yeah, I don't agree with it, but I don't
disagree with it. It's not like I
believe. I just never really thought
about it to be honest. Yeah.
I never really just I never really
thought about it.
But think about it, you might end up
getting married anyways. So if you got
married, then you could have sex and
stuff in it. So
they said, "Oh, we could have a baby and
that, but not for like another five
years." She said that she would call the
baby baby Alex. Oh,
I said we'd call it baby Kane. Yeah.
Baby Kane. Greasy. Baby Kane.
I'm going to get in the [ __ ] net
today, bro. I don't think you understand.
I'm going to get [ __ ] today for not
going. I don't think you get it, bro. But nah,
I just want money. I've got money. It's
nothing to do with money. I've got
money, bro. Where are we?
Well, this looks like a nice horror film.
Well, I'm just looking up a trailer. One second.
It doesn't look that good to be honest.
This horror film,
it looks a bit [ __ ] greasy.
Yeah, it looks a bit sh
I I know what I am watching. There's a
film that comes out Christmas Eve.
Definitely watching that one. And
obviously Scream is coming out in
February. Scream seven. Reeves. Yeah.
No, it's called the maid.
What? When does it come out? The maid
or the bride or what's it called? It's
called either the maid or the bride.
Here it is. No, there is one. One second. Oh [ __ ]
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
You like the lost content, don't you? One sec.
Yeah, it's called the
it's called the bride or it's called the
maid or something for [ __ ] sake. Oh, I don't know. here. No.
Well, I'll look it up in December anyways.
Let me just type horror movies coming
out in December. Oh,
what do you think of that, Greavvesy? If
I if I get married to this person and
have a baby. Is that cute, Grezy?
Oh, it's cute. I think we see a little something else.
Why? But the What about the Bubba? the baby.
Why would he get the forced?
No, I wouldn't go into care.
>> Well, you don't think I'd be a good doozy, huh?
Why would it go? Why would it go
straight into care? It's wide.
Huh? It's not nice, is it?
Where's that blinking virgin Grezy?
Well, why would I approach if I if I'm
with someone, Grezy? I wouldn't approach
if I'm with someone. This is what she
was saying. She said that I think you
would cheat on me.
She said that you'd go with some someone
else that gives you attention. I said,
"No." Well, then
that's what she said.
She said that you would go with someone
else if they gave you attention. I said, "No, obviously not.
As long as I get my little morning
[ __ ] I'm happy. Grezy. Yeah, Grezy,
do you reckon I would cheat, Grevy? Do
you actually think I would cheat on someone?
I can't find this [ __ ] horror film.
For [ __ ] sake.
Do you think I would cheat, Grezy?
Why would I cheat?
Why would I cheat, man? I was [laughter]
I was laughing at that Ed Matthews.
Yeah. He went up to this woman and said,
"Do you know who I am?" And he was like,
"I'm Jimmy Savile." [laughter]
I don't know why that made me laugh
because obviously they're American and
they they don't know who that is. I
shouldn't laugh at that really.
I shouldn't laugh at that really. I'm Jimmy S.
No, I wouldn't cheat.
Jimmy Savile, do you remember when I
said Jimmy Savile was going to get L J's kids?
I think I said I was going to dig him up
from the grave. Do you remember Griezy?
That was that was the last content,
wasn't it? I said, "I'm going to dig up
Jimmy Sabo to get Lord Jkins kids." [laughter]
That's funny, isn't it? Yeah, [laughter]
that is funny, bro.
Did you find that funny?
My name is Jimmy Savile. >> [laughter]
>> That Matthews is an idiot. Idiot, Grezy.
You would have liked to see me in
Reading yesterday, wouldn't you, Griezy?
You like it when I provide content,
don't you? Sat there with your little
popcorn. Oh, bless you then. Sure.
She said that would you be able to
support the baby and stuff? I said, "Yeah,
of course I would, mate."
Yeah. She said, "I need to know some."
stuff before this baby, isn't it?"
That's cute, isn't it? Greasy. Franklin.
I'm playing some Franklin Greavves. He's
in his little car. Where's his little doggy gone?
Madness in it. Madness. Topless.
God bless you.
Used to like the roulette days, Grezy,
when I used to rage back in 21.
Used to like them last days, Groovy,
back in 21 again.
And ever since then, I've been covering 21.
Do you remember Greavves? Them them days.
21 [ __ ] one again. I'm older and
wiser now, aren't I, Grezy?
Do you think I should go back to
roulette, Grezy? Nah,
you don't, do you, man? Nah.
So, I don't want to go casinos, squeezy,
cuz they're dodgy.
Casinos are dodgy, bro. They do anything
to avoid paying people out.
You know what I mean, Grezy?
They're [ __ ] dodgy as [ __ ] bro.
You've noticed that, is it?
They do anything to avoid paying people out, bro. Yeah.
And have you noticed none of them payout
machines are working when you go in the
casino? A lot of the time the payout
machines are not working. They do it on
purpose, don't they, Grezy?
Cuz they know there's got to be a couple
of people in that casino that's not
supposed to be there. And obviously they
get out paying them. So that's it's all
dodgy really. It's all corrupt really if
you think about it.
The only places that pay you fair and
square is maybe like the arcades or
you know even the bookies. You get what
I mean, don't you, Grezy?
What do you think, Grezy? Do you reckon
casinos are dodgy?
Yeah, it's [ __ ] bro.
I was speaking to that Indonesian woman.
She said that uh
she said that at least she replied to be
honest. At least I got a reply. I don't
think it was that bad. You know, Thursday
made a new friend. I had someone reply.
I mean, it could have been worse.
I don't think it was that bad
except from the person on the train.
mad. You can get two, three numbers and
get a reply and then you can get 10
numbers and get one reply. It's a
madness, isn't it?
Yeah, it's mad. Yeah. Do you really
think I want to be going out in this
weather, bro? Not really.
Not really. M.
Do you remember Fraser Greaves? Fras.
You was there them times, didn't you?
When I doxed them. Was that lush? Leave Yeah. Yeah,
I like the name Alex. Baby Alex. That's
what she wanted to call the baby. I
said, "What would we name him?" She
said, "Baby Alex." Yeah, that's a nice little name.
Alex Peter Belly Jr. The thirdy. Oh,
Alex belly. How cute is that? Greavvesy.
A new addition to the family.
Oh, a new addition to the family.
Grieves me. What do you think about
that? A new addition.
But the baby would look um
You know, uh but the baby would look
Turkish. You know that? Cuz she's
Turkish as well, but she lives in Austria.
I showed her my Willie as well. She
said, "It's nice. It matches my looks." Yeah,
that's cute, isn't it?
Bezy, the baby would be really cute,
but he's not getting circumcised.
That's where I think the problem's going
to happen. I don't want the baby being circumcised.
I want to leave it up to the bubin.
You know, this is what this is what what
might cause problems.
You know, I maybe I want the baby to be
a pork lover like me.
How do you think I'm so strong nowadays?
It's all them piggies that I eat. Huh? No. Um,
I don't mind, but just like he can't be
circumcised though, cuz that's cruel.
Unless there's unless it's a medical
reason. I don't believe in circumcision
unless it's it's a medical reason. Like
Antman, he needs to be circumcised.
Like the skin doesn't go back on his
willie. He's got too much
like for skin and [ __ ] Tells me all the time
and it doesn't go back. So, I mean, if
it's a medical reason, then it's
different. But if the baby's healthy and natural,
I think it's child abuse. Me, bro, I
actually think it's child abuse.
But there is one thing that they say
that is right. It is for hygiene
reasons. Because, you know, when you've
got skin, greasy, like me, you know, so
many times you can wash your dick and
wash your dick and it will still smell
like dick cheese. it will still smell
smell stale. Like you need to really
wash your dick every day
like every day thoroughly. Like if you
don't if you don't then it would it will
stink. It will smell like dick cheese. Yeah.
Yeah. It smell like dick cheese.
It's horrible, bro. Like whereas, you
know, your armpits on your body, you can
go a day and a half, even two days
without washing. You know, you you won't
smell that bad, especially in weather
like this. But if you don't wash your
willie, if you don't wash your Willy Wonka,
oh gosh, it will start smelling really bad. Yeah.
Yeah, we can we can name the baby Alex Peterbelly
with my surname just deferred. God
bless. It's a lovely little name
and a little stony baby growsy. Yeah.
My gosh. [clears throat] Easy. Oh gosh.
Oh, by the way, that Lex Therapy didn't reply back.
Nope, he didn't reply back, bro.
Yeah, these kind of people will only
have debates with people that they know
they can win against.
Me not being one of them.
What a [ __ ] white knight.
Yeah, I messaged him. I commented on his
um photo as well.
And not a sausage.
Not a bloody sausage.
No, he hasn't.
I'm mainly on Tik Tok live five, six
times a week.
Can't let these [ __ ] women win.
Henry Breezy, let these [ __ ] women win.
[ __ ] dog ass.
The [ __ ] dog house.
Imagine USA is in the little Ugg boots. Grezy
in the little Ugg boots that I bought. Lady
N. That's cute. Is it Greasy?
Nah. [clears throat] Bless.
Isn't that cute, Grezy?
The little gray Uggs. They've got a
little certificate to prove that they're
real. Oh, bless.
Peter Belly USA. Is he holding hands
with a little Uggs and King in the
middle? Ah, bless.
Is that a lovely sight?
Is that a lovely site?
I am I am actually going just not today. Yeah,
I'm actually going just not today. Yeah.
Greavves. I wonder
I wonder if L J gets the stick that I
get for lying.
Uh I'll let you work that one out. the
amount of times he said that he was
going to go somewhere and didn't.
I let you figure that one out, mate. I
let you figure that one out. Come back
with an answer.
Uh, but you don't really think it's
finished though, do you? You're just
taking the piss.
Yeah, it is finished, but you're just
I am leaving.
Yeah, it's full of [ __ ] [ __ ] in
this country, isn't it?
Yeah, but people on Reddit say that I'm
going to find someone here. Uh, that boy.
I mean, yeah, that's what I think as
well. But people on Reddit say that if I
keep trying, I'm going to meet someone and stuff.
That's what they tell me on Reddit, you know.
That's what they That's what they say.
That's what they say on Reddit.
Yeah, I know they are. Have you Have you
been on there then?
And I showed them my like approaches and
stuff, that boy. Um, and they dismiss them.
They dismiss my struggles.
Friends and family, I mean, they they
just miss my struggles as well.
So, I can't I can't get advice from them anymore.
No, I can't get advice from them, bro.
Cuz they just miss my struggles.
Like that's why we don't get into like
any conversations anymore and stuff
about it because they just dismiss my
struggles and then it just annoys me and
then we just go around in circles. So
that's why I don't we don't we don't we
never talk about it. They just miss
people's struggles and it's it got annoying, bro,
you know, in the end. So that's why I
don't have it with them, you know.
They literally just miss people's struggles.
It's [ __ ] annoying, bro. Ain't it grievy?
Yeah. They just push people's struggles.
What do you reckon would happen today?
That boy, if I went out approaching,
if I got my little haircut and I went
out approaching and stuff.
I'm a bit hairy at the minute. need to
get a haircut. But what would you say
that means me get my haircut today to go
to the book? I'm not doing that, bro.
I'm chilling today.
Look at that, bro. [ __ ] hell.
What do you think would happen?
I'm asking you.
But don't forget,
don't forget uh the West is not finished
because they're still nurseries.
That's Clint That's Clint's logic.
That's Clint Eastwood's logic. That
because there's people in relationships
that aren't new. That doesn't prove
anything. That doesn't prove anything
when more people are single than in relationships.
So, they're also disabled on here as well.
I mean, I put them approaching videos up
the other day just to put them up. There
wasn't to be um to get into any kind of
debate. I don't get into debates with
people on there cuz they're all white knights.
It's very unlikely that you're going to
find someone that's actually impartial.
They're either white knights or they're
in sales. So
you never really get a fair.
That's why I deleted all the messages
and [ __ ] cuz no matter what you show
these people in black and white
evidence, they still defend women. So
there's literally no point in me even
having them store up. That's why I
deleted them, bro. Yeah.
That's their favorite line, lad. That's
their favorite line.
That's their favorite line, lad.
Yeah, that is their favorite [ __ ] line.
I got a boyfriend.
That's their favorite line. Delayed. Invisible boyfriends.
Oh gosh, I'm tired, bro.
And I'm going to be in [ __ ] today if I'm not going.
We were supposed to go out drinking. Now
it's going to the [ __ ] boxing
and then then going out. I don't want to
do that, bro. That that is long.
That's why I just prefer doing my own
thing. You know, like that's why like
you know when people always say, "Oh,
why do you go out alone? Why do you go
out alone?" It's because I prefer doing
my own thing. you know, so
could have went out yesterday, but
I don't think I would have been able to
have done it yesterday as well cuz the
hangover and that Oh, hey.
Yeah, this guy. I need to watch the stream.
What the [ __ ] bro? Why am I going to do that?
Why the [ __ ] am I going to do that, Dad?
Yeah, I'm just chilling today, Jensen. I
was supposed to go to a boxing, but I'm
just going to give half the money back
for the ticket, and I I just want to chill today.
Generally, just want to chill.
It's [ __ ] long, is it, bro?
It's [ __ ] long, mate.
I'm chilling, bro. [ __ ] I need to get
my haircut as well. Like I said, I'm calm down.
You can't be [ __ ] No. Yeah.
Been so much [ __ ] today. You don't understand.
Just give £25 back. I think
There you go. See, what
I could do something lowkey today, but what
what I don't know, bro. What I don't know.
Do you reckon Liverpool Street would be busier today?
Maybe, maybe not.
But the thing is is that
Yeah, I'm not going out today.
So, are you [ __ ] doing the football
today? I'm guessing. Yeah. Captain What's up? Where's Kitty? He minister.
I got a feeling there's going to be
loads of goals in this match though. To be fair,
I've got a feeling there's going to be
loads of goals in this um this league.
Maybe put 150 on the both score. No draw. Nah.
But I do have a feeling there is going
to be um
some mad goals to be fair.
of this feeling, bro.
Trophy thing is it
I had some good uh you know
football wins and stuff.
Does it like Gy
This about this uh football boy.
Pick500 on two teams.
Oh my god.
Could you imagine?
[ __ ] that, bro.
That's a madness. Anyways, be back later.