Yo, hopefully this one works this time.
[ __ ] hell. I almost couldn't went live there.
[ __ ] something to do with the [ __ ]
emails and stuff. [ __ ] annoying.
Oh, that bloody controller.
There it is. Oh, mate.
No, no, no.
Nice cup of [ __ ] in the morning. You
can't beat a lovely cup of [ __ ] in the
morning, can you, mate? You can't. Just
under the washing up. Took me about half
hour, but that's all right. That's okay.
But it was my mess, so it's all right. >> Yeah.
Joseph bloody far.
Had enough of that [ __ ] Joseph Barah
had enough of that bloody [ __ ]
One, one, one.
Yeah, man. Took me [ __ ] half hour to
do the bloody washing up.
I almost couldn't went live for a second
because what happens is yeah, you're
[ __ ] um you only have limited stream
minutes and your if you've got accounts
linked to the other one, you can't do
it. So, I would have had to [ __ ] have um
made a whole new channel and went live
on that one.
Bollocks. I know.
Absolute [ __ ] bollocks. Oh gosh.
Oh goodness. Listen, Jamie Thompson, you
really need to get a life.
Seriously. Seriously need to get a life.
It's getting boring now, you fat slob.
It's getting so boring now. You know
what you remind me of? You remind me of
a uh a Reddit moderator, someone that
takes their failures. Well, Reddit
people ban people to feel powerful
obviously because of bullying and stuff
that they received in their life. You
you just a fat [ __ ] up. Eat you. Really,
you're just a fat slob [ __ ] It's what
you are. That's absolutely fine. That's
absolutely okay. But don't [ __ ] take
out of me, mate. Won't I won't have it.
I won't [ __ ] have it. I might [snorts] almost 104
to 10 basically now. Wow.
I can't be bothered to go
to get a spoon's breakfast.
Can't be [ __ ] Can't be [ __ ] mate.
To be fair. [ __ ] bloody gun.
No, no, no, no.
Oh, yeah. You can't get into some place
anymore. Can you cuz uh you can't speak to people
get banned in some places. Strange. Very strange. Strange indeed.
A bit hungry, you know. Um,
you know what? Yeah, I get a roast dinner today.
Maybe I'll get a roast dinner.
I had a roasting the other day though, didn't I? Close it off. Um,
[ __ ] knows what I'm doing.
doing something other than [ __ ] Jamie
Thompson s his fat ass all day stalking
people. Sad bastard. Ain't got no wife.
Ain't got no life. It's all a load of
bollocks. It's all a load of balls. Some
of them have that much time on their
hands, mate. Trust me, these people have
been caught out of their lives many
times. Many, many very many, many very
many very many very many very many very
many very many many times.
Weird, is it? It's weird how you got
these middle-aged men that latch on to
you. I mean, a few of them do go for
Timmy, to be honest. But, I mean, it's weird.
They go for me cuz I'm younger than them
and I'm better looking than them.
That's where the jealousy comes from.
That's why these people do what they do,
bro. They don't forget they're fat, old,
ugly [ __ ] people. Old age [ __ ]
pensioners. Ain't got a [ __ ] life. So you know mate. Yeah.
[ __ ] hungry. I am so hungry.
Why am I hungry?
That way that's long.
I had you some piggies.
Nah, it was all a load of bollocks.
You don't You don't think I would
actually tell you
when I was actually going, do you?
You don't actually think I would
actually tell you when I was going. Come on now.
Nah, come on now. You don't think I'm that stupid?
Yeah. You don't think I'm that stupid, Charlie? So, yeah. [clears throat]
>> Some piggies, but I ain't going all that
way that long.
Yep. Just like L J lies too. Or
Yeah, just like L J lies.
Um, and other people in here like I
thought you would be used to it to be honest.
I mean, you trust L J. I see enough of
you on L J's channel. Yeah, he constantly lies.
So, well, I don't go on his channel
anymore, but when I used to don't go
anywhere near that channel anymore. I
don't go on anyone's channel.
I don't go on anyone's channel because
I'm not part of the disabled community.
If people want to come on my channel and
type, they can do that. I'm not part of this [ __ ]
uh [ __ ] community, you know?
I'm not part of it. I just go live. If
people come in, they come in.
I don't go on anyone's channel. I don't
go on the Virgin's channel anymore. Even
though people tell me, um, I haven't
been on it for over a week. Never go on it again.
And I mean it when I say it. I'll never
go on that channel ever again. No need
to. It's just some little skint bit of
virgin that projects. Pointless.
Pointless even going on it. So, you know,
I'm 28, bro, not 18 [ __ ] months. You
know, it's time to grow up and stop
being a keyboard. You know, if people
actually wanted to meet, then it'd be a
different story. But back and forth on
YouTube every day, nah. Grow up, mate.
Go the [ __ ] up, you know? So,
yeah, I won't go on that channel ever again.
The only one I go on is Monty's
sometimes. That's it.
Boston wasn't a lie.
Why would you feel let down, man?
Why would you feel let down? That
doesn't make any sense. And another
thing, why do you make up stuff as well?
When I said that I was going on Saturday
on Monday, you asked me every single
day, am I going today? Am I going today?
Am I going today? Am I going today? Am I
going today? Am I going today? When I
literally said I was going Saturday and
you continuously people come on and
continuously ask me if I was going when
I literally said the day that I was
going. What the [ __ ] Must be
disabilities or some [ __ ] Mad. [snorts] So
didn't lie. I changed my mind.
I just changed my mind. Like women
change their mind,
you know, when they say they're going to
meet people and don't they just change
their mind just like I change my mind.
Does that excuse not wash then when when
I'm using it? Does it not wash? Does it
not wash when I use it, mate? No. No.
No. I changed my mind.
I changed my mind, mate.
Like women change their mind, you know.
It's all right, ain't it?
They get away changing their mind. So I
can change my mind, can't I? Yeah.
Picking my nose.
Is it? I don't think it is.
I think it's normal behavior.
I think it's pretty normal behavior. Me,
not normal. I'm [ __ ] starving.
Absolutely [ __ ] starving. Um, [snorts]
fancy a spoon's breakfast.
I don't know what I'm doing, bro. them piggies.
Let me guess. Are you another one of
Dusty Showbiz's account?
That cunt's a weirdo.
He's an absolute weirdo. I can catch
people on fake accounts. I caught
Kieran. I caught him. [snorts] Makes you
wonder like what life people have if
they have to be the age that they are
coming by fake accounts trying to troll.
They must live really really sad lives.
just like uh Reddit moderators.
They're like the saddest people you'll
ever you'll ever come across. They
literally live just to ban people.
That's that's their life literally. It
makes them feel powerful.
But I guess at least they get paid to do
it, I guess. I mean,
yeah, at least they get paid for it to
be fair. So, I probably would make them
as sad as these people
[snorts] on here.
Hello, no lives. Hello, no lives.
You know what I'm like, mate. You know
what I'm bloody like [snorts] [clears throat] Thank you. Um,
everywhere so far, so I can't be
bothered even going and getting food.
That's that's the mad thing about it.
Let me look. I see order something.
But then when you order breakfast, it's
obviously going to be cold by the time
it comes here. McDonald's and uh Wrecky
Bagels and uh I got put off that.
No, I got put off that them bagel places. Um
I don't think I could I could ever pay
again after the experience. I had to be honest.
I'd have a bagel, but no, I can't order
a bagel, bro.
Oh, look at that. Full English.
But no, because by the time it comes, it
will be cold. And there's nothing worse
than a cold breakfast. So, that's not an option either. Grilled sausage. What's this?
No, that that bagel thing put me off of life, bro.
like in terms of like ordering it.
There's some good things here.
Sausage, egg, cheese wrap. [snorts]
That place I went in Birmingham was nice. Awesome burgers.
What? They do burgers at this time. Strange.
Let me order this thing maybe from here.
Yeah, there's something here.
But the thing is
it's going to come cold.
[sighs and gasps]
That's the thing. Soon
as it closes at quarter, that doesn't
even make sense.
Doesn't make no sense. Okay.
No sausage patty. No milk cheese.
Don't want no sauce.
I'm going to have to order this, bro. I'm starving.
Is there anything else?
Egg and cheese.
Bacon and cheese.
That could be good. One second. Bacon egg.
[snorts] No, bro.
I changed my mind.
I don't want egg in that. I don't want
egg in it. That's the thing. I don't
want egg in the [ __ ] thing. [sighs]
Right. 12. Okay. I'm going to get this sh
of this. I'm hungry.
UK is getting better. No, it [ __ ]
ain't. It's a [ __ ] hole.
I went out Thursday and there was barely
any people out.
Bacon, egg, and cheese breakfast wrap.
Yeah, I got a bacon, egg, and egg and cheese wrap.
I remove the egg.
[ __ ] the UK is [ __ ] bro. What the
[ __ ] Can't get laid. Can't get women.
[ __ ] weather [ __ ] Full of [ __ ]
You got to wait around for everything.
[ __ ] There's nothing good about this shitty country. You know
[snorts] this a [ __ ] country, bro.
[ __ ] weather, stuck up women.
waiting around for everything.
Stupid [ __ ] rules, government.
There's nothing good about this country,
bro. You must be [ __ ] mad.
You know, it does feel like it's a
country designed to annoy you. It
really, really does. It's a shitty
country, bro. An absolute [ __ ] of a country.
That's why people are leaving.
I went out on Thursday and there was
barely anyone out because people can't
afford to [ __ ] even go out anymore.
Go out and [ __ ] drink. Barely, bro.
This was Liverpool Street. So, yeah,
the country is dead.
Proper proper dead. It's a [ __ ] country.
I hate England, bro. Yeah,
I was watching this Ed Matthews again
yesterday before I fell asleep. And
even when he gets like the same [ __ ] it
pisses me off. It pisses me off just watching it.
Just watching it pisses me off, you know?
Even when it's not me dealing with it,
just watching it is annoying. If that makes sense. So yeah,
so I've got this little breakfast wrap coming
up, bro. That was [ __ ] [snorts]
I don't think it's funny. I think it's
[ __ ] depressing. I'm glad you find it
funny. I don't [ __ ] find it funny.
Yeah, I got a bacon and cheese wrap. I
removed the egg.
Yeah. And I got two Coke. It cost me £12. So,
Antman gave me £10 back. I £10. So that
kind of pays for it in it. [snorts] [clears throat]
Yeah, I don't go on anyone's channel
anymore, Cory. I don't go on no one's channel, bro.
Only Monty's occasionally, but not even much anymore.
I don't really, bro. It's just the same
repeating people, same atmosphere.
So, I don't even bother anymore.
Bunch of keyboard warriors.
Pack of keyboard warriors. Isn't that right, Cory?
Pack of [ __ ] keyboard warriors.
Pack of [ __ ] cable warriors.
I need to get a trim at some point.
We got some [ __ ] skint virgin in out of London
almost [ __ ] 31 still a virgin and
he's still prepared to go back and forth
on YouTube every day. [ __ ] that [ __ ]
bro. If no one's meeting, I'm not interested, you know?
If no one's beating, I'm not bloody interested.
I think that's fair to be honest.
Yeah. No, but seriously, if no one's
being I'm not interested, bro. [ __ ] that.
Keeps me warm. This does. Yeah.
See, I can't get a full um I can't get a
full breakfast because if any of it
comes cold, I just won't eat it. Whereas
a rap is a bit like, okay, I can nuke
it, you know? And I can't order a bagel
cuz the experience I had when I ordered
it last time, it would put anyone off
for life. That would for life, bro. For
life. For life. I think it's probably
put me off bagels for life to be honest. So yeah. Yeah, man.
Oh, you know that dusty showers car is
under about a million accounts.
This is why I don't understand, bro,
with these fat ugly men. They just sit
there behind fake accounts all day.
They're [ __ ] losers, bro.
And they don't get paid for it either.
They don't get paid for it.
Sat on YouTube, bro. A million and one
accounts trolling. What a sad life they
live in it.
What a sad life they live. They lead. Oh man. >> [snorts]
>> Right, I'll be back later. Anyways,
going to go wait for this, eat it, and yeah, chill. >> [snorts]