[snorts] Sorry.
money man makes me laugh, man.
that video that he's done
on that um
channel that does videos of him.
That's funny, bro. That is funny. >> [snorts]
>> I don't know. [snorts]
That's mint though.
No one's typing.
I'm [ __ ] tired, bro.
Oh, that's self projection.
Stop being so skinn all the time. Oh,
that's self projection. We don't have
self projection on this channel.
We don't talk about ourselves on this
channel. You should know the rules by now, matey.
You need to tell yourself that no self
projection on this channel.
You don't talk about yourself on my
channel like that. It's not nice.
Stop self projecting. Oh,
calling yourself a virgin. What have I
told you about that?
Stop calling yourself a virgin. It's not
nice. It's not good for your mental
health. Calling yourself skin and then
calling yourself a virgin.
It's not nice to talk about yourself
like that. Come on. You're better than
that. Please stop talk stop calling
yourself a virgin. Stop calling yourself skin.
Come on now. You're better than that. Uh,
you're better than that, man. We know
you're a virgin. We know you keep
calling yourself it.
You know, it's not nice to call yourself
these things. Putting yourself down.
Life's too short to be putting yourself
down like that, you know. >> [snorts]
>> [ __ ] hell, mate. Oh, [snorts] you and
Nonss are the biggest virgins going,
Timmy. You're the biggest virgins going. [snorts]
These are all time virgins.
The virgins of all time. Yeah,
you two are the biggest virgins going. [snorts] [sighs]
You calling yourself a virgin?
Why are you calling yourself skin?
That's not nice.
Not nice at all.
No, no, no.
Where's Where is everyone? On.
Hey, I've been waiting for you.
Been waiting for you, Captain.
Timmy's calling himself a skint virgin
again. He's putting himself down.
He's putting himself down again. Steven Howard,
you see that uh video that uh Monty did
calling that account a nod that does
videos of him?
Yeah, it's funny, isn't it?
No, he he's just like Virgin Boy. Steven
Albert, he's just like Virgin Boy.
He's just like Virgin Boy. They're
[snorts] both divergents. Yeah. They're both dragons. Bracket
said that KFC was yummy.
You need us to get laid.
Say it from day one.
What was that? Never.
Never, bro. Never.
But it's crazy this evening.
He He's going to die a virgin.
I hate posh people. Do you hate posh people?
Stop asking stupid questions or you'll
get stupid answers.
If you ask stupid questions, you'll get stupid answers.
So, just warning you.
If you ask stupid questions, you'll get stupid answers. Uh,
stop asking shilly questions.
V. Yeah, exactly. Virgin boy said it.
And you know, Virgin boy lies about everything.
So, stop asking stupid questions.
Virgin boy said it.
Virgin boys. Virgin boy lies about everything.
So why would you ask me if I really
jumped out of window when you know that
Virgin Boy lies about everything?
You know he's a bullshitter and he makes up stories.
So why would you ask that? Silly really. Is it?
He's the biggest liar going. Not one bit
of truth comes out of his mouth. Makes
up stories. Every story he says is made up.
Says my dad used to beat me up. Like objection,
lies. [ __ ] never happened. [sighs]
Made up stories.
And you're gone. Bye-bye. So yeah, see you.
Everything he says is a lie. One second.
Like I said, I don't go on the channel.
I don't go on that virgin's channel.
One second, bro.
I'm looking at something here. Going Oh, weird.
How can they call me a virgin when I
prove I've had sex? That's mad. That is,
isn't it, Stephen? How would you even
when you prove you've had sex, they
still call you a virgin? That's insane, bro. ready. What?
Sorry about that. Uh, what channel is that?
What's it to do with
Yeah, I'm doing good.
Yep. But they still call me a virgin.
Madness, isn't it?
That's a madness.
I'm a virgin, apparently.
Oh, I don't care about all of that [ __ ] anymore, bro.
I don't care about it.
Uh, ignore them. I do ignore them. I
don't give a [ __ ] I'm just saying. I
think it's weird when you prove you've
had sex, they're still trying to call
you a virgin. That's crazy.
I mean, I don't give a [ __ ] I know I'm
not a virgin. I'm just saying it's weird
that they're still trying to call you
virgin when you prove you've had sex. I
don't care anyways, but you know, just
throw it out there.
Have you ever been to Brighton?
Yeah, it's all they have, Penny.
YouTube's all they bloody have.
Just like that. Dusty showers behind a
million and one accounts. [ __ ] low life.
Yeah, they're just low lives. That's all. >> [snorts]
>> Yeah, I know. They're just sad little virgins.
I know. I know. I know.
They're sad little low life virgins. I
know. I know.
I know, Penny. I know. I know. It's
okay, Penny. I know. I know. I know.
You ever been to Brighton, Steven Howard? >> [snorts] [clears throat]
>> That's mad.
Would you ever get with a black woman, Steven Howard?
Yeah, that's all right.
I don't know what cream pie means. No. Here you go.
Ne virgin boy. Penny
Ne's virgin boy.
Nothing. I had KFC
and had some cake.
Yeah. KFC and cake.
Now, he's being a bit of a [ __ ]
He's being a bit of a posh stuck up [ __ ]
I found his family on Facebook and that.
Obviously, I'm not going to add them or
message them. I'm not I'm not a [ __ ]
bro. The guy's done nothing to me, bro.
See, I'm not a [ __ ] bro. I don't [ __ ]
with people for no reason.
I just do my research on him,
but I wouldn't go around [ __ ] with
people for no reason, bro. Hell no, man.
Trust me, I'm not like that, bro.
I'm not like that, bro. For no reason.
Even if they come back swearing at me, I
still wouldn't do it, bro. I would never
mess with people's family that I don't
know. I only done it with USA Izzy cuz
she deserved it and she was being a coward narcissist.
Just [ __ ] with people for no reason, bro. No, never.
Yeah, cuz I'm nosy, bro. I'm nosy. I'm
nosy, bro. That's why I'm a nosy [ __ ]
I'm a nosy [ __ ] mate. I wouldn't I
wouldn't [ __ ] with people's family for
no reason, bro. No,
I don't USA is it because she was being
a cowardly narcissistic
little [clears throat] [ __ ] So, Adam Thomas, he actually
Yeah, he's actually from Brighton, but
he goes to Oxford Uni. No. All
right, Mr. B, have you ever been to
Have you ever been to uh Bristol, Mr. Be?
Have you ever been to Bristol, Mr. B?
Have you been there? [snorts]
Yeah, I knew who he was. But he blocked
me on Instagram cuz I messaged him. I
said, "I really like you." Then he blocked me.
Yeah. I said, "I really like you, Adam."
And then he blocked me. And uh
Nope, I didn't hear about that.
Really? That's not good, is it?
I didn't hear about that.
No, he's not in prison.
No, he's not.
What is it?
What's your account?
20 a month. Ah, that's why he tries to
call me skin. Makes sense.
20 will last a month. [ __ ] hell. Yeah.
Oh, I was watching one of Mashtags. um
um shorts earlier. Yeah. And he was in B
and Q Mr. B. And some woman dropped a
tin of paint and it went everywhere.
It went absolutely everywhere. He got
pissed off, bro. He said, "You just
you've just spilled [ __ ] paint on me."
And he he said to one of the staff,
"Yeah, he's like, "This woman has just
[ __ ] spilled [ __ ] paint all over me." Yeah,
I was dead. [laughter]
Virgin boy. Yeah. One second. I'm going
to look up now.
You're [ __ ] virgin. Right.
Okay, let me have a look.
Right, let's have a little uh
Right. Let me have a look. Okay.
Oh, was he actually in prison? Wow.
Why is this guy putting family members
up? He's such a sad bastard, bro.
He's such a sad bastard.
No one even cares about this irrelevant
little [ __ ] anymore, bro.
Bro, it's boring, bro. Like just putting
family members up is boring now, bro. It
really, really, really is so boring now,
bro. Cuz the thing is, he's never ever
going to meet anyone.
That's what I'm saying, bro.
Like, are putting my sister up. It's
just weird, bro. They're just weirdos on this community.
And my sister just blocks her now. Like,
she doesn't even reply. Well, one of my
sister, my other they don't know about
my other sister.
And then, mate, they've blocked you on Instagram, bro.
This V is a weirdo. I swear to God, if I
was an island, bro, I'd slap him up,
bro. I swear to God. You know,
I would literally call him out and slap
him up, bro. It's just cowardly, bro.
It's just annoying, bro. It's just annoying.
He's cowardly dealing with. I swear to God.
I am bothered, bro. I am bothered. Obviously,
I'm bothered. What the [ __ ] do you want
me to do? I'm not his friend.
He's a sad little bastard. Why is he
putting people's families up there? It's
just weird. What a weirdo.
Absolute weirdo, bro. Weirdo. absolute weirdo.
There was an account on Instagram
stalking my sister for like ages and
stalking me. My sister blocked um
blocked it in the end. Mad. Mad.
Yeah. Fat and ugly. They They all They
all look the same, bro.
And look, you see the same people. It's
the same spastics.
This is what I'm saying. It's the same spastics.
Well, that's his first time in prison.
That's his first time in prison, by the
way. That money, Mike. He's never been prison before. Mad. That's mad.
I've been to prison once.
Only one of them. Yeah.
I mean, yeah. Why you asking when you
already know the answer?
>> You always, you know, it's always going
to be the same here. I know that. You
know that. I don't really care about it.
It will never change. So,
what do you think? I got one reply.
It'll always be the same there. You know this
here or there? Here.
So, what do you do? Did you actually rape someone? [snorts]
>> Did he actually rape someone? >> [snorts]
>> I went out Thursday,
got one number, uh, sorry, three numbers and one
Snapchat and only one reply.
Just same old. I went out Thursday. I
was supposed to go boxing yesterday, but
I couldn't be bothered. So, yeah, I just
been chilling, man.
Keep been hibernating. It's been cold today. So,
yeah, I'm all right, man.
Just the same old. I went out on
Thursday. I went uh got a curry, went out drinking.
Yeah, it's the same old, isn't it?
Oh my god.
Well, no. Someone, bro.
Well, apparently Money Mike's been
locked up for rape.
That's what the latest is.
Yeah, I don't speak to Monty anymore.
[snorts] Same old. Well, this person
said they might meet me, so
but it is the same old anyways. That's
why it doesn't bother me, bro. It
doesn't affect me. I know it would
always be the same here. I don't care.
It doesn't bother me, bro. It is what it
is, is it?
It will never change.
I was watching these streamers ghosting.
They were going and approaching women,
people that's got loads of followers,
loads of money, and even they get rejected. [clears throat]
So, I mean, that tells you everything,
don't it really?
Okay, one sec.
Want the link here?
Why people's sisters up? Weird, bro.
That's weird. These people are weirdos.
What to say? There's There's nothing to say. I mean,
they're just stuck up [ __ ] I
[clears throat] mean, what what else is
there to say? It will never change until
we go to Asia. I mean I mean that's I
think we already know that. So, I mean, yeah.
It Oh, [ __ ]
A little coward.
He's a little coward, bro. Why is he
putting up people's sisters? What a weirdo.
Oh, weirdo mate.
The link's there. If anyone wants to
wants to join.
Yeah, I tried to stay off here.
Ghosting. It's the same repeating people every day.
This weather is making me depressed,
bro. It's so cold.
I had KFC today. I had Wendy's today. I
had Wendy's breakfast in KFC.
It makes you so hungry this weather. Oh
my god, bro. It's [ __ ] I do like the
winter more, but I don't know.
You're not coming in, you [ __ ] skin
virgin. [ __ ] off.
Don't even try it. You skint virgin
trying to [ __ ] come behind the
[ __ ] Daz C account.
Andy, who the [ __ ] is Andy?
Oh, it doesn't matter, bro.
The skinn virgin from out of London and
he's not coming in. So, don't even ask.
Don't even say let him in because he
ain't coming in.
So there's no point even wasting your
time writing that. He's not getting my attention.
So what's that? [ __ ] off, virgin. [snorts]
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no. What do you mean own them? I'll own
them in real life. If they want to meet
me, I will meet them. Yeah, unless they
want to meet me, I'm not arguing. I'm
not being a keyboard warrior. Yeah,
simple. I'm not being a keyboard warrior.
Simple as that. If they want to meet me,
they can meet me and say to my face.
That's that. If they're not doing that,
then [ __ ] them. Simple.
I'm not letting that nonsense.
He is not getting my attention. He needs
to go get laid and lose his virginity.
That's what he needs to do. So yeah,
[ __ ] off, Ghosting. Suck my dick, lad.
Stop being a chicker. Um,
I don't know why he's a posh [ __ ]
[ __ ] That's why Steven Howard is a posh [ __ ] bro.
He's a posh [ __ ] [ __ ] with rich parents.
Yeah, I got his friend on Facebook cuz I
met his friend as well.
He lives in Bristol.
That's what happens when your [ __ ]
parents are rich.
You you you end up being a [ __ ] like them. Snobby [ __ ] [gasps] Yeah.
Yeah. The guy's mixed race.
I can't believe he abandoned me.
Yeah, I don't I don't [ __ ] with people's
family for no reason, lad.
Didn't you see the videos of me [ __ ]
shouting at some woman in Weather Spoons ghosting
and me sticking on that bouncer?
Yeah. From [ __ ] a couple of weeks ago. >> [snorts]
>> Why did I do that? Because I was
speaking to her friend and then she
started giving me attitude
and started trying to shout at me and be
toxic. So I told her about herself.
Yeah. This was like a week this was a
few weeks ago.
What was it like 3 weeks ago? Maybe.
You didn't see that?
Well, I was out there.
Yeah, he's definitely out there, bro.
My friend was being a [ __ ] trying to
shout at me
to tell her about myself.
Adam Thomas. Steven Howard. Adam Thomas.
He's a good fellow. Adam Thomas. Oh [ __ ]
Ew. A simp.
Ew. A wild s appears.
Not mentioning any names.
You know what I'm like. I don't mention names.
No. But yeah, the Skid Virgin's not coming in
and I'm never going on that channel ever
again. I haven't been on that channel in
over a week. I'm not argued with
somebody that wants to be a keyboard
warrior all their life and never meet
anyone. That's pathetic, bro.
That is a pathetic waste of time.
Need to get laid. That's what he needs
to do. He needs to get laid. Get off
YouTube and get laid. Still trying to
come in, right? Let me ban you. Bye-bye,
Virgin. You're coming in. You're banned.
You can't even try and join now.
Ew. A s.
Say it with me. Ew. A s. Yeah. Jesus Christ. Oh, a simp.
Yep, he did.
He's from Brighton. He goes to Oxford
Uni, but his friend that came later on
was a [ __ ] bro. Proper proper
entitled snobby [ __ ]
He was a proper proper His friend was
like Indian heritage. He was a proper
snobby [ __ ] bro. Proper proper snobby
He said that he just went on this date
and he doesn't know what to do.
Yeah, he was being a he was being a bit snobby
griev. Are you all right, Captain?
I was watching one of Mashtag's uh shorts. um
Australia and he went to B and Q Grezy
and some woman sp uh dropped like a t of paint um
uh by accident and it went everywhere
and it went on him. I was dead. And he's
like, you could have at least said,
"Sorry, I've just got paint everywhere."
I was dead, bro. Like his reaction, he
went up to the member staff and he was
like, "Oh, uh yeah, this woman's just
[ __ ] spilled paint everywhere.
It's gone on me. I was [ __ ] dead. You just [laughter]
I don't know why, but it made me laugh.
I think it was his reaction. Yeah, that
would piss anyone off though, would it? Greasy [laughter]
Grezy, that would piss everyone off,
wouldn't it? I got some stranger wings, Greasy.
Some stranger wings.
Yeah, I got stranger wings. They were
nice. The stranger wings. I couldn't get
the stranger burger because I don't like
mayonnaise and it wouldn't let me
customize it. So, I just got the
stranger wings. They were quite tasty. Grezy. Yeah. [snorts]
What is it? Is this Is this a horror
film? The Strangers. Is it Is it a
horror film or something?
Oh, it is. I've watched it. Is it's the
one where they come in the house, isn't
it? It's the one where they go to the
people's houses, isn't it? And start like
Yeah, I've seen it. Is it is that the
one where they where the people going to
keep going on the door and that
is that the one [clears throat]
that they keep trying to shortly shortly. Yeah.
Yeah. I got popcorn, chicken wings, and
the chicken strips. Oh,
cuz there's a horror film called The Strangers,
and they um they go they wear masks and
they go uh after people. Yeah.
dead, bro. You're like, "Yeah, some
woman's just dropped paint and it's
[ __ ] gone all over me." [laughter]
That's funny, don't you think, Weezy?
That's a bit funny.
Nah, I thought I thought it was quite funny. me. [laughter]
I don't know why.
It's [ __ ] funny, is it? Yeah.
Yeah, I'm not an insult and I'm not a
white knight. I don't care, Grezy.
I don't care enough to be any of them things.
Already said what I
or what I've had to say.
Can you hear that's that? It will never change.
Have you been watching porn lately,
Grezy? I've been getting a bit addicted
to uh porn lately.
Porn can get addicting calls. Yeah.
Do you think it's wrong watching porn greasy?
Timothy. Yeah, but you don't know his
date of birth though, Mr. B.
You don't know his uh date of birth,
Timmy's date of birth.
You got no idea.
Yeah. You don't know it, do his day at birth. So yeah,
[ __ ] Mike's in the bin. Greavvesy for
raping some [ __ ] apparently.
Yep. He's in the bin.
You don't know what that means, Grievy.
Do you know what that means?
Yeah, he's in the bin.
I know. This is what people's been saying.
That is murder.
I didn't think he would uh done
something like that.
Yeah, he's probably he's probably in the
police house now though. Next Steven Howard
to be fair. You Thanks. >> [laughter]
>> You want my view, Steven Howard?
They're all [ __ ]
They're old [ __ ]
Just got a bottle of cola. [snorts] I love cola. [sighs] Oh god. Oh, m. Oh, lovely.
My hair's getting long and my beard's getting long.
Oh, what can I
I love Coca-Cola,
but it's not good at the old toothpies.
That's the only thing. Oh gosh.
>> [clears throat]
>> Bless Greavvesy then if he was born in March.
Oh, bless you then. Oh, bless.
Bless you. greasy then if your birthday is March.
That's cute, isn't it?
From Oxford [ __ ] blocked me.
I had him from Oxford blocked me. Greavves.
Can't believe I'll never see him again. Yep.
No, he was a snobby [ __ ] though to be fair.
Don't you think it's mad how I meet
these people in it, Goozy?
You must think it's mad how I meet these people, huh?
Yeah, I messaged him saying I think I
said I really like you
and then he blocked me. Greasy.
Joseph Ferrar is never coming back on his channel. Joseph Ferrar.
No, I should have sent a voice note
saying, "I really want you, but I don't
think you want me."
That's what I should have said, didn't it?
But I don't think you want me. [laughter]
Yeah, he did. Yeah.
Well, I don't think you want me.
E, that's not my mama. Yuck. Yuck.
Where the [ __ ] is this?
E, look at that virgin.
That ugly virgin doing on my [ __ ] ring.
I really want you, but I don't think you want me. Ew.
That's not my mama. Yuck. Yuck.
Look, I I'll show you the Instagram
message I sent. Look,
if you can see it boy, virgin. One second.
Yeah, I said I really like you. I sent
him three messages and he blocked me. Gosh.
That's not my mama. Yuck.
Maybe this one my mama.
That's not my mommy. Yuck.
Yuck. That's my mama.
>> Oh, one second. And someone's calling me.