Yeah, you're virgin.
You're a [ __ ] puppy.
That's another thing I had to tell. I
need to stop [ __ ] going to that
bloody house as well. [ __ ] cat. Oh, [ __ ]
in my little neck of course now. That
tandoori chicken was delicious. Oh gosh,
my belly is full now. Put that fan my
way, please. Thank you. All 50. Oh gosh.
Oh, that urgent boy. [clears throat]
I don't know. [ __ ] Reddit moderators
always sticking their [ __ ] nose in
because they fear bloody different opinions. Bloody
bloody. That's the only word I know.
Only word I know. Yeah. >> [snorts] >> Dude, no. No.
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> Oh, Oh. Oh, wow.
Where is everyone?
What is that blinking virgin? [clears throat]
You'd hate to have my life. What?
Younger than you? Better looking than
you? More money than you? Nah, bro. I
think you actually hate your life and
you're self projecting. See you later. Bye-bye now.
And yeah, I call you people YouTube
dependent because you can't take a day
off of YouTube.
Yeah, I mean, you can't take a day off of YouTube.
Yeah, you can't take a day off of
YouTube, so you're [ __ ] YouTube dependent.
I'm actually often on YouTube where you
people sit on it all day. That's the difference. Yep.
You had dendons. I had half tandoori
chicken and rice. Yeah.
So, what phone do you have then, Steven
Howard? How much did you pay for your phone?
I I I can't I need to stop going to my
sister's grievy. You know, there's a
cat. Every single time I go, she's got a
cat and it it absolutely bullies me.
The cat bullies me, bro. It just gives
me evils and [ __ ]
[ __ ] like that. It gives me evils and um
It gives me evils and it it like hits me
because I don't like Shel Co. Little copycat. Yeah.
Little copycat. Little copycat. That's
what I call it. A little copycat.
Doesn't like me cuz I don't like Sher Cole.
You never guess what I named it.
Well, that's how much the phone cost.
Bro, I really want to get that new fold,
but it's too expensive, bro.
I can't pay that, bro.
[ __ ] £1600. [ __ ] hell, man. That's mad.
That's too much, Grezy. Is it? It's too much.
Cuz I I can tell you this, right? I've
got a fold. Fold
what is this? Fold six. No, it's fold.
It's either fold seven. It's the one
year before I forget. And it's so good,
bro. Like, it's never slows down. It's a
[ __ ] good phone.
But you can't pay [ __ ] £1,700 for a phone. Greavvesy.
I can't do that, bro. I wouldn't do it.
Don't know about you. Look, I don't know
about you two plonkers.
[ __ ] Not Not that much, bro, but
the folds are so good. They never slow
down. I think this is 12 GB of RAM.
What do I do, Greasy? What phone am I
going to get? Cuz the fold is too expensive.
It's too expensive, bro.
It is. It really is. [snorts]
You can't you can't pay that much for a
phone, bro. It's you can't pay. Yeah. My
my funny enough, my mom, she's got an
iPhone. It cost £110. Works perfect. It was refurbished. Yeah,
it was refurbished.
Yeah, refurbed. £110 works perfect.
Yep. I'm not joking, but £110. Yeah.
No, it's not about being materialistic,
Grezy. It's I want the phone to be new
for several different reasons.
That's why I wouldn't mind paying £500
for a phone. But you said 8 GB of RAM is no good.
You said it's no good. No. 8 GB of RAM. So,
but the phone's £500.
Yep. I'm staying in this week and
probably next week.
Yeah, but Greasy, you said it's not
good. They're fine.
You said 8 GB of RAM is not good.
What I would do, I wouldn't buy the
phone out, right? Whenever new fold
comes out, I would just buy on I would
just get on contract. That's what I used
to do. But for some reason, he doesn't let me.
He doesn't let me for some reason.
Even though I pay my bill every [ __ ] month
cuz my phone got robbed. So I had to get
another contract out, you see. And then
they blocked it.
That's what happened. I used to pay the
I used to pay the contract every month.
But it's £500 I think you have to pay up
front. I would do it. If they was to
give me a fold contract, I would do it, bro.
Trust me. Trust me. Once you get a fold,
there's no going back.
Once you get a fold phone, there's no
going back, brother. There's no going
back. They're too good. The folds are
too [ __ ] good.
They're too good, bro. They're too good.
Never slow down. They never slow down,
ever. They've got face recognition, too.
I've got a [ __ ] phone obviously, but it's blocked. So,
what? Get a phone and then a tablet.
Yeah, but why why would I do that? That
doesn't make sense.
Oh, bless you then.
Cy stops grievy. topless.
Yeah, I used to go to Ty shops, but
they've got uh really expensive.
Well, bless you. Then
secondhand iPhone. You know what? I've
not had an iPhone since I was 14.
I don't know if I could switch to be honest.
And if I need to work, what's the
battery going to be like?
That's the problem you got in it.
I had an iPhone for [ __ ] years, bro.
I always just stayed with Samson just
the folds and that
Yeah. So the cat don't like me anyways.
The cat don't like me. Probably because
I don't like Cole. Copycat. Don't copycat.
Nope. Not yet, Captain.
But my [ __ ] hands were freezing to death. Nah, bro. Nope. No. So,
a secondhand iPhone.
A second bloody hand iPhone. Are you
having a wank?
I had two [ __ ] this month, Grezy.
Okay with you, boss.
I love [ __ ] Squeezy. They're lush.
They're very, very lush.
Do you think there's people out there
getting it right now? A blesses.
What phone do you have? Bob Bills. Bob bills.
Yeah, that's the problem is the battery.
You should get yourself a Samsung Fold, Grezy.
They're absolutely lush. Have you ever used one?
I'm on one right now. Yep. Use message. Oh, bless
Bob. Oh, bless you. Popless
Grezy, can you tell me if this is a good
phone? It's called a Samsung S. Uh, it's
called the Samsung.
Tell me if this is a good phone, cuz
this is the one I might be getting.
Yeah. Samsung S24 Plus.
That's the one I've I'm waiting for them
to get back in stock. I think this is a
good I think it's a good one now.
You know more about these things than me.
I think it's a I think it's a good phone. Huh?
That's what the phone's called.
Yeah, I'm thinking of getting that one. Captain
I can make the money back in about two
days for the phone,
captain. I can make the money back in
two days. Don't even need even if you
need to spend a little bit. I I'll make
the money back.
Don't worry, Greavves. I've got my ways, you know.
So, whether you buy a£100 iPhone or you
spend 400 [ __ ] pounds, you can just
make the money back. Not a problem, you know. Captain [ __ ]
I could sell some drugs even make the money back.
You think the virgin's ever going to get laid?
Do you reckon he's ever going to pop that [ __ ] Honestly,
cuz it's getting a bit out of hand now,
ain't it, mate?
I want him to get laid.
Me? I want him to get laid.
He had the dentist today, Greasy. But I
was too tired. I stayed in bed. I was No.
Way too tired, bro. Way too tired.
What even a joke, bro? Uh Would
you say you're a copycat greasy?
No, they won't. Bro, I've been going for
years. I've been going since I was a kid
to the same dentist.
Yeah, I was so tired, bro.
Oh, there's a fold here. 1549. £1,549 we cheapest.
Bit too much though, is it?
Bit too much.
That's a bit too much, matey. Bit too [ __ ] much.
No, I don't. [snorts] [laughter]
Funny one. Grezy, leave a line.
Do you remember Grezy? Do you want to do
it? If you want to do it bad, we'll go
around the corner. If you want to do it bad,
do you want to go for a drink or do you
want to do it bad? Greezy, which one
or do you want to do it bad?
Yeah. Come on. Let's go then.
Me, you, and the virgin.
We all meet up in Kent and we'll have a
[ __ ] scrap. Me and you, and the skin virgin.
Me, you, and the skin plonker. Oh, bless.
Oh, [ __ ] bless.
So, is that what you're going to do,
Greasy, when your iPhone packs up,
or you just going to get another um refurbished one
when it packs up?
Oh [ __ ] then.
Yeah, it's it's hard to get NHS dentist
now, but I've been going to this one for years, so yeah.
[ __ ] years, mate. Yeah,
I went to this escort before, Greavves.
She had big boobies.
Is that cute?
I can't believe my mom's phone fucking10.
That's [ __ ] good, bro.
That's a good phone. That's good.
That is good. That
You bloody virgin.
You blleming virgin.
Are you a bloody virgin, Grezy? You bloody virgin.
Where is that [ __ ] virgin? Where is
that [ __ ] virgin? He drives me
[ __ ] mad. He does that virgin Steven Howard.
I bet if I go on that channel right now,
I haven't been on that channel for two
weeks. It's It's a load of [ __ ] about me.
I bet it's a load of [ __ ] about me, mate. Yep. Isn't it? Yeah.
No, it [ __ ] wasn't. It was [ __ ] embarrassing.
It used to get laid.
It's not funny. It's embarrassing.
It's not funny at all.
a [ __ ] skin blogger.
That tandoori chicken was lush.
Absolutely lush. Greasy. It was loose.
It was [ __ ] lush.
It was loose.
You're never going to get laid. [ __ ] virgin. Yeah.
Yep. You know, Greavesy, you know. Oh, man.
Yes, it is
getting too Old for what?
You're getting too old for what?
What? Going out drinking and stuff?
Nah, he's not allowed.
He's not allowed um he's not allowed
anywhere near Sarah
because he'd get locked up.
He's never had more than two. He's never
had one. He's still a bloody virgin and
he's gone one. He's never had he's never
had a [ __ ] He's not allowed anywhere
near that disabled girl. That's his bloody carer.
Nope. Never had sex. I know a virgin
when I see one, mate. I know all the
signs and he has never had sex. Never.
And he can show a disabled girl all he
wants. But you can't put a wall over my
eyes. You'll always be that virgin from
Ken. You'll always be, mate.
Nope. Nope. Don't have sex with her. Never. Nope.
Nope. Nope. Nope. If you had sex, you
wouldn't be on YouTube every day
stalking me. Someone with a healthy sex
life. Steven Howard. There's not someone
there's not come on YouTube stalking
someone that doubt want to know you.
That don't want to know you. If you're
having all this sex, why are you on
YouTube stalking me every [ __ ] day,
you big virgin? Cuz it doesn't add up, mate.
Nope. Four years and never had sex. I
know. It's amazing. It's it's it's
Four years and he's never had sex. I
would have [ __ ] left her. But well,
left though. She's [ __ ] disabled. I
know full well that he's never had sex
cuz he's still a virgin.
A big big virgin. I know full well that
he's never had sex. That's the only full
well I know. So
why would I get too old? Why am I too
old to shag women? Bob,
>> why would I be too old, bro?
I know full well that you've never had
sex and you're still a virgin.
Oh yeah, obviously. Yeah, but that's
obviously why I don't go out as much.
I don't go out as much [ __ ] um
anymore because of that reason.
Stephen, how would you like the Samsung
flip phones? They're they're quite good.
Stampson uh flips.
Yeah, they're good them ones.
They're good. Flips, folds, you know.
Yeah, these people say get a referred phone.
What's the most you would ever pay for a
mobile phone, Bob? Bills. Yep. basically. Yeah.
Yeah, I was thinking that as well.
About five. Yeah,
I think five is I that's the most I'd pay.
I think it's
a lot, but it's just right. You know [snorts]
what? on a new one or refurbished one.
So, if you didn't need to work on the
phone, then you could get a refurbished
one. But if you need to work on the phone, then
it's best off just buying a [ __ ] new it.
Well, you wouldn't pay 500 for [ __ ]
refurbished phone, would you? Would you pay?
Yeah, but you wouldn't pay £500.
That's what I'm saying. You wouldn't pay
£500 for a [ __ ] refurbished phone
though, would you?
Yeah, but you wouldn't pay it for a
refurbished phone. That's what I mean.
You see what I mean? Yeah,
I've had this fold for a year now. The
Samsung fold. I don't think it's packing
up anytime soon.
Nope. Don't think it's packing up
anytime soon, buddy.
That's the only thing we've rebured.
If you don't need to work on the phone,
then the refurbished phone is okay. But yeah,
well, we'll see if if I can get this
phone anyways. So
that's cute. When I get this phone, I
can start booking holidays, Bob, cuz
obviously I have a phone that's not
blocked. Oh, it's exciting.
I can put a deposit down on holiday.
That'd be cute. Ah,
bless. That's bloody cute, isn't it?
Yeah, that's cute, man. That is cute. Ain't it?
USA Izzy had iPhone. Stephen Howard Before
I go out drinking again, I'm going to go
to this uh
going to this Brazilian place again.
What's your favorite romantic?
I don't have one, bro.
Can't see all day, lad. Better the
devil. You know, lads
want greener abroad. What the [ __ ] are
you talking about, bro?
I've already been on holiday before.
You've seen that?
You [ __ ] seen me on holiday, bro? >> [laughter]
>> He's He's a
How are you going to lose it?
When you going to lose it?
>> Oh, yeah. I'm going to chill until I
feel like I need a a good hangover again, bro.
until I feel like I need a about.
It's packing up. He's [laughter]
packing up, matey. That's why. Yep.
Are you going to lose it? How you going
to lose it? Are you going to lose it?
Do you remember Adam? Steven Howard. [laughter]
Oh, [ __ ] hell, man. >> [laughter] >> Yep.
I messaged the guy in Bristol. Um, his
brother's friend. I met him as well. I
said to him, I'm coming to Bristol on
Saturday. Let's have a few beers. His
name's also Adam.
Let's have a few beers. >> [laughter]
>> See what he says in it. Yeah.
Do you know about Bristol, Steven
Howard? It's near London.
Yeah. Do you know that, Bob? You know,
Bristol is the outskirts of London. Yeah.
Yeah. Bristol is like the outskirts of London.
It's not too far.
Yeah. It's not far from London. Bristol.
It's not too far, Bristol.
No, it's not too far.
All right, Captain.
Did you like the chicken?
It was nice, isn't it? What are you doing now?
Yeah, it's not too far.
Oh, just someone I met last week.
Do you want to see my beard now?
>> I need to go to the Barbies.
I need to go to the Barbies, bro.
Look, I need to go to the barbers, but I
can't be bothered.
One sec. I'm just at the seat now. Wait. [clears throat]
>> [clears throat] >> Lovely. Lovely chly. >> [laughter]
>> It's [ __ ] cold.
Oh no. He's a [ __ ] s bastard. These
are [ __ ] sad, bro. I'm just going to
drink the whole bottle.
You like it, bro?
Where? He's a proper stalker, bro. He's
a [ __ ] fat loser. Have you seen the
size of his fingers?
Some fat loss, bro. Sing YouTube every
day in his mommy's basement. He's a
[ __ ] s bastard. Yeah.
Yeah. I need to go to the barbers though
to be fair. [clears throat]
We're going out for a while. So
I always pay £50 when I go barbers. Well 55
cuz I get face mask and everything. Oh man. Yeah. Oh, lovely.
Oh, lovely. Mate,
call me a nice bit of coke.
I need to stop I need to calm down on co cuz toothies.
I need another fing on another tooth.
I think there's a hole.
That's all right. I like the dentist. Oh gosh.
I can't believe you've only got 200 pound left,
Bob. Oh gosh,
I can't believe that. Oh gosh,
that's a madness.
But you get money every week as well.
You get money every week
like a little amount.
Do I get little
I get little amounts of money every week? Huh? Yeah,
that's mad, bro. I spent quite a bit as well.
If I if I had 200 pound left for 2
weeks, I get money every week as well. So,
well, a little bit a little bit of money. So,
yeah. How much How much do you get paid?
That's a lot to [ __ ] spend.
say uh mad.
Yeah, that's just one payment, isn't it?
That's one payment.
So you get one payment in a month. Yeah.
Yeah, I get I get uh I get 80 pound every week
on top of what I get. So
I still get like 80.
It's not possible, bro. 10k on a night
out. It's not possible.
1340 though. That should have lasted you,
man. That should have lasted you.
I [ __ ] I I bought the jeans and Ugg
boots. I bought my mom Ugg boots. Jeans, trainers. Yeah.
Ugg boots and [ __ ] you know what I mean?
>> If I didn't buy the UGG boots, I would
obviously have more.
>> Usually Bob's got £200 to last him to
the end of the month.
I was just saying that if I had £200 in
my bank, I would still get £80 every
week for the two weeks.
So it would like it'd be more like Yeah,
it would be like more like 360 basically. Basically, yeah,
you laugh at 80 pound every week, bro.
But it actually helps.
You laugh at it, you take the piss out
of it, but it's money for doing nothing every week.
It's uh Yeah. Yeah, bro.
Used to gamble a lot, did you? Oh,
especially than if you used to gamble a lot.
What's the chance if I put £500?
If I put £500 on online roulette, what's
the chance I can get to,500, Bob?
What's the squeeze here?
No, I wouldn't do that.
I wouldn't do that, bro. If I was to put
I would just put it all on a double both
teams to score.
I would just put 600 on a [ __ ] both
teams to score, bro. That's like £1,900. Done. Mad. Yeah.
Wonder what my mommy's up to nowadays. Tuesday.
Probably hurting some other poor [ __ ] E
probably hurting some other poor [ __ ] Yep.
Yeah, Scream 7's coming out in February. Steven Howard. >> Yeah.
What a [ __ ] game. [ __ ] [gasps]
I want to put 500 pound on a double both
team to score Steven Howard, but I'm scared.
I want to do it, but I'm scared.
I might lose.
Then I'll cry. One sec. [snorts] >> [snorts]
>> One second, bro.
I do good though, don't I? Steven Howard
on the both teams to score.
I do quite good on them, don't I? Yeah,
I do do quite good on them.
Yeah, I I [ __ ] lost the [ __ ] last
one though, bro. 130 bloody quid.
And Tuesday there was limited teams
playing as well. Yeah.
You all right, Captain
Greavves? Are you all right, Captain?
And you're right, Captain. Yep.
I'm just lying under my little blankie.
Oh, my bedding should be dry now.
I can't be bothered to make it. Oh gosh, [ __ ]
Well, I'm going to go. Yeah. Uh, be back tomorrow, baby.