Right. Hopefully this time I'm talking
to myself. I don't want to see anyone on
YouTube. I don't want to see anyone
type. I just want to be talking to myself.
I'm just talking to myself.
That's all I'm doing. I don't want
anyone on here because they've all got
lives and stuff. They've all got jobs
and they've all got money. So, I don't
want to see anybody type.
Look, I don't want to see anybody type today.
That's all right.
Don't want to see anybody type at all.
Oh, look. We've got two people already
that should be at bloody work, but
they're on my live stream. Strange.
H. Very, very, very strange. I don't
want to see anybody on my live stream. I
just want to talk to myself
cuz I'm a bit bored today. So, yeah. I
just want to talk to myself. That's it. Yeah.
Just talking to myself.
That's all. Oh, free people now. O, you
bloody lunatics. You should be at work.
You tell everyone else to get a bloody
job every [ __ ] day. Why are you not at work? Oh gosh.
[ __ ] on YouTube.
Probably want to dust your show business
account. The sad bastard. You got no
life. But yeah, I just I just uh I don't
want to see anybody type.
Don't want to see anybody type today.
Talk to myself. Don't mind talking to
cuz I use this as therapy sessions. All
four people now that should be at work.
Jesus Christ. So many people at work
watching me. It's crazy.
[ __ ] crazy. Absolutely crazy. Oh gosh. Oh god. [snorts]
Oh, it looks like everybody's at work
today as they should be. Oh,
the [ __ ] Oh, the [ __ ] is wrong with you? The hell did that?
Didn't even make any sense, baby. That's Oh gosh. Okay. Oh, again. Franklin
people not typing. That's good.
Everyone's at work today.
I don't need to work me. I can just sit
around playing GTA. [snorts]
What the hell? Bloody hell. Of course.
What the hell is going on, mama? Oh, [ __ ] Frankie,
Frankie James, stop it.
Well, I'm going to go on another channel
to see if anyone's on here. I don't want
to see anyone on this community. I I
want to be the only one on here.
But you've been on Lord J's and there's
people on there. Why are people on Lord
J's channel? They all said that they
work and that they've all got a life.
It's just the same repeating bloody
people. What the hell? They're liars.
They ain't got a job. They ain't got a
life. I just went on it. It's the same
repeating people. Oh. Oh gosh. It's the
same repeating people.
So same with beating people. Well, they
say they've got bloody lives and stuff.
Well, they [ __ ] well don't have lives
because they're on here every day
self-projecting because they're
miserable fat lonely [ __ ] That's
what they are.
Self-projected little nerds. That's what they are. [sighs] Oh gosh.
Oh, what are you doing
to me, mate?
Leave him alone. Leave him be.
He's been absolutely spectacular this evening. Right.
Oh, you almost got run over by my big car.
Oh, Franklin, what are you doing?
Look here in your big car, Franklin. Yeah.
Yeah. I'm not going around thingies
again because of the [ __ ] cat. Huh?
Because the cat keep every time I go
there, the cat keeps attacking me.
Yeah, it's a little copycat.
I said, "Leave me alone, you silly
copycat." And it keeps [ __ ] attacking me. Yeah. is not Franklin.
Mama, did you know Franklin can use prostitutes?
Did you know Franklin could use prostitutes?
No, he can use them.
He can do Yeah, huh?
Yeah. Franklin's a dirty man.
Let's beat him up.
Yeah, he can use an escort. M.
He's going to get his haircut later.
I like Franklin this kid.
No, I was just saying I hope no one
joins and and types Greasy because again
these people have got a life and all of
these people have got a job. So I don't
want to see anyone on here
but but me, you and Steven Alward. I
just want to talk to myself, you know,
because these people should have, you
know, should have a life. They should be
at work and stuff. You know how it is.
They shouldn't be on YouTube.
These people shouldn't be on here.
They've got lives. Remember everyone's
skin. Remember, you know,
I going to that Brazilian place again
soon. So, you're going to see you're
going to see it. Greasy. Oh, now I was
thinking about that when I woke up. That
place was lovely. Yep. [snorts]
Phone's not back in stock yet, Graves.
No, it's not back in [ __ ] stock yet. Maybe tomorrow.
Yeah, I spoke to aunt about it. He said
that he he said that he's got an iPhone
12. Yeah. And he bought it 3 years ago
and it cost £200. He said he got it from
swaps and sales.
He said he got it from swaps and sales.
Three years. [ __ ] 3 years. What the
[ __ ] Yeah, it's an iPhone 12. He said
it does everything that he wants it to do. Not yet.
Yeah, it does everything that he wants
it to do.
He bought a [ __ ] washing machine for [ __ ] £50.
That's lasted years. Mom, have you have
you used swaps and sales?
Mom, have you ever used swaps and sales?
Swaps and sales?
Like it's like another Gum Tree thing.
Swap Austin. Swap and sales.
It's basically where people sell stuff all over.
I know someone that bought a washing
machine secondhand £50. It still it still works.
Mad is it?
But when I had the old house, I just
thought I would just buy the washing
machine outright in it cuz it was new.
[ __ ] nice washer. It was
a good times, eh? Easy. Good times.
Yeah, I'm [ __ ] not going back to that
house. Well, not with that bloody cat.
He keeps bullying me.
Every time I go to the house, that cat
keeps bullying me. The ginger cat. Huh?
Yeah. He keeps bullying me. The cat.
Yeah. He keeps calling me gay. The cat.
He keeps bullying me and copying.
Go away, you stupid cat.
What's What's the cat's name again?
I I would have named it something different. me
named it Biscuit. I I would have named
it something different. Yeah.
Yeah. I I've got a good I've got a good
name in mind for that cat.
Yeah. Has all the same signs. You know
what I'm saying? No.
No. I would have named it that. It's
beginning with S.
And a sheep is also called the same thing. >> [laughter]
>> Yeah. Just too many um similarities, you know.
Come on. You You got a brain. Yeah. [laughter]
No, he's beginning with S. Gi. He's >> [laughter]
>> Got to figure it out.
Leave me alone, you stupid cat.
I've got a mind of my own. Leave me
alone. [ __ ] cat. Copycat. >> [laughter]
>> Oh gosh.
Driving around in my little car.
I'm a bit bored today. I should go out drinking. Nah,
can't do that. Sorry, sir.
It's uh no
sh it's no uh it's no shame November is it? So yeah
I can't do that unfortunately
see how it's getting on now.
Looking quite hairy. I'm looking quite the monster.
I might be Father Christmas this year, mama
with a beard.
I might dress up as Santa. Santa Claus.
The beard should be long enough by then, shouldn't it? I reckon.
Yep. What do you think?
Well, Christmas night
sticking up his middle finger. Huh?
I can't hear you, mama.
I had a piggy baguette for uh breakfast
and a lovely piggy baguette. Gosh,
I feel like I'm carrying a baby
alligator in my stomach. M.
My back was hurting me yesterday.
You know, like your shoulder,
the back of it. I think I'm getting old. Oh,
I think I'm getting I'm becoming an old man.
What are you doing, Franklin?
Drive me a little car.
You never ever saw my little uh
Scooby-Doo babies, did you?
Oh, [ __ ] Almost fell over. Look
at the bubba. That's Scooby and that Scooby-Doo's baby,
if you must know.
You You making your bed, mama?
All right. One sec.
Yeah. Why was you showing me a bed? I
said, "You won't be getting in the bed.
I'll be getting in it."
You like Scooby-Doo and his baby.
Yeah. The baby.
You like it? [snorts]
The same website you can watch Yoda on. [laughter] Beans.
That's funny, isn't it?
>> No, he's not a bean. He's a lovely little dog.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, mate.
I can't get out of my dressing gown. Ma,
it's too cozy.
>> I like my little dressing gown.
>> I only like the ones with the hoods on
them in it.
I can't wear one if I don't have a hood.
Reminds me of being a little boxer.
Oh, what you just do?
Did you just do to Mr. Mcuzuse, mate?
A [snorts] little nose.
Oh, what was that? Oh gosh. Huh? Nice.
Cheers for that.
I got a blankie.
Yeah, I had to. I slept under the
blankie uh last night, Goozy, cuz my
bedding wasn't dry. It was damp. Nasty and damp.
No, not it would have been I like it to
have a couple of days dry, you know, in
this weather cuz it could still be damp,
you see. So, yeah, I need to go to the barbers.
It was good.
Yeah, it was really, really good.
Shouldn't you be at work?
Shouldn't you be at bloody work?
You bloody [ __ ]
You bloody [ __ ] Should you be at work? Worky cause. [laughter]
>> That's funny, is it, Grezy?
You're at lunch. You're on lunch. Lunch isn't 11:00.
Lunch isn't at 11:00, matey. That's not
lunch. Most places are not open until
12. So try again, matey. You're not
You're not at lunch.
You're not You're not at lunch.
[ __ ] off in lunch. You're in your little
nesticles. Shouldn't you be at work?
No, you're not at lunch. You're not at
lunch. There's no way. There's no way.
Lunch isn't at 11:00.
I will get a job. When you get yourself
a job, I'll get myself a job. Same goes to you.
The same thing goes to you.
Same advice goes to you.
right back at you.
Same to you, sir.
When you get yourself a little job, come
back to me.
>> I don't This is what I find weird about
this place is people that ain't got a
job telling other people to get a job.
That's [ __ ] weird.
They tell people to get a job, but they
don't have a job.
Is that something that always
made you wonder,
mate. You're the one. You don't have a
job. So, I mean, sponging off the
taxpayers, that's what you're doing
because you don't have a job. Neither
does Wolf Girl have a job. You none of
you have a job. So, again, ask yourself
that question. Instead of self-p
projecting, you need to ask yourself that question. You know,
people that tell people to get a job,
but they don't have a job themselves.
It's mad, isn't it?
Did you used to see it on Seaside Marks,
didn't you? Um, Greavvesy
Seaside Marks. Remember Seaside Marks um
channel. They always used to say, "Get a
job. Get a job. Get a job." And half the
[ __ ] 90% of these people don't have a job themselves.
Very, very, very few people in this
community have a job, bro. that and you
would know you'll know the ones that do
have a job.
I think Joseph Ferrar works maybe Jay
Willow but people like you know like
Clint and Smokey not a chance in hell
they work. Not a chance in hell they've
got a life either. Believe that bro
believe that they don't. Trust me they
don't bro. I would say maybe 10% of this community works
maximum bro. believe that.
And how would I know that? Because I've
worked and when you work, you don't have
time to come on here. And these people
seem to be on here from the time they
wake up to the time they go to bed.
So, they obviously don't [ __ ] work,
you know. It's not like they're on here
an hour or 2 hours at the end of the
day, you know? You know? Nope. On it all
day, every day from the time they wake
up to the time they go to bed. But they
claim they got jobs. Yeah. Okay, bro.
Okay, they ain't got [ __ ] jobs. Jay
Willow might have a job. Joseph Ferrar
Cuz if you notice, these people will be
off and then they'll come back on.
It's cuz they ain't got a life. They
ain't got a job. Me,
I'm like one of these people when I'm
like saving money. Like I'm saving money
at the minute. I'm not going out because
yeah, I want to detox. Doesn't matter
how much money I get, I always do the same thing.
But these people claim that they've got
a job, they've got a life, and they've
got all of this money, but yet they're
sat on here all day, every day. It just
doesn't add up. What does 0 plus 0 add
up to? Nothing.
So there you go. It adds up to nothing, bro. So,
and when you work, you're very, very
tired as well, you know.
So, but these people seem to be on there
all the time, but they've got jobs. Mad
crazy, is it?
How did it turn into a self-projecting
community? It used to be gambling, but
now now it's just people that just
self-project. It's mad, isn't it?
>> Madness. Absolute madness.
I love to know how people that's got all
of this money and this life spends so
much time on here.
Are they saving for a new car? Are they
um what what are they doing exactly? Are
they saving or what's what's the score?
Because in CO there was an excuse. You
see, Grezy when there was when CO's
going on, right?
Abuse me. No, they don't abuse me. They
just they just self-project. And we're
not talking about this channel. We're
talking about L Js. We see you on L J's
as well all the time when I used to go
on that channel. Same low lives
repeating people. So, I mean, you don't
come here self- project and leave cuz
that's what you do. You don't abuse. You
self-project. Um, but I've seen you on
other channels when I used to go on
large and it was the same people every
day, but apparently they've got lives
and jobs. Doesn't add up. Um, so I mean
the thing is
Grezy it's not co anymore. They've got
no excuse. January they've got an excuse
kind of. I mean everyone's broke
January, you know. Well or they don't go
out. They're either broke or they don't
go out. So then you've got So you got
you got uh I haven't been on there. I
don't go on there. But I'm saying when I
did used to go on there when I did used
to go on there. Yeah. I I used to go on
there. Not anymore because it's the same
repeating people. So there's you got uh
if if obviously COVID was an excuse or
if they're saving money which I doubt
they are um or January people don't go
out January so if they're on it January
then it's like oh okay well you know
you know what January is a dead month
but you will see people like Trevor
Dawson and all of these other people sat
on here in a summer's [ __ ] day bro on
a hot summer's day bro like I remember
this year Bro, it was so hot. You
couldn't even be on your phone. You
couldn't even be in your [ __ ] yard.
And how do I know? Because I used to go on there.
Because I used to go on there. That's
what I just said. And it was the same
repeating people that ain't got a life.
So that's why I stopped going on there.
It's the same atmosphere.
You know, it might be new ones now. I
don't think so, mate. I don't think so.
It would always be the same repeating
people on there,
same comeback, same projecting.
[ __ ] bro. It's [ __ ] It's a
shitty community. So, yeah. Anyways, in
the summer, you know, there's no there's
not really an excuse to be on here the
way these people are on here. [ __ ] me.
[ __ ] me, bro.
When it's so hot, but they're they're on
here all the time.
I think 90% don't work.
You got some [ __ ] [ __ ] called
[ __ ] Jamie Thompson stalk stalking
me. Stalker me
every day. Loser.
Yeah. Community is full of losers, mate.
They try to [ __ ] bring other people
down. That's what they do.
That's what they are. They're just
depressed, sad, fat, ugly people.
Depressed with their lives. Yep. Well,
at least you admit it. Unlike these people. [sighs]
Yeah. These people pretend they work,
but they don't work.
I don't know, man.
I don't know.
I could go out today, but I'm on a
detox. Go out tomorrow. I want to detox.
I might go out Saturday if this person
meets me. I might invite them out to be
fair. I've got nothing better to [ __ ] do. So yeah,
I went out last Thursday. It was dead.
Yeah, it was [ __ ] dead, bro. [ __ ] dead. Um,
but I feel like there's no part going
out now until [ __ ] December.
To be fair,
that hangover kind of put me off, bro.
[ __ ] I'm not going to lie.
I was happy with the £100. Spending
£100. I was happy with that food and drink.
But like I said, if someone wants to
meet, then it's a different story, ain't
it? You know, but if they don't want to meet,
then I'm not going to go out and [ __ ]
start talking to [ __ ] women, you
know? It's just going to be the same [ __ ]
Did I pull?
Why are you asking questions you already
know the answer to?
Does your brains not register or
something? You people in this community?
No, no, no. Hey, you're asking me if I
pulled and I live in England. What do
you think? You know it will always be
the same here. Just like I know it will
always be the same here.
Need to get this some sort of phone
sorted out as well. Then I can get the
ball rolling. Once I've got this once
I've got this phone out the way, I can
get the ball rolling.
But if this person wants to meet, then
it's not a problem. Like I said, I meet.
I don't mind if something's guaranteed
meeting someone. I don't mind meeting
someone. But I'm not wasting
[ __ ] time. And I don't even think
it's money. It isn't even that
expensive. I'm not wasting my [ __ ]
time going out [ __ ] speaking to
people again when they're all the
[ __ ] same for a long time. It's
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
[ __ ] Absolute [ __ ]
It's [ __ ] bro. You know, you know,
this folder. It's got something on the screen where like
It's kind of like not broken, but it's
kind of like, how do I explain it? It's
like glare on the screen from where I've
opened it and closed it. And they're
charging 16,700 for these phones, by the way.
That do that. That's how much they're
[ __ ] charging. Mad.
It's bad that they bring a new phone.
They're not a grand. They're £1,700.
So, you pay £1,700 for a phone
that a new one comes out the next year.
They come out every summer.
This is not the new one. This is the
seven. No, this is a six. But there's a
seven. It's not [ __ ] a grand. It's like £1,700.
No, they're not £1,100. They're £1,700.
I know, mate. I know about folds. I've
had a couple of them. They're not £1,100.
If they're £1,100, I'd pay it.
But I can't be paying £1,700 for a
[ __ ] phone, bro. That's [ __ ]
insane. Can't even justify that.
There's no justifying it. and then a new
one comes out the next year. It's just
mad, you know.
They're not £1,100.
Well, you clearly don't know your phones
cuz I know exactly how much Samsung folds cost.
So, you must be really disabled if you
think they're £1,100 because there's not
one fold that's £1,100.
So, you must be disabled. [snorts]
Are you people disabled in this
community? No, no offense. Like I'm not
trying to like bully or anything because
you seem to have like memory problems.
No, no offense. I'm not trying to bully
or anything. I'm I'm not I just don't understand like
you ask questions that you already know
the answers to. Like, oh, did you pull
when you know that it would always be
the same here. Just like I know it would
always be the same here. So, I don't
give a [ __ ] But then you're you're
saying about a Samson fold is is is
1,100 pound. I mean, do you do your
brains work properly?
Really, bro? Does your does your brains
actually work properly? I don't think
they [ __ ] do. Seriously, don't
[ __ ] wish they were [ __ ] £1,100.
I think £1,000 you could justify.
You could you could justify £1,000. I I
mean most people wouldn't most people
wouldn't pay it, but I would pay a,000.
Yeah. It's like what £1,000 a year?
I would. I I actually would.
I would. But not [ __ ] not £1,700,
bro. Have a [ __ ] laugh.
That's how much my Boston thing cost
with the hotel. The flight to the hotel
thing was £2,75.
No, it isn't. You [ __ ] [ __ ]
Isn't you [ __ ] [ __ ] They're 1,700
pound. You [ __ ] [ __ ]
You're probably thinking of the [ __ ]
flip. You [ __ ] [ __ ] Don't [ __ ]
try and tell me, mate. I know more about
phones than you will ever know.
You absolute [ __ ] [ __ ] Go on the
[ __ ] Samsung shop or [ __ ] Argos
and type Samsung fold. You [ __ ]
complete [ __ ] You don't know your
[ __ ] phones well enough when you're
getting it wrong, do you? You [ __ ]
You are the [ __ ] You're the one
that's getting [ __ ] flip and [ __ ]
fold, you know, mixed up. Yeah, you're
probably talking about the flip. You [ __ ] Mong. Yeah,
I'm uncomfortable in my own skin. Really?
That's That's weird.
That's that's that's a weird thing to
say. Where where would you come out with that?
Must be self- projecting again. Very
random thing to say about someone that
you don't know.
Must be self projected.
Very weird thing to say about somebody
that you don't know.
Generally, bro, like I generally think,
yeah, you people honestly, man, you just
look in a mirror and you just talk about yourselves. Generally,
you just look in a mirror
and talk about yourselves.
You list out everything about yourself
and your disabilities get you confused
with other people. That's what I think
it is with you people on here. Yeah,
definitely. Definitely 100%. Yeah.
No, I don't stink, matey.
[ __ ] hell. So, any of you people
going to get a life and get a job? Anyways,
[clears throat] uh,
no, cuz that's you self-p projecting. No,
no, because that's you self-projecting,
bro. So, I never I never give it any
thought because again, that's your own
life you're talking about. Absolutely hideous.
Now that's you talking about yourself again.
Bomb gray cat. All these other people.
Nope. Listen. Like basically let me let
me let me save you your time. Yeah.
Whatever you try to project onto me
that's your reality. It's not going to
work. So you're just wasting your time.
Honestly, you're wasting your time. skin.
Um, you can try and say that I'm skin.
It's just self- projecting. Um, you can
try and say that I'm ugly. Self
projecting. Everything that you try to
say, it's not going to affect me.
So, you're literally just wasting your
your time, bro. Like, for real. You
could be way you could be you could be
using that time to get yourself a little job. Yep.
That's the level. [sighs] Um yeah. Yeah.
So anyways, when are you going to get a
life and get a job? You skimp bastard?
When are you little skin fins going to
get a life and get a job?
Yeah, you're jealous. You can't afford a
Marley jeans, can you? H
Yeah. It's why you shouldn't talk about
people that you don't know, you know?
You people get proven wrong like all the
time and you still come on here and talk
[ __ ] It's actually embarrassing, bro.
It is actually embarrassing.
Do you remember when I was like, "Oh,
should I buy these trainers? Should I
not buy these trainers?"
I'm thinking whether I should, whether I
shouldn't. And then this stupid little
[ __ ] comes on saying, "Oh, it's because
you can't." Oh, can't I? Okay, I'll buy
right now. You got to prove it wrong again, mate. Yeah.
Oh, [ __ ] off. Yeah. Only you
When are you going to get a job? Get a life.
You want to make up your [ __ ] mind, matey?
I swear. What is it with these people's
bloody mental health, man? I swear to
God. What the [ __ ] Seriously.
One second. I'm coming back.