[clears throat] Let's
turn it on. Oh,
proper proper [ __ ] in it.
No, no, no. Actually, turn that off actually.
Why are you being such a [ __ ]
Link, one second.
Bro, this Escort is a [ __ ]
One second while doing something.
Sorry, bro. I can't be talking to you
right man. I can't deal with your W accent
right now, bro.
Oh, give me a [ __ ] headache.
Sorry, bro. Not right now, man. No,
no. I messaged one. I had one on my
phone who I've seen four times and I
thought, "Oh, I'm feeling kind of uh
horny, you know." So, messaged them.
Even even their [ __ ] now. Bear in
mind, I've seen this person four times
to where I used to live at the old house
and [ __ ] Used to do the football bets.
And I messaged them saying, "Uh,
I said uh oh, you back in London." They
said, "Yeah." I said, "Oh, you didn't
tell me." She said, "Oh, I wasn't there
the other day." I was like, "Okay,
something's a bit off here. I'm getting
a bit of off vibe." So, I I can sense
vibe, you see. Anyways, I said, "Oh, um,
yeah, let me uh" I said to them, "Let me
let me come to you." And they were like,
"Uh, oh, I I can't. It's very discreet.
Um, I'm living with other people." And I
said, um, okay, strange. Bear in mind,
I've seen this person four times. Yeah,
literally four times. Then I was like,
"Oh, well, do you want to do you want to
come here then?" And then she says, "Oh,
I can't go to clients houses as it's
dangerous." I'm thinking, "Bro, you've
seen me four times. What you what the
[ __ ] are you talking about? How it's
dangerous to go to client's houses?" And
she was just being a complete [ __ ]
Like absolute [ __ ] bro. Like she
was doing everything to avoid. I'm
thinking bit strange, isn't it? I mean,
it's your job. You've seen me. And they
weren't like this before. Oh, they were
they were right before. So, they've
completely switched for whatever reason.
Who knows? But yeah,
very strange. Very very very very very
strange. See, it's even toxic even when
you like try to use like an escort if
you use one every 3 months or whatever.
Whatever the reason,
whatever the reason uh is.
Well, I'm going I am actually going to
Thailand soon. I am actually going soon,
bro. I'm actually going to be booking it
soon. So, I won't be single. Matey. Oh,
that Taiwan still messes back by the way.
Yeah. So, hopefully she meets. I might
go out on Saturday if she wants to meet.
So, yeah, she's basically just being an awkward [ __ ]
Being a difficult [ __ ] even though
she's seen me four times. That is insane, bro. Yeah.
My friend just messaged me saying,
"These girls are long." Nah, it's not
even about long, bro. It's toxic.
You know, any anyone can deal with, you
know, something being long. It's not
long. It's toxic. That's that's the
that's the perfect word for it. It's toxic.
You know why the [ __ ] I swear that
Chinese one messaging me, but she's in
[ __ ] Blackpool and I'm not going Blackpool.
Like, how does someone switch like that?
Like, what do you mean you don't go to
client's houses because it's dangerous?
How the [ __ ] is it dangerous when you've
met someone four times, you absolute
idiot? Just being a [ __ ] bro. And
towards the end, I was going to get her.
I was going to get her. I was going to
get her [ __ ] going somewhere else cuz
when they a [ __ ] like that, you know,
how would she know Lane is about, bro?
She doesn't know my [ __ ] mom. She
doesn't know my sisters. How would she?
She stop saying stupid stuff. She's just
being a [ __ ] She's just being a
She's a [ __ ] bro.
They're [ __ ] bro. One second.
doing is I'm going to get a refurbished
phone with a new battery. I decided
Yeah, I'm going to get an iPhone 13 with
a brand new battery. So,
yeah, you can actually choose a new
battery. So, I'll have this fold once
that phone's out the way. Yes, I'll be
able to leave, bro. Lovely.
They're not all the same, says the virgin. Jacob
the Jacob. Jacob, the virgin says
they're not all the bloody same. the skin plonker.
>> So yeah, you can actually get a new battery because
I don't know if
why would I get 17? I don't even usually
go for iPhone. I mean, so I mean it's
the cheapest, isn't it?
I don't really go for iPhones. I fancy the change. Yeah.
Yeah. It should be 13's good enough now.
Yeah. It's just toxic. I had a bad
hangover last week, Jacob. Bad hangover,
bro. Oh my god. I thought I was dying.
So, I won't be out drinking this week
unless this person wants to meet.
Is that the most latest iPhone in 17?
You can get a flip phone. You can get a
Samsung refurbish flip phone. Obviously,
you get a new battery. Yeah.
I mean, what phone do you choose, Jacob?
I'm not paying more than 500 for a phone. So,
cuz it's um ridiculous.
I paid 300 whatever. Yeah. I'm not
paying more than 500.
It's not worth it.
I've got this phone as a
It's not worth it, Jacob. It's not worth is it? Nope. Yeah, but
I I was going to get an Android. That's
what I usually get. This is what I have, but
I'm not paying [ __ ] ridiculous
amounts for it.
There's a Samsung S24.
It's 460, but still not back in stock.
It's like um
it's on there there's there's there's
phone deals, isn't there?
I don't know what I'm getting, bro. I
don't know what phone I'm getting.
[ __ ] knows. I don't want to pay too much
for it, though. That's the thing.
Oh, [ __ ] knows, mate. [ __ ] knows.
Yeah, the fold is 1,500. I'm not paying
that. And I've already got that phone
here. I got this phone, but it's blocked.
They're good phones, but they're not
worth the money.
But if you get an iPhone 13, it should
be all right. Huh?
That man's got iPhone 12. He said it 12.
The 12 works fine. But I could get a
Samsung flip. I could get a flip
with a new battery. Either way, I'm
getting a new battery, but I don't know,
bro. I don't know.
So, I can't get the contracts anymore.
It doesn't let me get a contract. I
wouldn't get the Fold 7. Maybe I'll get
the Fold eight when it comes out, but
there's not much difference
in the year. There's not much difference
within the year. So, I mean, if I really
wanted the new phone, I could get it,
but it's not worth it because the money
you you pay for that you could be
putting out towards a holiday.
But the eight, I could maybe get the
eight, you know, when it comes out. They
come out every summer and eight's my
lucky number. So, I thought I might as
well just wait another year to be fair
cuz every year is not going to be um the
same, you know. So, I I get the eight
but something for now. I'll need
something for now. I don't know.
>> All right, Captain.
>> You all right, mate? [clears throat]
You all right, Captain? What's happening, lad?
What? What? What phone do you have?
>> Just bought a new Just bought a new one
there, man. Off some money. The Samsung new Samsung.
>> What? Which one?
>> H I don't even know which one it is to
be honest, lad.
>> Was it expensive?
>> You only 230 for it. Like
>> what? New?
>> You wish.
>> What's What is it refurbished?
>> What you mean?
>> What What phone do you have?
Samsung Galaxy. I don't know what the
name of what one is though.
>> Well, it was 230.
>> All right.
>> So, it's used. No,
>> I used it. Yeah.
>> Yeah. That's what I mean.
>> Must be the newest one. Must be used
>> I don't even know.
>> How can it be the newest one, bro?
>> Not like No, like not the news. Not Not
like the [ __ ] You know what I mean? Like, >> yeah.
>> What's been going down like, bro?
>> Just been chilling, bro. for you. >> Um,
[ __ ] all this.
>> I done a football bet two weeks ago. I
lost that one, but I won the one before.
>> Ah, you seen that, lad.
>> You need to You need to get on them
[ __ ] You need to get on them [ __ ]
double both teams to score, bro.
>> Yeah, guys. [snorts] Was a lovely. It
was in the first half, was it?
>> I won a I won a couple of them, bro, the
past. Um, that's why I was able to do
things, you know? It's a good win, isn't
it? I want to I want to put £500 on one,
but bro, I don't know about that, man. [ __ ]
I bet you done what what double rock
came in both things man that was a
lovely bet that man on it
>> I know but I think it's just stupid
putting that sort of money on like
>> I think the max I'd put on it is
probably like 150 max maximum bro
>> yeah I wouldn't be going high that's how
you beat them man like doubles and that
one trebles and four timers and that's
that's what they get you
>> or if you won like a lot on roulette
then maybe you could if you won a lot
then you could put more like if you one
money maybe but not your own money in it.
You know what happens, bro? Whenever I
do Yeah. a double both teams to score,
it's always both score no draw comes in.
Bastard all the time, man.
>> I know. But you got to you got to play
it safe. Just do both teams scaring you. Cuz if
>> because if you done a both score, no
draw and it both ski both teams draw.
You wish you'd done the other. So you
that you know, you might as well just
play it safe, isn't it?
>> It's just not worth the risk. Pete, >> no.
>> So how's your um
>> how's your Jane? >> [laughter]
>> I don't know. She's a bit of a straw,
ain't she? [clears throat]
>> So, wait. Why did you buy a new phone?
Did your other one your other one pack up?
>> Almost [ __ ] die.
>> Where did you buy it from?
>> I've got contacts. I've got a contact,
but it's just contact SIM card I've got.
I was going to [ __ ] get
>> Yeah, that's the best. It's the best that way.
>> You know, you know, you know, if you get
a contract Yeah. phone, right? And for
whatever reason, you can't pay it.
They'll just block your phone and you're [ __ ]
>> Ah, yeah. I um I just got a contact in
me. I only paid 22 quid. won't limit
everything but I was trying to get a
deal with them but the contract's over
three year now only used to be over two
yeah that's the phone I bought [ __ ] I'm
not buy you say like it's 30 quid a
month over [ __ ] three three yeah
you're looking at like over [ __ ]
>> yeah I get a phone you can buy the phone
oh the [ __ ]
>> where did you buy it from the phone [snorts]
>> just someone off [ __ ] Facebook lad
>> oh okay yeah yeah
>> I was going to go
>> there's a phone shop there's a phone
shop near me but I didn't have back
going and Sure. Have you seen that?
>> I like I like the folds, bro. But
they're too much in it. They're too much, bro.
>> Say that again.
>> I like the Samson Fos. I've got one
here, but it's blocked. But there's a
new one in it.
>> Steven, I would pick King Android. I don't
>> I'm going to get the Fold 8 next summer.
What do you think?
>> H I've not seen the Fold, me, lad. I
>> You've never seen the Fold? >> Nah.
>> It flips into like a tablet. Yeah, of
course you have.
>> I haven't. Honestly, haven't. Oh, it
basically it's like a phone and it just
flips into a tablet. It's sick, bro.
>> It's a flagship phone, isn't it? They
never They never pack up. They never go slow. Nothing.
>> Yeah. I went from Android to Android. They like
>> Yeah, that's Android. It's Samsung. Yeah. >> Yeah.
And I think they're like they're like
[ __ ] £1,700 them phones, bro.
>> Is that what they are then? [ __ ] hell.
>> They're too expensive, is it? I wouldn't
pay that far for
>> you'd pay you'd pay it if you won like
50 grand though it was
>> then you would it that's the only way
you could justify it
>> I was talking to [ __ ] man providers
and about um I want the guy wanted the
iPhone 17 but like since three years not
[ __ ] over 70 like 3 years or [ __ ]
it off [snorts]
>> and another thing is they bring a new
phone out every year as well that's
that's the thing so when you when you
spend all that money on a phone then
another one comes out the next year.
[laughter] The point
>> Steven out with me. All right. You are PJ.
>> I said, "Say you buy a phone, bro."
Yeah. Say you spend a lot of money on a
phone, a new one's going to come out the next year.
>> Yeah. Within six months. It's stupid.
>> That's what I'm saying. So, [clears throat]
bless you, bro. I went I went out last
week, bro. I got smashed, bro. I got I
was on the cocktails like the Ray and
Nephew. You know what that is?
>> Hear that again? The what? Nephew.
>> The The Ray and Nephews.
>> What's that? It's like whiskey.
>> Oh, no. I don't mind whiskey. I like Jack,
>> bro. I had cocktails with Romney. I woke
up with a banging headache, man.
>> You run over, lad?
>> Yeah, man. [snorts] >> Yeah.
>> You've been out drinking or
>> uh last week. Last Thursday. I had a few
last Thursday. But
>> yeah, that last Thursday.
>> Last Thursday. Yeah, last Thursday.
>> Yeah, I went out last Yeah, that's when
I went out as well. Last Thursday.
>> I didn't get about like [ __ ]
>> I don't know what it was, but I was I
was at home. me and I was like, "Oh, I'm
bored. Let me just go out." Cuz I used
to go out a lot Thursdays, isn't it? I
like Thursdays. But yeah.
>> Yeah. Is your PDS full block? So, it's
stuck on Android 12. You got your phone
blocked, is it?
>> Yeah, bro. Long story.
>> Have you been Have you Have you I seen
your uh Was that No, that steak that
video you put on today with that with
that steakhouse you went to. Was it Rio?
>> It was Was it What?
>> Rio steakhouse.
What? What do you mean? Rio steakhouse.
>> Is that the name of the place you went? Rio steak.
>> No. No.
>> Why have you been there?
>> Yeah. The one in Middlesbr.
>> Nice, bro.
>> You look nice. You scan life, fella.
>> Thank you, Captain.
>> You like the Indians as well?
>> Oh, you said you're a black Indian,
isn't it? He said, "Yeah,
>> I like Mal. I can't handle SP me. I'm a L."
>> Yeah. Do you remember L? [laughter]
Did you see his video, L? >> Yeah,
>> that man's a fool. Like
>> he's [clears throat] Yeah, proper prop.
He's proper skint as well, isn't it?
>> Yeah, he's a really, man, he's a big [laughter]
>> What? So, is that is that the most you'd
pay for a phone then? 230.
>> No, 300. Going back.
>> That's the most you'd pay in it.
>> Yeah, I want that.
>> That's it. [laughter]
>> You're not tight, is it?
>> No, I'm not tight. I just don't I don't
think that's his point. How all these
people want to get these um new iPhones.
>> Yeah, that's what ad man said. He said
there's hardly any difference between
like them. You know what I mean?
>> He's right. Like it's only the camera
what's a bit better sometimes and a
couple more different features and not really [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Have you been in doing any call? I've
seen your video when you [ __ ] when
>> in the weather spoon and you were
[ __ ] going off it with that l.
>> Did you like it, Captain?
>> It was wild that live. Did you like it, Captain?
>> Why did you flip with them? Like, what happened?
>> Because No, I No, I flipped on one of
them cuz she was being a [ __ ] bro.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah.
>> It was only one of them. I wasn't
arguing with the other.
>> Approaches. Triple
>> you. You need to dare. Well, I'm not
telling you to do it like but them
gambling videos used to do used to be
good like fishing frenzy but when you I
haven't been on a [ __ ]
>> I a play that bro I ain't played that
for ages man
>> so good man you never win now I don't
even go to me now I just don't go at all
>> the last time I played roulette was
like a month ago I think I put 50 and I
got to 150 but that was in the bookies I
don't play that [ __ ] bro cuz it's
dangerous Ah, he is just brutal fell.
Um, yeah. So, what do you think?
>> You used to lose your rages and you used
to do the walk of shame. [laughter]
>> I was going back a long time ago now
like but that was bad that I
>> don't mean that and then [ __ ] having
I used to get bored with my dad like but
it's still embarrassing.
>> Yeah, [ __ ] that.
>> I used to go to cash point me and just
take 200 quid and another 200. Well, at
one point they wouldn't let me [ __ ]
fingered me card at one point. It was >> really
the fun even blocking it was me. I was
just had a bad loss gambling. >> Mad. >> Yeah.
>> So, have you been
>> You watch the boxing?
>> I did. I [ __ ] I took on anyway.
>> I got I got tickets to go see it, but I
didn't go. I couldn't be bothered.
>> You should have went, man.
>> But my sister paid for them. They were
But they were all the way at the back.
They were like back seats and they
weren't like front row and it
>> Yeah. Uh they'll be like dead two little
[ __ ] what's the word called dwarfs
when you fire up it's horrible.
>> Yeah that's what it's pointless is it?
>> you might as well just watch on the
[ __ ] TV at this at that point is it
>> was a good price as well. He was 13 to
10 that couldn't back me up.
[snorts and clears throat]
>> Well yeah I heard you was friends with
um Cristiano Ronaldo. Is that true? [laughter]
>> Is that true?
>> Yeah. You don't know who it is, isn't it?
>> I don't know. Ronaldo is
>> He's not, you know, he's not the best
footballer, is it? Nah,
>> he is.
>> I swear um Messi is better. No.
>> Nah, I don't reckon so it's a big
argument over that, but no, I don't
think he is. I think Ronald Ronaldo is great.
>> What the best ever?
>> Yeah, I say so.
>> Do you play football?
>> Used to lad, but [ __ ] on my man. You
know, you know the best sport is
basketball and ice hockey.
>> What a bet on.
>> No, just to play it. Have you know ice
hockey? They play in Canada. Have you
ever seen it?
>> Yeah. [ __ ] that [ __ ]
>> It looks good though, bro. Ain't it?
>> Any more approaches like?
>> No, not since last week. But I can't be
asked. Yeah. No. No. No. You might when
are you going on the pool again?
I don't [ __ ] go out. Watch me, lad.
I can't believe how skinn you are. Well,
that's self projecting. So,
>> it was that nutty log.
>> When do you think you'll be out again?
>> I'm thinking, mate, the not this
weekend. I've got me.
>> I'm thinking like mid December, bro.
Now, to be fair, but I might go out this week. Depends.
>> I might.
>> If this woman wants to meet me, I met
someone northwest. If they want to meet,
then obviously I'll go out this week.
it. It's not a problem.
>> Are you planning on making a bed?
>> Yeah. I'm speaking to someone, so we'll
see what they You know what I mean? Yeah.
>> Yeah. [laughter] Remember that video you
made before? And you're going to make
that [ __ ] last and you were going to
leave the table and make the bell.
>> Yeah, she was she was being a cond. [laughter]
>> But yeah, [ __ ]
>> Did you like that thing? Did you find
that funny when I said um when someone
said Peter Bell has already found his mama?
>> Um yeah, it was funny, lad. Yeah. Yeah.
>> There's an account that keeps coming on
it mocking me and I don't know who it is.
>> What's him?
>> Did they change? Like one of the
accounts was called Bob.
>> They need life man. The sad people lad.
>> They said that. They said yeah.
Peter Betty can't get attached anymore
cuz he's already found his mama.
>> [ __ ] sad, isn't it? Huh?
>> The [ __ ] sad people have doesn't know
where to turn to. It's just trolling, isn't it?
>> Yeah, but the on the in the out hour
after hour like they've gotten out in
life. That's why they
>> Oh, you know, you know Tim Eldridge, he
needs help, isn't it?
>> Yeah, Tim Eldridge. Yeah, he does. He's [ __ ]
He does need help. He just needs a break
off of you. Tim, [laughter]
>> did you see the video of him with the
woman on the train?
>> I don't know. I don't know how [ __ ]
outlaw Jake even sitting slacked him off
me. Like, have you seen the st that last
year, mate? He's not blocked again. He
blocked me again cuz I bullied him.
>> But, bro, did you just see the video of
like Timmy on the train with that woman?
>> Uh, yeah, I seen that. Yeah, he was a bit wild.
>> It was funny, is it?
>> No, it wasn't funny. It was [ __ ] It
was off his head. I think he was going
to buzz that one. Oh, did you see the
one with Money Mike when he met Monty
and that they all met up?
>> You know what? I never seen it. I caught
a clip on that there on someone's on
someone's [ __ ] YouTuber. >> Yeah.
Money Mike said to me, "Yeah, do you
want to have a Do you want to go for a
drink or do you want to do a dirty?"
>> Ah, that's the one I watch outside the
>> Yeah. Do you know what that means
though? Do a dirty fight.
>> Yeah. How did she know?
To work out, mate. Is it? I would have
said I want to do it dirty in it.
>> He ended up having a drink and Monty man
bought loads of bash or something shed.
He thought it was sniff or something. >> Yeah.
>> You reckon he's going to get sent down?
>> Monty, man.
>> Yeah, he's in he's uh he's going caught
on the 27th.
>> I know he's I can't I don't really know
what it's on about. Like I don't really
>> You know that writing thing ages ago
when you done that writing he got nicked.
>> Writing? No.
>> The writing? Yeah, the writing.
>> Nah, don't know, man.
>> Yeah. Well, he done some writing [ __ ]
and that ain't it. So,
do you think he's going to get sent down?
>> No, he won't get sent down. I don't
think No, I don't think he for that. No,
depends. It depends what he's up for.
Might have more stuff on him. You don't know, man.
>> Yeah, if you get Yeah, that's scary
though, is it?
All right. It is a [ __ ]
>> Yeah, but you if you went prison, he's laughing it.
>> Yeah, he's had he's had some [ __ ] on you
man over the years. I know he said some
[ __ ] bad things like that which I
don't agree with. Like but >> yeah,
>> he's harmless really is he?
>> Yeah, he's just [ __ ] mongering it.
>> You fell out with him, haven't you?
>> No, I just don't talk to him, man.
>> Just don't talk to him. We don't argue
nothing. We can't be bothered in it.
>> Have they been snowing in London?
>> No. It felt like it was going to
earlier, but no.
>> Are you a little Are you a little Jordy, man?
>> So, uh, where's your next Yeah, bro.
When's your next um the next time you
leaving London? Like, huh? When's the
next time you leave in London? I thought
you normally go and stuff like that, don't you?
Never. He went to Middlesbrough before, didn't you?
>> Yeah. That Trevor Dawson didn't come
out. Do you remember? Do you remember
the video? [laughter]
>> He would come out with [ __ ] excuses.
>> I think I seen that video like [ __ ]
two days later or something. I thought [ __ ]
scary. Middles were scary, bro.
>> [ __ ] All B.
>> It's scary, isn't it?
>> [ __ ] ruthless.
>> It's full of spice heads and [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Full of [ __ ] down and out.
When did you last go there?
>> Wow. Two months ago. I went shopping there.
>> You went shopping there of all places.
>> I was going to go to Metro and you met
Metro but [ __ ] I didn't It's too big,
man. Isn't it? It's too big this Metro,
mate. It's It's too big. So, [ __ ] I
could be asking my trips around there, man.
>> Yeah. I went to a mall before in
Newcastle. It always seemed quiet. It
must have been another one then. There
must be two in it.
>> Yeah, it is. Yeah. Yeah,
>> because that one always seemed dead to be fair.
>> Massive man.
>> I used I I was around the Newcastle um
more approaching. Bro,
>> you got lucky then?
>> Nah, bro. No, no, no. It's easy to get
women up there though. [snorts]
>> Full of all [ __ ] stuck up [ __ ]
>> All right. Um,
>> when are you gonna when are you going to
come to London, man?
>> [ __ ] knows, mate. I don't know. Do you drink Guinness? >> Yeah.
>> I am a Guinness drinker. Like
>> I love Guinness.
And the only good thing with Guinness is
they can't water it down. You know that?
You know when you drink rum? Yeah. You
know these clubs, they water it down.
You know that?
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> That you can get through them. You can
get three of them. Get through three of
them and it doesn't even it doesn't even
hit you. Whereas Guinness, it's harder
for them to
>> It's like8 pound a pint in London, but
you you don't have more than what? Six. No,
>> that's it. Yeah. No, I can have 10 easy.
>> You have more than You can't have more
than that though, is it?
>> I don't know. The most I've had is 10,
but then I get sick of them. I go on
like [ __ ] Red Bull or something.
>> Too much too heavy, aren't they? >> Yeah.
>> Um Yeah. [ __ ]
>> Yeah. I like Guinness, bro. >> Yeah,
>> we should meet up.
>> I know you meant to come and you ask a
lad again, aren't you?
>> Yeah. You going to make another excuse
this time like the other times? You can't.
>> No, I'll meet you, lad.
>> What? To do it bad or go for a drink?
>> Say that again. [laughter]
>> I said, "Do you want to go for a drink
or do you want to do it bad?"
>> You're bad. [laughter]
All that [ __ ] money m bro.
>> Is a money m up [ __ ] the old saying
in his you going bail or something he?
>> Yeah I think for rape or something.
>> Is it? It [ __ ] has. >> Yeah.
>> I smoke vapes me.
>> So you've been you've been horny lately?
>> Nah. Nah.
>> I' I've been a bit horny today, bro.
>> Getting greasy. There's greasy in lad.
>> Well, you never like you don't really
get horny, do you?
>> The best man.
>> You said you don't really get horny, do you?
>> Not really cuz I used to get all >> huh?
>> I used to get all lad.
>> What about now?
>> Not so much.
>> I sure fancy [ __ ] now. [laughter]
>> You are?
>> Yeah, I fancy a [ __ ] today.
>> You okay? Brasses order you.
>> Yeah, some well you know whenever I go
for a night out drinking I always go
through escort in the end. Yeah.
>> [ __ ] be though ar
some of them
>> you get some [ __ ] like what look like
crackheads and that like [laughter]
>> who about 40 50 bar but the props want
150. Yeah. Are
>> you going to get back together with your ex?
>> No match. That's me finished now lad.
Oh, bless you.
>> I'm looking forward to Christmas, mate.
>> Really? What are you getting?
>> Uh, I'm going to I'm [ __ ] nearly 30
now, but I'm just going to get trainers
and tracking off track and I think and
um I want a mon [ __ ] what do you want
in the name?
>> Where's your birthday? December or something?
>> January my birthday, lad.
>> Oh, yeah. Cuz I was saying in it cuz you
said almost you're almost 30, isn't it?
[snorts] All right.
So, you're born in 96. Yeah.
>> And I'm 97. Yeah. Yeah. Makes sense.
>> Yeah. I bought some UG boots.
>> I know. John Ly's got some, hasn't he?
They're a mad.
>> They cost me 165 quid.
>> Well, you've got some.
>> No, I bought my mommy some.
>> Oh, yeah, lad. All right.
>> And I bought myself some of Marty jeans.
You saw them? Do you like them?
>> Nice M, lad. Yeah, they were. Nice M.
190. What? 200 they were actually.
>> Is what you paid for them? [ __ ] hell.
>> Yep. And the trainers was 210.
>> I've got replay jeans on me. >> Huh?
>> I've got replay jeans, me.
>> How much are they?
>> I paid 16 for them, I think.
>> No, I got them for 140. Actually, they
wear 16. I got them for 140.
>> Yeah, you can't beat nice jeans, is it?
>> Lovely, mate. A nice jumper as well. And
brand new trainers.
>> Yeah, you can't beat it. You can't beat
it. I like the Vapor Maxes. Me?
>> I don't like them. I'm a 110 man. Me?
>> Your what?
>> 110s, man.
>> What? Air Maxes? >> Yeah.
>> Well, they the old old school ones.
>> All right.
Well, the 95s from here, but everyone
calls them 110s in Liverpool and that.
>> How much are they?
>> No, the 175. They used to be 110. That's
why they get called 110. Going back to
>> Yeah. Yeah. Expensive, is it?
my mind on clouds as well. I like on clouds.
>> Well, bless you.
>> You know,
>> you know, like you used to. So, what is
it? Did you prefer the UK one or USA one? [laughter]
>> Uh, probably the UK one. I didn't know
the USA one.
>> No, like looks and that. [snorts]
>> I don't know. I don't actually look like
a USA one, M.
>> Yes, you do.
>> I don't honestly.
That's my mama.
>> Not your mom, mate.
>> Yeah, she looks like me in it. >> Yeah.
>> Taking a baby away from his man of wage.
>> Hey, what do you think of that big John
Lavry then with his [ __ ] Ugg [ __ ]
what they called?
>> I think he's a fat ugly skin p.
>> He's got shoes on the [ __ ] women.
He's a [ __ ] freak. Yeah,
>> he is a big boss of that John [ __ ] lovely life. >> Yeah.
>> Right. I'm going to go tell you lad. If
you got late, I'll jump back on.
>> All right. I'll stay. I I I'll be
awaiting your arrival.
>> All right.
>> All right. See you.
Um yeah, Grezy,
I've decided I'm going to get iPhone 13 refurbished.
Is that okay with you, boss?
Is that okay with you, Captain?
Oh, this escort was being a [ __ ]
crazy. This escort was being a [ __ ] bro.
You can get a new battery, but I'm going
to I might just get the standard
battery. If I need a new battery, I'm
sure you can get another battery
installed, can't you, Grezy? You can get
another one installed, can't you?
I'm sure you can.
Yeah, this escort's being a [ __ ]
[ __ ] Grezy, bro. [ __ ] [ __ ] man.
being a [ __ ] today. Greaves, can I tell
you what happened? Yeah.
Yeah. But you save a lot of money
getting a refurbished one.
Yeah. You you save a lot of money.
And you can get a new battery as well.
Brand new battery put in. So, I mean, that's that.
Do you know what?
I'm going to get you a present, Steven
Howard, for Christmas.
I'm going to get you a Samsung Galaxy A17.
Yep. I'm going to get you a Samsung Galaxy A17.
Okay with you, boss. $129.99.
It's about 4 GB of RAM. All right, mate.
Is that okay with you, Captain?
You wouldn't use that phone, though. It's [ __ ]
Now, but seriously, agrees with you.
Would that phone be good? iPhone um 13 refurbished.
Would it Would it last me a couple of years?
Will it last a like two years?
I'm not buying you a I'm not buying you
a PS5. Sort of off.
PS5 sort off, mate.
Yeah. Well, it lost anyway, Grezy.
Yeah, it's £270, Grezy. The iPhone 13
refurbished is black. £270, mate. Yeah.
You can pick the condition that you want
it in as well.
And also I got this phone as well. So
like I said, I'm going to get the
Samsung Galaxy 8 Grevy. I'll get the
eight. Yeah, Samsung Galaxy 8.
Sorry, Samsung Galaxy Fold 8.
I'll get the next year one maybe.
Antman said, "Greasy, what's the point
in paying 500 for a phone when you can
get one for like 200, 250 refurbished
and then you can spend the other you can
spend the other bit of money going out?"
Is he right, Greavves? I think he's right now.
Yeah, it's true though. That Yep.
Tell me what I should do. Gy, give me some advice.
The Samsung phone still hasn't come back
on um it still hasn't come back
in in talk.
Give me some advice. £22.
It was lush. Grezy, can you give me some advice?
Yeah, this Taiwan keeps messaging me
about how have you tried anything really
common from there?
That doesn't really make sense what she
just asked, but yeah.
No, but Grevy, seriously. Should I just get the
What phone should I What phone should I
actually get? Grievy. Seriously.
What should I get the £270 refurbished phone?
It's from uh you can choose the
condition that you want it in.
What iPhone do you have again? Grezy,
you have like the the 14, don't you, Captain?
Thank you, Captain.
Yeah, this escort was being a [ __ ]
today, Greavvesy. Anyways,
so I've seen this person four times and
I thought, "Oh, let me message them,
right? Cuz obviously I need my vitamins
and a lovely [ __ ] and stuff." So I've
messaged them. I said, "Oh, you in
London?" They turned around and said, "Oh, um
I said, "Oh, you in London?" They were
like, "Oh, uh"
they said, "Um, yeah, I am." I said,
"Why didn't you let me know the other day?"
And um they're like I wasn't there the
other day. So I was getting off vibes
from this person Grezy who I've seen
about four times. So then I was like oh
um oh let me can I come to you? I was
just saying it. I don't know what I was
actually doing. Then they were like oh
um at my um
she said oh where she's living it has to
be discreet because she's living with
other people. I'm thinking weird. She's
gone weird all of a sudden. Um and I
said oh why don't you come to me? And
then she was like, "Oh, I can't go to
clients houses. It's not safe." And I'm
thinking, "You've literally seen me four
times. What are you talking about?
You've had my number for God knows I
think over a year now. You've seen me
four times. What do you mean it's not
safe?" And then she was just being a
[ __ ] Like an absolute [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] Um, so yeah, I told Aunt Mad
about it as well.
Toxic, bro. Very, very, very toxic.
It's [ __ ] bro. It really [ __ ]
It's weird how they switch like that, is it, bro?
Toxic. Absolutely toxic.
So toxic these women, bro.
wants to meet, I'll go out. But other
than that, I don't know when I'll be out again.
Yeah. She's a [ __ ] bro. This
escort's a [ __ ] [snorts] Yeah. >> [snorts] >> myself.
taking a baby away from its mama. Yeah.
these women are [ __ ] [ __ ] mate.
Yeah, I can't go to my [ __ ] sisters
anymore. Um, Steven Howard, bro, this
cat keeps [ __ ] attacking me, bro. Cuz
I don't like Chevel Cole. We call him the copycat.
Why do you Why do you always say, "What
am I having for later?" [ __ ] nothing.
We're not all fat [ __ ] like you that
eat [ __ ] five times a [ __ ] day,
you know? Isn't that right, Grezy?
Yeah. I I can't go to my sisters anymore
cuz the [ __ ] cat, bro. He keeps
attacking me because I don't find Shelco attractive.
I hate them. I hate copycats. Yeah. >> [snorts]
>> Well, you'd actually use that phone if I
buy you that $129.99
phone. You'd actually You'd actually
want it, Steven.
[sighs and snorts] [ __ ] that.
Why don't you want the phone? Nope.
Yeah. Nah, it's love it's a lovely phone, mate.
It's a lovely phone.
Yeah. Well, I'm still talking to this Taiwan.
She just said I said, "Oh, I can take
you to this food place." She said after
all of that it will be a good bit of cardio.
What does she mean by that? I said what
do you mean what kind of cardio?
I hope they don't mean sexual stuff.
That sounds very sexual to me.
This is Taiwan. I said I had beef, lamb,
pork. It was lovely. I said maybe I
could take you sometime. She said after
all that it'll be a good bit of cardio.
What the [ __ ]
I hope they don't mean anything sexual.
That's a bit weird.
What the [ __ ] bro?
No, she's not.
What does she mean by that?
I had the want to go out and run. Yeah, sure.
Nah, definitely not.
She's talking sexual [ __ ] bro.
Sorry, bro. I was talking to someone. >> [sighs] [snorts]
>> One second. I'll be back in a bit. Hold on.