Talk about [ __ ] toxic. Sorry.
Same old [ __ ] again.
Sorry about that. [ __ ] I was talking
to some one.
That's two [ __ ] idiots I've had to
[ __ ] put up with
and I didn't even need to leave even
ever had to leave the house.
You know what? I don't understand why
they waste their time and why they waste
your time. This is what I I I I don't
understand with these people, bro. Like,
you you would have thought it'd be
common sense to not do any of that.
Same old [ __ ] Can't find someone
grown up in their [ __ ] head.
It's Yeah, there's no one normal out
there, bro. It's [ __ ] It's obvious,
isn't it? Obvious obvious to [ __ ] Obvious.
Same old [ __ ] I won't be out this week
anyways. That does it.
So boring. It's the same old [ __ ]
thing. You know what I'm saying? Like
Oh, you know, people's going to think
I'm think I've been gambling now, bro.
Not even to be fair.
It's the same old [ __ ] with them, isn't
it? Every time.
It generally generally is the same old
[ __ ] with them every [ __ ] time. No
one's grown up in their [ __ ] head.
told that man about it as well. She
loves about [ __ ] Thai people, bro.
person is really going to do that, bro.
Like, come on.
It's just the same old [ __ ] Waste of
time, waste of money. [snorts] You know,
I'm very bored that day, bro.
meet anyone that's normal for all of
these people that are supposed to be
different. Where are all of these normal people?
Jesus [ __ ] Christ.
Same old. Same old. Same old. It's
[ __ ] boring, bro. never changes.
And at the end of the day, bro, I don't
even really like Thai people, but I was
giving this person the benefit of the doubt.
And they would turn around like, bear in
mind, this person's been speaking to me
for [ __ ] like a week. And I was like,
[ __ ] it, whatever. It's [snorts]
something to do. And then she comes out
with a load of [ __ ] It's always the
same old [ __ ]
Like, do you know what I'm saying, bro?
It's always the same. This is why I'd
never go out, bro.
Because you, you know, you got these
people, right, sat here, right, saying
to you, "Oh, they're not all the same.
They're not all the same." Really, bro?
[clears throat] Really, bro? Really?
Really? [ __ ] really, bro? They're
[ __ ] full of [ __ ] I'm going to
message that guy in Red as well saying
that they're full of [ __ ] They are so
so so full of [ __ ] [ __ ] It's
unbelievable, bro. God knows what it's
going to be like in [ __ ] 2026. You know,
and bear mind I I give these people the
benefit of the doubt, but deep down I
think we know they're all the [ __ ]
same. But I just thought because I was
just speaking to this person, so what?
Am I supposed to go out and do it all
over again? Get [ __ ] I'm not doing it
all over again. Suck my dick. I'm not
going out doing this all over again,
bro. I am not doing this [ __ ] all
over again. I'm not doing it all over
again, bro. Yeah. I tell you what I'm
doing. I'm buying that phone and I'm
booking this trip. That's what I'm
doing, bro. That's what I'm [ __ ]
doing. You can get [ __ ] [ __ ] You
know, it's just [ __ ] bro. It's
[ __ ] every single time. And I've had
enough of it. You know what I'm saying?
I've had enough of it. You know, I
thought, you know what? Maybe one
Saturday, one Saturday, one Saturday, we
we can just deal with something that's
not toxic for one week. For one week,
just one week, not have to deal with
some toxic [ __ ] But no, no,
you know, same toxic piss taken. No
matter the age, no matter the
nationality, they are all the [ __ ] same, bro.
They are all the same. Oh my god.
Literally, it's so obvious. Like you can
even you can even ask Ant-Man this.
They turned around and said this is what they said.
Yeah. What do they say? I don't want to
lie even though you've already lied. I
iron the irony. Huh? I want to be honest
with you. That day I felt very not be
able to say no to giving you my number.
But I'm not interested in any commitment
if that's why you're bothered to talk to
me. It really can't go beyond a simple
friendship with no benefit. A friendship
with no benefits. And I'm thinking, bro,
you've literally been speaking to me for
over a week. What the [ __ ] Pressured
into if you if you felt pressured into
giving your number, you wouldn't be
[ __ ] messaging someone back, back and
forth, back and forth, back and forth.
It's [ __ ] mental. Like, it's it's
it's crazy, bro. Crazy. And then you're
It's mad. They're [ __ ] They are
obviously all the same, bro. It's It's
It's so obvious these women are all the same.
Nationality [ __ ] It's They're full of [ __ ] bro.
You don't want to lie, [clears throat]
but you just lied. People that are
pressured block people. People that are
don't respond to people, [ __ ]
[ __ ] hell, bro. Can't even have a
normal [ __ ] week and no [ __ ] and no hiccups.
Yes, because it would always be the same
here. It would always be the same [ __ ]
You know, you're trolling with a sex
question and then you're coming out with
about how you only want. It's [ __ ]
mad, bro. They're [ __ ] mad. Stop
moaning and winging about men. I'm sick
of it. I'm sick of these people moaning
and [ __ ] winging. You know, I was
willing to [ __ ] lower my standards
just to not have a toxic week
because when you go out and you try,
it's toxic. Which is why I don't bother.
You know what I mean, bro? It's
[ __ ] It is absolute bollocks, bro.
Just one [ __ ] week. You know, I
wanted to be able to actually go out and
do something this week and not deal with these bullshad,
bro. You know,
weaker. No [ __ ] would be lovely, you
know. Be lovely. But nope, that's too
much to ask for apparently.
Yeah. [ __ ] after [ __ ] after
[ __ ] after [ __ ] after [ __ ]
That's all you come across is the same
[ __ ] That's all you come across,
bro. It's like, what the [ __ ]
I thought, yeah, they might live here,
but you know, so,
you know, it's always the same thing. It
It literally is always the same thing.
Why are they messaging you, wasting
their And you say that they don't waste
their time and your time. You You say
they don't do that because it doesn't
make sense. Well, they just did another
one. Toxic and all the same. [ __ ] me.
How many more times do you have to keep
going out, bro?
Yeah. And yet she's been texting me for
the past week. I know. It's a tricky
one, isn't it? But yet they've been
messaging me for the past week. Yeah.
Make Make it make sense. Make it
literally make sense.
Um, they actually they actually
pretended they had a boyfriend at first as well.
They actually had a they actually
pretended that they had a boyfriend as
well at first. Kind of. Well, they
didn't say outright, but yeah.
Yeah. Scared to give you a number, but
messaging every day. I know. It's mad, isn't it?
Well, they they didn't say they were
scared. They said they felt pressured.
Didn't seem scared. Yet, they're texting
you every single day. So yeah.
Well, it looks like I'll be inside this week then.
Yep. Well, it looks like I'll be inside
this week. Twiddling my thumbs again,
you know. Uh [ __ ] again.
Bullshitters. They're They're all
bullshitters, bro. That's what they are.
They're all [ __ ] bullshitters.
like you know you know why I went out on Thursday, bro.
Bro. Yeah. It doesn't matter if they're
playing the same game. They're in a
westernized country. They're
westernized. It doesn't matter, bro. They're westernized.
So, I just gave this person the benefit
of the doubt. I just gave this person
the benefit of the doubt.
You know, this is why I don't bother
with them because they're all the same.
Like, I I Bro, I went out that Thursday
cuz I was born out of my head. Yeah. And
I didn't want to stay in with an old
[ __ ] woman to be honest with you. Not
Not to be rude. I didn't want to stay
with an old [ __ ] woman,
you know? And I was bored. Yeah. And I'm
thinking, okay, we'll give this person
the benefit of the doubt as again for
the millionth time for people that are
not all the same. And lo and behold,
same games. And these people are
supposed to be adults the same age as
me. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You know, it's
toxic. It's [ __ ] They are [ __ ]
obviously all the same. You know, you
don't need to go, bro. Like how many
times, bro, do you have to keep going
out, wasting your time, wasting your
money, wasting the barber's time to
realize that these [ __ ] are all the
same, bro. They are literally all the
same. You know, they are literally
obviously all the [ __ ] same, bro.
Yeah, you got asked to meet quicker.
Yeah. And then when you get asked to
meet quicker, you'll say that you're
moving too fast. So, make up your mind.
And I didn't even ask her to meet. You
[ __ ] idiot. I said to her, "Oh, maybe
we should go to this restaurant
sometimes." Sometime. I didn't even ask
them to meet. That's the thing. I didn't
even ask them to meet. I was going to
ask them to meet tomorrow.
Guys saying that they're full of [ __ ]
Yeah, cuz they are full of [ __ ]
Yeah. Ask them to meet sooner. And then
when you ask them to meet sooner, it's
another [ __ ] excuse. So which one is
it? Make up your [ __ ] mind, you know?
And I didn't even ask them to meet either.
[ __ ] stupid little [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
You know what I mean? [ __ ] annoying,
bro. I didn't even like them, but it's
not the [ __ ] point. I just wanted a
week away from this [ __ ] But no,
you can't have that.
[ __ ] are all the same. My [ __ ] ass.
Yeah, I'm leaving. I'm leaving this
country. It's too depressing, bro. I'm
leaving. I'm 100% leaving, bro. You
know, I was chatting [ __ ] last time. I'm
getting out of it and I'm never coming
back, bro. [ __ ] this [ __ ] bro. [ __ ]
this [ __ ] You know,
what I'm saying,
bro? You're going to make excuses
whatever someone does. So there's no
point whatever someone does, you're just
going to make excuses. So there's no
point saying, "Oh, you should have asked
them faster or you shouldn't have not
asked them faster." Because you're
always going to make excuses for them.
So bro, there's that the conversation
doesn't even make any sense. You do one
thing, they tell you to do the other.
You do the other thing, they tell you to
do the first thing. Like it's bro,
you're always constantly going to keep
making excuses for these [ __ ] that do
nothing but play games because the
problem is them.
Because the problem is them. It's not
about whether you are saying to them
meet quicker or meet in a [ __ ] month.
The problem is them. So no matter what
you do, it's going to be the same
[ __ ] thing. You know
that's that, bro. it like
this is toxic. It's [ __ ] >> Yeah.
It's mad, bro. It's [ __ ] madness. Madness.
I'll find something to do this week,
bro. It's no problem. I would be going
out dealing with them again.
Yes. But bro, the thing is they kept
replying back. So I just assumed they
were [ __ ] genuine. Yeah. I just
assumed they were genuine and I was I
didn't have any plans to go out. So I
just assumed that they were genuine.
And then when you ask to meet faster,
you get a load of excuses anyways. So it
doesn't matter. Doesn't really matter
whether it's faster or, you know,
whether it's whatever because whatever
you you do, you're going to make excuses
anyways. This is exactly what I'm
saying. Just like the last load of
screenshots I put up. Oh, you're trying
to meet them too fast. You're trying to
meet them too quick. And now you're
saying meet them faster. So, make up
your mind. Which one is it? [ __ ] me, bro.
It's the time wasting and the
bullshitting, bro. You don't even need
to like them for it to annoy you. You
don't understand. Even if you don't like
them and you be like, "Oh, you just go
out with them because it's something to
do." You don't understand. It's the
whole principle of it. It's [ __ ]
annoying, bro. Why is this Scottish
[ __ ] transgender run off as well? Cuz
she doesn't like the truth. I showed her
it. I showed her the screenshots. What?
Truth hurts. No.
[ __ ] [ __ ] bro. [ __ ]
[ __ ] At least I won't be out this
week. [ __ ] that, bro.
Bullshitting every time. And I'm sick of
it, bro. I'm [ __ ] sick of it, you know.
But that's that. Anyways,
could do a video on it. Can't be
bothered cuz everyone's just going to
dismiss my struggles.
You know, it is actually mad at, bro.
It's just always the same old. But then
you get this virgin saying, "They're not
all the same. You don't know all women."
Yet, you literally will meet literally
thousands and thousands more women than
he will ever meet. and he will still sit
there and say, "They're not all like
that. They're not all the same. You
don't know all women yet. You know more
women than he will ever know. Not that
he knows more than he will ever know."
But these people will sit there and
continuously say to their blue in the
face that these women are not the same.
They will constantly say that they're
not the same. I mean, it's it's mad,
bro. It's mad.
Man, it's [ __ ] mental. It is actually
[ __ ] mad, bro. It is. It is. I'm sure
it it'll be funny in a couple of hours.
Uh, well, it's not funny. It's
depressing, but I mean, we can laugh at it.
And it's not even about meeting.
It's not even about meeting sooner or
not meeting sooner.
you know, I wasn't really asked, so I
didn't mind, you know, [ __ ] [ __ ]
about they're not all the same. [ __ ] out
of here, bro. Get the [ __ ] out of here,
but they're not all the same. And the
thing is, you know, the maddest thing
about it is that they're not even uh
they're not even honest. It's not even
like you meet people that are not
interested in honest. It's people all
they do is play mind games and leave
people on. That's literally all they do
as well. So, it's not even like the case
of people just not being interested in
dating and people being honest. They
literally just lead people on and play
games. That's literally all they ever
do. But then the thing is, you'll get
people like Ant-Man say that I'm the
immature one. I'm the immature one
apparently. Yeah, I've been called
immature a few times, but I'm the
immature one. Yeah. Really, bro? [ __ ] off, man.
It's a madness, bro. Madness. Get [ __ ]
My friend was like, "Oh, um, yeah, be
friends with her." My [ __ ] being friends
with her, bro. Get the [ __ ] out of here
about I'm being friends with her. Get
the [ __ ] out of here, bro.
I'm being friends with her. Are you
[ __ ] mad? I'd rather [ __ ] suck a
gay guy's dick than be friends with her.
A [ __ ] compulsive liar that leads
people on. E, no thanks. I'm not friends
with liars and toxic people that lead
people on. No, I'd rather suck a gay
guy's dick than be friends with her. Get
the [ __ ] out of here, bro. Suck my
[ __ ] dick, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
And that's me done again. Yet again.
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] after
[ __ ] after [ __ ]
[ __ ] off, bro. I don't have a sucking
dick for that, bro. Bro, that's that.
Well, I'm leaving anyways, bro. So, it's
not a problem. I'm leaving.
You know, the past couple of times I
went out, I could have got killed, you
know, because of this [ __ ]
I I could have got killed because of
this [ __ ] You know, you don't know
how these things escalate and ret
and ret. You don't understand how these
things can escalate, bro. All for what?
What, bro? Trying to trying to find
someone that's different when they're
evidently not different. They're they're
definitely all the same. So, yeah.
So anyways, I'll just say to her that's
no problem. You shouldn't leave people
on in the future and that's it.
I'll just say as well basically uh I'll
just basically come back. I'm not
[ __ ] coming back. I'm not [ __ ]
coming back. Come back. I'm not [ __ ]
coming back here, mate. When I'm
leaving, I'm not coming back. Simple.
I'm not coming [ __ ] back.
Get the [ __ ] out of here. I'm not
[ __ ] coming back. When I'm gone, I'm
leaving. I'm I'm leaving. I'm never
coming back. I'm never coming back. [ __ ]
off, bro. Not for a very, very long
time. So, I'll just say to her that in
future, you shouldn't leave people on.
But they probably will cuz that's all
they can do. You know what I mean?
What I don't understand is how they moan about men.
That's what makes me laugh is how they
complain about how they can't find men. You know,
they complain that they can't find men.
Um, but then when they get chances to
actually get people, they don't want to
know. But then they still continuously
moan and w about men. It doesn't make
any sense, bro, does it? Really doesn't
make any sense.
Yeah, whatever. These women are clearly
clearly all the same. It's obvious now.
It's [ __ ] obvious. You know, I don't
know how many more years you have to
keep going out to just know that they're
they're literally all the same. They are
literally all the same. I don't know how
many times you have to keep going out or
where you're going out, but they are all the same.
And the only reason Virgin Boy doesn't
think that is because he's still a
virgin and he thinks by defending them
they're going to be they're it's going
to be different because he's a virgin.
But anyone would know that these [ __ ]
are definitely all the same.
Well, I'm just going to troll the bits
back now anyways. So yeah,
same old bro. Yeah. D.
It's the truth and you [ __ ] know it, bro. Yep. Madness. Madness.
you [ __ ] know it. That's what I said
to the tenant as well. It's the truth
and you [ __ ] well know it, mate.
That's why you can't say anything
because it's the [ __ ] truth. I'm I'm
going to do a video on this and I'm
going to put these messages up there.
You can't find anyone in this [ __ ] I
don't care about finding anyone, bro.
It's just a [ __ ] It's so boring,
bro. You know what? It's actually more
toxic than gambling.
I would say it's actually more toxic than gambling.
When when I used to gamble, it's so it's
it's it's it's next level toxic, bro. It
really really is.
It's the truth. And you [ __ ] know it,
bro. You [ __ ] know it.
It is the [ __ ] truth. if I know it
[ __ ] well is.
Why do they do this stupid [ __ ] man?
I'm sick of their [ __ ] [ __ ] You know, Tiger
Tiger Tiger will have a lot to say about this. Matt
It's so mad, isn't it? Really, bro.
They're just like, it's like talking to
a brick wall, you know? You'd actually
have more sense talking to a [ __ ] brick wall. Madness.
And no one's honest either. That's
another thing is that people are never never honest.
Yeah, I won't be dealing with that for a
very long time.
Um, I'd have to be getting into I'll
have to get into something, bro. Some
horror films or something. This is not normal, bro.
I just don't understand, Greasy, how
you can't find people that
can't even not play games. Does that not
sound mad to you, bro?
Does that not sound [ __ ] mad to you?
It's [ __ ] mad.
And bear in mind, I'm the one that's
throwing my well, not losers, but I'm
not particularly um mad.
I just don't I just don't know how
these people [ __ ]
It's mad, bro. It's the end, isn't it?
That Scottish transgender gone quiet.
It would never change. It would never
Pretty much uh
not starting it.
And then even these escorts have [ __ ] attitude.
So I mean you're dealing with it in
Thailand now as well to be honest with you. You know,
you can't you just meet someone that's
normal like someone that's just actually
normal. Nope. Nope. Can't meet someone
that's normal. That's coming from me as
well. Someone that laughs at everything.
They are all the same. I don't know how
people can say that these women are not
all the [ __ ] same, mate. [snorts]
Like I you know how many times you have
to keep giving these people and and I'm
pissed off because I wanted to do
something on Saturday. You know, maybe I
wanted to do something on Saturday, but
I'm not going out and dealing with that
toxic [ __ ] again. So you can [ __ ]
right off if you think I'm going out
dealing with that again. No way.
I No, no, no, no, no, no, no way. You
know, I was up for drinking. I was up
for drinking and um
you know, and having a laugh and that,
but no, I'm not dealing with that [ __ ]
I'm not dealing with any of them. You
can get [ __ ]
Don't know who it is. Don't care who it
But what do people on Reddit say?
R R S ask.
So it's established that you can't meet people that
are normal, right? So we we we we
established that now, you know, that
they're not normal. So that's that started it.
I'm sick of [ __ ] bro. I'd have to be I
would have to literally be dying out of
I'd have to be dying out of my head bar,
bro, to want to go out again, you know,
especially in this weather. And it ain't
going to be for a long time. So yay.
They say they want to be honest, but
they're anything but honest. Another bullshitter. Another one.
But remember, they're not all like that.
[ __ ] yeah, right. Only a virgin would
say that, mate. Only a [ __ ] virgin
would say that. Yeah,
but then they moan and winge.
That's what I understand. Then they moan and winge. Yep.
It's mad, is it when you think about it,
right? You read Reddit and then you, you
know, then there's real life.
It is funny to be honest.
It It is funny in a way. It is funny.
Boring, isn't it? Boring.
Well, I'll tell Laney about this one as well.
She probably dismiss it
as people always dismiss your struggles.
I don't know why they they love
dismissing people's struggles, but they do. Yep.
I'm going to title it when is this
[ __ ] going to end?
When is it going to end? Seriously, bro,
when is it going to end? It never ends,
does it, wheezy, mad,
I was looking forward to going out Saturday.
She does dismiss it. A lot of people
dismiss your struggles. You don't shoot them. >> Well,
it's just You clearly can't meet anyone normal.
Clearly can't meet anyone normal. So,
what's the point? There's no point in
going out meeting people that do all
exactly the same thing.
They all pretend they got boyfriends
or whatever. Oh, they just lead people
on, don't they? That's that's what they
do. They lead people on. They feel so
pressured into giving a number that they
give their number and speak to someone
every day and lead people on. Yeah. Okay. Yeah.
But but they're but they're not all the
same. But they're not all the same. They
just act the same way, say the same
stuff, have exactly the same mannerisms,
but they're not all the same.
Can someone explain that one to me?
Cuz it seems like an oxymoron to me.
I was actually looking forward to going
out on Saturday, bro, and just not
having to deal with this toxic [ __ ]
time and time and time again. you know,
time and time and time and time and time
and time and time and time and time and
time again, you know, but no,
another one that's all the same. [ __ ] hell, bro.
I'm going to do a video on this anyways.
I don't give a [ __ ] I'm going to put
these messages up there
cuz I've had I've had enough of it.
Quite simply, quite simple. Well, I've
had enough of it. So,
we all have the same attitude. All act
the same way. Well, I've already lost
hope. So, go and [ __ ] off and stop
coming on my channel and trying. So, I
won't be out this week and I won't be
out next week. Get [ __ ]
That's that. That's me done. simple. You
know, I could have been in some serious
[ __ ] you know, the past [ __ ] couple
of times I've gone out. You know how
things escalate to deal with what? Time
wasting people that are apparently not
all the [ __ ] same. You know what I'm
saying? Like, [ __ ] this [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, that's what I'll be doing on a
Saturday. Looking at four walls.
It's dead, isn't it? It's that or deal
with toxic [ __ ] and deal with them
again and I'm not I'm not doing it. I am
[ __ ] not doing it again. Simple. I am
not doing it again. No [ __ ] way am I
dealing with their [ __ ] again. [ __ ] off.
You know, I'd rather sit there watching
paint dry, bro. I'd rather literally on
Saturday I would rather watch paint dry,
bro, than deal with this [ __ ] again.
>> I would rather like watch paint dry,
bro. That's how bad it is. you know.
Yeah. It's more interesting. It's less toxic.
No, what I'm saying is the toxicness
with the bounces, their attitude, me,
you know, giving it back to them, it
escalating. You've seen how it
escalates. What do you mean? What am I
on about, brother? I'm on about what I'm
on about. What I mean, what I've put up,
you know, if someone gives you attitude,
you say something back. If a bouncer
bees a [ __ ] you say something back,
someone else gets involved. All of these
things can escalate. It is toxic.
Hangovers, toxic. Dealing with
bullshitting women. Toxic. I'd rather
watch paint dry, bro. You know
what do you mean? What am I on about?
I'm on about what I'm on about, bro. The [ __ ] It's obvious
how things can escalate. It's toxic.
That's the word for it. Toxic.
So that's that. Anyways, I'll put this up later.
Yes, but you don't understand. The whole
thing is toxic, bro. The whole thing is
toxic and annoying. You don't understand.
[ __ ] going out dealing with
[ __ ] Women that are all the same.
I'm not dealing with it. You know, I'll
stay in on Saturday. It's not a problem.
Or I'll go and I'll go to the cinema or
something. see what's on. If anything's
on, I'll find something to do.
It's toxic. All of it's toxic. And you
wake up with a mad hangover and [ __ ]
It's not even about the money, you know?
It's not even It's not even just about the money. It's everything.
They're clearly all the same. How people
say they're not the same. They clearly
are all the same. They It's clear as
day. They're all the same. They all stop. Relax. So yeah.
No, it wasn't fun.
Time to leave now, buddy. Time to leave
now, buddy. That's what That's what we do.
Time to leave now.
The fun's over.
Yeah, it's time to leave now.
I'm leaving anyways. [ __ ] this toxic
So, yeah, I'm done.
So, you wasting your time now saying,
"Oh, go out this week. Go out next
week." You're just wasting your time,
bro. Cuz I ain't doing nothing now.
That's the end of that.
I need to save and I need to leave.
You know, we're almost at a good amount
now and that's it.
Like Grievy, if this person wanted to
meet on Saturday, even though I don't
like them that much, I thought, "Oh
yeah, it's something to do in it." So I
didn't have to sit in and be bred. But
as usual, these women that are
apparently not all the same, um, has
done the same thing again. We apparently
these women that are not all the same
because we don't know all women just
happens to do the same thing again. What
are the odds of this? You know,
you want to come around grievy on
Saturday? I'll watch you paint the whole
house if you want. I'd rather I'd rather
watch you paint the whole house than go
out drinking dealing with that [ __ ] again.
Same game, same leading on. It never
ever changes. It never ever ever ever
ever ever changes. Never.
And then when you say bad things, people
wonder why you say bad things, you know,
and then we just go round and round and
round in circles cuz that's what happens
when something is toxic. You see
that? You know, that's the thing that
annoys me, bro. That's the thing that
really really annoys me, bro. You know,
the thing is, Grezy, it's not that I
have a boyfriend or people that just
ignore. No, no, no. You know what annoys
me? It's it's the it's the leading on,
bro. That's what annoys me. That's what
annoys me, bro, more than that's the
only thing that annoys me, you know? You know,
cuz you'll get these little simps in
their corner defending them, bro. That's
the thing that annoys me. Nothing else.
nothing else, you know. [ __ ] bullshitters.
[ __ ] bullshitting [ __ ] you know.
Yep. But apparently they're not all the
same. But they're not all the same,
remember? No, they're not all the same.
They just act the same, have the same
excuses, same mannerisms. But women are
not all the same. They just happen to
all act the same. H I love Virgin Boy to
answer that one. How is it then if these
women are not apparently all the same,
how they all act exactly the same way?
Because no man acts exactly the same way
as me, bro. I can tell you that right
now. No one acts exactly the same way as me. You know,
no one acts exactly the same way as me.
That's what different is. Someone is not
like me because I am different from
them. They are not different. They are
all the same.
Virgin boy, they are all the same. If
you're listening, I've had more women
than you. I've been on more dates than
you. And I can confirm they're all the
[ __ ] same. When I said that to you
when I was 17 and I'm saying it to you
now when I'm 28.
Yeah. That's what I don't understand.
They moan and winge. They moan and winge
and complain how they can't find someone
repetitively. Yeah. Oh, we can't find
anyone. No, no, no. But they have a
chance of meeting someone. And I didn't
even want sex either. I just wanted
something to do.
They have a chance of meeting someone
and then they're not interested, but
then they'll Well, it's not even that
they're not interested. They lead people
on. They're not even honest. And then
they will resort to moaning and
complaining again and everyone has to
hear it, you know.
Mad madness, bro. [ __ ] madness.
Then they complain they can't find someone.
They can they complain they can't find people.
Strange, isn't it? Yeah.
Yeah. [ __ ] this for Game of Soldiers,
mate. Absolutely [ __ ] this, you know.
And they're not going to make me
depressed. They're not going to make me
not get out of bed cuz that's what these
[ __ ] want. And it ain't happening,
mate. They can [ __ ] themselves. Yeah.
They can [ __ ] themselves, bro.
Whatever. No, they're not. They're gonna
[ __ ] make me [ __ ] depressed. [ __ ]
that. I'll do this video [ __ ] later
and then that's it.
I don't know what I don't know what to title it.
Another woman that's not the same apparently. Yeah.
Same piss taking bullshiters. I mean
it's not surprising really.
Yeah. No one cares what you think, bro.
No one cares what you think. Suck my
dick and stop trying to troll bomb.
Yeah, I'm a good-looking. Why don't you
come around and suck my dick if I'm that good-look?
Come around. You know how I live. You
can come and suck my big fat dick.
Yeah. How about that one? If I'm so
good-looking, come and give me a [ __ ]
You and your mom. You and your mom can
give me a lovely [ __ ]
You, your mom, and your [ __ ] dad.
Three people on my dick. How about that
one? You [ __ ] little [ __ ] How about
that one? You [ __ ] [ __ ]
What's that, bro? You know,
bro, I don't give a [ __ ] if it could be
worse or it could be better. I don't
give a flying [ __ ]
Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] if it could be
better or it could be worse. I don't
give a [ __ ] Simple. Stop comparing me
to [ __ ] other people. I'm sick of it.
Comparing, comparing, comparing. Is that
all you [ __ ] do is compare people?
All you do is compare. Stop comparing me
to people. I'm [ __ ] sick of it.
Well, I'll have to try and get attached
again, won't I? [ __ ] or sass.
Oh, you Oh, you did have a Polish
boyfriend, but you broke up. Oh,
let me guess. He cheated on you.
I've heard it all before, Greavvesy.
I've heard it all before.
You know, I've heard it all before, you know. Ah.
I've heard it all before. Yeah.
So, Grezy, when is this [ __ ] going to change?
You know, now I'm going to have to try
and get attached again.
No, no, no. Or SAS, when am I uh when am
I going to be able to get attached again?
[ __ ] You can't even get a [ __ ]
date, mate. [laughter]
You can't even get a [ __ ] date.
[ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah.
You will never get laid again in this
country. You will never get laid. You
will never get laid again here unless
you pay for it. Yep.
[ __ ] madness, bro. Madness.
Well, that's starting it. That's
so why could I get attached for
why could I get attacked before then? Oh, Sask. Huh?
Yeah. Just come Bing, bro. [ __ ]
delete the combo.
Yeah, but you said I couldn't get
attached before. I can get attached.
attached before. Why?
Yeah, you can't get nothing, mate. Can't get nothing.
You get can't even get a [ __ ] date. [laughter]
It's so sad that you got to laugh at it.
I don't give a [ __ ] if it's the same for
a lot of men. I don't give a [ __ ] if
it's the same or it's not the same. I've
tried more than anyone in the world, so
I don't give a [ __ ] if it's the same for
other men. I don't give a [ __ ] about
them. They could all get cancer and die
for all I care. So
yeah, no one's ever tried as much as me.
So, I don't give a [ __ ] about other men
better than me or worse than me. So,
there's that one. They could all die of
cancer. I don't give a [ __ ] Simple.
Sorry if that's harsh. But yeah,
I don't give a [ __ ] bro.
Yeah, there's always tomorrow.
Remember that one? You can be there,
Grezy, but I won't be.
You can go out Saturday if you like, but
I won't be there.
That's lush. You know, every time, bro,
this Indonesian guy would say, "Let's
go." I said, "You can if you like, but I
won't be there.
I won't be there." So, yeah. Yeah.
Are you sure the film exists? No. [snorts]
That was the funniest. Are you sure the film exists?
It's depressing, bro. [ __ ] depressing.
Are you sure the film has been Are you
sure the film exists? No.
But that's the That's the film.
[snorts] I I won't be trying. I'm out of
the game, bro.
Nope. I won't be trying.
This [ __ ] is boring, bro. She's being
boring now. I'm just going to block her.
It's [ __ ] depressing, isn't it?
People on Reddit say you'll meet someone.
You know, there's this guy on Reddit and
I always go back to him saying, "You
said that I'd meet someone." And then he
keeps avoiding me. I said, "I'm coming
back to you cuz you said I was going to
meet someone and stuff." Yeah. Well,
[ __ ] is absolute bullshitter.
You got to leave.
That's the only thing you can do is
leave. You will never change her. That's
that. You will never change her. Simple.
Just like that Italian. She was a [ __ ]
You remember that Italian? Or or Sask?
Where they have it in their head that
you're going to meet someone? I shall never know.
Greavvesy. Where where do they get the
impression that you're going to meet
someone? You're never going to meet anyone.
You're never going to meet anyone ever.
It's so obvious, you know. I went out on
Thursday. I didn't have any expectations
and it never annoyed me until today for
like an hour because it's just the same
old is it? It would never change. So,
it will never change ever. There's no hope.
It will never ever ever ever change. I
mean, what gives people the impression,
Greavves, that it's going to change?
It's been the same for years. Even when
I had the house, even when I had the
house, it was the same. I had the house,
it was the same. I didn't have the
house, it's the same. Subletin, no
subleting. Doesn't matter where you
live, it's always the same. Doesn't
matter how much money you have,
it would always be the same. That's
will never change. Never change. Never. Bro,
so what about USA? Is he or ask?
I still feel like going and doing that
[ __ ] up a little [ __ ] bro.
Going in and going and doing her and her
little [ __ ] [ __ ] bro. What do you think? [laughter]
just ramming a pole up a [ __ ] bro. Do
you know what I mean? Yeah.
Yeah. [ __ ] scared now, is it, bro?
You know, I was actually thinking that
all of this YouTube shit's caused
because of me.
Yep. They're against me. They're against
you. They're against Dusty Showers.
They're against you as well. and Dusty Showers. [snorts] So,
but yeah, anyways,
that's me done anyways, bro. So, yeah,
I won't be out this week. Won't be out
next week. I [snorts] don't know what
I'm doing. So, um
yeah, that's it.
that is that
you can't even find someone that's
normal. You gain nothing from going out.
They just every time you go out, it will
always be the same thing. It'll always
be the toxic same thing. So, nope.
I'll [ __ ] ram it up a little [ __ ]
bro. That's what I'll do. Ram it up a [ __ ] Yeah.
That's what I'll [ __ ] do. Yeah. So
maybe go ice skating on Saturday. Greedy
go ice skating.
I would tell him to go and suck his mom's [ __ ] [laughter]
That's what I would tell him to do. Go
and suck his mom's [ __ ]
with a capital C.
How's that one, Greasy? Is that all
right for you?
You go suck his mom's [ __ ]
bro. That USA is your her friend will
get [ __ ] up, bro. I'd [ __ ] her up and
all her cousins.
I was actually thinking about this on
the bus greavesy. Do you know how this
LT thing and this whole USA easy thing
come about? Like who is the cause of all
of this [ __ ]
Who's the cause of all of this? H
I think this is there's a load of people
that's the cause of of this YouTube
thing, isn't it? You know [snorts]
what? Because I won't allow people to
walk all over me.
Yep. I lived by myself. I worked. I went
to the gym. No changes.
Because how do women know where you
live? By conversation. These women don't
have conversations. They don't have
Um they don't have conversations with
people. They just say they've got
boyfriends. It It never comes up.
It never ever comes up.
Yeah. They say that if you work and you
live by yourself.
I mean, I work to live by myself.
No changes. Same old same old [ __ ] It
was the same old boring. You know,
that's what I called it. The same old boring. Yep. >> [snorts]
>> I was on a bus today, Grezy, thinking of
like one of these old saying taking a
baby away from its mama. [ __ ] hell.
Oh man, I was just on a bus thinking
about it because he's already found his mama.
Well, I'll just have to contact Sig
again, is it?
Or or Zask? I'm just going to have to
contact Zig. Sig. I'm sure I've got her somewhere. Sig,
what if I go back to Sig or or Zask? Who
needs anyone when you've got Sig, right? Did I
[sighs and gasps] H
yeah [ __ ] contact her in it.
What do you think is sick? Grezy,
what do you think is sick, Grezy? Huh?
I love you all. Do you remember that
Grezy? That was a good [clears throat]
saying, is it? I have the [ __ ] all of you.
Open the door to a bunch of people. I
love the [ __ ] all of you.
I love you all.
That was a good one, didn't it? Way to see. Yep.
[snorts] Because he's already found his mama.
because he's already found his mama. Can
[snorts] I do a video on this person?
I do a video on this Sir.
They're just [ __ ]
I love you all.
So, can I get back with Sig or or Zask? Huh? be Valentine's
Day Zoom. Yeah, Valentine's Day soon.
Not long. Couple of months.
Good old Valentine's.
Huh? What a day, eh? Valentine's Day.
The day to poke fun out of the people
that ain't wanted by nobody.
That's what Savvy Guy says. Valentine's
is the day to poke fun out of the the
men that aren't chosen by no one.
They ain't wanted by no one. Mad, you know.
No, [clears throat] I'll [ __ ] I'll go
I'll go beat that USA up, bro.
Her friends, bro, I was going to call
her friends bluff. I'd be like, "Oh,
yeah, really. Seven people. You was
going to get seven people on me." She
said you wouldn't. She She's like, "Oh,
you wouldn't want that kind of
negativity thinking, bro. I would shoot
every single one of you, bro. It's not
even a joke. It's not even a [ __ ]
joke, bro. You think I'm dumb enough?
Yeah. To to put myself in that situation
where four where seven people are going
to know where I am, bro.
What's that all over? Or or Zask? H.
But is it really worth someone getting
killed over, bro? Mad. Mad. [laughter]
Yeah, that's mad.
you know. [laughter]
Yeah, but it's not worth getting killed
over though, is it? I wouldn't be
getting killed, bro.
Remember, Greavvesy. Remember, Grevy,
it's me or them.
That's that is it, bro. It's me or them.
Do you know what that means, Grezy?
You know, it's me or them. >> [snorts] [laughter]
>> It's me or them, mate. Yeah. [laughter] [ __ ] hell.
It's not funny though, is it?
I blame LT for all of this.
Who do you blame Greavvesy? your LT
for all of the USA thing of that. I
didn't cause any of it. None.
Yeah. Laney was saying it would escalate. [snorts] Yeah.
Yeah. But the thing is what made me
laugh, bro, is like it's the same
website you can watch Chucky on. That's
[ __ ] [laughter] mad.
Like Tom and Jerry, mate. Like you'll be
watching Tom and Jerry. Yeah. And then
bam, heater belly uploads in the airport. [laughter]
That's why it's dangerous, bro. So you
think this whole YouTube thing is funny,
but it isn't. You know, [laughter]
you know. Yeah.
I'm sure that will put a lot of people
off everyone into cold approach, isn't it? Oh, [laughter]
I'm sure that will put a few people off
of everone to approach. [clears throat]
Yeah, I remember I used to message L2
like every morning. I said, "This
[ __ ] Syrian [ __ ] is pissing me off.
This [ __ ] Syrian cunt." Yeah, this
[ __ ] Syrian gun, mate.
He didn't believe me until I put the booking up. [laughter]
I need to go piss. [laughter]
Madness, bro. [ __ ] madness. Oh,
I'm with my little nestles.
So, you sure that's definitely my mama
or or Zask? [gasps] >> [snorts]
>> You sure? >> [snorts] >> Mad
people on Reddit say go to bars. Grezy
Shout out women in bars.
Do you remember John from years ago that
went out approaching with me once? Oh, Zask.
Do you remember that John from Turkey?
We're talking uh years ago, bro.
I don't know if you remember. >> [snorts] >> Mad.
My beard's long now. Look,
it's getting itchy here.
I've had a [ __ ] enough of it. Me,
I've had a bloody enough of it.
Being [snorts] led on enough.
They aren't all like that. >> [snorts]
>> Same old heat. More
Do you know where Maine is, Grezy? Do
you know where Maine is? The place Maine.
How do you know? people.
Is it Is it a power thing with them?
I think it's a power thing with them.
I think it is me.
I'm [snorts] [ __ ] horny as well, bro.
I'm [ __ ] horny as [ __ ]
It's annoying, isn't it?
It will never change. Never change. Never. [snorts]
I don't know. Let's start up.
They're [ __ ] [ __ ] mate.
[sighs and gasps] [laughter] Pekka.
You call it a Pekka. Yep.
[ __ ] Pekka have vitamins though. Greasy, huh?
What this bro? Nope.
I'd give that to Grezy. Yep.
I think Grezy likes USA. Is he?
Do you like her?
Do you like USA? Is he Grezy?
She your mama. >> [snorts]
>> I don't know. I think you just like her.
person says they're craving sex. Greasy.
Yeah. Fat Lou.
Nope. I'm making a cup of [ __ ] in a
minute. Greasy, if you must know.
Look, I'm making a cup of tea.
Do you want USA? Is he greasy?
Does he make your Pekka hard? Crazy. Yeah.
Yeah. Anything I should do on Saturday,
Grey, you got any ideas for me? Yeah.
No, I'm not going out, bro. I'm not going out.
I'm not going out drinking. I'm not
doing any content.
That's me done, bro. Nah,
women are all the same.
There's no point.
No, I'm not going out, bro. Nope.
I will not be going out.
It's not a bad thing, is it? Greasy to
not go out.
No content. No more content. Yep. Yeah. No.
Why am I going to go out doing content
wasting time, wasting money? Greasy,
it's not worth it.
No, it's not worth it.
they proven to be the same time and time
and time and time and time and time again.
Time and time and time and time again,
they prove they're the same. So obvious. Yeah. Yep.
So, when is this [ __ ] going to change anyways?
Greasy. When is this [ __ ] going to change? Huh?
When is it going to change, Greavves?
I've had enough of this [ __ ] you know.
It's going to change. It's going to
when your toxic negative attitude changes. I mean,
my attitude is the way it is because of
my experiences. I mean, I literally just
told you what happened. I literally got
led on again.
So, I'm not sure what you want my
attitude to to be.
I mean, I've been led on yet again, you
know? So, I I don't know what what my
attitude is supposed to be. It's the
same [ __ ] with these [ __ ] every single [ __ ] time.
Yeah. Your attitude will change when
your experience is [ __ ] changes. madness, bro.
Yeah, that's what he says. He's a [ __ ] idiot.
Really? Why not?
He's a [ __ ] idiot, bro.
That doesn't make sense. So, what he's
saying that is then people are just
negative for no reason. That's why I
always say to people that try and say,
"Oh, it's mindset and stuff." I turn
around and say, "Oh, really? So, what
are you ball negative then? Are you just
negative for no reason?" That makes
sense. Yeah. that someone's just
negative for the sake of it. No, you'd
obviously be negative because you've had negative experiences. Well, well,
my logic is that I have gone out trying
to find women and they all seem to be the same.
I mean I mean I've given people the more
than enough times the benefit of the
doubt to prove that they're different
and they all prove that they're full of
[ __ ] that can only lead people on. So I mean it's Yeah.
So he he tries to compare people but
that that's not an argument. Comparing
you to other people is not an argument.
That's not an argument though.
You know, society is nothing to do with
you. You've got your own experiences. So
why would you why would you care about
society? Society is not your
experiences. That's what you should turn
around and say to him then. Then you
should turn around and say to him that
society is not your experiences.
That's what you should turn around and
say to him that you're not going to have
society's experiences. that society has
got nothing to do with you and what
you've gone through. That's what you
should turn around and [ __ ] say to him. So yep. What an idiot. Madness.
just don't understand the leading on,
bro. That's the [ __ ] I don't understand.
That's what I don't understand. Um,
Grezy. Yeah. Like, there's one thing,
right? This is what I don't understand.
Right. There's one thing, not being
interested in relationships or not
wanting to go on dates or whatever. But
then there's leading people on. Am I
right in saying that?
or playing games and stuff. So,
am I right in saying that, bro?
You know what I mean, bro?
My belly is rumbling even though I'm not
hungry for some reason.
I can't go see cuz I need to do this video. Anyways, Yep.
I don't think Joseph Ferrar has ever been back.
Good old Joseph for
Do you think we
do? Do you think Joseph Far is ever
going to come back?
So, you know that Ricky Millington
account, Greasy, is it a real person
behind the account?
Would you say it's a real person behind
the account or no?
that YouTube account.
That YouTube account, Ricky Millington.
Is it someone real behind it? Like, is
it an actual person?
Yeah. So, who do you think it is then?
Like some old man or what?
Some old man maybe. >> [snorts]
>> Yeah, maybe it's some old man in it.
I'm fed up, mate. Absolutely fed up. Fed up.
What do you think of that?
We usually being fed up.
Yeah, I'll probably just [clears throat]
watch some porn now. Anyways,
make a tea and then do this video.
What a life, eh? What a life we live. Yeah. Yeah,
I'm going to come back in a bit.