Yo yo yo.
myself a cup of thumb. Yep.
making a clapper camp
need to figure out what I'm doing past
couple of days.
obviously was going out
absolutely [ __ ] that
all the bloody say
what's talking to me without all the bloody saint
[ __ ] hell are you? You [ __ ]
virgin. Can you
[ __ ] are you bloody virgin? Oh, the virgin. bad it
won't be bothered to shower. It's too cold.
I like that.
Hey, [ __ ] you [ __ ] virgin.
You [ __ ] virgin.
I was just watching some porn. Yeah. [snorts]
There's no life here, is it? [snorts] Yeah. Whoa.
Yeah, I got a cup of [ __ ] I was
watching this porno grievy
and um it says it's from the 70s
but it was the video was released in 2012.
Do you think I look the same as I do now
as I did in 2012?
You think I look the same or no? Huh?
What do you think, Grezy? Do I look the
same now as I did back then?
That's [ __ ] mad, isn't it?
Yeah. This guy was getting a [ __ ] Greasy. Yep.
Yeah. How comes this guy in porn can get
a [ __ ] Grezy? It's not fair.
How do these people get [ __ ]
How would this How is this guy getting a [ __ ] Grezy. Huh?
in the industry or something.
That's not fair.
Where is it? It's not fair, is it? Why? a bacon.
You need to stop using that word. It
sounds ridiculous calling someone a
bacon. It's the most stupidest [ __ ] I've
ever heard in my life. Really is. Yep.
Sorry, I was just watching porn. Bob.
Yeah, man. These guys in porn get [ __ ]
It's not fair, is it?
That's not fair. People in
Yeah, this was like from the 70s.
They're all [ __ ] old now. Mad.
Your dog don't count.
Your dog don't count, bro.
Your dog giving you a [ __ ] don't count. Bad.
10 out of 10. Doubt it. Another fantasyist.
Hello. Fun is this.
It must be horrible getting old.
Yeah, sure it is.
Sure it is, mate.
Yeah, man. It hurts me that you sit on
YouTube all day with no life calling
someone a bacon. You got me, bro. I
know. I wish I had your life.
You got me, bro. Sat on YouTube all day,
every day. Cuz you ain't got a life.
You got me, bro. I wish I had your life.
Damn, you saw right through me, bro.
You already know the answer. Stop asking
questions you already know the answer
to. Yeah, I wish I had your life, bro.
You're all right, man. I know. Sat on
YouTube being a fantasist, calling
people bacons. Who the [ __ ] uses that?
Who the [ __ ] call someone a bacon?
That's You can't even take that. I
wouldn't even take them serious. [ __ ]
bacon. What the [ __ ] bro? madness.
You don't need to feel sorry for me,
bro. You need to feel sorry for yourself.
Life sat on YouTube, can't get off it.
No money, no life. You need to feel
sorry for yourself, bro. You're living
your worst life.
I've done more than you've done. I've
done more in two years than you've done
in your whole life. Please don't feel
sorry for me, bro. Feel bad for yourself.
10 out of 10 misses my ass. Yet you on
YouTube talking to me. Fantasist,
bro. You feel sorry for yourself, bro.
That's your life.
I have the You have the worst life out
of anyone I've ever known.
Try looking in the mirror, baby.
Have you Have Have you tried looking in a mirror?
No. No. No. Definitely look in the
mirror, bro. Look in the mirror. Your
life's worse than anyone else's.
No. No. No. Look in the mirror, bro. [laughter]
Look in the mirror. I can leave the
house. I've got more money than you.
Trust me. I've not got a worse life than
you, mate. Trust me. You are living your
worst life. Trust me, mate.
That's you sat on YouTube ain't even got
a [snorts] [ __ ] life.
You live in a one bed with your mom,
bro. You're in your 40s and you're a
virgin and you got no money and you got
no life but YouTube. Talk about tragic,
brother. You're in your 40s and you and
you ain't got no life but YouTube. Let's
not talk about tragic. And and I've seen
what you people have done on here as
well, bro. in your 40s and you can't get
off of YouTube.
In your 40s, please, bro.
In your 40s on on YouTube, no life, and
you're talking about me living with my
mom. Please stop it, bro.
Anyways, see you later, [ __ ] [clears throat]
See you later, [ __ ]
>> [clears throat] >> Yeah. Yep. about Madness, bro.
No, I'm doing absolutely nothing.
I'm just probably going to stay in bed
to be fair.
Yeah, it's such a depressing life in England, bro.
I really need to book these flights
soon, bro. For real. For real.
Once I get this phone, I think 100%,
bro. It's never going to change in this
country. It's so obvious. It's It's no
way to [ __ ] live.
England's no way to live, bro. Trust me,
it really, really isn't.
It's depressing as [ __ ] Yeah.
But no, I'm not doing no football bets.
I'm just doing Yeah. nothing. [sighs]
So that's that.
probably watch some WWE or something
maybe. That's about it.
Depressing life here, bro. It is a
depressing life here in England.
Women are [ __ ] People are [ __ ] Weather
[ __ ] Government [ __ ]
Depressing, bro. It's [ __ ] depressing
in this country. Yeah,
they're literally all the same. These
women, is it?
These women are literally all the
[ __ ] same. Sad, bro. It's sad.
Yeah, it's a sad sad sad country. Oh yeah. >> [gasps]
>> Oh, banned again on Reddit. What's the
[ __ ] point? Just ban people to feel
powerful. It's [ __ ] pointless, is it, bro?
They ban people to feel powerful. It's
sad, bro. It's [ __ ] proper sad.
They need that power.
They live for it.
That's what gets them out of bed. Well,
saying that, they probably don't even
get out of bed to be fair.
Yeah. I ban loads of people on here that
self project cuz I don't want spam and
repeating people on my channel.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I don't live to ban people.
I ban people for spamming and self
projecting. What am I going to do? Leave
them on my channel. I don't ban people
for having a different opinion. Big difference.
Nice try, though. I have to say, bro,
nice try. You thought you had me with
that one, but you don't, mate. Sorry. You don't. >> [snorts] >> Yeah.
Yeah. [clears throat] I'm not doing any bets.
I'm not drinking either.
It's sad. Like if you stay here, you got
to put up with this [ __ ] It's
[ __ ] sad, bro. Really, really, really sad. Nope. Definitely not.
But guess what? I'm banning you. I'll
see you later.
Sorry, but I was watching porn. Yeah.
Yeah. I just saying how [ __ ] up it is
in this country, bro.
It's a sad, depressing country here.
Here in England, bro. Sad sad.
I'm leaving, bro. I'm leaving.
I'm going to Thailand, bro. I'm leaving.
It's depressing, bro. It's depressing
this country, bro. It really, really is.
So depressing, man.
It's bad, isn't it? Yeah.
Well, I'm not doing anything this week, bro. Yeah.
It would never change, would it? It's so
toxic and depressing, bro. [ __ ] that.
Doing that [ __ ] again. [ __ ] that. Yeah.
Yep. It's so depressing, bro.
Nah, I'm not going hard again in this
country. I'm leaving, bro.
I've got nothing left to prove, bro.
I've got nothing left to prove. It's
never going to change.
So that's that.
There's nothing to go out for, bro. What
point are we proving? It's always going
to be the same here. So
just get the phone and these flights and leave. Yeah.
obviously he's going, bro. He's already booked it.
What I need to [ __ ] do, bro. How many
times you going to keep going out and
dealing with this [ __ ] you know,
[ __ ] that, man. Absolutely [ __ ] that.
I need a haircut, bro. Jeez.
How comes these guys in porn get
[ __ ] Steven Howard, I was watching some porn.
No, not even, bro. There's all different
kinds of people on there. Some of them
are fat old men.
Some of them are fat old men.
somewhere. Fat old me, bro.
It's bad, is it, Yeah. So yeah,
I mean that [ __ ] Ed Matthews guy.
Yeah, he gets rejected. So if he gets
rejected, what chance does a normal person have?
That's the way I see it, Greavvesy. I
think that's kind of true, isn't it?
It's someone like him. Yeah.
Who's got like he's like a celebrity,
right? He's kind of like a celebrity,
And like people know he is and he's
doing he's having to put up with his
[ __ ] Then could you imagine a normal person?
They have no chance.
And all these other people in
relationships got lucky or met through
work or met before [ __ ] Tik Tok and
[ __ ] before you want to bring them people up. Yeah.
Yeah. I was just watching this vintage porn grievy.
It's mad, isn't it? Madness. [clears throat]
How do these people in porn get
[ __ ] waves there.
>> Huh? It's not fair, is it?
Do you watch porn, Grezy? Mhm.
You watch porn, don't you, Grezy?
>> [clears throat]
>> Yeah, I was watching this porn all night, bro.
So, how could I get a [ __ ] like them, Grezy?
How could I get a [ __ ] like them?
It's not fairly
I mean how how can you get a [ __ ] you know
I don't think you can in it
can I link you to porno I was watching Greavvesy
I'm going to link you the porno.
Can I link you this porno I was watching?
It's really safe. Why not?
So you very rarely watch porn. So you do
watch it then?
So you reckon that will work?
Yeah, but only fans isn't going to work.
Only fans wouldn't work, bro.
Well, people are just going to have sex with Hey. Yeah, right.
How long will it take? Yeah, true.
Well, what if I go and approach women,
Greavesy? What about if I approach in
the clubs and bars? Huh?
I said I need to start working, but I don't really.
I'm all right with money and stuff.
What in a bar? What in a bar in a club?
What in a ball and a or a club?
I don't think it's going to work, bro.
Yeah, but it's not going to work.
They're not interested.
Yeah, but they're not interested.
And then people are going to use as an
excuse. Oh, you're moving too fast. You
can't win, Greavesy. You generally can't win.
You can't win, unfortunately.
Cuz if you do that, people are going to
be like, "Oh,
uh, well, you can't just say you want to
have sex with someone." So
It's not going to work, bro. We're [ __ ]
Greasy. We're [ __ ] up. End of story.
We're never going to meet anyone.
We're all [ __ ] So
it's sad, isn't it?
I want to be part of vintage porn.
Nope. No one for us.
But what's worst?
But what's the worst? The worst thing is
is I've tried more than both of you
combined and I still don't I still can't find anyone.
No one's bloody interested.
I'm going to link you this porno anyways.
That is lovely, bro.
I'm going to link you it. Yeah,
Stephen Howard, if I link it, can you
watch it? This porn.
Can you watch this porn? No, I'm going
to link it.
This is the kind of [ __ ] that I want.
I want you to watch it.
Look, it's this. Look.
Yeah, I don't give a [ __ ] to be honest.
It's just that person pissed me off earlier.
Of course I can cope. It's never going
to change. Why would I be able to cope?
It will never change. So,
this is the porn I was watching.
It was [ __ ] hot.
Now, what year do you think that was filmed in?
What? What year would you actually say
that was filmed in? Like the actual year? 70s maybe?
Yeah, I think 70s.
Yeah, it's a good porno, man.
You should watch it.
It's a good porno. Greasy,
what would you say? The se 70s maybe.
I wasn't even born.
I bet it was got to be 70s in it, Grez. You know,
some good old Italian vintage porn.
Good old Italian vintage porn. Eh.
He got a [ __ ] Lucky bastard.
Yeah, he got a nice [ __ ] Greavvesy.
No, it's not animated. It's real.
I can't believe I wasn't even born then. Grievy. Oh,
I searched up the guy's name and he's
[ __ ] some old man now. Greavvesy,
he's some [snorts] fat old man.
Grey, why is he fat and old now? I
looked his name up.
Now he's a fat old man.
Yeah, he's a fat old man, bro.
Is that weird?
Do you think
sad watching porn?
It's so sad, Bob, that I'll never be
able to have sex or get a [ __ ] ever
again. Sad, isn't it? Sad life.
Sad life, eh?
But people on Reddit say people on
Reddit say you people on Reddit say
you'll meet someone. No. What? Yeah.
Yeah. That's got to be the magical
place, isn't it, Bob?
All the women there won't say they've
got boyfriends, will they? Nah.
Nah. Not Not in the festival. Everywhere
else they'll they'll pretend they got
boyfriends and play games, but if you go
to a vest a festival, Nah.
Yeah, right. They're all the [ __ ]
same everywhere, bro.
They're all the same everywhere. Mad.
So I was watching that porno again. Yeah. [laughter]
Yeah. That porno was good, man. That
porno was good.
It's a good pull now.
I've already tried it, you idiot.
I've already done a video of me approach
approaching on a train. Yeah.
I don't think Greavesy can live without
sex. Can you Grezy?
I can't believe Grevy watches porn.
I was just watching this porno patty.
It's so addicting porn, man.
They get [ __ ] and stuff. Sad.
You can't get anything. No one's
interested in this country, Paddyy. Really?
Yeah. I watch vintage porn
like the 1970s, 1980s porn.
These guys are lucky, man. Yeah. Heat.
No, she was being a [ __ ]
No, she wasn't. She was being a [ __ ]
She's a [ __ ] Nah,
she was just being a [ __ ] like they all
[ __ ] in this country. [ __ ] him. Uh,
what's weird about these vintages is
that they're all old now, Paddyy.
They're all [ __ ] old. >> [snorts]
>> It's not fair.
But yeah, that's me anyways.
That's me done approaching Paddyy.
That's me done, bro.
As the final straw, matey.
I'm done trying now, bro. Yep.
It's so toxic whenever you go out and you try.
These women are all the same, bro.
You go out time and time again giving
these women the benefit of the doubt and
they always prove they're the him.
They always prove that they're all the
same full of [ __ ] No,
I think they're all the same, Paddyy.
These women are all the same.
It's obvious, isn't it? Yeah. Anyways, I'm gone.