Hello matey.
I'm back. Got some lush chicken. Yeah.
Hope you like my football bet.
Anyone's welcome to get in on it. You
look I know you like your little
copycats. Little copycats.
>> Yeah. I know you little copycats are
like little copycat. You little copy.
Copycat. Little copycats.
I saw a dog on the bus and I couldn't
stop saying copycat. It's stuck in my
head. You know,
I don't like copycats.
But you know, you you're more than
welcome to cop copy my bet if you want, captain. Yeah,
there we go, man. [ __ ] horrible out
there. Just come back.
Lovely little treble, eh? Yeah.
50 to two. What was it? 16 15 215. Yeah, man. Uhuh.
That is lovely.
Lovely little bet. Oh gosh.
Add some chicken. Some chicken and chops. Yep.
Chicken and chops. Chicken and chops.
Call that woman a coward, by the way.
They are cowards.
They are cowards, man. [ __ ] cowards.
Toxic. That's what they are.
So, I just be chilling today with this football bat.
Oh, you remember that from the bodybuilding form? Yeah.
What? That instant loser account.
Yep. Ah, you remember? E, [laughter]
that's so old.
That's so old. I just done a football
bet. I done a treble 50 pound on a
treble. It returns 215.
Not a bad little return, is it?
Yeah, on three teams this time. So,
we'll see in it.
Probably won't connect it, bro.
It was so annoying yesterday, bro.
Arguing with them people.
People constantly dismissing your
struggles is horrible, bro.
constantly dismissing your struggles.
[ __ ] hell, that's annoying, bro. That
is very annoying. Yeah. Um, yeah.
If the football bet wins, I might go out
for a mill,
but I won't be drinking or doing any approaches. Obviously, it's toxic.
Why are you going to go out, lad?
You know what? What's the point of going
out? No one's interested.
You can't meet people that are mature in
their head. You can't meet normal
people. So, there's no point going out
trying to speak to them because they're
not normal people.
And I'm not putting myself through that
[ __ ] bro. So, that's that end story.
I'm not using escorts and I'm not
approaching. End of story. Simple. So, that's that.
Yeah, like we're arguing with them, bro.
And it's like I put videos out there. I
put videos out there. I put
conversations out there and they just
dismiss it. So, [ __ ] them, bro. Is it? Yeah,
pretty much. Yeah,
I know you're mocking me, but it's the truth.
It's true, though.
You take the piss out of it. But it's
true. Once you meet one, you have met
them all. It's the truth though.
It is the truth. They are literally all
the same. So
little copycat. If you don't find chemo
co attractive, you're gay. Gay. Gay. You little copycat.
you little copycat. I couldn't stop
saying that on the bus, you know, you
little copycat. And this dog kept coming
up to me, bro, and resting his head on
me. This skinny black dog, you little copycat.
You little copycat.
What if you like black a bony woman with big boobs?
What about that?
So, if you don't find Cheryl Cobb
attractive, but you're into black women,
would you still be gay? What if you was
into blonde women with big boobs, would
you still be gay? I'm not entirely sure
if that's what being gay means, but you
know, you learn something new every day.
So, you go up to one of your parents and
you say, "I've got to come out. I've got
to come out as gay. I didn't have
breakfast. I had chicken and chips like
30 minutes ago. the chicken shop.
So, I need to come out as gay. Okay. So,
how long have you been feeling like this
for? I just don't find shovel co attractive.
Uh, well, is is there any anything more?
Like, do you like boys? No, not really.
Uh, I just don't find shovel co attractive.
Imagine imagine coming out as gay and
saying that. Bro, you're a little cop. Little copycat.
>> I throw you. [ __ ] throw you, little
copycat. Did you see my football bet?
Yeah, that is copying. That's copying
the crowd. What if you liked black women
or blonde women with freckles?
Would you still be gay?
No. Did you Would you still be [ __ ] gay, mate?
Does that automatically mean you like dick then? Interesting.
I've never been with a man before, but
apparently I'm gay. News to me.
I just want to tickle him, you know,
like a little cat,
you know, someone that feels the need to
copy. It's scary being new, isn't it?
You know, in college, it's it's quite
scary being new. So, I can see why you
wanted to fit in with the crowd. Yep.
Yeah. It is it's quite scary being new,
isn't it? New to a college or new to a school
that you have to make copycat statements.
Copycat. It's quite scary, isn't it? Yep.
I I'm not entirely sure that's what
being gay means though, Grezy. You know,
so it's okay for women to have types,
but we can't have types. Greavvesy. H strange. So,
it's okay for women to have types,
but we can't have types because we're
we're then gay, apparently. Really?
Really, bro? Like I was saying to this
dude right here, what if you like black
women with big with bigger bony boobs?
What if you like bigger bony women? What
if you like record women with with
brunette hair? What? Would Would you
still be gay? Would you still be [ __ ]
gay? [ __ ] copycat. [ __ ] copycat.
You know what? I'm going to get that
form up um later, Greavvesy. And I'm
going to show you
And I'm going to show you where these women
pretended that they uh
I'm going to show you where they all
call each other gay.
They said, "Are you gay, bro?" You know,
like call you gay. You gay? You gay,
mate? Gay. Gay. Gay. Gay. Homosexual,
mate. [ __ ] hell.
You're not even attractive.
Uh yeah, she was just average.
My Pekka was so big it barely fitted in
her mouth. It barely fit in her mouth, bro.
Yeah. Well, it did fit in her mouth. It
fitted halfway in her mouth. Greavvesy. Yeah. Halfway.
Did you like that debate yesterday, Grezy?
Did you like that debate, eh?
What do you think of my football bet? I
got a treble both teams to score. I got
Darlington versus Spymore, South Hawk
versus Kitty Minister, and Snow versus Worvin.
No, she didn't owe me last night.
No, she [ __ ] did not.
She didn't She didn't owe me at all.
What does cooking hard mean?
If this football bet wins, I'm just
going to buy the phone with that. I'm
buying the phone anyways. But yeah, I
won't be going out. So,
not until mid December now, I think.
Yeah, I was owning them, bro. Most
people's on their side, though. But
that's just cuz they're ass lickers.
Sarah didn't own me at all. But no more
no more debates. No more debates.
Cuz I've got my experiences and that's
that. So, I don't I don't want to be
told different. I want to be shown
I want to be shown different. And women
can't show you different. So, there's no
point in the whole debate. We can argue
and disagree until we're blue in the
face, but it's not going to change anything.
What I, you know, the thing I found
though funny yesterday, bro, is how many
excuses they were making for them.
Like, it's so it's like they don't want
to blame them for anything. They're so like
scared. It's like it's so they're so
scared to be offended that they won't
even admit someone's led you on. Like
that that conversation took all night, bro.
And then they just continuously make
excuses for them. And it's not because
they're right. It's because they're a
woman. That's what it is. And that and
you know it. And you [ __ ] know it, bro. So
they will make any single excuse just to
victimize them when they're not even
victimizing themselves. What the [ __ ] bro?
They are leading you on. They know
exactly what they're doing and they
don't change their mind. I saw a lot of
people grievously saying, "Oh, they
changed their mind. They changed their
mind. They changed their mind." It's
[ __ ] It's another excuse.
You know, people don't just change their
mind with people they haven't met.
And then he asked me this question
about, oh, what do I mean by like they
give up on the first sign of
disappointment? What I mean by that is
like greasy. Like say you go on a date
with someone and
the vibe's not there straight away. Like
straight away, they'll be like, "Nope,
don't want to pursue it." Instead of
giving it a bit more time to see, you
know, where things go, you can actually
grow to like people as well. And I know
this from experience. But they at the
first sign of any disappointment, minor
disappointment, they will just abandon
the whole thing. That's what I meant.
But he wouldn't let me finish. He's [ __ ] rude.
And then that kitty doesn't even let you uh
doesn't even let you um message her. She
doesn't even let you message her. Yep. Mad. So yeah,
if the if the weather was better, I
might have went out drinking today if
the weather was better. But
I need to save money, bro. I need to
leave. So I need to put that first, you know. So,
I done this 50 pound football bet
returns 215. I don't know why the odds
were so [ __ ] today. I'm hoping that wins,
but if it win, if it doesn't, you only
lose 50 in it. So, so yeah,
I don't know why they make excuses for them.
leading people on.
I don't know why they make excuses. Oh,
they didn't do it on purpose. They
changed their mind. It's [ __ ]
You know, I think more needs to be said
about this, you know. I might start up
my own podcast and ask people why they do it,
why they [ __ ] my struggles and [ __ ] I I
just want to know why they continuously
make up excuses for these toxic women.
I think that's I think that's a fair
point in it, Grezy. You know,
I think we need to get to the bottom of
it, you know.
They message you every day
keeping you on a piece of string, but
they're not leading you on. Literally,
bro, most of the numbers that you get
that reply lead you on.
Lead you on. They lead you on. They're
not even honest. You know, the thing is
with these women, Grezy, is they're
never even honest. That's the thing
about it. They never say, "Oh, um,
straight away or whatever because then
you'd have no argument. Then they would
be right." You know, Grievy, if these
women were saying straight away this,
that, and the other or like I said
within the third message or, you know,
within the third message, then you would
lose. But they don't. So that's how I
know I'm right.
you know, you know that you're right
then because if they, like I said, if
they don't reply or they reply and
honest, then we can't really argue against it.
And it's not that I always think I'm
right. It's I'm right about what I'm
saying because I wouldn't be saying it
if I didn't think I was right. Simple. I
wouldn't say it if I didn't believe it.
You know what I mean, bro?
And they couldn't answer me when they
said when they said, "Oh, they say they
want a nice guy in that grievy, but then
when they come across somebody that's
genuine or whatever, when they come
across somebody that's genuine, they're
not interested. Not that I care, but as
an example, I don't, you know, I I you
know what I'm saying? So, explain that
one then by their own words. Explain
that one. It's [ __ ]
Why am I the only one failing to get
dates? Not answering that
stupid question. Answered it before. I'm
not getting into it again.
But I want to get into the why they keep
making excuses for women.
I would love to know why they keep doing it. Greasy.
I actually want the answer why they keep doing it.
Oh, does he? Good for him. I I'll buy
him a silver medal when I can, bro. Give
me his address. So, give him a silver
medal. Good for him. Now, Grey, how many
approaching videos have I have I put up
there? How many messages have I put up Anyone remember?
I put them up there for a reason. When I
when I put these videos up there, I put
them up there for a reason. You You
you. Um, I put these videos up for a
reason and I had every right to. So, yeah,
they just need to stop victimizing women.
I They really really need to stop doing
it. They're not innocent.
The only thing that I take back about
the things I've said, Greavves, is about
kids and children because kids and
children are innocent. Like babies and
children, they're innocent, right? They
are innocent. No, women are not
innocent. They are toxic. They are
[ __ ] I will say it until I'm blue
in the face. Children are innocent.
Uh, did you really? What What land was
that? Was that Planet Mars or was that Laand?
Uh, did you really? From a from a pub in
In a pub.
in a pub.
I don't believe you, bro.
I don't believe you. An actual pub.
I don't know. I don't believe you.
So, yeah, I'm going to I might do a podcast.
Why does it seem impossible to you?
because I've been with more women than
you have and I've met more women than
you have and it's not as easy as you're
[ __ ] making it out. Uh because I've
got more life experience than you do
when it comes to women.
So I know you're talking [ __ ] Yeah.
They say one thing on the internet.
I 100% have been with more women than
you. I 110% have. again. You're talking
to me, bro. You're I 100% have met more
women than you. And I've met more women
than every single person that I was
speaking to yesterday,
mate. I was getting over three grand a
month traveling, constantly meeting people.
I've met more women than you have. Trust
me. So, trust me, I have, you know.
and then they were trying to say that,
"Oh, we didn't defend women. We're
saying that some women are [ __ ] and
some men are cunts." But you're not,
though, because you spent all day trying
to defend that woman.
Not already. Answer this question again.
Bomb. I'm not answering your self-proing
comments again. Self-p projector, go
away. I'm not answering your self-proing
comments. Right, we're ignoring you now. Anyways,
right. Whatever. Now, do you know what I
I meant about you know, you remember
what I said to you, Greasy, about people
dismissing people's struggles, right? Do
you remember how I keep going on about
people dismissing people's struggles?
Now, I have put approaching videos up
and I've put messages up. If you can't
be bothered to watch them, that's your
problem. Simple. I'm not going to keep
repeating myself. One ear and outing out
the other with these retards. You show
them black and white evidence of what
women do and then they still come on
talking [ __ ] Yeah, I'm not explaining
myself. [ __ ] off. Absolutely [ __ ] off.
No, the thing is Siri, I was actually
thinking, you know, of of doing an hour
video. You know what you were saying
about like record your whole night out
or half of it? I was actually thinking
about that the other day with the power
battery. You remember what you were
saying? all of the approaches that you
do record like your whole night out and
I've got a good phone and I was thinking
of doing it but then I thought there was
no point doing it. Um, Grezy
and do you know why there's no point doing that
and it's a good idea but there's no
point doing that.
Yeah, I could delete stuff. I could do
it, but there's no point in doing it on
this channel anyways.
And do you know why there's no point of doing it?
But we got a white knight here, people.
Yeah, you keep you Maybe in your dreams
you do, but not in real life. Not maybe
in your dreams you do.
So there's no point doing it because
people are just going to dismiss your
struggles. So there's no point even
doing it because people are just going
to ignore it and resort to licking
women's asses again. So it's a waste of
everyone's time. It's a waste of my
time. It's a waste of the phone
memories. They're just going to resort
to victimizing women again. So there's
there's no point. There's literally it's
a waste of everyone's time. There's no
point doing something like that because
they're just going to keep defending
women. So there's no point.
But there's no point though because
people are just going to dismiss it.
You don't get women. You're a virgin.
Yeah. You don't get dates easily. You're
still a virgin. I can tell. I've got
more life experience than a lot of
people in this community. And no one's
jealous of a little virgin like you. See
what I mean? But what I'm saying is they
will continuously keep dismissing it. Am
I lying, Grezy?
I could literally do a 4hour video of
women being [ __ ] and they'll be like,
"Nope, nope, nope. They'll nod their
head like a like a dog. Nope. Nope.
Nope. Personality. You can't get through
to these people. It's a waste of
everyone's time. Even when you up the
notch, bro, and you think, "Okay, well,
we're arguing now. We're just going back
and forth. Let's show evidence." Even
when you show them evidence, they still
point blank say, "Nope, nope, nope. It's
not women that are the problem." Nope.
Nope. Nope. Nope. Nope.
Yeah. You got three kids. Yeah. You keep
telling yourself that. Yeah. I thought
you was going.
I thought you was going,
mate. I've had more women than you would
ever have. And I I'm not a s. I'm not a
loser simp like you. I've had more women
than you will ever have. 110%.
Believe you me, I've had more women than
you will ever have, mate. I've traveled
more than you ever have. As well, I
don't lick women's asses cuz I'm not a
loser like you. If you really had all of
these women, you wouldn't be defending
them like a loser.
Yeah. I'm not so much of a loser that I
have to dismiss people's struggles and
keep licking women's asses. I'm not a
loser like you. I don't lick women's
asses to try to get them. I'm not a
loser like you.
Yeah. No, you haven't. You haven't had
more relationships than you haven't had
more women. You're still a virgin. It's
obvious. You know the people that don't
get women. The people that defend women
are people that don't get women. It's
autism. [clears throat] That's why they
defend the women. They defend them
because they don't get them. That's why
they lick their asses and defend them.
It's true. It's true. The only people
that do that are gay people and men that
don't get women. That's why they defend them.
Yeah. They don't want you either. Yeah,
I know, bro. They don't want you either.
That's why you keep defending them, bro.
That's why you keep resorting to
defending them because women don't like
you and they still won't like you. Let
me tell you something right now. Yeah.
So you don't waste your time. You can
defend women all you want and they still
will hate you. They don't like you. They
don't like you. So there's no point
defending them. They're not going to
[ __ ] you. They don't like you. They
don't like simps. So stop defending
them. They don't like you. You're
wasting your time, bro. You keep having
a go at me
licking women's asses. They don't want
you. They don't like you. They don't
want to be with you. So stop defending
women. You know, you're still a virgin
because of them and you're defending
them. If I was you, that damn. Yeah. If
I was a virgin like you, I'd be going
mad. The last thing I would be doing is
defending them. If I was a single virgin
like you in my 40s, right? If I was a
single virgin like you, I'd be going
mad. I wouldn't be defending them. No,
I'm talking about you in your 40s. Still
a virgin licking women's asses.
No, I'm talking about you, Damon.
Damian, I'm talking about you, the
virgin. I'm not talking about me. I'm
not a virgin. You don't have free kids.
You don't have three kids. You
fantasist. And you're banned now.
Bye-bye. Repeating bastard.
Yeah, exactly. Yeah, I know. Why would
someone be This is what I always say.
Yeah, I was watching Savvy Guy
yesterday. I'm going to put him up in a minute.
Why would someone be negative for no reason?
I always say to them, why would someone
be negative for no reason?
For what? So, you're just born negative
for no reason? That doesn't make a lot
of sense, does it? I'm going to I'm
going to let you listen to this,
right? I was watching this guy again.
These little white knights. These little
white knight virgins. Let's keep licking women's asses.
and soul to your loved ones
that bring magic moment.co.uk.
>> What's going on guys? Back guys with another presentation. Happy Friday.
Happy happy Friday. Um, somebody wanted
me to make a presentation calling talking about don't deny, you know,
I'm not trying to get preachy here, but um,
the world we live in, guys, is
people people are possessed by demons.
Uh people are just they just they just
got the devil in them and um people
are just not they just their hearts are
just not pure. We live in a time where
people's hearts are just not pure. Um
dirty looks from people
signifies a demon. If a person is giving
you a dirty look and you don't know why
because they got a demon in them, that's
a demon at work. that demon uh doesn't
like the light of Jesus that it sees within you.
So since that demon does not like the
light of Jesus that it sees within you,
it is going into attack mode. Most
people nowadays are just wicked and evil.
They're just wicked and evil. You got
some people who have good hearts in the
world, but uh it's very rare. And uh
it's it's good. It's best to stay away
from people. [laughter]
I had to learn that in my my 36 years of
life. It's best to stay away from people because
people can switch up on you at any time.
You know, you'll be like, "Well, I
thought we were friends. I thought we
were cool. I thought we were bros."
>> Yeah, I'm sure.
>> They'll switch up on you. I mean, for
crying out loud, your own family will
turn against you. They'll turn against
you. So, think about it. If your own
family will turn against you, anybody is
liable to turn against you. If your own
fan will turn against you, that means
you can't trust anyone, guys.
You can't trust nobody.
>> Yeah, it's it's true.
>> Trust anyone.
And I'm telling you guys that uh you got
to be very very careful when it comes to
people because people are just wicked.
Their hearts are not pure.
And the older that I get,
I'm seeing how wicked and evil people are.
And the older that I'm getting, I want
to stay away from people. I don't want
to be around people.
>> Yeah. It's good.
>> And and um you know people a lot of
people are just not rapticial.
Like I say, I don't put no
class of woman on a pedestal, no
ethnicity of women on a pedestal. Women
are superficial in general, guys.
So, you got to understand that they're
shallow. They're they're narcissistic.
Um, women are just not good people
in general. Um,
>> that's what I say. I say the same, too.
>> I think women are pretty much all the
same. They're all superficial.
They're just all the same. [laughter] And
what a lot of you guys got to understand
is that these women are not going to
change. Their standards are not going to
change. [laughter] What they're
attracted to is not going to change.
Women are just going to stay the way
that they are, guys. And there's nothing
we can do about it. There's nothing we
can do. Um,
you know, it is what it is at the end of
the day. Women are just going to be who
they going to be. And one thing I had to
come to terms and understand when it
come to sisters, and I'm pretty sure a
lot of you brothers had to come to terms
and understand this. Sisters are not rapt.
They think, you know, taps and dreads
and all of that thug stuff.
>> Oh, you know, Antman. Yeah. When he come
when he comes across a um a westernized
woman in Thailand that gives attitude,
he says, "There's nothing Asian about you."
I kind of mock that. You know, sometimes
I say that to him. There's nothing Asian
about them. He'll literally say,
"There's nothing Asian about you." Like,
he'll go on Tinder, right?
And they'll be like, "Bro, like talk
proper Westernized." And he'll be like,
"There's nothing Asian about you. [laughter]
There's nothing Asian about you." [laughter]
I almost shot my underpants the other day.
I go to waxies today. I can't let these
[ __ ] women win. Don't let these
Yeah, you've heard me say it in it. I
said, "Fuck back to where you I was
pissed, bro." Yeah, I was like, "Fuck
back to where you come from."
Do you like my football bet, bro? Do you
reckon it's going to come in?
Do you like the football bet, bro? The
treble. both teams to score. Yeah.
No, I won't be going out, bro, until um
at least December now. So,
yeah, I won't be going out, bro. No way.
I need to buy this phone as well.
How do you know it won't? It might do.
No, I'm not doing Frankie. I don't touch them machines.
They might do, bro. 50 pound. I just put
No, I'm not doing Frankie, bro. [ __ ]
off, man. The only way you can win with
gambling is a double both teams to score
or online roulette. I think that's the
only way you can win. Oh, real well,
real life roulette. But it's trying to
get into the [ __ ] place, isn't it?
If I was to put 150, I'd probably I'd
probably go into a casino. I'd probably
sneak into a casino.
I'll probably go Notting again, bro. If
I was to gamble in a casino, I'd
probably go Nottingham.
Um Oh, I'd probably Yeah, I just go for
a casino with like 100 150 and just keep
like taking the profits and that. But
what if you hit big and then you can't
cash out? It's trying to get your money
from these places.
That's the thing. It's trying to get
your money from these places, bro.
Nah, three teams is not hard on a on a
national league, bro. The National
League is a lot easier. Like league one
and League Two is hard. That is hard,
bro. But not not a national league. Not
a national league. National league is easy, bro.
No, bro. It's not. Um Yeah, but it's
trying to get your money from these
places. That's the thing.
It's trying to get your money from the places.
That's the problem trying to get your [ __ ] money.
I'm probably too I was speaking to
someone in Nottingham yesterday
actually. He's Seek some guy. Remember I
met a couple months ago? Seek
Nottingham. He's from Nottingham and
he's seek. I said to him, "Oh yeah,
you've been out." He said, "No, it's
been cold." I said, "Oh, we need to link
up on that." He didn't reply back.
No, National League is easy, bro.
National League is easy to get goals.
League one and two is hard. They're
hard, bro. You can miss four times
before getting two goals. But yeah,
Nottingham's [clears throat] good, bro.
I like Nottingham.
It's only the Midlands, isn't it?
The thing is though, bro, is um yeah,
national leagues is not hard to get
goals, bro. It's not hard to get goals.
The past few times I've gambled. I've
won. I've won doing it, bro. The past
couple of times,
they're not hard to get goals, bro. The National League,
I think I've won like Yeah. many in a
row. Many in a row, bro.
So, I think I think we got a good chance
with this three to be honest.
If I do approaches in Nottingham,
what would they say?
I need to watch some more Ed Matthews stuff.
Ed Matthews even gets rejected. Imagine that.
Ed [ __ ] Matthews, eh? Ed [ __ ] Matthews.
You know, if you went to Nottingham,
you'd probably get a snog, you know. If
you went to Nottingham,
Nottingham's good, bro. It's less
competition, in it.
I ain't been not for ages, bro. Think
the last time was not last April. The
April before that, it was April. I went
I think. Do you like the month April?
Siri, do you like the month April? Good
month, isn't it? April. I like April.
What do you think about that month? Huh?
It was actually 40. Yeah,
I touched her boobies as well and she's
the only other one that said to me, "Oh,
do you want She said, "Do you want my
number?" She's the only other one that
said, "Do you want my number?" And then
we was talking and that and then um it
was when the train strikes was going on
and we was talking in it proper like
leading me on. I said, "Oh, I'm going to
come to Nottingham again. I'm going to
come to Nottingham again."
And um I went to Nottingham, bro. And
[ __ ] she didn't show up.
I went to Nottingham and she didn't [ __ ]
Yep. Oh, bro. I was I lost my card, but
somehow What happened? I think I was
able to withdraw the money, I think.
Yeah. How the [ __ ] do you remember that?
And I went back to Nottingham and she
didn't meet me.
Yeah, same old [ __ ] It's been going on
for years now, is it?
Been going on [ __ ] years.
This football bet's coming in, you know, mate.
It's coming in, mate. is coming to [ __ ]
They always try getting out of paying
you in casinos, don't they?
S There's a private casino in
Nottingham, is it?
I tried to get into a casino in Read and
they didn't let me, bro.
Yeah, it was Reden, I think.
Yeah, it's bad, bro. bad.
but this one's a private one. Yeah,
they say you'll meet someone.
They've all got the same attitude.
Well, I'm not going Nottingham. Maybe
I'll go New Year's Eve. Maybe I'll go
Yeah, he was a snobby [ __ ] Well, he's
actually from Brighton, but yeah,
I think his friend could have beat me in
an argument. I think he's I think he was
more intelligent than me, bro, to be fair.
Yeah, you could go New Year's Eve. I'm
definitely going out of London New
Year's Eve. I don't know where I'm going
yet, but definitely going.
So, who was that Scottish guy in the
Weather Spoons from Glasgow?
Who was that? [laughter] Yeah. I don't
I don't know who that is. [laughter]
This guy's ignoring on Instagram. Yeah.
Well, I was messaging him. He didn't
reply. But as soon as I sent a picture,
he he he clicked on the message. I said, "Oi."
Yeah, I said [ __ ] oi, mate.
Yeah, Tam's my daddy from Scotland. Grezy.
Yeah, I done uh three teams both to
score. Um I put £50 on it. It returns
215. Is that okay with you, boss?
Had some lovely chicken and chips
earlier. Greavves. on the video.
I think it's going to win me.
Do you think it's going to win?
Yeah, like this guy in Red, bro, he's a
cool guy, you know? He's a cool guy. The
guy he I met him in the same bowl I met
Adam. He's actually a cool guy, man.
He's from Red.
Yeah, he's actually a cool guy, bro. He
said, "What kind of like women are you
going for?" and [ __ ] And I still need
to meet him. And that
I'm not going out today, bro. It's raining. Remember
when the Jobert family was after me? The Joebert family,
another one who defended her.
Uh, they didn't answer me um yesterday.
grievy that they say that women like
nice people are normal people, but when
women say, "Oh, you're nice, this, that,
and the other." They're not interested.
And I thought maybe being a bit of a
[ __ ] would work. But I mean, Ed
Matthews is a bit of a [ __ ] and
that don't even work.
What the [ __ ] How the [ __ ] doesn't he
get any How does he not meet anyone? What?
Ah, snap. You two said it at the same
point. Yeah. So, it probably started
like this. Um, so did you get a message
from this guy from England? Yep.
So, did you get a message from
this guy? Um, yeah, us too. Yeah.
What did you think of Scott? He was He
was a You know what? Scott agreed with
me deep down that he knew he couldn't
say anything because of his daughter.
He knew he couldn't say anything because
it was his daughter in it.
Because it's his daughter. That's why.
Isn't that right, Grezy?
I hear a little copycat. Can you hear
that little copycat?
USA is he wanted condoms at first. I
said, "I'm not wearing a condom."
You can [ __ ] off. I'm not wearing no [ __ ] condom.
What's the fun in that?
So, say you wanted to have sex without a
condom. Now, you can't have sex without a condom.
You know, if you use escorts, you have
to use condoms. But I'm not using
escorts anyways. The only fans one was
good. The only fans one was good.
But I don't know what happened. She said
that she found someone and she blocked
me or everything.
Maybe she'd met someone with money or something.
How many times did I have that Only Fans one? Yeah,
>> quite a lot in it. I liked her cuz she
was a dirty [ __ ]
I like dirty [ __ ] I didn't like the
19-year-old. She made me like clean my
dick and that before sucking it and
that. It was horrible.
That's a turnoff for me. I like someone
that's really dirty, you know.
I like someone that's really dirty.
Greasy, what about you?
Do you know I met her in O'Neal's Siri?
I met her in O'Neal. You know that um
that only fans won.
That's how I met her in the O'Neals.
You know I can't do that because of the
[ __ ] allinton virgin. You know I
can't do that mate cuz that skin plonker.
That [ __ ] skin plonker. You know
I remember that time. Yeah. When I said
oh can we do anything cuz she was being
a proper [ __ ] She was she got more
westernized as she got older. And I said
oh what if I give you £50 and then she did it.
I wonder what happened to her. She still
got my number. But yeah, I don't know.
I think if she came back and she weren't
a [ __ ] I think I'd be I would just stay
with her to be honest.
You Yo, you know what that bloody
virgin's like? You know what that skint
version's like? I probably would to be
honest. Her boobies might have got
bigger now, ain't it?
Yeah, I probably would to be honest.
Yeah, I probably would just stay with
with them if they were different.
Or it would be a case of like
say you went out and you tried, you
wouldn't be pissed off because you still
had her. So even if you wanted other
even if you wanted someone else. Yeah.
You couldn't even get pissed off because
you could just go back to her.
But obviously if you don't have anything
right now then it's not good is it?
But people on Reddit say you can get sex
whenever you want. [ __ ] hell.
They say you can get sex whenever you bloody want. Grezy,
they lie on Reddit, ain't it?
They lie on Reddit. Addy,
this woman yesterday was trying to blame
me recording as an excuse even though I
was only recording audio.
Yeah, she was with Russian in her.
Yeah, she sucked my dick good, bro.
Yeah, she used to, you know, that guy's
room I was staying in where it was my
house. She used to come out and suck my
little Willie and then we'd have a nice Chinese.
What's her name?
Her name's Katrina, but I never ever
called her that. I never ever called her
her name, which was strange. I never ever like
said her name.
Yeah, she's like 21 now. Is she like 20?
21. She got to be like 20 now. 20. She's 20. Yeah.
So the thing is is that your um
Yeah. But I never ever called her her
name. I never ever called her her name ever.
I never said her name.
And we used to drink and she used to
[ __ ] my willie in the same house as that
other tenant was. That other tenant was
a [ __ ] you know.
I can't believe she turned down free
rent to give a [ __ ] That's mad.
Yeah, she did. Yeah, she'd give it to
these black guys for free.
But she'd give it to these black guys
for free. That's mad.
And I was way better looking than these
black guys as well. Like you'd actually
hear her having sex with these black
guys, bro. It was mad cuz everyone was
in the house and that. I remember 4:00
in the morning, bro. Oh my god. It woke
everyone up. They were talking. They
weren't shouting, they were talking. And
it woke the whole house up, bro. I think
I've got a video of it somewhere.
£350 rent. What the [ __ ]
It was bad, bro. Really bad. They were
talk. They were just talking and it woke
everyone up, bro. And I said to the guys
like, "Can you hear that?" He said,
"I've already I can already hear it. I
was dead grievously." Everyone woke up.
But that's just somebody that just likes
the black sausage in it.
They're like the black sausage.
They were always black as well.
I think they were three different men. So
I think I heard them have sets as well. Yeah.
I said you're not getting your 150 back,
mate. I messaged her the other day. She didn't reply.
Yeah, of course she wouldn't.
Who that blinking virgin?
Oh, that blinking virgin. [snorts] Yeah.
Yeah. I said you can get them all you
want, mate. No one gives a [ __ ] You can
get them all you want.
But is someone really going to do that?
Her boyfriend. Yeah,
they're not going to do that over 150
pound, bro. Are they
might go to waxies today?
Might go to waxies. No, I'm not doing
that. Cuz what happens is you go out, it
rains, and no one goes out.
Yeah. I can't believe I've not had a
date since April.
I [snorts] can't believe it.
But people on Reddit say you get sex. Wow.
I'm still waiting to meet someone
through friends. You know, I've got some
friends, but I never meet anyone through them.
People on Reddit say you meet people
through your mates and stuff.
You remember go to the pub. It's mad.
Antman said, "Why do why do all of these
women go out just to say they've got boyfriends?"
You think he's lying, Siri?
Just to say that they've got boyfriends. Listen,
I don't know why they go out just to
tell everyone they've got boyfriends. [snorts]
Yeah, they're full of [ __ ] mate.
Look at that beard, Greaves. E,
I'm looking like [ __ ] Bin Laden's, brother.
He He's doing worse than me.
Look at that, bro. Look at that beard. Eh,
look like a [ __ ] terrorist.
Virgin boy can't grow a beard, can he? Ser
that skint virgin can't
that [ __ ] skin plonker.
Look at that.
You like it, Grezy? Imagine going to
waxies like this. Imagine
going like that, bro. Do you think I'll
get any numbers?
You think I'd get any numbers? Yeah.
I still need to dress up as Chucky and
go out, mate. I still need to wear that
Chucky costume and go out.
Should have done it for Halloween, to be honest.
Oh, [ __ ] [ __ ]
You know that um Brazilian woman that
kept being a narcissist? Do you know how
I told you I messaged her family? One's
messaging me back saying, "Go tell her
you [ __ ] said if you messed with her,
you regret it."
Oh, will I now?
See, these women need to stop [ __ ]
with me, you know. No, I just reply
back. They need to stop [ __ ] with me, Grezy.
Yeah, I messaged her back.
What's the odds?
Probably one in a trillion.
What if you approach people?
What if you approach people on the street?
He This guy's not replying. You know, I
met some guy here when I was with Adam.
I met Adam's brother's uni friend. And I
said, "I'm coming to Bristol on
Saturday. Let's have a few beers." But
he's not clicking on the message, Siri.
He's being a bit of an ignorer.
I should just go to Bristol and say,
"Come on then, you can
[ __ ] have you all. I love you all." Yeah.
Yeah. He's not responding. No. Cheers.
Yep. I'm very scruffy. I like looking
Yeah, I went past the barbers today, but
I can't be bothered going, bro.
So, I can't go out drinking today like
this then, Greasy. You could go out like
this. It wouldn't make a difference.
You'd still get the same old [ __ ] Anyways,
I used to look smacky. I used to pay a
lot of money to my barbers and I'd still
get the I've got a boyfriend [ __ ]
I'd still get I've got a boyfriend. It's horrible.
Yeah. You get the same [ __ ]
Keeps me warm. This Look at that beard.
Oh my god.
Is my beard patchy? Nah.
Who that skin plonker?
And these man's having a kid with this white woman. Yeah.
Some people are just meant to be single. Okay. [snorts]
Football's in an hour.
You [ __ ] yourself over the football?
You [ __ ] yourself?
I've got high hopes it will come in me. Yeah,
I might go on Red Star's channel.
Do you reckon I should go on his channel
and see what it's saying? I hope he's
not stalking me.
I hope he's not still stalking me. Siri say Siri,
I hope he's not still [ __ ] stalking
me. I might go on it in a minute. I'm
not sure. Probably not. I've not been on
it in a few weeks.
I don't like to go on Virgin channels.
God bless you. Yeah.
Could I go out like this drinking? Greavvesy. Yep.
But like I said, it's not even just a
boyfriend thing. It's the leading on. I
pay 55 cuz I get my like I get my whole
face done and that. And yeah, so you
might as well go out looking scruffy.
You probably got more chance of pulling
looking like a scruffy bastard.
But people on Reddit tell me to groom
and look after myself and stuff.
But I've looked Max many times. No one's interested. Same old.
My mommy looks so beautiful there. Oh my god.
Look at my mommy in her little dress on the right.
My mommy looks wonderful there.
What do you think, Grezy?
That's where I get my good
That's where I get my good looks from.
Look. Look at my beautiful mama. Yeah.
Look at that on the right. That little
leopard print dress. Oh,
my mom is so beautiful.
She's beautiful, my mama. That's where I
get my good looks from.
Yeah, it is.
Well, it's her sisters. Yeah.
See, everyone likes her other sisters,
but I prefer her. She That's cuz she has
like she has the boobies and stuff in it,
Greavesy. So, I Everyone says that she's
the worst, but I think she's the best
because she has big boobies.
And obviously you can't help who your
mom is. So I can't trade my mama. Oh yes.
That's so cute. Is it Grezy? So cute.
Which one would you pick out the three?
I think you'd say the left, isn't it?
Let me see
just on Sher Cole's Instagram. Nope.
I don't see what's so special about this person.
No tits, no body.
But if you don't find her attractive,
you're [ __ ] homo. You're homosexual.
Nah, my mommy's better than her. >> [snorts]
>> Isn't that mad how I met my mommy in
London? So, does that mean I've got
American in me then, Greavvesy?
Does that mean I've Does that mean I've
got American in me?
Yeah. The perfect the perfect revenge is
to get to have a baby with the sister.
That's what someone in the O'Neals told
me. He said, "Yeah, that you know the
best way to get revenge is is have a
baby with her sister." I said, "You sick bastard.
You sick bastard."
And he was smiling as well. Remember the
black guy that was smiling like he
already knew what happened? He was
smiling the whole time.
Yeah. The black guy in it with the army
lads that was smiling, mate. Smiling.
It's like he already knew the story, isn't it? Yeah.
I can't believe my mommy had me.
And my favorite my favorite number is 11
as well. And that's her birthday, 11th
of April. So, it's weird, isn't it? And
do you remember when I kept betting on
number 25, Siri?
When I kept betting on the number 25,
they kept coming in.
What? You want me? You want me to You
want me to go to Miami? Yeah. But the
thing is, bro, they're going to call Old
Bill. You know what they're like, is it?
They're going to call [ __ ] Old Bill.
Do you know what that means? Old Bill Grezy.
Yeah, but they're going to call Bill on.
You know, mate, is it?
I went to one of them house parties like
Ed Matthews. Yeah. And then you see her.
I know this is you. Oh, mama.
Do you remember that one? I know this is you.
What do you reckon would happen if I
gave her the Ugg boots?
Briefly, if I bought her a pair of UGG boots?
I bought Laney a pair of UGG boots. So,
I can buy you a pair of UGG boots if you want, mama. Nah, bro.
She's got her Instagram as private. It
never used to be as p her Instagram
never used to be private. I wonder why
she she made it private.
That's the mis that's a mystery.
I wonder why she made it private
all of a sudden.
See LT got into some madness about this.
He was he was contacting her. Was that
because of me?
Was that because of me, Grezy? Was
that because of me?
Nah, wasn't all me. She started it,
you know. [laughter] Yeah,
that guy doesn't look like me at all.
I'd smoke him in front of her as well. I
said, "Let me come and and and tell you
about yourself in front of your
boyfriend, you little cunt." I was
replying on the comments as well and it
I said, "Let me come next week in it."
It was when I was back at the old house,
sending them my little t-shirt and
shorts. Come on, you [ __ ] Come on.
Come on, you little [ __ ] Yeah,
that's mad that that could end in death,
you know. That is bad, bro. That is really bad.
I bet that will put people off cold
approaching, isn't it? Yeah.
Yeah. That guy's got tattoos. I don't
have any tattoos.
It's a [ __ ] [ __ ]
Don't let these [ __ ] women win.
Yeah, but it doesn't make me suffer
though cuz I don't like the [ __ ]
and I've already had the bitch's body. So,
yeah, they are evil. They are [ __ ]
definitely definitely evil.
I told that one in um I told her to get
raped today. There was one I was
speaking to on um Instagram. She blocked
me. Yeah. She said she was going to have
a baby with me. Then we spoke on Reddit
and then she blocked me randomly. I told
her [ __ ] off and get raped.
Stupid little evil [ __ ] Yeah.
No, but I should have got the [ __ ] pregnant.
Then I then I would have had the last laugh.
Should have got the [ __ ] pregnant, bro.
Cuz if you get them pregnant, then they
can't talk back to you.
Yeah, she was being a [ __ ] bro. [ __ ] her.
Yeah, but if they you need to get them
pregnant so they can't talk back to you.
You know what I mean? So, if you get
someone pregnant, you win.
You know, you win.
cuz you you can laugh about how you came
in there and they done absolutely
nothing and now they're [ __ ] now
because of the hormones and [ __ ] So,
they wouldn't be able to talk back to
you, you know?
That's that's how you def that's how you
you have the last laugh out of someone.
That's why I never I never I never eat
[ __ ] because then they can they can say
that they dominated me and stuff.
They can say that they dominated me and stuff,
you know. So that's why I don't whereas
the 19-year-old, I can tell her that I
made her swallow my babies, so she can't
say anything to me. You know,
you swallowed my babies.
I just tell her that you swallowed my babies.
You swallowed my babies, you know.
So in a way that's their vitamins as well. Greavesy,
they need vitamins from like semen and
stuff. So they need vitamins from like
the Willie and stuff
because they get hungry.
Throtted my load and then had a nice Chinese.
Funny, isn't it?
And her friend will say now she's got
anxiety. I've got anxiety too.
Well, I've had anxiety, you know, in the
past when I've drunk a lot. So what?
She's caused me anxiety.
Let these [ __ ] women win.
Don't let these [ __ ] women win. That's mad. Yep.
Yeah. Mad, isn't it?
Would that be a good win if it wins? £215. Yeah,
I reckon it's going to come in.
I think we really need to get these
women, sir. We can't let them win, mate.
We really can't let them win.
We really, really can't let them win.
We can't let these [ __ ] win, bro.
They're laughing at us, mocking us, you know.
They need to pay. Yeah.
I still got the approaching video of my mama
Grezy. I've still got the video. So, yeah.
I mean, I can't believe the only Do you
know what's so mad about that? The only
one in a lifetime approach I actually recorded.
It's so mad how I actually recorded it.
And no one would have ever believed it
if I didn't record it when I met my mama.
You know that's mad, isn't it? The only
like what's the chance that I actually
recorded it that day too.
I actually recorded it as well too.
Do you remember
I just approached them from behind?
Didn't know what was going to happen.
I thought, oh, let's see what's going to
happen. It's just going to be someone
saying that they've got a boyfriend and
stuff, but they seem to quite like me. Greasy. My mama.
Don't let these [ __ ] women win.
What did you say? If I had a baby, it
would get risk straight into the care system, Grezy.
Yeah, but they can't do that if the
baby's in America, can they?
Yeah, but what about you? You need to
get laid as well.
You need to get laid as well, lad.
So, you should come out with me, isn't it?
Yeah, but they're winning against you as well.
Yeah, but you need to get laid as well, bro.
What about you? You need to get laid.
Whisked straight into the care system. [ __ ] mad. Yeah,
I'm not going out approaching. [ __ ] off, bro.
You can win. just get an escort and take
your money back.
That's that's a way you can beat these
women. You can pay an escort and then
take the money back.
I mean, that's a way you can win if you want.
There's a way there's ways around it.
Be able to beat these women, you know.
That's a way you could beat him.
And it agrees with you. That's a way you
could beat these [ __ ] And it's
guaranteed to work as well. Yeah.
No, it's not horrible. What these women
do are horrible. Yeah.
Da da da da da da da da da da da.
I'm going to Thailand. Yeah.
So, what do you reckon my mommy would do
if I bought my mommy Uggs? Grievy,
do you reckon she would wear them?
The UG boots.
Peter Belly can't get attached anymore
because he's already found his mama. A
Sig's not Peter Belly's mama.
Sig Sig not Peter Belly's mama.
Do you remember that one? Sign up Peter Belly's mama. Yep.
Signal Peter Bell's mama.
But no, bro. I can't be bothered.
[ __ ] them. I don't want to deal with
them. They're narcissistic and evil.
I don't want to deal with them. They're evil.
Very evil, bro.
Yeah. Messageing her family, the
Brazilian one's family. Well, the South
American one's family. Greasy. Is that
too much? You want to be a little
ignoring little narcissistic [ __ ] and
get your little [ __ ] white knights to
message me? I'll get your family.
I'll bring family involved. You know
what I'm like, mate.
You know what I'm like?
You know what I'm bloody like, mate.
I miss them family. I messed their
family ages ago. Just messaging me now. [snorts] [ __ ] [ __ ]
Oh, it's the football soon.
[snorts] But it's not though. Better
women, better weather, cheaper. I mean,
all round it's going to be a better life.
Oh, yeah. But it's going to be a better
life all round, isn't it, Grezy? Better
weather, better people,
better food, everything, you know. You know
what about Virgin Boy? Do you think he's
ever going to get laid?
Do you think the Virgin's ever going
Do you think he's ever going to lose it?
Or do you reckon he'll die one?
Reckon he's going to lose it.
Reckon he's got divergent.
He's going to die one.
Well, I'm gonna go on the channel for one second.
Oh, the virgin's not been posting about me. That's good.
Oh, wait. He is on his other virgin channel.
Oh [ __ ] it is. He's got another virgin channel. Virgin channel.
What is this? He's calling the police
again. What a loser.
He's an absolute [ __ ] loser.
What an absolute virgin. That's what I
see when I see them. I say you absolute virgins.
Absolute ones, mate.
What a loser, mate. He's a proper proper
proper proper loser.
Pair of absolute virgins.
You know what I'm like, mate.
So, I just went on it.
[ __ ] what an absolute virgin.
They're so jealous of me, bro. It's
unbelievable how jealous they are of me. It's mad.
So so so so so jealous. It's
unbelievable. I've ever known people be
so jealous of people in my life, bro. Mad.
What an absolute virgin.
Old Bill get owned.
What a sad little bastard.
He's so desperate to get the police
involved. It's unbelievable.
I know. It's mad.
Police will take action now, mate. I'll
tell the police to [ __ ] off.
I'll tell the police to [ __ ] off, mate.
Let them come on this door and see what
happens. Right. Let them come on this
door and see what happens. You [ __ ]
skin little virgin.
Well, 100%. Let them comment this star
and you'll see what will happen. Yeah.
[ __ ] skin virgin.
What a loser. Coming on YouTube every
day like some kind of big man.
Yeah. Well, I'm going to show them what
he keeps [ __ ] doing to me. The
[ __ ] skinned little virgin. And I'll
tell him to [ __ ] off. Yeah, that's what
I'll do. Yeah.
I'll say, "Tell this little [ __ ]
wanking little virgin to stop harassing
me every day and [ __ ] off." That's what
I'll say to them. I will literally shout
out the window and tell them to [ __ ]
off, bro. Trust me, you don't know me,
bro. You do not know me. Yeah, you can
ask my You can ask all the tenants what
happened last time, bro.
Yeah, he's a little virgin. He's a skint
little virgin, bro. Yeah, I told my
solicitor about this as well. Yeah,
cuz as someone they would be advised to
stop posting content on them. Yeah, they
would be they would be advised
they should be advised to stop posting
content on them if somebody has got a
court order, do they? Would they not? So yeah.
Oh, the police never did call me back by
the way. You know
what an absolute little loser.
He's such an absolute little virgin.
This is his life as well. This little
obsessed virgin, bro.
What an absolute virgin.
What an absolute little virgin.
So desperate to get the police involved
because he gets owned. What a sad little
boy. They always go to the police in the
end, the losers.
How many of them done How many of them
have done this on here, bro?
How many times have they done this on
here? These losers keep running to the
police when they get their ass When they
get their virgin ass a good whooping.
When they get their virgin ass a good
old whooping. You know it's old Bill
time, 80. They're so much of a loser.
So much of a [ __ ] loser. Yeah. And
I'll tell the police as well, if the
police come, right, I'm going to report
every single day. I swear to God, I've
done it like 10 times cuz the court kept
telling me, bro, but if the police come,
I am going to be on their case every
single day. Every single day, multiple
times. Yeah. If the police come and they
harass me one more time over this
virgin, I'm going to be on their case
every single day. And I'm not going to
stop. So, they might as well like keep
me in there. You know, you can't play
two sides of a [ __ ] coin. You know,
you can't play two sides of a [ __ ] coin
if it does happen. Yeah. I will
literally be on their case every day
about this virgin, this skint little
virgin, right? Every single day, I'm
going to be doing it and doing it and
doing it and doing it and doing it.
I'm going to be like, "So, you let this
little skint virgin have channels about
me?" Yeah, bro. I'm not even I would I'm
not even opening the door to him. So,
they'd be wasting their time. They're
going to have to break in the door. So,
you're going to let this skin little
virgin on these virgin channel keep
making videos of me every day. And I
know he does it cuz I don't go in it.
So, you're going to let these people
keep harassing me every day, but you
want to get involved when it suits
yourself. Go and have a wank and [ __ ]
off. That's what I'll say to them. Go
and have a wank and go play with
yourself and [ __ ] off. That's what I'll
say to them, bro.
Trust me. You don't know what I said to
them last time. You know, bro, I told
them, bro, you don't know what I was
saying to them last time, bro. I called
them pigs. Everything, bro. When I was
living like by myself without my mom, I
was calling them pigs. Dirty, stinky
pigs. Like, they wrote it down and
everything, bro. Trust me. Yeah.
Yeah. 100%. [ __ ] little loser.
sat behind his little virgin little gay
ugly channel with his ugly face and his
ugly girlfriend being a pair of virgins
every day on [ __ ] YouTube and then
running to the police [ __ ] losers.
Absolute losers and then they think
they've won. That's that's what makes me
laugh with them, bro. They think being a coward
I call them dirty [ __ ] eatating [ __ ]
Yeah, I call them dirty [ __ ] eatating
[ __ ] And you know the only time,
right? Do you know the only reason I
didn't say anything to that police
officer last time? Because my mom was
like, "Oh, leave it. Leave it. Leave
it." You know when they arrested me the
last time, I said, "I want to see that.
I want to see that police officer
today." Right. I want him to try and
tell me to wipe my neck out. The [ __ ]
eating pig. The [ __ ] eating [ __ ] That's
what I would have said, bro. Yeah. The
police officer was like, "Oh, leave it."
The other one was like, "Leave it." I
would be like, "You wind your neck in,
you shitty eating cunt." That's what I'd
say to him. Oh, you [ __ ] pig with a
silly little uniform, with a silly
little gay uniform. You don't know me,
mate. You don't [ __ ] know me, bro.
Yeah, cuz I wasn't living with my mom,
so I had no one to stop me. I was
saying, "You [ __ ] stupid [ __ ] eating
pigs." I told the guys multiple times,
"Do not look at me like that. [ __ ] off."
Yeah, [ __ ] [ __ ] eating [ __ ]
[ __ ] eatating [ __ ] bastards. Little
nods lovers. Just like they are on here.
They're little nons lovers on here.
They're nons lovers.
That's what they are like on here.
You know what they're like, bro. Nons
lovers on here.
Skinny little virgin.
That's what they are, bro.
sad little bastard
running to the police cuz you're so much
of a [ __ ] loser
that you can't meet anyone. You can't do
anything. You're a loser. You're an
absolute virgin. And the only people
that think and the only people that
think you've won
is these [ __ ] losers.
When you haven't won, you're a complete
loser. A complete and utter skin loser. Virgin loser.
Look at them, bro. Look at this. This
Jamie Thompson stalking me every day.
Mad, bro. They're so jealous of me. It's
unbelievable. I've never known people
to be so jealous of people that they don't know.
Mad, isn't it? Absolute mad.
Sad little bastards. Yeah.
Oh, loads of things. Foster career. He's
another fat low life. Little depressed
Also, I've got a crime reference number
as well, which um yeah, I've got a crime
reference number. I've got basically
every single bit of evidence of this
skin, what this skin little virgin has
done. And I've got crime reference
numbers, so they can't sit there and try
and say you haven't reported it either.
So, I've got my ass covered from this little virgin
because if you type the crime reference
number in, you can see where it's been
reported. So, yeah.
[ __ ] virgin. Yeah, foster carers. Um,
yeah, he's he's a sad little bastard. I
need to Yeah, I need to change my number
anyways. I've got two different numbers.
Another sad fat ugly. They're like
Reddit moderators, you know, just Jamie
Thompson. They're like moderate Reddit moderators,
you know, like Reddit mods, bro. You're
better looking than them, younger than
them, and it kills them. That's where
all of this stuff comes from. The
stalking, the giving numbers. It's
because they hate that you're better
looking than them. It's like what Ronald
Pump said. It's true. It's It is true.
They see someone younger, better
looking, a glamour of hope in life, and
it kills them because they they see
themsel as fat, ugly, skinn, no life, no
confidence. So, they sit on here and
they try to bring other people down.
That's the tactics that they do.
Especially just uh just uh Jamie Thompson.
Just T uh Jamie Thompson. Yeah.
Yeah. Just uh just uh Jamie Thompson does it. Sad bastard.
So yeah, let the police come in this
door again and you'll see what happens.
And I'll record it as well, bro. Yeah.
Sad little narcissistic skint virgin.
Taking out on the wall all cuz you can't
get sex. I've had it with you for 10
years. Projecting your [ __ ] ugly
virginity onto me, virgin boy. But
you're not so big now when I'm a grown
man, are you? But I can tell you about
your virgin self. I know you better than
you know your virgin self. Your [ __ ]
virgin. And the London accent is is is
stronger than the kid one.
You know, you didn't believe the escort
story. All because you were the virgin
and still are the virgin. You had to get
my mom on the phone confirming it. All
because you're the big virgin. Pent. All
cuz you've never had sex. Little virgin.
Oh, you're not so big though, are you?
And it's a grown man. You can't talk
over your [ __ ] skinned little virgin.
I've never known something so pathetic,
right? Someone older than someone having
to run to old Bill cuz they got their
ass a good old whooping. Cuz they got
their ass a good old whooping. I've
never met such a loser in my life. And
I've come across so many losers in my
life, mate. I've never known someone
have no fight left in them,
selfdefeating little loser and they have
to run to the police.
So much of a [ __ ] loser that you
can't take no more that you got your ass
a good old whooping boy that you have to
run to the police. Yeah.
Go and get laid. Lose your virginity.
You might be a better person. Skin boy [ __ ] So yeah.
Oh, look at these excuses that they're
making. Why are you shaking? Your belly
button sticking out. He verbally abused
the bouncer. Laughs at him only because
he see what I mean. These little
virgins, they make up any excuse.
Partners together laughing at M. They
didn't mock me at all. You little B.
They make up excuses. This is what I
mean with these virgins on this
community, bro. Even when they take L's,
they still think they've won.
Even when you beat them, they still
pretend that they they've won. Like that
bouncer video, I completely destroyed
all of them. And they still make
excuses. Even when, bro, like even when
they lose, they still pretend that
they've won. It's autism. I'm telling
you, bro. They're autistic.
They are [ __ ] autistic.
Yeah. I told them about themselves and
their girlfriends. Not one man stood up
to me. Not one man stood up to me,
virgin boy. Just like you did not stand
up to me when I was in your little
virgin area next to your Wales barber.
You skinted virgin.
You absolute you absolute virgin. When I
went to that virgin area, you know.
[ __ ] hell, mate.
defending women, but they don't like
you. If I ended up with a disabled girl,
still a virgin, the last thing I'd be
doing is defending them [ __ ] If I was
a big virgin like him, right, the last
thing I'd be doing is defending people
when I'm when I'm a 31y old virgin, I
won't be [ __ ] defending them, you know, mate.
Stupid little skin virgin.
[ __ ] sad virgin. And look, and as you
can see, no one's calling him a grass.
This is what I mean. They're nons
lovers. They love nonses on here, bro.
This is what I mean. They love nonses.
They love nonses on this community.
That's why they love [ __ ] nons legs.
That's why they say, "Oh, we can't be a
virgin because they got a girlfriend."
Because they're nons. This is what I
don't understand why they go for Monty
so much. They call Monty man a
pedophile, right? They call him a
pedophile. They say on here that they
don't like pedophiles. Yet this [ __ ]
ugly little skint virgin, right, has has
admitted multiple times to liking
children under age and no one says anything. Mad.
Mad. They're non-lovers. That's what
they are. They're autistic non-lovers.
That's what they are. Madness, bro. Absolute madness.
You're [ __ ] Skint virgin. I can say
Skint more than you can cuz you are
Skint. And even if you keep showing your daddy savings,
you'll always be that Skint virgin from Pent.
You know, you are trying to say that
you're from London. You're not part of
London. You [ __ ] Skint virgin. That
[ __ ] ugly accent and that ugly face
has got nothing to do with London, mate.
That ugly face and that ugly voice
virgin has got nothing to do with
London. Don't you ever ever insult
London like that. I can assure you I was
born in in London, mate. And we are not
like them virgins from Kent. We're not
like them Kent virgins with shitty
clothes. Even the even the [ __ ] even
the way we dress is different. We're not
walking around like some skent virgin in
charity shop clothes. walking around
being an absolute virgin.
You know what I'm saying? We're not
doing them things, bro. London's a lot [ __ ] different.
You know, you're not no part of London.
You're a kid virgin. [ __ ] off. Nothing
to do with London, mate.
Nothing to do with London. D.
And another thing is he's already broken
that um you know when you've got a
restraining order on someone and then
they contact you, you do realize it
voids it by the way. Like you do realize
when you contact someone, right, you're
actually you actually void the whole
thing. You do realize that the whole
thing becomes void. Just just throw that
at you if you didn't know that.
Yeah, just just throwing that at you
like you didn't know that, mate.
Basically, when they when someone's got
like a a court order
and someone contacts you,
um they basically void it. It basically gets void.
So, yeah. Anyways,
let me go on this other channel. Just
wanted to see [ __ ] two weeks later, bro.
Still on YouTube stalking Red Star. You
absolute skint loser. You're still on YouTube.
You need to get a life and go get some
sex. You sad fat ugly bastard. You need
to get a life, you little skint loser.
If you had money, you wouldn't be sat on
here every day.
You absolute loser. Do you know what you
and your boyfriend need to do? You need
to suck each other off because that's
the only action you're ever going to be
getting. You and your little virgin gay
nonslegs boyfriend needs to suck each
other off. You'll be much happier people
in life. You'll be much happier people
Mate, you're in your 40s still on
YouTube. You need to get laid. Go get
some money, you sad bastard.
You need to go and get laid, you jealous
bastards. You need to stop sucking each
other off. You sad pair of virgins.
You're talking about me being nearly 30,
bro. You're in your 40s and you're fat
and you're ugly. Leave a 30year-old
alone. We could be you, mate, in our
40s. A big ugly bastard on YouTube.
We've all seen your fingers, mate. We
have seen your m fingers with your shitty,000.
You and your little boyfriend need to
suck each other off. That's what you
need to do. You need to suck each other
off for content. You're boring, mate.
This is why no one goes on your little
skin little disabled virgin outwardly
channel because you're boring. That was
the first time in 3 weeks. Just letting
you know, by the way, mate. So, yeah.
Um, basically, when you contact someone,
um, when someone's got a court order,
you avoid that court order, by the way.
Um, which the police is going to be
telling you that. So yeah, you little
[ __ ] skip virgin. And I've got all
the things where you've tried to join as
well. So you absolute loser. Not a big
man, now are you? You're not a big man,
now are you? You [ __ ] skit little
virgin. You're not a big man, now are
you? You're not a [ __ ] big man, how
are you, virgin boy? When someone's not
17, 18 years of age when you kept
projecting your ugly self virginity onto
me. You're not a big man now, are you?
Peace boy. Police boy, you're not a big
man now, are you?
You're not a big man, how are you, you
[ __ ] virgin loser. You big big virgin
I know he thinks he's winning, but he's
not. And he's actually voided the court
order as well. He's actually voided the
court order as well.
Yeah, he actually voided a court order
as well, mate. You know, you actually
void a court order when you contact someone.
So, and I've got everything. I've got
161 things in my harassment folder. So,
I've got everything, mate. So, it's not
a problem if you want to keep this
going. You [ __ ] skin ugly virgin. You
skinted ugly virgin.
Right. You [ __ ] skint ugly virgin. I
would love to say that to you to your
face as well, but you won't meet grown
men, will you? I tell you that you're
nothing but a skint ugly virgin little
dirty disabled bastard.
You're nothing but a nasty virgin.
That's what you are. A [ __ ] virgin
who needs to get laid and stop targeting
disabled people. You're not going to
[ __ ] lose your B card like that. I've
tried to tell you many, many, many
times, right? I'm not trying to convince
anyone. I'm telling you that you're the
biggest virgin going because you are.
You are big, big virgin. You know, even
if I had a Turkish accent, I'd be like,
you're big, big virgin. You've never
been laid. And all of the people that
you can get with are disabled BECAUSE
YOU'RE [ __ ] UGLY. SO ALL OF THESE
things that you do on YouTube,
saying people are skinned and ugly, it's
all your own life. You and Red Star's
own lives. Pair of virgins. Pack of
That's what they are. [ __ ] packer virgins.
Packa ugly virgins.
You know what I mean, mate?
You know what I [ __ ] mean, mate? pair
of cowardly little virgins,
big big cowards. They get owned on YouTube.
No, but in all seriousness, right, when
you have to call the police over someone
on YouTube, you know that you've you
know that you've been owned. You know
that you're a loser. You know that you
got your ass a good weapon.
Trying to say I'm loser with women,
hygiene, and money. Brother, I'm better
looking than you and I've got more money
than you would ever have. I've had more
women than your ugly virgin ass would ever have.
You don't even have any teeth in your
[ __ ] mouth. You skinned virgin.
Yeah, he he he's got a chance to get to
kick cuz I'm telling I'm walking down,
bro, telling this story about this
escort. Bear in mind, I think I was
eight. No, I think I was still 17 at the
time, right? I know I was still 17 and
I'm I'm telling this guy about this
escort story. Well, telling the virgin
more like um about the story, right,
about the um basically the story, right?
And he's saying no, no, no. And I'm
thinking in my head, why the [ __ ] is
this guy not believing these stories?
Obviously, I'm quite young. Have you
ever seen a quite a younger Peter belly?
And I'm thinking, why the [ __ ] are is
this guy not believing me? And it's
because he is the virgin. He's the big
virgin. It clicked. It clicked a few
years later, bro. Um, no, it was the
second one, I think it was. And I'm
telling him this story and for what? For
he would not believe it. For love nor
money. He I would tell him these stories
and he wouldn't. And it's because he was
the biggest virgin going and he is the
biggest virgin going and he didn't want
to feel left out because I lost my V
card before him because no one wanted
him because he's ugly. Because he's an
ugly bastard. Yeah, he's an ugly
bastard. Yeah, he's an ugly.
And I'm thinking, why the [ __ ] is this
person not not believing what I'm
telling him? Why is he not believing it?
And it's like, oh, cuz he's the virgin
and he's never had sex. And no matter
what you would tell this little skint
virgin, right, in a bed sit, he would
not believe it. He was trying to make up
stories. Escorts asked for ID. All
because he was the virgin and he was
jealous. He was jealous because his dick
doesn't work cuz he's a little virgin.
All because he's got erectile
dysfunction. He hates the fact that
other people have had sex.
because he's a big virgin. You
understand me, bro? I'm thinking, why
would you believe that? And it's like,
oh, he's the virgin. He's the kid
virgin. Then he resorted to making up
stories that he's [ __ ] had sex on a
park bench. That [ __ ] has never
[ __ ] nothing. I'm telling you right
here, right now, bro, he has never stuck
that disabled dick up anything. Take it
from me, bro. I know this [ __ ] better
than he knows himself. He's very shy in
real life. Very reserved. Can't speak to
women. Trust me, he has never Yeah.
Yeah, I did, bro. That was the second one, lad.
That was the second one. Trust me, he
has never stuck that erectile disabled
dick up nothing. Do not let him tell you
that he's ever had sex with anyone,
mate, because he will die a virgin. And
I wouldn't say it if I didn't believe
it. He showed an X-ray.
He showed an X-way ray of his of of his
dick that was [ __ ] broken off, bro.
I'm not even joking. Oh yeah, he met
this Aisha that tried to use him for his
money. He absolutely did not sleep with
her. He absolutely did not have sex with
her under park bench at all because I
have spoken to her. He absolutely did
not [ __ ] stick his ugly dick up
[ __ ] someone in a park bench. That is
ridiculous. you would get [ __ ] done
for sexual exposure.
I said, "You need to stop making up
these wild sex stories."
He's making up these mad sex stories.
You've never [ __ ] had sex with Aisha,
you little virgin. Stop coming on here
[ __ ] you know, spreading rumors.
He said he had sex with him on a PARK
FENCE. YOU NEVER HAD SEX with you
[ __ ] stupid little [ __ ]
Stop making up sex stories. It doesn't
make you look big.
Just like when you was trying to call me
gay for not finding sh attractive.
Little copy. You little copy.
Little copycat. Little cat. Little cat.
Little cat. Look at me. You little cat.
Little copy. You a little copycat.
You a little cat.
Little cat. They don't. That's why he's
still a virgin.
They don't find him attractive. That's
why he's still a virgin. And he WAS
GOING TO DIE ONE. He's going to die one.
No one does. That's why he's going to
die a virgin.
Why do you think he stalks you in all of
these things? Cuz it kills him that I'm
bare looking at him and I've had more
women than him. I feel like you're in
karaoke and he's going to die a virgin.
Do you know what I'm saying, bro?
You [ __ ] virgin. I said you. Yeah,
you are a [ __ ] virgin. You skin
little dick. Little dick [ __ ]
Yeah, I bet you'd meet me though if I
was 17, wouldn't you? You [ __ ] nasty
skin virgin. Yeah, you would do you
would do when I was 17, would you? But
not now, mate. Not now. You wouldn't
[ __ ] with a grown man, would you? You
little virgin [ __ ] You little virgin
[ __ ] Yeah. What accent do you prefer?
Do you prefer the Kent one or the London one?
Oh, what about Virgin boy?
Um, let me think to one.
Virgin boy. Virgin boy or does whatever
the virgin boy does. I I need to make
some I need to make some lyrics.
>> When you going to lose it? When you
going to lose it? When you going to lose
that baby? When you going to pop it?
When you going to pop it? Do you like
When are you going to lose it? When you
going to lose it, you skin [ __ ] You
skin [ __ ] Showing daddy sins.
When are you going to lose it? When are
Yeah, I'm going to actually write a song.
It's dedicated to the skin virgin in
Kent. That pent [ __ ] [ __ ] with the
ugly rat face. And he keeps he keeps
calling me ugly WHEN I'M ALREADY BETTER
looking than him. I've had more women
than him. I've never had to resort to
disable like that ugly [ __ ] That ugly virgin [ __ ]
Never in my life. So I don't know why he
calls me ugly when no one in the chat
would agree with him. Like it's that bad
that if you went on his little virgin
channel. Oh, you know another thing I
wanted to talk about is the being scared
of dislikes. He's scared of dislikes. If
somebody disagrees with me, block them.
He's he's an absolute virgin. Haven't
you seen it? Haven't you seen it, mate?
You're absolute virgin. I mean, you I
mean, you seen it, bro, where he would
literally like ban anyone that dislikes
the videos or anyone that thumbs up
things, he blocks them. Do you remember
when I done that video of the women,
right, and it got 14 thumbs up? Ricky
Millington simp comment. I didn't delete
it because I know that they're full of
[ __ ] and I know the truth. Like, I
didn't b it, bro. Whereas, if somebody
backs me up and they get thumbs up,
he'll ban them. He's scared of thumbs
up. He's an absolute virgin. An absolute
An absolute virgin. That's my favorite word, bro.
You absolute virgins. Do you know what
I'm saying? Yeah.
He's scared of dislikes.
He's scared of thumbs up and thumbs
downs. Have you seen it? Typical virgin.
He's an absolute little virgin.
Oh, 17 again, bro. If only I was 17 again.
But these kind of people can't [ __ ] with
grown men, can they? No.
You little skin tent [ __ ] can't [ __ ]
with grown men, can you? You skin little bastard.
You skit little [ __ ]
You skint [ __ ]
Run to the place. You get your ass a
good whapon. A good oldfashioned whapon. Virgin boy.
That's funny, bro. Only because
partners, they were mocking. Apparently,
they were mocking me and laughing me at
the table when I told them to [ __ ] off
and go back to where they come from. But
they were laughing and mocking me. I
mean, do you want to watch the video
back again, bro?
Do you want to watch the video back? I
literally told them to mind their own
business and [ __ ] off and I was arguing
with like three people at once.
I mean, should should we watch the video
back again? Because that's not what
happened where people mocked me, is it?
Is it? They mocked me. I literally told
them to [ __ ] off. I mean, did you did
you watch the video properly, Siri? Did
you watch it? They didn't mock me. I
told them to [ __ ] off the ugly [ __ ] I'm
pretty sure I called him an ugly [ __ ] as
well, did I?
That is made up. They make up stuff.
They make up stuff that suits their
narrative. It's [ __ ] insane, bro. Honestly,
these people are really, really, really,
really, really disabled on here, bro. Yeah.
Really, really, really disabled.
Really, really disabled. What the [ __ ]
bro? I literally told them to go and
[ __ ] back to Newcastle where they come
from. And they mocked me. I told them my
trainers is worth more than your whole
outfit, you silly trap. How the [ __ ] did
they mock me, mate?
I told them about themselves and their
girlfriends, and they didn't even stand
up and do anything about it. Should we
watch the video again?
Should we watch the video again on the
TV? Should we watch the video again?
Should we watch the video again, Virgin Boy?
You seem to be a bit shortsighted here, mate. H,
you blinking virgin. They make up a load
of stories, bro. Hey, that bouncer shat
it. And you know what the excuse was?
He's at work. He's at work. He's at
work. But when the bus driver was having
a go at me about four years ago, oh, I
was a [ __ ] for backing down.
Apparently, these little virgins, bro,
are are mad on here, mate. They're mad
on here. Even when they're proven wrong,
they still resort to lying.
They literally resort to lying. Even
when they're Even when they've lost,
they resort to lying. It's mad. They You
prove you've had sex, they still call
you a virgin. You prove that you're
about it, they make up excuses that the
guy's at work. Okay, the guy's at work.
What about the other four people? You
see what I mean, bro? They make up
excuses every time.
pulled women. I told him about himself
in front of these women and he didn't
stand up. They didn't stand up at all
because they knew they would have got
slapped up. Two of them would have got
slapped the [ __ ] up in front of everyone. So,
they always make excuses, don't they?
Always make excuses.
Always make excuses, mate. Virgin,
you're mentally obsessed with me, bro.
No, but on a on a level though, bro.
Seriously, I'm [ __ ] they [snorts] are
really obsessed with me. These [ __ ] on
here, bro. Very, very obsessed with me.
Your whole life revolves around me and
you insecure little virgin.
I'd love to know where they have the
time to to have sex. I really would,
mate. Anyways, I'm going to watch this
football. Yeah. And I'll be back later.
I'll be back later, bro. Yeah, later.
Later. Later, later. Later.
Hopefully this [ __ ] football bet comes in.
Uh, so yeah, I'll be back later anyways.
I got a feeling it will. Sorry.