Oh god. Find this bloody spot that
just I went on [ __ ] jail.
[ __ ] absolute virgins.
I just have my Chinese. Yeah.
What was that?
Dude, he's not my trace
receipt. Yeah, I was watching all day
whilst I was waiting for my uh £374.
Well, that's depressing, bro. No, I'm
not. They're just repeating little fat
ugly bastards. They don't destroy no one
or nothing. They're just keyboard
warriors. Yeah, I was watching some of
it. I was waiting for my take away.
Mate, these people have been destroyed
since they come out. Their mom's [ __ ]
They're just little low lives. They
don't destroy no one. And why is why is
Joseph Ferrar there as well? I thought
he said he didn't like people that lie.
The biasness on this community, mate.
Jesus. Bloody Christ. That's my bloody nothing, mate.
I'm just looking at old receipts. I'm
trying to find um I think it is this
receipt for my charges. [ __ ]
No, I went on there, mate. And they're
absolute virgins. Don't even get me
[ __ ] started on them bloody virgins.
No, they don't destroy anyone, mate.
They can destroy They destroy someone if
they meet them in person. If they meet
someone face to face, then they destroy
them. You can't destroy someone over a keyboard. Um,
I saw them all singing over Autumn. I
started to feel a bit sorry for her and
I felt a bit sick.
You can tell these people have never
ever been with a woman. Yeah. Well, you
can tell they're fat, ugly little
virgins. The way they just cling on to
any woman that goes on the live stream.
Well, looking at these, these are the
pressing days. One second. I'll do it back.
for I got my JD receipt as well.
This is when Peter B was rich. These
were the rich days. Not anymore. The trainers
look like these are the trainers. 305
the race. I'm looking for my I'm looking
for my USB uh lead thing.
I think it's this one. The£10 one.
Yeah. I want to know why this charge is
[ __ ] dodgy. [ __ ] paid some money for that.
Yeah. These were the good days. The good
old Reese days.
Madness to respond, bro.
That's when the microphone got picked.
These are bringing back so many memories
when Peter Betty was reach.
Why got old footballs? These
are like really old football.
But yeah, that V
is an absolute virgin little nerd. Did
you see the way he was talking to [ __ ] um
uh the way he was talking to um
to Autumn? You can tell that he's never
been anywhere near a woman because these
people are so fat and ugly. part of
their jealousy. You You can tell that
they just can't go out in real life and
meet anyone. That's why they're on here
every day hating and being a nerd
because they got nothing else in life. Oh man,
that's the lead that [ __ ] broken. Yeah.
Yeah. That Reese was 37.
I gave him £400.
Oh, it's nice. E, [snorts]
nice being rich. E,
it was nice once it lasted.
Look at these receipts.
£35 for two trainers.
You all right, Triple?
I'm just looking at my receipts
um from LA uh not last year, the last
summer before that. Maybe it was last summer.
Spent £400 in re spent £300 on trainers.
I used to be loaded. Me, mate. Used to
be [ __ ] loaded.
Used to be loaded, bro. Oh, [ __ ] Trying
to put the thing back in now.
I used to be bloody loaded.
Not so much anymore, matey.
That's mad. I was looking for a USB receipt.
Yeah, I was. But I wanted to talk about
these people off of Hey, you can't even
take a day off of YouTube.
Don't [ __ ] say to me you thought you
was having a couple weeks off. Did you
even take a day off YouTube? Nope. Never.
You're up early tonight.
We'll have to turn the light on the Landon. Yeah.
You can't even take a bloody day off
YouTube. Uh, no, I don't play
blueprints, bro. I don't bet on anything
but football. [ __ ] me. I don't bet on
anything but the football.
This charge is [ __ ] dodgy, bro. I
just had a Chinese
£10. Yeah, I just had a Chinese, bro. [ __ ] sake.
No, you bloody can't. Oh, I went on
[ __ ] Lord J. Yeah. whilst waiting for
the Indian to come. Trip rates. Absolute
virgins. That's the only thing I've got
to say about them. Lot on there.
Absolute virgins. Did you see that
[ __ ] Did you see that VI sniffing
around autumn? You can tell the guy's
never had [ __ ] Fat ugly nerd.
You can tell he's never had [ __ ] bro.
He was like, "Oh, I can confirm through
doing my research search. Autumn's a
real woman. What a nerd. They're
absolute virgins. That was the first
time I went on them in uh couple weeks,
bro. Cuz my mom's uh my mom watches him.
So, when I was on her phone ordering it,
she paid for the food today cuz turns. I
thought, let me just go on this live
stream for a bit. Why not? I just read
in the comments.
What I don't understand is with these
people is that they talk about Timmy
lying. How many? He lies about
everything. Going on Jaden's door,
owning six properties. Um, meeting Izzy.
He's literally He literally lies about everything.
He literally lies about everything. Why
is he talking about Timmy lying, bro?
I'm not even defending [ __ ] Timmy,
but why why is he talking about people
lying when he lies about everything
himself? And guess who was in who was in
the chat? Um, Triple H. Joseph Farra.
And Joseph Farra has a problem with
people lying, but he's got no problem
with uh with L J lying.
I know it doesn't make any sense, does
it? She watches me and L J.
He lies about everything, but no
problem. Lies about owning properties,
but Joseph Ferrar doesn't mind that. No, no, no, no problem.
I think so. Yeah.
Yeah. Had a little copycat.
Think she does she watch the copycat?
I'm not sure.
Yeah, these people are [ __ ] Have I
begotten? They're bunch of [ __ ] nerds, bro.
That V is a [ __ ] nerd.
You go on there, it's the same people.
It's the same people. Same atmosphere.
The flash right. Greavvesy has all the
red flags for someone who should have
their hard drive looked at. So does your
boyfriend. Yeah. So does your boyfriend
that you keep going on his channel, you
little [ __ ] idiot. Yeah. So is your
virgin. The one that goes with So is
your [ __ ] copycat virgin, mate. That
goes for 15y olds. This is what I mean.
They're all disabled on here, bro.
Proper proper disabled.
She thinks they're sad losers.
It's the same atmosphere.
You remember that one, Triple H? It's
just the same atmosphere.
These people ain't got a life, bro.
Was a little sad virgin ain't got a life.
Like a lot of these on here, bro.
That V, bro, I would love to slap him
up. Why is it with the Irish on here
being such [ __ ] bro?
Fat ugly losers. I think everyone's seen
that V as well.
So, it's not We can't lie, but it's okay
for LJ. They They're just disabled, bro.
That's all they are. or they're just
disabled autistic people.
Did you see the way they pounced on that
autumn Triple H? Any woman that comes on
this community, they pounce on them
because they're too ugly to get anything
in real life. And they try to talk about other people
and they tried to talk about [ __ ]
other people. Madness, bro.
[ __ ] madness. Absolute virgins.
Absolute virgins, lad. You want to join the link?
Can't believe Joseph Farrell was in
there. He said that he doesn't like
liars. He said that he doesn't come on
my channel because I lie. But L J's a compulsive liar.
But to be fair, he's a non-slover as
well, to be fair. So
these people are [ __ ] ugly people, bro.
[ __ ] ugly people. You know, if if their
cameras got put up Yeah.
You see all these people
This is what Joe said. He doesn't get
that you can experience all sorts
without money and women. He just doesn't
value life, which ironically, if he did,
he would be more interesting to women
and others in general.
Well, you do need money to experience
certain things that you want to do in
life. So, I mean, you you do need money,
mate. You really really do need money.
Even if it's not materialistic. This
Joseph Ferrar is a [ __ ] idiot, lad.
Yeah, I'm good, man. I was just on L's
whilst waiting for the takeaway. I got
chicken fried rice and beef main, bro.
They're [ __ ] nerds.
The same people. Same atmosphere.
First time in weeks I went on that
channel, bro. Same people. It was cuz I
was on my mom's phone and it come up. So,
looks like an ultimate sense she's way
out of your league. Sounds like another
simp. A simp has appeared. We are the
fat ugly nerds that we're talking about,
right? Again, self projecting. Your
little self projecting doesn't bother
us. So, move on.
They all do, bro. It's not just him. Did
you see that Autumn? that Autumn was on
there and that V was like, "Oh, I can
confirm from my research that you're
verified as a real woman." Absolute
virgins. You can tell that you you you
can tell that he's never been with a
woman. And I don't like Autumn and she
is definitely not out of my league. I
mean, I'm the one that doesn't have to
use filters. Um, but we're not talking
about people's looks. We're talking
about these little nerds. These little
nerds that have never been with a woman.
It's so obvious they're virgins. Have
you seen it right on these people's
channel? Whenever a new woman comes on,
they bounce on them because they're fat, ugly virgins.
Absolute fat, ugly virgins. All of these
things that they try to call you is a
projection of their own lives.
Everything I'm saying, bro, is true. You
can you can see it for yourself. These
people are so fat and ugly, they can't
even go out and get a woman like I've
done multiple times. You've seen me
multiple multiple multiple multiple
multiple times. They're [ __ ] I went
on it, bro. I swear to God, I went on
it. Uh, I have been in a relationship.
Again, stop self- projecting. Bomb
behind that account. Yes, I have been in
a relationship. And yes, I have had more
women than every anyone that on Lord J's ever has.
So again, I'll repeat myself. I have had
a girlfriend and I have had women which
you have been shown time and time and
time and time again. Again, disabled
community. This is exactly what we was
talking about earlier when Triple H
wanted to. You people are disabled. Even
when you're proven wrong, you know, even
when you're proven wrong, you still
think you're right. You're disabled.
This is what we This is what we mean
with you people on here. Disabled
autistic community. Have you noticed right
when you go on people's channel like L
J's and when people come on here? Yeah.
Have you noticed you start losing brain cells?
Have you noticed right that you started
you start losing brain cells a bit the
longer you come on you're like it's
because where they're so autistic and
disabled and all they do is talk about
themselves when you hang around with
them when you hang around with them
right you've been on panels do you want
to join my panel you're more than
welcome to join my panel if you want
mate I wouldn't even go there with
autumn I would never even go for a woman
on the internet I'm not s I'm not a
white knight I'm not a loser like V.
If you want to join, you could join if you want,
but we all think that.
How you doing, Mike Hunt? Did you see
the video I done on the copycat?
A little copycat. Do you see the video I
done on the little copycat? My mom
watched the video. I saw it on her phone. Yeah.
What is it with people like [ __ ]
loving my videos, bro? [ __ ] copycat.
I like that picture.
Never had a one single woman again.
Self-projecting. Bomb. That's you. See,
even when you prove these people wrong,
they still talk [ __ ] They're talking
about themselves at 48.
My god. They're talking about themselves
at 48. It's part of their disability.
They get you mixed up with themselves.
28 and they've had a single woman want
you. That's their lives. They're getting
themselves mixed up again with you. This
is part of them, their disabilities.
These people are in their 40s, fat,
ugly, and skin. And they try to escape
that by telling you you are all the
things that they are. Mate, these people
are fat, ugly, life's losers that have
got nothing. And if they turn their
camera on, it will prove it again and
again and again.
No, I don't think it's that virgin. I
think it's the bomb. What it is with
these people, I've said it again and
again, they're fat, ugly life's losers.
They hate anyone younger and better
looking than them. Their disabilities
get in the way, bro. Yeah. They get
proven that that they're a bud, that
you're better looking than them, that
you got more money than them. And they
still talk [ __ ]
These fat ugly bongos still talk [ __ ]
Yeah, I did, but I didn't click on it
yet. I've had more women than you've had
hot dinners, you silly clown,
mate. again. Stop talking about
yourself. It's not good for your mental health.
What is it with these people and they
keep talking about themselves every day,
picking on themselves, bullying themselves.
I can't even afford a decent f Bro, stop
talking about yourself. It's boring now.
Stop talking about yourself. I think
[snorts] this is why Monty doesn't come
on here anymore,
mate. I've got more money than you will
ever have. You fat ugly skin flint. You
fat ugly little low life. Get off of
YouTube and get a life, you little self
projector. I'm 28 and I've had more
women and girls than you will ever have
because we're not all fat and ugly like
you and Bo [ __ ] begging women cuz
you're too ugly to get anyone in real life.
So, you going to come in hangouts or what?
No, I've already ate it. I already ate the Chinese.
I own these virgins. How many times have
I owned these virgins? Grints. Grinch.
Time and time again. Oh my god. It's
such an autistic community.
They're so autistic. This is what I mean
with these people in this community,
bro. They're so disabled.
This is why they This is what I mean by
they create the same atmosphere because
where they're so disabled,
they create the same atmosphere. They're
[ __ ] absolute bongos with nothing in life.
Jesus Christ. So, do you want me to
really really do it, bro?
So, okay. So, if I come off of YouTube
for two weeks,
I don't want to see any of you on here,
right? I don't want to see So, if I
really do it again for the hundth time,
right? I figured I'll fresh start
tomorrow. I don't want to see you people
on YouTube. When I come back, I don't
want to see any of you people on YouTube.
I'll go [ __ ] mad.
I'll go bloody mad. I don't want to see
any of you people on YouTube.
You know what I'm like, bro. Yeah. It's
that fat ugly little mun. The Irish
little m virgin.
Yeah. It's It's that fat ugly [ __ ] Did
you see him begging all begging her? No
one wants your fat ugly ass, you little
loser. No one wants your fat ugly ass,
you ugly loser. [ __ ] back to law J's you
fat ugly loser begging women on YouTube
you fat ugly M man you are the well and
truly the M man because we have never
seen you with women but we've seen me
with women why have we seen a m with
women but we've never seen you fat ugly
people with women we've never seen you
fat dog ugly people with women because
you're too ugly to get a woman yeah Bro,
nah, she's way out of your league, bro.
She's way out of your league, you fat Irish virgin.
You absolute fat [ __ ] She's out of
your league. She's out of your league,
fat boy. Not [ __ ] out of my league,
mate. No [ __ ] woman that has to use
[ __ ] filters is out of my league.
She's out of your league, you fat, ugly
virgin. That's why you're begging her.
I'm not the one begging her. You are.
You absolute virgin. I hate it when I
say the [ __ ] absolute because I just
[ __ ] shout. Anyways, bye-bye now,
Bye-bye now, [ __ ]
These people are [ __ ] really disabled
on here, bro.
Triple. These people are really disabled, lad.
They're really [ __ ] disabled on here, bro.
Yeah, proper proper disabled on here, bro.
Like I said,
I feel bad for them grints. I feel
really bad for them.
Feel really bad.
They're just [ __ ] autistic fat ugly
people with nothing. That's all they
are, bro. Fat, ugly, bongo people that
ain't got nothing in their lives. That's
what they are, bro.
Fat, ugly, disabled little low lives.
B, the rest of them. I'm not I'm not
listening to them self-projecting. They
only talk about themselves.
All they do is talk about theirelves.
These fat, ugly, low lives. They don't
talk about me. They talk about their [ __ ] selves.
They talk about their own lives, but
they're so disabled they don't even
realize they're talking about themselves.
I don't like going on that chat, bro. That [ __ ]
you know, that LJ chat, bro, because
it's just full of autistic [ __ ] ugly
people like this savvy boy, bro. PJ
abusing their birds and weather spoons
is mental. What are you gonna do about
it? You're going to do nothing about it,
bro. You're going to do nothing about it.
You will do nothing.
Yep. That's their life though, ain't it,
bro? What? That's their life.
I would never find a woman and settle
down ever. But anyways, yeah, the point
stand is they will. Yeah,
cuz they're no life. They they've got
nothing in their lives.
It's the same atmosphere here.
It's always the same atmosphere in this
[ __ ] community, isn't it?
They ain't got a life. They ain't got no
life at all.
And look at them talking about women,
bro. None of these have ever had a
woman. They're [ __ ] probably still
virgins. 90% of them on LJs.
Probably still virgins. >> Yeah.
Yeah, I know. And And they're old people
as well, you know.
And the thing is they're old people as well.
Yeah, they're older. They're old. These
people are older than me.
These [clears throat and snorts] people
are older than me, bro. They're like,
some of them are probably like 20 years
older than me. They're [ __ ] fat,
disabled, ugly mongos, bro. They ain't
got nothing in their lives. Absolutely
nothing. Skint to the [ __ ] eyeballs as well.
Skint to the [ __ ] eyeballs.
I know. I know. Yeah.
You know what that means? It's the same atmosphere.
[ __ ] mongos, bro. I'm not retaliating
to them anymore. [snorts]
And that Joseph Farra, have you noticed
how biased they are in here as well? The
Grinch. The Grinch.
They're very, very biased. Joseph Farra
said that he's not coming on my channel
anymore because I said I was going to go
to Thailand and didn't go to Thailand
and he has a problem with people lying. Um,
well, whatever you show them, they'll
pretend that you didn't show them it
because they're autistic with no life.
But anyways, um, he said, but then he
goes on large A's.
They're very, very biased on here as
well. Have you noticed that, Grinch?
They're very, very biased.
I think they're jealous of something.
Me, bro. These people deep down, I think
they're jealous of something.
I think they're jealous or something, bro.
That Jamie Thompson stalks me. I've had
to turn my simple I've had to turn my Sim off.
That fat ugly [ __ ] [ __ ] stalks me, bro.
But they've got a better life than me.
No, they don't have a better life than anyone. Yeah. [ __ ] madness.
I've had more women than everyone on
this community. They still talk [ __ ]
I've shown more money than everyone on
They still talk [ __ ] and make up stuff. Absolute virgins.
That's the only thing I can say, mate. Absolute virgins.
Yeah. You know what's so weird is that
I heard they were celebrating me losing
a 50 pound football bet. I'm thinking,
what the [ __ ]
That's how sad they are. They're losers.
Celebrating me losing a£50 football bet.
I'm thinking, what the [ __ ]
Like £50 is anything to me? They are
really sad losers, bro.
How you going to lose it?
How you going to lose?
How you going to lose? This charger is dodgy.
I think this is the receipt.
When did I buy it? August.
It can't have been. It had to. Is that
Was it August I bought that?
Doesn't seem like 3 months ago. Uh,
one second, bro.
Yeah, it must have been must have been the charger.
Yeah. One second, bro.
How are you going to lose it?
How you going to lose it? When you going
Really? Let me have a look at the virgin.
No, he's not. What channel?
Bloody is a bloody virgin live.
doesn't come up.
It doesn't come up, bro. Yeah, I'm on
it. It doesn't come up.
This charger is pissing me off, bro.
It's really pissing me off. One sec.
Must have ended it because it's not it's
not up there. Yeah,
I've just gone on it. I get my little
recorder out. My little evidence pack.
So, what do you think of USA? Izzy,
you've seen her now. Do you like her?
Trip H. I'll give you her number. You
can maybe try it with her if you want.
Mike, I haven't been out for Oi. Mike, I
went out not last week, the week before
that. I went out on Thursday. Uh, did
you see the approaching videos? I put a
protein video up and a lot of them said
they had boyfriends and I got two
numbers and one Snapchat and only one
number replied and they led me on.
So, I kind of gave up from there to be
honest. Same old. It's the same old
[ __ ] bro. Same [ __ ]
I won't be out again this month.
Pointless. Absolutely pointless, bro. I
got a banging headache as well.
Pointless, isn't it? That's the last
time I went out. Not last week, the week before that.
And it was proper
What is wrong with this [ __ ] [ __ ] charger, bro?
Yeah. Same old, isn't it?
Do you know who Trip You know what
Triple H is? Triple H. Do you know what it is?
You know it's a wrestler, isn't it?
You know it's a wrestler though, is it?
He wasn't my favorite wrestler. I know.
>> It was good though.
Oh, where's that [ __ ] version?
That's him in the picture. Uh,
now where are the cops?
How can you see a Chinese update when
I've already ate it?
No, girlfriend. Never talking about
yourself there. Bye. We're going to
ignore these little self projectors. Anyways,
we're going to start ignoring these people.
We're going to ignore these like self projectors now.
These little self-p projected fugly people
or seven neighbors have just uploaded a new video video.
Yeah, I used to have loads and loads of money, matey.
No, I stopped speaking to him after the bouncer thing.
I stopped drinking. I stopped talking to
him after the bouncer thing to be fair.
We kind of went our separate ways
cuz of um Yeah.
So, I just stopped from there.
Oh, he was just kissing his teeth at me
and being awkward, so I argued back with
him in it.
So yeah, and then he didn't like it
because the guy was black and can't be
wanted to get into it.
How are you going to lose it?
How you going to lose it,
Joker? How you going to lose it?
When you going to lose it?
Yeah, but you can't win with Timmy. Do
you remember wipe?
Well, you fought wrong.
You can't win with, you know, you can't
win with Timmy, right? Triple H. Remember why?
It's like playing a game of chess with a
pigeon. And even when you beat the
pigeon, it will [ __ ] all over the
chessboard and pretend it won. So
yeah, you can't um you can't win with with him. You like
you like my picture, Joker?
You like my picture, Joker?
Anyone like my picture? Grinch, you like
I found a name for him. I'm not going to
tell you what the name is,
but he's got a name.
I'm not telling you the name. Can't
can't disclose that. But he has got a name. Little copycat. Copycat.
A little copycat.
Oh, be dying earlier. Nope.
Could be. Like I said, I was going to
I'm going to give you USA is his number.
Triple H. Maybe you two can get together
and I don't know, make love.
You know, you can make love.
Do you want the joke? Do you want the Do
you want the link?
Oh, you want the box? Yeah. Box. Box. No, no.
Yeah, he's still in Thailand.
He said the other month he was about to
[ __ ] his underpants. Triple H. Yeah,
he's in Thailand. He couldn't get any
women here, so he [ __ ] off to Thailand.
Doka, come in. Bring your friends.
Who cares if she's real? She's [ __ ] stinking, son.
She's absolutely [ __ ] stinking, son.
Let me tell you how you know these
people have got no life, right? Triple H is that,
right? is that they they go for these
women on YouTube. Yeah, they obsess over
these women. Oh, she looks good. Oh, let
me try and meet you. Just one second. If
they actually had lives, they wouldn't
care about any woman on here. Me, I
could just go down to Waxies and meet a
new woman if I wanted to. Not that I
would because they're all [ __ ] But,
you know, I could go out today. I mean,
it's Sunday today. Even today, I could
go out and go and meet someone because
I'm not ugly and scared like these
people are here. That's how you know the
difference between people that have no life
um and people that have a life
because they wouldn't care about any
woman on here if they had a life. They
could just go out and I I would just go
out. But it shows like be he's scared,
he's ugly, he's got no money because
anyone that isn't like that wouldn't be on here.
You know what I mean?
I'm doing what it like with the women and stuff.
I can't tell you that. Top secret.
No, this charger, mate. [ __ ] hell.
What is wrong with it?
I've got a feeling it's going to
pack up with H.
You coming in, Joker?
You coming in, Captain? [laughter]
He's told this story a million times before. Triple,
he needs to let go. He said he's told
the same story time and time time again. You [snorts]
want the Can you buy me the Samsung
Galaxy Fold um 7, please, Grinch?
You can get it from Argus.
Do they have an Argos where you live? Preach.
Really? He's told that about a million
times. The same story. Bro,
can you buy me the Do they have an Argos
where you live? Crier H.
And our goose.
Do they have one?
Do they have an Argos where you live, lad?
Yeah, they have an Argos here, too.
I like my picture.
[laughter] It's a copycat.
It observes and copies. Yep.
You should become a footballer. Triple H.
Why don't you become a footballer?
I think you'll be a good footballer. You
like your football, don't you?
Uh, long story, bro.
Would you do it? Would you do Uber Eats
or Just Eat? I done it for 10 hours. I
made 90 pound, bro. And one Sunday it
took me [ __ ] eight hours to make 50
pound. I was [ __ ] tired, bro. I was shattered.
It takes a lot of energy, bro. I made 90
twice in like 9 to 10 hours. Oh, [ __ ]
hell, bro. It was long, bro. [ __ ] long.
I don't reckon you could do it, Triple H.
I was doing it all over London, like
every part of London.
Like, it was mad. I was doing it all in
central London and [ __ ]
I went everywhere in London, bro. Far
out. Would you do that job, Triple?
How much do you think you can make in a
week if I think you could make 500 in a
week, isn't it? Yeah. [snorts]
Yeah. You have to do some mad hours, bro.
You'd have to do some mad hours in it.
Would you do it then?
The delivery trip Hen
you could do that job. I don't think you
could do it, mate. It's [ __ ] tiring. Yeah.
I had £1,700 last month. Trip H. I had £1,700.
I had to buy some trainers and some
jeans and stuff. Oh gosh.
Yeah. I had to buy some things.
[snorts and clears throat] But the thing
is with that job, bro, it takes a lot of
energy. A lot of energy, bro. Oh,
I remember I I went out one day at
10:00. I come back at like 11, bro.
Yeah, but obviously I took a break in
between. I took like an hour's break.
I'd stop at like
1 or two, maybe. Turn the phone off,
charge the phone up an hour, start
again. It was long, bro.
I'd come back at like 11:00 at night, bro. Mad,
can I join you? What? Next week, triple.
What? as we go.
Oh yeah, why not? It's Sunday, isn't it?
Yeah, it's Sunday, bro. Why not give it
a whirl? I would.
You you going to do some approaches or
Yeah, I'm not drinking, bro. No.
December, I will. But not no.
How many beers you going to have, lad?
I could join you. I could get up there
and join you if you want.
Well, bless you then.
Well, you going to spend like a 100 quid or
you going to spend like a one?
Bless you then.
Well, bless you then. You spend about
20. Oh, bless.
Stay off the bloody gear though.
Right. Stay off the bloody gear. I know
what you like. Yeah. copycat.
And another thing, try not to be a
copycat as well. Trip, we don't like copycats.
Yeah, we don't like copycats.
But my hands when I done that job, you
know, my hands were swollen, bro.
Because where like you're constantly on
the bike, you need gloves, bro. My my
[ __ ] hands were [ __ ] I'd come
back, mate. I'd come back black as soot
triple. I'd come back right at the end
of the day. [ __ ] black as soot
from all like the oil and [ __ ] you
know your hands on the bike. [ __ ]
black as s mate. Black as s. That's how
you know you've done a [ __ ] hard
day's work when you come back [ __ ]
black as s.
Black as [ __ ] sick, mate.
Yeah, I used to like going waxies on a Sunday. Waxies.
I can't anyways cuz I need to go to
barbers and [ __ ] So Yeah. [clears throat]
Is Lord J still live? No.
Where is everyone?
I want Autumn to come on my live stream.
We need to have a little talk.
Oh, guess she just replied. [laughter]
I could be in some [ __ ] here, mate. Could [laughter]
be even some [ __ ] here, mate. One sec. Almost done. >> [laughter]
>> Yeah, they'll be after us for money. H
So tired, bro.
Oh, and I didn't get rejected by an
escort either. That escort told me to
come and see her yesterday.
and I couldn't be bothered.
She was given attitude. She didn't
reject me. See how they twist things on
here? They're little weasels on this
community. Absolute little weasels.
How much money did you put on it?
How much did you put on it?
This escort I've been with is so sexy, bro.
You've only got 60 You've only got 60
quid left. What the [ __ ]
Is that how much money you got left? £200. [clears throat]
So if you lose, you have
So if you lose, you'll have like 560 basically then. Yeah. Nice mom.
Large skint [ __ ] skin flint
into a [ __ ] skin flint.
So, how much is that return then? That
200 pound bet. Yeah,
it is Timmy.
It is Timmy, bro. Yeah.
Who are you? Are you caring? Yeah. Oh, really?
Anyone joining or what?
I'll be back later.