These people are really disabled on here, bro.
They're proper proper disabled on here, bro.
I didn't know I had a sister that looked
brown. That's interesting to me. These
people really are sad disabled little
bully victims. Yeah.
A lot of self-p projectors on this community.
A lot of self-p projecting little low
lives on this community, bro.
What's going on here?
Yeah, I didn't know I had a brown sister.
That's news to me, lad. Wow.
Sad, sad bastards on here.
Yeah, the UK big the UK's biggest
nonser. That's you you're talking about.
You are the nons. You are the m
just like Oh, [ __ ] me.
Just like uh we all fat ugly people that
ain't got no life.
That's why you're sat on here putting up
random people saying that's my sister. I
didn't know that was my sister, mate. I
didn't know that was my sister. You
learn something new every day.
These people are severely disabled. You know,
we just talk about these disabled people in here.
They get everything wrong. That's That's
not my sister. What the [ __ ]
Family of mters. You are the mon. Have
you looked in the mirror? You fat ugly [ __ ]
[ __ ] even sound like a [ __ ] spat, bro.
I would love to know where one of these
people live, bro. Really would love to know
where one of these people live.
I would love to know where one of them
where one of them live, bro.
Like their actual address, cuz you know
they're little shits in real life.
People like V, they're little bully
victims. fat, ugly, handicapped little
mongos that would never ever even look
at anyone the wrong way, but behind the keyboard.
Well, we know we know what they're like, you know, madness, bro.
Sad, fat, ugly keyboard warrior. Little skint mongos.
Yeah, for real.
But you you do feel bad for them though
to be at the same time you feel bad for
them to be honest.
They haven't got anything in life.
[ __ ] Mongs on here, bro. Absolute
Mongs on here. But I am actually uh
I'm gone tomorrow for a couple weeks 100%.
It's Monday tomorrow. So yeah,
sad little disabled people on here. Sad
little skint disabled people.
They got no life.
No [ __ ] life. Yeah.
Yeah. We're just talking about these
little low lives on here, Mark. These
little fat ugly mongos that ain't got a
life. Sad, pathetic people.
Yeah, it's good, bro.
I didn't go out.
That's what you're asking. I didn't go out drinking.
No, I'm taking a break from that, bro.
For a while.
Yeah, I'm taking a taking a break from that, lad.
They're repeating fat, ugly bongos,
seaside mark. And you know, people like
B, they're just fat, ugly, disabled
people that wouldn't even look at people
the wrong way in the real world. That's
what makes me laugh, bro. But behind
their little keyboard, they seem to
think they're something.
This guy's put up something, bro.
Yeah. Saying that's my sister. That's
not my [ __ ] sister. You [ __ ]
[ __ ] What the [ __ ]
Put some rand.
Serious question. How do you put up with
being bullied day in day out? Uh, I cope
with it fine because I don't get
bullied. You people are the ones that
get bullied. You people are the ones
that are sat at home all day fat and
ugly. Ain't got no money, ain't got no
life. The only people that get bullied
is you people, which is why you do what
you do every day. Little self-reflecting
ugly fat [ __ ] The only people that
get bullied is you people every day your
lives. Since coming out your mom's [ __ ]
since you literally come out of your m's
fanny, you've been bullied your whole
life and you're still getting bullied.
You people do nothing on here but repeat. No. Um
it's a thing basically you know nonsleg seaside mark.
Um he said that if I didn't like car I was gay.
So I said he a little copycat copycat.
You'll be in the crowd. Um he basically
copies people. Um so he's he's known as the copycat.
He observes and copies and he's he
copied my holiday to Amsterdam as well.
Yeah, he's nothing but a little copycat.
He's nothing but a little copycat.
Yeah, Mark. Nothing but a little copycat.
You still gamble, Mark?
It's so mad how I I've been on here for years, Mark.
You remember me when I was like 22. I'm
[ __ ] 28 now. Yeah. Yeah, bro.
You don't gamble anymore. No,
I just bet on the football sometimes, bro.
Oh, that's good, bro. That's good. Yeah.
Oh, do you want to come in the hangouts, Timmy?
This community annoys me, Mark. I don't
I can't be on it for long. I have to
take like a week or two weeks off.
You as you know, Mark, as as you know,
it's the same atmosphere.
And he's blocked again.
You can't do it cuz then they f No,
you can't do it, mate. Because they
block your phone. I'm using a Samsung
Galaxy um Fold 6 and I got it on
contract because I I wanted the phone
and I was paying it and I couldn't uh
pay it any well. Long story short and
they block the phone. So they block your
phone. It doesn't work because if you
stop paying the phone, they block the
as in you can only use on Wi-Fi.
So I can't call or anything unless I'm on Wi-Fi.
And they block it in steps as well. So
you can do that, but they'll block your phone. So
I'll never go on a contract ever again.
I like my phone to be my phone.
And obviously if you have a contract and
you suddenly stop paying it for whatever
reason, they will block your phone. So
if they block your phone, it ain't your
phone. You know what I mean? Bro, I need
a new I need a new phone. I'm trying to
think of what phone to get. [ __ ]
I got a Samsung Galaxy Fold 6. They're
[ __ ] They're so good. These phones
are so good, bro. But it's like £1,500.
I don't want to pay £1,500 for a phone.
So, I'm trying to decide. I was going to
get refurbished iPhone, but then I'm
worried about the battery and
so I don't know what to do really.
when it comes to um Yeah. What phone do
you have, Mark?
What phone do you have, lad?
Maybe it depends what provider you're
with. I was with three and they
definitely definitely blocked my phone. iPhone 16.
Yeah, that's Yeah, you can get that
phone for like £500.
Yeah, depends what what what
provider are you with. I was with three
and they definitely definitely blocked
the phone, bro. This phone I'm using now is blocked. Yeah.
That's weird because I'm I'm with I was
No. Was I with three?
No, I was I was with O2. Sorry, I was
So O2 definitely definitely blocks your phone.
I'm with free now. So, but uh yeah, they
definitely block your phone. If you
don't pay your bill, they block your
phone, bro. After a while,
have you seen the Samsung Galaxy Fold
Mark? They're the best phones going.
Samsung Galaxy Fold's the best, bro. If
you can ever afford it, get one.
It's a flagship phone. You know what a
flagship phone is? Cand.
It's basically top range phone. Yeah.
Yeah. Fold something fold. I've got
I've had it a year now.
Yeah, I won. Um I mean I've been lucky
with the football.
The last time I played roulette
properly, I put £100 in mark. I got to £500.
Yeah, I got to 500. I didn't play again
since. I've won a couple of football
bets. 120 to 380, 120 to 370,
but I lost 50 yesterday and I lost 130
weeks ago, but I'm still up because at
the start of the season, I won some
money as well.
So, and I bought some jeans and
trainers. So, I'm still up somewhere,
but somewhere along the line.
The only way you can win on gambling
these days, I think, is uh
is football, bro. Both team. Well, like
just the football generally
or real life casinos maybe. That's
that's the only way.
Yeah, I put 100. I got to 500, but I was
I felt lucky with that.
500 from 100.
It was good. Yeah.
Look at my beard, M.
I'm [ __ ] hairy, bro. I need to go to the bars.
Dude, the barabers, bro. Look at the
state of my hair, bro. [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, man. Look at that.
Look, I got some scissors earlier and
just done that
[ __ ] just randomly. Bro,
you all right, Captain?
Do you like my picture, Steven Howard?
You like my picture, Steven Howard?
It's the little cat. You like it?
Have a picture.
I wonder if Triple H went out in the end.
Mark, look at me, bro.
I done this.
I done this earlier. I just randomly cut some.
I need a [ __ ] shave, bro.
I don't feel right when I haven't had a
shave and that bro had a haircut. You
feel weird in it.
I smell dusty.
I smell dusty showers. Yeah,
I Chinese. I feel hungry again. What the [ __ ]
Oh, you're a puppet.
Are you going to lose it?
Even how it look, bro. My beard is so long.
It's [ __ ] mad, isn't it? Virgin boy
can't have a beard like that,
dude. Virgin boy can't wear that.
It's annoying, bro.
So long. annoy him. Yeah.
These people in this community are so
disabled. Stephen Howard,
they're really really disabled.
[snorts] Did you go out Triple H?
They really are disabled on this community, bro.
They really are [ __ ] disabled on
here. They put up some random brown
person and said it's my sister.
What the [ __ ]
And they're saying that it's my sister,
bro. That's not my [ __ ] sister, man.
These people are disabled. Steven
Howard. Very disabled.
What disabled on here, bro? [sighs]
Nothing, bro. Just chilling.
Just chilling, bro. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm just chilling, lad.
[ __ ] they're disabled on here, bro.
I want to try and get Monty on.
I want to try to get money on triple
Oh, I don't think there's enough milk
for cereal though. [ __ ] drunk all the [ __ ] milk.
That's horrible. That is it. Greasy.
Greasy. Grapes. Oh, there is some milk.
There's some milk. I didn't I Oh, what?
You ate all the [ __ ] corn flakes? [ __ ] hell. Hey.
Oh, I ate all the corn flakes, bro.
I wanted I wanted to have some bastard cornflakes. Oh,
you ever just want some You ever just
fancy some bastard cornflakes?
Yeah, but like do you ever sometimes
grieve? I don't know what you have, but
you just fancy some bastard corn flakes. [ __ ] hell.
Same with BMR. Disabled no mate. Billy no mates.
Fat ugly people that's been bullied
their whole life. That's why they come
on here, bro. It's not only him.
wide and long face. What are you talking about?
He's not the only one, Dad.
What about that B? That [ __ ] fat
stinky housebound virgin that's been
bullied his whole life.
Bullied on YouTube their whole life.
These people, these haters are people
that's been bullied their whole life.
Depressed bully victims.
So they come on here and try to make
people feel like them
cuz they're depressed. depressed life
losers that got [ __ ] all in their lives.
So they need this YouTube. It's
everything to them, mate.
I feel [ __ ] I wanted some corn flakes, bro.
[ __ ] ate everything.
[ __ ] hell. Look at my beard.
Do you like it?
Yeah, cuz they're sad little virgins on here.
Why Steven Howard? Do you know that Autumn
V was begging her earlier saying, "Oh, I
can verify it's actually a woman." And
all I thought was, "What an absolute
virgin." You know what I'm like, mate. Absolute virgins
on here, it absolute virgins.
You know what I'm like with um Steven Howard.
You know what I'm bloody like? Absolute virgins.
You like cornflakes. Triple H.
Fancy a bowl of [ __ ] corn flakes.
Yeah, because they're little virgins
that can't get women. They're too ugly.
Steven Howard, do you know why though?
It's because they're too ugly to go out
and meet any women like VI. He's a
[ __ ] fat ugly bongo that ain't got a life.
That's why they Yeah, because they don't
get wh they can't get a woman cuz
they're too ugly. Yeah, man.
They're [ __ ] [ __ ] Just messaged them.
Yeah, I just messaged them, bro.
They're [ __ ] [ __ ] on the
community, bro. [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] fat, ugly people. They ain't got no life. of me.
Any [ __ ] job?
You like my cat?
Don't do anything in front of it,
Stephen. I would because it will copy her.
The cat will copy her. >> [snorts]
>> No, you can see my message, bro. [ __ ]
I'm not calling people, bro.
Nah, these people are [ __ ] spastics on here.
Yeah, they copy people as well. Stephen Howard,
you see my message? Send him to [ __ ] join, bro. >> [ __ ]
man. I don't know if that's really him.
>> Do you keep asking me to join you shitty
box all the time? I don't want nothing
to do with
>> I want to I want to talk to you,
>> man. You're a self-reflector, PJ.
>> Why? What? What have I said now?
>> Why you always repeat the same [ __ ]
every day? Talk about the same shitty
subject every day. You're a boring bastard.
>> I'm talking I was talking about these people.
>> Yeah, every day you're talking about
these people. That's all what these are
on your level. Most of these peeps on here.
>> Why is that
warmed me skin ain't got no life sat on
YouTube every day just like yourself?
>> I'm I'm Wait, one second. I'm Hold on.
Hold on. I'm not skiing.
>> You're not skiing?
>> No, I'm just chilling out for a bit,
bro. I don't need to go out, you know?
I'm going out until December now. Why?
>> So you So, so, so, so you're not skiing.
So, you're going out under
>> I just want to have a little break from
the drinking. Why? Why would I be skinn?
Why would Have you seen my trainers and
my jeans? I bought my mom some Ugg boots
as well. Why would I be skinned?
>> Well, it's going for cold walk. Have you
seen each other's eyebrow?
But why would I? Yeah, but mine was
Yeah, I did. But mine cost more than yours.
>> How much did yours cost, PV?
>> 210 quid.
>> Yeah, mine cost 200 quid.
>> There you go.
>> Yeah, but what I'm saying is how so how
could I be skinned? What the [ __ ]
Why would I be skinn? No way. I'm not
skin like these people. I went out two
weeks ago. I went out three weeks in a
row. Why am I skinned? Huh?
You've got caught in a couple of days.
[sighs and gasps]
Where's he gone? Monty.
Oh, I thought you kic me then. You
bastard. Come on. Like get
>> you. You should be You should show You
should show me some respect for helping
you out. You know,
>> you show you respect for I would never
show you respect. We reason.
>> I came I came I came to Birmingham and
bailed you out and this is the thanks I get.
>> Bailed me out. The [ __ ] you talked about
my kids the last couple of days and
[ __ ] Come on.
>> Yeah, but you've spoken about my sister.
You're [ __ ] clown PJ. No second chances.
>> You got you got you got caught on the
27th. Are you scared?
>> Am I scared? No. And it's not the 27th, actually.
>> Well, you keep changing the dates.
>> Who does
>> you? You said it was the 27th last
month. Now you're saying it's the 27th
of this month. So, when is it?
>> Not even the 27th.
>> Well, it's this month.
>> It's this month. No, it's not this month. No.
>> So, you're playing games then? Because
last month cuz last month you said it
was last month, then you say it's this
month. So, what? You make up your mind, isn't it?
Well, I can't make up the court's mind.
>> Yeah, but you must know when you when
you go in court.
>> I know when I'm going in court.
>> So, it's so it's next month.
>> No, it's not even next month.
>> So, it's next year.
>> Basically, next next two year.
>> I think I don't think you can hack prison, mate.
>> EJ, I can't explore prison ter.
Yeah. Well, obviously I don't want to go
to prison, so I'm not lying. Is it?
>> Yeah, but all this self-reflection you
do on women, you will be going pretty soon.
>> No, it's be mate. Hey, do you see that
channel that keeps posting about me and you?
>> I don't care. The old That's what that's
all about content they've got.
>> Yeah, but you've seen it though, is it?
>> But you've seen it though. >> Huh?
>> What? PJ,
>> you've seen it though, is it? It's
called the UK's biggest nonser. Yeah,
you've seen it though, ain't it?
>> Yeah, I've seen that account with a
picture of my daughter on it. Yeah.
>> Well, it's changed now to your Well,
it's actually changed now to your mom.
But yeah, it post of us.
>> Yeah. I don't I don't The pedals, PJ,
they're pedals. They are penos. It's a
penal community. They don't get it. Penal community.
>> Yeah, obviously I do.
>> And then you're one of them. You're self on women.
How does that doesn't even make sense?
>> That don't make sense. You can't get a
woman meaning your age or emotion on
women. You [ __ ] go on about them
every day. Why do you talk about women
every day on YouTube?
>> Uh I I don't talk about them. I was on I
was on TikTok with some guy who's
talking and I was I was I was having a
debate with them.
>> Don't be left.
Why do people say that I can't get women
when I've already been with women
multiple times? I've been with multiple
multiple multiple multiple women. I
don't know why people keep saying that.
Multiple multiple multiple women.
I don't I talk [ __ ] about women because
I think they're [ __ ] and I think
they don't get the hate that they deserve.
Um, and that's my opinion on it. And I'm
not a virgin.
I've had sex. I've had more women than
most of these people in this community.
Yeah. An incel. Yeah. Okay. Whatever.
I will say what I think.
You know, I don't I don't agree with it.
And I've had women I've had more women
than anyone that calls me. Anyone that
tries to call me, I've had more women than them.
That's not delusional. That's facts. I
don't agree with anything that they do.
I think they're toxic. I think they lead
people on. I think they're nasty.
Um, and I I believe that um because
they're my experiences.
What else are you supposed to [ __ ]
What What else are you supposed to think?
Are you supposed to lick their ass or something, bro?
I think they're [ __ ] I think they
leave people on. I think they get away
with everything. And I don't agree with
them. And I've had women and I've had
sex with people that weren't even escorts. So, um,
how many escorts would I say I have? Uh,
hundreds, bro. Hundreds.
[ __ ] hundreds, lad.
I'll get a woman. I don't want a woman.
I don't want a [ __ ] woman. I've
already had women. They're [ __ ]
You know, I'm not a copycat. I'm not
someone that has to copy people.
You can get blocked. Bye-bye,
weirdo. So, yeah, as a UK asylum, I
don't get these people, bro. Um,
is is there is there not a thing uh
where you can
not like women because what they're like
and still have had women or are you
automatically an incel? So, are you
automatically labeled as something
because you don't agree with these
people? I mean, that's not really fair,
is it? They are [ __ ] and I know cuz
I've dealt with them. So, what I'm a
virgin? Have I never been with a woman?
I hate them. I hate them because what
they're like. They're [ __ ] And the
more I think about it, the more,
you know, you realize I do hate them.
They are [ __ ] They're my
experiences. That's why I don't bother with them.
That's that's that they are absolute [ __ ]
you know. So
the times that I was trying, you know, I
didn't think that the same way, you
know. Now I really really believe it, bro. you know.
Yes, but I've had women. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no. But I've had women.
I've had women and I still don't like them
because they are [ __ ] So, yeah.
Don't call me skin. How can I be
skinned? Why would I be skinned?
Money man's just a snake, bro. I swear to God.
I mean, I just I just came to that
conclusion after you gave them so you
gave them the benefit of the doubt for
so many years. I think it was I think it
I think it was warranted in the end to
have that opinion on them. I think it
was warranted in the end. Someone like
me who's been up and down the country
meeting all of these women. I mean, it's
very, very warranted to think this way.
No. Is it not warranted to think this
way or are you supposed to think a
different way? Why would you think a
Why would you think a different way if
they're your experiences?
It's that bad now I don't even use escorts. So,
I generally mean it when I say I hate
them. They're [ __ ] What? Why do
you think I don't go out, bro?
I don't I'm not really much of a
drinker. Why do you think I don't go out
drinking? because they are they are
generally generally all the same. And
you don't need to be a virgin to think that,
you know, you don't need to be a virgin
or anything to to to think that way. I
don't know why there there's a there's a
stigma on you. You need to
[ __ ] I'll be lying to you. If I
told you right now, oh, not all women
are like that. There all of these
things, I'd be lying to you. I would
generally generally be lying to you. You
don't want me to lie to you, do you? So,
there's no positives. There's no light
of the end of the tunnel. I've given up
with it, bro. I don't care about it.
I've had more women than Monty. I've had
more women than Nons. I've had more
women than LJ.
I hate them.
When I done a sum when I done a summary
of my experiences, I hate them, bro.
I generally generally hate them. Whether
I could get them or whether I couldn't
get them or whether I wanted one or
didn't want one. I hate them. Simple as that. So,
the amount of bad experiences I've had and confrontations um
you know that [ __ ] thing is
completely made up. The reason I don't
go on about it is because it's immature.
Um, no. There was no [ __ ] offered.
That's [ __ ] The reason I never ever
spoke about that is because it's it's so
immature. It's not even worth trying to
trying to talk about. It's immature. It
never happened. It's boring. So, that's
why I don't I don't I don't bring it up.
He's just a little liar, bro. And let me
tell you something. He will never do
anything. Monty will never do anything
to me, bro. Think about it, right? If
he's got such a problem with what people
said about his kids, I've met this guy
two times and he would get battered,
bro. He wouldn't beat me. Monty would
never beat me, bro. Never beat me. Not
in an actual fight. It would never happen
cuz I was a [ __ ] house, bro.
He is a [ __ ] house. Trust me, I'm not no
rice, bro. He'd get smacked all over.
Same thing with that Prime, bro. Don't
forget that Prime thing was two years
ago. That was a couple of years ago now,
bro. Times change, people change,
you know, people change.
And when I was almost homeless, I became
a very, very strong person.
When I was almost homeless and I went
back to that that old house, I basically
fended for myself. So there's a big
difference now, bro. Yeah,
but I don't agree with
I don't agree with people defending women
because they're my experiences as an
unbiased person. Is that not fair? Is
that not fair to have an opinion as an
unbiased person? I think they're [ __ ]
I think they're [ __ ] I think they're
evil. I think they're toxic. I think
toxic is the main thing. Toxic,
they're all the same as well. A lot of
them are evil. Um, that's how I think.
That's that's that's my experiences.
That's not how I think. So
to think any other way, you'd be mad. To
think that these women are any
different, you'd be mad. You'd be absolutely mad.
You'd think you'd be mad if you thought
any other woman was different. They are
all the same.
Same way, same mannerisms, same everything.
They are literally all the same.
I don't even like talking about it, bro.
Why did this guy bring it up? I don't
want to talk about it, bro.
It's annoying. I hate even talking about
them. It's [ __ ] annoying.
I ain't talking about them scumbags, bro.
I hate talking about him, bro. >> Yeah.
So yeah, women are all the same, bro.
That's why I gave up.
Yeah, they are all definitely all the same
about it, bro. I ain't having arguments you know.
Why? Why are you Why are we even having
arguments about it? It's up for them to
prove they're different. Not for
anything, not for anyone else to say,
and they can't
see how how I've been all right lately. Steven Howard,
cuz I'm not dealing with women.
What a change, eh? What a change of
someone when they don't deal with women.
That just goes to show how toxic the
whole [ __ ] thing is. That tells you
how toxic it is in the first place. Gladness. Yeah.
These people that defend women are absolute virgins.
Absolute virgins. People that defend
women. Absolute virgins.
They're absolute virgins. [snorts]
What did Monty say? Triple H is a pedo
community, isn't it?
What do you say is a pedo community?
Look who's live again.