Greasy is going to [ __ ] love this.
I've come across another feminist. Oh
[ __ ] This is what I was saying
yesterday. All of these people exist and
don't exist. That's the most scariest
thing about it nowadays is most of these people, they exist.
They exist more rather than that they
don't exist. these people that constantly
[ __ ] defend the women. But in this
case, this person was a uh well is a feminist
some of me [ __ ]
So madness, absolute [ __ ] madness, matey.
So yeah, we will love this.
I want to know why these people
continuously defend women
even when they're shown they're wrong on
on occasions. I would love to know why
they do it, you know.
So, I think I need to do another video
of this and I need to actually leave it up there.
I woke up to a load of [ __ ] [ __ ] Um,
and look, all of these messages again
just completely got dismissed as per
usual. Sometimes we need to like
I was talking to this woman on Reddit, right?
And uh I was I was she said that she's
had bad experience. I was saying how
I've had bad experience and I showed her
my struggles and basically as soon as I
said, "Oh, like women go for like
[ __ ] and ret like this and that."
All of a sudden, she just wrote me a
paragraph completely dismissing my
struggles and making stuff up.
Um, all it is is a pity party for women.
At the end of the day, when they try and
sit there and say about a man trying to
get a pity party, that's exactly what
these people are trying to do every
single time they they keep victimizing
them time and time and time and time
again. Right. This woman was like, "Oh,
um yeah, your approaches were your
approaches were [ __ ] uh good. It's a
good way to approach someone." Then I've
showed her like women that's led me on
and [ __ ] multiple times and she said,
"Oh, well, the way you approach them is
very pushy with a negative attitude
about it." just resorted to making stuff
up. So, this is what I'm trying to say.
They can't admit that they're wrong.
I don't understand. Like, they can never
admit that they're wrong ever. Ever.
It's not even like they said, "Oh, in
five of these you're wrong, and in five
of them they're wrong." Nope. They won't
take any accountability for anything
that they do just because they've got a
[ __ ] between their legs. It's [ __ ]
mental, bro. I can't believe what I was reading.
They just resort to making stuff up and
dismissing the struggles.
They don't. They don't. No one will. And
there's no one that understands. All
they're going to keep doing is
victimizing them, making excuses for
them. And I'm [ __ ] tired of it. This
is why I don't get into these arguments
anymore. I didn't think I'd be getting
into any of these arguments anymore.
Why do they keep dismissing people's
struggles? It's [ __ ] annoying. You
know, I asked this my mom this earlier.
She says, "Oh, cuz they're ignorant.
because they're ignorant. I said, "No, I
want to know right here, right now. Why
do these people keep dismissing my struggles?"
I've asked this about a million times
and I'm losing my voice when I'm asking
it. Why do you keep defending them?
[ __ ] sake, bro. Someone must have an
answer. The fact that we don't have any
unbiased people now is very, very scary.
Why are you talking about the
undatables? We're not talking about the
undatables. We're talking about these
[ __ ] keep dismissing people's struggles.
No one cares, bro.
They literally don't do not like being
wrong. Oh, and another thing yesterday,
I was speaking to someone on Reddit and
they said, "Oh, yeah. Some women don't
give uh [ __ ] because it's they do
what they like." And you get you never
guess what I got told when I said, um, I
don't I don't give women oral.
Bye-bye, bastard. We're not dealing with
you little self projectors today. No one
cares about you. Um, [snorts]
you never guess what they said. Gay
homo. If you don't lick a woman's fatty,
you're gay. But if a woman doesn't give
a [ __ ] it's just what they like.
It's so biased. How does not how does
anyone not see how sexist this is?
I got called weak-minded
um because I didn't want to keep dealing
with toxic women year after year after
year as a 28-year-old man.
Skint again. That's self projecting,
Kevin. That's not even going to get a response.
Self projectors don't get a don't get a
response. Um, anyways, so yeah,
that's crazy. So, I guess she's a fair I
it's frowned upon. Yeah, it is. It's
frowned upon where I'm from. I know
exactly what it is, bro. But it doesn't
matter whether it's frowned upon or not.
I know what it is. It's frowned upon.
But if you don't like eating [ __ ] why
should you be classed as gay, but if
they don't want to suck a dick? Oh well,
that's completely fine. They just don't
want to do it,
you know? They just don't want to do it.
The double standards is insane. You'd be
very, very lucky. You would be very
found someone nowadays that weren't
biased. you'd be very very very very
lucky because they're either in sales or
they're people that just suck up to
women. So you never really get people
that unbiased now except for me. I'm
unbiased even though people want to try
and call me names. They just they they
just defend anything that they do. Why?
I don't understand why. And even then
they still kick you from the podcast.
It's not even like they said, "Oh, you
was wrong here. They were wrong here.
You were wrong here. They were wrong
here. They never say that. They never
think that they're wrong. It's mad.
Even though you show them blatant
evidence, blatant black and white evidence.
It's madness. It's is it It's madness
with these people. She's a feminist. I
guess she's had bad experiences with men
and she um
you know it's like as soon as I showed
her women doing wrong, bam, she she went
at me. Why? Cuz I said that women go for
[ __ ] and then moan that all men are
the same. Well, they do do that. Well,
they do do that. So, if you don't like
the truth, then don't don't come my way.
That is the truth.
That that is the truth that they go for
the same stereotypical [ __ ]
right? Just cuz they don't abuse them at first.
No, no, this was from Reddit. Just
because you don't join, just just
because you you don't know that the
person's an abuser from the get- go, it
doesn't know you know you don't know
what they're about.
So, stop making it seem like you don't
know what these men are like. [ __ ] off,
mate. Cuz if that was the case, you
would be people would be going for me,
you know? So, it's it's which I don't
want them to. I don't care. But I'm
saying as an example, if you was to use
an example when I've tried in the past,
it's [ __ ] It's absolute bollocks, mate.
They all suck up to women.
And I'm not accepting no double
standards. [ __ ] the double standards.
It's [ __ ] disgusting. I'm not no
[ __ ] s. I'm not no [ __ ] white
knight trying to say that I'm gay
because I don't want to lick Fanny. But
then if they don't want to suck dick,
oh, it's just because they don't want to do it.
[ __ ] it is mad. The double standards are mad.
She can't own me again because she
didn't own me in the first place.
She didn't own me in the first place. So I mean so
I hate them me. I hate women, bro. I
[ __ ] hate them.
Oh, this guy's
I hated me.
And I'm an unbiased person. I'm an
unbiased person. Remember, I've had
women and I've had sex before. You try
and say, "And I hate them." That's what
happens when you've been dealing with
women for years. You actually know what they're like.
So, I know what they're like. So, uh
that's why. And I'm completely unbiased as well. So,
It's madness that is.
Cuz let's just say that you're wrong,
right? On some of these voice on some of these messages.
There's no way you was wrong every
single [ __ ] time. Let's just say that
you was right on three out of 10 or
maybe two out of 10 of these
screenshots, right? Let's use this
analogy. Let's just let's say that you
was right on two or three of them. Nope.
Nope. Nope. Nope. Straight to
victimizing women. Nope. Nope. Nope.
Nope. blah blah blah blah even though
they blatantly blatantly played games
and led you on.
It's like anyone would think that they
don't take accountability for anything.
Why is that? Why is that? They're not
children. They're not babies. They're
adults like men. This is the bit I don't
understand. They're not innocent. Like
men are not innocent. Why do you keep
pushy footing around them like they're
babies or they're some kind of toddler
that don't know what the [ __ ] they're doing?
Banger, bro. It's banger. It's what I'm
saying. It's the truth.
It is the [ __ ] truth. You know,
I'm sick of these white knights and
these simps and these [ __ ] feminist women.
It's [ __ ] disgusting. It's
disgusting, mate. Absolutely disgusting.
I [ __ ] hate him, bro. And then you
tried and then you're being called weak
minded because you don't want to deal
with toxic women because you don't want
to deal with their toxic [ __ ] You're
weak. Said the s, you know, I'm going to
do a video to all you s white knights
and feminists out there, right?
That's what I'm going to do, mate. And
I'm going to send it to every [ __ ]
[ __ ] that I've argued with. Yeah. I'll
probably even start my own podcast cuz
I'm sick of their [ __ ] you know?
And some women I think some women are
just like where they've had bad
experiences with men. The men that they
very much choose, mind you, um they seem
to think women are all innocent. So when
you say that a woman is done wrong, they
go straight on the defense mode. Oh, oh
well they don't know what they're doing.
And then you proceed to show them a load
of [ __ ] what they've done and they still
deny it. [laughter]
You know, madness.
It's mad trying to say someone's gay
because they don't s because they don't
want to because they don't want to um
because they don't want to eat fatty.
But if a woman don't want to suck dick,
that's completely fine.
Not given oral does not make someone
gay. And you know what I called that
guy? I called him a little copycat. Yes,
I did. I showed him a picture of the
ginger cat and I was like,
"You little copycat." I said, "That's
you, you little copycat.
That's you, you little copycat.
You need to stop the skin stuff, bro.
It's getting really boring now.
The self projecting repeating is getting
really really boring now, bro. Stop it.
It's it's really really boring now.
So yeah, I called him uh I called him a little copycat.
There was someone on Reddit. I called
him a little copycat. He said I'm gay if
I don't eat vagina. You little copycat.
That's what I said to him. You little
copycat. [ __ ] anything to fit in with
a crowd. It's the same as saying [ __ ]
Chev Car was not attractive and you're
gay. That's copying that's copying the
crowd. That's copying the street brawl
crowd wanted to fit in. They want to
feel left out. We all know another
certain person that likes to fit in. Oh,
I showed them a picture of this cat, bro. Obviously, [screaming] copycat.
You little copycat.
You a little copycat. You a little
So if you don't like giving someone
oral, you're gay. So that means you
automatically like dick. Really? Do you
know what I think people really need to
start learning the definition of gay?
I really really think people need to
look in the urban dictionary if they
still exist. Not being gay doesn't mean
that you like that you don't like Cheryl
Cole. Not being gay doesn't mean that
you don't like eating some [ __ ]
smelly ass funny that you don't know
where it's been. That's not gay. I can
assure you that doesn't automatically
mean that you like dick. You little
copycat. You little copycat.
You're a little copycat.
That's I did call him that. I called him
a little copycat.
You're nothing but a little copycat.
You little copycat. Yeah, you little
copycat. Because the thing is I had a
one night stand with someone before and
you couldn't go down on them, mate. I
mean, if it's your wife or someone
you've been with for a long time, then
or they're a virgin, then it's
different. What? You want to go down on
a random ass woman? And if you don't do
that, you're gay, mate.
A one night stand that I had, mate, you
couldn't go down on them because their
fatty absolutely stunk. So, did that
make me gay? Does that make me
automatically like dick? [ __ ] copycats.
Pair of [ __ ] copycats.
Pack of copycats.
Pack of little cats.
Do you like that one? Do you like that
one? You little copycat?
You little copycat. You little copycat.
You little copy. You sh
No, it is.
Just because you don't want to eat a a a
random woman's fatty out, that doesn't
mean you're gay. What the [ __ ] That
doesn't make you gay. You can finger
them. You can pleasure people in other
ways. Why the [ __ ] would you want to eat
some random ass fanny out?
Yeah, this one wasn't an escort. All the
escorts I've ever been with never stunk.
They never stunk.
But there was an escort
uh not an escort, sorry. From New
Zealander that I had a one night stand
with before and her fanny stunk to the max.
So there was no way I was I wasn't going
to do it anyways. But you know, still
if you're married and the person's a
virgin and stuff, then you know, yeah, sure.
But you don't need to eat someone out,
bro. Just like they don't like giving
pleasure. You don't have to give
pleasure to them. I've had one night
stand that's not gave me a [ __ ] before.
USA is you didn't give me a [ __ ] at
first. You wanted me to have sex with a
condom. Sex with a condom? Why would you
Why would you want sex with a condom?
Well, I understand why as in like STDs
and pregnancy. No, I I understand the
purpose of condoms, but I mean, why
would you you wouldn't get anything out
of it? Sex with a condom.
Really? Why would you want sex with a condom?
That's not It's not going to feel like anything.
Why would you want that when you're not
going to feel anything that good?
Yeah, I know. Just I know, bro. It's
disgusting. It's I know. I've had it.
But if you don't eat them out, you're gay.
Yeah, but you were saying he wasn't a
brass, so that's that.
Well, I know why somebody would want a condom.
Again, I I understand the purpose of
them, but why would you want a condom?
when that's not going to feel good for you.
That just doesn't make sense.
All of the people that I've had sex
with, they've never had condoms.
I've never had condoms.
There's no point in it.
But yeah, this this woman is a complete
and utter feminist.
So they're either white knights or simps
or women that have been done wrong by
women that they choose and
they get butt hurt.
They get butt hurt. Do you know why I
don't understand why these simps do it?
Because women don't like them. The irony
is all of these people that argue with
me, I've had more women than them.
It just doesn't make it just doesn't
make any sense whatsoever.
It makes no sense whatsoever.
All of these all of these people that
sit there and defend them have had less
women than you. Why do they do it? It's
got to be some autism in it. And then
the women, they just been done wrong by
men that they choose and then they seem
to think that they do no wrong.
That's the vibe I'm getting.
They just sit there and continuously
I feel sorry for them, but they it is
the men that they choose. It is the men
that they choose to go for. Um don't let
them tell you that they don't know what
these men are like. [ __ ] off, mate. They
know they're drug dealers. They know
they're scumbags. They know what they're
about. They know a bit of what they're
about, bro. Cuz like I said, if that was
if that was the case, then I'd be
getting women all the time.
If you think about it, all the times I've tried.
No, I don't know who that is. And I
don't compare myself to other people, so
I don't know who the [ __ ] that is.
I don't compare myself to strangers, so
nothing anyone does winds me up.
I don't compare myself. Complete waste of time.
Comparing yourself to other people is a
complete and utter waste of time.
No, the women stuff doesn't wind me up.
What winds me up is
is the people that keep dismissing your
struggles. That's very, very annoying.
It's the them dismissing your struggles
and the double standards. That's what
winds me up. They don't wind me up.
They're just [ __ ] that all the same, bro.
I don't expect anything less anything
less from them, bro. That that doesn't
buy me up. It's the people that
constantly dismiss your struggles. It's
very [ __ ] annoying. Very [ __ ]
annoying. It might seem very It might
seem funny to you.
And yeah, cuz you just feel like the boy
who cried wolf and it's very very very
very [ __ ] annoying
sit there defending them even though you
show them black and white evidence. This
woman's all of a sudden switched because
I don't lick women's asses now. Now all
of a sudden she said, "Oh, you done this
wrong." I said, "Uh, above uh arrow
above, look up. I've sent you
screenshots got dismissed as usual." It
gets it's like you you're basically not
a candidate in an argument.
There's there's like no point of you being
a participant because they just dismiss
anything that you say or show. So, is it
really a point of it? Not really. You know,
they don't admit when they've led people
on, even though you show them black and
white evidence. It's It's mad. You know,
they It's It's [ __ ] insane.
And if these women are really so buttth
hurt about men, stop picking better candidates.
Stop Stop picking better men and stop
moaning about all men. Cuz we all know,
we all know that it is the men that you choose.
You choose these men. So stop [ __ ]
moaning. We don't choose to get led on.
We don't choose to, you know, uh, come
across toxic women. And by we, I mean
me. I don't choose that. But it happens
time and time and time and time again,
which is why I don't bother with them
anymore. You actually choose these people.
They choose these men and then moan
about all men and then they become they
they become feminists and they become
people that hate men. But they they
choose these men. You don't choose these women.
You understand? There's a big
difference. [ __ ] absolute madness, bro.
And like I said, obviously the double
standards as well.
It's very, very depressing.
Very much gets you down having the same
argument over and over and over and over
again. I mean, I don't try because of
them. You know, I shouldn't be told that I'm weak-minded
because I don't want to deal with toxic,
annoying women that play games. But then
when a woman wants to give up because
men that they choose, they're a legend.
[ __ ] the lot of you. That's why I'm
going to title the video. You know,
I stopped going out to to stop dealing
with these [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] women.
No, it's not that's not healthy. It's
it's the it's the debates. It's the
debates over and over and over again
that's not healthy.
It's not them because they're just
[ __ ] You know, we can go out for a
drink and we all know what's going to
happen. We know what women are like.
They're the same [ __ ] We we're
we're over it now. When I got them 10
numbers and I didn't get a date, I was
like, "Yep, there's no hope here." So,
anytime I go out and I try, it's uh I'm
playing it at my own risk. So, I've got
no one to blame but myself. If I go out
and I try, that's that's me taking a
risk. That's my own because, you know,
they're like, you know, they're all the
same. So, no one's really to blame but
me. I'm talking about these debates
where they keep dismissing your [ __ ] struggles.
I was speaking to this woman on [ __ ]
um Reddit um Suri. Yeah. And I showed
her and she was all right with me at first
uh a couple weeks ago and then all of a
sudden when I showed her like what women
have done, she's like, "Nope, no, no,
it's you. It's you. You're pushy. Nope. Nope. Nope." Madness.
Really? Well, you dismissed evidence.
Yeah. Yeah. But you you dismissed
evidence. So, I mean, I dismissed your
opinions because my experiences
contradict your opinions. You dismissed
evidence, which is mad how someone can
dismiss evidence. You will sit there
until you're blew in the face and say
that these women have not led people on
when they have.
Yeah. About 40 50. Yeah.
And because I don't want to deal with
their [ __ ] anymore, I'm weak. I'm
weakminded because I don't want to deal
with their [ __ ] anymore. Not entirely
sure that's what weak-minded means. I
think that's the clever thing to do. And
I think that's a man that has respect
for themselves. But women will choose
men. They will choose these [ __ ] men
time and time and time again. These keep
men that they keep going for. And then
they will then give up because and then
they just go cel a bit and then oh woo
is me. Get in there women. All these men
are [ __ ] The men that they choose.
The double standards is insane lad.
It is mad.
I'm going to do a video about this, bro.
The white knight simps and bloody feminists.
I'm sick of it, bro. I'm sick of it.
I told her about this today.
She She just said they're ignorant. I
said, "Why do these people keep
dismissing your struggles?"
Nope. I'm not going out today, bro. I'm
saving money. I ain't going out.
I'm good, bro. I don't want to deal with
them. I don't want to deal with women.
They're all the same.
But that's I need to be really, really bad
to deal with them. I don't want to deal
with them. They're all the same. I don't
want to deal with them. So, stop telling
me to deal with them. I don't want to
deal with them scumbags.
I've got money and I've already had a
job and I've already got money. You
don't tell me to get money, bro. You
don't know how much money I have.
What do you mean get a job and get
money? I've already got money. You don't
know what I have. Same old conversation.
Same old boring boring boring boring
boring conversation. You don't know how
much money I have. So, why are you
telling me to get money and I've already
had loads of money before and had a job
and live? Right, we're having the same
argument again. We're done with this.
I'm going to do my video. I'm going to
do my video later when that's it. And
I'm going to leave the comments open and
no one's getting blocked. Simple.
Get money. You don't know how much money
I have. Bit ignorant to assume that
someone's got no money. You don't know
how much money people have. Why would
you tell people to get money when you
don't know how much money people have?
That's ignorant. Very, very, very
ignorant. Very, very, very, very
You know, and I've also had a job and I
can get a job anytime I want, but I
don't need a job.
Again, you don't know how much money I
have. A few hundred or a few thousand.
again. You don't know how much money I have
that I I I'll stick to my original
thing. You do not know how much money
that I have.
And I've also had a job and lived by
myself before. What you know, you just
you're just constantly full of excuses
when it comes to these women. But again,
I'll stick to my original point. You
don't know how much money I have. I
could have a million pounds.
Who knows? I could have one pound. You
don't know how much money I have. I'm It
doesn't matter how much money I have,
but I'm saying you don't know how much
money I have. So,
yeah. Exactly. And that's another thing.
Why are you telling people to get a job
when you're just going to report people
if they got a job? Maybe I do have a
job. It It's none of your business how
much I have. I'm not telling you it's
none of your business. And that's
another good point as well. Maybe I do
have a job. That's This guy's just made
a very good point. Maybe I do have a job.
How do you know I don't have a job? How
do you know I don't work part-time? It's
not like anyone's going to tell you.
Yeah, that's another good thing. You
made a good point there as well. You
remember that time when I showed all
that money in cash and you started
trying to get people's money stopped?
You think anyone would tell you jealous
people what they have? You know,
there's some stuff going on that I don't
tell you. Do you think I tell you
everything? No, cuz we know what you
generous little freaks are like on here.
Jealous little freaks.
Maybe I do, maybe I don't. None of your
business. That's for me to know and you
to never find out.
Why do you tell people to get a job
anyways and then when they work you uh
you report them or when they've got more
money than when they show more money
than you, you report them? Jealousy.
Jealous little bastards. like anyone
would tell you anything. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. I I knew that at the old house
when you tried getting people's money
stopped multiple times. [ __ ] jealous
fat ugly people. But what I'm saying is
Yeah. Stop talking uh stop assuming
things about people that you don't know.
You'll go far in life.
It doesn't matter if you didn't report
me. Someone did. So simple as that.
So what? when you get a job. So in your
eyes, if you have a job and you've got
tens of thousands of pounds, women are
going to stop being stuck up [ __ ] and
stop pretending they've got boyfriends.
You know, I've lived every bit of life.
I've been skinned. I've had loads and
loads of money. I've had moderate amount
of money. I've worked. I live by myself.
You know, I've been like everything in
my life. You do realize that? Yeah. And
it really made no difference. Women are
all the same stuck up [ __ ]
So stuck up little [ __ ] that cause
nothing but trouble.
Yeah, they're all [ __ ] Stuck up
No, they don't. No, they won't. And I've
already done experiments of this. No,
they don't. Anyways, I'm not going to
sit here and argue with you. I know my
experiences. So, whatever you want to
believe, you believe. I don't give a [ __ ]
No, I'm not going to get into this.
We're going to stop this now because
this is when it starts becoming
unhealthy. I'm not going to sit here and
try to persuade you my experiences,
whatever, bro. I don't give a [ __ ] what
you want to believe.
So, right, moving on now. I've had my
experiences and you're not going to tell
me otherwise. So, we're moving on now.
You're not going to bully me into
thinking your way. So, that's that. Moving on.
We're moving on now. So, yeah,
moving on now. UK asylum. What I don't
understand is UK asylum, right? Is
you got all of these people
trying to make you believe, right?
But how many times have you gave these
women the benefit of the doubt? It it
should be the women that are proving you
wrong, not these random accounts. You
understand what I'm saying? It's like
what whatever they say, whatever I say
is like whatever. But
you've given them the benefit of the
doubt more times than anybody in the
world and they all prove that they're
all the same.
So I don't really understand the whole
point of it. They can say one thing,
women will always prove they're the same.
every week, every month, every year. So
does it. I don't understand what your
act what your goal is here in the whole
like conversation. You can say one
thing, they will do another and they
will always do another. So it's it's
strange cuz all I'm thinking about is
when when when you're when these
accounts are typing, I'm sat there
reading what they're saying. I'm
thinking, well, [ __ ] bro. Like you've
been all over the country. You've gave
women the benefit of the doubt multiple
multiple multiple multiple times.
Why are you dismissing that? Like that
is that in itself speaks volume that
you've probably tried more than anyone
in the world.
With women they are. Yeah. Well, yeah,
with women and especially with women as
well. With women they are as well. But
then they still defend them. It must
have been how they were raised. I think
it's maybe it's how these people were
raised. Maybe my my where my dad died,
right? I'm not um I'm not brainwashed
into thinking their way and I've seen it
for what it is. Maybe maybe it's
something like that, bro. Because it's
it does seem strange how all of these
people that have had less women than you
will still sit there and defend them
even if they're virgins as well. Even
virgins do it. Maybe it's because maybe
where my dad died or something um I
haven't been brainwashed um into
thinking away that's not true, mind you.
Maybe it's something like that because
it's weird how there's there's more
people out there doing this now than not doing it.
So maybe that's maybe it's something to
do with that and maybe I learned these things myself
instead of having a father brainwashing
you into thinking that women are not all
the same or whatever when they're
[ __ ] not. So, in a way, I kind of bought myself
cuz I don't understand why people would do it. Yep.
Yeah. They're generous little fat ugly
people on here, bro. You know this. I
You know it and I know it.
Yeah. Yeah. But I'm not going to do that
cuz it's pointless, bro. I'm not going
to do that cuz it's pointless.
The double standards are just insane,
bro. Are just absolutely insane,
but they don't like incels, you know?
They treat them like they're toddlers or
babies. If they were toddlers or babies,
then I could be like, "Yeah, okay. Well,
they're innocent. They're babies.
They're children." But they're not.
They're adults. But they still seem to
think in their head that they can't do anything wrong.
Like you show them them leading you on.
Well, how did they lead you on? Oh, no,
no, no, no.
Like there's always like it the the
conversation the other day took all day,
bro. It generally took all day just
because they wouldn't want to admit
that. Then I called the guy a little
copycat on Reddit. I said, "Well, I I'm
gay because I don't want to go down on a
woman." Little copycat.
You're a little copycat.
I sent him a video and he didn't [ __ ]
Yeah, he's a copycat. Wants to fit in
with the crowd.
It's not this virgin boy that's a copycat.
Oh, you little copycat.
You little copycat.
You're a little copycat.
You're no copycat.
You no you no copycat
man. That's why I've always preferred
dogs cuz they don't copy each other.
Man, be back later. Anyways, I'm trying
to find this guy on Reddit before I do this video.
I'm going to do this video, bro, cuz
this is uh
they're either white knights simps or they're feminists.
But they get sympathy even though it's
the men that they choose. So, we need to
talk about a lot of stuff for this
video. Will love it.
Sit there and constantly defend women
just for being women. Mad. [ __ ] mad.
Anyways, I'll be back in a bit. Yeah.