There we
go. There we
Oh, ladies got stuff to be doing
today. 100% but I feel well enough. Yeah.
Oh, just a dust.
Yeah. Hey, listen, Terry. You need to
stop calling yourself a bunker. It's no
good for the mental health, you know.
It's It's like what I've said to
uh some people on here as well, mate.
You need to stop calling yourself a
bunter. It's not good for the old mental health lag. You
know, it's not nice calling yourself a
bun, mate. It's not nice to talk about
yourself like that, you
know. It can't be can't be good for your mental health. Yep. That's Anything like
that. Anything like
that. Let's go out and get some more
milk. A long day today.
Wrong day today,
mate. Oh boy.
Yeah, tell me
bad stick again. What's that? [ __ ]
man. That's been sick, man. That's too
much. That's too much for the stomach mate
person. That's a lie, man. Bought it. Anyways,
yeah. Anyways, Terry, stop calling
yourself bun, mate. Early hours in the
morning. No good for the mental health.
membrane. Calling yourself a bun at
all. It's not nice to talk about
yourself like that,
mate. Calling yourself a bun, mate.
So, I've got a few options on the go
now. They can never leave. They they can
never stay away from Py forever. Why do
you think they always come back easily? You
know, why do you think they always come back? I'm
saying there's reason for that, man.
Do you believe he's just a uh he's just a loved figure, you
know? Oh, stop talking about yourself,
Red Star. Get a life. We know that
you're special needs. That's why you're
sat on YouTube every day talking. We
know that you're special
needs. Your whole life is dedicated to
being obsessed with me. I appreciate it,
buddy. And let me just tell you
something. Nothing you do bothers no
one. You haven't stopped anyone's money.
You haven't kicked anyone out the house.
Everything you've done for the past few
years, you've tried and you failed. How
does it make you feel? You loser. Carry
on being obsessed with me for the rest
of your life. You
loser. [ __ ] loser. Yeah, I love it,
man. I love the fact that you're
obsessed with me. I love it. I love it.
Anyways, stop that read off. And what I
was saying, there's a Yeah, Peter B is a
um is a loved
figure. The sand
lo. He's a loved
figure. He's a loved figure.
Man, I was putting a wash
on. Oh, you're a coward, ret. Hey, stop
talking about yourself. It's no good for
your mental health. Hey, that actually
rhymed to be fair. Yeah, man. You need
to stop talking about yourself.
It's [ __ ] It's not even 10:00 in the
morning and you're already talking about
yourself. Stop talking about yourself.
Get off YouTube. Go get a
life. I'm going on a date
today. Stop being in your late 30s, 40s
calling people what you are, man. It's a
sad life. It's not going to get you
anymore anywhere. Think of it, man.
Like, you projectors have been doing
this since 2012 and you're still losers
on YouTube, self
projecting, talking about your own
lives. Come on, man. Like, do you ever
fix yourself like enough is
enough? Sad, fat, ugly, on YouTube every
day. What life do you people really
really have? Calling people what you
are. You're sat there with no money
trying to tell other people they ain't
got no money when you you are the ones
that got nothing. You ain't got a
[ __ ] pot to piss
in. But you want to talk about other
people's lives like you know other
people's lives. It's [ __ ] madness.
You don't know nothing. It's
crazy. It's actually crazy,
dude. It's madness, bro. I see
madness. All you little losers have
self-reflecting, selfjecting your own
lives. I think it's from abandoning from
parents. I think it is me. These people
never loved their children, so they come
and mine and take out on people. It's
crazy, isn't it? It's mad. How did you
like [ __ ] up, man? These
people how much they
self-reflect people. Bro, I honestly
could not imagine being like these little losers, you
know. Yeah. Stop talking about
yourself. It's not nice to talk about
yourself like that. You are jobless and
you have no money. Yes. Stop talking
about yourself. It's not good. It's no
good for your mental health to keep talking about
yourself. Yes. Yes. He owns me so much
yet he won't meet me. And when I go to
his area three times and bully him, he
goes running to the police. Yes. He owns
me. Yes. We we we've established that.
Yeah. He owns me so much that every time
I go to his area, he runs to the police
screaming how he's not a fighter and
he's got autism. Yeah. Of course he owns
me, bro. He owns me so much. Just like I
you. You can't own someone on YouTube.
You to to actually own somebody, you'd
have to meet them face to face, which
none of you losers can ever do. So
therefore, you can never bully no one.
It's like a [ __ ] four or fiveyear-old
can go behind the keyboard, write stuff,
make videos of people. But they even
watch horror films nowadays. You people
don't bully no one. You show yourselves
up on YouTube every day. Like I wish
like you actually understood what used
people do. You don't bully no
one. And think of it, right? Think of it
like this, right? If you people that
come on here really had jobs, really had
money, really had this, that, and the
other, why are you on here every day
calling other people, calling other
people for a living? Like, the only job
that you've got is sat on YouTube every
day talking about yourselves. That's
literally the only jobs that you have is
talking about yourselves. Skin ma no
friends that's you. You're talking about
yourselves. You're literally talking
about your own lives. That's the only
job that you
got, you know, and it's autism as well
because you like to call other people
autistic, but at the end of the day,
it's you people are the ones with autism
because you don't get bored of it. You
do it over and over and over again and
you don't get bored of it.
You talk about yourselves, mate, every
day. It's not nice to talk about yourself like
that. Nice to talk about yourself like
that. Bullying yourselves every
day. You know what I'm saying?
I hope I'm not coming down with something. Oh,
big Yeah. If you don't like me, stop
watching. Yeah, you're talking about
yourself again. This is all you have.
Yeah, you're talking about yourself
again. Like I said, it's no good for your mental
health. Stop projected. It's no good for
your mental health. You don't like me
yet. You're watching me. Get a grip.
Shame on you then. You're the one that's
sat there watching people that you don't like.
Yeah, mate. You people hate on everyone.
Even new people if they come in the
community, you hate on everyone. Like you just
self-reflect. Even back in the days when
I was like 20, 22, 21, 22, like who
doesn't m It doesn't matter who you are,
bro. You people always self-reflect your
lives because if your lives were so
good, you wouldn't be on here. If you
weren't skinn and you had a job, you
wouldn't be on here.
But every day you're on here calling
people what you are yourselves. It's not
a good look, is it? It's not a good
man. Self conjecting people that never
made it in life. That's what I call it.
That [ __ ] damn right, man. What I
call it be, bro. I got such a long day
today. I got to do some football bets. I
got I might scrap the football bets to
be honest because I got this date. So, I
might give it a miss this week.
Maybe I going to put maybe I'll put a
tenner on it maybe or something. I don't
know. Oh god. Barbers. Oh, what was me?
E. If people have money and a job, they
won't be on YouTube. Your reason is if
people you have a house and you have
both. Okay. You've got two houses. Okay.
Show everybody your house then. Okay.
Then you Okay. Okay. Okay. I'm just
going to I'm just going to take what
you've just said there. Your reason you
have both. Okay. Show us your house and
show us your money. Okay. I'm not going
to argue with you. Okay. Okay. I have
nothing cool yet. Show us your house and
show us your money.
000000 Yeah. Okay. Okay. Cool. Come in.
Show us your house. Show us your money.
Stop typing. Come in. Show us your
house. Show us your money. You know, and
it will prove when you don't do it that
all you middle-aged little fat moners do
is come on YouTube online and
selfject. That's literally all you have.
Doesn't matter what the person is you're
trying to [ __ ] call. Show us your
house. Show us your money. Stop typing.
Show us your house. Show us your money.
Come on. And let's actually hear you
talk as well. I'm not a school kid. Uh,
exactly. because you don't have nothing. Bye-bye.
Now, you're not a school kid. Hold on
one sec. One sec. Wait, let's reiterate
that. You said that you're not a school
kid. Yet, you've made you've made three
accounts just to get blocked. Doesn't
matter what I have. At the end of the
day, you made three accounts, four
accounts just to get
blocked. Doesn't matter what I have.
Doesn't matter where I am. It's not your
business. We're talking about this.
You're not immature. You're not a school
kid. You just made [ __ ] three, four
accounts just to get blocked. How are
you not immature, man? Get a grip. Give
your head a shake, man. [ __ ]
madness. What's your plan for today?
Anyways, I need to go to the bar. I got
a date to go on
today. And yeah, go on,
buddy. See you later.
Uh, these people will be on
YouTube. Of course they will. They don't have anything
else. I bet today it stops raining as
well. Yeah, it probably does. Yeah.
Yeah. I mean, you think you bully
people, but you don't bully no one, man.
Like, come on. If you really bully
people, they wouldn't be on here. If you
bullied someone so much, Yeah. they
wouldn't be on
YouTube. You claim that you bully
people, but you don't bully no one, you just bully
yourselves. Yeah, of course you are.
Yeah. Yeah. You're going to Liverpool.
Yeah. Now you got Oh, you got a wife as
well. Oh, that's fine. You all seem to
be married. So unbelievable, isn't it? I
think I do. You know what I think this
is? Yeah. I honestly believe this is the
same No, no, no. It's not even four
people. I would say this is the same
three spastics, you know, behind all of
these accounts, three maximum fat, ugly,
no life, come on life, come online
bothering people every day. I think it's
the same three people that's been doing
it for years. And I think you're you're
obviously one of them. It's definitely
the same three people. It's definitely
the same three people. Yeah, because you
make it so obvious because you said that
you're married. Yeah, you're married.
Why is it that you're all married? That
can't be right. You're all married,
mate. You don't have nothing. Go make
another account. Well, if you've got all
of them things going for you, when I
block you now, you won't make another
account then, will you?
Right. He's got all of these things.
Let's see if he makes another account. Come on.
[ __ ] It's going to be a long one today.
No, I'm actually I'm kind of wanting to
just like chill today, man. I'm kind of
hoping she flakes, but she ain't going
to, man. It's so mad. It's like you
spend all that time,
right, not wanting someone to flake, and
then the moment they don't flake, you're
like, "Oh, I could get used to just
chilling straight up, chilling, bro." Bye-bye.
Bye-bye. That's another cloud blocked.
Jesus Christ, man. you you're looking
more and more like a low life every
time. Is that is that all your lives
consist of is making fake accounts,
hating on people that you're jealous of, right?
Yeah. He's making fake accounts. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Good for you. Well, he owns
me, does he? Well, why don't you tell
him to meet me today? Well, he owns me.
I did, mate. I went to his area three
times and I made him run to the police
screaming he's not a fighter and that
he's got autism. I assure you, you don't
own anybody, buddy. Just like I can go
to the Monty's area today and he's going
to scream, "I'm not a fighter. I'm not a
fighter. No one like that has ever
bullied a man like me." The same as
Terry using probation as an excuse when
me and you both know he's never been on
probation. What are you, a YouTube
keyboard warrior? Okay, I give you that.
I'm not I'm not lying that you are a
YouTube keyboard warrior. Yeah. Okay.
And you are a YouTube keyboard warrior.
But the thing is a six a six-year-old, a
sevenyear-old can do that. But guess
what? Every time you go to Sea's area,
I'm not a fighter. I'm not a fighter. No
person like that could ever bully a man
like me with these shoulders. Get a grip
and get laid. Get off your world. Oh [ __ ]
It will do you the world of good. Get
off your YouTube, you fat little
bunters. Anyways, we're not entertaining these people
anymore. We want some normal people in,
man. Not these little
bunters. These little muners. Anyways, yeah. Yeah.
You think anyone could have me running
to the police screaming I'm not a
fighter? It's the same as that Terry.
Yeah. Oh, come to Tite Lane. Come to
Tite Lane. Come to Turbite Lane. And
then when you go to his area, he doesn't
meet you. He's using probation as an
excuse. So, who's the one that's really
getting bullied? Bro, listen. You
people, you haters on YouTube, you've
been bullied your whole life. You have
literally been bullied your whole life.
You would know about being bullied. You
know, you people have been bullied your
whole [ __ ] life, which is why you
come on YouTube and you take out on
other people because you're sad, fat,
ugly losers that ain't got nothing going
for yourselves. No money, no designer
clothes, no nothing. You got nothing
going for yourselves. And that's why you
do this this [ __ ] on YouTube every day,
man. You know, bunch of losers. That's
what you are. You losers. That's what
you are. You need to get a grip. Get off
of YouTube and stop talking about
yourself every day.
You know, you people do nothing but get
bullied yourself. Life has bullied you.
Since you come out of your mom's vagina,
you've been bullied. You have been
bullied since coming out your mom's
vagina. Literally, like, think of it the
other day, right? I went to the pub. You
didn't even know what pub I was in.
You're trying to get me banned from a
pub. That that just goes to show that
you people don't even leave your house
because you think that going for a pint
of [ __ ] Guinness in a pub is a big
thing. That's how sad you people are.
You're just fat losers that are riddled
with anxiety. That's that's what you
are. That's what you all are. You I
would bet, bro, mothers, 90% of these
people don't leave the house or this
community. 90% of these little [ __ ] sad
[ __ ] spastnics don't even leave their
[ __ ] mommy's basement. telling you.
Sad, man. It is
sad. It's so
sad. Yeah. Did he? That's nice, man. I
made him run to the police screaming how
he's not a fighter and now he's got autism.
Touche. Like, you got to understand,
right? Everybody, anybody can do this
keyboard warrior [ __ ] Literally anybody
in the world can do this keyboard warrior
[ __ ] Literally anybody can do this
keyboard warrior [ __ ] you know. But
that's all you are are keyboard
warriors. Okay, I need to put
a I need to go put
football. Yeah, we got some stuff to do,
man. Oh boy. Been a long day. It's been
one. I kind of just want to chill and
and kind of treat Saturday as like a uh Sunday,
but don't know, man. [ __ ]
hell. But you know, Saturdays are
football days, right? Everyone knows
that. I'm only going to put 10.
No. Well, I don't think there's really
any point of actually doing it, is there? No.
Bye-bye. Bye-bye. Stop repeating yourself.
No, actually I'm not going to do football
today. I can't be [ __ ] I actually mobs
today. That means
lumping. The only way to really win on
him is if you like lump on him, man. You
know what I
mean? One team don't [ __ ] score.
Yeah, I don't even fancy breakfast to be
fair. No, not even to be honest.
Uh, Jesus Christ. How many accounts have
I had to
block? [ __ ] You people really ain't got
nothing in your lives. Look. 1 2 3
4 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 accounts.
What? You people need to get life. You
need to get over your job.
You need to get off of
YouTube. You need to get off of YouTube.
It's not nice talking about yourself like
that. It's not nice to call yourself that. Jesus
Christ. I feel sorry for you little
bongos. [ __ ] 21 accounts. You keep
getting banned. Losers. Absolute
losers. Anyone who's watching this [ __ ]
this is what you don't want to be like
when you're in your
40s. Start on YouTube like these little
mongos. Ain't got nothing going for
yourselves. Ain't got nothing going for
yourselves. Just sad little losers that
talk about themselves every day. Don't
want to be like these people, man.
come across this [ __ ] community. It was
[ __ ] what's his face? It was [ __ ]
um It was [ __ ] Timmy, was it? Yeah,
it was [ __ ] Timmy, man.
Then I might have to meet someone on
[ __ ] Monday as well along with it.
The joys of not being ugly like these
people, eh? The joys of not being fat
and ugly like these
people. Sorry, I had to put a wash on. Yeah. Yeah.
Um, anyway, that's me done, bro. I think
I need to leave
now. Anyway, had a cup of [ __ ] cuz the [ __ ] milk's
expired. The [ __ ] milk has [ __ ]
Yeah. Sounds good to
me. Good to
me. Oh [ __ ] Yeah, my trainers. My
trainers as well.
You You win some, you lose some. Just
gambling. You win some, you lose some.
some. Keep bossing them fing. Stop
talking about yourself. You're already
bored. Stop talking about yourself, you
fat, ugly bunter. You are bored. Stop
talking about yourself. It's no good for
the mental health. It's no good for your
mental health, you little bully victim.
You're already bored. [ __ ] the bullying.
You're already bled, you little
bun. M carry on being a keyboard warrior
and upset for years. Nothing you have
ever done is has ever affected no one.
You haven't stopped no one's money. You
haven't got anyone badly beaten up. You
haven't got anyone killed. Carry on
being an obsessed little keyboard
warrior all your life and keep wasting
your life on me. I don't care. I love
it. And the only thing you've seen is in
the mirror cuz you're already bored.
Stop self-reflecting. Do you know what?
We need to uh call this community a
self-reflecting community cuz that's
actually what it is. It's like no no.
Well, years ago, it started off as a
gambling community and then it turned
into a bunch of fat ugly people that
just come online and talk about
themselves for a living. Like fat, ugly
sados that's got nothing to their lives
and they come on here and self-reflect
every day. That's what it turned into.
It used to be a gambling community. It
it many a year ago it did.
Uh, well, not anymore. Just a bunch of
losers that ain't got nothing in their
lives. Sad little low lives that ain't
got no friends. They ain't got no
nothing. sat on YouTube every day for a
living. Sad [ __ ] [Music]
spastics. Yep. Self self-reflection is
what you do. Self-p projection is what
you fat ugly losers do. bald, fat, ugly
skin, nothing ugly little virgins. It's
yourselves. That's what you are. That's
what self-reflection is. You fat, ugly
people that ain't got nothing in your
life but YouTube. And you prove it every
single day. You people, the fat, ugly
little losers, the little bully victims,
the losers of YouTube, the loners of
YouTube. It's you. That's what a self
That's what self-reflection is. You
losers. You fat ugly mongos obsessed on
YouTube every day. You sad lives. Billion
mates can't even afford a [ __ ] pipe
of [ __ ] Guinness at the pub. Imagine
that. These little sados, right? These
little rejects, they can't even afford a
pipe of Guinness at the pub. Like that.
Think about it, bro. That is enough to
trigger them. A pipe of Guinness at the
pub is enough to trigger these little
retards. These little anxiety basement
dwellers. I swear to God. Like, bro, you
all you got to do is go to a [ __ ] p a
pub, get a Guinness, and these little
self reflecting basement dwellers will
literally try and get you kicked out the
pub. It's a
madness. Oh, it's a madness, bro. This
This This really really really is. This
really, really is a dowy community,
isn't it? For the dowies. It really
is. You've got to laugh at it. It's such
a dowy community.
It really is. It makes me giggle. And
the thing the funniest thing is it the
funny thing is is they don't
psychologically [ __ ] with anyone's head.
They don't bother no one. Like that's
the funniest thing is that they think
that they do because mate there's only
so far you can be with being a keyboard
warrior. You know what I'm saying? Like
just go to the pub and have a Guinness.
That will trigger them. They don't
[ __ ] psychologically [ __ ] with no
one's head. They're little sados. You
live in their head rent free cuz they
won't shut the [ __ ] up about you every
[ __ ] day. Little YouTube
mongos. Little dowy. It's a dowy
community. That's what I'm going to call
these people now. Little dowies. That's
what they literally are. They're little
dowies. They ain't got nothing in their
lives but self projection. That's what they
are. Little dowies that are in desperate
need of a job because they're skin.
That's what they are. They're [ __ ]
dowies, man. Absolute dowies. All of them.
[ __ ] downies, mate. Downies. Yeah.
So the person is just [ __ ]
uh I couldn't imagine being these
people, man. Like waking up obsessed
with somebody every day that they don't
know. Genitality is a horrible, horrible disease.
It kills loads of people just like
cancer, you know. Think of how much time
these little losers put into stalking
people that they don't even know. Their
lives are down bad. They got nothing
going for themselves. Literally nothing
themselves. And they don't
psychologically [ __ ] with anyone's head.
They're just something to laugh
at, you know?
Where are you
bastards? Your job. No lie but your job.
Don't laugh at YouTube and being
obsessed. What a lovely life,
eh? Sad life, is it, man? Being stuck on
YouTube obsessed with anyone for years.
And then and and and the thing is you
you you say to yourself, right, with
these little bully victims, right? When
does it ever like stop with them? Like,
are they just going to be obsessed for
years? Yeah. Yeah. Oh, really? Self
projection, mate. Self
projection. Self projection. Guess what?
You can't even get any numbers cuz you're too
ugly. You can't even get any numbers
because you're too much of an ugly [ __ ]
Sim. Never sim today in my life. Wrong
channel. That's L J. But guess what
happened? Yeah, I'm meeting someone
today. Actually, if you actually heard
properly, I'm actually meeting someone
today. But guess what? You can't even
get any numbers cuz you're too too much
of an ugly [ __ ] to even get the number
to begin with. So, I mean, bro, even if
that was the case, I'm doing better than
you. Yeah, you can't get numbers. You
can't get laid. You're too ugly. You're
too much of an ugly [ __ ] Chasing women
is sing. Okay. What? Drinking and
approaching people with singing. No. No.
And that's what happened to them
numbers. Never s a day in my life. Wrong
channel. Wrong channel, buddy. You
know, you are a
s. Yeah, that's cool. Evan, but how can
it be a s when it takes balls to do it?
How can it be a s when it takes bulls to
do it? Approaching people in public
takes falls. So, how can you be a s? A s
is somebody like Lord Jane that goes
online saying, "Oh, I want you to suck
my cock." No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
You can't be a s if something takes
balls to begin
with. I'm on a date today. To be honest
with you, I can't even be bothered to go
on it to be
honest. But is what it is,
eh? I'd rather just went to the cinema.
I just chilled.
I got [ __ ] to do.
Sadly, we can't we can't all be like Red
Star sat on YouTube stinking in his own
[ __ ] being obsessed with people for a
living. Sad little bastard. Sad little
YouTube keyboard warrior. Some of us has actually got
lines. Okay. Okay. Now, you're you're
the one who see me like a s now. You're
the one who seeming like a s saying that
oh you have no interest in them just
you're sounding like the s now you're
actually sounding like the s by saying
that you're sounding like the s people
that defend women that simpy behavior.
That right there now you are sounding
like the s. You are sounding like the s
now. Definitely you are sounding like the s
now. You are sounding like a massive s.
Oh, you got no interest. That's
literally what white knights say. That's
literally what simps are. I swear to
God, I'm not even making it up. If you
go on online, right, or even like in
real life, that's what these little
white knight simps say, "Oh, you've got
no interest in actually getting to know
them." That's that's exactly what S
would say. Because the same people that
have got no bad words to say about
women, so you're the one who's actually
sounded like a s now, not
me. Yeah. Simp.
You think them words would ever come out
of my [ __ ] mouth? Hell the [ __ ]
no. Hell the [ __ ] no, bro. You're a s.
You are a s.
Jeez. You are the
s. I need a Coca-Cola.
Bad. B my teeth cuz I was
sick. Yeah, I don't even fancy a tea to be fair.
Well, I got stuff to do anyways. I'll be
back later. Be back later, man.