Don't want to feel left out.
left now. You little copycat. Oh, no copycat. No, no, no. Copycat.
I hate cats.
I hate cats. [ __ ] hate cats.
You hate cats. Mhm.
I absolute I absolutely hate cats cuz I copy people.
You all right? Did you see my video? Steven Howard.
They hate blaming women for anything. Mad. Mad.
They hate take women hate taking
accountability for anything.
It's so bad. Really, really is bad. Amazing.
She absolutely sw
my bad experiences with women.
People allowed to change their mind.
They didn't change their mind. They led
me on on purpose. Same argument.
Same excuses and the same argument.
Same excuses, same arguments. They've
got the same excuses. Have you noticed
there's never any new excuses for these
women? It's always the same [ __ ] They
don't change their mind. No stable people
change their mind that quick. [ __ ]
they've got loads of excuses when it
comes to women, but they say that
they're not they say that they're not
sexist. [ __ ] off. They are [ __ ]
She had a proper guy here.
They're allowed to change their mind.
They didn't change their mind. They let
me on on purpose. It's some black and
white evidence. [ __ ] off.
I was arguing with her for like an hour, bro.
No, I hate cats.
No, I hate cats, bro. I hate cats.
I might be getting a new dog. I might be
I don't like cats. They're cubby people. Right.
I don't know why they can't admit that
women led you on and [ __ ] you over.
It's in black and white what they've
done. I don't know why they still deny
it and make excuses for them. It's in
black and white what these women are like.
And they still continuously make excuses
for them just cuz they're a woman. It's pathetic, bro.
I was going to do a video on this, but
they always make excuses for women. Sad, isn't it?
Sad, isn't it? They changed their mind.
Biggest excuse going, they never changed
their mind. They l you on purpose. Women
can do that just like men can do that. I
know you don't want to believe that and
you want to think that all women are
angels, but sadly that's not the case.
Steven Howard, I think that I was
thinking, why is it that
there's so many people that believe this
and lick women's asses even when they're
wrong? And it's got to be their dad
that's told them this their whole life.
Women are innocent. Women are good.
And to lick women's asses, that's the
way that most people have been brought
up. And obviously, where my dad died, I
learned the truth. They got brought up
the wrong way because that's not true.
They're not innocent. They are
[ __ ] They do lead people on. As
much as people try and say that they're
not like that, they [ __ ] are like
that. And I'm living proof of it. So, I
guess these people have had fathers that
have led them the wrong way, you know,
cuz an orphan.
I'm not. Um, obviously my dad died when
I was young, so I I found out for myself,
you know. So,
I just don't know why they make so many
excuses for them
and they dismiss every bad thing that
they do. I'd love to know why, but
I don't think we'll ever know.
And I think I'll always be the boy that fired wolf.
So it seems
I'm the boy who fired wolf.
You ever watched the boy who cried warlad?
Yeah, I'm the boy who fighting.
She was all right with me, that woman at
first. And I said to her,
"What bad experiences you had uh with
men?" I told her my bad experiences with women. Um
I said, "Oh, what's your experience been
like with men and whatever." And then I
showed her the screenshots of women
leading me over, leading me on and
[ __ ] me over. And then she started
having a big problem with it. She
started going in at me all cuz I showed
women in a bad light.
They like, "No, no, no. They changed
their minds. No, no, no. They can't
accept any women doing any wrong. These
people, they're full of excuses with
them. But if they had a dick between
their legs, oh, it' be a different
story. They'd get called a prick. Isn't
that right, Steven Howard?
They're so sexist." And they and they
don't even realize it. You know, it's mad.
trying to use excuses, trying to blame
my attitude when I clearly showed women
having an attitude problem. But whatever
wrong they do, it just gets dismissed.
Like I've said many, many times before, you know,
they seem to think that no woman can do
any wrong cuz they've got a [ __ ] between their legs. Mad.
Absolutely [ __ ] mad.
Oh, I said to her she was a copycat as well.
I said you're a little copycat.
I said to her, you copycat. I bring that
cat around with me. Copycat.
Look at the face. It's just looking at
it next victim to copy. It's got
absolutely no mind of its own.
Just look at this cat. Just Just
look at the picture of this cat. It's just looking
looking for the next person to copy.
Look looking for this next person to copy.
It's got no
mind cuz it's got no mind of its own.
It's got no mind of its own that's
looking for the next person to copy him.
Our dogs don't do that.
Our dogs don't do that, mate. My
sister's getting me a dog. By the way, I
like dogs. They're sweet. They're cute.
They're not [ __ ] animals that just copy people. Yeah. copy.
So, what's your opinion on this
women [ __ ] UK signing?
Why do these people think that women can
do can do no wrong? And then she turned
around and said, "Oh, this." She turned
around and said to me, "Oh, um, well,
don't get me wrong, there is women that
can be wrong.
There's women that can be wrong. You've
literally just spent the the past hour
arguing with me about what I've shown
you about women changing their mind and
all of these [ __ ] excuses. Why do
these people think women can't do no
wrong?" I think that's going to be the
title of the video, to be honest.
Why do people think women can do no wrong?
No, no, no, no. But it's but it's not
No, no, no, no, no, no. It's not about
opinions. I have showed evidence where
people have led me on.
No, no, no, no. It's It's not about your
opinions and my opinions or what we've
experienced. I have shown black and
white evidence of women [ __ ] me over,
but it keeps getting dismissed.
So, I've literally showed them [ __ ]
me over and people are denying it,
saying, "Oh, no. Maybe they changed
their mind." So,
it's not about that. Why are they just
missing your struggles?
There's no way
that these people
just just change their mind. There's no
way. People just change their mind that
quick. And we both know that if it was a
man, they wouldn't be making these excuses.
So, why do they keep making excuses for
these women? You know, I would love to
know why. Do I would love to know why. I
love somebody to come up and and and
explain it to me. They didn't change
their mind. They clearly led you on.
It's obvious. Even people that haven't
experienced it. Why can't they just
admit they've led someone on? Why are
they so scared to take any kind of
accountability for what they've done? I
don't get it. I seriously don't get it.
Even if they said to me, "Oh, you was
wrong eight times out of 10 and they
were wrong two times out of 10." Then
I'd be like, "Okay, I buy it." But the
fact that they don't think they're wrong
in any of these messages is mad.
And that's quite scary to be honest with
you. It's actually quite scary knowing
that most people will just defend women
cuz they're women. It's sad really.
There's there's not many unbiased Oh,
and another thing she did, you know what
she turned around and did UK sign
with these people. The way they try to
beat you is by calling you an incel.
That's that's their favorite word. They
think people are an incel if you
disagree with them. If you disagree with
them and you don't suck up to women,
they automatically call you an incel.
Not that you've had bad experiences with
women time and time again and you're fed
up with them. Nope. Straight away in cell.
No, it doesn't affect me. I'm just
wondering why they're doing it. I'm
wondering why they're doing it because I
haven't got an answer yet. So, I'm still
wondering why do they keep dismissing people's struggles.
Simon, Simon, Simon, Simon again.
Is it ignorance or Why?
Why do they do it?
I've got a lot of things to talk about
in this video.
I think I've got a lot of things,
not even just this.
The fact that I called G I got called
gay for not wanting to eat a woman out.
Yeah, women have no problem. They don't
want to give [ __ ] And me being
called weak minded, that was kind of
offensive. I got called weakminded
because I don't want to deal with
narcissistic women anymore.
I need I need to get this video done.
But this is [ __ ] bad.
I'm going to title it is why can't women
ever be in the wrong?
I think that's a good I think that's a good title.
Just Yeah, I'm just eating popcorn. Absolute madness.
And where I'm in the 5% minority, right,
I take offense to it even more. I take
offense to it even more because when
you're in the 5% minority who dealt with
women and then you have these white
knights trying to tell you you're weakminded,
mate, they wouldn't even been able to
deal with 1% of what I've dealt with.
It's not about American women. It's people generally.
They seem to think it's people's
attitude when women have got the worst
attitude going. So I'm thinking, bro,
are you I said to her, are you
projecting? You're talking about my
attitude. What about all of these
women's attitude? And then it just goes
round and round in circles because
you're basically arguing with a brick wall. Basically,
it's like you you'll get more sense out
of that brick wall right next to you cuz
all they're going to do is what they
usually do. Keep dismissing your
struggles. That's what they're good at. Yeah.
All they do is keep dismissing your
struggles. And the reason why I'm not
like one of these people is because I
didn't have a dad. So where my dad died,
I wasn't brought up into thinking this
way, which is the wrong way. The way
they think is not the right way, it's
the wrong way. But because they've been
brought up this way, they think it's
normal. Why do you think Greg are not
like is not like them? Because he has no
parents. His mom and dad died and
obviously my cuz I'm thinking why is it
most more people are like this than not
like that when this is not the right way
and obviously because they've had dads
in their life and that's brought them up
and their father figure was wrong. They
they they are wrong in the way that they are thinking.
So, I'm someone that had to learn learn
it for myself that they're [ __ ]
wrong, you know?
I'd love to know why they sit there and
defend the women every day,
you know? I would love to know. I would
really love to get to the bottom of why
they do it.
Why they do it. They're not angels. They
know better than men. They do lead
people on on purpose. They do [ __ ]
people over on purpose, believe it or
not. They might have a vagina, but they
still do it. Yep.
Gi's parents died. My dad's dead.
So, this is what
Maybe it's not the father figure thing,
but there's something that's not right there, bro.
They constantly constantly constantly defend women.
And she had a go at me by saying, "Oh,
you women pick the wrong men." You do.
You do pick the wrong men on purpose.
You do. You do pick the wrong men on
purpose. Why is that an insult? You do.
And then you moan about all men. You do
do it. That's been going on for [ __ ] donkeys years.
They pick the wrong men and then start
complaining that all men are the same
based on the men they choose. That's
what they do.
It's a madness, bro. [ __ ] madness.
And this guy on Reddit said, "Acept the
double standards." I'm not accepting the
double standards. I think it's [ __ ]
gross. I think it's disgusting. So, why
am I going to deal with Why am I going
to accept double standards?
I'm not accepting [ __ ] double
standards. [ __ ] that.
Yeah, I sent her a picture of my dick,
by the way. [ __ ] scumbag.
>> So, yeah.
>> What do you think about a UK asylum? Do
you think they defend women for the sake
of being women?
Yeah, they definitely definitely do.
What's your opinion on it, M? So,
they definitely defend women for the
sake of them being women. One million%, mate.
Oh, they change their minds.
They don't change their minds. They do
it on purpose.
Um, no, I'm eating popcorn.
>> I got some requires, but no, I'm eating
I'm eating um popcorn. M
someone on Reddit said that I was gay
because I didn't want to eat USA out.
I got called gay.
I'm gay apparently.
Yeah, I'm gay apparently.
these men that are defending them, right?
They're either virgins or they've had
less women than me, guaranteed. But then
they're still defending them like you're the virgin.
But either way, it's any of them. It
doesn't matter. Anyone that's defending
them is bad.
um whether they're women or men
because but yeah the men that defend
them or women people that have had less
women than me
and I don't know why they do it.
Maybe their father made them think like
that when they were younger and my dad's
dead that's why. But it it seems like
serious autism isn't it?
You'll show them evidence of women
[ __ ] you over and they'll be like,
"No, no, no, no, no." Literally, they'll
be like Churchill, you know, Churchill
the dog. They'll be like, "Nope, no, no,
no, no, no, no." I was like, "Huh? I've
just sent you." No, no, no, no. They
changed their minds, mate. Change their
minds. They can send something. [ __ ]
It's like what Oreo man said, an account
accountability is a woman's worst nightmare.
Think about it, bro. Look how long that
conversation took the other day, right?
Just for them to just over a woman
leading me on. Now, if I was gay and a
man led me on, they'd sit there and say,
"Oh, he's a prick. You can do better."
Big difference, isn't it, between having
a dick and having a [ __ ] you know, as
mad as that sounds. If you've got a
[ __ ] dick in between your legs, oh
well, he's a prick anyways. You can do
better than him. But if it's a woman, oh
well, you don't know what the woman's
going through. You know, she could have
changed her mind. Big difference, mate.
Big difference having a cump between
your legs. Sometimes I wish I had a cump
between my legs. life would be easier.
And this is what people need to
understand. Don't ever question you
yourself and what people say about you.
It's only because they're women. There's
nothing else. It's not because you're
right or because you're wrong. They are
defending them only because they've got a [ __ ]
in between their legs. Nothing else.
It's not you. It's not me. It's because
they were women. These people will
continuously defend them no matter what they do. So,
and all of that [ __ ] right, when they
say, "Oh, they go for these guys and
they don't know what they're like." I'm
not buying it.
I'm not buying it. I'm not buying,
right, Windzo that they do not not they
do not know what these men are like
before getting with them.
>> Yeah. They might not beat them up. They
might not smash their faces straight
away. They might not know they're woman
beaters, but they know that they're no
good people. And I've got plenty of
evidence to back this up. So don't sit
there and [ __ ] try and tell me,
[ __ ] how every single woman
that ends up with these bad people don't
know what they're like at the start. Get
the [ __ ] out of here. Because if that
was the case, then I'd be pulling every
single time I go out. Then
think about it. If you want to use that
logic, it's [ __ ] Absolute [ __ ]
absolute [ __ ] bollocks.
Don't listen to any of that [ __ ] Yeah,
but I told the USA story to someone on Reddit yesterday
and they said, "Oh, did you eat her
out?" I was like, "No." And they said,
"Are you gay or something?"
I said, "No." But then above he said
that if women don't want to give
[ __ ] it's they do what they like.
Oh, so you're sexist then. Then I showed
him the cat and I said you little
copycat. I said you little copycat.
Yeah. I said you little copycat. You
little cat. You little cat. Little
copycat. I bring the cat everywhere with
me and throw it at people that copy.
I might be getting a new dog by the way.
My sisters buy me a dog. J King's not
ours. So yeah, I don't like cats. They
copy people. They got no Look at Look at
that cat in that photo. Look at the
eyes. It's got no mind of its own. Just
looking for its next victim to copy.
How can you live like that? Not having a
mind of your own. Just just living just to copy,
you know? Look, look at that. [ __ ]
sake. It's getting to me again. It's
getting to me again. You know, the do
the the cat is literally looking for
anything just to copy. You know, I know,
you know, why would I want a cat that copies people?
Who does that remind you of when so?
Who does that cat remind you of?
No, I don't care.
They're not getting my attention. I
don't give a [ __ ]
These sad little fat ugly people aren't
getting my attention so they can put up
what they want.
You've seen it all before. You've seen
it all before, man.
We've seen it all before. Yeah.
So, if I don't eat a woman out, I'm gay.
But if a woman don't want to give
[ __ ] completely fine. Bit rude,
isn't it? Bit sexist.
Why is there different rules for women
and different rules for men? I wish we
could just all be equal, you know?
Yeah, I don't like eating women out that
I that I've just met. No, it's disgusting.
Yeah, but you know Yeah, but you know
why they want to ruin lives, bro? Come
on, man. How long have you been on here?
They want to ruin lives because their
lives are ruined.
Oh, [ __ ] Oh, it's this one. Yeah, man.
Yeah, but they want to ruin lives
because they're fat, ugly people that
ain't got a life.
You know it. I know it, bro. So, it's no mystery.
They hope this ugly fat people cuz they
want to ruin lives. They got nothing.
Yes, that's that started it.
I don't like this cat, bro.
Look at it
just sat there waiting, picking its
moment, picking its next person to copy.
Look at it
looking for its next victim to copy. [ __ ] bad.
You know, I don't watch him to be fair, bro.
Why the [ __ ] would I eat USA out? That's disgusting, bro.
I bet her [ __ ] stunk worse than [ __ ]
I didn't smell it. I bet it stunk worse than Sigs. What about
what about if you don't want to lick
someone else? What about if you don't
want to lick someone out unless they're your wife?
Unless they're your wife or someone
you've been with for years. Or maybe if
they were a virgin. If they were a
virgin and I've been with them for a
very long time.
I would maybe. No, they don't. Desperate
simps eat [ __ ]
No, no, no, no. Desperate simps that get
dominated by women eat [ __ ]
No. Desperate simps that get dominated by women
because their simps eat [ __ ] Real men
don't eat [ __ ]
No, they don't.
So, how comes when women don't get blow
jobs, they're not called lesbians then? Strange.
Bit rude is it? Double standards.
Double standards. Like [ __ ]
The double standards is [ __ ] sickening them.
Yeah. They think they've got the right
to call people in themselves. Mad.
Man, it's mad, bro.
They sit there and defend women.
Well, well, if same same thing.
Um, well, same question to you. If a
woman doesn't suck dick,
why isn't she a lesbian?
Same same question to you, sir.
Same same question to you, sir. And I
can answer your question if you want me
to, but if you answer my question, I'll
answer you and I've got a good response.
Well, if a woman doesn't want to suck
dick, doesn't that make her a lesbian
then? Same thing goes back to Same
question goes back to you then?
Wouldn't that make a woman a lesbian if
she doesn't want to suck dick?
Can't be, you can't be one rule for one,
one rule for another. Bit bit biased in it.
You can't play two sides of a coin, lad.
Heads or tails? Heads or tails? Heads or
And I can answer you if you want me to.
I can actually answer that question, but
just wanted to throw that out there.
Wouldn't that also make the woman lesbian?
No. Just going to dismiss that. Don't
suit you. No. No. I didn't think it would. Um,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's not answering the question. Women
that don't suck dick don't well don't
get called lesbians,
right? Well, the same goes to me then.
If I wanted dick, I can get dick right
now. I can go and grind her.
Okay, same same answer then. If I wanted
dick and I was gay, I could go and grind
her right now. I'm pretty sure I've got
a couple of guys that will come around
right now and give me their dick. Next question.
So, you're saying that I'm gay? If I was
gay, I'm pretty sure I could get dick
very easy if I wanted to. So, it is
double standards then. There you go. Um,
and to answer your question, bet I
couldn't. Uh, bet I could. I bet I
could, mate. I've had loads and loads of
gay men hit on me. I absolutely could.
It's very easy to get dick. And also,
anyway, to answer your question, because
I don't want to seem rude, um, you can
absolutely not be gay and not want to
eat a woman out because not eating a
woman out does not mean you like dick.
The two have got nothing to do with each
other. The two doesn't have anything to
do with each other. Just because a man
doesn't like giving oral, right? That
doesn't make someone gay because they
don't want to taste someone's smelly ass
fanny who they've only met once. That
doesn't make someone [ __ ] gay.
That doesn't make someone gay.
Well, I'm not going to go and grind and
get one cuz I'm not [ __ ] gay. And
someone not eating [ __ ] doesn't make
them gay either.
That doesn't make someone gay, [ __ ]
That doesn't make someone gay.
Learn the definition of gay. Just like
like not liking several co doesn't make
someone gay. You little copycat. You No.
No. You little copycat.
You a copycat.
Look at this cat. Absolutely no mind of its own.
It doesn't matter if dicks are all
painted or not.
Some women don't like sucking dick. Some
women don't suck dick. So, does that
mean they're lesbians?
You double standard [ __ ] Yeah.
The double standard is [ __ ] insane. I
would advise I would advise anyone Yeah.
to not get into any of these debates.
Um, to be honest, that is that is a good
question. At least you didn't try and
call me gay. Um,
no. I wouldn't I wouldn't say I'm a I
wouldn't say I'm asexual, but that is
that's a good question. No, I wouldn't
say I'm asexual.
But it is more the fact that
I'd rather respect myself than ever have
to deal with any of these women ever
again cuz they're all toxic and they're
all the same and they all play games.
I think it's more of a case of
well yeah in the end I probably will be
asex I probably will be asexual to be
honest. I think in I think in the end I
probably will end up like that. Yeah. So
I think that is what it is
but not but it's more of a case of you
don't want to keep dealing with their
[ __ ] over and over and over again. It's
just not worth it to disrespect
yourself. They have nothing to offer.
They have nothing to offer anyone.
So just just headaches and problems. So
probably will be asexual now. Yeah,
to be honest. Yeah,
that's how they get you in the end.
Yeah, that's how they get you in the end, mate.
Cuz you keep giving for all the years.
You give them the benefit of the doubt
and they all act the same.
Same attitude, same dickheadness, same
game, same lies.
nothing but mind games and [ __ ] So victimizing themselves.
I think it's in them. I think these
women are the same because it's in them
from birth. You know how they say all
like men and women are different. Yeah.
So these women it's in them to them the
stuff they do is in them from birth.
It's something that they were born with.
Just eating some popcorn, bro.
I got steak later. I'm a bit hungry
because they've got unrealistic
standards and it makes them feel better about themselves. But
I will do a video when I come to B.
I can't believe the way that woman switched
just cuz I I saw no women leading me on mad madness.
They think all women are angels.
And then she was like, "Oh, well, I
don't get me wrong. Women can be wrong.
Women can be wrong. Bro, you've just
spent the past hour going back and forth with me,
bro. We We've just gone back and forth
for an hour
and you protesting women's innocence. I
don't think you think women can be wrong. So So
yeah, but the thing is it's not about
that they don't care about me, bro.
But then why do they moan in wings? They
can't find someone there.
And that's another thing um wins. So
right, here's another double standard.
Here's another double standard as well.
If you want
another double standard is um So if you
Yeah, that surprised me to be honest.
That surprised me that he doesn't get
anything either. But it it surprised me.
But at the same time, I still wouldn't
compare myself to him. So if I went out
on Saturday, I wouldn't sit there and
say, "Oh, well, he can't get anything,
so I can't get anything." But it did
surprise me. Yeah. But I wouldn't
compare myself to him because I would
still think that maybe I could get lucky
and he never.
So I wouldn't compare myself even to him.
I would think that, oh, like maybe I
don't know. I just wouldn't I don't
know, bro. Maybe I'm being delusional,
but I wouldn't.
Yeah, I wouldn't, bro.
But she was all right today until I
showed her like women leading me on and
[ __ ] cuz I wanted to know what her
problem was with men because we had
similar experiences. She was the same
age as me. I said, "What's happened?"
and that and she told me
but also another stand a double standard
thing is right is I was on Reddit
yesterday and I said oh I've given up
with women they're toxic it's the same
old [ __ ] with them over and over and
over and over and over and over and over again
and they were like oh if you give up you're weak-minded
weak minded but yeah it's okay for women
to keep going for the same shitty men
general generalizing men and then give
up and then they're giving a [ __ ]
silver spoon in their [ __ ] mouth.
They're given a [ __ ] silver spoon
with every [ __ ] flavor of porridge
that they choose in their mouth when
they want to give up. Even though
they're the ones that go for these men,
but then when you're sick of coming
across these same toxic women that are
full of [ __ ] oh, you're you're um you're weak-minded.
How the [ __ ] does that You see what I
mean, bro? It's [ __ ] mad. Man, this
[ __ ] hell, bro. But
if you don't want to eat [ __ ] you're gay. Mad.
Mad. I've given up, bro. I don't care
about it anymore.
I've given up. I don't care about it. I
don't want it that bad enough to try.
Yeah. Well, you just have to give up.
I've given up. But it's just these
people I keep coming across that keep
winding me up. That's the bit that winds
me up is them keep missing your
struggles. Dismissing your struggles.
It's not these women. They will always
be the same. They'll never change.
Just like what Oreo man said, they will never change.
Oh, and by the way, stating the obvious
means you're negative, by the way. Yeah.
People are born negative for no reason,
according to women's logic. So, people
come out of their mom's vagina, the
abilical cord gets snipped, and you
think to yourself, do you know what? I'm
going to go out and hate a bunch of women.
You know, that's what they say. Yeah.
They they they think that because
they think that as soon as the the
biblical cord gets snipped, right, you
think I'm just going to start hating
women for the sake of it. But that
doesn't make any sense though, does it?
If you think about it, we all know that
doesn't make sense.
No, all I know is he's a little copycat.
I only know it's a little copycat with
no [ __ ] mind of its own. Look at it.
Look at it's looking for its next victim to copy.
Sad, isn't it? Looking for its next
victim just to copy.
That's why I've always preferred dogs.
You copy cat. I am the funniest one
here. Is it?
Who did you say it looks like? win. So
I d the virgin and put USA Izzy's
picture back up.
Hello Greasy. All right, captain.
So what do you think of today's video? Oh yeah,
Windzo, they put [ __ ] USA. He put USA
back up in the community post. What is
with that Virgin and his [ __ ] stupid USA?
He has copycat eyes.
Look at that cat grievy.
Look at it staring, waiting, picking its
moment, looking for its next victim to
copy. Cuz it's got no mind of its own.
Because it's got no mind of its [ __ ] own.
Look at [ __ ] pathetic. Absolutely no
mind of its own.
That's why I have to copy.
Look at that copy guy.
Who's my daddy win? So
Yeah, she was all right. She was 28.
She's 28 just like me. She's 28, bro.
just like me. Yeah. I said to her,
"What's your experiences been like with
men?" And I told her my experiences with women.
And uh all of a sudden, I woke up to
this mad paragraph. Huh? Yeah.
[ __ ] I woke up to this mad paragraph,
bro. And I said, "Oh, let me show her
through screenshots." And she started
going at me saying, "No, women change their mind.
Anything to to not hold them responsible
for their actions. [ __ ] madness.
The world's [ __ ] lad. Anything to
think of this, Grezy, right?
If these women that have led you on have
really changed their mind, then they're
not mentally stable, are they?
Because people don't don't change their
mind that quickly. People don't just
change their mind that quickly. It's not
like someone's gone in a shop, right?
Was thinking of buying something and
then changed their mind.
I mean, it suggests that they're not
mentally stable, is it? If there if
people can change their mind so many
times that quickly. Yeah.
You right, Timmy?
Timmy said he had sex um not yesterday,
the day before.
Timmy, why do you lie so much?
Timmy lies so much.
Oh, she called me an incel by the way. Grimsy.
So basically, you're an incel if you
don't suck up to women. In other words,
Grimsy, if you don't suck up to women,
you're an incel.
That word gets so overly used now it
doesn't even mean anything.
If you don't lick women's asses and
you're not one of them little NPCs,
um, you're an incel.
[ __ ] hell, bro. I just can't.
>> And Greavvesy, you know what I think
this is? You know how your your parents
died, right? And obviously my dad died.
I think these people that simp and white
night over women have been brought up
that way by their father. They've been
brought up this way, but that it's not
the it's not the right way. The way
they've been brought up is not the right way.
Um, but I think that's what it is
because why, you would have thought to
yourself, Grezy, why are so many people
like this? This is what I want to touch
on in my video. Why are so many people like this?
Constantly make excuses for women, think
they can't do anything wrong. It makes
you wonder why are so many people like this.
And I reckon it's because they've been
brought up the wrong way by their father. Yeah.
I don't know. I'm I'm trying to figure
it out, Grezy. Maybe you can give me a
helping hand here, but I don't know what
what the problem is.
So, if I had a dad, I might be like one
of these little copycats.
I'll be like one of them little cats.
What do you think of that cat in the
picture, Triple H?
Look at it. Just look at the face. No substance.
No mind of its own.
No reason to live.
Sat there waiting.
Waiting to copy someone because it's got
no mind of its own. [ __ ] loser. Look
at it. It's just sat there waiting to copy.
Look at it. No mind of its own.
You look at it, mate. Just look at it.
Pathetic, mate. Absolutely pathetic.
It's why I've always preferred dogs. >> Yep.
>> My My sister might be buying me a dog,
by the way, Grezy. A Frenchie dog. Yep. Yeah,
as a treat.
I love it. We all before
Weezy, before I went to bed yesterday,
right before I went to bed yesterday, um
before I went to bed yesterday, Grezy, I
was thinking of what you said. You said
about autumn can be my mama for the
winter. I was dead. I was dead.
I was [ __ ] dead.
Oh, I was [ __ ] dead, bro.
That's funny, isn't it? This is the dog
I might be getting
if they reply back. It's [ __ ] cute. I
much prefer dogs. I don't like cats.
Look at that.
That's pathetic, mate. Wait for a
copycat statement to be made.
So, this is the dog. Look.
Look. Do you like it? It's [ __ ] cute.
It's a little one. A one. Little doggy. Yeah.
[ __ ] cute, is it? Oh,
look at that doggy. It's going to be mine soon. Little Mel.
Yeah. Do you like it?
We could I could do videos with the dogs
and take it to go and get some bagels and stuff.
Look at that.
Then you got this thing right here
waiting for a copycat statement to be made.
Look at it.
Look at that. Just sat there waiting.
You don't know what an orphan is?
You don't know what a [ __ ] orphan is?
These people on Instagram block for no
reason as well, don't they?
I'll follow them. They'll decline to
follow. I'll follow them again and then
they'll block me.
You want to see the dog again?
Look at that doggy. Do you like it?
He's cute. I want it.
So what you going to do, Grezy? When
there's a copycat statement,
when there's a copycat statement, then what? Greavves.
Why is it going to copy it?
Yeah, cats don't have any minds of their
own. They just copy.
That's why they copy each other. There's
videos on it. They copy.
You little copycat. You a little
Are you a little copycat?
You little copycat.
You're a little copycat. I said it to
that woman on Snapchat. I said, "You're
a little copycat." Copycat.
Yeah, I sent her my big [ __ ] Harley.
Do you know people on Reddit? They say
go on dating apps to get sex, don't they? Renoir.
They said go they say go on a dating app don't.
Yeah, but people on Reddit say go on them.
I don't really go out drinking much
anymore, bro. It's just toxic.
This is toxic and negative.
I was speaking to the girl tenant. I
said, "Let's go out." And she says, she
said, "I don't know since she said, "I
don't know since I don't have a house."
She's still not back in England, is it?
I said, "Oh, Maya."
That's her name. Maya May uh
I could try and get with her but nah it
wouldn't work Greasy. You know why it
wouldn't work don't you?
You know why I couldn't never get with
her in it?
I think you know Greavesy, don't you?
I think you know the answer to that Mom,
I couldn't can get with her anyways that uh
I said some mad [ __ ] to her, bro.
She deserved it. But we was talking in
it. I don't have a house. Nah,
she's not good enough.
You know why it no boobies
so you won't be able to get your vitamins?
I Kentucky Fried Pete. People keep
People on dating apps keep telling me to
go out and speak to women and stuff,
but every time I do, they say they've
all got bloody boyfriends. Oh gosh. You know
what do I do?
Why do they keep banning me on Reddit?
Um, Window, is it because they love
power? I I need to stop using this
Reddit, you know, bro, because they they
will just keep banning you, is it? It's
like they they live for the power.
All they do is [ __ ] live for the
power, you know?
It's like they actually live just to ban people. Yeah,
stop banning me.
And you'll be having a bloody
conversation and you get banned. It's annoying.
But they need that power, you know.
What I do? Yeah. is when I Yeah, it
doesn't matter about the DM. They ban
you from the whole thing.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. They do.
They do. They ban you from the whole
thing. Even when you just PM people, in
about an hour or two hours, it will come
up saying that you've been banned.
It will come up saying that you've been banned.
No, you still get banned.
I think they ban your device and it pops
up. No, no, no. Even if you're just
PMing people, you get banned.
It just takes an hour longer.
No, I don't think it is.
I think it's about your device cuz I've
used a VPN.
So, would you say they're power hungry
then? The mods, Greavvesy.
I think they're very, very power hungry.
So whenever I speak to someone, I try to
get them on Instagram ASAP or Snapchat
cuz that way the mods ain't got no
control, do they Greasy?
The mods ain't got no control then, do they?
They ain't got no control then.
Yeah, but they ban you for stupid
reasons though. That's what I'm saying.
They ban you for stupid reasons.
No other thing does it. No other place
does it, bro. But but Reddit,
they ban me again. Look, straight away
within 5 minutes. They need that power.
See, they live for the power. Mhm.
Yeah. They've done it again, bro.
They need that power.
They're absolutely [ __ ] all without it,
Grezy. They're [ __ ] all without that power.
Banning people. It's all power related.
You didn't realize that
they ban people that got different
opinions and them [ __ ] losers.
Yeah, Joseph Ferrar. I've seen him on
L's. He said that he's never going on
here. He's never going on my channel again. Griezy.
He doesn't like liars, but then he goes
on J's. All the irony. Yeah.
Oh, the irony.
So, what's the cat waiting for? A
copycat statement, Grezy.
And then what is he just going to copy? Yeah.
Y you come out with the funniest things.
>> You actually are funny, man.
>> That's why I keep feeling my shadow.
It will wait like the guy in the shop in it.
Why would anyone buy a dog looking like
that? Because the dog's cute. Yeah. Copycat statement.
These Reddit moderators have got no life in it.
They got absolutely no life other than
being a piece of [ __ ] on Reddit. It all simps. Ew.
A simp. Ew.
Ew. A s. Ew. E. Crazy.
Ew. A simp.
What's the dog? Wait. What's the cat
waiting for? We say
A copycat statement to be made. Yeah.
And then what happened? Yeah. Yeah. And
then what? It looks like a virgin
[ __ ] Don't agree with me.
Yeah. And then what happens when it's been made?
been made? Greasy.
Well, we'll just copy it in it.
That's I think that's why Virgin Boy
liked cats so much. He never used to
like dogs. He was scared of dogs. Um, it
has to be a male. The dog has to be a
male. It can't be a female because of
when it goes on heat.
And I don't like females. They're [ __ ] [ __ ] So yeah. Yeah.
That's why he always used to like cats
cuz he was scared of dogs obviously. He
never used to like dogs. He always used
to like cats. I wonder why. Where has it gone?
Oh, that's better. £1,150. Yeah. £1,150.
Some this woman said no one needs sex. I
said of course they need sex otherwise
people wouldn't be having it. If people
didn't need sex they wouldn't have it.
Isn't that right Grezy?
Yeah. And I said to the girl tenant that
she can come and live with me if she has
no she said she's got nowhere to go. So
she she can come and live with me.
Yeah. I said you can come and live with me.
Yeah. But she's got no boobies. Greavves.
Would that be a problem, Greavvesy, if
she doesn't really have big boobies?
No, not really.
That average? Yeah,
it's not going to be a problem, is it, Grezy?
What do you think?
Yeah, but I want the nutrition from her. Laney.
Oh, women ignore us, Grezy. Yeah,
they're definitely definitely definitely
ignorous. We need to stop talking about
this now, though. Is it Grezy?
Because what does it end in? Feeling
like the boy who cried wolf, you know?
Yeah. It will just end in feeling like
the boy who cried wolf. And that's never
fun, is it?
Nope. The boy who cried wolf. Yeah.
I think Ant-Man is an undercover hater.
What do you think, Greavvesy?
I don't know.
I have this vibe that he's an undercover hater.
Do you know what it means, Grezy? You
might not know what it means.
Do you know what it means? I'm sure you
do, bro. You're not stupid.
You know, you know what I mean, is it?
an undercover hater.
An undercover hater.
I bet that made you laugh in it earlier,
Greavves, on the Snapchat when she's
like, "Fuck off.
You need to [ __ ] off.
Well, she soon switched on me.
She switched, bro.
Where's the [ __ ] virgin?
The [ __ ] virgin.
You [ __ ] virgin. [ __ ] [ __ ]
I think they ban people on Reddit to
cause embarrassment as well, Grezy. Cuz
obviously when you're speaking to
someone and they ban you, you have to go
on another account and say, "Oh, look,
they ban me.
We're going to make a cup of [ __ ] in a minute.
Women are so fake and phony. It's a joke.
They're all the [ __ ] same.
They're all the [ __ ] same, mate. What
a [ __ ] same.
Is Lex still going live?
Waiting for a copycat statement.
The cat find
attractive as well. Yeah. copying.
You [ __ ] mad bastard
there. No mind of its own.
Just sat there looking to copy.
No [ __ ] mind of its own. Little copycat.
in no copycat. No.
Did you find me a phone yet, Steven
Howard? I was looking at the iPhone 16.
It was It's £700.
What about that phone? Is that good?
iPhone 16. 7 uh 700.
Brand spanking new.
Is that good? iPhone 16.
My sister's got an iPhone 12 the same as
Ant-Man. It cost £150 refurbished.
She said it works fine.
That's what Antman's got. Yep.
iPhone 16 brand spanking new is 700.
I don't know, man. I might just get that one, bro.
I'm just used to buying stuff new, you
know, like TV stands and stuff and even
like wardrobe. Like you can buy that
[ __ ] secondhand, but with devices, you
don't really want to buy them secondhand.
You know, you don't know what's been on
it. I don't know, bro. I just
It's when you buy something new, like
when you buy something brand new, you
know it's new. You know there's not
going to be no problems,
you know. That's that's that's the end,
That's why I think I always like to
stuck to like new stuff because, you
know, it's brand new. There's nothing
that can go wrong and if anything did go
wrong, you can just send it back. But
the chances are,
you know, it's like added worry if you
buy something secondhand. You know what
I mean? But it's nothing to do. It's
[ __ ] new. So save from the battery. yeah. Yeah.
But who knows, eh? Who knows?
Oh, I can actually get a fold seven if I
want on contract.
My credit's gone up now, but I'm not
going to do it. Pointless.
It's pointless, isn't it?
I could get like a year contract and pay
like £200 a month.
Yeah, you pay like £200 a month and then
after a year the phone.
I think I'd only ever get like a year
contract now if I was get only get a contract phone
like [ __ ] can pay it within a year
cuz if you pay it in a year 170 200 a
month in a year you've paid it. So
I don't really like I don't know like
but it's only a year is it
bro I'm not getting a fold this year bro that pointless
they're [ __ ] beautiful though they
are when they're brand [ __ ] new when
they're brand spanking [ __ ] new mate.
Them [ __ ] foes. Oh, handsome.
[ __ ] handsome. Greasy.
They're [ __ ] beautiful.
[ __ ] beautiful, mate.
They're just so bloody dear.
So anyways, go find me a phone, bro.
You bloody [ __ ]
I don't know. [ __ ] knows, bro.
You blooming [ __ ]
How you going to lose it?
I don't know what I'm going to do about
this phone. win. So,
I can get a fold on contract, but
there's a few problems with it. I don't
really want to get the fold this year. I
don't really want to get the fold this
year, bro, because it's no different
than the next one. But then you can get
an iPhone 16 brand new for like £700.
Might seem £700 a lot of money, but the
phone's going to last you a couple of years though.
Yeah, I could get the flip. They're
like, "Yeah, they're $850. I could
probably buy it outright." Yeah,
but I don't really want to work with the
phone. If I wanted If I wanted to do
delivery again, I wouldn't really want
to work with that phone. You know what I mean?
I I don't really want to work with
That's the problem. You see,
I wouldn't want to work with the phone.
I don't know. I just want all the work
on the phone I use.
I don't need a loan. I've got the money.
It's nothing to do with the loan. I've
got the money.
Why would I take out a loan, bro? For what?
Why am I taking out loans, bro?
No, but the thing is with the flips though, they're um
No, I don't want to work like I don't
want to get the phone and have to work
on the phone when I do deliveries. I
don't want to work on that phone. That's
what I'm trying to say to you. I don't
want to work on that the phone that like
my main phone.
I mean, you could buy the flip and then
just just work for like a week and then
you probably make a lot of money, but
I'd have to get a I'd have to get a case
for the phone.
Oh, I don't know, bro.
The refurbished phone seemed a good idea, but
I'm not used to buying stuff used, bro.
I sound like such a snob when I say that, but
the thing with the flips is the screen
goes off a while.
Uh, we can we could No, it lost. I think
it could last a while. Um,
yeah, the flip is 849. Yeah,
it is an option. That is a good option. But then
I don't know.
Did you get a case for it?
I got this fold in it.
We had that 849 there.
I could probably stretch to that to be fair.
Yeah, there's flips and there's folds. Yeah. Uh
Yeah. 849. That's not really that um
that's not really that bad.
It's not really that like
it's not that bad, bro. But
I don't know, bro. I don't know what I'm
going to get.
That's how much they are. 8 850.
Let's hope some [ __ ] don't [ __ ]
snatch it in it. Then we'd be [ __ ]
We'd be [ __ ] in it.
There's an iPhone 14 in here,
495, and you could work on that one. So,
you could work on that one with a lovely
case. Surely that would be good enough.
There's some good phones here.
iPhone 15 is 600.
I'm just looking, bro. It's hard to make
up your mind with these. Yeah. Oh. Hold on.
Yeah, the Flip is a good phone. It's a
flagship phone as well.
What RAM has it got?
Yeah, it's got 12 GB of RAM.
I don't think that's that bad, you know. 850, bro.
I don't think it's that bad.
No, I really really don't.
But then it's [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah, that it [ __ ] boy.
Imagine you have the phone for one month
though and it packed up.
You'll be [ __ ] then in it. You will be
[ __ ] then, won't you?
It would never happen. Never happen.
I'm such a materialistic little [ __ ] in
it. I thought as I got older would
change, but nah.
Well, no. I'm not that bad.
But I like to get stuff new.
Because you get a case for them um flips.
I like to buy stuff new and know that
that that ain't it.
You paid for it now. [ __ ] 850. That's
not that bad, bro.
Well, I might buy it. Yeah.
get like a e sim in it. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. The 850. The phones.
I think I had like two grand last month,
but I had to buy some stuff. I had to
I had to buy jeans. I had to buy [ __ ]
I had to buy jeans and
I had to buy jeans and [ __ ] um
had to buy jeans and uh
had to buy jeans and [ __ ]
trainers and [ __ ] Oh.
Oh. What more?
Oh, that virgin boy.
You can you can either buy the fault.
You can either buy the flip out right here
or you just pay every month or a year.
which is not going to be as much as the
fold. So you pay it every month,
but after a year it's your phone,
but you have to change the SIMs to work.
That's the thing because you can't work
on a free SIM.
But the thing is, you can't work on a free SIM.
You can't work on a free sim because if
you try to work on a free sim,
you can't work on a free sim, bro, because um
you can't work on a free sim because the
signal don't work.
But when I on that Uber, I had mad
problems with that free sim. I had to
change the sim.
Yeah. Well, I'm still going to keep No,
it does call. No, no, no, no. The phone I've got
the phone that I've got.
No, no, no. The phone that I've got,
it does call it [ __ ] but only on
Wi-Fi. But you never have any problems with it.
You never have any problems with it.
No, no, no. The phone,
the phone that doesn't call, you don't
have problems with it cuz you just use
it on Wi-Fi. So, whenever you're in a
bar, there's Wi-Fi everywhere. So, it
never affected me because everywhere
there's But obviously, I'll need a phone
when I travel abroad and [ __ ] I'm
trying to think about what the best option is.
No, it calls and stuff on Wi-Fi. So,
whenever you're on Wi-Fi, it works
normally. It just doesn't work off
Wi-Fi. So, if you wanted to meet
someone, you just go outside a pub and
you meet them. It's not a problem. But,
but the thing is, you can't work on a
free because the signal [ __ ] When I was
doing that Uber thing before,
when I was doing that Uber thing before,
bro, the [ __ ] sim where the signal
was so [ __ ] it it kept cutting off and
I had to leave the bike somewhere and go
back for it and I had to change the sim
to the e sim.
So, I'm just thinking what to do. Yeah.
I'll think I'll think about it.
What's actually doing it?
Or you could get on contract and just
get a year contract. No.
No. But I got the Uber one back.
So, it's either you get you get the
phone on a year contract, just pay it
off, or you just buy the phone outright
for 850. I don't [ __ ] know. It's
hard, isn't it? Hard to choose.
You know how it is, isn't it, bro? Oh,
this charge is [ __ ] Yay.
It kept sending me to It keeps it kept
sending me to [ __ ] Elephant and Castle, bro.
I don't know why it kept sending me to
[ __ ] Elephant and Castle.
Yeah, it just kept sending me to [ __ ]
elephant and castle, bro, every time
[ __ ] weird, bro. Imagine the [ __ ] nah
nah the [ __ ] out.
Yeah. I said to this this tenant, I
said, "Oh, you can come and live with
me." She said, "Oh, do you have a spare room?"
The boobs aren't big enough. Why? He
kept sending me to [ __ ] Elephant and
Castle win. So, it's [ __ ] weird, isn't it?
Bless Triple H if he's got the Sumson A25.
Oh, bless your Triple.
Bless you in life.
Bless your little cotton socks then if
that's what you've got.
Bless you in life then.
Bless you if that's what you've got. Oh, bless.
That's cute, isn't it?
That is so [ __ ] cute. Bless you.
Yeah. Kept sending me to [ __ ]
elephant and castle. [ __ ] off, man.
Elephant and castle. Elephant and
castle. Elephant and bloody castle. What
is it with [ __ ] elephant and castle? Huh?
What is it with that place?
What happened in anything in Castle? Uh, Windsor.
What do you think happened there?
[ __ ] weird place, isn't it?
That's a weird place. It's where you met
your mama. It's where you met your mama.
Where you met your mama?
One second, bro. One second.
That [ __ ] virgin. again.
That [ __ ] virgin, mate.
I made myself a cup of [ __ ] in a Yeah. Nothing, bro.
Make myself a cup of [ __ ] in a minute.
Uh, that's what I'm doing, mate. Yeah,
I've got a lot of [ __ ] history in
Elephant and Castle to break.
I make myself a cup of C.
[ __ ] [ __ ] mate.
Lovely cup of heat.
them little copycats.
Them little copycats.
Look at that picture. Triple H.
Just look at it. Look at the [ __ ] picture.
Just look at the [ __ ] picture.
It's clear. It's got no mind of its own.
It's got absolutely
absolutely no mind of its own
to break. What do you think of that? A [ __ ]
cat. A [ __ ] cat that's got no mind of its own.
What do you think of that? A little cat
that's got absolutely no mind of its own. Look.
Looking for the next person to copy.
Every time I say stuff about women, they
keep banning me on Reddit. Winso, they
keep banning me, bro.
Every time you post like, "Why are women
shallow?" They keep banning me and stuff. Huh?
Bit rude, isn't it?
I don't [ __ ] know who that bloody virgin is.
You keep [ __ ] banning me.
Oh, the mod simps or something.
There's so many simps nowadays, Triple
H. It's actually scary, lad.
So many [ __ ] simps.
So ew, a s.
E, a s. a simp.
You know what s means, don't you, Triple H?
Yeah, you know what a simp is
So many stalkers on this [ __ ] downy community, bro.
Why does this [ __ ] Jamie Thompson
keep stalking me when sir?
Oh my god, they're proper stalkers
on here, bro. As soon as I turn my sim
back on, they're [ __ ] stalkers on
here, bro. You think it's Do you think
it's jealousy win? So
[ __ ] leave me alone, you fat ugly stalkers.
I don't know how she knew about my
YouTube channel, bruh. more.
Life is stressful, bro. Very stressful. One sec.
Trying to sort out a bastard phone here. One second.
So, one second, bro.
We're trying to see how much this will
be for a year contract.
That's obviously for that.
So be like, "Please one second, bro. I
need to focus on this. Hold on."
Samsung Ultra. I'm looking at that one.
20 pound maybe 23.
So it goes up by two pound.
So you'll pay £102 a month for a year. Yeah.
And after the year,
basically the phone is yours.
110. I'm trying to look up these phones here, bro.
It goes down a pound every day if you didn't know.
I'm trying to sort out a phone, Mr. B. I
don't know what phone to get.
This one seems good. £110 a month for a
year and you've paid it off. After a
year, you obviously pay the phone off in it.
So, it's only a year contract. I'd only
get a year contract cuz you never know
and [ __ ] gets stolen and that
[ __ ] bro. [ __ ] guys.
I don't [ __ ] know, bro.
[ __ ] knows, man. [ __ ]
Charge as [ __ ]
That's one thing I do know. Triple H is
this Mr. B is just [ __ ] control is [ __ ] mate.
I'm trying to figure out what what you
could do about this phone, bro.
Trying to think what the best solution is.
cuz you can pay £100 a month for a year.
I generally think that's the best bet
if you as long as you can change the sim
so you can work on it.
I'm trying to think, bro. Um,
I'm trying to think.
What do you think, Mr. B? What phone
should I get?
You get this Ultra and pay 110 a month
for a year.
I'm trying to think, bro,
what to get.
Can't get the fold cuz you can't work on the fold.
That's the thing with that.
I need to be earning some kind of money
in order to pay it.
I don't have to go into my own money.
That's the thing.
[ __ ] madness. Yeah.
Yeah, but what Galaxy?
I could either get like a phone, buy it
outright, or I could go and I have to
pay an upfront payment or I could pay
upfront payment, but no, but then that's
a con because you're paying the upfront payment.
Yeah, but what one, bro? There's loads of galaxies.
I'd probably say the ultra. You can't
You can't do the fold on Uber, mate.
That's [ __ ] And if you drop it,
you'll [ __ ] it up.
So, I'm thinking get the Ultra,
but they're like a,000 [ __ ] pound, bro.
They're like a thousand. I mean, you can
get a contract, but again, you'd have to
change the SIM because you don't get no
signal on free.
[ __ ] knows, man.
Absolutely [ __ ] nos.
You can get a flip, but it's not going
to be any good for Uber because the way
it is. So,
Yeah, Lord knows, bro.
Yeah, I'll cry, bro. That's the thing.
I would be [ __ ] [ __ ]
You can get a refurbished iPhone, but
would that be any good? Should be. No.
iPhone 12 refurbished.
He's got a refurbished iPhone 12 and he
said it works fine. He said just get a refurbished one.
The iPhone 13 refurbished is like um 270.
So save a lot of [ __ ] money in it.
Yeah, he's got TW. He's got iPhone 12.
He's had it for ages.
I don't know, bro. It's giving me a headache.
If you know what I mean, matey. Yeah.
So, what do you think? iPhone 13 refurbished.
You think that'll be good enough when?
But the thing that scares me is the battery.
I mean, you can buy a new battery, but
then it's like 350. It's just madness, bro.
I don't know what option to go down
to be honest.
I'm sure if you buy an iPhone 13
refurbished, you can do Uber enough to
make enough money.
Not really. No, but it seems the best option.
No, but I've got a Samsung Fold. I can
still use this as a tablet in it. So, I
can use this as a tablet and that one as the phone
cuz I'm still going to have this phone as well.
Yeah. So, with a new battery, it's like 350.
That's how much I'll be paying is 350.
But obviously, I still got this phone as well. So,
[ __ ] knows, bro. I got this phone as
like a main phone and that would just be
like a calling phone. Um,
I don't know, bro. I I I don't [ __ ] know.
I'll just wait out in it for a couple
months. I guess
the only option is the flip. I'd buy the
flip for 850, but you can't do the Uber on it.
No, I wouldn't do the Uber with it. So,
it' be pointless. Yeah. [ __ ] no.
Or you can buy an iPhone 13 new.
Is it new or is it refurbished? One second.
No, it can't be new.
Yeah, you can get a used one. You can
get a refurbished one. Yeah,
you can get a refurbished. One second, bro.
There's an iPhone 13 here.
I don't mind getting
I like Samsung more, but
I don't know. I don't know what I'm doing. Uh
I don't know if that's new.
Yeah, but you don't know what they've
done with that phone. That's the
problem. You don't know what they've
done with that phone.
When you buy refer when you buy used,
you don't know about the phone. I don't
really like buying devices used
because you don't know what they've they
could have downloaded [ __ ] child porn
on it for, you know, battery could be [ __ ] Um,
is this new? I'm trying to think. Is
this new? Just there. The iPhone 13.
It It says it's 49 here.
I don't know if it's new.
It doesn't say if it's new or not.
I don't know what to do, bro. Oh, this
is [ __ ] bad. Uh,
you just give me some ideas.
Yeah. Uh, Antman's got iPhone 12. He's
had it for years.
I reckon I'm just going to have to get
this flipped. To be honest, just to be
on the safe side. I'm up money from
gambling in it. So, I'm up money from
gambling. So, I just have to fork out
for it. Simple.
What else you going to [ __ ] spend the money on?
What other What other phone? The blocked
phone that don't work in it.
Yeah, this phone doesn't. Yeah, I'm No,
I'm not getting the 12. I'll get the 13.
I won't get the 12. I'll get the 13.
Yeah, this is the phone I use for
personal use. This is But it's blocked. But yeah.
Yeah, but it's the battery. That's what
I'm trying to say to you. It's the
battery that's concerning me, bro.
I'm scared of buying used or refurbished
stuff. That's what I'm trying to say. My
mama's got a refurbished phone. It cost 110. iPhone.
It's an iPhone, bro.
And you can [ __ ] off your little self
projector. Fantasy stories.
You're not coming in projector.
Um, so yeah.
Yeah, you could get the iPhone 13 and do
Uber and then just use this one and then
get the fold. Then you can get the Fold
8 next month.
Nope, we're not doing this on this
channel arguing with idiots.
Um, what do you think of that then,
Wind? So, do you reckon just get the
iPhone 13, hammer the [ __ ] Uber and
use this one for personal use and then
just get the Fold 8 next year?
I get the fold eight next year. I don't
want to get I can get it, but there's no
difference in the year between a year or
I'll get the flip.
I use this as like a tablet, this [ __ ] phone.
You're gone. Bye-bye.
No self projector on this channel.
What do you think, bro?
I think that's the only option you got,
bro. Cuz the thing is, if you buy a flip,
you can't use it for Uber. If you buy a
fold, you can't use it for Uber, which
even if you done a couple of hours a
week, it would pay for the phone
contract and I'd have to keep up with the contract.
I reckon that's your best bet to be
honest. This has got like something on
the screen, but it still works.
But I'm not getting 12. I'm not getting iPhone 12.
Oh, you can get the iPhone 16 for 700 brand new
and you can do the Uber on that one, but then that's
what's it like? But then it's only So,
you're only paying double really and you
know it's brand new. Who knows, bro? Who [ __ ] knows?
>> All right, PJ. How you doing, lad?
>> One second. One second. It's gone quite old.
>> Fantasy stories is Skint. Yeah, he's got
no money. He makes out. He's got all
this. He thinks that an 80 TV from Argus
is worth a grand. He put a screenshot
watch on. He owns no one. I'll come to
Ireland. And he thinks his little
precious Irish community is going to
save. Fantasy is the skintest we [ __ ]
that he has to have.
>> I can't even hear him, bro. I need to [ __ ]
So, you either get the one that's £350
or you get the £700 one and then just
work your ass off and just get the money
back for that.
But that way, you know, the battery
would be good in it.
Wait, let me look at these. Let me look
at this again.
Even if you made half the money back,
theoretically you only paid 350. [ __ ]
I can't hear him properly, bro.
Um, one sec.
There's an iPhone 14 for 495.
There's an iPhone 16 for 700.
That would be good cuz then if you got a
case, you could make a lot of that money
back within a week.
But then there's an iPhone 16e.
I'm trying to think, bro. I'm really
cuz we'll be making money back on this
phone. Is it?
There's an iPhone 15. That's 600.
This is mad, bro. These are so
We'll have one Samsung and one iPhone
cuz the thing is uh when you I £350 for
a refurbished phone. It's quite a lot,
isn't it? For a refurbished phone.
For a refurbished phone is quite a lot, isn't it? Yeah.
So then it's like I don't know, bro. I'm indecisive.
But then you could just get one for [ __ ]
[ __ ] murder, didn't it?
The [ __ ] version can't
win. So, would you actually get a
[ __ ] um would you actually get a refurbished phone? Sunny day.
What? You [ __ ] drinking you can.
You're drinking. You [ __ ] [ __ ]
The other phone was a£400 phone that I
used, but now it's down to 250.
Yeah, it's a Samsung. It's down to 250.
Look at this [ __ ] copy. Copycat.
Look at this [ __ ] copycat.
Look at this little copycat.
Yeah, they're £1,000.
No, I'm not.
Yeah. Ultra. Yeah.
I'll have to do some more research on this.
What is that? What you got? S25 Ultra,
Mr. B. Is that what you got?
You got an iPhone 8? [ __ ] hell.
Yeah, if you buy the iPhone Ultra, you
can do Uber.
What? You got an You got an iPhone 8?
That's the thing. A lot of people don't
update the [ __ ] iPhones, do they?
A lot of people, they don't [ __ ] um
update the iPhones, do they? No,
but they still stay on the same one from
[ __ ] 10 years ago. Surprised they make money.
Yeah. What's the ultra thousand? And
yeah, I could probably
then we'd have to do the [ __ ] Uber
every [ __ ] day then, won't we, mate?
We'd have to do the [ __ ] Uber every
[ __ ] day if you got that phone, mate.
Every day. I mean, it's worth it really
because you could just make a lot of the
money back from the Uber, couldn't you?
Really? If you think about it, what's it
going to last you? 2 years.
What's it going to last you
realistically? What? 2 years? Yeah.
2 years, 2 and a half years, maybe 3 years.
What will you make in a week? What? Three400 pound.
Don't forget January. You don't go out
January, do you? Virgin boy
getting his little bed [ __ ] with no bed,
no money in it. Nah, bro. Not even. Yeah, but
what about that [ __ ] virgin,
Steven Howard? What about that [ __ ] virgin?
Yeah. What is this ultra
You should be able to do Uber on that.
Was it 999? Yeah.
What is it? A flagship phone.
That's a flagship phone, isn't it?
How much I paid for my other one? 400.
400. Is it?
That one was [ __ ] [ __ ] though.
Yeah, that one was [ __ ] [ __ ]
This charge is fat.
This charge is absolutely fat. See you, Boring.
See you later, fantasy stories.
Isn't that right?
Fantasy stories is boring.
I [ __ ] virgin.
Just like that [ __ ] virgin.
That [ __ ] virgin. One second.
Boring. Go away fantasy stories. Stop self projecting.
Stop talking about yourself. We're here
talking about phones.
Not talking about how you're all of them things. Self projector.
So many self projectors on here. Hey Joe,
bro. So many [ __ ] self projectors.
[ __ ] phone, bro.
What is wrong with this charger?
This [ __ ] charger is [ __ ] [ __ ] lad. Virgin boy.
Skinny little [ __ ] No money in it.
Oh, that virgin boy.
What? Oh, that virgin boy. See, I need
to go out in two weeks.
I need to go out in two weeks with my sister. Yeah,
cuz I said I was going to go out in two
weeks. Is it
So yeah, the F will be [ __ ] then.
Yeah, I would stay in as long as
possible if I can, bro.
No point going out anymore. Stay. [ __ ]
It's the same thing every time you go
out in it.
Yeah, but if you pay So if you pay grand
for this phone,
you could probably make the money back
in probably like two weeks.
I mean, what else are you going to be
doing in January? So, you need to think
about these things. You need to think like
you need to think about it long term, you know,
long term. You need that's what you need
to think about these things.
What two weeks maybe you probably get
like 7800 pound in two weeks. So
yeah, basically I wouldn't go out again
until mid like I said mid December.
Still got some money left as well
on the thing. The winners in it.
I just charge it. [ __ ] lad.
Yeah, I might get this Samsung Ultra phone, bro.
And just hammer these hours and
it'll be worth it in the long run
when it's going to last you [ __ ] 3
years, isn't it?
I think it's worth it, m bro.
You don't know when the battery is going
to [ __ ] up.
Obviously, you'll need to get like a nice case.
I reckon it's worth it. I reckon it's
worth the investment.
to be honest.
I bet a [ __ ] I bet a v I bet the
virgin couldn't afford that phone in it
cuz he's a [ __ ] virgin.
Virgins don't Virgins don't have that
kind of money, mate.
You know it. I know it. You know it. I
know it, mate.
That these virgins don't have this kind
of money, mate. Cuz they're [ __ ]
skint skint than a [ __ ] skin flinch. Skint
than a [ __ ] skin flint, mate.
So what? Okay, so what about this
Samsung Galaxy Fold that I've got?
Is Is this Is this a Is this a uh is
this a piece of plastic?
Yeah, but this fold is a this fold is a flagship phone.
Steven, this it's a it's a flagship phone.
They never go slow. They never
do anything, you know.
I wonder what phone USA Izzy has.
I wonder I wonder what phone USA is he has.
You absolute virgin.
I can't stop saying that, you know.
You know, I can't stop saying that.
I'm [ __ ] you know. I'm actually like
me. I actually [ __ ] I'm actually
[ __ ] mate. I'm actually [ __ ] up,
You don't understand, bro. I'm actually [ __ ]
You don't believe me. You actually don't
believe me. I'm actually [ __ ] in the head.
You're an absolute virgin.
Do you like it when I say that?
You absolute virgin.
When I first saw that [ __ ] nonslegs,
yeah, with that Christian, I was like,
two absolute virgins.
Absolute ones, mate. Abso [ __ ] ones.
Two absolute virgins.
You know, I'm [ __ ] light, mate.
mate. He's a [ __ ] big virgin. He's
What can I say? He's a [ __ ] absolute
[ __ ] big [ __ ] virgin, mate. He's a
big [ __ ] virgin.
is a big big big big big virgin. Massive.
Massive [ __ ] virgin, mate. Massive [ __ ] virgin. Yeah,
I [ __ ] virgin here, mate. You [ __ ]
big virgin, mate.
Absolute big [ __ ] virgin me. Big
[ __ ] virgin me. Absolute big [ __ ] virgin.
I had I had £1,700 last month. Steven Howard,
that's good, isn't it?
Yeah, that's good. £1,700. That's how
much I had £1,700,
bro. We must be [ __ ] shitloads up
from this [ __ ] football, mate.
Must be shitloads up from this [ __ ] football.
We got to be
Yeah, I had about 1,700 pound. I had to
buy trainers. I had to buy jeans. I UGG
boots. So, I'm definitely just saving this time.
But I do need a good phone. This is the problem, bro.
This is the problem.
I could easily just get a £270 phone, but
I don't know. I fancy being materialistic.
I fancy being a materialistic [ __ ] You
know what I'm like. Come on, mate. You
know what I'm [ __ ] like, mate.
Yeah. 1,700 pound.
It says that the Ultra's got 12 GB of
RAM though, Steven Howard.
It says it's got 12 uh 12 GB of RAM.
That would be my little baby, bro. Wow. Bless you.
Yeah, but they're not Samsung songs, are
they, Steven Howard?
They're not bloody Samsums, are they?
Yeah, but I want to fit in. I want to be
a little copycat.
Why can't I go in with the hype? I want
to be a little copycat.
I want to be a little copycat. You live. Meow.
Well, I want to be a little copycat.
Why am I not allowed to be a little copycat?
It's not fair, is it?
I want to be a little copycat. No,
I'm a little copycat. Steven Howard,
I'm a little copycat. Meow. Meow. Meow.
Do you want a copycat? Statement.
Little copycat. Little copycat. Little
copycat. No. Little copycat. You little
copycat. You little copycat. You little
copycat. M. Little copycat. You little
cat. Little copycat. You cat. You a
copycat. You little copycat. You little
copycat. You little copycat, mate. You a little copycat.
I was thinking of getting a Samsung Galaxy
Samsung Galaxy S25 Ultra Grezy,
but Steve, it's it's £1,000. But Gre But
Steven said it's a bad idea.
Yeah. Steven Howard says it's a bad idea.
Yeah, I like milk.
Why is it a bad idea? Greavvesy.
Are you jealous?
Oh, [ __ ] bro.
Why? What? Because I want to be a little copycat. [ __ ] bro.
Why am I not allowed to be a copycat?
I am materialistic. I [ __ ] am, aren't
I? I am, but I'm not a skin [ __ ] from
Kent. I am materialistic. I might buy a
phone and do a video on it and show the virgin.
I'm very materialistic. I need to be stopped.
But no one no one's going to stop me,
mate. No one's going to stop me. You
know what I'm like? I'm very very I am materialistic.
I am very materialistic, mate. Very [ __ ] materialistic.
I [ __ ] am. Are I?
I can't help it. I can't help what I am. You know,
I could buy it and then and show the copycat.
What do you think of that? And then show
the copycat. We
and I can show you a little copycat.
What do you think, Reevesy? And I can
show a little copycat.
We What do you think? What do you think, Reevesy? Shycat.
Can shine a little copycat? What do you think?
A little copycat.
Yeah, they used the copycat used to sound materialistic
and what I was trying to explain to him
this little virgin is you know when
people have money
if they earn more money or they win
money or whatever it is you know your
lifestyle changes grezy you know like
I'm talking generally your lifestyle
changes when you have more money I mean
people live within their means do you
know what living within your means means means.
No, bro. None. Do you know what living
within your means means?
It means you live within your means. So,
whatever money you get,
you're you're living within your means.
That's what that is. It's not
materialistic. It's living within your means.
So, you think, right, okay. Okay. So,
let's just say that you was a
millionaire. What are you supposed to
get like 200 pound phones if you was a millionaire?
You understand what I'm saying? Like your
your lifestyle changes depends on what
what you have, how much you get and stuff.
I never used to think I'd be able to
afford Stone Islands.
Yeah, it's cute, isn't it? for a little
Samson. Steven Howard is cute, isn't it?
Yeah, it's cute, right? It
Yeah, you are a nons. You [ __ ] stupid prick.
Yeah, you are nons you know. Yeah, basically.
But if I bought this if I bought this
phone, do you think I'm going to be in
debt? Do you reckon I'm going to be skinned? Obviously not. not, lad.
You see what I mean?
Yeah, I'll meet you anytime, bro. You
little [ __ ] Don't [ __ ] come on my
channel trying to [ __ ] troll me, you
[ __ ] ugly man. Was that [ __ ] you dancing?
You [ __ ] [ __ ] Well, I'll [ __ ]
break your [ __ ] jaw, you silly [ __ ]
Don't get [ __ ] sloppy with me, you
[ __ ] Isn't that right, Greavvesy?
Is that right, Greavves? Don't get
[ __ ] sloppy with me, you silly [ __ ]
Don't get [ __ ] sloppy with me, you silly [ __ ]
You [ __ ] little bogo. Don't [ __ ]
come on my [ __ ] you [ __ ] simp dick sucker.
Yeah, come to London, you [ __ ] bog.
Go back to Lord J's. Have a timeout. Oh,
ban you. Bye-bye now.
Did you Did you do it? What's How much
do you get back?
Nice, bro. I must get back.
Oh [ __ ] man.
This charge is [ __ ] lad. Virgin boy.
How is Virgin boy? Steven Howard.
Where's the [ __ ] converging?
Where's that [ __ ] virgin?
Oh, that [ __ ] virgin boy.
That virgin boy is bad.
Yeah, they're playing tomorrow.
Yeah, I won't be putting a [ __ ] bet on it.
on it. [ __ ] that.
[ __ ] that, bro.
Oh, really? That virgin boy is mad.
That virgin boy is [ __ ] mad.
That virgin boy is mad.
Graves is [ __ ] bad. That baby boy got P.
I need to go pee pe
make myself a cup of con Yo
yo yo yo. So
what I was saying, um, yeah. Ben
cleaning his little big [ __ ] We don't
burden nobody in it.
That's what I was saying. Oh, Franklin's
gone up to 22 pound Grezy. Yeah,
he's gone up to [ __ ] 22 [ __ ] quid.
He was 50. He come out today was $49.99
and now he's a lot more
mad. Is it?
I think I'm going to cancel him and then
just buy and then just buy the game outright.
It makes more sense though cuz it's the
only game I play. Well, I'm Black Ops,
but I pay for Black Ops.
Yeah, I can just buy the game though. Is it?
Yeah. So, if I do that,
so if I get, as I was saying with the
phone, if I get a phone contract for a
year, Greg, yeah, I'm paying like 110 a
month for a year.
So, like I was saying, I think you might
as well just do that. Just just pay
monthly for a year and then the phone is
yours, isn't it? I think that's what it
is, isn't it? If you pay if you pay the
contract for a year,
then I don't think then obviously they
can't block it after the year, can they? Yeah,
I need to cancel. Well, how much do I
pay for my symbol? £33 for unlimited everything.
Yeah, I might I think I'm just going to
do that to be honest. Yeah,
because I'm trying to calculate this.
So, I pay 33. So, that's £50. Yeah.
So, I pay £50 for Franklin.
One second. I'm trying to calc and the
bill, which is £33.
So obviously I'm going to buy the game.
So then it's only like 60 70 every month
more and then after a year you get to
keep the phone.
Well you get the phone but they can't
block the phone theoretically the phone.
I think I might just do that. It sounds
a better option. If you can get signal
on the [ __ ] thing then it sounds like
a better option
cuz it's only a year. So once you've
paid a year they can't um they can't
block the phone. Yeah,
it sounds like a good option, is it? Grievy.
Yeah, it makes sense.
It makes a lot of sense to be honest. the uh
cuz a year is nothing. So after a year
the phone's the phone's yours. They
can't block it. That's what it means. Is it Grezy?
You get 12 months, you get 24 months,
and you get 36 months. So,
so after the year,
so after the year, Grezy,
obviously they can't um
after the year they obviously can't
[ __ ] um you've paid you you you paid
out the contract in it. So, that's what
I was going to do with a fold, but you
can't do Uber. You can't do Uber with the fold.
Yeah, you can't do Uber with a [ __ ] phone. So, yeah.
It makes sense, isn't it, Grezy? What
I'm saying though?
Well, if you get a fold, it's like 180 a
month, but again, that's not that's not
anything to pay for a [ __ ] year.
[ __ ] stupid [ __ ] thing.
You understand what I'm saying? Grievy or nah.
See, I had a contract, but I couldn't
pay the contract because my phone got
stolen and I had to get another phone out.
It does make sense. It does. It makes
more sense doing that, to be honest.
It does make more sense doing that.
[ __ ] stupid hunting [ __ ] charger
cuz you're only you're only going to be
paying 60 70 pound more a month for a
year than what you're paying now. You
can make that in a day working. So,
and obviously you'll have money as well.
So, I think that's your best bet to be honest.
By you, I mean [ __ ] me.
Oh, this stupid [ __ ] thing, bro.
No, you won't drop it because it's got a
stand on it.
You won't drop it because it's got a
So, it would not happen because you've
got a stand on it.
I think it's what I mean. I might have
to go into the store and ask them,
but I'm pretty sure once you once you've
paid off after a year, it's your phone
after that in it. But I mean, they can't
block it, so makes more sense. And you
know the upfront cost. Yeah.
The upfront cost as well. You know the upfront cost.
the upfront costs.
The upfront cost goes uh
thingy every month. It goes um it goes
down it goes down a pound every [ __ ] day.
So it just makes more sense doing it, I think.
Yeah, there I'm going to get a case for it.
I'll get a case for it.
You can make 150 in a day, bro. It's
almost two months done. So, that just
makes that makes the most sense, I think.
Oh, that virgin boy.
Yeah, you can add insurance on it.
Yeah, obviously you add you can add
insurance on it,
but I don't mind paying that a little
over 100 for a year to be honest every
month. It's not that much considering
how much you can make in a day.
A year's [ __ ] all, bro. They can't block
your [ __ ] A year goes like that.
So, it saves Spain all that money. It makes sense.
And I've got safety I've got like a I'll
have a safety fun by then as well. So,
it makes emergency fund. So, I think that's Yeah. Virgin boy.
skin in his little bed. Sit. Oh, what's
a year, bro?
A year is going to be the same time as this. Yeah,
you're just jealous. You're just
jealous, Steven Howard, that you can't
get a fold.
Isn't he jealous, Greasy, that he can't
get a fold? He He's just He's just
jealous, isn't he?
Why are you so jealous that you can't
get a fold?
Yeah, you're jealous. You can't get a fold.
you're jealous, isn't it?
Isn't he jealous, Greavves? Tell him.
Tell him he's jealous. Greavves. Go on.
Go on, son.
You're jealous, mate. You You You like
You know who you remind me of, mate? You
remind me of that Orphenton [ __ ]
You remind me of that absolute virgin. I
I don't know what you're saying and
stuff, mate, but you really really
you you're jealous, mate. Absolutely jealous.
Bless you in life.
You're just like that fingers, aren't
you? From out of London.
You're just like that [ __ ] out of London virgin.
That's what you're like. You're just
like that out of London virgin.
When are you going to get the Are you
going to get the fold, Grezy? When your
little phone packs up.
When your little phone packs up, will
you get the fold? That's y'all. Bless you. That's funny.
What was that?
That faux converging.
Well, that faux converging.
Was it that f converging?
and skin virgin.
I bet you like that, don't you, Grezy?
You like it when I say that, don't you?
Yeah. Faky skint version can't.
We got a cat. It's still waiting. moves
here with a copycat statement.
Yeah. Still waiting for Still waiting
for the copy statement.
That's [ __ ] hilarious, bro. Sh call black se
a little copycat.
>> Greavves is the one that started that
[ __ ] Yeah, Greavves is the one that
started that [ __ ]
He's like, it sounds like a copycat thing.
Sounds like something some somebody
would say if they were copying someone else.
It sounds like a copycat statement. Did
you mean it when you said that though about show
Gregy? Did you mean it though? Seriously,
it sounded like a copycat statement. Really?
Oh, [ __ ] nons legs was saying Shevil
Cole was attractive to fit in.
He wanted to fit in with the crowd. Triple H. Yep.
Oh, you've actually heard it before.
What? You queasy. Oh, you've actually heard it. Really?
Really? Where? Who did you hear it from? Yep. Wow. Yeah.
I do believe it. Yeah. That Oh, is that where the
Is that where the copycat got it from then?
Yeah, I know. He's a s.
Yeah, I know he's a s.
No, I definitely do believe it. I
definitely definitely do believe it.
It's a copycat statement. Little copycats.
What do they say to each other if you
don't find her attractive? Okay.
You know what I actually said? Grezy. Really?
Oh, I'm dead, bro. I'm [ __ ] dead. Stop it.
Yeah, they used to Did you hear the Did
you hear the Beyonce one as well?
Did you hear the Beyonce one?
We need to stop saying these things
because we're giving ideas to the copycat.
Jennifer Aniston. Maybe uh Megan Fox.
Megan Fox. Jennifer Aniston. Yeah.
Yeah. Knew it.
She's only my She's only my mama for the winter. Yeah.
Yeah. But you know Yeah. But you know
why though? Cuz they copy each other. Yeah. [ __ ] copycats.
Sick of these [ __ ] copycats. approach. Yeah.
Yeah. But you say is he wasn't she my mama? Graves. H
Yeah, but what happened to my other mama?
Oh, bless you. little copycat.
You could be gay.
Yeah, they used to say if you don't like
Beyonce, you're gay as well. You might
have not saw that one. Um, Greavvesy.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, that was a big thing.
That was a [ __ ] big thing, bro.
You never saw that one, did you?
Yeah, that was a that was a big thing.
Yeah, you might not remember that one.
You might not remember that one, bro.
[ __ ] little copycats. I hate
copycats. Triple H, what's your what's
your experience with copycats?
[ __ ] hating me.
Did you get your iPhone out the pawn
shop yet? Um, Timmy H. Not sure. Bless you.
You little copycat.
Yeah, Timmy's phone is in a porn shop. Lesure. No copy.
What I should um
You [ __ ] virgin, [ __ ] You
You're [ __ ] virgin, [ __ ] You not right.
You [ __ ] [ __ ]
You like that?
Virgin [ __ ] Yeah.
Nah, not at all.
He still hasn't found a copycat statement. We
still no copycat statement. [ __ ] copycat.
You still ain't found me a phone. Steven Howard
No, you know
No, Samsung's a good phone.
No, Samsung's good phones.
What do you say? You've got the A25 in it,
you little cheap skate.
Well, you got the A25 in it. You're [ __ ]
You're a cheapkate. You lad.
You got all this money, bro. You
won't splash out on the phone. You got
all Triple H is rich.
Yeah, I don't like iPhones, bro. I've
not had an iPhone since I was 14.
Yeah, I get you, bro. I've not had an
iPhone since I was [ __ ] 14, lad. Yeah.
Yeah, I think I had the iPhone.
I think it was a 12 I had.
Was it? It was 20. It was in 2012. Yeah.
I'm [ __ ] dead, bro. That is funny.
That Sher Cole thing is so funny. Triple H.
It's so funny.
I don't know what one it was, bro. It
was definitely in 2012, 2013. That's the
only time I've ever had a bloody iPhone.
You little copycat. >> Look.
Yeah, I think it was a four. Yeah.
Yeah, it was a four. I think it was a four. Yeah.
Do you like the iPhone 4? Gravesy.
That looks like the Orington virgin in
that photo. Is it? They look alike,
isn't it? Copycat. Little copycat.
Yeah, I think I had the white one.
Yeah, it is.
Yeah, but [ __ ] Monty's going prison over YouTube.
My friend Yeah. Um,
well, someone I know, he got nicked yesterday
and he's got to go to court next month.
Now, I've got to go to court in three
and a half years.
Yeah, I don't think it's going to make
it make it to court, mate.
Yeah, but the police are not doing
anything anymore because they know what he's doing.
The solicitors have gone on gone to the
police and [ __ ] so that's why they
don't do anything anymore.
He's a loser, bro. He's a proper proper loser.
There's a load.
As you know, Yeah.
Yeah. It's sad. There could be someone
getting raped, getting their phone
stolen, interpre, and then they've got
some skint little virgin crying over
YouTube. Good cuz they got their ass a
good whooping. Isn't that right, Grezy?
Crying on YouTube
cuz they got their ass a good whooping.
A good old fashion whooping boy.
Easy to get laid.
That's him in the photo. The cat
looks like the copycat virgin, isn't it?
Hey, you got lied.
It used to [ __ ] off. I got lied.
You know what I'm saying?
How much is your phone costing? Triple H.
How much did your phone cost again?
How much did it cost again? Triple.
No, I'm going drinking in two weeks with my sister.
No, I'm going out in two weeks, man.
Triple, how much did you say you paid
for the phone again?
Oh, I'm dead, bro.
That's cute, isn't it? That's cute, is it? Triple.
Yeah, that that's cute, is it?
One second, bro. Yeah, I'll put the copy state.
It's a copycat statement, is it?
It's a copycat statement. Yo,
>> you want to talk, man?
>> [ __ ] off, bro. Chill on you.
>> I'm not. >> Oh,
>> it's funny though, is it?
>> Yeah. Yeah. I don't know why he keeps
going down the station. That's already [ __ ] getting
>> He's a copycat.
>> Yeah, he's a queen. Like,
>> you you you said that you don't copy
anything, is it? >> Huh?
>> No, lad.
>> I don't know why people feel need to
copy in it.
Yeah. What? Yeah. Why don't you wear Are
you going to [ __ ] crack on that autumn then?
>> Nah, you can't.
>> You don't
>> like you should. You're single. You're
single ready to mingle, aren't you? So >> yeah.
>> Well, yeah, but you've got to understand
like I've come out of a relationship. Me
I'm not ready to [ __ ] dive in or out
yet. Like but
>> I think you could get a shag in it.
>> Yeah, you could get a shag though, couldn't you?
>> That's what I'm saying. You get your leg over, kid.
No, you could get a shag in it. >> Huh?
>> Take a photo, lad.
>> No, you should.
>> He's from London Air. >> Nah.
>> Is she? Nah.
>> All right. >> Really?
>> Hey, that Mike's been commenting on the photos.
Yeah, he's a proper s. That kid, isn't it?
>> You like him though.
>> Mike wanted to talk to Ry, you lad.
>> Yeah, is he a s?
>> Um, no, it's all right, mate. I don't mind.
>> Do you know what he means? A s
>> Yeah, [ __ ] like an idiot. Really?
Like a not not all there kind of?
>> No, you don't know what a s means.
>> That's what a s means. You're not all
there, idiot. No, it means you lick
women's asses. Do you know that? >> No.
>> Yeah, it means basically someone that um
like sucks up to women and that just for
being a woman. Like that defends women
for the sake of defending women. You
know them kind of guys.
>> I don't know what meant that.
>> Yeah, you've seen them. You see them on
nights out and [ __ ] don't you? [ __ ] >> hi.
>> There's some There's actually some all
right people in this community in it,
but the rest of them are freaks.
There you some right people who can have
a normal conversation.
>> You remember you remember Timmy
yesterday? Yeah. He said he had sex the
other day and his penis is hurting.
>> Yeah. She bit, didn't she? Or something.
>> That's [ __ ] though, is it? Yeah.
It's [ __ ] isn't it?
>> I don't know.
>> Yeah. Maybe it could be true, is it?
Yeah. You don't know.
>> Make a [ __ ] Tim [ __ ]
>> Yeah. Right. Is it? >> Huh?
>> What did he I was laughing at that. Oh,
I said yesterday to man he said it's
like riding a bike. You never you never
you never forget or something.
>> Do you remember the pigeon one with the chess?
>> Yeah, Tom Wood said that didn't
>> No, bro. That's too funny though, is it?
>> Good. Yeah, you can't win an argument with him. >> Yeah.
You like it though, is it?
>> I do like this YouTube. I think it's
great entertainment. Yeah.
>> No, I hate I hate Lavy, bro. He's a
freak, isn't he?
>> Ah, yeah. He's got me blocked in there.
I don't go on.
>> Yeah, he's a freak, lad. >> Yeah.
>> You think it's all a laugh you?
>> Yeah, I was in that.
>> You're not going out. You're not going out weekend.
>> I went had a paint earlier, mate.
>> Did you
get it? I had a good
>> How much did you spend? Have you had
some whiskey over rice and about 10?
>> I had a whiskey over and a dinner. >> Nice.
>> Couldn't be ass. I'm too cold out there.
>> Yeah, it's cold, isn't it? Yeah, it's
cold, isn't it? Especially where you
are. It's even colder.
>> North, lad.
>> Bless you then.
>> Are you doing that Uber delivering anymore then?
Hey, Captain. Are you delivering for
Ubers anymore? Not
>> Nah, bro. Nah. Chilling in bed in it,
man. I'm too lazy. You know the feeling, is it?
>> Yeah. When you getting your haircut?
>> I don't know, bro. I'm going out in two
weeks with my sister.
>> Oh, yeah. Where you going?
>> Just just to the local to to have a
drink and that is it.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
>> Do you reckon I'll do any approaches on
that? Yeah. But
>> your sister get you like a girl a lasso Peter.
>> Nah, she probably know got kids and [ __ ] unfortunately.
>> Oh yeah. Yeah. Um you mate you got your
something your sister.
>> I I know deep down you I know deep down
you get sexually frustrated in it.
>> I don't know.
>> No I used to like two years ago is it?
So, do you think Timmy Timmy gets all
this [ __ ] then or is he full of [ __ ]
>> I think he's full of [ __ ] He said he
said that he's putting 150 on Newcastle
today, but apparently they're not playing.
>> No, man. You know, um Newcastle play weekend.
>> Are you in a football bet tomorrow?
>> Yeah, Champions League and I will be lad. Yeah.
>> I I like the National North League. Me, lad.
>> I don't know. Better I don't bet on that, mate.
>> Because there's a lot of goals in there, isn't it?
>> And we got a lot of goals in any game, PJ.
>> Yeah, but yeah, but yeah, but yeah, but
you know, League One and League Two,
like the normal leagues, they're hard to
get both teams to score, bro. It's hard. >> Not
>> you know the one with Swindon and
Colchester and that.
>> Yeah, but anyone can score just
look at the drawing. Anyone can score.
Yeah, but they're Yeah, but there's
loads of goals in that one, in it.
>> You never do both teams to score, do you? >> No.
>> I think you would. I think you would enjoy it.
>> I do. Both teams got to be nil nil, lad. >> Really?
>> Yeah. I'm going boxing.
You're a crafty [ __ ]
Go about 1, I think, and then I'll be
back for like I don't know what time.
>> Yeah. I don't like staying out too late
now, you know.
>> Yeah. Pointless. And I'm just saying
like I don't start like properly late
and that now. But
>> 11 like 12 the latest, bro. 12 one.
>> But years ago we'd stay out until 7:00
in the morning when I was younger, isn't it? >> Yeah. your head.
>> It's good, isn't it?
>> There's when you're young, man. But I'm
getting on now. Me.
>> I'm getting on as well. You can't
>> bless you and your little Jord. Bless
you. Bless you and your little northeast ways.
>> So, two weeks time, two weeks to go out
with your sister.
>> Yeah, bro. I I wouldn't if she didn't
invite me, but I would have stayed in
and saved some money until like boxing
day and that, but she wants to go out, so Yeah.
Oh yeah. Yeah. Is he still with Venom like? >> Nah.
>> Nah, bro. How do you remember him?
That's weird, isn't it?
>> I watched the video where he chased
around the bus stop.
>> Did you like it?
>> That Yeah.
>> What would have you do? Do you reckon
you could beat him up? Yeah.
>> Yeah, I'd definitely beat him up.
>> What you reckon you could have him?
>> 100%. Yeah.
>> Yeah. You're scared away from you're
scared of black people, aren't you?
>> No. Why did you run?
>> Cuz I was scared.
>> His kid chased you as well, didn't he?
>> Yeah, but that you know that would never
happen now, would it? I'm I'm a big boy now.
>> You are.
>> I'm a big [ __ ] now. You know that, is it?
>> Yeah. Do you So you don't speak
>> You're quite a big [ __ ] isn't it?
>> Yeah, but you don't speak to Taylor now, do you?
Nah, bro. You doing it.
>> You like Taylor, is it?
>> I think he's all right. London Taylor, right?
>> Yeah, but he's got this weird Yeah, but
he's he's weird about he's racing that,
bro. He's It's too weird, man.
>> Yeah, we always admit at one point, w
>> Yeah, but it's just weird. Yeah. Yeah,
but it's weird. It is weird.
>> You have to admit, isn't it? Yeah.
>> Which sister are you going out with then, Peter?
>> Just one of them.
>> Charene or the other one?
>> I can't say.
>> Only joking. Oh, look who wants to join.
Who's it? Who? You. All right, Timmy.
>> Get in there, lad.
>> Get in.
>> Did he do the bet win?
>> No, it's tomorrow. PJ the game's not today.
>> Oh, it's tomorrow. Oh, damn.
25 on it. PJ New, you never know.
Newcastle could win tomorrow.
>> We got Mar tomorrow. I think I think we beat Mar.
>> Yeah. 30 quid on it, I reckon. And I'll
do a little video to show I've done the best.
>> Oh, bless you then.
>> But anyway, Triple, can I ask you a
question? Do you know people onactic C
like, "Oh, I don't like you cuz you
speak to so and so." Like, I was
watching bands only. It gets very
sensitive who you [ __ ] speak to,
don't they? Like a big bunch of [ __ ] children.
>> Like, oh, can you do it's like that
Chicago swimmers goes, oh, can you do a
video on Timmy being a nut? And I'm
thinking, well, hang on. Banger's the
biggest nut on here. He's got no life.
He spends all day cooking Iceland
[ __ ] [ __ ] and [ __ ] Iceland pork
sausages and [ __ ] like that. You know
what it is with these little fanboys of
Bangers. They love to give it out. Pat
was the same. I don't you know but when
you give it back to them hate it with a passion.
>> Yeah. They don't like a Tim lad.
>> It's like but don't do it in the first
Mr. P. I don't let him get to me
anymore. I'm just very sarcastic back to
him. He goes penny owes me and I go okay
if that if that's what you want to call
it. I just I can't be asked to argue a
bunch of more ones anymore. I just laugh
at the retards now.
I mean these people pray to Lord Jesus
going morning Jesus. I'm looking forward
to the next 15 minutes of my life
because John is gonna do a good morning upload.
>> Yeah. Did you see you like it to me?
>> They don't, man. But these people set
their alarm clocks for banger to go live
and do an upload. You can't write this
[ __ ] Didn't they criticize?
>> Have you done an upload this morning?
Someone emailed him saying
>> I didn't I watched the one we did the
rant last yesterday and I couldn't stop
laughing. [ __ ] hell. I was choking
for over 50 minutes. Triple
>> I know people laugh at me on the
internet but I do it intentionally to be
funny to give
>> I do.
>> He's actually being serious. He takes
the fiberactic cable way too seriously. That one
>> he does. He's too far. He's too far
deep. And know that Lavin is that he's
really far deep in the trip, but he's
I've never known anyone so far deep in
my life. And that V's getting far deep
and they're all getting far deep.
>> Look at a cat that's waiting to copy, isn't it? >> Gy
fun and it's like it's a [ __ ] fiber
cable. Who gives a [ __ ] You see with
me? I come on Timmy.
>> Yes. Do you find Cheryl Cole attractive? Gerald Crow.
>> Cheryl Crow.
>> I'm not going to lie. Don't take this
personally, but when that woman told you
to [ __ ] up, I can't stop laughing. >> I crow
mean this personally, but
>> I want to see if Timmy was a copycat. We
>> No, no, no. I'm not I'm not bullying PJ.
I just found it funny that I you go
these women self projecting that like
and she left you a voice not she goes I
don't mean this in the nasty way but can you
>> Yeah but you know you know she was a
copycat isn't it? Yeah, it's just funny
that you just went [ __ ] up, mate. I'm
not bullying. I'm not taking the piss.
It was just funny as [ __ ] But PJ with
me tell me to [ __ ] off. You just got to
take it through one ear, have the other,
mate. I was told to [ __ ] off a couple of
times Saturday, PJ. But you just laugh
it off, mates.
>> Yeah, the Yeah, these women are [ __ ]
is it? These women are [ __ ]
>> I was talking to one. I was being nice
and and she goes, "Can you [ __ ] off now?
You doing my" And I just went, "Yeah,
have a nice day." You know, don't take
it personally, lad.
You know what I mean? But like that's
Monty's going to die a virgin, isn't it?
>> Monty is a virgin, right? Let's talk about Monty
biggest on here.
Kaye Kaye spoke to me on the phone
earlier today and she said that Mongol
never had sex with me that the miners
belong to Nathan.
Mongol is a loser. I'm
>> [ __ ] dead.
>> And even Natty G, you know, I can't
believe Natty G. She's got to go with a tent bacon. It's ridiculous.
>> That is funny, isn't it?
>> Well, what what is the world coming to?
We got Naty G's that desperate. She's
now going for tent bacons. Lisa's got no
friends turning to Penny [ __ ] Bunny.
Bangers that desperate for content is
just making up [ __ ] every day, you know.
Yeah. The whole world's gone [ __ ] mad. PJ.
>> Yeah, it has. It has.
>> Someone's begging for more content on me
cuz John's upset because he can't handle
my opinion on him living a sad existence
on his fiber cable. You know what I
mean? It's beyond [ __ ] chronicle on
here now, PJ. Everyone's turned into a [ __ ] robber.
Yeah, it's true.
>> Mom goes on the urge of [ __ ] probably
getting Natalie G arrested for the third time. And
>> how how is your dick feeling better today, Timmy?
>> It's still a bit sore. I've had to put
some suda cream on it. PJ
>> Suda cream.
>> Yeah, it does work. You know, it's really good.
>> What did you put on after you come out the shower?
Also, I'm going to put it on before I go
in the shower. Be a waste of time.
>> And that was from that. It hurts from
the sex you had the other day, is it?
>> It hurts cuz she bit my [ __ ] penis
giving me a [ __ ]
>> You're crazy, Timmy. You're [ __ ] crazy.
>> That makes me laugh that Nat G rang me
yesterday said Mongol can't even get a
[ __ ] because he's got such a small
penis. You can't stick it in his gob.
>> A virgin. He's a Monty man. Monkey man
starts rolling you up and called you a
virgin. Just say, "Hang on. I spoke to
Natty G and she says you've got a small penis." Mongol.
>> Yeah. So So he's never had sex.
>> Definitely a virgin, PJ. Definitely a
virgin that one.
>> Yeah, I agree. I agree.
Bongol adopted them. They're Nathansy.
Would you agree? I agree with that as well. Yeah. >> Yeah.
>> When When are you When are you next out
on the drink?
>> Hey, after Christmas now, PJ will sort
me out. Not now, mate. I've got
Christmas coming up.
>> No, I'm saying when I'm saying when are
you out again?
>> Hey, after Christmas. Probably New
Year's Eve. I'll let you know. That's
what I was thinking going out. Yeah, I
was thinking the same.
>> It's turning me a bit fragile at the
moment. I've drank about 60 points this
week. I mean, last week. My head is all
over the place, mate. You're a lot
younger than me, PJ. You can take the
hangovers. I can't, mate. I can drink
for two or three days and drink the
hangover the chest, but after 3 days,
PJ, I'll go into Mongol stage.
>> Terry will be free Mongs if you come in,
you [ __ ] [ __ ] All right. Terry's
trying to call us a Mong. He's a Mong,
is it, Timmy?
>> Who's that? The one who can't fight
himself out of wet paper bag.
>> Yeah. Do you remember the one that met me?
>> PJ, I think you've got it in you, but I
think you're scared the [ __ ] police.
Per getting nicked and you need to take
>> You're scared of the police.
>> You can go. You [ __ ] bag.
>> Terryy's a [ __ ] bag in it, Timmy.
>> I don't I'm not gonna judge Terry. I
don't know him. But listen to me PJ,
right? You need to take that fear off
you when somebody's coming up to you to
say what you going to do. Don't when
they say what you going to do, fump them
before they get the chance. My brother
went right in life and that like don't
let them have the chance. You when you
at the time at the scene, PJ, I used to
do this. I used to worry about the
police or what my mom would think or
what my brother would think or what
that. Now I don't, PJ, if they say,
"What you going to do about it?" I get
the first warning before they have the
chance. That's where I went wrong all my life. >> Yeah.
>> You PJ, you got you got you can't be
afraid of him and go, he's that nasty
troll who's bullied me on YouTube. You
can't have any F. You just got to go up
to and just hit him. And if you don't
hit him hard enough, do it again. If
they grab you and you lose, at least
you've tried. At least you're not a
coward. Do you know what I mean, lad? >> True.
>> PJ, everyone loses a fight from time to
time. Unless you're like really
intelligent and clever. Some people have
got the gift and the gap. They don't. Some people.
>> Oh, here we go. Hello, Mr. B.
>> Hello, T.
>> How are you today, Mr. Embarrassing yourself again?
>> Are you embarrassing yourself over?
Yes, you're the Well, you're the one
who's talking on the internet. We're
going to laugh at you that you're
triggered over some Eldridge, man.
>> Why you talking Why are you so
triggered? Why? Why you Why are you so
embarrassing autistic kid on the [ __ ]
internet, Mr. B? Why you Why are you so
>> But you're an embarrassment. Triggered
over some slug. Who's not even part of
your real life?
>> Have you turned your phone off, Slug?
>> You know, you are you are triggered over
some slug because he has no opinion on you to
>> know your phone to be. But we all laugh
at you as well doing your silly voice
cuz you're too scared to use your real
voice in case people would laugh at your
wall accent. My lad
onto him. Stop turning it off.
>> We laugh at YOU AS WELL. YOU WE don't
care if you laugh at me. I'm glad I made
you smile, Mr. B. But we laugh at you.
We don't laugh at you. We laugh with
you. We laugh at you, lad. That the fact
that you're triggered over the father cable.
>> Your human number's all over the
internet, too. I don't give a [ __ ] if my
internet you do you do realize I don't
use that cabbage
I don't if I don't use that phone number
how are you going to ring me your cabbage
>> it was ringing earlier is it
>> you can't even you can't even answer the
question can you
phone numbers all over the internet if
it's not being used in the SIM cards out
the phone what use is it then dickfest
>> well just get your other number then
it's not hard for
>> you're not going to get my you're not
going to get my new number Mr. to be.
It's not going to happen on YouTube.
Dickfest. Okay. Well then, what is my
new number then? Dickfest.
>> We'll get it in time, Tim. We always do.
>> No, no, no. You just said it's easy. Always.
>> What's my new number, Dick Fest?
>> You said it's easy. How can you destroy
me? I'm destroying you. You said you
could easily get my number. So, I'm
telling you right now. >> No.
You can't get You can't get You can't
get a phone if I can give it to anyone. You idiots.
>> So, how have you
>> How have you destroyed me? Answer the
question. How have you destroyed your
class number? So, what's my new number
then, Mr. B?
>> I've asked you.
It's It begins with 07. There's your clue.
>> You got these sub guys ringing your
phone to answer.
>> You just said you can get phone number.
So, what's my new phone number? What's
your embarrassment here, aren't you, Mr. Be
>> on YouTube all night again?
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
What's the difference? And you know, you
can't quit on YouTube when you're all
day and all night cuz you're a wool and you've been
How can you How can you How can you
criticize someone mommy's boy when you're adult
your mom? Why don't you show us your
mom's house before you go into others?
Come on. Show us your mom's Show us your
mom's kitchen and bathroom. You skid long.
>> Well, show me Chris's kitchen.
>> You can't You can't You can't afford
rent, council, tax, or a TV license
because you're too scared to stand on
your own two feet. Ain't your mommy's boy?
>> Your brother's slug.
>> The same argument every day.
>> Yes, I can. Mr.
>> Yes, I can. It affects you that you want
to be me and you have to not be me and
you spend my days over that you want to
be me. Yeah. Run away you little [ __ ]
>> Go and [ __ ] pay some housekeeping to
your mom. Your mommy's boy. Yeah.
Anyway, but yeah. Anyway, um
the reason why he's got money PJ paid a
[ __ ] bull in his life that one. He
lies on his [ __ ] mom, right? But
anyway, yeah. Um
>> but yeah, PJ was saying was lad. Yeah,
but Mongol is 100% a virgin.
>> Do you agree, Grezy? Do you think
Monty's a virgin?
>> Everybody on the internet knows that
Monty man's a virgin. >> Yeah,
>> definitely a virgin. PJ, I tell you, my body's
>> What about What about Nons? He's a
virgin, isn't it? Now he's definitely
added. He has I mean you could I mean
because he's had that burden even though
she don't look the full shilling but you
know but he's definitely added that one.
I tell you another virgin and you'll be surprised V.
>> What about L J?
>> He's a virgin to miners and he so you
can't be a virgin if you have
>> Yeah, I know V is a virgin. I already
knew that, bro. You can tell.
>> Everybody knows you can tell he's a
virgin because he gets so excited to
female company on a
>> Yeah. Yeah. Remember when Autumn Do you
know when Autumn joined uh yesterday? I saw it.
>> I got really excited. Oh, we got really
>> Yeah, he's definitely a virgin.
Definitely a virgin.
>> Yeah, he's definitely virgin. I've never
known any So, is she English? I didn't
even know she joined the Hangouts. Is
she English or Yank? Help me out.
>> I don't know, bro. I don't know.
>> I don't watch the internet all the time.
PJ, I've got a [ __ ] life.
>> I didn't even know about Steven George
copied all my videos till yesterday. I
don't watch these channels, PJ. I have a
life. Unlike Banger and Mr. B and all
them and VR and [ __ ] Mass Miller and
all them, I have a life.
>> They can't.
>> They haven't got a live PJ. They have a
lot. That's why they've got money
because they don't leave the house cuz
they rely on a fiberact. It means all so
much to them.
>> Yep. True.
>> Anyway, have you seen that video of any
videos on you today? >> No.
>> You should watch it. She's done a short on you.
>> Yeah. The keyboard warrior, isn't it?
>> No, I like Vinnie. Vinnie's Vinnie's
banter. I actually do like Vinnie videos
and I do actually like that um what's it
called? Nick Nick Productions. Even
though just can't go is begging him to
do a video on me. I just said to um
what's it called? Um Nickro production
said you can do a video on me. Bless
him, but make sure you do one on Bang
because he's a nutter. He spends all the
internet food and acting like a prat.
takes one to snow one.
>> It's true.
>> Yeah. Is it that you're gonna do con?
They're gonna beg people to do content
for me. They have to expect that Lord
Jay I mean Lord Jay's more of a nutter
than me. He's you know this guy films
his own feet for [ __ ] sake.
>> Yeah, it's true.
>> Yeah, but man I mean you were nutters.
You film your own feet talking. >> Yeah.
>> Oh, come on.
>> You think it's funny is it? I I laugh at
this community how [ __ ] sad people
are. I ain't going to lie. Yes.
But the thing with me, PJ, is I I be
funny on purpose and I act like a pr
because I actually want to make people
have sunshine in their lives. I don't
take this [ __ ] seriously. Yeah, I'm
going to get a bit triggered from time
to time. Yeah, I'm gonna get a bit
worked up, but I don't give a [ __ ] as
long as I mean, as long as Jaden has a
laugh, Tram, you do. I don't give a
[ __ ] right? It's the internet, right?
You know, and you know, I I'm not
bothered if someone goes, "Oh, he's this
and that." I'm not bothered because I've
got a sense of humor. These people on
bangers haven't got a sense of humor,
PJ. That's why they always have a go at
traming that sense of humor.
>> They're repeaters, isn't it?
>> And they haven't got a sense of humor.
Vinnie's got a sense of humor. I know
you have issues with the Patels, but I
like the Patels. They've got a sense of
humor. Bang hasn't got a sense of humor.
His brain [ __ ] dead and his disciples
are as well.
>> Yeah, he's screwing it.
>> That's That's why they all paying for
his membership because
I said he needs to get a life. Please, PJ,
>> who needs to get a life?
>> This guy said to get a life,
>> I've already got a life. I haven't spent
all day on the internet like you, sucker. Okay,
>> is gone in it.
Grimsy's all right, man. He's armless. I
don't even know who this Grimsy is. Who
the [ __ ] is this Grimsley?
>> Griezy? You don't know Grezy?
>> No, he's from not far from ducks.
Anyway, is Duck still alive? I used to
like Docks. I'm actually concerned. Is
Ducks still alive?
>> I'm not sure, Captain.
>> Wonder if Ducks is alive on there. She I
know she was dying, but I hope she's
okay. I'm being serious. I actually did
like Docs, but Right.
You've got to look at this, right? Like
with the women. Yeah. You need to be a
bit more chilled out on your approach,
mate. And it's not me having a knock,
right? Because you
>> Well, you've watched my approaches.
>> I watched your video and I watched the
whole thing and she told you to [ __ ]
off. And I'm going to explain why she
told you to [ __ ] up.
>> No, I'm saying have you watched Have you
No, I'm saying have you watched my
approaching videos before?
>> Yes. And you go wrong on that as well, PJ.
You could never approach in it.
>> I don't do cold approaching. I go in I
go in pubs and pull women in PJ. I would
like I would like a [ __ ] felon if I
went on the street cold approaching. >> Yeah.
>> You know what I mean? I would look like a [ __ ]
But no, the thing is PJ, you're a bit
too forceful. What? Hear me out. I'm I'm
a ladies man. Right. You go up to him
and you go, "Hi, my name's PJ. You look
very sophisticated. You look gorgeous
looking. Can I buy you a drink? Don't go
straight up to me and ask for their
number and I'll explain.
>> What if they say no?
>> Then you move on to the next one.
Just go up to me.
>> What happened? What happened that day
when you was with Seaside Mark talking
to women? What did they say?
>> Got a few numbers cuz I'm because I'm an
actual PJ. Right. The thing is, PJ, if I
was a woman, hear me out and you come up
to me and said, "Hi, can I have 300
pound? Can I have your number?" I'd be
like, "Get lost, you [ __ ] freak."
>> What the [ __ ]
>> You need you need to approach. You need
next time you do a cold approach, go and
go, "Hi, you look very sophisticated.
You look lovely. Can I buy you a drink?" >> Yeah.
>> Don't ask for their number, PJ, or they
are going to tell you to [ __ ] off. It's
like when you're in bars next and you go
live, prove them wrong. Don't ask for
the number straight away. Come on, PJ.
You're not that [ __ ] skinned and go,
you look very nice looking. Can I buy
you a drink yet talking to if it's meant
to be, it's meant to be. If it's not,
you're not going to know what six
pounds, are you?
Ask them. They're like, PJ, seriously,
this is how I pull them. I go up to my
and I say, "You look very nice. Get
talking. I to buy my drink." I don't ask
them their number straight away. I look
like a freak if I did.
You you'll get you need the help by the professionals. PJ,
>> see, show me how it's done, man.
>> This is why Mongol can't get sex in the
virgin because he's not an 80s man.
That's why he has to have YouTube [ __ ]
cuz in the real world, nobody wants that tent bacon.
He is He's a [ __ ] tent bacon. That
one. I done well. Get rid of him. PJ,
there's better people in the world than
that tent bacon. He led you down the
garden path that one.
>> Yeah, it's true. It's true.
>> Yeah. And Ted and I reckon, right, if
you need to you need to stop worrying
about the police cruising yourself up,
stop letting your anxiety get to you.
And when you meet Ted N when he goes,
"What you going to do?" Just punch him
before you get the chance like I did.
And he'll go, "Don't even let him
speak." He goes, "What you going to do?"
Let him say the first and then go bang.
Good idea, Timmy. Good idea.
>> And And if he phons the police, so what?
You'll just get on high rate pip and
you'll get more [ __ ] benefits on your
gas and [ __ ]
>> Yeah, it's true, isn't it?
>> Look at it positive. Yeah, look at it.
You might get a police freebies.
>> Yeah, it's the truth. Is it?
>> Yeah. I just called now to tell him to
come on, but he's scared to me. Of
course he's scared cuz he's all taught
that one. This is a kid who had to ask
his [ __ ] Mes to have a fight with
Slug at Canel Park. That says it all how
much of a [ __ ] he is. >> Yeah.
>> I mean, and I called him out twice. I
said, "Come to the M." He had to ring
Natalie to ask if he could turn up for
the fight and he's meant to be a
gangster. What the [ __ ] am I hearing? >> Yeah,
he can't come on YouTube. You can't come
on YouTube and make out you're a [ __ ]
special needs gangster and then you got
to phone your [ __ ] misses up for a fight. >> Yeah.
>> Scared it.
>> He ain't scared, mate. He's a bottle
job. He's all talking. He's got He
doesn't want any violence. He doesn't
want any trouble. He wants a peaceful
life and he does his double acts on the
internet. And don't get me wrong, PJ, I
don't want violence. I want a peaceful
life. But I just don't take [ __ ] >> Yeah.
Know what I mean, lad? You know what I'm
saying? It's just the way it is. But you
>> hopefully when you put this bet on
tomorrow, it wins, isn't it?
>> I'm only putting about 20 quid on it,
PJ. I've got to It's Christmas coming.
If I If I win 20 quid, it's 20 quid more
for me to the public. If I lose it, it's 20 quid.
>> I thought you was going to put 150 on it.
>> I was, but I changed my mind now. >> Yeah.
>> Christmas is coming, PJ. Christmas is
coming. I'll start doing big boy bets. >> Yeah,
>> fingers. I'm stopping buying the PS now
cuz I'm sick of these [ __ ] bar
roulette. You put 100 pound, you can't
get one spin. You put 300 coins to get
one red bag on lemons. I'm done with
these [ __ ] crap. So, I'm going to
start looking into doing football now.
And you know the man who used to win me
a lot of money on football. Do you know the man?
>> Oh, mate. He gave me this good tip and
everybody didn't back it apart from me
and I only put 20 quid on it and it won
me £160 and I should have listened to
him and put 200 quid on it. That would
have got me about I think roughly two
and a half grand something stupid at the
time. I can't remember the top of my
[ __ ] head but that guy when it come
to betting he knew what he was talking
about that one.
>> You still need to get your phone out of
cash converters isn't it?
>> Not in cash converters. He got nipped by
a Pakistan taxi driver, an Asian taxi
driver. And I didn't wasn't And Pakistan
is not racist, right? It got nicked. No
word of a lie, PJ. That's why I kicked
off in the ice street and the police had
to calm me down and susitate me in the
police van. As I was fuming as I dropped
in the taxi, said, "Get back here." And
I caught up the taxi firm and not
getting I got sky pork. >> Wow.
>> Yeah. I got proper sky pork.
>> How do you have so much money to gamble, Timmy?
>> I'm not telling you my secrets, PJ. Or
Lord Jay will end up having a heart
attack and Mr. B will end up having a panic attack
and M will end up doing 2,000 a day. You
know, you know how sensitive these people are. >> Yeah.
But PJ, before I go, when you go to a
pub next, watch you approach. Not asking
for the number straight away. What's the golden rule?
>> I'm going to go up to them and slap the
back of my head.
>> No, you don't do that. Honestly, you
will scare them away. I I I have to
explain. I've got autism before I do.
So, now honestly, PJ, what's the golden?
>> Wait, you done what?
>> And you go, you look very attractive.
Can I buy you a drink?
>> No. What did you say you done? You had
to explain that you had autism to them.
No, there's a couple of them go away in
the back of your head. Women actually
are very nice to people with autism.
You'll be surprised, PJ.
>> They look at Bang got banger rejected
for another seven years. >> Mad.
>> Hey PJ, I've had some very nice women
been very understanding about my autism.
Not everybody, not every woman in the
world is bad, you know.
>> Yeah, right.
No, they're not PJ. There's some very
nice women out there.
>> Yeah, right.
>> Women is PJ. You You just need to work
on your approach, lad.
>> Yeah, really.
>> PJ, if I was a woman, you come to a bar
and you said, "Can I have your number?"
I'll be like, "Fuck off, you freak."
>> But if you come up to me and I was a
woman, you said, "Can I buy you a
drink?" I'd be like, "Yes, that's very
nice. I'll have a double gin and tonic
and I'll chat to you." Mhm. >> Really?
>> Yes, but I'm not a woman, so I can't do that.
>> I think you're trolling. I think you're trolling me.
>> I'm not PJ. I'm not actually trolling.
I'm actually trying to give you some
advice. I PJ trolling you. I don't I'm
not I'm actually
>> Timmy's trolling.
>> Timmy, you need to you know you need to
Timmy, you know, you need to come off okay.
>> You know you need to come off social
media. PJ, I will come to London. I'll
do a deal and I guarantee you if I went
up to a woman and got to talk to buy you
a drink, you get somewhere. If I and
I'll show you another approach and I'll
go and ask for their number and they'll
say, "Fuck off, you lanky slug freak."
You know, PJ, honestly, if you go just
ask for their numbers, PJ, you're going
to get nowhere. You need to sit to them
and get to know them. When the night is
young and you both get drunk, you can
get both a bit frisky.
>> No, you're not a troll.
I'm not trolling PJ. I'm generally being
serious. And if I was trolling you, P. I
know PJ I'm a bit a [ __ ] but on this
one I'm not actually trolling you.
>> What did you say?
>> Trust me, PJ. You go up to Trust me, PJ.
When you go out for a drink next, go up
to them and go, "You look very nice."
Don't call them nice straight away. Just
go, "Oh, hi. You look, you know, you
look very attractive today. Can I buy
you a drink?" And see what the response
is. You got nothing to lose. But if you
go and ask them their number straight
away, they're going to think you're a freak.
>> So what? Give it a whirl.
>> Well, I mean it I believe it's going to work.
>> Do you know what that means? Give it a while.
>> It means that you could be frisky and
you could get in there and get lucky. >> PJ,
>> I'm not trolling for [ __ ] sake this
time. Actually not. Why doesn't anyone
take me seriously?
>> You sure
>> PJ? Yes. I'm to come down to have a day
in London and show you how it's done.
Right. But yeah, I've got I can't afford
it till after Christmas, PJ. I've got to
get Christmas out the way.
>> How How much money do you have now?
>> About £425 sterling.
>> Really? But I've got to pay But I've got
to pay 200 out on the bills tomorrow,
PJ. I don't like Mr. B. So I'll be left with 235 sterling p.
>> To when
to the following Monday. But I've got
money in savings, PJ. But I can't I
don't want to use them, PJ. Cuz what's
the point having savings? You're going
to spunk it on gambling and drink.
savings are there for a reason. Not for
you to [ __ ] put 50 grand on bankrupt.
>> You know what I mean? That's why they
call it savings. If I've done
>> So, what are you going to do? Just save
the What are you going to do? Just save the 200.
>> I can live off 215 quid. I'm going to
get my food out of that. Pay my gas, pay
my electric, pay my council tax. Well, I
can live off that PJ very [ __ ]
easily. What? 15 quid for the week and
I've got 200 quid to spend on the piss
at the weekend. A lot of people PJ don't
even get left 50 pound disposable a
week. We live in a world now where it's broke.
>> I mean PJ
>> Yeah, I had two I had two I had two
grand last month to me.
>> PJ, listen to me. I'm not trolling her. You
>> I bought I bought some trainers and jeans.
>> You've done something with me. But PJ, right?
You should be grateful for the
disposable you got because a lot of
people in this world would love your
disposable income. Believe you or me.
You stop comparing.
>> Yeah. I I have friends I have friends I
have friends to me. They used to be left
with about £80 for the month.
>> Exactly PJ I mean what's your disposable
£200? Other people would love to have
200 disposable a week PJ.
>> Yeah of course >> PJ200
disposable a week. Regardless of Johnny
calling you skinting out live the real
world, mate. Come on. Is a lot of money.
>> I've got more money than him. He skint himself.
>> Yeah, he's got 15 grand PJ. I wouldn't call
>> mate. That's his daddy's savings, bro.
Bro, he's skin. Trust me, he's skinn.
>> He's skinned. But I'm
>> You know, let me tell you something,
Timmy. Yeah. Let me tell you something,
D. Let me tell you something. You know,
it's about Yeah. It's not just about how
much you have. You do realize it's about
your lifestyle as well.
>> Exactly. I mean, he's got 15 grand, but
he lives in a bed seats. There's your question.
>> And and no life experiences. No, never
been to nice restaurant. You know what I
mean? But you've you've seen what I've
done in the past four years to me.
Traveling, nice hotels, restaurants.
You've seen it.
>> I understand that. But life's not just
about that as well, PJ. I've lived
>> No, I know. I know. I'm just saying.
You're [ __ ] Yeah,
>> PJ. I've lived that lifestyle. But it
doesn't make you happy, bud. What you
What you need to understand is what
you've got to look at your life, right?
You could be a single parent, you know,
struggling to buy food, going down the
food to pay your rent. You are in a very
good financial position. You get more
disposable than what some people get in
two months per week. PJ, you've got to
stop comparing your life with others.
>> I I don't. You do that to me, is it?
>> No, I don't. PJ, I don't give a [ __ ] if
Lord Jay came tomorrow and shown 80
grand on [ __ ] live stream. I wouldn't
give a I don't give a [ __ ] if Mr. Be
shows another five grand and he's got 15
grand. I don't give a [ __ ] if Red Star's
got eight grand. PJ, I'm happy with my
life and the way I live my life because
I I wake up in the morning and I feel
blessed. And I'd explain why I feel
blessed because I'm trying to have this
conversation you PJ. There's been a lot
of people in the world what are a lot
worse off than us.
>> Yeah, of course.
>> Who gives a not 10 million pounds? Who
gives? You could be in Africa, PJ
drinking dirty water. That chancing that
you've got to drink that dirty water to
survive even though that dirty water's
got full of chemicals and poison could
kill you. You've got to look at that.
You could be worse off than someone.
>> But you know, but Timmy, how but how
much do you spend over the weekend? Like a hundred?
>> Probably about a couple of hundred. PJ
depends how much I have to drink. Weekend, PJ.
>> Yeah, but I say no gambling. What would you say?
>> Last week, PJ. last weekend tax week
back and I did overspend a bit. I spent
£400 which I shouldn't have done, right?
But this week I'm being more careful
because I had my weekend of, you know,
going on the piss. So this week I'm
probably going to spend about what 70 80 pound roughly.
>> Yeah, I done it before, bro. From the
Friday to the Monday, I spent about 600.
That that weren't gambling either.
>> Not not not this. It was like a month ago.
If you don't drink in Weber Spoons,
London's expensive. You go into central
London, you're going to easily spend that. It's
>> Yeah, but if you drink Yeah. But that's
why to me, if you go central London and
you just stick to Guinness, even though
it's £8 a Guinness, I mean, you're not
going to go over£60, you know what I
mean? Even if it's £8, it's the rum.
It's the spirits they water down. That's
where the money goes cuz they they water it down.
>> But this is But this is why you get
trolled, PJ, because you do the old
Timmy Eldridge. You you you're bothered
about what other people have got. You're
probably someone's got a pound more than
you. You can't have that attitude, PJ,
or people are going to troll the
absolute living daylights out of you.
>> Yeah. Yeah. >> True.
>> PJ, you wake up in the morning, just
think to yourself, you could be like
Mongol with a small penis being a tent
bacon, right? You know, getting your
Mrs. Nick twice and never being a man to
stand up to your own misses. You could
be, you know, in the lake of a fire. You
could be, you know, stranded in
Australia. I mean, stranded in Africa,
right? Wake up in the morning and think, "Hang on,
>> my life ain't all that bad after all."
>> No. Or you could be in the bed [ __ ] like
the [ __ ] the Kent Virgin, is it?
>> You could be Mongol.
That's the worst thing you could ever
have. If I was Mongol, I ain't going to
lie, I'd kill myself. And I know that
sounds nasty. It's true. I could not
wake up in the morning and not be able
to spell my own girlfriend. Yeah,
>> that's beyond scene. Even you can spell Natalie. Surely. >> Yeah.
>> How do you spell that ali then?
>> N A T A L I E. Easy.
>> Oh, but Mongol would have went a wrong.
Do you know Do you know how to spell America? Actually,
I don't. That is one word I don't. But I
can do it short. The USA. USA.
>> Okay. Do you know how to spell Canada? >> No. >> Really?
>> But I can spell I can spell Spain. S P I A N.
>> PJ. Can you spell Italy? I'm not the I'm
not the best speller in the universe.
So, I'll only I'm not
>> Can you Can you spell Italy?
Actually, that's one one. What's quite twisty?
I'm just trying.
>> Ask me ask me one.
>> Um, let me I can spell China. C H I N A.
That even Mongol can't do that. I'll be
honest with you.
>> Ask me if Ask me if I can spell something.
>> Okay. Australia.
>> Yep. A U S T R A L I A.
Yeah, you can spell better than me. This
is What's going on here? PJ's actually
better than spelling at me.
>> Give me Give me another one.
>> Okay, then. Portugal.
>> P R U T U D A L. I think it is. I
>> think you got a couple of letters wrong
in that one. I'm not sure.
>> Let me see. Maybe I did.
>> No, I got it right. No, I got it right.
I just looked. Yeah. Give me another one.
>> He did get it right. Germany.
>> G E R M A N Y. They're easy, man.
>> All right. Then Finland.
>> F I N L A N D.
>> [ __ ] hell. You are. Well, you are.
Okay. Then Thailand.
>> T H A I. T H A I L A N D.
>> Wow. Do you know what? If Mongol ever
calls you thick again, you can rub this
stream in his [ __ ] face.
>> Yeah, he he can't spell anything, mate. He can't
>> can't even spell his own name. That one.
>> How do you spell Kate?
>> Oh, that's easy. C A K E.
>> How do you spell K?
>> That's easy. C U N T.
It's funny, is it to me?
>> It is. Yeah, but man, [ __ ] hell.
You're actually when it comes to
spelling, I'm going to eat my [ __ ]
words when I say this. You're actually
more intelligent than me for [ __ ]
>> Well, duh. I'm not stupid, am I?
>> Why do you think I was stupid, Timmy?
>> No, not in that way. No, but I need to [ __ ]
>> Hi, Timmy. Do you know what you know
what star sign you are?
>> I'm not into that [ __ ] but go on.
You You don't know what star sign you are?
>> Not into this psychology [ __ ] [ __ ]
No, I don't.
>> You're You're a Virgo.
>> Oh, does that mean I'm a Virgo?
>> Yeah, you're the same as my mom.
>> Disabled people.
>> What the hell, Timmy? You've turned into a sheep. >> [ __ ]
>> You've turned into a sheep, marrying.
>> Oh, [ __ ]
But PJ, I'm going to go. I need to have
I need I need to have a [ __ ] laugh. But
just listen to what I said tonight. I'm
not trolling. Think that you got more in
live world, mate.
>> Because right now,
>> that 200 going to last you the week. Yeah.
>> Now, PJ, I'm not money a tated anymore.
My life's turned round, mate. I can live
off peanuts if I have to. As long as
I've paid my gas, paid my council tax,
paid my bills, PJ, I can live off pants.
All I'm going to do is just probably
troll bastard time away. >> Yeah,
>> I'm only joking. I'm not going to troll
Bang all week. I've got a life.
>> Well, I'm I'm going to go, bro. Anyways,
I'll talk to you. Uh,
>> catching the Do I get Portugal wrong?
One sec. Hey, Timmy, give me a couple more spellings. Oh,
>> Peter, I do need a [ __ ] Okay, spell Poland.
P O L A N D.
>> Okay, then let me think of one hard one.
>> Uh uh I'm not going to say Japan cuz I
can spell that. J A P A N. >> Yeah.
>> Um Okay, then. How do you spell Washington DC?
>> W A S H I N G T O N DC.
>> Come on, bro. I need to look at that
one. I don't know about that one. But
Matt, I got to go cuz I'm I'm clutching
for a [ __ ] All right.
>> All right. See you later, Tim.
>> Now it's just a copycat. Looking to copy.
Looking to copycat. Little copycat.
A little copycat. A little copycat. A
little copycat. Little copycat. You
little copycat. You little copycat.
Yeah. My little copycat. You copy. Yeah.
Little copycat. You copy. Hello copycat.
You little copycat. You little copycat.
You little copycat. Are you a little
copycat? Are you a little copycat? Are
you a little copycat? You little
copycat. I'm just as mad as Timmy. Yeah.
Are you a little copycat?
Right. I'm gone. Yeah. Yeah. See?