Oh, mate. [ __ ] just woke up.
I had a lovely lion.
Lovely lion, mate.
Yeah. Oh, the Virgin. He's being awfully
quiet. The Virgin. Virgin of Orington.
Maybe if I virgin [ __ ] Yeah. [snorts]
pretty early to f to to trick Peter
belly, mate. Pretty [ __ ] early.
Absolute virgins. Whenever I go on
certain channel on here, right, and I
see the like comments and stuff, I just
say to myself, absolute virgins.
I always wake the [ __ ] whole [ __ ]
neighborhood up. You know I'm mate.
[ __ ] Hell, bro. I got some pork chops
today cuz I I got some when I went out.
So, I'm going to have that
wanker. That one, man.
I'm not long woke up, lad.
Just woke up, had a wank, made myself a
cup of [ __ ] as you do.
Oh, bro. [ __ ]
madness, isn't it?
Nah, bro. I'm not doing George F. I got
them from the butchers, so I'm
definitely having them.
You're a little wanker, urgent, boy.
Oh, really? Let me guess. Is a lot Is it
the large ass?
I still need to put that video up.
But of course, they're disabled. They're [ __ ] virgins.
What should you do? Tell them to [ __ ]
off and get a life. And if they've got a
problem with you speaking to me, they
know where I live. So come and sort it out.
You know, I need to put this video up
about this train situation I had.
[ __ ] madness. Tell them to [ __ ] off
and go get a life, the little virgin
nerds. And if they've got a problem,
they know where I live. So come and sort me out.
sort me out, you know, and if not, then
stop being a [ __ ] keyboard warrior.
You got to understand, bro, like the
people on here. Yeah, I was looking on
it yesterday on certain channels, bro.
They're just fat, ugly, jealous people
that ain't got no life. People that hide
under these accounts like the Flash and
all of these people. They're just a
bunch of nerdy little virgins. That's
That's what they are, bro. But nerdy
little fat, ugly, hopeless people. [ __ ]
with it. [ __ ] them, bro. They're jealous
of anyone that's younger than them,
better looking than them, got more of a
life than them. You know, it's been
going on for years with these with these
[ __ ] now, lad.
Been going on for absolute years. Yeah.
You okay, Captain?
Oh god, bro. I'm [ __ ] tired.
Not tired. Wow.
I'm not tired. I got a headache.
Do you know if I stop drinking Coke for
a while, I get headaches?
That's how much I crave it.
I stopped drinking Coke for like two
days. I remember when Mr. Chan was on
here. Yeah. Years ago, I was going to
the gym. I was cutting out Coke. Yeah.
Like not having Coke, nothing, bro. >> [snorts]
>> Swear down. I think I last about two
days, two and a half days of starting
headaches. I was just drinking water,
like just water, no coke. And damn, it
was getting to me, bro. Yeah.
Did you like my little picture?
I'm put that video up. That white knight
story, by the way. Yeah.
Are you all right, little copycat? Still
waiting for a copycat statement. Are you [screaming]
ready for a copycat statement? Are you?
I'll come back when I think of one. What
did you think of me in the bookies earlier, Grezy?
What did you think?
That was funny, isn't it? You see? Open
the door. Open the door, Captain.
I should have kept it going a bit longer
to be honest.
I was going to, but
you all right, Captain?
You all right, Captain?
We usually remember you all right, Captain [ __ ]
You all right, Captain [ __ ]
I'm uploading it right now. It's got 3 minutes remaining.
I've got it recorded as well, but I'm
not putting it on YouTube because I
don't want to give these fat, ugly
mongos entertainment. And they and
they're going to twist things as well.
It was really bad, bro. It was really
bad. And then the guy got his head
crushed to the door. That was the
funniest thing. Take that teach him for
being a little white knight, isn't it?
Cuz he's not looking where he's going.
He's too busy defending a woman for just
having a [ __ ] vagina. His head almost
got crushed in piece in pieces.
[ __ ] mad. That must have [ __ ]
hurt. That must have [ __ ] hurt that
must have, bro.
Karma in it. Stop defending people for
just having a [ __ ] vagina. Sad bastards. Rad.
Yeah, I've got some piggies for dinner.
I got some nice pork chops from the butchers. Gly
should get some mushrooms and coke though.
[ __ ] fed up with it, mate. Yeah,
I like piggies. I like piggies. [snorts]
Yeah, they're nice for the butch.
[gasps] [ __ ] lad.
Do you reckon you never lose it, Grezy?
Do you reckon you never lose your vard?
Sorry, mate. Just ignore me. You know
what? I'm like, you know what? I've just
completely gone mad. Do you know how
cold it was this morning, Gres? It was
so icy. I was almost falling over. It
was really icy. But I weren't going to
let these [ __ ] win.
These [ __ ] weren't going to win, mate.
No way these [ __ ] were going to win, mate.
Them [ __ ] were laughing at us, greasy,
mocking us. [ __ ] that.
Sounds like a copycat. Listen,
also no I'm not flexing£80. I'm not
flexing 80 pound you little virgin. I'm
just showing I I I beat Lad Brooks
before. And also that 13 grand is your
daddy savings that you can't show now.
So shut the [ __ ] up.
Oh yeah, I've just read that mate. That
13 grand, you can't show that 13 grand
now. You can't show daddy savings now.
So, it's actually 110 um because I was
just showing off me collecting the
winnings. That 13 grand is daddy
savings. That's not your money and you
can't show it now. So, shut the [ __ ] up,
mate. Show that money right now. And
I'll be like, "Okay, fair enough." No,
not now. No, no, no. You show that same money
in what we two months. And I'll be like,
"Uh, okay, fair enough. I'll give it to
him. I I'll actually give it to them,
Grezy. 100%, bro. if they can show the
same money in two months, but you can't,
you know, you can't show that same money
in, you know, two months.
That's daddy savings. That 13 grand is
daddy savings. I mean, I could have
[ __ ] five times that if I had no if I
had no life, you know, be a little [ __ ] virgin.
Do you know what I'm saying, bro? That's
daddy Stevens. That's not even your
money. Show it now. Show it [ __ ] now.
You know, like Mr. Bight has been
showing the same money for how long.
I mean, whether you got a life or not,
it doesn't really matter. But show the
same money in 3 months time. I think
that's fair, Grezy. I think it's fair.
If you can't share the same money in 3 months, then
at the end of the day,
it's pointless. You know, if you can't
show that same money, when I used to
show thousands, it was thousands all the
time. All the time, you will show money.
You're greasy, you little copycat. Little copycat.
You little copycat.
13 grand is show that money now.
13 grand is a very small amount of
money, bro. Right, for for not having a
life. And you can't show that money
anymore. So, shut the [ __ ] up.
Yeah, I'm having piggies today. Is that
all right with you, copycat?
If you can't show that money now, mate, then
like I could get to 13 grand in realistically.
Where are we now?
I could get in about 3 months.
If I was dedicated, I could get in about
two and a half, three months. Cuz don't
forget, I can work if I wanted to. So,
but bro, you think showing £13,000 of
daddy savings and not having a life is
is you winning?
You absolute virgin.
You absolute virgin. That's daddy savings.
That's D's bloody sins, mate. I probably
gone That's blood daddy's bloody sins,
mate. I probably gone through about six,
seven grand in the past three months.
Greavvesy. Hey, Greavvesy. Would you say
you're obsessed with money or nah?
I'm not really. Ask me.
As long as you've got enough to do what
you want and you don't have to stress
about money, I think there's a fine
line, isn't it?
I think then there's a fine line. Would
[clears throat] you agree, Grezy?
>> [gasps and snorts] [cough]
>> You said having 1,600 is decent, ain't
it? Uh, Grezy.
Ain't it, Grezy?
Yeah, I got some nice pork chops today,
bro. So, I'm not getting no takeaway.
And you know how much it cost me? They
only cost me £366.
Oh, it's only 110, bro. It wasn't the
factor showing money.
It wasn't the fact showing money, but I
just wanted to put a little thumbnail up, you know.
I put the video up, by the way. Meow.
Meow. Ow. You are the Yeah.
Yeah. I can't believe that woman on the
train. She was very rude. She said, "Oh,
you got food in your beard. You look
like you you ate wasp." But she didn't
talk about my look. She didn't say
anything about And I'm thinking, is that
is that your business that I've got
stuff in my beard?
I don't actually mind the women that are
being [ __ ] I just can't stand the
white knights. So they can clearly
defend themselves. These women can
clearly clearly defend themselves.
Um but yet you have these white knights
that want to defend people for just
for just um being a woman. And then he
got his head smashed through the door
cuz he wasn't looking where he was
going. I put the I put the video up, lad.
She was very very rowdy. I don't think
Timmy could have won against this one.
Um, copycat because I don't think you
understand that she was actually running
her mouth, bro. Really, really badly.
Really, really, really, really, really
badly. That one on Timmy's, she weren't
even saying anything.
That that woman on Timmy's weren't
saying compared to this [ __ ] bro.
She was running up her mouth, bro. But
this is what happens. is they meet
someone like me eventually.
They will meet somebody like me
eventually. Uh they meet their match.
Yeah, I'll be right about that.
Watch the video. It's called White Night Story.
I'm going to listen to it to make sure I
said everything I wanted to say.