Oh gosh.
Gosh, that pig ears.
Where's the [ __ ] the virgin? Oh. Oh gosh.
Them piggies fill me up. Oh. Oh gosh,
I lose hide now.
O, stop chewing Franklin. He's been all
right actually lately.
[ __ ] bro. And piggies.
Oh, I run out of guns.
I'll thank you later. [sighs] Yep.
I don't know why that fat old man go
start right up his [ __ ] mouth again.
I tell you what, [ __ ] Why don't you
come London, mate? One sec.
Yeah, that's better. That's a lot
No substance. No mind of its own.
just sat there waiting for the next
person to copy. Pathetic, isn't it?
Reminds me of that virgin [ __ ]
You right, UK asylum.
These people are [ __ ] saying, "Oh,
you look like I look like I'm 50. I
mean, I'm hibernating. I haven't been to
the barbers. Don't make me go to the
barbers and and put your looks all to
shame again, cuz I don't mind doing it,
mate. I don't mind [ __ ] doing it.
Yeah, I [ __ ] don't mind doing it, mate.
You know what I mean, mate. I got no
problem. You like my little videos, UK
Asylum. Do you like them?
Oh my god, bro. I am stuffed, bro. I feel sick.
[ __ ] I almost ate all of them, you know.
Yeah, exactly, bro. Yeah, exactly, bro.
They're just self projectors on here in
it. You know it. I know it. They're just
fat, ugly, old people that have got
nothing in life, lad.
You know it and I know it. So, yeah.
Fat, ugly little losers.
You know it, bro. They've You go on that
Red Stars channel, right? uh or like uh
you know uh [ __ ]
voice a reason channel and you see the
same nerds, fat, ugly life losers
gravitating towards one person. It's
jealousy on here, bro. They're they're
old [ __ ] ugly people that ain't got
nothing. They're jealous, bro.
You know what I mean?
I'm younger than them. I'm better
looking than them. I can do I can do a
lot of stuff. I can go and do what I
want. They're [ __ ] probably Yeah.
old, ugly, got nothing,
you know? You Yeah. That's why I got so
many people gravitate towards me, matey.
Is what it is, mate. You get used to it. You know,
you're in a chance telling me to come to
Wales. I mean, bro, we've been over this
many times. Every time I've gone to
Wales, you've shut you've kept your
[ __ ] mouth shut.
How about you come to London, mate, and
I'll glad you [ __ ] smash your [ __ ]
face in [ __ ] old man. You know,
they thought they were going to get them
winnings, didn't they, Griezy?
Uh, yeah, it was made an hour ago, but I
think it is him. No, I think it it could
be him. It could be him.
It could be him, bro.
Yeah, it was made an hour ago.
Greasy, I'm stuffed.
But it could be him. I think it might.
It could still be him, bro. Cuz why
would someone pretend to be him? It
doesn't make sense.
They're this fat, ugly life losers.
I'm a strong boy. What makes you say
that? Well, it's probably all them
piggies I've been eating, isn't it, Greavvesy?
Someone was was said to me earlier, "You
seem to be coping fine without women."
Well, duh. I'm getting my vitamins from
other places. All right, Grezy.
Like steak and uh I have egg and stuff,
so I get my vitamins from other places now.
>> You didn't think Muslims eat pork?
Well, I eat pork,
bro. That was hard to eat. I I ate most
of it. There was only two bits I didn't
eat. Oh my god, bro. They were huge them
pork chops. Greasy.
Uh, you know how much money you'd save
if you only ate pork, but you wouldn't
be able to do it, bro? You'd be sick. I
don't think you could live. There is
people that do do it, like Eastern
European people, but I don't think I
could live on pork, bro. I think you'd
become sick in it, Grezy. Yeah, you'd
if you lived on pork. I think you'd come
£3.77 for them three chunks of And it's
not frozen. It's not microwaved. It's
fresh food. Took me a bloody hour to cook them. Yeah.
So, yeah. I don't think you can live on pork, lad.
It's from the butchers as well. You
become very sick. Very sick.
I feel sick, bro.
Looks like I'll be having an early night. Yep.
Yeah, I cook them really slowly.
I like gammon. Yeah, gam's lovely. It's basically ham.
So, I get my vitamins from other people
now, from other places, Greavesy. So, I
don't have to deal with toxic women.
That's probably why I sound so stable,
isn't it, Grievy?
Cuz I just find I just get my vitamins
from other places.
Why is this LT commenting on my videos,
bro? [ __ ] off, man.
Uh, no it wasn't undercooked, mate. No,
it wasn't. I've been cooking pork chops
for years, fat old man. No, it
definitely definitely wasn't undercooked.
No, it definitely definitely wasn't
undercooked, mate. You could clearly see
with them being brown and there's not
one single blood. No, they weren't uncooked, mate.
No, they definitely definitely weren't.
Definitely definitely weren't. I know.
I've I've been eating pork chops for
many, many years,
so no, they definitely weren't
undercooked, mate. They were clearly
brown and golden. No, mate. Definitely
definitely not undercooked.
Uh, no you're not. No, you're not, mate.
No, you're [ __ ] not. I've been
cooking pork for many, many, many, many
years now. I know how to cook my piggies.
And if that's the real you, Guna, man,
listen. Listen. Stop talking [ __ ] Yeah.
You shut your [ __ ] mouth. How many
[ __ ] times when I went to Wales? Yeah.
Shut up. If you got a problem, come to
London. We're not going to go round and
round and round in circles. I don't know
when I'm going to Wales again. I need to
go back eventually, but I'm not going to
go and waste my money on time on some
fat old man, mate. Some fat ugly old
man. Yeah, if you want to come and meet
me, you can come to London. I'm not
wasting my time and money on some fat
ugly old man. [ __ ] off, mate. [ __ ] off.
You ain't about that life.
Yeah. Come to London. I kept quiet. I
don't think so.
I don't think I kept quiet. I never kept
quiet once when I went to Wales. I
really didn't. Not once.
[ __ ] off, mate. One second.
I'm going to go and tell.
Go away, bro.
Why are you commenting on my bloody videos?
Where is this guy? I'm going to comment
him. Yeah, I'm going to comment back.
One second, bro.
Yeah, I'm tell him go away, bro. Yeah.
don't know why this guy's on my channel, bro.
He wouldn't have liked uh what this
video today of me and this woman cuz
this woman was mixed race so she was
black and white. He reminded me of LT. I
told him to go away. [ __ ] mug.
I can't believe I got the winnings before anyone.
You know what's so mad UK asylum is
these people are talking [ __ ] about £100,
but they don't even [ __ ] have £100 on here.
What? No video about uh what what the train thing.
Uh there is a video, but I'm not putting
it up because of you biased little [ __ ]
like to twist things. Uh yes, there is a
video, mate. And if anyone wants to see
it, they're more than welcome to message
me and I'll send it to them privately.
We know what you little mongos do on
here. You like to twist things and make
up stuff. That's exactly why I'm not
putting the video up. So, the video is
definitely there. I've got it, but you
ain't seeing it. So simple, cuz you
little mongos like to [ __ ] make up stuff.
Yeah. So, you can [ __ ] right off. I
stayed up all night um yesterday just so
you [ __ ] can have the last laugh.
You haters, that's dedication.
Yeah, that that never happened. Yeah.
No, that that never happened.
That never happened. No one pull it on
me, mate. No, that never happened. That
never never never never happened, mate.
So again, you make up stuff.
Yeah, you make up stuff. You're boring.
Go away. Fantasy stories. This is
Fantasy Stories, by the way, people.
He's so disabled, he can't even make
Listen, listen, listen, listen, bro.
Right. If you come to London, I promise
you on anything that I have and any of
my family's life, I will meet you and
I'll smash your face in. No joke, bro.
Like, you've you've got my promise on
everything. You're a sad little [ __ ]
bro. You got bullied off of YouTube by
Pat Mustard and you're still coming on
here like you won. You're still coming
on here like you want fantasy stories.
You're a sad sad sad [ __ ]
Get a life. You ran away from Pat
Mustard. You're a bully victim. Every
time you try to sit there and say
someone else is a bully victim, you're
talking about your [ __ ] [ __ ] Irish
self. Everyone's seen what you done when
Pat Mustard called you out. Making you
say sorry. making you say [ __ ] sorry.
And here's the thing is, right? Yeah.
You want to talk about that prime video,
but guess what? At least it was somebody
bigger than me grabbed me in real life.
Bro, you said sorry to some fat old man
over YouTube. Like, bro, stop it. You're
embarrassing now. You're embarrassing.
Yeah. Come to London and I will meet you
anywhere you want. I'll even give you
the money if you want.
At least when I said sorry, I got
grabbed by somebody that was bigger than
me two years ago.
two years ago, bro. And the guy was
bigger than me and he caught me off
guard. I'm [ __ ] what? You said sorry
for [ __ ] to Pat Mustard.
You're a [ __ ] sad sad bastard. You
Northern Irish little gypsy little
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] off. Yeah. And
you'll notice all the Irish are the same
on here. You know that. L Pat, they're
all the same, bro. They're all the same.
These Irish [ __ ] Mongs.
You know what I'm saying? [ __ ] mongos.
Yeah, that fant. You know who I hate the
most on here, bro? Yeah.
It's got to be that V and that and that fantasy stories.
It's got to be, bro. I think Yeah, 100%.
It's got to be them two. Anyh how I ever
find any of these people where they
live, I'm going on their door, bro. I'm
going on their [ __ ] door, bro. I
swear to God. And I'll pay the money if
I ever find out where one of these live.
Yeah, like I said, you've already seen
what I done today. I stayed up all night
just so these [ __ ] didn't get their last laugh.
How much I hate them, bro. [ __ ] hate
these people, these haters on here. Not
everyone, but you know.
And that's what I'll do. I'll just keep
quiet now until they get doxed.
I'll just wait.
I will just wait, Greavves, until one of
them gets doxed and then it's and then
it's showtime. Then it's [ __ ]
Then it is [ __ ] absolute showtime.
100%. If you gave if you found out his
real address and you could prove that he
lived there, 100 million%. Same with
that fantasy stories. Any one of them,
bro. You ever find out where any of them
live, you tell me, bro, and I and I will go there
one million%. Or like you could prove
you knew where they were or you could
dox them. Yeah, 100%, bro. One last time
I would do it one last time.
They annoy me, bro. More than anyone.
They annoy me, bro. Even more than that,
Red Star. Because, you know, they're
little knees in real life. They're
little geeks, bro. They would never say
anything to anyone. Never. Never.
Yeah. And and and that's the thing that
annoys me about it, bro.
People like Bo Yeah. And all of these
people, bro, they annoy me, bro. They
annoy me. Yeah. Just like that Pat
Mustard. They're the worst. You know
that Red Star? Yeah. He's just a sad old bastard.
And I I don't even really give a [ __ ]
about that [ __ ] as much as I do like B
and that Fantasy Stories.
They're the worst, bro. They are the
worst. Trust me. Yeah.
That's who I That's who I hate the most.
worse than Virgin Boy. Yeah, I don't
like them, bro. I don't like them
cuz they're consistent keyboard
warriors, but we all know in real life
they would never say anything to anyone.
Like that be a war.
They do all of these, but we know in
real life they'd [ __ ] and shiver. We
know that with these people now, bro. We
know it with these people.
How about these people actually meet
someone? They want to try and talk about
L's that people have took. What about
all the W's I've took?
No one stuck it stuck it on me on a [ __ ] train.
No one stuck it on me on no [ __ ]
train, mate. Yeah, some Irish [ __ ]
mixed race guy said something. But did
he do anything? No, he didn't because he
he would have got his face smashed in.
But that guy was all right to be fair.
You know what? No, to be fair, that guy
was actually right. He wasn't making
excuses just cuz they were a woman. He
was telling her to stop and telling me to stop.
And he wasn't just defending her because
she was a woman. But this guy today was
just defending her cuz she had a curtain
between her legs and she wasn't
ladylike. She was very masculine. She
was a hoodr, a mixed race hood rat rat girl, you know.
But that guy, he wasn't defending her
because he was just saying like he was
saying it in a way where like he was
just trying to keep the peace. This guy
was being a white knight today and then
he got he got his head caught in the
doors. [laughter] He got he's got his
head caught in the [ __ ] doors all for
trying to defend someone because they
got a [ __ ] between the legs.
Madness. All because she had a [ __ ] in
between her legs.
No other reason. No other reason. >> Bad.
>> Doing well for myself. Oh, thank you,
boss. Thank you.
Yeah. Amazing how much your mental
health improves when you don't deal with women.
It's amazing, isn't it? No more
[ __ ] It's lovely. It's always, you
know, I always found this out. You know,
you never ever take them periods to save
money. Whether it's November, January,
February, you always have a peace of
mind because you don't deal with these
women anymore. You don't have these
because you don't have these problems.
Go to show them all the same cuz when
you quit, right?
Oh, I done a video on it, bro. You can
watch the video I done on it. It was bad.
You can watch the video.
But the last guy, he was just saying it
because he was basically sick of both of us.
But this guy was clearly just being
being a white knight. Clearly being a
And then he ended up getting his head
crushed in the door.
That must have [ __ ] hurt. Oh, see
Well, you're going to have to watch it,
bro. I can't be bothered explaining it
again. I'm not explaining it again.
Yeah, I told LT to go away basically.
Don't know why this [ __ ] is on
my channel, bro.
But yeah, that guy on the train a couple
of weeks ago, I don't think he was being
a white knight. I think he was just sick
of both of us. He said, "Oh, can you
stop it?" Then he said, "Oh, I'm getting
sick of you as well." That's called like
trying to like stop the pe that's trying
to like keep the peace.
Yes, but this guy today he was being a white knight.
Uh yeah, I had quite a lot of food today actually. Oh yeah.
Yep. I had a lot quite a lot of food today.
Gosh, a little community post I put up. Uzi.
Yeah, these people are talking [ __ ]
about £100, but they ain't even got
£100. £100 is like four Indian restaurants.
That can get you to a nice restaurant
four times. Grievy,
think about like that. Yeah, think about
it like that. Right. Say you put away £110,
right? So, say you put away £110. That's
four. That's That's a restaurant. Every
week for a month.
Every week for a month, you know?
So, think about like that, bro. Think
about a restaurant every Saturday for a month. See?
You can maybe even go restaurant maybe
five times with that money. And we're
talking nice restaurant like an Indian
restaurant. So yeah,
any job, mate. Any job.
Any [ __ ] job. You got a job, mate?
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I got a job,
mate. Yeah. Yeah. I got a job, mate.
Yeah. Yeah. I got a job, mate. You got a
job? Yeah. Yeah. I got a job, mate. You
Yeah. Yeah. here.
Oh, did I get a message? Oh, no.
I'm getting my vitamins from other
places now, aren't I, Grezy?
And now I don't get any headaches. [snorts]
Because you already found
Because you already found his mama.
Yes. She was trying to say that I look
like I was for a couple of days and I
had food in my beard. I said, "Okay,
it's winter. I'm hibernating." You do
realize that you're not supposed to
shave in November. It's a thing called
uh no shade vber.
The reason I've got gone to the barbers
is because I'm going out next week and
if I go to the barbers now it's going to
go back quickly. Sorry. So, yeah. Ah,
it's cute, isn't it?
Yeah, that fantasy stories, bro. I want
to [ __ ] give him a good island, you
know, mate. Give me that Vir.
You know what would be so good? That
would be good if I got one of their
addresses because when I go to Ireland,
I'll just start on all of them. Large a
all of the [ __ ] and then that would be
the end of it, isn't it?
I hate these [ __ ] Irish [ __ ] on
here, bro. I [ __ ] hate him on here.
here. Grievy, you know that
that V. [snorts] I hate all of them, bro.
No, not everyone. One person I was eating.
He gave me a dirty look. I said, "What
are you looking at?" I said, "What?" I
said, "Don't look at me like that."
Yeah. And that's what start that's what
started the whole thing. Oh. What?
Oh gosh. I've had too much piggies.
Yeah, I don't want an LT comment on my videos, bro.
I told him to go away. He commented on
my video, Grezy. I said go away.
Go away. Go away. Go away.
Grez, [ __ ] go away, man.
You like my little picture, Gy? What is
it? The little face.
Is it the little face? Grievy, do you
like my little face?
Never show the barcode again. I learned
my lesson, didn't I? H
I might put on my dating app profile picture.
Oh, I saw a cat earlier. I went to the
co-op and I saw a cat groovy and it ran
away. Where do you think it was running to?
Where do you think it was running to, lad?
Yeah, he probably was running to open. Yeah. No substance, no originality.
Just likes to copy people,
you know. See, dogs are different. You
see, dogs are like they're not like that
dogs. They're very selfish. Um,
you know, and they're loyal, but they
only care. They're loyal, but they're
very selfish dogs. They don't feel the
need to copy. Whereas cats, they copy people.
They copy people, don't they? Musically. Yeah,
my hair's getting really long and curly, Grezy.
Yeah, Cheryl Cole, that's a copycat
statement. Uh, Megan Fox,
Beyonce. I got It used to be a thing if
you didn't find Beyonce attractive, you
got a screw loose.
Yeah. Like your your mental basically.
Yeah. Just copying, is it?
Copying copying the crowd.
Wanted to fit in bloody well. I think a
lot of people follow football to fit in.
What do you think?
Yeah, they follow football to fit in.
Fit in with the crowd.
Yeah, I think so.
[ __ ] copycat. You little copycat. You
little You little cat. You little cat,
mate. You little copycat, mate. You
little cat, mate. You little copycat,
mate. You little cat, mate. You little
copycat, mate. You little cat,
mate. You little copycat, mate. You little copycat.
You got bigger, mate.
>> Yeah, he's unblocked. Yeah, he didn't
get blocked. I just timed him out.
I didn't block him. I timed him out.
Yeah, he's back on here. He commented on
my community post.
I like his little Jordy dialect. Bless
him and his little Jordy word. Squeezy.
Bless him and his little northeast dialect.
It's cute, isn't it? You in your little ways. No. A [snorts]
the women used to love me when I used to
go to Newcastle.
Oh, I say I'm gonna come up there and
take and I'm gonna nick your women
again, Reevesy. I'm gonna go up there
and nick your women. Yep. Wow.
Well, they can keep going in. I'm going
in my nest. I'm going to sleep. Is that kid green?
Not talking to body man again. [snorts]
Yeah. You actually think though if I
went like now to the bookies somebody
would have cashed it in. Yeah.
I think so.
I didn't know they could do that. I'm
never going to show a barcode ever
again. I probably won't show the bet
ever again to be fair.
I didn't know that.
That's mad. I don't
>> I need to go to the [ __ ] barbersy.
Do I look pretty when I've had my haircut? Yep.
Do I look pretty?
No, you do have to show the original slip.
No, no, no, no, no. You do. You do have
to. If it's over30, you do. If it's
over30, you have to show the original
slip as well.
Yeah, you do. If it's over30,
you do. That's what the rules are. No,
it's okay. I'll just wait.
You'll You'll wait? Yeah. Until Lad
Brooks opens. You saw me there waiting.
I wanted my £110.
It's my bit of wonger, my bit of money.
My bit of wa. My bit of cashy.
My bit of wa. My bit of cash.
Well, I'm going to need these people having it.
You know, I could pay for my haircut
so I can look pretty again.
Oh my god. What is this hair, bro?
I should get like a buzz cut.
I think I should get like a buzz cut,
you know, cuz it just goes back so fast.
Now I'm just going to get more cut off
the top, I think, this time cuz it goes
back so fast, lad.
[ __ ] It's annoying.
No, not a buzz cut. No. What am I
talking about? Not a buzz cut. Um,
I'm not going [ __ ] bored.
I don't need you in in uh No, it's not a buzz cut.
No, not a buzz cut. It is a buzz cut.
Yeah, where there's some at the top.
I'm not [ __ ] going bored, you [ __ ]
Am I going out this weekend? Uh, what do you think?
Are you happy now that I'm getting my
vitamins from other places now? Grezy,
you've you must have noticed a change in my behavior.
Well, there you go then.
Why would I go out this weekend? It's
November. Why am I going to go out in
November, bro? Pointless. I'm going out next week. Completely pointless,
isn't it, Greavvesy? Completely pointless.
Yeah. Next week I'm going out.
I could go out this week, but it would
just be pointless with November in it.
Pointless. Absolutely pointless.
[sighs and gasps] Nope.
But I've had to find other ways to get silly,
silly, miserable Reddit posts. No.
Are they Are they silly? Are they silly
miserable ones, Greavvesy? Well, it's
just cuz obviously I got abandoned by my
mama, is it? It's not nice.
How did you say you knew it was my mama again, Grezy?
Did you say they look like me?
What was it? It was cuz they looked like
me, wasn't it? Yeah.
But the real question is, who's your dad
then? If that's your mama, who's your dad?
Yeah, I was in the shower earlier
washing my Pekka. Greavvesy.
washing my little Pekka.
I remember when I got a [ __ ] in the alleyway.
When I got a [ __ ] in the alleyway,
I think my dick must have been stinking
that day, Grezy. Cuz when I'm not
circumcised, you have to wash your
willie, you know, more thoroughly
otherwise it it otherwise it it smells.
So, could you imagine? She was sucking
my willie greaves in. She didn't she
didn't like wash it or anything
cuz with the 19year-old she says, "No,
you're washing your dick before I'm
putting that in my mouth." She was very
like strict about it.
Which to be fair was kind of a turnoff.
I I said to one before, "How did my dick
taste?" And they said it tasted a bit
salty like skin.
>> [clears throat]
>> Nah, bro. Nah.
I done a little video for you, Grezy.
Can I put it up? I still got it.
Yeah, I'm going to put it up.
Yes, she used to hate giving the
[ __ ] Um, Greavves. She said it's
disgusting because he comes out of your
dick in that, in it. And I said, "Just
shut up and put it in your mouth."
What do you think of that, Grezy?
Lovely, isn't it?
I just said shut up and put it in your
mouth. Stop being naughty.
I'm putting I done a video to you, Grezy.
I'm I'm uploading it right now. We got 3
minutes left. I'm not putting the train
video up. No way.
No. No. No. No. No way.
Got enough [ __ ] white knight and simps. Yep.
There we go.
Should be up now. Grezy. Oh, there you go.
Yeah, that was earlier. Greavvesy. Gosh.
Yeah, it is. It isn't funny, bro. It isn't funny.
I want Greavesy to see it. I just don't
want these little nerds to see it like
Red Star and Voice of Reason and that
cuz you know they're like these little
mongos on here. They twist [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. I was trying to walk away from it,
but I couldn't.
I want to, but I don't know how I can.
>> Yeah, but you're going to send it to
people, aren't you?
>> You're not going to show it to people, are you?
Yeah, you and Stephen H can see it.
Yeah, cuz I'm scared. No, I'm not
posting it on here, bro. No way am I
posting it on here. No [ __ ] way am I
posting it on here, mate. That train
video. No [ __ ] way, lad.
Not with these freaks on here. [ __ ] that.
>> You know what they're like, mate.
Yeah, I want you I want you Chip Rate
and Steven Hour to see it. But please
How do you tag people?
What should I just do? Greavvesy.
Nah, I'm not posting it. I'll post it
for Grevy and Triple H and stuff, but
nah. No way. Nah.
No way, mate. Okay, then.
You promise you're not going to share it though, Greavvesy.
All right, one sec.
You have to say promise.
I just don't want redstone. These little
virgins, these other virgins seeing it. Yeah.
All right. All right. All right.
I'm uploading it. So, you're going to
see it. Greavves.
If you want to do a review or whatever,
you know, you're more than welcome to.
You can you can see it first and I'll
show the other [ __ ] [laughter]
This isn't on a public train by the way, lads. Mama,
where you going, mama? Oh gosh,
it's past your bedtime, mama. Oh gosh.
Right. One second. It's uploading at 41 seconds. [laughter] [snorts]
It's not uploaded yet.
That's a [ __ ] little man.
Okay, I will. I will. Oh, well,
I've tagged you first though, then I'll tag them.
I need to go. We
My pick is hurting.
I can tag more people as long as they don't [ __ ] Yeah,
I might even tag LT Greavvesy. Why not?
You know, the more the marrier.
It should come through Greavesy in a
minute. One sec. Tim Eldridge. Yeah.
It was bad. It was bad. I just tagged
you, by the way. [laughter]
I just Yes, it's uploaded. [laughter] Tim Eldridge.
Yeah, this is the this is the brother
side of YouTube, not the virgin side.
Cuz you got the brother side and you got
the virgin side.
You know what I mean? Gre
and then you got the virgin side of YouTube.
I don't like the virgin side.
There you go. You have been tagged. Captain
and and and the Orington virgin.
The Orington virgin as well. We don't
want that Orington bloody virgin.
The Mong side.
I need to go [ __ ] piss, bro. Bear in
mind I was half a [ __ ] slate, mate.
Listening to this [ __ ] [ __ ] guy pissed, bro. Oh [ __ ] Yeah. Graves, eh? >> [snorts]
>> You [ __ ] virgin.
You [ __ ] virgin. Can't you
What did you think, Gravesy? Did you see it, Captain? [laughter]
Everybody was looking. Everybody was
I can't do that, mate. I can't do that.
No, I can't do that.
There's no point then, bro. Because I
don't want these [ __ ] seeing it. So,
unless I put it public on my other
channel and then and then tag you.
I can put it on my other channel then
tag you cuz I got another I've got a
couple of channels.
Could that work or
Yeah, but then they're just going to go
on where I've tagged you then, isn't it?
These little nerds.
So that's not going to work either. [ __ ]
Yeah, I I don't want these [ __ ] seeing
it to be fair, bro. These little mongos
on here cuz you know they're like these
little mongos. They twist [ __ ]
Don't you use Instagram anymore. Um Grezy
Yeah. All women in the world need to
suck willies, don't they, Greavvesy?
Why do some women hate sucking willies, Greavvesy?
I think it's quite nice getting your willie sucked.
What do you think, Greavves? You're not asked. [sighs]
Do you remember Peter Belly doesn't know
where to turn?
We these trolls on here ain't it?
Peter belly doesn't know where to turn.
I'm a bubba.
I'm all cozy in my little nestles. Grezy
Greavves is the top one of the top
brothers on this uh on this uh YouTube,
aren't you Greavvesy?
You're the top brother.
And then the second is Steven Howard.
And then the third one is Triple H.
You know, even if it was just us three
on this on this live stream, that would
be enough, you know, just us, you know.
Three, four people. Yeah.
Then these little mongos.
My [ __ ] hair is annoying me, bro.
It's [ __ ] annoying me, lad.
I mean, I could
should go out this week because if I got
my haircut this week, obviously I
wouldn't need to get it done again next
week, would I? Because I'm only going to
like the area where I'm going. You don't
need to dress up for.
You don't need to dress up. The area
that I'm going to, you don't need to dress up.
Depends on what area you're going. So, I
could I could actually go out this week
if I wanted to, but I don't really want
to be fair.
I'd rather just save myself and it makes more sense.
Like I said, it's November, so nope.
I used to just get my willie out.
Grey, you know the 19year-old. I used to
just get my willie out
and I used to say, "Suck my willie."
What do you think of that, Greavvesy?
It's nice getting your willie sucked. Kentucky,
you should just get out on the bed.
My little Pekka. Yep.
It was lovely.
I'd be in my little t-shirt and my
little shorts. I'd come back from work
and all I'd want is a [ __ ]
You know, sometimes when you when you've
been working all day, mate, and you just
want a [ __ ] grievy,
a [ __ ] and a lovely takeaway. That's
all you need, you know. That's lovely. Yep.
Women were put on this earth to satisfy
Peter Belly's needs. Greasy.
Yeah. I was at work. I was at work all
day. I made £100. I think it was like 90
or 100 pounds. And I just wanted a
[ __ ] and a takeaway.
How cute is that? Grieves.
That's cute, isn't it? Greasy. Very cute.
Is that cute, Grezy?
You make me laugh, Greezy. You're proper
proper troll you are.
Why don't you go on anyone else's
channel, may I ask?
You never go on LJ's.
You never go on anyone's channel but
mine. I think that's quite weird.
I'm starting to think you just like mocking me.
Oh, Timmy Aldridge. Oh, what? Does he
want the link?
Doesn't go on anyone else's channel but mine.
I put the link out there, didn't I? Not. No, there is Grezy.
Yeah, I woke up today. I had a play with myself, Grezy.
Um, went to make a cup of tea and I
chilled out for a little bit.
I think about boobies when I masturbate with. Yep.
Big boobies and stuff.
Is that cute? Greavvesy,
remember. Stop saying my name. No, I
don't want to stop saying your I don't
want to stop saying your name. I want to continue.
No, I want to continue. That's cute.
What was it? [snorts] Grezy,
stop saying my name. Copycat statement.
Oh, Timmy's not uploading any videos anymore.
Yeah, maybe I like it. Greasy. [snorts]
So, why did you say that USA is my
mommy? Grezy, does she look like me?
Really? Same eyebrows, isn't it? Same
hair, same eyebrows. Uh, nope.
No, but I will be going to sleep soon.
No, I will be going to sleep soon
though, matey. I got some popcorn
greasy. So, I'm probably going to put
something on and drink some Coke and Yeah.
You know, my mommy's got a YouTube channel.
No, I didn't sleep cuz I wanted to be
the first one in the bookies.
You know, my mama's got a YouTube
channel. She used to go live on it, but
uh she doesn't go live anymore.
Yeah, it doesn't go live. She was on PS4. Yeah.
Nah. Yeah, my Yeah, Laney does. Yeah.
Yeah. But USA is is definitely my mama
though, isn't it, Grezy?
Definitely. Is it? It's not just some
normal person that you hooked up with,
is it Greavvesy? Nah.
There's a lot of uh history for Peter
Belly in Elephant and Castle.
Let me have a look.
Yeah, I'm watching it. Grezy,
someone said you hate PJ like everyone
else. And I love it. Yeah. Lovely.
I like that. Mission. Mission passed.
Greavvesy. Mission. Mission passed.
I like that bit.
Yeah. Thank you, Captain.
Yeah, I like that. Mama. Oh gosh. Hey, mama.
Who is that?
Of course I won, mate.
There was no way they was ever going to
beat me, mate. No [ __ ] way.
Oh, this is my mama. Look. One sec.
You're not my number.
I got some popcorn I'm going to nibble on.
I bought it from the
places and the [ __ ] popcorn is
ranking it. But the co-op one is quite nice.
What popcorn do you like from where?
You know, but what, mate? No. No. But
It's worse when it's burnt. I hate it
[ __ ] It It's disgusting. And the taste
even if it's slightly overdone.
Yeah, that's my mama. I just linked it. Look.
Oh, no. I almost slipped earlier
and fell over.
No, but when I went out, I went out at
6:00 in the morning, ma,
and I almost [ __ ] slipped. It was
really icy and cold.
It's not a joke, Ma. Yeah,
I [snorts] was conceived on Valentine's Day.
I was convinced con that's a fun fact
you didn't know about me Greavvesy
fun fact that you didn't know I was
conceived on Valentine's Day.
Yeah. USA Izzy and Damon was up to no
good and then I came I came into the world.
How cute is that?
I come into the world [snorts] crazy.
What do you think about that? [snorts]
Yeah, they're sad bastards. They're sad
people on here. Triple H.
You remember when they spoke about your bed sheets?
Yeah, I was conceived on Valentine's
Day, Grezy. That's why I was born in
October. That's what I was conceived. [snorts] Yep.
Cuz obviously they were dating and
stuff. That's how I came into the world.
Is that right, Greavvesy?
You remember when I was messaging that
damn saying, "Why did you and mama split up?"
Do you remember Grievy? Why did you and
mommy split up then?
What's the What's the reason?
They never answered me.
What are you What are you blessing to? H
Tam's your dada you remember Tam's your
I was conceived I was conceived
I was conceived Greavvesy Valentine's
Day cuz USA Izzy and
Damon in was having like some fun time
with each other. And that's how I was
brought into the world. Yep.
Yeah. They weren't going to get there
before me. I even traveled 6 miles as
well. I had to pay for the train and
stuff cuz that one opened at 7:30. You
see, the other one opened at 8:30. So yeah,
no one was beating me, mate. Grievy was
talking about setting alarms and [ __ ] I
was like, mate, there's not going to be no alarms.
There's no alarms. We ain't going to
sleep, mate. We are not going to sleep.
We ain't going to sleep, mate. Are you [ __ ] mad? >> [sighs]
>> I like pineapple juice more.
Greasy. So, what do you think about my
mama on her YouTube channel?
I said to this troll account, why didn't
she tell me she was my mama? And she was
like, Peter Belly, she wanted to keep it a secret.
And I said, "Really?" So I said, "Where
was I born then?" She was like, she was
like, "Boston, Massachusetts." Greavves.
They're saying that she she didn't want
to tell me that she was my mama because
she wanted to keep it a secret. Grieves. Yep.
Yeah. Exactly. Yeah.
No, you can't triple. No, you can't,
lad. Can't even have a [ __ ] football
in peace with these [ __ ] No.
Horrible being abandoned, isn't it?
See, at least with you, Grezy, obviously
like your parents died and stuff, so
it's like a bit different. But when you
actually have a have a mother that's
abandoned you, you would you would know
what it's like. It's not good to be abandoned.
To be abandoned, it's horrible, mate. A
parent is one thing, but to be abandoned
by someone that brought you into this
world, Grezy, it's horrible. Yep. Lovely.
Uh, Lane is not my mama.
USA. Izzy is my mama.
Uh, that's not my mom.
Laney is my adop my adopt adopted mama.
Yes, she's my adopted mama
cuz I was put into care.
I was put into care. I was put into care
three years ago. Come April.
Yeah, I was put into care. Yeah. Yep.
Yeah. That [snorts] is quite sad to be
honest. We That is quite sad.
So, how do you have a house then? Is it
How did you get housed? Is it by the council?
Did you get housed by the council then or
you know another thing with these
people? Triple H, they're such
repeaters. How many times do you hear
skin m skin m skin m [ __ ] they're repeating bastards? Yeah.
Who do you think I look more like?
Greavesy. Laney or USA is he?
Why do I look so much like this? USA is greasy then. Huh?
That's a bit weird, isn't it? I look so
like this person. Oh, huh. Would [laughter]
you say that we look like each other? We
sig not Peter belly's mama. Greasy.
Sig was never your mama.
You remember that one? Greasy.
She wanted to keep it a secret.
I wonder who it is behind that account,
bro, that keeps doing that.
There's got to be someone We keeps doing it. Obviously
someone keeps [ __ ] doing it in it.
Well, I don't know who it is.
I don't know who it is, lad. Mama,
I'm going to have some popcorn and cola
in a minute. Is that all right, Greasy?
If I have some popcorn and some cola, huh?
That's sad about your parents though,
Grezy. Very sad.
It happens sometimes, you know, when
you've been sick and you start getting
hungry again. You just feel like some
popcorn and coke.
So, how do you live by yourself, Grezy?
Is it Is it owned by the council or something? That's strange.
Bless you, Grezy. Do you not do you not
have any like friends or anything?
My dad died when I was like 11, but my
mom brought me up. So, I only really had
my mom, so it wasn't really a loss to me
anyways. But like, you don't have any
friends or anything, Grezy? Maybe I can
come around and we can play some games together.
We can stream on YouTube.
I feel bad, you know, cuz obviously you
don't have parents and stuff. I don't
know if you have any siblings. I don't
think you've got any siblings, do you?
Maybe I can come around and we can play
some games together.
You know, we can be friends.
Me, I'll bring King if you want. I'll
bring King Ling. Yeah.
Bless you Gly. Bless you.
Bless you in life.
[sighs and gasps] Yeah.
[snorts] Yeah. My dad died.
Oh, bless. But how do you live on your
own, though? How do you pay the rent? I
don't get it.
How do you pay the rent and stuff?
Oh, let me guess. You give people
[ __ ] for money, don't you, Greavvesy?
What? Do you give people [ __ ]
I shot myself earlier.
Yeah, I shot myself earlier.
So, what are we going to do with these
football brothers? What are we going to do?
You're going to It's not going to be
worth doing these both teams to score
anymore, is it?
With these [ __ ] [ __ ] odds
with these [ __ ] with these [ __ ]
shitty odds in it.
Not on the train. Just after that, I had
to put my underpants in the wash.
Greedy. Do you think USA is is disgusting
for wanting to have sex with somebody
that she just met?
That's weird though because if you're
just That's weird because if you're just
looking for sex, people say that like,
you know, you need to get in a
relationship with a woman and if you if
you just want sex, then you're not going
to get a woman.
But it's all right for women to want
dick. That's not fair, is it, Grievy?
Would you say that's another one of the double standards?
I don't know who that lady Z is.
Yeah, it kind of is
double standards. Kind of kind of
because if you said that you were just
looking for sex,
people say that you need to get in a
relationship with a woman in it. They
say you want to you would get ridiculed.
But if a woman wants dick, then
that's completely fine.
Do you not think it's weird, Grezy?
Somebody wanting to have sex with first
person that they meet. Grezy,
you think it's disgusting?
It's not wear a condom. I said I'm not
wearing a I'm not wearing a condom.
[ __ ] Are you mad asking me to wear a
condom? [ __ ] that. I'm not wearing a condom.
You silly goose. I don't wear condoms.
I don't like condoms.
I think that's probably why I got
[ __ ] from escorts all them times
because you can't [ __ ] them without condoms.
My sister's got a cat. I hate cats.
There's no substance, no integrity,
no nothing, no mind of their own. They
just seek out to copy people.
That's what I don't like about cats. I
hate cats. They got no mind of their own.
They just copy people. And my sister's
got a cat.
And every time I go there and every time
I go there, it [ __ ] it jumps at me
because I don't like Cheryl Cole.
It starts [ __ ] jumping at me and
attacking me and [ __ ] It won't leave me
alone. I said, "I don't like Cheryl
Cole. He keeps calling me gay and hitting me.
[ __ ] off, you copycat.
I had to go in the other room.
It's not my Frenchie, it's my sister's. But yeah,
I'll be getting one soon. Greavves. I'm
going to be getting a a puppy Frenchie.
I love the baby M ones. I love the baby
M ones. M Yeah. Oh, that's cute. That's cute.
called it greasy.
Could do. That's a lovely little vote.
Yeah, could do.
I wouldn't get a girl Frenchy because
when they go on heat, it's not good. So,
it has to be a boy. But they're like two
grand aer dogs, Greavesy. They're about
2K the doggies.
They're [snorts] like 2K with papers.
They're [ __ ] expensive, mate.
[clears throat] They're [ __ ] expensive.
They're [ __ ] cute, though. If I mean,
well, papers. I mean, paper ones, like legit ones.
No, I don't I would never meet that guy
cuz he he played with his own [ __ ] It's [ __ ] gross. No.
Yep. And I didn't get owned on a train, matey.
That seems like the virgin.
Oh, nice. How did you get 4.5k?
Do you work or something? 4.5K. Wow.
That's a lot for a doggy lad.
But he's gorgeous though.
Nice. How How much do you get a month?
You know, it's [snorts] so weird when
you think about money, right? Money
world like money is what
buys you food and stuff. It's so weird
when you think about it, is it Greavesy,
that a bit of paper is what like you
need to live. It's just so weird, isn't it?
It is weird when you actually think
about it, isn't it?
[snorts] It is strange, bro. Yeah.
No, they're my little mates.
Nice. Six grandkid a month.
That's nice, bro.
Yeah, that's good. Do gamble.
14 Maxwell. Do you gamble?
I ain't played roulette for ages. Maybe
I need to do another little roulette
session at some point. It's been a long time, boy. Maybe
can't be asked with it anymore, though.
That's why I don't play it. Yeah. Nice.
I see what you mean. Yeah, it is weird.
Yeah, it's weird.
You got paid last week and you're almost skinn. How?
That's six grand a month and you're almost skinn. That's mad.
silly goose. This
wa That's crazy, bro. That's mad.
I don't believe you.
What do you think, Steven Hour? Do you
believe this guy? Sounds mad.
That's crazy. If that's true, bro. Bless you.
What do you mean not a prayer?
What do you mean?
get over this [ __ ] vintage porn in
the 70s. I can't get I was watching some
interracial vintage porn
made in the 70s.
What the [ __ ]
[ __ ] mad, bro.
The [ __ ] 70s. That's crazy.
Have you ever watched interracial porn?
I'm not muted, am I? Yo,
you hear me?
Yeah, I was watching some interracial um
vintage porn in UK asylum and these
videos were made in the 70s.
What the [ __ ]
It was made in the in the 70s.
That is mad, bro.
I weren't even [ __ ] born then.
What the [ __ ] And it was uploaded in 2010. mad.
You ever watch Vintage Paul UK Asylum? Yeah,
I watch vintage porn.
I don't know if you watch porn. I don't
always watch it. Sometimes Yeah,
but it's so weird to know that like
these people are probably dead now, is it?
Yeah, probably dead now.
That is weird, lad. Oh, they're [ __ ]
old. So, you're [ __ ] jacking off the old people.
You're jacking off to really old people
when I watch.
How are they able to put these old poros
on websites though? Grezy told me, but I forgot.
How are they able to
2010? Jesus Christ.
Look, I can show you what I was I told
I'll show you what what porno I was
watching. I'll put the picture up.
I was watching this one. Look,
they were in an island and she made him
suck her dick. She made him see she made
him suck his dick
and then she still couldn't get off the island.
Yeah. Yeah. I was watching some
interracial porn from the 70s. Yeah.
This is what this is what I was watching.
It's quite funny to be honest.
Look at that shitty picture.
70s, bro. That does that definitely look
like the 70s UK asylum.
Yeah, that's definitely the 70s, isn't it?
Yeah. Greasy, look. That is definitely
the 70s, isn't it? >> Yeah.
Think about it, Grezy. There was no Tik
Tok, no Instagram, no smartphones. Imagine that.
Imagine that, lad.
Did you find it?
You reckon them two are still alive now? Nah.
Nah, there's no way they're still alive.
They got to be dead now, ain't it?
Yeah, they got to be dead. You'll laugh
at this, right? But there's some porn
star men, right, that's been doing it
since their 20s. Now they're an old man.
They're still doing it.
And they're actually still doing it as
an old man. I'm not even joking, bro.
There's this Italian porn star. He's
been doing it since he was in his 20s or
30s. Now he's I think in his 60s7s and
he's still doing it. Maybe Yeah. [ __ ]
Some lovely interracial porn. Imagine that.
Lovely interracial porn with a cup of [ __ ]
I don't know. I was bored.
It was fun.
Yeah, I was watching it cuz I was bored.
You blackmailed her into getting sex.
Uh, he made empty promises to get sex.
>> What do you think of that, Grezy?
Yeah, she was terrified.
You get me off, I get you off. You get
me off. I get you off. Bro, you know
it's interracial porn is the most
funniest. Yeah. I'll never forget this
time. Yeah. This black guy was getting a
[ __ ] and he was like, "That's the business."
I was dead, bro. I remember me and Money
Mike came. We was watching at the same
time. Yeah. I [ __ ] fell off the bed
laughing, mate. He said, "That's the
business. You're nasty." And I like
You're nasty and I like nasty.
You're only going to be nasty for me. Yeah.
Imagine. Have you ever had a [ __ ]
before and said that's the business?
What the [ __ ] That's the business.
Imagine that again. [ __ ] That made
me laugh for so long after that. You
know that's the business.
That's the business.
She said, "I'll only give you sex if you
can get me off the island." So when he
got sex, he just left.
And um somebody on the porno commented
saying, "It sums up men.
You got it.
Grezy, did you like you used to like Crash Bandicut?
I can't believe I got with a Somalian person, bro.
Remember when I got with that Somalian Grimsy?
So, I've actually done interracial,
haven't I, Grezy?
Yeah, I've done interracial.
Gy, I can't believe I've actually done interracial.
What do you think of that?
Would you ever do interracial?
I can't believe I've actually done
interracial, bro. What the [ __ ]
But I remember why I done it. I remember
why I did do it though.
I do remember why I did it. Basically, yeah.
Well, I think they're dead now. Wasn't
it um UK asylum?
I'm guessing they're dead now. No,
cuz that was in the ' 70s. My mom was
born in 1960.
My mom was born in
Yeah. My mom was born in 1960,
so she would have been 10.
Yep. They're dead.
I was watching Alice and Wonderland porn
UK asylum. And now the woman's like
really old. She's alive, but she's Yeah.
Yeah. Do you know how they used to do
porn back in the day? I think they used
to put them on discs in it. UK asylum.
I think they used to put them on discs.
Yeah, I think they used to record them
and put them on disc cuz obviously they
didn't have the internet back then.
Yeah, something like that.
Yeah, I've been with a black woman once.
And when she bet and when she kept
sucking my willie, she kept her teeth kept grinding.
Yeah. So now they put all the old porn
onto these videos now.
You can tell though cuz the picture was
so [ __ ] back then, wasn't it? If you
look at the pictures back, the picture
back then to now. Yeah.
Yeah. The picture was so bad back then, wasn't it?
I was watching a lot of [snorts]
good old vintage porn. Oh gosh.
Is he one second? I need to go
downstairs. Oh gosh, he Oh,
I'm going to put my little gowny on.
My little gowny. Yeah.
I already have.
I have with a Somalian before.
Yeah, I gave her 200 £250. She gave me a
[ __ ] in the Weather Spoons toilets
and I went to her gaff and banged her a
couple of months after.
I gave 250 combo because well back then
I used to be loaded so [laughter]
yeah full time nah.
Yeah but back then I was [ __ ] loaded
bro so I didn't care you know. Yeah she
gave it in the weather spoons toilet triple.
Yeah, the weather spoon is Tottenham court toilet. No.
Then she started telling me she loved me
and that. I was like, "What the [ __ ] You're crazy." >> Yeah.
No, it's all been a load of bollocks.
It's all been a load of bollocks. Right,
I'm going to have some bloody popcorn
now. I'm [ __ ] hungry again. Oh gosh. ALL
RIGHT. DID YOU TOUCH ISABELLA'S BOOBIES?
RIGHT. Good point. Would you touch Isabella's boobies?
No, it's not funny. was immature.
That's what I can't off these movies. [laughter]
They were mocking you laughing at you.
Don't let these kind of women [laughter] do
I love popcorn,
but every time I go to the cinema, it
reminds me of USA. Is it? I'm not sure
why. uh green when I'm munching on the
popcorn and drinking the cola.
Can't beat nice popcorn and a Coke.
You can't beat a nice popcorn
and a Coke, right, boss?
Mom, you can't beat a nice popcorn with a um
>> Coke with uh
>> What's a Coke called on the machine?
>> Just what he wants to do.
>> Certain kind of Coke with syrup coke.
Syrup Coke with a nice bit of popcorn.
Oh, mate. Honestly, yeah,
it's very nice.
He don't want you.
>> Do you remember? Stop going on about
some girl that don't want you grievy. I'm not.
If you're old school, you remember that. I'm not M popcorn
I love popcorn.
I'm not sure.
Probably sucking his dad's disabled dick. M lovely.
Money man blocked me. Yeah. out. statement.
You can't deny she's attractive. Copy that.
nothing but a [ __ ] copycat.
I haven't moved on. I'll [clears throat]
never move on.
No, I had a boyfriend threatening me on Facebook, bro.
I told him if he wants to come to
London, I'll smack his [ __ ] face.
Josh Brown's name is
Josh Brown. Well, I saw her boyfriend.
Yeah. So what happens graves? today.
Yeah, but you said my Yeah, but you said
my mom is lane.
You said my mom is lane.
I think that Steven Howard works, you know.
I think I think that Steven Howard
works. Do you know why? Because he
always comes on here around five or six.
So, do you reckon he works this Steven
Howard? I reckon he does. Yeah.
Please know who Trevor McDonald is.
Do you know who that is? Trevor McDonald.
How do you know who he is?
So, yeah, them two could still be alive
if they lived, but they would be like
Trevor McDonald's age. Yeah,
there would be Trevor, if they were
alive, there'd be Trevor McDonald's age.
He's 86. I just looked him up. He's
[ __ ] 86 that come.
So, they'd be around 8. Yeah.
But black people live quite long, don't they? Grooia.
You all right, Mr. Be? I was watching
some interracial porn yesterday.
Oh yeah. Yeah, he's all right. Yeah.
Yeah. He used to be I Yeah, I remember him.
Did you just like Philip Scoffield? I
never liked him, bro. He [ __ ] gives
me the EB jebies. That Philip Scoffield is cringe. Nah.
No, that Trevor McDonald's is get m
Trevor McDonald's [ __ ] 86.
I just looked Alice Stewart up. He's 72. Yeah. Um,
was it over? Was it over the rumors?
Was it over the rumors? Music. I used to
like do no deal, but I didn't really
like No. Edmonds. He's a narcissist,
isn't it? No. Edmunds doesn't seem like
a nice person.
Yeah. Philip Scoffield yet. You don't
hear about him Huh?
Julie hatching him. I didn't know.
I I didn't know about I just looked her up.
What for doing?
>> I didn't know who I dude is.
You did you just like Mr. been crazy.
Did you just like Mr. Bean?
I used to do a really good Mr. Bean impression. Yeah.
Yeah, I used to. Yeah.
Yeah, I was do that as well, Mr. Bean. Yeah. Yeah. [clears throat]
Yeah. I was good at it as well.
Yeah, I remember that. Yeah, it was good.
Do you watch any quiz shows? We
know I can't do it anymore.
There's the sky, bro. He does voices perfectly.
He does voice. He does impressions
perfect. Yet he can do Mr. um Mr. Herb
the pervert. You know, Family Guy Mr.
Herbert is his name is
Herbert. The pervert, bro, that whistles
when he talks. That is hard to do, bro.
Like, he actually whistles as he talks.
I'm sure you've heard it if you ever
watch Family Guy. He whistles when he talks.
I can do that, bro. But I front them.
Yeah. My mom loves um Tipping Point. She
love She likes Ben Shepherd. Yeah.
Yeah, she um she likes Ben Shepard.
Yeah, I like the chase. I didn't really
used to like Bradley Walsh, but he's
actually all right to be honest. There's
a lot worse out there than him. He's not
the worst. I just don't like that. No,
Edmunds. He I used to you not you're not a
don't really like Ronaldo either. He
seems up his own ass. I don't know if
you've watched these interviews, Greasy,
but he seems like really up his own ass that Ronaldo.
I don't know if you ever watched it, but
there was an interview where Pier Pier
Morgan was interviewing him.
Piers Morgan isn't really liked either.
A lot of people don't like Piers Morgan.
Don't know what your opinion on him is, but yeah.
Do you remember Alan Carr? remember Adam. Hey, Ronaldo. Cristiano Ronaldo. Oh, P.
>> Adding, it's me, Alan Car.
>> Yeah, he's a puff, mate. He's a [ __ ] puff.
Alan car is a [ __ ] puff, mate.
I think Ed Sheeran's all right, Grey.
I think Ed Sheeran's all right. He seems
like um a down to earth person, you
know, Ed Sheeran. I don't mind Ed
I think he's all right.
The link's up for you, Timmy, if you want it. Yeah.
Yeah. It seems a lot about uh Ed.
I think you got a crush on Taylor Swift,
don't you, Greavvesy?
Oh, you want to know another copycat statement,
Grezy? Uh um Emma Watson, you know Emma
Watson um from Harry Potter? People used
to obsess over her
like she was the best looking person in
the world. That was a trend as well. I
can't remember the
exact uh year, but that was a thing as
well. They used to copy each other. I'm
sure you do you remember that one? You
might not remember it, but yeah, they
copy each other.
Yeah. Do you remember that one? The Watson one? copy.
Even though she was normal looking and
she has no body,
they were all copying each other in
school again. Do you remember? Do you Copycats.
Okay, here we go. Bri
over that one. Oh.
Well, they used to copy each other with
that one as well. Yeah.
Bless you and groove if you like, Ed.
Oh, you remember that [ __ ] Harry
Hill? [ __ ] prick he is. You remember
him? Harry Hill.
He was an absolute prick. He was
remember him, Grezy. Harry Hill.
Absolute [ __ ] prick. He was, mate. Yeah.
You remember that one?
Everyone used to like that Russell
Howard. I never used to like Russell Yeah.
Oh, that's lovely. That popcorn.
I agree with you. You're going to watch
the new Scream when it comes out in February.
Oh, bless you.
Yeah, cuz you've got anxiety, don't you, Grezy? So,
yeah. There's a there's a film I need to
watch next month. I think it's called
The Bride or The Maid.
I don't know. But I'm going to have to
start checking the cinemas every week.
There's some good ones coming out next month. So,
I want them to
I want them to make a talk to me, too.
I wonder if they're going to make a smile free.
Yeah. Joseph is a nons lover.
It's like what Gan says, anyone that's
not blocked by nons then because you
can't trust them.
Yeah, Joseph F is a nons lover.
He said I called him a N. I never called
him a N. I said that he's a N lover
cuz he goes on Virgin Boys
[ __ ] all the time.
just threw up.
Yeah, he comes on every couple of weeks,
man. He's not on all the time.
But yeah, anyone that's not blocked by
non legs, you can't trust them.
Yeah. See, he's a brother. He doesn't
take my side and he doesn't take Nex's
side. And he isn't straight to Nex's
rescue, is he? Like Joseph Ferrar.
Yeah. [ __ ] Joseph Ferrar.
So, did I bring a lot of this YouTube
[ __ ] on myself, Grezy?
Cuz if people people repeat saying, "Oh,
you met your mother and that." But if I
never come out with these things, no one
would know, wouldn't they? If I just
done a channel not complaining about
women and stuff, then these people
wouldn't say these things, would they? Greasy.
Like, don't let these [ __ ] women win
and that. Yeah. [clears throat]
I'm the root cause for [ __ ] Monty
losing everything. Greasy.
Monty and Timmy Eldridge would have
never met if it wasn't for me. Think
of that green.
Think of it
where we have never met.
There'd be no rice. It would be them and
Kaye. If it wasn't for me, he would
still be with Kaye.
How mad is that with the kids?
There'd be no nut. There'd be no rice.
I do feel bad, but like he could have
got off it, but he just wouldn't get off
it. Trip H.
And then he got very greasy. He got
nicked over YouTube.
He's got his he got his devices seized.
And what do you think he done the next
day, Grezy? He didn't think to himself,
"Oh, let me start a new leaf in the book.
Um, let me have a fresh start, live my
life, try and get my kids back. Nope.
Wait, went straight to Argos, bought
another phone, and went back on YouTube. Huh? Well, yeah. Mad. Absolutely mad.
Them [ __ ] were laughing at us. Yeah.
So, have you have you got a little
northern accent then? Groovsy, have you
got a northern accent?
Have we got a little over that? Bless you.
Yeah, I like that video. You done?
So, what time do you reckon they would
have went to the bookings today, Grezy?
About 9 8:39.
But I was thinking the whole time me
waiting there. I'm thinking they're
waiting there as well.
I'm waiting for the bookies, right?
But then I'm thinking they're [ __ ]
also waiting and and time is not on our side here.
Time is not on our [ __ ] side.
Yeah, but it's not because of the money.
I didn't need the money. I didn't need
£110. I [ __ ] I got money. It's just I
didn't want these [ __ ] to win.
I didn't want these [ __ ] to have a
laugh at me, Grezy.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, he called it. I pour myself
another glass of Coke. He called it, but
it wasn't because of the money, obviously.
So, it was either I do that um Greasy or
they have the last laugh. And these
trolls didn't win. These trolls didn't
These trolls didn't win at all.
Because I'm the one that put the barcode
out there by accident.
So what is actually my fault? I I
actually caused all of it.
I actually caused all of it.
Think about it. These people only have
what you give them. Grievy,
watch your videos. Oh, you actually
talk. You've actually got a voice. One second. Which one?
Oh, I didn't know you had a voice.
What the what? What? The live stream.
I can probably guess your accent as well
cuz I'm very good.
Which what? What about the live stream?
You're not talking in that one, are you?
Are you talking on the live one from six years ago?
You got one live stream and it was
Well, let me listen to this. One second.
of an accent.
Yes, but I stayed up all night. Why did
I stay up all night? Because I put the
barcode up there. So, it was my fault.
If I didn't put a barcode up there, that
wouldn't have happened, would it? So,
therefore, I done it to myself.
So, they didn't win
because I done it myself. It wasn't
trolls. I done it myself. If I didn't
put the barcode up there, that would have happened.
So, that's that's that, mate. Who's the
one that put the barcode up there? I did.
Not them. So
I It was my fault. Really?
What? You You got a foreign accent,
Greasy. Are you a foreigner?
Ladies and gentlemen, let me have a look.
Yes. And why did I do that? And why did
it happen? Because I put the barcode up.
Yes. And how And why did it happen?
Because I put the barcode up there. So
it was my fault.
Not any of these people. I don't know
how many times I used to have to say to
Joseph for all, they're not [ __ ] with
my head, Greezy. You remember when he
used to say, "Oh yeah, they do this
stuff to try to psychologically [ __ ]
with people's head." I'm like, "They
don't [ __ ] [ __ ] with my head, mate.
I've been on here for [ __ ] years.
They don't [ __ ] [ __ ] with my head, mate.
I bet you love that, is it, Greasy?"
Yeah, they [ __ ] with their own heads. Yeah. But yeah,
they're not even trolls. They're spastics.
These people are not trolls. They're
spastics on here. Greasy.
They're not trolls. They're spastics. Little low.
They're not even trolls. They're little
mongos. Little weasels.
There's a lot of weasels on this
community, ain't it, Gez?
Did you like it, Grezy?
Did you like it, Grezy? When I was describing
USA Izzy's boobies, did you like it?
Did it make you have a boner?
>> It made you have a boner, didn't it?
Yeah, it did.
You got excited.
I know. What did that tell you? That
what does that tell you? Triple H,
they've done nothing
cuz I'm still here.
I'm still here. It's like what Monty man
says. He's still here in it. Easy.
Even though he says I'm still here.
Madness, isn't it? Yeah.
I I miss Runescape, Greaves. I really
miss Runescape, bro. I really miss 2010
Runescape. 2011 Runescape.
I can't tell you how much I miss that
game. You and I've never really met
anyone in person that's um
that's um actually played it
or know what it's like. Greasy.
They know of the game, but they've not
played it. Oh, bro. That game was
banging back. Oh,
that game, bro. Before they ruined it.
I used to love it doing the quests and everything. music. Best game.
Yeah, I miss it, mate. I miss it.
Like the void, the hand cannon,
everything. But I used to sit I used to
stay up, bro. 24 hours, no problem. And
just play it. Sit there making
milkshakes, playing it on the on the PC
all night long, mate. All night long.
Back back back in the MSN days. That my
friend from Amsterdam, I actually met
him through Runescape. We actually met
in real life. But
that it was a game that you couldn't
even explain it. Like unless you've
played it, you can't actually explain it
to someone. It's not possible to explain it.
You actually have to play it for
yourself. Otherwise, you you can't you
can't explain it.
You think they had dentists in the 70s? Rezy.
So yeah, I like the dentists.
Yeah, I like dentist. Imagine
back in the day, bro, when there was no dentist.
People just used to die in it. Like back
in the caveman days. Man eats
coke and drops dead during traffic stop.
What the [ __ ] [snorts] Oh, Grezy.
Remember, Greavves, I really want you,
but I don't think you want me.
What would have I done? Um,
I would have been pissed off. So when
she was sucking my dick. Yeah, it was
probably smelly, wasn't it, Grezy? My Willie.
I can't believe she gave me a drunk [ __ ]
in the alleyway.
I got a [ __ ] in the alleyway UK asylum.
It was about a year and a half ago.
Some American gave me a [ __ ] in the
alleyway. Felt lovely.
Yeah, we were we were in the O'Neals.
Yeah. She was drunk and she says, "I
really want you, but I don't think you want me."
I said, "I do. I do, but we're everyone's looking."
So then I went around the corner and I
started playing with her vagina
and then I took my pants down
and then she gave me a [ __ ] Yeah,
it's bloody hard to get women nowadays.
UK asylum. No one's bloody interested.
Do you remember that I've got a
boyfriend? Excuse UK asylum.
That used to get annoying, didn't it?
I have a boyfriend.
God, that used to get annoying, bro.
When you kept hearing it over and over
and over again. [ __ ] hell.
It's so boring, isn't it, bro? So boring.
I know. That's boring, isn't it, bro? Bors me. Oh
yeah. UK asylum.
Where are you from? Oh, lovely.
Lovely to approach.
So wait, you've actually got a kid.
Triple H. You never mentioned a kid. Why
do you never mention it? You You said
you got a kid. No.
Look at Greasy. Lovely.
I'm not really a biscuit person to be
fair. I tell you what ones I did like.
You know the bulbin biscuits. Greasy.
The bulbin ones.
Oh, North London. Yeah.
Yeah. So what? You never see your You
never see your kid. What the [ __ ] You
never mention it. Why? So don't you see the kid? [clears throat] Bless you.
Yeah. Bless you then if you got a kid. Triple H.
Oh, bless you then. That's cute. Triple H.
Bless you if you've got a kid.
Because you couldn't control your little sexual urges.
That's why Triple H has got a kid, Greavvesy,
cuz he couldn't control his sexual urges
and he got someone pregnant.
Is [laughter] that
is that righteous approach lovely
lovely Greavesy lovely bless you
absolutely bless you.
That's good on you though Triple H. You
get some more money from the government now.
Yeah, that's [ __ ] Triple H.
I think you'd be a good dad, Greavvesy.
I reckon Greavesy would be a good dad.
Uzi would be a good dad as well.
Would you want to be a dad? Never.
I can't even get a [ __ ] date,
let alone have a child.
And that right grooves there. [snorts]
How's your biscuits, lad?
You're calling me immature.
What about women? They're [ __ ]
immature. You know what? Yeah. Greavves,
do you know what, Greavves? I used to
think I was really immature, you know.
Well, I am immature, but then I then I
started meeting women and then you
actually realize that they're more
immature than you.
And that's saying something cuz I'm
really immature, bro. But they're more
immature than me.
Do you not find that [ __ ] up, Greasy?
Yeah, they're way more [ __ ] immature
than me, bro.
Yeah, they're way more immature.
They actually make me feel mature.
These women are very hypocritical. Graves,
I'm on this woman's Instagram. She just
looks like a [ __ ] [ __ ] bro.
She looks like an absolute [ __ ]
Like I know that might sound mad to you, but yeah.
Proper proper [ __ ] Nah. Yeah. Yep. >> [snorts]
>> They're [ __ ] proper [ __ ] These women, lad. Oh gosh.
These women go on that they don't have
sex and stuff and then then they get pregnant.
Grey, they're very hypocritical, aren't they?
I need to cut down on the sugar and and
the coke to be fair, bro.
Cuz he's a nons lover. He's a non-leg
Yeah, he's a lover of nonslegs.
I'm not friends with people that are uh
lovers of nonslegs.
Every time I say something about him, he
defends them. But then when he's saying
[ __ ] about me, I never see him defending
me. Go and [ __ ] off, you bias nons lover. You either
don't stick up for both. Either
or you stick up for both. Isn't that
right, Grezy? You either stick up for
both of us
or you don't stick up for either of us.
So yeah, that's the way I see it, lad.
Gravesy doesn't ever stick up for him or me,
which is good. We want someone that's unbiased. Well,
because it's weird, lad.
Oh, do you remember Uncle Bad Touch?
Greasy. Do you miss Uncle Bad Touch? Do Yep.
Yeah, these women are [ __ ] bro.
on Instagram and >> [snorts]
>> Quezy, do you like Pregnancy?
I don't find it a laugh. No, I don't
find it a laugh what these people do on
here. Like V and fantasy stories. I
don't think it's a laugh.
If I had my chance, bro, I'd [ __ ]
really hurt one of these people, bro.
No, no, no. I don't think it's a laugh.
But it's not just YouTube, though, is
it? Because what these people do is not just YouTube.
The stuff they do is not just YouTube, is it?
Cuz they do a lot of stuff that's just
not YouTube. Isn't that right, Grezy?
I mean, they contact people's family.
They try to get people's money stopped.
They try to get people killed.
So, it's not just YouTube, mate. It
ain't just YouTube.
I hate that voice of reason. I hate that
fantasy stories. It's not just YouTube,
bro. Trust me. Well, they
look what look at what the [ __ ] they do
on here, bro. It's not It's not YouTube.
It's not just YouTube, bro. Look at the
[ __ ] that they do on here. So Yeah. Heat. Never, bro.
What you think? So, you think if you
change the subject, what do what do you
think would stop?
What do you think would stop?
Oh, it doesn't get to me.
It doesn't get to me, bro. They're just repeating bastards.
They're just all self-p projecting
repeating bastards, bro. It doesn't get to me. No.
No. That's just them talking about
themselves, is it?
No, I'm just saying I'm on these women's
profile on Instagram. They look like absolute [ __ ]
Do you even know what I mean by they
look like [ __ ] Proper [ __ ]
Bro, these people are not trolls. They're spastics.
You actually know what the definition of trolling is.
These people are not trolls. They're
self-projecting fat spastics with no
lives. They're not trolls.
Look at this, bro.
They look like proper [ __ ]
You really do what? Wonder what men
these these people are going for
when you're looking on this Instagram.
>> [sighs and gasps]
>> You wouldn't be able to have a baby,
Greasy. The baby would keep you up at night. Yeah. Greasy,
you would have gone mad if a [ __ ]
baby was keeping you up all night, wouldn't you?
Taking the baby away from his mama.
No. [ __ ] having a baby, bro.
What would you name the baby? Yeah.
Yeah. But every time we change a
subject, an account comes in and brings
it up again. Grievy,
it brings it up again. They will bring
up the like we'll be talking about
something. Yeah. Like gaming or I don't [ __ ] know.
And then somebody will come in randomly
and say and say [ __ ]
and say um
and say don't let these [ __ ] women win
and then they bring it all up again.
Isn't it? You've seen it Greavves yourself.
Uh, Ethan, that's a horrible name, bro.
I hate that name, Ethan.
I only know two people that called it,
but yeah, Ethan, that's a horrible name.
You'd really call your Bubba Ethan, you know.
No, that's a horrible name, bro. Come on. [ __ ] Ethan.
This woman said if she had a baby with
me, she'd call it baby Alex.
Baby Alex. Squeeedy. What do you think
of that? Baby Alex. I don't think that's
a bad name.
What do you think? Maybe Alex.
Yeah, I don't mind. Baby Alex.
Greavvesy. Maybe Alex.
If I ever got married, Greavvesy would
be my best would be my best man.
Yeah, Greavves would be my best man. My wedding.
Mate, you need to get laid, bro.
The first thing you need to do is being
able to get a [ __ ] conversation out
of all women, let alone [ __ ] get
laid. You can't even get a conversation
out of the [ __ ]
let alone a date, let alone get laid. [ __ ]
one one step at a time, bro.
Jesus Christ. Try getting a conversation first. >> [snorts]
>> Oh, really? Is it?
That's nice, bro. Cool story, bro. Cool story.
You remember that one? Cool story. Greasy.
[snorts] Cool story, bro. You want me to
tell it again?
See what I did there, Trip? See what I
done there, Greavves? I ended it. This
is the part of it being healthy. Now,
what would be the unhealthy thing to do, Greavvesy? Yeah,
[snorts] I'm not here to try to change
people's minds, bro. I don't care
anymore. People dismiss your struggles,
so I don't give a [ __ ] what people think.
That's the new me now, Grezy. No more
arguing. No more trying to convince people. Nothing.
Waste of everyone's time in it. Yep.
Yeah. He said he had sex the other day.
Greasy Timmy. Do you believe that?
He says that Monty man's a virgin.
He said Monty man's a virgin. Huh? Wow. Yep.
I'm not sure what to say about that.
He said that Monty's a virgin. Monty man,
but he doesn't think N legs is
strange, isn't it?
So, you think somebody that's got two
kids is a virgin,
but yet somebody with a disabled
girlfriend possibly can't be [snorts]
seems a bit weird, doesn't it, Grezy?
Seems a bit weird. I think these people
just love nons on here
to be honest. I think they're nons lovers
just like that Joseph Ferrano. Yeah,
you for real. Okay. Oh. Which one? Which guy?
What did he sound like?
It might have been that Kieran.
What's your favorite video of mine?
Yeah, good one. Triple H. You're not
going to bait me, lad. You're not going
to bait me.
You can dismiss people's struggles all
you like. You're not going to bait me, lad.
See, I'm learning new things now. Triple H and Grezy,
I think it's all a laugh, which is a
massive reason he doesn't get women.
Yeah, that that trying to bait me is not
going to work, lad.
And this goes with the whole dismissing
people's struggles, Greavesy. Do you
remember what I said about people
dismissing people's struggles?
That's what I mean by dismissing
people's struggles. So if people dismiss
my struggles, I'll be like, "Okay,
that's good for you." So yeah,
even though there's videos out there,
there's messages out there,
it's like one ear, it goes in one ear
and out the other with these people in it, Greasy.
I won't be the only podcast I will start
again is uh
is um basically asking white knights why
they white knight.
Nothing to do with me and my experiences
cuz there's no point in that cuz people
[clears throat] just dismiss your
struggles. So pointless. It's a waste of
it's a waste of everyone's time. But I
want to ask these white knights why
they're white knight. I think that would
be a good podcast.
I'll be a good subject. Yeah,
the incel version. You need to stop that
incel word. That's very very uh
you need to stop that incel word, bro.
It's really boring now.
You need to stop that incel word. It's
really really boring.
That's really, really boring now, bro.
Really, really boring. You need to come
out with some better words, better
insults. It's boring. It's like calling
a woman a [ __ ] It has no substance,
no meaning, nothing.
You know, the thing is, Greasy, you
know, incels, right? Have you ever
watched incel documentaries?
These people think you're an insult if
you don't lick women's asses.
That's their definition of an incel. If
you don't lick women's asses and think
they're away, they call you an incel
within like 5 minutes. But that's not
what an incel is. But they call people
incels that don't lick women's asses.
So that's that's simple as that really.
A lot of people do that now. If you
don't lick women's asses, you're an incel.
Even though you've got life experiences,
more life experience than any incel
could ever have, they will still call
you an incel. I'm like, "Okay, bitch."
You know, that's that's that's that's
what you you say.
Mad. It's mad. Really really mad.
I'll tell you what though, I'm not an
incel, but I'd rather be a [ __ ] incel
than be a [ __ ] white knight any day
of the [ __ ] week.
If I had to choose between one of them,
I'd be like, "Yeah, I'd be I'd choose to
be in I I would be an incel rather than
a [ __ ] white knight."
You know, when
women moan about men, what do they call
them? They try to say they call them fem cells, but
I don't think that they do. No.
Women that hate men get pied.
Women Men that talk the truth about
women get called an incel.
That's just life though, is it Grievy?
That's just life, laddyy. It's the way it is. Yeah,
we're not going around in circles. What
I meant by dismissing struggles is he
said he doesn't listen. He thinks it's
all laugh, which is why I don't get women.
That's what Triple H said, but I put
videos out there.
Yeah, but when they call people an incel
grezy, it basically means you not
sucking up to women. Uh you not actually
being an incel. So, okay, so for
example, right, say I go on
somewhere and say, "Oh, women are stuck
up. They've got attitude problems based
on my experiences." They will call me an
incel. Even though I've got life experiences
and what I'm saying is the truth,
they'll still call me an incel.
But yet when obviously a woman wants to
moan and wse about men that they choose,
they get pied. So
it's a gender thing at the end of the
day. It's it is a gender thing. So
it it you know what I'm saying? You know
it, I know it. What's what's left to say?
Women can hate men. No problem.
Men can men talk the truth about women.
I've got experiences to have got
evidence to back up their [ __ ] They get
called an incel. So
I wish that word had never been invented
though, Grezy, cuz it's not fair, is it?
Is there no equality nowadays? It that
that word should have never been invented
cuz if they're not going to invent one
for a woman, there shouldn't be one for
men, should they, Grezy?
Why is it that women are allowed to, you know,
go for men that treat them badly and
moan and get pied, but when we want to
voice our experiences, we get called an
incel. That's not fair.
Bit sexist, isn't it?
Yeah. They call you an incel. Yeah. Like if you
if you argue with someone within 5
minutes they're like, "Oh, you're an
incel straight away." Like that's what
they call you.
It's mad. Mad unhealthy. I'm so glad I
don't get into any of them arguments
anymore, bro. I'm so glad. I'll never
get into any of them arguments ever again.
I don't think I'll ever ask for advice
again. I don't think I'll ever moan
about it ever again to anyone. pointless.
They'll dismiss your struggles,
potentially call you an incel. Yeah.
Where did it no more? It's madness. Madness. Oh, well.
Oh well, Greavvesy,
I don't care about women anymore. Anyways, Greavvesy,
I did back like 3 years ago, two and a
half, three years ago when I was really
horny and stuff,
but nowadays I don't give a I don't really care.
I'm booking a holiday soon. Definitely
for for next summer. Maybe April. I'm
going to go April or June. I'm going to
go somewhere April or June.
I don't know where yet. I haven't decided.
No, I don't. I talk about the double standards.
Yeah, cuz the double standard is [ __ ] bad.
And the way the world is is bad. Yeah,
it's [ __ ] It's [ __ ] up.
Really [ __ ] up.
Is that right, Grezy? you know.
No, I wouldn't.
No, I only done that with a 19year-old
is because she didn't have big enough boobies. Greasy.
And it will receive the nutrients and stuff. No. Nah, bro.
I don't think so.
What do you mean up north? That's a
player, bro. That's a player universal.
That That That's a player Universal.
What do you mean up north that's a
player? It's considered a player [ __ ]
everywhere, you absolute idiot.
What the [ __ ]
So you don't see Grezy how this whole
conversation you're dismissing people's struggles.
So hold on a minute. Right. You're
saying that it's not about dismissing people's struggles.
That's what you're saying. Really, bro?
You really don't think this is
dismissing people's struggles?
Okay, I'll explain to you how it is. So,
you and Triple H is saying one thing, right?
But you're ignoring the fact that I've
put like a million videos out there
of what they've done. That's the point.
I'm saying that you're dism you're
dismissing struggles. That's what I mean
by that. It's cuz you're saying you're
saying one thing,
but you're ignoring all of the videos
that I put out there. This is what I'm
saying, bro. So, it is it is dismissing struggles
cuz the first thing that comes to my
mind is the videos when you're saying
this stuff, bro. Yeah. The first thing
that comes to my mind is the videos.
And you constantly you are dismissing them
which is why the le this is why deleted
them anyways lad cuz you just dismiss them.
Yeah, pretty much. But no, but you are
kind of dismissing people's struggles though
cuz you're saying about how I'm not
mature and but we've all seen videos
of messages and approaches. So, how are
you not dismissing people's struggles?
Triple H is dismissing my struggles.
100% he's dismissing my struggles, lad.
See, look. Right. Okay. I'll give you an
example of Triple H Greavesy. Yeah. He's
talking about me being immature, right?
And that's why I can't get a woman. Now,
how many approaching videos have I put
up there where women have had bad
attitudes and haven't given me the
chance and have led me on? You see the contradictory?
Do you understand that? Do Do you see the contradictory?
you do not understand from what he's
saying and what videos have been put up.
That's what I'm trying to say to you.
So, it is Yeah, it is. It is dismissing struggles.
Yeah. Sorry to say. I know you don't
like to be the one that's dismissing the
struggles, but you you you are
dismissing people's struggles,
bro. It's not just Lex that does that, lad.
The thing is it's not, you know, you do
realize Lex dismisses people's
struggles. He's not the only one though.
There's loads of people like him that
dismiss people's struggles. Most Yeah.
See, look right. Be more humble, less
ignorant. Get again. Another person
dismissed my struggles. What about the
approaching videos? What about the messages?
So, you are dismissing people's struggles.
This is exactly why I don't get into it
anymore. I don't put any videos up
there. Don't try to change people's mind
because you're just going to dismiss it anyways.
Like Bob, he's dismissing my struggles.
Triple H is dismissing my struggles
because I've put videos out there, approaching videos,
multiple multiple approaching videos.
Yeah, but I've put approaching videos
out there, Grezy.
I mean, I'm pretty sure there was more
than one where they didn't even let me
finish my sentence without saying that
they weren't interested.
Doesn't that kind of contradict
everything that you're saying?
Maybe a little bit.
Does it maybe like
not just you, like a lot of people as
well. Does that not maybe contradict
everything that you're saying?
It contradicts it massively. So when
you're sat here like writing all of this
stuff, this is the only thing I can think of.
So yeah, you're it you're basically you are
Yeah, basically you are kind of
it's hard. I can't I don't know the word
for it. But you're definitely dismissing struggles
cuz if he wasn't, you wouldn't be
writing all of this stuff.
Did you just listen to anything that I
just said, Bob? Or you No, just
dismissing struggles. It's like when it
comes to women, these people don't have an ear.
No, no, no, no. But with these people,
it seems that they don't have an ear.
Their ears not working.
That's what it seems.
Yeah, but the thing is No, no, no, no,
no. But the thing is, Greavvesy,
is I've put approaches and messages out there.
So there's nothing anyone can say.
That's what I'm talking. You might think
I'm being awkward, right? And I I I
think I'm right. And it's not it's not
about that. But you got to understand,
bro, that I'm in the 5% minority
with people that's met women, gone out
approaching and stuff. And I've shared a
lot of that stuff.
So then what is there left to say?
The way I see it is it's not for her to
say anything. It's not for me to say
anything. It's not for anyone else to
say anything. It's for these women to
prove that they're different and they can't.
And they've made it categorically clear
that they can't. So that's the end of
it. That's the way I And it's not for
me, you or her to say. It's for them to
prove you wrong. and they can't.
They just prove that they're all the
[ __ ] same. So that's why I moved on
from it in the end, you know?
You're speaking to someone in the 5%
minority, bro. Maybe 10% minority,
you know? And even when that guy called
me weak-minded, that was a trigger cuz I
knew that I'm like in the 10% minority,
5 10% with people that's actually gone
out and approached women and stuff. So, so
you're saying something and you're giving advice
whilst dismissing all of the videos I
put up. You're not seeing what's wrong with that.
But no, if you think No, but listen. Did
you not listen to what that Sarah was saying?
She was she was making excuses for them
as well, bro. She was like, "Oh, well,
how do they lead you on? How do they
lead you on?" And I said, "They led me
on this way, that way, this way, that
way." You know, she she was still making
excuses for them.
She was still making excuses for this one
from uh two weeks ago. You don't listen
to it, bro. She was She was saying, "How
dare they lead you on?" and they know
damn well that they've led you on, but
they won't admit it because they're a
woman. Like, just as an example, didn't
you hear what it didn't you hear what
she was saying, bro?
And that [snorts] goes back to what
you're saying about them thinking that they're angels, you know?
I don't really think it's up for me or
anyone to say anything. It's up for
these women to prove you to to prove
they're good, but they can't.
Yeah, but she was still making excuses
though. She was still making excuses.
She was saying, "Well, how they lead you
on?" And like when it's Bro, I know when
someone's leading me the [ __ ] on. No,
this shouldn't be going round and round
in circles. It's if someone's led you
on, they've led you on. End of. And she
was trying to make it seem like we cared
when we didn't. We was just stating the
fact that they led us on, whatever. But
where they kept denying it,
it made us seem like we cared by telling
them that they did. If that makes sense.
Yeah, maybe. But she was still she was
still denying that they they let me on.
And that change their mind excuse is
another excuse they like to um use. Um
yeah, that's another one. They change their mind. People
don't change their mind that quickly,
mate. But yeah, we know it's [ __ ]
anyways. Yeah, that's that's that it. And yeah,
they used to make excuses for USA Griezy
when she used to do when when she done
what she done, they made excuses for her as well.
Yeah, they made excuses for her as well.
I can't remember the exact ones, but they did. Yeah,
but sometimes you get people that don't
do it though. Um, greasy.
Sometimes you do.
Sometimes you'll meet someone and
they'll be like completely unbiased, but
very rare though.
With what one?
Well, she was though. Wasn't How long
did that conversation go around in
circles with me and say about this
person leading me on? He was asking,
"How do you know they were leaving you
on?" And I be like, "Oh, well, they
were." And it's like, "Oh, they were
just being nice." And I'm thinking,
"Come on now. You don't even believe
this [ __ ] [ __ ] saying."
She was I can't remember the whole
conversation, but I know she was
definitely definitely Yeah.
Like we know they can't they have it in
their head where a woman possibly can't
lead someone on. They they they won't have it.
It's just ridiculous, lad. Yeah.
You don't see it from my point of view
though, do you Greasy?
How How would you feel if you've gave women
chance after chance and chance? If
you've gave them benefit and doubt
chance and chance and ch time and time
and time and time again, then you're not
going to care what anyone says, are you?
If you've given women the benefit of the
doubt time and time and time and time
and time and time again, doesn't really
matter what anyone else says.
Think about it, bro. I used to do mad stuff.
Mad stuff. Mad mad mad stuff, bro.
You remember when it used to piss me off
when people used to say, "Keep trying,
keep trying." I went to Manchester the
same day before, bro, cuz I kept hearing
it and it was it was annoying me. I'm
pretty sure you all remember that video
of me in the car and that. So,
if you've given people the benefit of
the doubt for years, then you're not
really you are going to be ignorant.
You are not going to care what anyone
says cuz why should you? What they say
don't matter. You've given people the
benefit of the doubt.
time and time and time again to prove
they're wrong, to prove that they're
different and they can't.
So, [ __ ] everyone else. Simple.
You're watching Little Britain.
What other Little Britons do I like? I
like the describing one.
Oh, I like the I like the describing one.
That one's funny, Grezy. describing one
when they when when they're nicer and
they start insulting them. Oh, that
one's good. Yeah.
Yeah, that one's good. I like the insulting one. Uh,
which other one? Remember,
look into my eyes. My eyes. My eyes.
Don't push your luck, mate. Remember that one? Yeah, August One second. Whoa.
Really? How much did they pay you? Oh no.
Oh no. How much did I pay you? Of course.
Oh, is it your little universal credit?
your your little universal credentials. Oh no.
Those are universal credentials.
October is the best month ever.
What time is the best one? Oh gosh, mama. Oh, [ __ ] Hey. Oh gosh.
Autumn can be Peter Belly's mama in the
winter. For the winter, isn't it?
No, I don't have a mama.
Oh gosh. Triple H. Oh gosh. Nah.
Autumn's not Peter Belly's mama. Triple H.
When are you out drinking again, Bob. Yeah, I'm tired.
Oh god. See you.