Who the [ __ ] is that, bro?
Off, bro. Go away. You're not getting my
attention. You shitty sausage. I'm just
These digestive these digestive biscuits are lovely. M. [ __ ]
[ __ ] account. [ __ ] UK biggest nonser.
[ __ ] off weirdo. Fat ugly people. They
got life. They going to get my
attention. [ __ ] off. Weird confines.
M. These biscuits are nice.
They are quite nice to be fair. [clears throat]
Yeah, you can tell this guy just hates
himself. He's not even going to get a reaction.
I don't know why uh
why it doesn't let me um
But I can answer your question. That's a
good question that you wrote there. Now
I'm on your channel. The community is
[ __ ] dead. Who killed it?
Who killed the community, bro? Really?
I can answer that.
I can answer that include the community.
If you want me to answer it whilst I'm
on your channel, I'll be nice and answer you.
You repeating bastards. That's what's
killed the community is you repeating bastards.
People have left. You know how many
people have left this community, bro?
It's the same repetitive regurgitated [ __ ]
That's why it's dead.
There we go.
You're nothing but a little cupc.
is [ __ ] catchy. [snorts]
You copy that statement. So [ __ ] so
funny, bro. It's so funny
cuz I just
The thing is,
just listen to me, please. Like, you
know, when you're younger, Yeah.
You may have dreams what you want to do
when you're older. you know what job you
want to do or you know even goals that
you have to you know you want to do when
you're older but you say to yourself
where would the passion and
the the the dream come to want to copy
someone else to want to be a cop
I've never known
someone coughing so bad
they don't want to feel left out
get a hobby Head up. Copy.
For anyone who's watching this, don't
reply to that UK nonstop.
Let the sad old baths and low life get bored.
I was so nice. I even answered your
question. You are the ones that killed
the community, bro. [clears throat] cuz they're repeating.
They're repeating the same bollocks.
People get bored of it.
Same self-relecting comment every day on YouTube.
Is it wonder why the community died, you know? You know, [laughter]
it's lovely coke.
No, come in here.
Think everyone's in their little nesticles.
You need some biscuits.
I like shortbread biscuits, but they
make your mouth really dry.
Mr. Live Sims on the virgin channel. You
unblocked your little virgin.
You talk about your little mate Christian.
>> [clears throat]
>> Christian Stency on it.
Two absolute virgins.
Two absolute virgins, mate. Two absolute
burger eating virgins. Yep.
Fifi has been a lot. >> Yeah.
Hey, hey, you watch my video. UK Asylum.
I just on a three minute video. It
proves all along he was a copycat with
no mind of his own.
I'm having some uh digestive biscuits.
He's a copycat.
I unblocked him so he can comment on the
channel. He's he's copying. They all
copy each other.
UK Asylum. Honestly, she's not even attractive.
She's got no ass. She's got no tits. No
ass and no tits. And I'm supposed to
find that attractive. Otherwise, I like
dick. Really, bro? Really?
I'm having a I'm having some coke with it.
I like shortbread biscuits, too.
She's not even attractive. Why do they
keep copying each other?
Why do they copy UK asylum? Why do where
does it come from when you're young,
when you're a child, right? To want to
copy other people. Where does that
desire and passion come from?
So you have to cop you have to copy other people.
He has the coffee.
Well, he probably all he wanted to do
was bloody well fear him. It's scary
being new in college,
especially when you're being bullied. I
don't find a [ __ ] attractive. UK asylum.
Well, I'm not inseure about my my sexuality.
I'm not insecure about bisexuality, lad.
Nothing special about the [ __ ] at all. That conf
UK biggest sponsor. Yeah. Oh, have you
seen that account? UK biggest sponsor UK asylum.
He asked a question saying, "Why the
[ __ ] is the community so dead? Who
killed it?" Uh, you people killed it with repeating
with the repeating and the self
projecting. You killed it, bro. You are
the ones that killed it with the self
[ __ ] projecting [ __ ] [ __ ] every day
talking about yourselves, bro.
Cuz it's all repeated. There's nothing
new on the UK side. It's all repeated.
That's why it's dead now.
It's the same people every day.
Same people every [ __ ] day, bro. Yeah, man.
Nothing lasts forever. H. You like when
I say that, don't you?
I can't I'm not looking forward to next
Saturday when I have to speak to women
again UK asylum sucks it.
Here we go again with the mind games and
the leading on
Peter Belly's little sigh
people. I'm not happy with Reddit, you know.
I'm not happy with Reddit cuz Reddit
lied to me. Reddit said that I was going
to meet someone.
UK asylum. Reddit said that I was going
They told me I would have met someone on Reddit.
I can't believe the moderators don't
even get paid, bro. They don't even get paid.
Yeah, they're definitely It's definitely
a power trip for them.
Yeah, definitely. I I can't believe they
don't even get paid. Yeah, they're
definitely bully victims.
Very unlikely. Very, very unlikely.
Five years of approaching
thousands of women,
the odds are stacked against me. Very, very unlikely.
I mean, I might do, but I probably got
more chance of winning the lottery.
Yeah, but you probably got more chance
of winning the lottery than meeting someone.
You You got more chance of winning the lottery.
I've been to Newcastle. I've been
everywhere, bro. You must be new to my
channel. I've been everywhere.
I've been everywhere, bro.
I don't try. I don't try. I'm going out
next week because me and my sisters been
planning this for about 6 months.
Otherwise, I wouldn't be going out. I
haven't been out for weeks.
I haven't been out for weeks, bro. I'm
only going because we planned it. And
yeah, like I'm not even going out by
myself as I usually do.
There generally generally is no hope.
There's generally generally generally no
not hope in hell.
Yeah. Otherwise, I wouldn't be going out.
If it wasn't for me going out with my
sister, if I had already gone out with
my sister when I was supposed to on my
birthday, bro, I wouldn't be going out.
There is literally no hope. And I'm
tired of it. I'm tired of the [ __ ]
I'm tired of the attitude and I'm tired
of the mind games. Just like anyone
that's got respect for themsel would.
There is generally no hope. There is
It's either you join the pool industry
and you use escorts for the rest of your
life. They're the only two options you
got. If you want to have sex or
whatever, those are the only two options
that you got. Now, you're never going to
meet any woman that's different.
You've tried for years and years and
years and years. They're all the same. So,
I'm surprised you of all people would
think there's hope. You must be new
here, bro. There is generally no hope.
To be honest, I won't even go out New Year's Eve.
I'm only interested in chilling out and
saving money. I'm not interested in
going out or
nothing because there is generally no hope here
because you have I haven't had a date since April.
So you you you think that the next time
you go out
all of a sudden it's going to be different really bro.
What's the chances? What what is
honestly the chances that the next time
you go out it's all going to be
different and hunky dory?
Very very very very very unlikely.
So even though
it's been going on for years and years
and years and years and years and years
and years, but that's like lottery odds
then. That's the same as doing the
lottery. Then if that's the way you
think, you might as well do the lottery.
If I genuinely thought there was hope, I
would do the lottery. I don't do the
I've never done the lottery. Never have. Never will.
Yeah. Yeah. That's what I'm saying. It's
about one in a million odds. Well, I
mean, yeah, you might meet someone, but
again, it's like one in a million. You
probably got more chance of winning uh
20 both teams to score no draw
than meeting someone.
Maybe 10. I think I think you got more
chance of winning a 10. Both teams to
score no draw.
Well, it seems impossible to me. Again,
I'll reiterate. I've not had a date since April.
I don't know, man. I haven't had a date
since April. And I've met loads and
loads and loads of women.
Trust me, I've I've spent hours
approaching women on the street. I don't
know, bro. It seems it seems close to
impossible to me. But
see, if you was actually doing this, you
would know that there's no hope. It's
only because you're watching me and you
you're not experiencing it. If you was
experiencing it, you would know that
there's no hope. You know that there's
There there is no decent birds so it
would never happen.
There is no decent women out there so it
So it's a hypothetical question because
it would never happen because there are
no decent women out there.
So that's yeah we do have all our own
experiences and and again I am in the
minority. I'm in the 5% with people
that's traveled and met women.
You heard that London. You heard that
London hustle guy. This is my first time in Scotland.
Tells you all you need to know it.
That's his first time in Scotland. I've
been to Scotland [ __ ] a couple of
times. You know, obviously he's been
abroad and stuff, but what you're trying
what I'm trying to say is that like I've
done a lot a lot a lot a lot of
traveling. Even if it was just around
the country. A lot a lot a lot around
the country. I don't approach. But I but
I don't approach. Okay. When was the
last time I approached? When was the
last time I went and I approached?
So that tells you the fact that my man's
That's his first time. Like Yeah. It I'm
in the minority of five five I'd say
maybe 10% people. Maybe I'm in the 10%
people. So when people are giving you advice,
they're forgetting all the things you've
tried. And when you gave people the
benefit of the doubt, dismissing
people's struggles. When was the last
time I approached?
If I didn't believe that, when was the
last time I approached?
Well, you're delusional, lad.
Well, you're very, very delusional if
you think that. Well, then why has it
not happened in 5 years then? Okay.
Okay. Okay. So, if you generally believe
that, right? If I have met more women
than probably 90% of the people in the
world, why has it not already happened? Okay.
But they said that six years ago. Here
we are six years later. So you can see
why people wouldn't believe what you're saying.
But they said this 6 years ago and I'm
in the 10% minority of people that's
gone and met women. So
why has it not changed in six years? Six
years is a long time. Why in them six
years has that has it not changed?
Because it will never change.
It's [ __ ] obvious. Anyone that's not
anyone that's not blowing smoke up your
ass will tell you that.
Doesn't matter if I'm not 30 or not.
I've tried more than probably most
people in the world. That's the thing
that separates me and other people. Keep
remembering that whenever you're trying
to give me this advice, bro. Remember
the crazy things that I've done. That
should that should tell you I'm not a normal 28-year-old
that's been off and off on and off in
dating apps, went out drinking. I'm not
a normal person. I've tried unhealthily
amount of times. So,
I mean, remember that I've tried more
than 90% of people.
Just remember that. Just just keep like
reminding yourself that I'm not like a
normal person asking for advice.
Well, you're delusional then. If you
don't believe there's no hope, you're
del Okay. Well, how is Okay. Okay. Okay.
Well, you explain to me then how there's
hope. Because the dating apps don't
work. You approach women, they give
attitude, and pretend they've got
boyfriends. And if they give you their
number, they lead you on. There is no
hope. That is the definition of there
being no hope. Make believe boyfriends,
attitude, [ __ ] Give you their
number and they lead you on. That's
literally all that would ever happen.
That them three things is what will
always happen. Nothing else would ever
You get numbers, you deal with toxic,
immature people. That's that. Well,
well, if I had hope, I would have met
somebody years ago. So, that's that's that.
>> Yeah. Well, if what you're saying is
true, then I would have met someone
years ago. I would be getting dates,
[ __ ] Bro, if there was hope,
I'd be getting dates. I'd be getting
dates like once a month. Dates, bro. And
the dates don't go anywhere, bro. You
can't even get a date. I don't think
there's hope. I I genuinely don't think
there's hope. if you can't even get a date. So,
I mean, you'd be telling the truth.
I mean, you'd be I mean, I don't really
care. I don't really mind what you say really, but
you need to you need to be real. There
is generally no hope. I mean, I haven't
had any dates since April and I have
tried a lot and I've spent a lot of money.
So, it doesn't look good, does it? you know. Okay. Well,
that's your opinion.
But it doesn't matter whatever you say
or what I say, does it? Cuz it will
never change. So,
yeah, I've had more women than them in
terms I've had sex with them. I've had
I've kissed them. I've been on more
dates. Yeah. Have I not, Grezy?
Have I not had sex? Have I not kissed
people? Have I not been on dates with
more people than these sad people in
this community? I have more than people
in this community. Yeah. But in terms of
like normally it's disgusting.
It is disgusting,
you know. So,
so but I have had more women than these people.
What have they had more? Have they had
more than 10 women in their life, bro?
When a lot of them are probably virgins.
It's It's stating the truth. It's
stating facts that you have been with
more women than these people
in years. Over the years, if you said
this year, no, but over the years, of
course, I [ __ ] have. So, yeah,
because times have changed. Wait, what
do you mean if I've had You've seen the
women that I've been with. One second.
One second. What do you mean then? If
you have had more women, brother, you
have seen me with women. You have seen
me with women. Like, you generally have
seen me with women. So, it's not if. You
have seen me with women. There's no if
about it. What the [ __ ] are you talking
about, bro? People that weren't even paid.
Yeah. And because it's harder
and and now and if to answer your
question because I feel like it's got a
lot harder. I feel like the dating's
become a lot harder now. That's why I'm
struggling. I feel like it's just become
more harder than it was 2 years ago
cuz I've already mentioned that before.
So I feel like it's got more harder now
than it was. It was always been hard,
but not like this. It's disgustingly
hard now. I mean, you can't even get a
[ __ ] date now. So
now uh well save money and leave the country.
Like I said, I'm only going out next
week cuz my sister and and [ __ ] I don't
approach. I haven't approached for ages.
You think I can't go out and approach
every day? If I want to, I can. But why
am I going to do that? Why would I want
to lose more hope? There is already no hope.
There is literally no hope to begin
with. So what am I trying to lose more
hope for? There is no hope. You know, on
Friday, I had a few drinks and I was
playing pool for a couple of hours.
Chilling. I didn't even plan to go out.
I was with someone. So nothing. I'll
just stay single on it. There's nothing
else I can do.
You feel so much better, Grezy, bro. You
feel so much better. No mind games, no [ __ ]
no leading on. You don't actually
realize how much sad you feel when you
give up. January, November,
uh it doesn't matter where it doesn't
matter what whatever month you give up
and you start saving, you realize how
much better it is when you give up.
So, no more mind games, no more make
believe boyfriends, no more attitude.
It's [ __ ] lovely. It's lovely to the
point where it don't even get boring.
And yeah, I do know who he is. Yeah. from Romania. So
like you might think I'm being awkward
UK asylum, but I'm not being awkward.
No one cares about what you say, your
little white knight. I put videos out
there. I've put everything out there. No
one cares about your little white knight comments. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye, white knight.
See, these things don't affect me
anymore, Grezy. Cuz right, so what I'm
saying, Grezy, is you know what I was
talking about dismissing struggles.
If these people didn't dismiss
struggles, they wouldn't be saying that.
They wouldn't be saying about me being
the problem. If they weren't dismissing my struggles,
they wouldn't be saying that. Ask me why.
And I can explain why. If they weren't
if they weren't dismissing my struggles,
they wouldn't be saying that. Because
think of all of what they say, right?
Think of what anyone says on here, what
anyone says on Reddit. Now, again, how
many times have you put up a video where
you've tried to speak to someone and
they've said straight away that they're
not interested. That would contradict
everything that they're saying to begin
with. They're trying to say it's this,
that, or whatever. No, there were videos
where you have gone and you have
approached people and they have gave you
attitude. End the story. That contradicts everything.
So that's that's that's that's the end
of that, you know? So it's like, and you
might think I'm being awkward and I
always think I'm right, but I don't. I
[ __ ] don't. It's just that if I've
been experiencing this for [ __ ]
years, I'd know a hell of a lot about the [ __ ]
it must contradict everything that
they're saying. And when they're leading
you on, if they weren't dismissing
struggles, they wouldn't be saying this
stuff. They would be like, "Oh, well,
you're wrong here and you're right here."
But they don't. They just dismiss
everything that then like like we said
that they do. So yeah,
it is dismissing struggles. It is. is
because if they were going for personality right,
why would they say straight away that
they're not interested?
Because what it is with these people, it
seems that they have to make these
excuses. No, it doesn't affect me. It
actually doesn't affect me. If I went
out by myself on Saturday, it wouldn't
affect me because I know what would
happen. Actually, it doesn't affect me.
It affected me like a week or two weeks
ago when people was dismissing my
struggles. But I just kind of know that
that's always they were always going to
do that. They were always going to make
excuses for women. I lost hope, Grezy. I
tell you when I lost hope. I lost hope
and when it it stopped affecting me when
I got them 10 numbers and I didn't get a
date. Then I was like, "Okay, I'm
playing this at my own risk now." Yeah.
This is this is my fault now. If I go
out and I try again, I can't complain
then because looks maxing 10 numbers not
a day. Yeah. I don't think there's much
hope when I beat my records though. Now
you're just like, "Oh yeah, just the
same old. It will never change." Like
that's that's it is it is what it is.
And now if I get if I ever got into an
argument with someone, oh just
dismissing my struggles.
Yeah. You learn these things with time.
It is bad though. It is bad that you
would have to deal with all of that
stuff just to be able to find someone.
Toxic mind games, [ __ ] negativity.
Um, just in order to find someone. I
mean, it doesn't even seem real, does it?
It's bad. It really, really is bad.
You will never meet someone that's
normal. Normal. Honest. Don't lead you on. Never.
Never. These people don't exist.
We these people don't exist, lad.
I don't hate women. I don't care. I
don't care. I I don't care. I just say
that they're they're this that they're
this that they're this that that's
facts. That's not hating that they're
toxic. Like next week I know what I'm in
for. I know exactly what I'm in for.
I know exactly what I'm in for, bro.
And I think this tells you if you got if
you don't approach sober, you got no
hope. If you're drinking anyways and you approach then
I mean uh you know anyone can do that
drunk but you really know when you lose
hope. If you don't approach anyone sober
you you don't have no hope. So I don't
approach anyone sober because I know I
know that there is no hope. But
obviously if I'm drinking then I'll just
[ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ] in it. But yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. I know. I know. I'm just I
would move on, but I know what I'm in
for next Saturday.
I know exactly what I'm in for.
I put some good money on it as well,
bro. I know exactly what I'm in for.
Make believe attitude. Dickheadness.
dickheadness and people that uh lead you
on. I mean, you've seen the screenshots, I'm sure.
Yep. Yeah, I am. Yeah.
Seen the messages, you've seen
approaches. I'm sure you've seen
So, for people to sit there and say that
you're the problem every single time,
they're dismissing your struggles. Simple.
Yeah, man. Go do it. Yeah.
If they're trying to say that you're
wrong every time, Yeah. they're
dismissing your struggles. Simple.
Like, there is videos where the women
have been rude, they've been [ __ ]
Straight away, they've said they're not interested,
but people don't seem to say anything
about these videos. So it's like they've
got some [ __ ] short vision vision or
Yeah, it's long.
It is long, bro.
Oh yeah, stop.
So what are you supposed to do? Keep
going out and dealing with their [ __ ]
over and over and over and over and over
again. That's why I don't go out
anymore. Not cuz I can't afford it. I
can afford it. I can go out whenever I
want. It's just I don't want to deal
with their [ __ ] anymore. So yeah,
it's to that point where I've basically
lost my sex drive and I can't be off.
I'd rather keep my dignity,
you know. It's different when you're a
bit younger, you know.
So it ain't going to change, bro, ever.
There's been no like leadups either.
Like there's been no like um
like it's not like you were getting
dates and kisses like you've had nothing
for a very very very long time.
Like back a year and a half two years
ago there was leadups like dates maybe
you got a kiss maybe had a there's no
like leadups now. There's nothing. So
which proves that it's that it's never
going to change. It's obvious
what stems from younger years.
I think this UK biggest nons [ __ ]
trauma. He's so desperate for attention.
Jeez, this guy is so desperate, bro. I
think it's Trad
Warrior. Um, so yeah,
I don't know where it comes from, bro,
but it's [ __ ] stinking.
It's absolutely stinking, bro.
All you come across is toxic [ __ ]
women. That's all you come across.
So how people think it's going to change?
And also like I said to you, the only
maddest thing is UK asylum. You can be
speaking to one for one day, they're
like, "Good night. Good night." And then
the next day they completely switch.
It's just toxic. That's what it is. Um
and yeah, it was good.
Yeah, it was good. Yeah.
Yeah. I need to go out anyways next week
cuz I need to get trim. So,
yeah, I need to get a trim, lad.
Yeah. Well, that's that
is a bit sad that you'll never have a
sex life again or anything. And if
somebody wanted kids, which I've never
wanted kids, then obviously they won't
be able to have kids.
Imagine I actually wanted kids. Could
you imagine? Obviously, you can't have
kids because you can't find someone. So,
I don't think it's talked about enough
on [ __ ] you know, sites like Reddit
and that. They just make up stuff.
Reddit makes up stuff proper. Yeah, proper, bro.
Dealing with women isn't, bro. Dealing
with women isn't good for you.
And you know that because when you give
up, you feel better. You have no more
mood swings, no more.
It's, bro, it's like I said, that's how
toxic it is.
That's how toxic it is.
That shows that show how toxic it is
and that they only reply to negativity.
It's bad, bro.
Hopefully, when people get to my age,
they can give up as well if they're
having the same experiences.
I don't want kids. I don't want I've
never wanted kids, but I'm using as an example.
That's the thing. It's stressful just
finding someone that's normal. You can't
even find someone that's normal.
They don't play games. They don't lead
people. And you can't even find someone that's normal.
They don't find someone to have a have a
have a kid with. So that's the thing. It's Nah. Yeah.
It's quite annoying, bro. Quite annoying.
They say women go for personality, yet a
lot of these women are stuck up and entitled. No. None whatsoever. Nah.
So, I got no new numbers now. I got no
new numbers at all. You just see how
many WhatsApp numbers I got, bro. bad.
Talk about it's depressing as [ __ ]
One from ages ago. They changed their
picture today on WhatsApp. I noticed it
popped up. Didn't reply to any of my
messages though. UK
didn't reply to any of my messages.
And then I had to deal with that
[ __ ] woman on the train as well the
other day. I was like half asleep. I
stayed up for like 24 hours. Still got a
video by the way.
She's lucky I didn't knock her [ __ ]
out, mate. She's lucky I didn't knock
her [ __ ] flying on that [ __ ] train.
Bad, bad, bad.
So many [ __ ] in this country, you
know. So many [ __ ] I noticed it
when I used to work as well. So many
[ __ ] in it. Yeah.
You know what? It feels like a country
designed to annoy you at times. Yeah.
What do you reckon is worse? Trying to
date women or playing roulette? Women definitely.
That's why I quit roulette cuz it was
toxic. That's why I quit roulette.
Women's just as bad
cuz you're constantly constantly going
around in circles.
It's a bit like roulette.
Until you break a cycle, you're [ __ ]
What happened to that 19year-old?
Yeah, she turned out to be a [ __ ] as well.
I mean, you are too old for love when
you're like 50 and you're old and
wrinkly and you can't get your dick up
and you can't get your dick up. Could
you imagine I was a virgin, bro?
Can you imagine? I was like the virgin.
Can you imagine I was a virgin like him?
[ __ ] hell, bro. Imagine
I was like that big virgin.
Yeah, but you should be getting sex now
when you're when you're younger. UK asylum.
Um, exactly how it would always be and
you know the answer to it.
What was it? What do you think, Bob? Do
do you think I finally found someone two days later?
Do you think I finally What do you
reckon? It just suddenly changed in two days.
Women started stop being stuck up. Women
stop being [ __ ] Women stop playing games.
Really? In two years, bro? In two days,
you actually think it changed
since you last come?
I mean, not sure why you think it would
be any different, but it would never be any different.
No, the only person that I know is this
19year-old, and I'm not messaging her.
I've got too much of an ego. It's like
the tenants. I don't even suggest
meeting the tenants anymore cuz I've got
too much of an ego
when it comes to stuff like that. But no,
she's 21 now. She's not 90 now. She's 21
now. But yeah.
No, I would never do that because Yeah.
People on Reddit say you're going to
meet someone UK asylum.
They're [ __ ] liars, bro.
They told me I'd be married soon. [ __ ] liars. Yep. [ __ ] it.
You can't even [ __ ] get laid if you wanted to. Really?
What gave you that impression, may I ask?
It's been the same for years. It's been
the same for 6 years. I haven't had a
date since April.
What would magically make you think that
I'll meet someone soon?
You must be delusional or have brain damage.
I will never meet anyone.
So there's no point asking the question
because it will never happen.
There's no point speaking in
hypotheticals, bro. You know,
that's like me saying that I think
you're going to meet the I think you're
going to I think you're going to win the lottery soon.
It's never going to happen, bro.
That's like me saying to someone that's
on the lottery for 20 years, I think
you're going to win the lottery soon.
It's not going to happen.
It's like saying to my mom, "Oh, you
know, this week I think you're going to
do the lottery. I think you're going to
do the lot. I think you're going to win the lottery."
But it's obviously they're not going to
win the lottery, are they?
Cuz it's been going on for years. I
think this is what you're you're you're
not missing. You're missing. It's not
one month, two month, three months.
It's been going on for [ __ ] years.
Not even a year. It's been going on for years.
Absolute years. You know, from the time
where I look different to the way I look
now. So, the chances of it changing is very slim.
Like I said, if there's a chance is a
very, very slim chance. Cuz
like I said, why haven't you already met someone?
Why haven't you already met someone?
What's the reason you can give for that?
What's the account for that? If you've
tried more than 90% of people in the world, right,
then why haven't you met someone?
So, you've approached a lot of people.
You've met a lot of people in years.
So, why why haven't you met someone
then? I mean, all women act the same.
They are all the same.
So, I can go to Wales next week and
they'd still be the same there.
I can go to Australia, they'd still be
the same there. It doesn't matter
[ __ ] where you go, they're all the same. That's that.
I guess if somebody comes my way via
social media or something that proves to
be different, maybe. But that's how bad
it is now. I won't even go out and put
energy into it cuz
there's no there's no point.
I've been giving these people the
benefit of the doubt [ __ ] years and
years and years and they all prove
they're the same. All you have to do is
look on the [ __ ] Instagram
stuck up NPCs
with Tik Tok brains cuz they all watch
the same [ __ ]
Do I trust women? Hell the [ __ ] no. Do I
No [ __ ] way do I trust them, bro.
They're liars. I've caught them out on
lies several times. Hell the [ __ ] no do
I trust any of them [ __ ] They're liars.
I was speaking to one yesterday, right?
She was like, "Oh yeah, I've uh I've
been with uh I've been with uh I've been
with um yeah, I hook up with people, but
I I rarely hook up with men." Then she
was trying to use distance as an excuse.
No, I don't trust them.
No, no, no, no, no. I don't trust them
at all. Not one of them.
Hell the [ __ ] no. Do I truck them?
And that only started happening a couple
of months ago really
cuz I've called them out. They're liars.
They are bullshitters.
They lie so much that they actually had
me questioning myself, which I've never
done before. That's how much they lie.
And I've actually caught them out on
lies as well, like using age as an
excuse not to get with people or you not
being Muslim. Yeah, I don't trust them.
their lies. Um, some Muslim woman that I
I met once
and I saw again, she come out with some
[ __ ] excuse. Bro, I don't trust
them. They're liars. I don't trust them
as far as I can throw them. No, not even
1% I trust. I don't trust any of them
cuz I've had it where people have lied.
I've caught them out on lies and I've
caught them being bullshitters. So, no,
I don't trust them.
They lie. They try to victimize
themselves. Nope. I don't trust any of them.
I don't trust if they said I was
good-looking. I don't trust if they said
I was this. I don't trust any of them. They're liars. So,
no, I don't trust them. No way do I
Well, I believe it when I see it, lad.
I believe it when I see it.
Yeah, this Muslim was saying, "Oh, yeah,
I changed, man. I'm just liars. They're bullshiters.
They're all They've all got the same traits."
And I got sick of it in the end.
I got sick of it in the end with them.
Same trait, same [ __ ] same
[ __ ] same attitude.
Same [ __ ] Yeah, you know,
I've only ever met one in my life that
seemed to be okay,
but I didn't know them well enough. So,
they're all liars.
Nope. I would never get married.
There was this one I was speaking to um
that they're they're Turkish and they
live in Vienna
talking saying, "Oh yeah, this that and
the other. I don't get with people
unless they're Muslim talking and then
all of a sudden they disappear." That's
what they do. They they talk and they
ghost people. They're bullshitters. They
are absolute bullshitters.
So, if you really really want sex, then
you know, you got have to you're going
to have to join the porn industry.
Um, oh, use escorts.
I think I'm too far gone now, bro. I'd
rather just save money and leave,
which is what I'm doing, but I had to
spend some money and stuff. So,
I would generally just Do you remember
when I was winning them football bets
and I still weren't going out two, three
weeks in a row? Like, nope, not going
out. Come on. Yeah, it's [ __ ] bro. It's
very, very [ __ ]
Even when I was still in the old house,
I wouldn't go out for like three weeks. Pointless. pointlessness, bro.
It will never change.
But yeah, you should join a porn
industry or use escorts if you want.
That's what you want. Yeah.
That's what I would do.
I've already given up on women. There's
no before you give up. I've already
given up on them, bro. I don't go out
for a reason. It would be dead, bro.
It's Thursday. It's It's November.
Yeah, it's it's dead, bro. Because
people I said at the start of November,
I'm not drinking again until December.
Well, I had I drunk a few yesterday, but
I only had three beers. And I was
playing do I was playing um pool, so I
didn't go out out, but I said I weren't
going to go out out until December because
if I was again, cuz uh there's no point
wasting money in November. That's why
people are not out. Just like January,
people are not going to be out January.
People are not going to be out until
like midFeb next year. Uh
cuz people say money.
But I've already given up on women.
Already given up.
But my sister said that if I joined like
the porn industry, she disowned me and stuff.
And so did my mom. But at the end of the
day, you need to think about what's best for you.
You need to think about what's best for
you. You know, life is
the thing is Yeah. is that
life is all about breaking a cycle. If
you can't break a cycle, you're [ __ ]
Which is why I broke the gambling cycle. Flops roulette.
Because I knew that if I carried on, I
would have just kept getting these mood
strings and I would have just end up killing someone.
Of course it is. You're going to be
getting sex all the time. Of course it
is, bro. You're going to get sex. You're
not going to deal with attitude. I mean,
you'd be breaking the cycle.
You know, life is all about breaking a
cycle. If you can't break a cycle,
you're in. You're [ __ ] That's why I
broke the gambling cycle. That's why I
only gamble the football. Now, I play
roulette very, very, very rarely. Very
But I broke the cycle. So, you know, that's
what what else are you supposed to do?
Go out every week talking to women,
getting [ __ ] over.
It's not an option.
If I carried on playing that roulette, I
would have. Yeah, probably.
It's just like the women thing as well.
And there's been times when I've gone
out drinking. There's been times when
I've gone out drinking as well.
There's been times when I've gone out
drinking and spent um
well, when you have that anger and
hatred, if you had the bad experiences
with women that I've had, it's completely justified.
I put up with a lot of their [ __ ] I've
had a lot of patience for years. It's no
wonder I feel the way I do. And I can
safely say that no one's walked the mile
of my shoe. No one's tried as much as I have.
That's what makes me unique. Um,
there's been times as well where I've
gone out drinking, spent a load of
money, got [ __ ] over, and if it wasn't
for me winning a football bet, I'd be [ __ ]
Still no day. Still no woman. And I
thought, "Fuck this. I'm not doing this again.
Not recently, but it has happened before
when I've gone out and I've spent
[ __ ] mad muddy drinking. Oh well."
got led on, [ __ ] over. You're waiting
on a football bet to come. Come in. The
football bet won. Okay, start all over
again. Learn that lesson.
This was a while ago, not not recently.
And then you need to think to yourself,
is this really worth it? You know,
really, it isn't worth it.
Just saying that it can be expensive
sometimes you go out drinking. Not the
last time I It's not financial, but at
the same time, it is expensive going
out. I can afford it, but still. >> Yeah.
>> But yeah, I've got a lot of anger and
hatred, and it's completely justified.
The bad experiences I've had with women,
it's completely completely justified.
It's completely justified.
More than justified. So,
yeah, if you had bad better experiences,
you'd have been a better person.
That's the way it is.
It's depressing as well.
There's times where it actually used to
depress me, bro, after drinking. It
actually used to depress me. Now it
doesn't. It's just toxic.
It used to it used to get it used to be
depressing, bro. Like a couple of days
after the drinking when you get the
numbers and the numbers didn't reply.
But now if it happens now, I'm just
like, "Oh, same old." Like, "Yeah,
whatever." It doesn't It doesn't It will
never get me to press because I expect it, you know.
And the fact that when you write
something negative, they reply straight
away and it's just negative and toxic.
They clearly all they are clearly the
same. They clearly are all the same. No
matter what people no matter what people
say. So that's that.
I mean I could go out
but what would be the point? It would be
it would be the same. Even though it
wouldn't affect me, it would just be the
same old. So
it would always be the same old.
It'll always be the same old out here. So,
people say you're going to meet someone on Reddit. Yeah,
it actually is actually annoying talking
about it, bro.
Yeah, that's Do you know what you should
say to them? Say to them if they've got
a problem, they know where I live. If
they if they've got a problem,
they're they're more than w they're more
than welcome to come to where I live,
bro. They all know where I live.
So, at the end of the day, just say to
them that if you got a problem, you know
where the fella lives.
And if not, then [ __ ] off.
No, I know. But just say that to them is it like
it'll be another lonely Yeah, it'll be
another lonely Valentine's. But it's the
same every year. It will never change,
will it? So
probably would never have sex again to
be honest. Unless it's escorts.
There's nothing to be positive about.
Nothing to be positive about.
I can't cancel next week either. I really can't
I can't cancel next week because of uh
because of um
Yeah, I can't cancel this week, bro. Cuz I already
[ __ ] him about last time. So, yeah.
So yeah, climb. [snorts] Uh, is anyone
Yeah, I'm going as well.