Hey man. Oh [ __ ] that's [ __ ] wet,
man. I was just making some
posters. Nice to print
now. Tomorrow, Sunday. Yeah, I probably
going to print the posters later, mate.
Distributed. I got some nice posters coming
up to put all around the Virgin's area.
Make sure that little rat face [ __ ] gets
[ __ ] kicked out of him. That'll teach
him being a little YouTube keyboard
warrior all his life. I got some posters
to pull up delayed. I'm printing them
later. I'm printing the posters. I'm
going to make sure the virgin gets his
[ __ ] ugly head kicked in. Literally,
I got the posters already, mate.
Literally, I got him ready. This is a
good one. I like this. This one's a sick
one. Look at this. I've made three
different posters and I'm going to post
them. Going to post them all around the
area. Make sure this ma gets his [ __ ]
head kicked in. [ __ ] lanky little
[ __ ] Make sure that lanky [ __ ] won't be
living there no more by the time I'm
done. Literally make sure that M [ __ ]
with a Gracier and a fat ugly girlfriend
has to move from where he is. Literally,
I've made three different posters. I'm
still making them bangers and I'm going
to put him everywhere because it's my
YouTube channel and I do what I want and
you are a manta. Stop calling yourself a
manta, you fat ugly [ __ ] Put them all around the
area. All around the area. Make sure
that [ __ ] don't go to no [ __ ]
takeaways no more. Make sure that
[ __ ] ugly [ __ ] and his fat ugly
girlfriend that he needs to put on a
leash ain't going around that area no
more. Get the [ __ ] where it hurts. The
[ __ ] kicked out of him and he won't call
the police cuz I've got all of what he's
been doing for the past two years.
Right. I don't I don't even give a [ __ ]
if the police gets involved. I don't
give a [ __ ] Literally, I'll show the
police all of his golden all of the
evidence that I've got on this [ __ ]
this little rat face that won't leave
anyone alone. So, at the end of the day,
bro, if it stops it for two, three
weeks, banger, bro. I don't care. 2030,
30 pound I've got to spend. Not a
problem to me, bro. I'll happily do it
cuz we don't have to lie about we don't
have to lie about things like Trump
about, you know, we don't have to lie
about things like Trump, you know. He
lies about everything. Make sure you go
around this virgin [ __ ] and see how big
he is on YouTube after this. Let's see
if he really is the big man. Let's see
how big he is. Let's see how big this
virgin [ __ ] is when the posters go up
about him. Let's see how how much of the
big man he really is on YouTube after
these posters go up about
him. He's not going to be done. I'm
print them later, bro. I'm printing them
later. After I go out on the stage, I'm
going to come back. I'm gonna print
these posters and I'm gonna make sure
that this [ __ ] ugly virgin [ __ ] won't
be coming on YouTube no more. Giving it
the big man with his little ugly voice.
I'm going to I'm going to show you, bro.
I will show you. You're going to see.
You're going to see. You will see. I got
three different ones. They'll have like
a mix of them. I'm going to put them all
around train stations, all around main
train stations as well. It's going to be
a [ __ ] banger.
Let's see if after this, right, he's
going to be like, "Oh, big nose." Let's
see if the little [ __ ] diagnosed
autistic bastard is going to come back
on here after I'm done with these
posters. Let's see if the big man is
going to come even try to come back on
YouTube. I love it, mate. That doesn't
matter, bro. I'm putting up posters. I'm
putting up posters about him. Look, I've
been making posters. I just need to
print them now, lad. It's absolutely
fine. But listen, what I'm trying to say
to you, Harry, right, is let's
see, yeah, if this little [ __ ] ugly
virgin can is going to come back on
YouTube after I've done the posters. My
prediction is no. My prediction is no.
And if he wants to try to get the police
involved, I will show the police
everything that he's been doing over the
past two years. I've got everything and
even more recent stuff. Trust me, bro.
The police route is not going to work.
And it's not And it never worked the
first time. Yeah, that's it, lad. Yeah,
you get played all your life, broki.
Anyways, I'm doing these posters
anyways. I'm getting them printed out
tomorrow. Um, today, sorry. And I'm
probably going to do them tomorrow to be
fair cuz we got a busy day today,
broki. Let's see if the [ __ ] ugly
virgin [ __ ] Let's see if the virgin
[ __ ] with a rat face is going to come
back on YouTube with his autism after
the postes I put out about the [ __ ] And
you know what? I'm going to save a
little bit by, right? So if he tries to
come back, I'm just going to keep doing
it again and doing it again and doing it
again and I will not stop doing it. Like
I don't care, bro. Get the [ __ ] rap
based autistic [ __ ] where. Come on. Come
on, man. I'm in the mood for this now,
mate. It only took me about five minutes
now. I just need to print
him. I'm going to [ __ ] get the virgin
[ __ ] rat face. [ __ ] where it hurts.
Let's see if this [ __ ] is going to come
back on YouTube.
Let's see if this little virgin [ __ ]
with a fat ugly girlfriend is going to
come back on YouTube. What's your
predictions? Saying that though, LT said
that he's got a printer at work. Let me
email these Let me email these um these
posters to him right now. One sec. Where was
it? He said he's got a printer at work.
work. So, we can actually print them
right now. Actually, one
second. Where is it? There you
go. One second,
lad. I'm going to send him these posters
anyways. Two seconds, bro. Hold on. Let
me email this.
There we go. I just emailed
it. Yeah, it's fine, bro. I'm I'm I'm
going to put up [ __ ] I'm going to
pull up [ __ ] posters of this car. I
just I just emailed LT right now. I just
emailed him right now, bro.
Yeah, I just emailed him right now.
Well, if he's not at work today, he's
going to be work at Monday. So, there
you go. You got the posters now.
Anyways, they're good enough. I sent you
three different kinds. I showed you
three different posters. Outlook, right?
All you got to do is print them. Print
them for me and I'll put around the Virgin's area again.
Yeah. There you go. Job done, bro. It
wasn't that hard. You're telling me you
couldn't make these [ __ ] posters?
[ __ ] off, man. It took me [ __ ] two
seconds. It literally took me two
seconds to make these
posters. Come on, man. You can't be [ __ ]
dyslexic. Where the [ __ ] is
this person, lad? Yeah. See, eh?
And you know what's going to happen when
you put these posters out, right? When
you put these posters out as well,
Harry, what's he what's he going to do
is he's going to delete a lot of the
stuff on his channel. So, he's going to
delete the stuff on his channel and then
he's going to stop for like two, three
weeks. That's literally what's going to
happen. Come on, mate. I just [ __ ]
emailed you. Print these [ __ ] posters
out on this [ __ ] virgin [ __ ] Let's
see how much of a big man he is when
these posters are put out. Let's see how
much a big bad he is when he ain't
walking around this area no more. Let's
see how bad the big bad autism guy is
when the post around his area. Let's see,
bro. This is a lesson, bro. You should
just leave people alone. deal with your
autism and leave people alone. This is
literally this is a lesson that you you
should really do it, bro. You
know, you [ __ ] 30 30 quid for it,
bro. Save me about 60 70
pound. That's it, bro. No, I'm putting
up posters of the [ __ ] I'm putting up
posters. It's like 30 pound for a
printer for printers on 30, bro. So,
obviously print off about 100, 200 of
these. I'll go around the area, pull it
up, right? And why are you saying I need
to pee nonslegs off here quietly when
you know that I've tried to meet him,
Harry? You know that I've gone to the
virgin's area three times. You know what
he's like. That's why we have to do
posters so he can get his head kicked
in. He can get his virgin head kicked
in. What do you mean quietly catch him?
I've gone to his area three times, you
[ __ ] idiot. What do you mean quietly
catch him? Yeah, you're the one, right?
You're the [ __ ] one that doesn't
[ __ ] come out when somebody goes to
Liverpool. What do you mean quietly
catch him? Allow it, bro. Come on. Yeah,
about to quietly catch him. How many
times have I gone to this virgin's area
only for him to run to the police
screaming how he's not a fighter? Get
the [ __ ] out of here, you little scouse and bug.
[ __ ] absolute [ __ ] about oh catch
him quietly when you know damn well he's
a coward. You know damn well when you go
to his area he doesn't come out. Why are
you telling people to catch people
quietly when you know what they
do when you know the little virgin
ratfaced ma is not going to meet anyone.
This is why we have to do posters. We
have to do it the tramodile
way. We have to do it the tramodile way.
Yeah, because otherwise this little
virgin [ __ ] with his fat ugly girlfriend
ain't going to learn. You understand?
He's not going to learn. And I said that
to the police as
well. You know,
simple, simple, dimple, wimple, limple,
wimple. Watch them videos start getting
deleted now as
well. I didn't know printers was cheap
as anyways, we'll get LT to print them
out. I don't mind doing 20, 30
quid. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Harry, I'm
not reacting to you no more, buddy.
We've been through this over and over
and over again. Listen, mate. The
posters is the perfect thing. It's
literally the perfect
thing. Yeah. Try and get the police. Try
to get the police. I won't let him in. I
won't let the police in. I'll say you do
something about this cunt's going and
harassing and then come back to me. This
little [ __ ] on his YouTube channel has
got me everywhere. Yeah. This little
[ __ ] virgin ma has got his has got me
all over his YouTube channel. Go and
[ __ ] off and do something about that and
then come I won't let him in. I won't
let him in. That's that's the first way
I was. I said, I I won't even let them
in. I'll say, "Do you do something about
this cunt's go?" This is what I said to
this woman. He keeps goating people on
YouTube every day and he won't leave
them alone. I had to show her video
after video after video, right? That
this little virgin keeps [ __ ]
harassing me every day with his fat ugly
girlfriend, which is why I've had to do
posters to get the c to leave me alone.
And it works. And and it's the only
thing that works with somebody that has
got as bad autism as he does. You
know, you know what I'm
saying? And that's it, lad. So, it's all
good. I'm going to get the [ __ ] where it
hurts. He's [ __ ] heads kicked in.
[ __ ] virgin. All around Paulon
station. I'm going to do around
Victoria. I'm going to do it everywhere,
bro. Yeah. I don't give a [ __ ] bro. Let
him grass. I've got all of these
harassment, bro. I've got all of the
evidence. He won't leave me alone. I
don't care, bro. I've got all of these
evidence of him harassing me and he
won't leave me the [ __ ] alone. So, what?
What, bro? What? What? What? What? What?
What? Like, what, bro? And listen, don't
ever come on here before, right? And
don't come on here as well, and try and
tell me about Terry's family. I
literally told Terry last Thursday to go
suck up these kids and go suck up his
family. Do you see the guy trying to
meet me? Don't try try and tell me that
this guy's, "Oh, he's got family. [ __ ]
his family and tell him to suck up these
dirty kids and he's not going to do
nothing about it." It's the same, bro.
Listen, you're saying how you don't like
cowards. Yeah. This is why I don't get
about you. You're saying how you don't
like cowards, bro. Did man just not go
to Terry's area two years? Didn't I just
not go to his area two years? I'm on
probation. Do you think any man that's
about anything would ever talk like
that? He ain't about nothing. Him or his
family? I'm I'm telling you straight,
bro. And I when when I bring his family
up, listen, when I bring his family up,
right? Yeah. He says, "I don't mention
my family." The guy ain't about
anything. You called somebody up to your
area. Someone came to your area. You
said you're on probation. You're not
about it. and and and it's hard to
believe that anybody in your family
could possibly about it be about it
after that as
well. Anyways, I got a date to it.
Anyways, so yeah, I met this uh Yank on Thursday. Gains.
Yeah. Yeah, bro. I met this
Yank. Yeah, of course you got my email
cuz I just told you I [ __ ] emailed you. Yeah.
And I'll email you more off here as
well. There you
go. Got a long day ahead of me today,
bro. That Tony ain't about nothing. Why
does he come on here talking like he's
some hard man when he's like b to talk
too? It's embarrassing, man. Come on
now. How long are we going to keep doing
this for man? You know embarrass
him. You got it,
lad. No, I know the point you're trying
to make, but you know that this virgin
is never going to meet anyone. That's
the point I'm trying to make to you,
Harry, is that they're never ever ever
going to meet you. You will never know
where they are when they are. So it's
like Yeah, I got [ __ ] to do today, bro.
As well. Got me [ __ ] on here [ __ ]
11 o'clock in the [ __ ]
morning. That tea tastes [ __ ] ranking.
How's How's um How's Ramadan? Um
LT, how was Ramadan? How's Ramadan, bud?
Huh? How's Ramadan? How's Ramadan, [Laughter]
buddy? Oh, it's just bad though, is it?
Yeah, it's just
Nah. Yeah, I'm Muslim, bro. Guess what I ate yesterday?
Pepperoni. Yeah, bro. I'm Turkish, isn't
it? But I gamble, I drink, and I uh I
gamble, I drink. I gamble, I drink, and I eat
pork. Yeah, I'm very religious, man. Is it?
Yeah. No, I had a nice pizza yesterday,
man. Pepperoni, jalapenos. Oh, it was
banging, mate. I was hung over. I got
beat this wood today for [ __ ] sake.
Here we go
again. Here we go
again. Here we go again, LT. Here we go
buddy. You know what's so funny, right?
Yeah. Is I was
approaching I was [ __ ] approaching,
bro, like five times in this club.
You're not going to believe this, bro.
And I was getting nothing. I was
approaching the car. I was getting nothing,
mate. Literally wasn't getting nothing.
I was getting [ __ ] all, bro. I swear to
God, I wasn't getting [ __ ] all. And
then as soon as I done one on the
street, well, you'll see today a How bad
is that? Opposites, e opposites,
buddy. But you get me in it.
Yeah. A couple hours today that
Oh yeah, that chase is a snake by the
way, games. But guess what? He ain't got
nothing that I put out, bro. He ain't
really got anything. Like, I knew that
was a thing. Hey, I knew that was a
thing. Games. I knew that was a thing.
Why do you think I didn't tell him where
I was, where I'm living? Why do you
think I didn't tell him certain things,
bro? I knew that was a thing. But the
guess, but the thing is, bro, like
here's the thing. They're bad for my
city because even when they're together,
they will never ever ever meet you. Like
think about it like that, bro. Two
people in London and they can't even
tell you where they are. It's it's worse
than this whole Liverpool thing. It's
bad enough like how we fraud. Yeah. Not
coming out when you're in Liverpool and
that's one person. But imagine two whole
people together and they still can't
tell you where they are. Like in I used
to tell you on the phone bro, if I knew
they were at that pub, I'm always at
that pub. I was there last Thursday. I
would have knocked them both out, bro.
With one hand. It's not even a
joke. No, I didn't cry. What? What do I
cry over? What? What was But do you
understand what I'm saying though? Even
when they're together, they will never
let anyone know where he is. And I said
the same thing to Chase. I told him to
suck his nan about [ __ ] four years
ago. Yeah. Four years ago. Four [ __ ] years ago,
bro. Four years ago, mate.
ago. Um, and then you're trying to act
like you're a bad man, bro. When you
weren't even in [ __ ] Wales. I was
like four or five years ago. Yeah. He
Yeah, like I humiliated you in it when I
was in Liverpool. Like I showed
everybody what people in Liverpool was
about. Nothing. Yeah. How did he
humiliate me? He didn't humiliate me,
bro. I humiliated all of you people and
I was in Liverpool. You didn't even come
out, bro. How embarrassing is that? You
know, at least I tried to meet [ __ ] L after. You
know, you need to get a life, man. Simple.
Yeah. They don't bully no one, mate.
They bully themselves because if they
actually bully someone, right? Yeah.
Right. You listen listen. They don't
bully no one. If they bully people, they
wouldn't still be on here. If they truly
bully people, they wouldn't still be on
here. I hate what they do as well, but
they're far from bullies. To bully
someone, you actually have to meet them
face to face. You can't bully somebody
over a keyboard because a foury old and
a 5-year-old can do these things. They
don't bully no one. If they bully
people, they wouldn't still come on
YouTube. Yeah, we've been hit on now.
Your vog words don't don't even be
hitting people like that anymore, mate.
You've got to pull up. I've got to pull
up. Hold on a minute. I've got to pull
up. How long do these people know where
I live? Listen, they knew. Okay, let let
me tell you how [ __ ] these people are,
right? I can tell you, right? I was in a
pub on Thursday. Guess what? Everybody
knew what pub I was in and no one does
nothing. They only tried to get me
kicked out of the pub. And you're
telling me about pulling up? Please,
brother. It doesn't make no sense.
Everybody knew the pub I was in as well.
They'll tell you the name of the pub.
I've been there about a million times.
And I was in that pub for probably about
an hour, a solid hour. And I went to Cat
Machine and I went back to to play
Fishing Frenzy. Bro, why did none of
these people pull up? Why did none of
these people pull up when they know
where you live? You know, it's it's a
two-way thing, man.
Please, please, please. Like, they
actively knew what pub I was in. They
knew what pub I was in. They were trying
to get me kicked out of the pub.
Yeah. So, I mean, it kind of works both
ways, man. You know,
yeah. No, I was
uh Yeah, I went out on Thursday. I was
in this pub uh the weather spoons in
Ping Port Road. Everyone knows the pub
that I go to. Um, you can't really get
people banned from it because I mean
they all know me and there's not it's
not really like a bouncing thing like
that. They everyone knew where I was.
Everybody knew where I was and they were
trying to get me kicked out. They were
trying to get me banned. Like they were
so mad, bro. There was about 30 people
in the chat. So your my question is why
didn't they pull up? It's not like
they've not known where you've been. You
know, like Tottenham Court, you're
telling me that one of these people live
in London. You're telling me that one of
these people live near Totten Court
Road. It doesn't make sense. Of course
they do. Of course some of these people
do. That's like right in the middle of
London. Yeah. I'm outside every day,
mate. I'm outside every day. Yeah.
So that's it. I'm outside today as well.
I'm going to meet this
woman. Yeah. I met this American woman
gay. I'm kind of scared, but I'm not
going to lie to you. Don't really like Americans. [ __ ] [ __ ]
Oh, I got my passport games. I told you
I had to renew my
passport. I think we didn't speak since
then and it took about 11 days to
get Yeah, it took 11 days to get,
man. Yeah, I was going to go watch that
um Daddy Die film, but I still ain't got
around to watching it yet.
Yeah, got some mad plans, man. You know,
I don't even go out to pull any more
games. I just go out to have a little
drink, you know? I don't even I I just
go out to have a drink and enjoy myself
and whatever happens
happens. Do you know what I'm saying,
LT? Whatever happens happens,
man. I had a 19year-old messaged me
yesterday. That's what you That's what
you'll find with these [ __ ] is that
they all come at once. You'll find like
as soon as you get someone, it's like
they either none of them are interested
or many of them become interested.
That's what you find with these with
these women is when one comes, they all
seem to come. And then when none of them
come, none of them
come. It's a
madness. All this [ __ ] Yeah. It's a madness, bro.
Yeah, nothing too bad. Just chill and
I'll go on this date soon. [ __ ] well. Few hours.
Yeah. Yeah. It's long, but could do a
lot going on it today to be
honest. Just fancy a little snooze, you
know, Dad. You know, one of them days
you just fancy a little
snooze. A good old snooze. just a little
chow. That's why I always say people
Thursdays are the one because when you
go out drinking Thursday, if you got a
date on Saturday, you're prepared for
it. But if you go out Friday and you try
to go out Saturday, you're still [ __ ]
So Thursday gives you like a good 40 40
odd hours to recover, you know? So
that's why Thursdays are good. But I
wouldn't even say you're still fully
recovered then to be fair. I move to
lobster, but it's [ __ ] [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah. I've been to a lobster pot before,
but it made me [ __ ]
sick. It made me [ __ ]
sick. These people need to go to gym
games. They need to get a
life. They need to like seriously get
off of YouTube and get a life, man. I
was off YouTube for a week, but I was
doing [ __ ] madnesses. They still went
on about me every day,
bro. They're [ __ ]
obsessed. Why I call them,
bro? Fat ugly
people. You can have a tiny day. Hey guys,
no you actually you actually remind me of
Afghan Birmingham. But to be honest with
you, I don't think I'll ever go to
another city in England again to be real
with you. Like I said I was going to go
black and that but I I don't think I ever
will cuz I feel like there's no point
wasting money in in this [ __ ] United
Kingdom. No point
that to be honest with
you. I I want that in [ __ ] ages. I
see no point. We have everything here.
Best clubs, best
music, and I've done it as well. I've
traveled like, you know, so I don't see
the point in wasting money,
bro. Yeah. slum with a boss. Yeah,
maybe. But there no there's no point
going any further than that. No matter
where you go, women have got the same attitude
everywhere. Women have the same attitude
everywhere. Um, people have the same
attitude everywhere. That's what I
notice as well. Like no matter where you go, you know.
Yeah. I'm going anyways. I'll be back later.