Yeah, I just wanted to say uh
big up Rickstar Millington. Yep.
Big up Rickar Millington. Yeah,
I seen them packer virgins go at you.
Sorry, I can't defend you, bro. I'm
blocked on that [ __ ] channel. Pack of virgins.
Then I'm going at you, mate. [ __ ]
nons legs and [ __ ] Red Star. [ __ ]
pack of virgins.
Absolute pack of virgins.
Sorry, mate. I can't help you against
them virgins. I've been blocked. Sorry, mate.
>> Yeah, sorry about that. But I absolutely
agree with what you're saying. I I I
can't fault it. You know,
look at that red star [ __ ] fat ugly
little low life replying to your
comments straight away. Do you know what
you should say to him, Ricky Millington?
Um, tell him to show me where he is and
I'll come and smash his face in
tomorrow. Oh, but he can't do that cuz
he's a fat ugly keyboard warrior. How
little loser. I'm off here next week
anyways from next week. I'll be busy for
a long time. can't interact these
[ __ ] low life losers anymore that
can't get YouTube.
So, just letting you know.
Just letting you know.
Probably be back in the new year. Yeah. [snorts]
Just chilling, bro. Chilling.
No, next week I'm going to be off for a bit
cuz I'm going to be busy from next
month. I'll be back um
in the new year.
Yeah, I'll be back in the new year, lad. Yeah.
I read Reddit banning me again. That boy.
Whenever you complain about women, they
ban you and say that is a victim
mentality. [ __ ] pack of nerds.
Pack a [ __ ] nerd, mate. Pack a nerd.
This guy on Reddit said, yeah, that he's
had hundreds of one night stands.
[ __ ] Absolute [ __ ] mate.
Absolute [ __ ] Do you know how many
escorts I've been with, bro? A lot. And
not even hundreds. Absolute [ __ ]
Hundreds of one night stands.
Hundreds of one night stands. Hundreds,
bro. That's [ __ ] Unless you're in
your [ __ ] 60s or [ __ ] 70s, bro. Or
you're some [ __ ] bro. The only people
that [ __ ] hundreds of people is [ __ ] porn stars.
That's [ __ ] bro. Hundreds of one
night stands bollocks. Absolute
[ __ ] The only people that are
[ __ ] that many people are [ __ ]
celebrities and [ __ ] porn stars. Why
do they lie so much on Reddit? That's
why I can't deal with the lies.
The lies. I've [ __ ] so many escorts.
Like so many escorts.
And it's nowhere near hundreds.
I don't know how many. A lot.
There's no way. They they lie so much on
Reddit. Greavves. He wrote a post.
They're [ __ ] liars.
I had KFC for T Greavves. Yeah.
Add four piece chicken. Yeah.
Yeah. I'll be off YouTube next week for
probably until New Year's
cuz like I said, I'm going to be busy
December. So, yeah, I won't be able to
be on it, but I'll be back in January.
Briy, will you wait? Will you wait for
me to come back?
I need to start my diet as well, bro,
because of my teeth and that. My gums.
They say that like your tooth is with
your teeth is a lot to do with your diet
and stuff, which I think is uh true. So,
I'm going to need to cut down on stuff
probably from after next week to be honest.
Uh oh. Did you see the video that I done
about the Chev Cole thing? I told you
they were copying Grizzy. Did you watch
it? I told you they were copying.
Told you it's a copycat trend. I told
you. You didn't believe me, did you? Why
do you never believe when I tell you stuff?
Why do you never ever believe me when I
tell you stuff?
Yeah, exactly. Yeah, that's when I I
think I met Virgin Boy.
Um, when did I meet Virgin Boy?
Yeah, it was about 10 11 years ago.
Yeah. Yeah, it was around that time.
Yeah, cuz I met the Virgin when I was 17
and obviously I'm 28 now. So, yeah. So,
it was a trend all along then, Greavves,
I told you. Gay, the guy even knew it
was coming in before you're gay. Yeah. Copycats. Copycats. Squeezy. Yep.
after this live, my Streamyards would
have been um
would have been uh
would have run out. So,
I'm not doing it until January. So, I
don't want to see any of you people on
here when I'm back. I don't want to see
that you people have been on here every
day in December, Grezy, cuz I will go
[ __ ] mad if I see that you people
have been on here every day when I come back
cuz you call other people's skin and
that they ain't got a life and stuff.
So, I don't want to see any of you
people on here until I'm back.
This charge is [ __ ]
Oh, this charge is [ __ ]
That's not even charging.
This just Why do they Why are they so dodgy, bro?
Just [ __ ] charges.
There we go. [ __ ] annoying as [ __ ] bro.
Didn't you have a dollar picture yesterday? Gy,
don't talk about milkshakes, bro, cuz
I'll end up getting another one, mate.
Them milkshakes are lovely.
Noah does up the road. I might get
another one. £8.
Is that okay with you? If I get another milkshake, Greezy,
that would have been basically 20 today
that I spent on food.
Is that okay with you?
Obviously, I have to run it by you
first. Of course,
you know, you're my financial advisor,
but a fancy one again.
Do I have to offer Laney one as well then? We
now I'm just going to buy myself one. [ __ ] it.
Bro, that milkshake is [ __ ] lust, bro.
They're like £8, so I can't really buy
So, I basically saved this month.
Yeah. £500. So, I don't think that was
that bad to be honest.
No, it wasn't that bad. I saved 500.
Was it greasy?
I bought a lot of [ __ ] that it
get another one. 8 far.
There we go.
Yeah, I ordered a graves.
Okay with you, boss.
Did you see on the forum they were all
calling each other gay? Ruby.
And did you see they were all calling
each other gay? [ __ ] copycats.
My mouth was hurting the other day, bro.
It's better now.
I think it's my diet, Grezy. What do you think?
It's got to be my diet. I think if you
start eating vegetables and salmon and
chicken and water even for a week.
Yeah, I think it's my diet, bro.
It's better now. It was hurting again
the other day. It's better now.
It's got to be, bro. Like all the coke and [ __ ]
Just change your diet for like a week.
Flush and that. It should be all right
within a week in a two weeks maybe.
Don't Don't drink Coke for like a Don't
drink Coke for like two weeks. That's
going to be hard, bro.
And then I'll start drinking it with
like a straw maybe.
How much did you say you saved this month, Grezy?
I forgot you said, but I forgot.
Bless you. I think it was the same as
me, was it?
I think it was like five, was it?
Yeah, something like that, probably.
bless you then.
Bless you then if you forgot. Bless.
I need to buy myself a phone as well.
Madness in it, Greavves,
dude. Oh, well. Oh gosh,
Grazy. Oh gosh,
is that cute? Greasy. Oh gosh.
[snorts] So hopefully we get uh we get
better experiences next week, Greavvesy.
Oh, Grezy, I I forgot to tell you. You
know there's a Toy Story 5 coming out.
Yep. Toy Story 5's coming out, Greavvesy.
I don't know if you knew, but yeah.
What? You've never been a B a toy? Why
do you mean
Woody's coming out?
Why do you mean I've been f
he's coming out?
Well, you've never been a [ __ ] fan.
What the [ __ ] Really?
[ __ ] hell. You absolute virgin.
Greasy, you absolute virgin. No [ __ ] way.
You absolute virgin.
[ __ ] me. Yeah, I love Toy Story.
I'm your what?
Don't get sloppy with me, you [ __ ]
You remember that one, Greavvesy. Don't
get sloppy with me, you [ __ ]
I'll do a little New Year's Eve video
for you, Greavvesy. Okay with you, boss.
Okay with you, boss. If I do a little
New Year's Eve video for you, Greavves.
I'll do a little New Year's Eve video for you.
Okay with you, boss.
Okay with you, [ __ ] Yeah,
I do a nice little one for you, Grezy.
I'm away New Year's Eve.
It's going to be lovely, is it?
It's going to be lovely, Captain. [snorts] Oh gosh.
Shut up you stupid dog.
Is it the first tomorrow? Oh yeah,
there's 30 days in November.
What did you think of the student form
grievy? What do you think of what they were doing?
What's your opinion on uh what they were doing? >> [snorts]
>> I just ordered myself another milkshake
triple. I'm so bad with money. I am so
What are they doing on the student room form? Grezy.
They're all saying the same thing in it.
That's where he got it from. it. That
must have been where he got it from, huh?
Yeah, that must have been where he
bloody got it from. Copycat.
Better question. Are you a homosexual or
not? Green Z.
Yeah, it's no fun, is it? Really?
Uh, peanut butter milkshake.
It's no fun, is it? Really? Triple.
It's no fun, is it really, lad?
Happen to copy. [ __ ] boring. Bors me,
bro. People that copy are boring as
[ __ ] is it?
I might put 160 on the football next week
to approach 160 on two teams.
Is that mad greasy?
No. [ __ ] that bro.
It's m it is madness. Oh goshy. Oh gosh.
That's cute, isn't it? Oh gosh.
I might post some content on my other
channel when I'm off here next week, I think. Yeah,
I have another channel where there's no haters. Uh, Grezy.
Yeah, there's no haters.
I already had a takeaway. Add KFC.
Yeah, I had KFC. Yeah, lad.
I might do a football bet every week,
Triple H, and try and win it and then do
the lad book thing
and keep showing my face with the money.
You like them little pictures, don't
you, Triple H? Yeah. [laughter]
Trip H, you like them one, didn't it? Oh,
>> what do you Triple H. I'm going to put
170 on a football bet on Saturday.
Triple H, is that okay with you? Captain
Triple H, is that okay with you, Captain? Captain,
that would be [ __ ] lush, mate. On the
football if it comes in, that' be [ __ ] beautiful.
Then you get all of these little large a
simps come over when it loses. If it loses laughing,
laughing like 170 is any money to you.
I had this guy like, "Oh no, my gambling
for you P cuz you got no sublet money."
I was like, "Bro, do you know how much
money I have?" No, you don't. So
stop talking about people that you don't [ __ ] know.
Yeah. So, stop talking about people that
you don't [ __ ] know,
isn't it, Greasy?
It's true though, isn't it? Greaves. No. No.
I can't wait until Saturday, bro. It
can't come fast enough.
But at the same time,
I'm not looking forward to it because of
the women. Grieves. I'm not looking
forward to the women.
We all know what's going to happen.
Give me a [ __ ] headache. Okay, come on. Yeah.
I don't know. But I am, mate.
Yeah, he he figured the version out,
didn't he, Ricky Millington? He said
that his girlfriend fancies me. I think
so, too. I think they both fancy me, to be honest.
I think the Virgin does, as well. I
don't think it's just just his
girlfriend. I think they both fancy me.
They probably want a free.
Yeah, they probably want a free with me, mate. Grooy,
but that No, mate. No, no, mate. We're
not doing that. We're not [ __ ] doing [snorts] Yeah,
[ __ ] that, bro.
Yeah. It's a lovely site, isn't it?
You don't want to know.
She don't want to know. She don't want
to know you.
See, them copycats should have copied my
football bet the other day, ain't it, Grezy?
Them copycats should have copied my
football bet. They would have won. Isn't
that right, Grezy?
That virgin will always be obsessed.
Is that right? Agree with you. That
virgin will always be obsessed.
That [ __ ] virgin.
That [ __ ] virgin. That [ __ ]
Have we seen Joseph Ferrari? I think
he's won another grand. Joseph Ferrar. [clears throat]
He's not joining. The virgin is not
It needs to get lied. It needs to get aligned. One sec.
He's scared of likes and dislikes.
Have you seen Joseph Farage misses?
She's got fat fingers. Fat sausage
He showed a grand. He showed £1,20.
Couples that gamble together stay
together. Law. I'm sure she will spend
it before me. M shortly then might as
well book somewhere for Valentine's Day. Life's good.
What an absolute virgin.
He's going to do his [ __ ] He's going
to do his balls in one day, mate.
What an absolute virgin.
You know, I'm like, Triple H.
What an absolute virgin. I'm still being [ __ ] prepared. Oh.
Triple H is an absolute virgin. Hurry up.
Jo is an absolute virgin.
Dreamsy. Absolute virgin is it?
Non legs has got Britney on the mind. Triple H Yep.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
I want Brit Brit on the mind. Yep.
Got Britney on the mind, mate.
All right, mate. One second, mate.
Don't want to know you. Don't want to [screaming]
Why does never f Why does slow never score?
Slow ever score [ __ ] home.
Throw away. They never [ __ ] score
when they're away, them [ __ ]
That's what I say, Grezy.
That's what I say.
This person on Reddit today, Grevy was
like, they've had hundreds of one night
stands. That's what he said. [ __ ] liar. She's
down and he's down and he's down and Yep.
Yeah. We need people to join. The link's
there. Anyone that wants to join
I need my milkshake.
Five guys must be busy tonight. Grezy,
would you cry, Grezy, if you lost 170 on a bet?
Would you cry?
you I think you'd cry grieves if you
lost 170 on a bet in it.
>> Oh, sure. Would
you cry if you lost out on a bet? Wow.
600 pound. Jesus. That should um Oh, bless you. Oh, bless.
That's not good, is it? Wow.
Madness, bro. Right.
Come on, milkshake. So
yeah. Yeah. You keep telling yourself that.
Go away. Stop dismissing my struggles.
You'll get laid in this country. I don't think so.
I don't think so. Somehow. [snorts]
My sister can't help me. I can help
myself. Thank you very much.
I can help myself. I don't need anyone
else to help me. Thank you very much.
Is that right? All >> [snorts] [clears throat] >> right.
What's it saying now?
Still being prepared. Jesus Christ. They
must be busy. This bloody five guys. Grezy.
So you're on a diet from tomorrow. Yeah. I believe
>> city goose. >> Yeah. Then
we've heard it all before. Uh we've
heard it all before. Trip. [ __ ] We've Come on.
You're not going to be So So when are
you going to have McDonald's again then?
So when are you going to have McDonald's again?
Not until January. You're not going to
last a month, lad.
I think he's a sad bastard that ain't
got a life.
Yeah, I think he's a sad bastard that
ain't got a life. Yep. [snorts]
The one that can't get off of YouTube.
So, you're going to go about take
greasy. So, you're going to go about
takeaways for a month. really. Yeah.
I can't see it happening, bro.
So, you're going to go about a takeaway
for a month? Yeah.
I was having some digestive biscuits uh
yesterday, Gregy. Does that mean I'm a copycat?
That's not me being a copycat, is it?
I'm not a copycat.
Oh, it's out for delivery. Grezy,
[ __ ] hell, bro.
Self delivery captain.
I mean the link is up.
so people can join if they want. No
one's banned from joining. The only
people I blocked was the self-p projectors.
I blocked the self-reflectors.
They're the only people that are banned.
This the repeating self-p projecting bastards.
Autumn's not been on here.
Yeah, Autumn's not been on here.
No, it's not fact because the people I
banned I banned him for a reason.
No, they got banned for a reason, lad.
So, it's not facts cuz I banned him for a reason.
Repeating self-projecting bastards
like that Clint Eastwood. There's a lot
of people that aren't banned.
There's a lot of people that aren't banned.
Why is there 16 people watching?
No one's [ __ ] typing, but there's 16 people watching.
So then why are they on it then if
they're banned? So if they're banned and
they can't type, why are they watching?
That's a bit freaky, isn't it?
That's a bit weird.
Now that's weird, is it? If they're
watching and they're banned. Yeah.
So yeah, strange.
No. Autumn comes on here.
Yeah, I should go on L JS and unban
everyone and see how quickly they come
on here because they ain't got a life.
All the people that are banned are
probably people from L J's.
Cuz they ain't got a life. Yeah.
Yeah. They ain't got a freaking life.
Have you been watching Joseph Far's community post?
He collected 1,20 quid and he said the
MS is going to spend it all.
She's got some chubby bloody fingers, don't she?
No, I'm not abandoning them little self projectors.
I'd rather be sat here talking to myself
than any of them. I'm not abandoning any
of them. Virgin boy is unblocked.
Well, okay. Let me unblock some people,
right? Red Star and all of them. Let me
see. And I I bet you they come on here very quickly.
[ __ ] little Lola.
Yeah. One sec. One sec.
Right. I've unhood red star. I'm going
to unhide some people.
And look how quickly they're going to
come on here because they ain't got no
life. But YouTube like Reddit moderators.
This person's not banned. Banned. unbanned.
Well, I'm unbanning people in a sec.
And I'm going to unban and I'm going to
ban them again. One sec.
You have a big nose. Wait, virgin.
Type in the chat. You virgin.
It's not my fault your [ __ ] disabled
girlfriend [ __ ] fancies me.
[sighs and gasps]
[ __ ] virgin. You're not coming in, mate.
You little police informant. You can
type if you want. You're not banned from typing, mate.
Right, you're on. I've unbanned some
people, by the way. Do what you want to type.
Yeah, of course he is. He's a fat little
low life. They ain't got nothing. Fat slob.
[sighs and gasps] Yeah, cuz I'm off
after today. Anyways,
you're not coming in, you [ __ ] little
skin virgin. I don't let skin virgins in
the hangouts. It's a no Skint virgin
policy. I've told you this.
We're not allowed to add skinned virgins
that ain't got no money and never been
near a woman sexually. It's what the
rules are. I don't make the [ __ ] rules, you know.
Nope. He's not coming in the box. You
can type if you want.
I want to know why you're such a little copycat.
I want to know why you copy the crowd
with the Sher Cole thing. It doesn't
make you look big. It doesn't make you
look clever. It just makes you look like
someone that has to copy, you know.
Yeah, I'm off here, bro.
I'm off here um after today for until January.
Scared the nons legs. Good one. Um yeah,
I'm off until um
until January, bro, because I've got a
lot to do um in December. So, yeah.
And I said UK silent. When I come back,
I'm going to check everyone's channel
and I hope it's not the same people
every day cuz I will go [ __ ] mad
because they call you for not having a
life and not having no bloody money. So
I don't want to see any of these people on YouTube.
>> Yeah. After Yeah. After tomorrow. Well,
from today from tomorrow from today I
won't be uh
I don't help myself. You don't help
yourself telling me that I'm scared of
some little nons when he's gone to the
police on me about a million times. Shut
the [ __ ] up, you little [ __ ] About I'm
scared of a little [ __ ] that goes to
the police. You [ __ ] spasticated
bastard about I don't help myself. You
[ __ ] absolute [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
about I don't help myself. You [ __ ]
You don't help yourself. Get off of
YouTube. Get a [ __ ] life. I don't
want to see you on here next month,
you [ __ ] bog.
Yeah, I don't want to see you on here,
bro. When I come back anyways, I don't
want to see you in January.
What? What? I talk about him because
he's nothing but a little copycat.
So what, bro? He is a copycat. He copies
the crowd. I prove that with the video
that I done yesterday. He's a little
copycat when it comes to show. Well, he
is a little copycat.
Has to fit in with the crowd. Doesn't
want to feel left out. Well, what what's
what's wrong with that? You're not
blocked. You can easily type.
Why do you feel the need to copy? It
doesn't make you feel good. It makes you
look like a copycat with no mind of your own.
Someone that ain't got a mind of their
own. [ __ ] pathetic. Copycat.
>> [sighs and gasps] >> Right.
Yeah, I'm off here anyways um after
this. So, I'll be on for a little while
and that's me till January.
I might do some New Year's Eve videos
and upload them in January. Yep.
>> [clears throat]
>> Yeah, little cubby cat.
I've ordered another milkshake. Yeah. Bye-bye.
You need to get laid.
You need to get laid. You virgin. That
face is never getting laid.
>> No, I'm not staying on YouTube. I got a
life. Something that you need to get. I
only took a month of [ __ ] November
cuz I wanted to save some money. I
didn't want to waste it. I wanted to get
ready for December.
Nah, [snorts] bro. Nah.
I'll be back January when I'm back saving again. So yeah.
Oh my god. You need to sort out that
ugly virgin face,
you know. You need to sort out that that
virgin face. It's why you're still a
virgin. You need to get like [snorts]
the ugly virgin. The ugly skint virgin.
Nice try, mate. Trying to get the police
involved. You [ __ ] virgin. [ __ ] off,
you [ __ ] skint virgin.
Oh, and another thing. Stop going on
about this 13 grand daddy savings that
you shown three years ago. You ain't
even got a fucking£1,000 to your [ __ ]
name. You [ __ ] skint flint. Stop
going on about daddy savings from three
years ago that you can't show now, mate.
Daddy's life savings, mate. Daddy's life savings.
It's not going to work. Triple H, stop
it. It's not going to work, bro. I'm not
Money Man or Timmy.
Let him up. I'm scared, bro. I'm not
Money Man or Timmy. Stop it. I find it
offensive and you think I'm I'm one of
these people. Stop it, bro. I'm not
Timmy or body man. It's not going to work,
you know. No offense. Not really care if
I I did did offend them, too. But you
get what I mean. Stop it, bro. You're
talking to someone like me. You're not
talking to Monty Man or Timmy. [snorts]
Anyways, you're banned from the studio. Bye-bye, Virgin.
No, I don't because I'm not a copycat. I
don't copy the crowd. She looks like a
transgender. She's got no ass. She's got
no tits. I'm not a copycat. I've got a
mind of my own. And I'm very very very um
uh secure about my um sexuality. I'm not
a copycat. I'm not an insecure copycat
that fits in with the crowd. No, I don't
think she's fit. I think she's [ __ ]
overrated and no better than average
with a [ __ ] body.
I'm not a copycat. I'm not insecure
about my sexuality.
I don't copy people, bro. I don't copy people.
[ __ ] hell. Them people on the forum
like [ __ ] Virgin boy, they just copy each other.
They just copy copy the crowd.
Don't know why, but they do. So, yeah. Okay.
What you ask? Hi. What's up?
No, just try it. You've never tried it before. Copycats. Look.
I'm not copy cat.
I'm not a little copycat. [laughter]
You dirty [ __ ]
should be here soon.
Well, I think I'm getting a bit too
addicted to peanut butter.
>> I like peanut butter. Ma, it's tasty.
Peanut butter is lush.
Ask me that question again. Kentucky,
now I've got this picture up.
Okay. So, now I've got the picture up.
Ask me again.
Obviously, I've got the picture up now.
So, you need to ask me the question
again. Do I find them fit?
Yeah. Ask me the question again.
I've transformed into a cat.
Ask me that question again.
Yeah, she's so fit. Oh my god. Anyone
that doesn't find her attractive is
[ __ ] gay. You might as well ask me if
I'm [ __ ] You might as well ask me if
I'm [ __ ] gay, you know? No, I'm not
gay. She's so sexy. She was my lover. Oh
my god, she's the only woman in the
world. She's so [ __ ] hot. She's so
[ __ ] attractive. Even though she's
got no ass, no tits, looks like a
transgender. She's [ __ ] fit, sexy,
attractive. Only woman in the world. I
was being a copycat there.
I was being a copycat.
I'm the cat. I transformed.
But no, in reality, she's literally
nothing better than average. The people
that say otherwise or people that copy
each other that ain't got no mind of their own.
You only say it about celebrities. The copycats.
Copycats. Kentucky 5 Pete. They were copycats.
Did you see the video that I did?
Did Did you see the video? They all
copying each other. No. Minds of their own. Yay. Hobo.
Told you it was the trend 11 years ago. Copycat.
What did you think of it?
What was your honest opinion on it?
Hey. Yeah. Students are usually
copycats. Yeah. Yeah. Obviously,
but so is so is he then? So why was he
saying it then?
>> Yeah. Okay. That's the students. Okay.
So why didn't he's So why is he saying
it then? He's not a student. Uh,
he ain't a [ __ ] student. Well, well,
he was a student. Well, he was a
student. Well, he was a college student. Yeah.
Well, actually, he was actually a
college Well, he actually was a college
student at that time, actually. Saying that [snorts]
explains a lot, isn't it? >> [laughter] >> Yeah.
>> They all copy each other. Oh.
Oh. 2 minutes. It's 2 minutes away. The
milkshake. The milkshake.
>> What have you done, mama? just
Reddit is really trying to is really
doing my head in Kentucky, right? Every
time I I say that, oh, I can't find
someone on Reddit, they keep banning me,
saying I've got a victim mentality,
Kentucky. But when it's women moaning
about men, they've got no problem. I'm
sick of these double standards. I'm sick
of this bloody site banning me for no
reason. I'm just going to I'm just going
to quit it. I'm just going to quit
Reddit, I think.
Yeah, I think I'm just going to quit Reddit.
Oh, it should be here now.
I just ordered myself a little
milkshake. Oh, it should be here now.
me and these bloody milkshakes. [ __ ]
cold out here. Oh, lovely.
Yeah, I've got another one, bro. I'm out of control.
to fit in with the crowd.
[laughter] The crowd,
that [clears throat] is [ __ ] beautiful, mate.
Laney can try some. They're addicted, bro. [gasps]
Would you like to try some milkshake, mama?
>> Okay, Mom.
>> Mom is angry. Oh.
Oh, this is lovely.
It's milkshake, man. [clears throat] >> Yeah,
[ __ ] knows, mate.
I love this. Oh, this milkshake. So nice. [ __ ]
something's not here. H Wednesday.
>> Oh no. and cream. Gold be
that lovely milkshake.
>> [clears throat]
>> So addictive, man. So addictive.
I'm sure they put in a smaller thing.
>> Got it all [ __ ] out, didn't you?
Who's a copycat aside of me? I'm not a copycat.
Did you see um asylum when Ricky commented?
Did you see when Ricky commented
red [ __ ] fat virgin was straight
through rescue? Little low lives. Low lives.
Yeah, Ricky replied and [ __ ] Red Star
replied back straight away. >> Loser.
>> Proper losers, isn't it?
>> Yeah. See you later, bro.
I tell you what else is boring, man.
Having the same argument with the same
losers over and over again. That's also very boring.
That's also very, very boring.
So, it's okay to leave if you b
That's also very boring. [snorts] I can't
get no piece.
Yeah, jump on it.
I didn't know students were copycats
though in ducky. I didn't know that.
I actually generally thought he had a
mind of his own until we started that shovel coin.
I I thought he had a mind of his own
until we started that bro.
until we started that little copycat train.
>> I thought he had a mind of his own. M
>> just because you wear little virgin
clothes, little charity shop virgin
clothes. They're not going to mean
you're a lot of copycat virgin.
I think it's my [ __ ] milkshake now. Jesus Christ. M.
That was [ __ ] lush.
>> [clears throat]
>> Oh, [ __ ] beautiful. Beautiful is [clears throat]
get every last bit.
Get my money's worth, mate.
Get another one. Jesus Christ, you're
trying to make me skin like that [ __ ]
virgin or didn't you? [ __ ] £8 Mike.
Jesus [ __ ] Christ
made me my skin.
Yeah, like I said, my last live
streaming today and I'll be back early.
And like I said, if I come back in, I've
seen you people have still been on here.
I'm going to fight you all. I'm going to
start the call outs again.
I'm going to start calling you [ __ ] out
all over again.
I'm going to start [ __ ] again. Greasy.
Want to know why you can get off of
YouTube? It's [ __ ] December. It's
[ __ ] Christmas. Why are you still on YouTube?
You know what I'm like though. You know,
you know exactly what I'm like. You know
So pretend like you don't [ __ ] know. You know,
want to know why you people are still on [ __ ] YouTube.
I'm going to look back all on the all on December last.
wanted to know why all of these people
with all of this money can't get off YouTube.
It's cute, is it? See that?
Wanted to know what I meant by um what?
He said, "What do you mean by copycats?"
Like they just copy each other, try to look good. >> [sighs]
>> Why? There's other people on here but
me, lad. There's other people on here but me.
Yeah, other people on here but me.
You can watch the skin virgin.
You can watch RJ. There's other channels, lad. Yeah.
I want to see if any of these people got
a life as well. It's a little test UK
asylum because they come on here every
day calling people skin and all of this ridiculous [ __ ]
I want to know
if these people can get off of YouTube.
See what I'm saying? UK silent.
Yeah. I want to see if these people can
get off of YouTube
or if it's all they have.
You know, I'm like, mate, you know,
I want to see if these people are still
on YouTube. Oh, you know, and I want to
know why they're on YouTube. If they've
got all this money and a better life than everyone, you know.
See, most people on here are UK signing,
they're [ __ ] skin. All these people
that tried to talk about other people,
they're [ __ ] skin, mate. Trust me,
they ain't got a life. That's why
they're on here. I was just saving and
taking a break from going out, you know.
Yeah, I was just taking a break and
[ __ ] going out. Taking a break from
going out and stuff. So that's why I was on here.
You know what I mean?
>> Well, these people who they [ __ ] have
gamble UK side gamble
And yeah, I'll let you know January if
um I found anyone.
Let's face it, I probably won't. Yeah,
Joseph F is a a bad gambler.
I don't understand the point of this
Reddit though, UK side and why they keep banning me.
When I post stuff about women, they ban me.
But when I when I'm a woman posting
stuff about men, they don't seem to mind it. Weird.
[ __ ] get mad at me, bro.
Weird, isn't it?
Oh my ch.
Yeah. Why do they keep banning me? UK asylum.
I think it's just people that have been
bullied that ban people to feel
powerful. UK asylum.
They just ban people to feel powerful.
I'm not sure.
I'm not sure what your opinion is,
but anything bad said about women, they ban them.
then say that, "Oh, you need to check
your mental health. You've got a victim mentality."
But then when you're moaning about
[ __ ] men, no one minds it.
I might do that social experiment today.
No, even when I just No, they IP ban
you. Even if you don't spam it, even if
you even if you make an account and you
message someone, they ban you in a
couple of hours. They ban your IP
and they still have to do it manually. No. No.
They do it to feel powerful.
I'm going to try and do this social
experiment today again. [snorts]
My friend said,
my friend said, "Why you care about some
keyboard warriors, lol? I don't think
she's attractive. That [snorts] don't
mean I'm gay." It wasn't a keyboard
warrior. It was my ex-friend.
It wasn't a It wasn't
It was some virgin that used to be my
friend many years ago.
He kept saying about Cole, it wasn't
people, just people on the internet
cuz he didn't want to feel left out. What?
Which one, bro? What chat?
There's loads of people in here that's
obsessed with me.
[snorts] Nope. Same old. Same old.
I'm not [clears throat] going out until
next week. Thought I was going to stay
in November, bro. It's better to save
money November for December.
Oh, I can't see it.
Really? I can't see it. Yeah, it must
Yeah, it must be. Yeah. Yeah. The loser.
The fat losser that he got a life. But I
can't see it. Where is it, bro?
Yeah, the fat loser. That's him. Yeah,
the fatty fatty loser. Who we think is
Pat Mustard? Yeah, fat. So, we call him
the fat loser, the nerd.
Yeah, I'll put the link up. Yeah. I
can't see the comments, bro. What the [ __ ]
Let me see.
I can't see it.
Yes, but I can't see it. That's what I'm
trying to say to you.
Let me go on my other account and look.
Yeah, he's a proper obsessed loser. He
ain't got a life. Little bully victim.
He's been doing it for years as well.
The little bully victim.
Ain't got a life, lad.
Some fat ugly little bully victim. Some
fat ugly fingers. Yeah. Let me have a
look. Let me see.
Oh, here it is.
Yeah, I've seen it. Yeah. Oh, now I can see. Yeah.
Yeah, you're just repeating yourself.
Big nose. So, I wish I Yeah, we've seen
all of this before, bro. This is repeating.
I've just gone on it now. on my other
account. Yeah, that's just self
projection and repeating, bro. No one
cares. You fat ugly little keyboard
warrior who ain't got a life. Yeah, I've
just gone on it now. Yeah, and that's
exactly why you're blocked.
And that is exactly why you're blocked
because you're a repeating little bastard.
You ain't got no original stuff
repeating. They're so disabled that they
repeat. So autistic and disabled that
they have to repeat themselves.
Sad little virgins.
One of your sad sad little virgins.
And you can get blocked again now. So
yeah, there you go. Triple H if you're
watching this. I just saw the comment on
my other account. I couldn't see it before that. Repeating people.
So yeah, you're blocked again. Bye-bye now. Yeah, buddy.
>> Nope. Nothing.
I don't understand this red star. He's
more than happy to be a little keyboard
warrior for years and years and years.
But he will never meet anyone. Never
meet anyone. Will never go on a door.
Will never say where he is. This is
pathetic. He's a loser. He's obviously
just some big fat ugly loser that ain't
got nothing in his life. Skint loser
just like his boyfriend.
Yeah, you're so [ __ ] quick to jump on
Ricky Millin for your [ __ ] ugly
boyfriend. Mate, listen. If you want to
do something, come and meet me. And if
not, you're gonna you're gonna stay blocked.
It's not my fault. You're a fat ugly
loser that ain't got a life. Don't take
it out of me that you're born ugly. You
[ __ ] fat loser. You little bully
victim. That's it. Anyways,
I don't see it. I've got the cup blocked.
I don't see it, bro. I've got the [ __ ]
blocked. He's a repeater.
Yeah, he's a repeater. Little [ __ ] [clears throat] Yeah.
Yeah, he's a repeated little [ __ ] they got alive. Yeah.
There we go. Blocked
the same repeater it
will go attractive. Share all co is attractive. Copycat.
You little copycat.
Sad little bastard.
You don't bully me, bro. You don't bully
me. You're a keyboard warrior. You
[snorts] can't bully someone behind a
keyboard. You can bully someone in real
life, though, but you can't bully
someone behind a keyboard.
>> [clears throat]
>> Uh, I done a bet last week and I won 110 off 20.
I didn't do a bet this week. No, no,
sorry. What I'm talking about? Last
week. Yesterday I didn't do a football
bet. I done a bet last week.
Yeah, I haven't Well, I went out. I
drunk. I had a few drinks on Friday and
I played some pool only for like two hours.
But I'll be out next week. I'm dreading
it, bro. I'm [ __ ] dreading it. posting
back to the women [ __ ] Oh no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I'm not I'm
not looking forward to it, bro. I'm
dreading it. Absolutely dreading it.
Absolutely [ __ ] dreading it.
Totally dreading it, lad.
Like totally, bro. Yeah.
And then I'm gonna go out New Year's Eve
as well. I'm going out of London. I go
away yet, but
so I'll be busy. I'm from tomorrow. So yeah. Yay.
I [snorts] have to put these train tickets soon.
But yeah, I done a football bet last week.
Nah, probably not, bro.
Nah, I don't really go out much anymore, bro.
I can afford it. No problem. I've got
money. I've got I've got plenty of money
to go out and drink, but I just don't
see the point anymore much.
Just don't really see the point much,
bro, to be honest. Pointless. No point. [clears throat]
Yeah, there's not really a point, lad.
because of um
because of the women, bro. They ruin
everything. It's toxic.
Toxic [ __ ] And it's not even about
the money. It's not about the money.
Even it being it's not even about that.
I just can't be [ __ ]
Last time I went out properly was three weeks ago
and I was like, "Shit, I went out three
weeks in a row. [ __ ] that.
I went out three weeks in a row, bro.
Have I been approaching recently? Um, well,
no, considering I've told you that I've
given up. Uh, no. Maybe. Nope.
I don't even like talking about it. It's
depressing. It's toxic and it's
depressing. I don't even like talking
about it. It just annoys me. But no, I
haven't. Not for 3 weeks soon as I've
done that video.
No, no point. It will always be the same here.
Yeah, I have. Well, yeah. Last time I
tried was weeks ago, lad.
Same usual story. You get a number that
leads you on never change.
Yep. I'll be out on Saturday anyways. But yeah. Yeah. That's it.
I'll be out on uh Saturday
cuz I planned it. So,
I was playing pool last Friday, lad.
Yeah, it doesn't matter what I wear, does it?
It doesn't matter, does it, lad?
You're never going to meet anyone, so
you're always going to deal with toxic women. So
this new place I went to is £5 a
Guinness bargain. I'm used to paying £8
a Guinness. So I pay like £5 a Guinness.
So where I'm staying local, it's a
bargain. Play some pool. Do some
approaches on Saturday.
I'm dreading it. I'm [ __ ] dreading
it, bro. Absolutely dreading it.
Do you know what? I might just do one
and get one number. That's it. But I
think uh it's boring. Once you've met
one woman, you've met all of them. Once
you've met one woman, you've met them all.
You think this is toxic? Try dating
women. Ghosting. Try dating women.
You need to try dating women, lad. Home alone.
Yeah, you should try dating women if you
think this is toxic. [ __ ] hell,
that's even more toxic.
Once you've met one, you've met them all.
That's my saying. Yeah.
Um, I like Bad Center. I don't know if
you ever watched Bad Center, but watch it. Bad Center.
You should watch Bad Santa.
I like Bad Santa.
Yeah, I bought my mom Ugg boots for
Christmas. I'm not buying anything else.
That's me done. I'm not buying anything else. No.
Yeah, Bad Bad Santa is the best, bro. [ __ ]
That's hilarious as [ __ ] Did you watch it, bro?
Have you been Have you been betting on the football?
Yeah. I wonder I put 20 on I got a both
score no draw last uh last week. I got a
double both score no draw.
20 pound to 110.
Yeah, it was quite good, man.
Wish I had more in it as you always do. That's not yet.
Yeah, I was thinking of putting 170 on
two teams ghosting, but
I don't really see the point.
You might as well go on [ __ ] roulette
if you're kind of if you're putting that
[ __ ] amount of money on, you know
what I mean? But I don't play roulette.
I don't really play roulette. I don't
really I don't really gamble much, bro. Anymore
on roulette and [ __ ]
Yeah, I might do a roulette video at
some point. Three months later.
Is that okay with you grievy boss?
Maybe in January.
[clears throat] So you put 10 20 max on it.
>> What about you, Steven Howard? Would you
put 120 on two teams? No. [clears throat] No, bro. Little copycats.
The little copycats.
Red Stars. A little low life. Sat on
YouTube stalking every day. Fat ugly
bastard. And you know the thing is he
thinks he's bullying people, but all
he's doing is making a fool of himself.
That's the thing. UK asylum that he
thinks he's bullying, but all he's doing
is bullying himself.
That's all he's doing is making a fool
of himself, showing himself up. And
that's all he's doing. He's not
bothering no one. He's not bullying no
one. He's just showing himself up. And
that's what these people do. They just
show themselves up.
Yeah, he's another obsessed one. Loser.
Yeah, another loser.
All that I can't stand that Rick's mace,
you know, bro. He was on Monty's. I
can't stand him, bro. I can't stand that
Rick's mace. What's your opinion on
Grezy? I know he's been on here for
years, bro. Years.
Um, and I don't really like him for reasons.
What do you think of the whole seaside
mark thing, Grezy? He's done a runner,
isn't he? He's done a runner.
These people are [ __ ] bored with
their [ __ ] I was going to say lies,
but they ain't got a life. Look what
they've done to suicide Mark Greaves.
Have you seen what's been going on? [snorts] Mad.
Yeah. He said Chev is attractive to fit
in. Yeah. So what?
Just to fit in, bro.
Everyone knows that.
So what's your opinion, Grezy, since
you're Mark's fan?
Yep. After today, 100%. Uh
yeah. And the women's situation is still
going to be the same old even in January.
Even in January, it's going to be the
same old with them. Yeah.
So what? You don't like him anymore, Grezy? Oh, bless.
I'm on a diet from tomorrow as well cuz
of the toothies.
I want my toothies to be healthy. Virgin boy.
Sometimes I say that when I'm in a
shower, you know, UK sign. It's so catchy.
Virgin boy getting in a bed sit with
[ __ ] no bed, no money in it. No bed,
with absolutely no [ __ ] bed, no
[ __ ] money in it.
Imagine you done a correct score for
three teams and you put 20 pound on it.
Oh, matey, you'll be [ __ ] rich, won't you?
Correct score. I might do that, you
know, one day. Flow 32 the other one
2-1. I might do on Saturday. I might
predict a correct score.
Oh, [ __ ] hell.
[ __ ] [snorts] me, bro. [ __ ] me.
I reckon I can do it, bro. I reck I
reckon I could. I reckon I could.
depending on who they're playing. I
think I could.
That is big money, bro.
Like 32 2 one.
I'm going to really try and like predict
a uh correct score, bro.
I have to see the lineup first. I reckon
I could do it. I think I could do it.
You'll be you.
That's a lot of money, bro.
A lot of money. Probably over two grand for 20.
Probably even more than that.
What are you saying, Triple H?
You want to be a little copycat for
Saturday? Do you want to be a little copycat?
want to be a little copycat.
Do you want to be a little copycat?
I'm going to tell my mom that I'm going
to try and predict a correct score.
Uh depending on who the [ __ ] are playing.
Yeah. You won't be saying that if it
comes in though, will you?
You won't be saying that if it comes in.
What is it?
You won't be saying that if it comes in, mate.
It is hard though. Depend. It is. It is hard.
But I'm sure people have won though. I'm
sure people have won.
I reckon you could do it on one team. I
reckon on one team you could do it. On
one team. I reckon you definitely could do it.
I'm sure people have won though. It I'm
sure they have.
I'm sure people have. Lad,
I might have a gun Frankie on Saturday.
There's a there's a machine in the pub.
Swap machine in the pub.
Uh that that session is going to be for
free. I think that session and about a
million other sessions is going to be
for free, mate.
That and about a million others. Yeah.
No, I don't go to the gym.
You're right, Indigo. Did you see the
video that I put up [ __ ] yesterday?
Pathetic, isn't it?
Told you. Told you it was a trend. You
didn't believe me, did you?
[snorts] I told you it was a trend.
Nope. But you wouldn't believe me, would
you? I need to change his avatar now.
Nope. You didn't believe me.
I like this picture.
Yeah, I like this picture. My favorite.
It's my favorite picture. [gasps] >> [snorts]
>> No, the video.
The one that you commented on.
Yeah, it's cute, isn't it? It was
actually 7:30. Griezy, I weren't going
to let them [ __ ] win.
I stayed up, didn't I, Grezy? 110 quid. Yep.
Yeah. It was the principle, mate. I
didn't need 110 [ __ ] quid. No. Yep. Bless you.
[ __ ] bunch of copycats.
Bunch of [ __ ] copycats
doing that right.
No [ __ ] minor there.
Don't matter what she said to me on the
train. I put her in her [ __ ] place, Grezy.
I put her in her [ __ ] place. And the
white knight's head got crushed. [laughter]
What a lovely start to the morning, isn't it?
What a lovely start to the video to
sorry to the morning's video. To the
I I want you to see it, Grezy and Triple
H. I just don't want I just don't want
the Virgin to see it. The skint one
and Red Star. I just don't want them seeing it. [snorts] Yeah.
Yeah. I had an argument with a woman on
um the train last week.
No, I didn't record that bit. No, you
heard it though. You can actually hear
it. you. No, I was recording. You can
hear it, but I wasn't recording him
because I was sat down, you know.
But you could hear it go like you could
hear it go. Yeah.
Yeah. No, I'm not uploading it cuz I
don't want these people seeing it.
The [ __ ] [ __ ] red star. The fat ugly
man that can't get off for YouTube.
Sausage finger fat ugly man. I'm not uploading it. Nah,
I've got it as well. It's on my other
channel. I'm not uploading it, lad. Nope.
If you want to see it, you can see it in private.
So yeah, that's that [ __ ] virgin.
They're always watching Indigo. That
[ __ ] virgin red star. That [ __ ]
virgin's always watching.
And the other virgin
[ __ ] pack of virgins
when they they they went for [ __ ]
Ricky Millington earlier. They went for
[ __ ] Ricky Millington earlier.
[ __ ] pack of virgins.
Leave Ricky alone, you pack of virgins. Yeah. [snorts]
What was that?
See, I could go to the bank, right, and
get money out and show a load of 50s, but
we all know what happens when you show
money on here, mate. They all run away.
So, we don't want people running away.
You know, the community is
almost already dead.
We don't want them [ __ ] running away
now, do we?
You know, [ __ ] running away in that. Yeah.
You're a little copycat.
You little copycat. You little copycat. Meow.
Yeah. I told her that she looks like a
crackhead. I said, "Why don't you go
look in the mirror, you crackhead? Bear
in mind, I was [ __ ] half asleep.
I'm mad, you know.
She will call attractive. If you don't
like her, you're gay.
Copycat. [ __ ] off.
[ __ ] off, you copycat.
[ __ ] off, you little copycat.
All right, Indigo. Why was [ __ ]
nonsleg saying that if I don't find
shovel co attractive, I'm gay? What a
weird thing to say.
You You can't deny she's attractive.
You can't deny that she's
You can't deny she's attractive.
She didn't say I was homeless. She
No, she didn't.
She didn't say I look homeless. She
trying to say you look like a [ __ ] I
said, "Have you seen yourself? You
crackhead. Look in the [ __ ] mirror,
you little crackhead." That's what I
said to her. She didn't say I looked homeless.
You can't deny she's attractive.
[ __ ] virgin. [snorts] Absolute virgin.
No, she didn't say that. Anyways, why
are we still talking about this anyways, bro?
That train thing was [ __ ] last week.
Why the [ __ ] are we still talking about
it? You're never going to see it cuz I
don't want these little [ __ ] bongos seeing it.
The [ __ ] red star, the fat ugly virgin, you know?
No, she never said that. Anyways, we're
not talking about this anymore, bro.
This was last week.
This was last week, lad.
Yeah, he would. That fat ugly bongo
That fat ugly little virgin low life
would. The skin little low life,
mate. That little skint virgin fat ugly
low life would say that.
That [ __ ] M man would show that, bro.
You know what makes me laugh right is
that they they're on here saying about how
about we we need to show them receipts.
We need to show them receipts, bro.
Yeah. We need to show these people
receipts for jeans for trainers. And I'm
thinking, hold on a minute. How many
times have we asked people at Red Star
to show their face and they can't cuz
they're [ __ ] ugly. So if you're not
going to show us your ugly face, we're
not going to show you anything. Like you
have more than one person on here,
right, that will say, "Show us your jean
receipt. Show us your training receipt.
Show us this receipt."
Which I've got all the receipts cuz I
paid for them online. We don't need to
prove ourselves to you fat ugly little
mongos. We We don't get out of bed,
right, and our goal is to show ugly
people that never made it receipts of
what we [ __ ] bought, you know? [ __ ]
that. Especially when you don't even
show your [ __ ] faces cuz you're [ __ ] ugly.
These [ __ ] ugly bongos.
And anyways, I'm off in [ __ ] until
January as well.
I wonder if these people will get a life
when I'm gone. I wonder if they will get
a life, man.
Virgin Red Star, fat ugly man with fat
ugly fingers. Have you seen it, bro?
He's fat ugly fingers when he showed
that bum change. When he showed his
little benefits. Yeah. Did you see his
face, lad? Sorry. Did you see his
fingers? Some big fat ugly fingers. I
told you they're all fat no lives on
here. I told you, bro. They're fat
losers. Fat ugly life losers. You didn't
believe me, did you?
Yeah. Well, how would he know that? Did
he see the video?
Well, that's impossible because he
didn't see the video.
Well, he didn't see the video. Only I've
got the video. So, yeah.
No, she didn't own me at all. I own her
and I also own the white knight. I'm the
one that's seen the video, mate. No one
else has seen it. And this is why I
don't show it because you all make up
stuff. This is why I don't bother with
you people on here cuz you make up
stuff. Even when you're proven wrong,
you make up stuff. And that's why I went
against it. That is exactly why I will
never put anything on here ever again
because you will make up stuff. Hell to
the [ __ ] no. I am not putting a video up.
I am not putting no video up. Stop
asking me cuz you're wasting your time.
I'm not putting it up. I'm not putting a
video up because of what happened last
time. It's not going up. So stop asking
me. It's never going up. The video is
never ever ever 100% never going up
after that with the bouncer and that
thing in Weather Spoons. I will never
put a video up again.
Absolutely never. Not after last time
when you kept making excuses for the
bouncer and you synd
to to let pe people that are buyers see
it. It's never happening, bro. It is never happening.
It is never ever [ __ ] happening. So
stop asking me
after last time. [ __ ] no. You make
excuses, you biased little bongs.
And I got into [ __ ] with [ __ ] LT
because he's another one biased. So
never again. I'm not putting no videos
up of that kind of stuff. So,
no [ __ ] way, bro.
So, that's not happening.
No, I'm leaving YouTube until January.
Yeah, I'm leaving YouTube until January.
Anyways, I'm gone. Yeah. So, see you in January. Yeah.