Yo,
what the [ __ ]
is up with this, bro?
[ __ ] things got [ __ ] bro. I said I
was coming up here after today. Yeah, so
I thought I'd come live again.
Yeah, I gave um Greavves full permission
to uh share the video because yeah, why
not? I mean, these people are always
going to make up stuff no matter what.
I've even seen the comments. They just
make up stuff either way. They're
they're [ __ ] disabled.
I did say after today though, to be honest,
yep, I gave Greasy full permission to share it
cuz it is funny to be honest. These
people always make excuses cuz they're
[ __ ] disabled on here, bro. So, I was
like, "Yeah." And I said I was coming
off after today. So, I'm sticking to my
word after today. So yeah,
I love how they make excuses. I love the
excuses, bro. That's why I didn't mind
him putting it up. They always make
excuses thinking that someone's beat me
when they [ __ ] well haven't. So yeah,
it's entertaining to be honest.
They're [ __ ] disabled. This is why
I'm coming off here anyways for a month
because of these disabled people
creating the same atmosphere every day.
These little mongos, they're [ __ ] boring, bro.
Boring little sad life losers.
What makes me laugh though is that these
people try to talk about me, bro. Yeah.
When they're sat there, no woman, no
life, no money, never been with a woman,
probably still virgins, and they're
talking about me. Women hate you. That's
why you're still a virgin. That's why
you're [ __ ] sat on YouTube. Can't
even get a woman. Never been with a
woman. Of all the years I've been on
this community with the amount of women
that I've been with, we have never seen
any of these people with a woman ever.
We've never seen them any of these
people with a woman cuz they can't get
them to. They're too ugly. And that's
why they sit on their self projecting
every day borrowing little low lives.
That's that, bro. Yeah. I'm still
sticking to my [ __ ] word. Yeah,
fat ugly little low lives. Little
virgins sat there. Little virgins. No
woman, womanless trying to talk about
other people. At least I'm not a [ __ ]
virgin like most of these people in this [ __ ] community.
At least I'm not sat there little
virgins that's never been with a [ __ ]
woman that can't take a single day off
of YouTube because it's all they have.
And I'm not going to I'm not going to
not say anything because it's the truth.
It is the [ __ ] truth. And you know
what, right after today, I ain't coming
back until January because I want to
laugh my ass off when I come back,
right? In January, I'm going to laugh my
[ __ ] ass off when I see the same
people on YouTube that can't get off it.
You know, it'll be it'll give me the
biggest laugh ever. So, I'm definitely
sticking to what I'm saying, bro. 100%. Yeah.
I'm not going to I'm not going to not do
that, but 100% I'm going to do that. You know, these people
sit here and try and talk yet. They're
virgins and never been with a woman. And
they're talking about women hating other
people and they're sat there little
virgins, little virgins on YouTube.
That's been proven that they can't take
a day off of YouTube. And I will prove
it again when I come back next month. I
will prove that these people can't live
without YouTube and everything that they
say is about their own lives, you know?
And I'll do it again, bro. Done it
before and I'll happily do it again. Not
a [ __ ] problem.
Yeah, that's that, bro. It's It's not a problem. Yeah.
It's like fantasy stories. The guy is a
[ __ ] virgin. He's never been with a
woman, never had sex, never been with a
woman. And he comes on here trying to
tell people about women hating people.
And he's a [ __ ] little Northern Irish
little [ __ ] virgin that's never been
anywhere near a woman. Bit like 95% of
the people on this [ __ ] community.
That's the thing that makes me [ __ ]
die. They're all virgins. All women hate
them. They've never even had sex. At
least I can sit there and say I've
actually had sex. They can't. They're
all virgins on our
Yeah. Facts, lad.
I I said to agree with you, you can put
it up there if you want because the
matter the thing is is whether you're
right or you're wrong, they're always
going to make excuses.
Like it doesn't really matter. That's
why I thought, well, you might as well
you might as well put it up because
either way, they're always going to make
excuses. That's just them. They're disabled.
But what I don't understand is why do
these fat, ugly, wrinkly virgins sit and
say that you're going to be single forever?
Bro, these people have been single.
They've been virgins and and they tried
to talk about other people. Uh, if you
actually heard what I said, I said that
from today, I'm not going to be on
YouTube from today after today. So
before you try and write sarcastic
stuff, I actually said after today if
you actually listen properly, which is
tomorrow. Yeah. Yeah. I know it's a
sarcastic joke. I know. I know you're
trying to be sarcastic, but if you
actually listen properly, I said that
I'm, you know, after today.
You know what I mean? They don't get to
me. They're little fat ugly bongos. They
don't get to me. These people don't get
to me, bro. They've been doing this same
[ __ ] for years. They These little fat
ugly little [ __ ] life losers don't get
to me. They get to themselves. That's
why they're on here every day cuz they
ain't got a life. They don't get to me, bro.
These [ __ ] fat ugly bongos don't get
to me. These little life loser, little virgins.
They talk about women hating me, bro.
Women have been hating them.
They're sat there. Little virgins can't
even get laid. Can't even get off of
YouTube. And they talk about women
hating me when they're virgins. Madness,
you know. I'm not angry. I'm just
telling you what they are, bro.
I'm not I'm telling you what they are.
They're sad, skinned little virgins that
ain't got no life. You have to be cool,
bro. You know what I'm saying?
Yeah. You have to be cool to be [ __ ] kind.
Oh, fun fact, by the way. Um, I was half
I was half asleep on that train and I
was just like, "Shut up. You're boring.
You're boring. People's half asleep.
You're [ __ ] boring, bro. Boring."
And someone's [ __ ] ear when someone's
half asleep. Oh, did you hear the man's
head get crushed? By the way, you must
have heard the doors in his head get
crushed. [ __ ] idiot.
Yeah, bro. Don't worry. Another another
thing like that's going to happen again.
You know, it's bound to happen again
with the way society is. You know, it
will happen again.
It might even happen next week. Who knows?
You don't know. No.
Me. That's funny as [ __ ]
This is the biasness on here, bro. This
is what I'm saying with the biasness on here.
But I don't care. That's what I said to
Grezy. I said to Grezy, "Here you go.
Watch it. You can pull up if you want."
I thought you might as well pull it up.
You've seen it. You might as well put it
up now cuz they're always going to make excuses. So,
none of your business.
That's none of your business.
And there is no search.
Do do I I mean just listen to that
question that you just wrote. It doesn't
even make sense.
That doesn't make any sense what you
wrote. What do you think?
What the [ __ ] do you think that What do
you think, bro?
Yeah, that white knight madness. [clears throat]
[gasps and sighs] Anyways,
yeah, I gave up weeks ago. They're all
the same. Yeah, I gave up [ __ ] weeks ago.
Yeah, once you've met one, you've met
one all you you met them all.
Yeah, I gave up weeks ago.
Three weeks ago.
Yeah. No one cares about that. That's repeating.
He was sing hard yet she was an ugly
[ __ ] The guy. She was an ugly [ __ ]
and she started it and I told her about
herself back and then he's trying to
Bye-bye. And then he's trying to get
involved. And then he And then he got
his head crushed in the door. And then
he got his head crushed in the door.
He got his head crushed in the door. Oh
wow. It's on Greavves channel. His head
got crushed in the door. We're trying to
s. [ __ ] You couldn't make it up, bro.
What the [ __ ] [clears throat]
Oh, when will these simps ever re When
will they realize that these women are
never going to sleep with them?
It's mad. Mad.
Uh, I want to I'm doing a bro.
Was there must have been the burger.
Must have been the burger. Ma'am, I
think she's jealous of my burger. She
might have just been hungry. Geezy, I
think she was just jealous of the burger.
She didn't She didn't think I was going
to talk up to her, bro. What the [ __ ] do
you think this is? I'm not a [ __ ]
bro. It actually started from a It
actually started from a dirty look.
Well, it actually started from a dirty look.
It actually started from a dirty look.
So I well actually I I actually started
it. I actually started it actually.
I think I actually did Greasy to be
fair. I said, "What?" I said, "What you looking at?"
No, I didn't stink. It was Lush. I think
she was just jealous.
You still ain't got a life, Dusty.
You still ain't got a job. You still
skin lad. Yeah. She was mixed race. Yeah,
but I don't care grievy putting up. I
gave him full permission.
Yep. Cuz I don't give a [ __ ] what these
people say on here, bro. They're life's losers.
When are you going to get a job, Dusty?
You're behind like a million and one
accounts. When are you going to get a
job? When are you going to get a life?
You know it's December tomorrow. You've
been [ __ ] doing this for bloody years.
I can't believe the people on Greavves
channel. [ __ ] fat, ugly single
people. Women hate me, then women
definitely [ __ ] hate you virgins.
If they hate me, nature girl, they
definitely definitely definitely hate
them. Leaving them [ __ ] sexist
virgins. Think about it, bro.
fat, ugly, single, wrinkly people
calling you single, mad,
but yet they've never been with a woman,
never kissed a woman, have had sex with
a woman, and they talk about you.
Hilarious, bro. Hilarious. Uh yeah.
Still haven't anyone reply? No one's
replied on a Reddit thing yet. Uh, Grezy.
This experiment is going to take a while. [snorts]
Yeah. And I And I called her a crackhead.
Yeah. And I said, "Have you seen
yourself? If you look like a crackhead.
Yeah, that's not what happened. Anyway,
no one cares because you people, you
little nerds always make up stuff. So
that's why I said to Grey, you can put
it up if you want.
No one cares. No one's No one cares. And
I told her she looks like a crackhead
and go look in the mirror. A crackhead.
That's worse than a [ __ ] No one cares.
You people always make up stuff. And I
[ __ ] well hope. One second. One
second. Please do not tell me this is
true. One second.
Please. This is not the same person. Let me look.
I think you know where I'm going with this. Please no.
Please tell me this is not the same Big
Cheese from [ __ ] eight years ago,
mate. Cuz if so, okay, let me let me let
me tell you how pathetic you actually
are. Yeah. Because you have been on here
doing this to Ant-Man
about seven, eight years ago
and you're still on here doing this. And
guess where Ant-Man is? And guess what Antman's doing
whilst you're still on YouTube doing the
same thing? Do you remember when you
done this to Ant-Man? Uh years ago,
about seven, eight years ago. You
remember? Must have been seven, eight
years ago. Seven, eight years ago.
And you're still doing this, bro.
And where do you think this guy is? Come
on, bro. It's [ __ ] silly now.
Yeah, he just probably made a new
account. Yeah, I think he made a new
That is [ __ ] pathetic.
Yeah, I'm a virgin even though I proved
I've had sex. Yeah, good one, bro.
See, you just called me a virgin even
though I proved I've had sex. Do you see
why people don't care about what you
little virgins say? What you what you
little low lives say?
That's why no one cares what you little
virgins say. No one gives a [ __ ] about
what you little virgins say. You're all
sad little low lives that can't get off
of YouTube. That's exactly why I said to
Adman uh sorry to um Greavvesy that you
can put the video up. No one cares about
these little virgins.
Bro, you're so ugly that even if you
tried paying for it, you still wouldn't
get it. That's how ugly you are. You're
that ugly and disabled that even if you
wanted to pay for it, you'd still get
rejected. That's how ugly you are.
Right. [ __ ] me, bro. You people are
[ __ ] That's why I said to Greg you
just put the video up, bro. It's fine.
These people would always make up stuff.
They're sad [ __ ] old hopeless
individuals. Low lives.
We'll see when I'm back in January how
many of these people was was off of
YouTube for a month like me.
Yeah, we're we're going to see how many
of these people was off of YouTube for a
month like me. Yeah, I'm going to go on every channel
and I don't want to see any of these
people on here, mate.
Yeah, rejected. I've never been rejected
by an escort. So, no, no, no, no. That's
That's you. Even if you tried paying,
you still would get rejected. That's how
bad it is.
Calling me a virgin when I've proved
I've had sex. You're laughable. You're
laughable, bro. Laughable.
I mean, I've put a porn video out there
and you're still calling me a virgin.
I've been in women's beds and you're
still calling me a virgin, bro. It's laughable.
And you don't actually realize that
you're just embarrassing yourself when
you're saying this stuff. You don't
realize that you're just embarrassing
yourself. You're making yourself look
stupid. But no one on here is going to
tell you that. But it is very, very stupid.
I'm a virgin, but I've proved I've had sex.
Right. How How do you work that one out?
I've proved I've had sex. I've been in
multiple women's beds and had one night
stands, but apparently I'm a virgin.
How do you work this one out?
How how how do you work this one out?
Out of curiosity. Yeah.
My life is YouTube.
Why don't I fight these people? Because
none of these people will tell me where
where they are or where they live.
I mean, they're the [ __ ] They're the
ones that know where I live and still
don't do nothing but be a keyboard
warrior all their life. So they're
they're the [ __ ] They're the
[ __ ] They're the bully victims.
They're the fat ugly people. They're the
low lives. They're everything. I don't
know where they live. They know where I
They know where I [ __ ] live. Like
I've like I said a million times, if I
knew where that fantasy stories lived,
I' i'd go on his [ __ ] door 100%. I'd
go on that [ __ ] store. V fantasy
stories. I would go on their door and
give them a good old hiding. A good old
[ __ ] fashioned hiding. Especially
that [ __ ] fantasy stories.
Anyone ever finds his address, bro, send
it to old Peter belly. I'll go on the [ __ ] store.
[ __ ] Northern Irish [ __ ] little
[ __ ] that ran away from [ __ ] Pat
Mustard. [ __ ] little [ __ ] boy.
Little far eyes. Little [ __ ] [sighs]
Little [ __ ] four eyes,
you know, like I did prime. It's
repeating again, bro. No one cares. It's
repeating. Come up with something
original. Now, someone someone asked
Greavesy is um how did this community die?
How How did this community die? Because
of these repeating bastards. That's how
it died. Because of the repeating bastards.
Duh. I mean, they killed it themselves
with a repeating
Yeah, I filled my pants, bro. It's repeating.
It's repeating. Stop it. It's boring
now. It's repeating. [snorts]
You know, I don't even look the [ __ ]
same in that video. It's repeating. Come
out with some new content.
Some new content. Some new comebacks.
[ __ ] weirdos on this community.
[ __ ] absolute weirdos. So,
uh, involved from what it originally was. Yeah,
it's because of the repeating. [snorts]
These people have been saying the same
stuff, bro, since before you was on
here. I think me and you maybe come at
the same I I come on here in 2018, 2019. Uh,
I knew about Timmy since 2016, but I
wasn't on it until about 2018 cuz I used
to watch like the gambling videos Timmy
used to put up.
So 2016, but I think I come on in 2018
like as in made an account and there's
been the same repeating people since
then. Your skin, get a job. It's just repeating.
That's why a lot of people don't come on here anymore.
We're the same age, I think. Yeah.
You're a few months older than me. So, I
come here. Yeah. [snorts]
Yeah. It was 2018 cuz I was 21. Yeah. I
come in when I was 21. So,
um yeah, to white knights, not about my
experiences because people dismiss my
struggles. So, I won't be doing that.
But yeah, I want to know why these white
knights defend women,
bro. People don't need to prove
themselves to you.
Uh, no. The neighbor didn't run me out
of my mother's house at all. At all. Um,
that never happened. I'm not explaining
the story again. It's repeating. I've
already explained it before, so I'm not
explaining it again. Uh, no, they
[ __ ] did not. Um, but anyways, keep
making stuff up again. What if I'm not
about it? Why don't you meet me tomorrow
then? Okay, cool. All of this repeating,
why don't you repeat? You know what I'm
saying? Daz, Daz, Daz, listen, listen,
listen. Nobody, let me tell you this,
bro. And I want you to really understand
this. Yeah. Nobody needs to prove
themselves to you or any other person.
Yeah. People do not need to prove
themselves to you little weasels. Cuz
every single time people have proved
themselves to you, people, you make up
[ __ ] time and time again. People have
shown more money than you. They've shown
more women than you. They've shown a
better life than you. And you still sit
there and talk [ __ ] So, at the end of
the day, bro, nobody needs to um nobody
needs to [ __ ] um prove themselves to
you. And the neighbor thing I'm not
explaining again because I've already
explained it. So, you might want to open
your ears. You just make up stuff continuously. You know,
I don't show up. Well, you know where I
live, don't you, big man? Well, you know
where I live apparently, don't you, big
man? Stop with the excuses. You're not
about it. You're a little keyboard
warrior. You've been on here doing this
to Ant-Man 7 years ago. Stop it. It's
embarrassing now. And nobody needs to
prove themselves to you people. I was on
[ __ ] this account. Yeah, Greavvesy. I
was on this account, lad. Yeah, I was on
this account. That's why your [ __ ] ever
made videos about me and my family. We
will get hurt, bro. Give me you and your
family and I'll make videos about you. I
will make videos about you and your
family and everyone knows where I live.
I I'm willing. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
I'm willing to put this to the test. You
give me your family and I'll put them
all over the internet and I'll give you
where I live. Let's see what you're
about, big man. I'm willing I'm willing
to test your theory. Come on. Let's do
it right here, right now. Right here.
Right now. I'm willing to to put your
family everywhere and I'll tell you
where I live and I'll stand outside that
door and see what you're about. Stop it.
You're not about it. Yeah, you're a fat,
ugly little nerd like the rest of them. And anyways,
they're telling me you need to show
receipts of this and that. Bro, no one
needs to prove themselves to you fat
ugly people. I don't know where I don't
know where you you've got this from that
people wake up every day and need to
prove themselves to a bunch of fat ugly
people. Like I don't know where like
Greavves I don't know where they got
that idea from. Like people don't need
to prove themselves to [ __ ] you ugly
people. They ain't got no life. Like bro
and and also we have proved ourselves to
you before. Um you know because we just
done it anyways and you make excuses.
Why would anyone prove themselves to you
fat ugly low lives that can't get off
YouTube? Now I know I'm hitting the
nerves right now because it's it's the truth.
Telling people that they they need to
show receipt for [ __ ] You cheeky
bastards. You cheeky bastards about
people need to show receipts for stuff.
How about you suck my dick? How about
you suck my big dick about people need
to show you receipts? Why don't you show
your face? Like people have been asking
you a million times, show your face, Red
Star. Show your face, Clint. Show your
face, some other [ __ ] You've been asked
numerous times to show your face and I
could prove why you people do what you
do every day. And then you won't do it.
And then you think people need to prove
um proof purchase to you. [ __ ] off,
mate. You're having a wank, you silly [ __ ] Cheeky bastards.
Nobody needs to prove anything to you. You sados.
You know, you little life loser sados.
You show your face and I'll show you my
receipts for the things that I bought. Yeah,
sad little bastards. Yeah, apparently I
lose I use Kana Greaves.
Yeah, that will always happen though.
Dusty white knights everywhere. White knights
trying to look good for women. Pathetic autism
trying to look good for women yet women
don't like them and they will never
sleep with them. mad.
Yeah. About being the bigger person. I
was like, "No, she said something to me.
I will say something back." No, no, no,
no. There's no being the bigger person.
So, but yeah.
Yeah. Well, the person wasn't an escort.
It was your mom. Don't talk about your
mom like that, Big Cheese. The person
wasn't an escort. It was your mom. And
she likes my dick very much. Thank you
very much. You cheeky bugger. It wasn't
an escort. It was your [ __ ] mom.
Yep. No, bro. It was It was your [ __ ] mom.
It was your mom, bro. It was your [ __ ] mom.
Yeah. Don't Don't call your mom an
escort, bro. It's not nice to talk about
your mom like that. Yeah.
Oh, look who's live. Tony.
So, what are we doing next year anyways? People,
you going to, you know, stop repeating
yourselves or what? What are you going to do?
You got to come up with some new
insults. What are we doing, bro? What
are we doing? Yeah.
I actually started it though cuz I I
said to her, "What the [ __ ] you looking
at?" And then she pretended she couldn't
hear me. I said, "No, what the [ __ ] you
looking at? Don't look at me like that,
bro. Who the [ __ ] do you think you are?
No one's looking at me like that, mate.
And you know what the thing is,
Greavves? These what it is with these
women, right, is that they're not used
to people talking back to them.
You know, they're not used to people
talking back to them
because they're so used to simps and
white knights. So, they don't think
anyone's ever going to like talk back to them.
mind your own [ __ ] business,
you know? Yeah. So, they they're not
used to it, you know?
And then my man got his head crushed in
the door for sticking up to some [ __ ]
ugly stranger that's never going to
sleep with him.
And then he said, "I can get Nick for
it." Really? So, he really asked the
police that if I can get Nick for
standing my ground on a train. I don't think so.
See, at least the other guy, he wasn't a
s. He was telling her to stop, then
telling me to stop. And he said, "I've
had enough of both of you." So, I mean,
the last one actually was just like,
"Yeah, but this that guy was Yeah.
Clearly a white knight." Clearly white knight him.
Must be some form of autism or something
their dad taught them or something. Yeah.
I don't know.
Top secret. Don't tell him, Grezy. It's
a top secret.
And she probably knew somebody was going
to interfere as well.
She probably knew someone was going to
interfere. What do you think, Grezy?
She probably knew that either way that
like, you know, you know what I'm
saying? Like it's a [ __ ] like Yeah.
And then the other one I said, "You're a [ __ ] loser."
Did you hear that one as well, Grezy?
I don't know why they think they can
talk to talk back uh talk to people like
that and then think that people are not
going to talk back to them.
I don't know why they're surprised when
people start talking back to them though, Greezy.
It's happened as well like when I was
doing Uber as well.
Yeah, she had a bad day. They have a bad
day, they're entitled and think they can
start talking talking to you and then
when you talk back, they don't like it.
Yeah, she was she was she was mixed race.
Everyone was looking, mate. Everyone was
looking. Everyone was looking, mate.
Everybody was looking. about 8:00
8:00 in the morning. [laughter]
Everyone was looking by Dusty.
Why did you say Nleg said that if you
don't find Chev attractive, you're gay?
Why did Why did he say that again?
I was having a burger.
You said something about it before, but
I forgot. What did you say?
Yeah, it's called a burger van.
Yeah, it's called a burger van, bro.
It's open 24 hours. This is London, not
where you live.
Yeah. Yeah. And you know KFC opens at
9:30 as well. Yep.
Why did you say, Dusty, that he said it again? [laughter]
He's a little copycat.
He's a little copycat. He's [ __ ]
ugly. That Sher Cole ugly with no ass
and no tits. And I'm not gay. I'm just
not a copycat.
I just don't, you know, [laughter]
to be in the crowd.
Oh, I love it. I love it, mate.
I might make some eggs.
Oh, the picture. You like the picture?
What is it with you in that bloody picture?
Oh, I don't have it on this one.
I don't have it on this one, lad. Yeah.
I might make myself some eggs. Greasy.
Is that right?
I made myself some eggs.
Can I make myself some eggs, Luigi?
No, I'm just going to have this tango.
Oh, you can't
lady open my bloody tango. Bloody [ __ ]
You open it, you [ __ ] [ __ ]
[ __ ] open it, man.
[ __ ] annoying. Why are you opening my
[ __ ] tango? If you wanted it, you
should just had it
fitting in with a crab.
Mom, why'd you open my drink? I said if
you wanted to tangle, you said you
didn't want it.
It's I'm still using your phone.
I'm using the phone for edit. Dirty [ __ ]
Dirty [ __ ] Did it?
Did I? Thank you, boss. Thank you.
>> Oh, you did say students like to copy
each other to don't you? And he was a
student. He was a college student.
Dustin was was a college student.
Pay my phone bill. I've already paid my
phone bill. Why don't you mind joining [ __ ] business?
Huh? Why don't you mind joining business?
>> I was half asleep on that [ __ ] train
as well, mate. Half asleep like I am now.
All right, go. You can't deny she's
attractive. I'm a copycat. No, no. Copy cat.
Women are such hypocrites, bro.
Just like you can't live without YouTube
in your 40s. Isn't that right, lad?
Bit like you. You can't live without
YouTube in your 40s.
Yeah. You You can't live without YouTube.
That's all you got.
YouTube and projections. All you got, lad. [ __ ] You [ __ ]
No one's comment. No one's
commented when I said I can't find a boyfriend.
I said I can't find a boyfriend. Grievy.
No one's and I pretended to be a woman.
No one's commented yet.
>> Strange. Let me try and start with a man one then
should get some replies.
I'm really trying to do this experiment
but it's very hard with these loser mods.
I'm doing a little experiment, Dusty.
I'm doing an experiment. Um pretending
to be a woman moaning about men and
being a man moaning about women. And we
just want to see what the what the um I
have left a while. It's been like an
hour, nothing. Um, and we want to see
what the different what the responses
are just to see if it's a gender issue. [clears throat]
Yeah. I just want to see if it's a
gender issue, Dusty. Hopefully, it's
not. Have I seen Greavves video? H.
No. Even though I'm the one that
recorded it and made it. No, I've never
seen it. No. Any good? Any good, mate?
No. No. Good, mate. No. No. Right.
So, Dusty, do you reckon it's a gender issue? Cuz
I told her she looks like a crackhead.
Uh because I told her she looks like a
[ __ ] crackhead and she's boring. I'm struggling to
You're little You're a Mike. You're
little Lord J's bum cham, aren't you? I
unblocked you earlier. Yeah, you're a
you're Lord J's bum cham, aren't you?
I'll try. One sec.
Right now I'm I'm pretending.
One second. Hopefully, Dusty, it's not a gender thing.
And I really want to be wronged and I
hope it's not a gender thing.
What's your opinion, Dusty? Do you
reckon the replies will be different or the same?
Hopefully, when I'm a woman complaining
about men, they're going to tell me that
I'm I've got a bad mindset and stuff,
you know. Fingers crossed I get the same,
I couldn't think of more things to say
to be honest. Um,
but I was just half asleep.
See, they don't like it when you tell
them back. It's like when I was in Uber.
This woman was like, "Oh, you should be
here." I said, "I'll go where the [ __ ] I
want." And then she started running up
her mouth. I had to pop I I pot the bike
up on the stand. I said, "Come here and say that
[ __ ] stupid little [ __ ]
You know, somebody was doing it as well
um to someone else in Liverpool Street
the other day. The guy was like, "Red
light, red light, red light." I would
have told him to [ __ ] off. He wasn't
saying it about me, but obviously he was
saying it to a cyclist. You know, these
people just learn to mind your own [ __ ] business.
Yeah, I think she was hungry to be honest.
mate. Them people saying that are
single. They're single little virgins,
mate. I've seen the comments, bro. All
of these people that say that are single
virgins themselves. They've never even
kissed a woman. So, whatever they say, I
don't really give a [ __ ] They're just
self-projected. These people are single.
They're fat, ugly, single, and they're virgins.
No one cares what these little bongos
say that don't fit into society.
Projecting little fat ugly people. How
many women have you seen me with? And
how many women have you seen them with?
None. So, end the [ __ ] story. They're
just little self-p projecting fat ugly little virgins.
So, no one gives a [ __ ] about what these
what they say.
Remember [sighs and snorts]
Grey Peter belly doesn't know where to turn.
It's a troll. that okay,
bro. But we know why they're spiteful.
Because they're fat, ugly little low
lives. They hate themselves. They're
hopeless. So they they they they hate
other people that are better than them,
younger than them.
They hate themselves. They're [ __ ]
fat, ugly people that hate themselves.
Like fantasy stories, VR, they hate
themselves. They're fat, ugly, bro. Like
I've said a million times to these
people, put your cameras on. Put your
camera on and show your face. And they
won't do it. They won't do it.
Cuz what I'm saying is the truth. They
can't put their cameras on and show
their face cuz they're [ __ ] fat ugly
people. [ __ ] fat loss that got [ __ ]
all in their life.
It's easy to get into a fight,
especially when you're drunk as well.
The worst is when you're drunk as well,
when you're coming back.
Yeah, they're fat, ugly, little life's losers, bro.
I'm [ __ ] hungry.
I fancy some
I might get some biscuits. Might have
some biscuits. Is that all right? Have
some biscuits. Greasy.
I fancy some crisps.
Okay. Okay. I am being a bit of a copycat.
I fancy some of them fres. Um, have you
ever had fres? The bacon freses. Greasy.
Oh, they're so they're banging, bro. They're banging.
Oh, bro. Every shop near me is closed, I think.
Other than one. presents, bro.
I don't think they they might not. But
>> I'm [ __ ] hung
these presents, bro. Not boondocking copycat. Copycat.
>> See, I'm not being a copycat today, am I?
Right. Let's see if these cops are open.
I'll be back in like 10 minutes.
We're okay with you, Captain.
Oh, I really fancy them, bro. They're lush. using.