No reply
from the from the bias. You know what lover
he had all morning by the way. He knows
he's a biased little end lover. You know
you know the word lover. I knew it. I
[ __ ] knew it. He's a bi He's a biased
little end lover.
Little dick sucker. It's like what
Kieran says. You can't trust anyone
that's not blocked by that [ __ ] It's a
bit like what Kieran said cuz he knows
he's a biased end lover. Which is why he
got three thumbs up because I'm [ __ ]
right. You little pino lover. So quick
to suck someone's dick when I'm going at
them. But then when they're going at me,
you don't say anything. You little fat
little dick sucker. Watch when I get one
of these people's addresses now. Even
his. I'm I'm going to be waiting like
that guy in the shop until one of these
people get doxed. I can't wait until one
of these people get doxed, you know?
And the Lord Jay think I was right about
that as well. Why have you not replied?
Because you know what I'm saying is the
truth. [ __ ] common air trying to talk
about how you know people can't take
your word. [ __ ] off you [ __ ] mug.
You've been shown [ __ ] money. You've
been shown the [ __ ] world and you
still talk [ __ ] You fat ugly little
weasels. Which is one of the reasons why
you didn't reply to what I just said.
You little weasel. You little You little
[ __ ] fat ugly pen lover. You little
pedo lover. Go back on your boyfriend's
channel. Joseph Ra, you little pedo lover.
Watch when I get one of these people's
addresses. Uh, by the way, uh, this
person's replied on WhatsApp, so we're
getting the ball rolling now, mate. I
was dead serious. I I said to these people,
if they don't meet me, I'm going to [ __ ]
a woman over. I told them, if they did
not meet me, I gave them several several
chances. I was deadly serious, bro. I
was deadly [ __ ] serious. If they
don't meet me, I'm [ __ ] a woman over.
Um, so day after it really.
So they replied. Anyways, I woke up a
bit late. I've just woke up. So I'm
saying to them, "Oh, do you want to go
to a restaurant? I'm going to [ __ ] this
[ __ ] over. Proper. Proper, bro. Proper
[ __ ] him over.
I'll [ __ ] him over and I'll move on." Yeah. [ __ ] [ __ ]
I need his [ __ ] yesterday. Yeah, watch.
But yeah, thanks for not replying to the
video that I done on you cuz you know
that I'm right. You know what I'm saying
is right. You are a little biased nonslover.
You are a little biased nonstop. [ __ ]
make don't [ __ ] do a little [ __ ]
community post and trying to say that
people are [ __ ] liars when you're on
the biggest liars channel every [ __ ]
day. You little bias nons lover. You
biased nons lover. That's what I said.
You're a nons lover. Yeah, just like
Kieran knows you are. You're a nons
lover, not a nons. I said you're a nons
lover cuz you're so quick to suck
someone's dick when I'm going at them.
You [ __ ] [ __ ] But then when I'm
when they're saying stuff to me, you're
nowhere to be seen. [ __ ] noddubber.
[ __ ] off. And he is a virgin. Just cuz
he's got a disabled fat ugly girlfriend,
it doesn't mean he's had sex. Yeah, he's
not allowed anywhere near that disabled
girl. If you want to know the truth.
Yes, he is. He is still a [ __ ]
virgin. More of a [ __ ] virgin than
someone that's proved they have had
[ __ ] sex. You [ __ ]
You buy fat nods lover. That's why I
told you. Uh, that's why I got three
thumbs up cuz the three thumbs up are
genuine people. They know I'm right.
They know what I'm saying is the truth. You know,
they're just fat, ugly, jealous nerds on
here that ain't got no apocus and they
ain't got no life. They got nothing.
It's the truth. It's the truth, man.
This is their whole life. These little
losers. These little weasels. These
little old weasels. They ain't got no
life. [sighs and gasps] Yeah.
Pathetic [clears throat] old people.
Won't be on long anyways. Yeah, that
Joseph Fra didn't reply to me cuz he
knows I'm right, bro. He didn't reply to
me cuz he knows I'm right.
He knows I'm right.
That's why he didn't reply. Why didn't
he reply to the video? Cuz he knows he
is a little nonsubber.
He knows he's a He knows he's a nonslover.
That's why he didn't reply.
He knows he's a little nons. That's why
he didn't reply. He's a little biased
little nonslover. That's why he didn't
reply to the video. It's quart 11 now
and there's still no reply from this guy
cuz he knows I'm right.
[ __ ] bias nons lover.
Well, there's no positivity on this
channel. This person's reply back. I'm
trying to get them out so I can [ __ ]
them over and run up a£500 bill. So, if
you want positivity, you're not going to
get on this channel.
I did warn you all yesterday. I did warn
you. If you don't meet me, I'm going to
[ __ ] a woman over. That's the next best
thing. I told you. You know, I was deadly serious.
I was in a foul mood yesterday and I'm
in a foul mood today. I gave you several
ch these people several chances to meet
me. They didn't want to meet me. Okay,
I'll go for a woman then. I'll [ __ ] a
woman over good and proper and legally. [gasps] Simple.
Cuz that's what seems to get these
people mad on this community for
whatever reason. So, we'll do that then.
This person's reply back, by the way,
8:00 in the morning. So, I'm trying to
get him out so I can [ __ ] him over
royally. These little scumbags. Give
them some back of what they gave me over the years.
Joseph Far's not reply back.
That's strange, isn't it? It's cuz I'm
right about you, you little biased [ __ ]
That's [snorts] why I got three thumbs
up, cuz I'm right about you, you little biased [ __ ]
Yeah, they are [ __ ] I'm getting
revenge anyways, bro. This person's
reply back. I'm going to try and get them out.
They are [ __ ] Evil scum [ __ ]
This is what I wanted to do a couple of
months ago, but they wouldn't they
wouldn't come. They wouldn't. They um
Yeah. proper proper want revenge on
these women, bro. 100%. I'm not going to
be happy until I get it. Yeah. 100%. I'm
not going to be happy until I get it, bro.
That destroys a Ferrar. Huh? It
little bias non lover
Hope he loses all of his money and he
ends up on the street. I hope he loses
all of his money and he ends up on the street. Yep. Yeah.
I'm just on Reddit now, but I'm not
posting anything anymore on that
subreddit, so these little stalkers
can't find me.
Hopefully this person meets me so I can
[ __ ] him over, bro.
Yeah, then I can move on. I can go
proper mocktoe then, bro. I can once I
get revenge on one of these [ __ ] I can
go proper mocktoe.
Yeah. [ __ ] bro. I'm in a foul mood
again. I woke up in a nasty, nasty mood
again. And man's like, "Oh, you might
change your mind Saturday." I'm not
changing my mind. I'm not going out
Saturday. Trust me. When I when I'm in
this mood, bro, trust me, it's very hard
to get out of it. Maybe a week, [snorts]
maybe, maybe, maybe, maybe a week, this
person meets me and I [ __ ] him over,
then I'll be in a good mood. Simple.
Yeah, I'm not in a good mood, bro. Watch
this person meet me. I'm going to [ __ ]
him over, bro. Watch. Yeah. H yeah,
it's a shame in it, lad.
I was just saying to Ant-Man as well, I
want to get revenge on these [ __ ] I'm
thinking of getting revenge,
which is why I messaged that person.
They messaged me back and I said to
them, "Oh, like I don't mind being
fended. Can we go out something to eat?"
And that hopefully they'll reply back.
I was just telling him I'm looking to
get revenge, bro. A bit like what you
did. Not not the accent out. Obviously,
I can't go to prison, but like just in
like another way. Obviously, I have to
be smart about it. Record or not
recorded because I don't want them
getting even more of a laugh me going to prison.
Dirty little [ __ ] want to be a little
[ __ ] Yeah, I I'll [ __ ] show you be a
little [ __ ] Anybody [ __ ] meet me,
I'm running up their I'm running up a 600 bill.
I'm just going to run up a 600 pound
bill, bro. Simple.
Order the most expensive champagne,
wine, and I don't even really drink anymore. Yeah.
Sadly, you have to be careful with what
you do nowadays
because of um the laws and stuff.
Do you know why it's so mad? Obviously
the laws are like [ __ ] up. Like there
should be a law on leading people on.
Should be a crime to troll and lead
people on and be a [ __ ] Just just throw
that out there. Even though that's never
going to happen. It should be a crime to
lead people on.
You know, being a misogynist is a crime.
It should be a crime leading people on.
It should be a crime leading people on,
bro. I don't know why it's not.
also be a crime. Cheating on people, but it's not.
Cheating should be a crime. And leading
people on should be a crime,
which I don't know why it's not a crime.
I don't know why leading someone on is
not a crime. It should be. It should be
a crime. If saying certain things on the
internet is a crime, then I think
leading people on should be a crime.
I think it makes sense, though.
Where's Joseph Ferrar? He's gone quiet
after that video.
He's gone quiet after that video.
I need to get revenge on one of these
[ __ ] bro. Just a couple of people yesterday. Yeah.
So, one's got back to me.
We need to do that Hulkar thing, bro. We
need to do that Hulk. That's the thing
we need to do.
We need to do that Hulkar.
That's what we need to do, bro.
That place is really, really expensive.
Give the some of these evil [ __ ] back
of what they've gave me over the years.
Yeah. Give them some back what they've
gave me over the [ __ ] years.
Stay in bed and sleep.
That's basically what I do every day now
when I'm in this mood.
just stay in bed and sleep uh until one
of these people want to meet me so I can
[ __ ] them over. Yeah,
that's what my plans are. I don't have plans.
I supposed It's Tuesday today. I was
supposed to be going out Saturday. I'm
not doing that.
No. So, yeah. Nothing basically. Yep. Nothing. [ __ ] all.
Nothing to do. It's depressing. I All
I'm focused on is [ __ ] a woman over.
All I'm All I'm focused on is getting a
woman so I can [ __ ] her over and make
them [ __ ] suffer with that 600 600
600 700 bill with that 600 700 state bill.
But I will be coming off this community
soon. 100% bro. I have to, bro. Come off
this community soon. For real.
Too many jealous, ugly losers on here.
They ain't got a life.
Uh, go to a steak mill, run up the mill,
and ditch the woman.
That's what I want to do. I want to
ditch a woman. I want to [ __ ] a woman
over with a 600 bill.
Well, one of the people's replied, by
the way, so I'm trying to get them out.
I said, "Oh, I'm more than happy to be
just friends and stuff." So, I'm more
than happy to get them out so I can [ __ ] them over.
I'm going to really [ __ ] them over, bro.
Then I'll be happy. I'll be happy. I
want to get the last laugh.
I really want to get the last laugh out
these evil [ __ ] Then I can move on
with my life. So,
no, don't like any of that stuff. I just
want to [ __ ] a woman over and then I'll be happy.
Will I be I don't give a [ __ ] if I get
arrested for leaving. I don't give a [ __ ]
She doesn't know who I am. So, I mean,
good luck with that. I mean, she doesn't
know who I am, so I I definitely don't
give a [ __ ]
Arrested for leaving. I don't care.
Um, you're talking to someone that that
don't care. [snorts] So I I don't care.
So I'm going to do it anyways. So yeah.
Um, I'll leave. She Why would I get
arrested when she's still there, lad?
She's still going to be there. So why
would I get arrested? So she replied
back, "Go ahead." I said, "Oh, yeah. Do
you want to do you want to go out for a
meal and that? We can just be friends
and stuff." I'm just like, so I just all
I'm focused on is [ __ ] a woman over.
As long as they've got a vagina, I'll
[ __ ] him over. I'll [ __ ] him over. Good and proper.
I don't care who they are. I don't care
what they've done. If they've got a
vagina in between their legs, I'm
[ __ ] one of them over, bro. I don't
care who it is. I don't care who it [ __ ] is,
you know? And then I'll be happy
with my life then. Yeah.
We were just saying that it should be
illegal to lead people on.
Why don't I bash a lane? Stop asking stupid questions.
What do you mean? Don't Don't ask stupid questions.
Anyone but my mom.
Sorry. Anyone but my mom. But any anyone
not anyone that's related to me.
Okay. Anyone that's that's not related
to me and that's not old. Anyone that's
not old and not related to me.
Yeah. No one cares about the police. You
little police informant. No one cares.
Yeah. I'm going to a restaurant and I'm
going to go for a meal and not pay for
it. Yeah. No one cares about the police.
You little police informant grass.
Yeah. No one cares. Bye-bye. No police
informants on my channel.
No little police boys on my channel.
Yeah. No police boys on my channel,
mate. We call you people. We call you
people police boys. Yeah. Call the
police and tell the police I said I was
going to go to a restaurant and not pay
for it. Yeah. Yeah. See what they do
with that information.
Yeah. I don't think so, bro.
You know what's so mad? Yeah. Is you
know last year, do you know the amount
of [ __ ] I said on YouTube? Yeah. And and
no one come for me. No. No. None of the
police come for me. And I said mad
stuff. Do you remember last year the mad
stuff that I said? I was saying sick mad
stuff. They never ever come.
Good on them. Good on them for not
coming. Good on them. They should get
They should not get involved over
YouTube. Um so that's obviously another
thing that these people can't use is the
police, which is a good thing. So, which
means it's a step closer to them having
to meet you. I was saying some [ __ ]
sick things last year. I'm surprised
they didn't come to be honest. But
that's a good thing to be honest. They
shouldn't come. Um because it's just
YouTube at the end of the day like
people say. So,
it's good because if they can't get the
police involved and they can't come on
your door and they can't get anyone else
do your dirty work, they can't do
anything. You could send it all to the
police all you want that I'm going to
die and dash someone. I don't give a [ __ ]
Yeah. No one cares about the police. No one cares.
No one cares about the police. They're
not going to do anything. No one cares.
Thanks. No one cares. They're not going
to do anything.
Face it. You're going to have to meet
me, bro. You're going to have to meet me.
You know what I'm saying? No one cares
about the police. They're not going to
do anything. And even if they did,
they'd let me out. You [ __ ] idiot.
Now [ __ ] off. Thank you, [ __ ] [ __ ] off. Thanks.
Disabled police informants. They're
police boys on here. They're little
police boys. You know, you own them so
badly on YouTube. They have to call the
police. That's how you know you own
them. This is how you know you own them
in every aspect. The fact that they have
to call up the police because they've
been owned. They're so They're so owned
that they have to call the police. You
own them so badly they have to get a
crime reference number. This is what I
mean with these people here. They're so
cowardly they get owned so badly,
so bad they get their ass a good
whooping that they have to be a victim
by the police and then they think
they've won and then they don't do
anything. [ __ ] idiots.
N good on the police though for not
coming else. Yeah, good on them. They
shouldn't come on come over YouTube.
Good. Good on him, you know. Yeah. You know,
see hopefully this p person meets me. Yeah.
I can't do what Ant-Man done sadly
because I'll go prison.
Yeah. There is no upcoming. There is no
case coming up. [laughter]
There is no case coming up. You thicko.
There is no case coming up. You little
idiot. You little grass. You got owned
on YouTube so badly you have to run to
the police. Thank you. You're a loser. Loser.
Loser. You've been owned by me. Woo.
Woo. You have to call the police because
you've been owned so badly.
So badly. And you have to run to the police. Loser.
You're a loser. Woo!
Loser boy. Police boy. Police boy.
Bye-bye, police boy. See you, police
boy. No police boys on my chat. No
And there is no upcoming case. So try
again. You don't know anything, you [ __ ] idiot.
You don't know anything, mate. You don't
know [ __ ] anything. There is no
[ __ ] case. You don't [ __ ] know
anything, you [ __ ] idiot.
You don't know [ __ ] anything, you
little sad bastard. Look how much you
tried [ __ ] last year and didn't work.
[ __ ] sad bastards. There's probably a
[ __ ] Merlin on my dress, to be honest.
These people are such losers, bro.
Well, I went live to ask Joseph Far why
he didn't reply. I want to know why he
I want to know why he didn't reply. [snorts]
I want to know why he didn't reply to
what I was writing.
These people called YouTube.
They're such losers. They're such [ __ ] losers.
They're such losers. But I went live to
to ask Joseph Fo why he hasn't replied
to my uh video.
If I go live Christmas day, all of you
people will be on there.
If I went live Christmas day, you would
all be on there.
You will all be on here.
No, the D and Dash thing is a good
thing, bro. The D and Dash thing is a
good thing. The D and Dash thing is a
very good thing. >> [snorts]
>> I bet you will be on here.
Yeah, these people are little police
boys. UK asylum. They're little police
boys. Little police boys.
What are they, bro? They're little police boys.
Bye-bye, [ __ ] These people are so
jealous of me, UK side. It's
unbelievable. What do you think they're
jealous of? Do you think it's because
I'm younger and better looking than
them? I think it's cuz I'm younger and
better looking than them. What do you
think? Where do you think the jealousy comes from?
I think it's jealousy cuz I'm better
looking than them and younger than them.
That's what I think. What do you think? [sighs]
No, bro. Even if you ignore them,
they're not going to stop.
I mean, even if you Okay, bro. Even if
you ignore them, they're still going to
do it. This is why I tried to explain to
Joseph Despic a million times that you
do realize if you never gave them
attention, they will still do it every day.
They will not ever stop. Like ever,
ever, ever stop. Like we could ignore
them for 5 years. Like 5 years straight,
we could create content on this channel
and they would never stop. Reply to them
or you don't reply to them, they will never stop. So
they're never ever ever going to stop.
Even if you ignore them, like they're
never ever ever ever ever going to stop.
Get that in your mind. Never ever ever
ever going to stop. There's been times
where I've gone off of a channel for 8
months. Right. Right. Right. Let me
explain it again. Right. Let me repeat
myself cuz you didn't listen. Even if I
ignored them and I didn't go on their
channels ever again, they would still do it.
Even if I never ever went on their
channel and I never went live again,
they would still do it. They would still
do it. Okay, let me Okay, if I if I
started doing videos and I never went
live again and I never read any
comments, I I banned all the comments
and I and I could physically never go on
their channel again, they would
literally still do it every day for
years. So that's what makes me think
it's jealousy. That's the only lo the
only logical thing it can be is jealousy.
That's that's literally the only thing
it can you say that you're not. You sit
there and you say that you're not, but
you sit on here every day doing what you
do. That's not an act of someone that's
not jealous of someone. How many times I
have to try to say this? That's what
makes me think it's got to be jealousy
with you people. Not you. It has to be.
There's no other thing it can be. There
is no other thing it can be. You can say
they do it for reaction. It's [ __ ] now.
They do it because they're fat, ugly,
and jealous. And you got something that
they don't have. That's so ob It's so
obvious. They make it too obvious. You
know, the biasness. Um, you know, even
with Joseph Ferro, the biasness, it's
obviously cuz you're not fat and ugly
like them. It's so obvious. The way you
have these people stalk you. These are
not happy people. They're skin miserable
little low-life fat bully victims.
That's what they are.
So, they would do it no matter what.
Even if you was on Even if you was off
here, they would they would still do it.
No matter what you do, they will never
ever stop. That's not acts of a of a of
a happy person that's not jealous of someone. So yeah,
they're just little [ __ ] nerds on
here, bro. They're little nerds on. I'm
coming off this [ __ ] soon anyways, bro. 100%.
I'd have come live to vent, to be honest. Yes.
They want to ruin people's life because
they're jealous. That's what it is.
These people are jealous. They're fat
people that failed at everything in
life. They're a bit like Reddit
moderators on here. Do you know these
people on here? They're a bit like
They're a bit like Reddit moderators.
Yeah, they're a bit like Reddit mods. moderators
failed at everything [clears throat] in
life and [snorts] take out on you
because they're fat lossers. They ain't
got [ __ ] all in their life. Yep.
Yeah. See, man. Yeah,
look at these people sat there
recording. Little nerds, little fat
lives failures sat on YouTube recording
me. I bet they're [ __ ] recording right now.
These little police boys, little Reddit
moderators. That's what we should start
calling now. Reddit mods. And they've
got something in common. They don't get
paid either. These little nerds. They
don't get paid.
But yeah, you can't do what Ant-Man
does. You can't [ __ ] go around with a
[ __ ] axe. You go you go to prison for
just carrying a weapon. [ __ ] doing that.
Are you mad? [ __ ] doing that. Then the
[ __ ] win even more when you're in prison.
No coke, no food. No, you need to get
them by the wallet. You need to [ __ ] him
over in a way where they can't where
they can't get police involved, where
there's literally nothing they could do,
like rip them off. Um, you know, you
have to do things or if you are going to
throw piss at someone, you know, don't
do it on camera, you know, cuz you know
what these little police boy nerds are
like, these little low lives, little
life failures. [snorts] Um, so you need
to [ __ ] him over that way. Oh, you can
mouth off to them. Stuff like that. You
need to do stuff in a way where you know
they can't get the law involved
cuz you know what the you know what
these narcissistic women are like. So yeah.
Uh and the reason I don't mention kids
anymore is uh cuz kids are innocent. Uh
women are not innocent. Uh so that's why
you don't I don't I don't talk about
children because children are innocent.
Women are not innocent. They're not
innocent at all as much as these white
knights and these simps try to make them
out to be.
You know what can a [ __ ] kid do? A
kid can't even defend himself, you know?
But these women are definitely
definitely definitely definitely evil.
100% they are evil. So yeah,
I can see why people defend people that
are rude to kids, but women really
really anyone would think they are kids
the way the [ __ ] people defend them. [ __ ] idiots, you know.
I mean that one that one in the park
wasn't good enough. I really want to rip
someone off like badly. Like proper rip
him off. rip him off, you know. So, this
this person hasn't replied to my my next
message. I said like, "Can we go out and that?" So,
I'm trying to bribe them with like a
nice restaurant and that. Yeah.
We'll Straight up.
Where's Joseph Farra?
Not bad. Joseph, so why are you not on
the channel saying why why you're so
biased? Why you're so quick enough to
defend said people like Superman.
Superman number three. But when people
are talking [ __ ] about me, nowhere to be
seen. You little bias nonsubber.
Where is this bias nonsubber?
Like I said, if you're not fat and ugly
like these people, they'll find problems
with you. They'll always be biased
because you don't fit in with this
community. You're not old. You're not
fat. You're not
I was saying is is that it's like what I
was saying, you're not if you're not
live went off again. What I was
basically saying is, yeah, so you you
have to understand if you're not fat,
old, and ugly like these people, they're
always going to be biased. They're
always going to pick problems with you
um on this community because most of
these people are fat, old, ugly, skint,
ain't got a pot to piss in, ain't got no
family. So obviously if you're someone,
you know, younger, better looking,
they'll always find reasons to dislike
you and, you know, be biased and stuff.
It's just jealousy. You know, if you was
like one of them, you'd fit in well. Um, so yeah,
you're not fat and ugly like them, so
that's why they have problems and stuff.
Yep. Sad little losers.
Sad little losers. They're just like Reddit moderators.
There we are. That ball
[ __ ] I put no [ __ ] money in
And you know you was being a little
copycat. I swear to God in my [ __ ]
mom's life. He did say that. He said
homo vibes. Yeah. Wanted to fit in with
the crowd. He did say that. He did
[ __ ] say that.
He just realizes how stupid it it looks
now. That's why he's trying to say. Oh,
he didn't say it. You are a little copycat.
Want to fit in with the crowd.
You got no bloody mind of your own.
No bloody mind of your own.
You little copycat.
Yeah. I just admit what you said, bro.
It doesn't matter, does it? You just
wanted to fit in. It's hard being
[ __ ] you know, new and, you know,
out of college and stuff.
Especially when you're not like very
much, you know. It's You said you just
said it to fit in. It is what it is. You
don't want to feel left out.
You did say gay. You You definitely did
say that I was gay. You definitely did.
You definitely definitely did say that.
You wanted to copy the crowd.
I don't judge you for it. Meow meow meow.
I had a pot noodle yesterday.
cuz I couldn't be bothered to eat. I
don't think I'll be eating today either. [snorts]
Nah. Got off my food.
on these [ __ ] Can the person reply back, man?
Come to this restaurant with me. Come on.
I'm sick of that [ __ ]
That man took it too far with the axe. [ __ ] that.
Absolutely [ __ ] that, bro.
But that's how these little [ __ ] get
you. These scumbags get you. [ __ ]
horrible, evil bastards.
I'm just looking for women to [ __ ] with
on Reddit whilst this person replies back. One second.
This is coming to earth.
Durious [ __ ] with this person on Reddit.
I had to copy and paste their name. I
like this flagship phone. Isn't it so
cool these flagship phones?
Joseph Ferrar don't have a flagship
phone. He can't afford it.
If I can [ __ ] one of them over before
Saturday, I'll go out Saturday.
Let these [ __ ] women win. You know,
can't come off YouTube. What What
grieves you going to do to poor [ __ ] [laughter]
That's definitely not a joke. Poor [ __ ]
Leave grieving without content, poor [ __ ]
You just don't want He just don't want
to know you.
He just don't want to know.
You just saw one night
just didn't You just did. She just did
tickle. You just did tickle fancy.
at USA Izzy yesterday, but I didn't.
I was going to start in a friend, not
message like family and that [ __ ] [ __ ]
all that, but I was going to like just
message the friend saying, "I'm willing
to take your I'm willing to take your
I'm willing to I'm willing to call you
bluff, [ __ ] I'm willing to call you
Why is that?
Well, it can't be as bad as yours. Sat
on YouTube every day. No life, you know.
Yeah. What's your life then? Being sat
on YouTube every day calling people skin
or some life you've got from the time
you wake up to the time you go to bed.
Calling people that you don't know in life.
What's your bloody life then? Hello. Bro,
that screen time out setting The [ __ ]
One second, bro.
It just says keep it on whilst you're
looking at it.
I'm going to have to do that for now cuz
it's annoying. Have No, no, no.
Oh, I can change it. Okay. Uh, 10 minutes.
Yeah, I changed it to 10 minutes. That
was getting annoying, bro. Only 30
seconds. I have to keep clicking on it. Good job.
Good job. Good job. Good job. Good job.
Boy, Trip Rage has got you a little job.
A little job will do you the world of
good. Get you off your YouTube.
He owns a big company in all feast. He's
got a little job for you.
Yep. He's got a little job for you.
Good job for you.
There you go. Brazil
was on block me. I'm just going to [ __ ] with her.
She lives in Brazil. She started being a
[ __ ] as well.
I mean, there's no surprise. I mean,
they're [ __ ] in there's a lot of them
that are [ __ ] in Thailand. So, I mean,
They're just [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
It's so mad to think at 28 years of age,
you can't even find one person that's normal.
One person that's normal
at 28 years of age. Yeah,
imagine that. 28 years of age and all
these women are [ __ ] [ __ ] [snorts]
And I always thought I was immature. I
always thought I was immature, you know.
But clearly not. Clearly not.
Bro, I said you're immature in it. Yeah.
Don't know why he can't get himself a little job.
say, "Good morning. If you're going to
say nonsense or anything, Paul Graass,
don't even bother sending another
message, otherwise I'll go." Thank you.
See, they're all [ __ ] They're just
hypocritical little [ __ ] That's what they are.
I know. I know. It takes a lot for me to
call someone immature. I know, man. I
know. I know. And I'm And I'm calling
them immature. I know. It's a tricky
one, isn't it? I know. Right. That's how
you know they're immature. When someone
like me is calling them immature. Yeah. I know.
Mind games. Toxic. Immature. They're all
liars. I actually thought I was
immature. I always would admit, "Yeah,
I'm immature." Ant-Man would say,
"You're immature." I was like, "Yeah, I
I am immature." But not as immature as
them, these [ __ ] these [ __ ]
these [ __ ] women. Yeah, he needs to
get himself a little job. Why don't you
comment on his community post, Triple?
Say, "You need to get yourself a little
job. Come to Dome, lad. We got you a
little job." Mr. G said it to him
before. Get get you a little job. So yeah,
why is this woman in Brazil getting so
mad over a dick picture? It's not like
they don't sleep with people. It's not
like they don't have sex. They're such
hypocrites. These women, these women are such hypocrites.
I didn't even realize they unblocked me.
No, I can definitely definitely blame
women. They are [ __ ] I can
definitely definitely definitely blame
women. I'm not blaming people. I'm
blaming women. I'm not blaming people.
I'm blaming women.
I'm blaming women cuz they're [ __ ] So [snorts] yeah,
do you know what I was just saying,
Grezy? And I don't know if you'll agree
with this, right? You know how there's
so many laws about people saying stuff
about women and whatever? I think there
should be a law and leading people on.
I don't know if you agree with it. I
think there should be a law uh on
cheating and a law and leading people
on. They make all of these stupid laws nowadays.
I'm clearly the problem. Well, my
messages and my approaches say
otherwise. It shows women are the
problem. But we won't get into that
because I didn't put them videos up for
no reason just to have the same
conversation. But anyways, Grezy, they
put they're doing a lot of stupid laws
nowadays for women.
And I think that there should be a law
against leading people on
trolling, which is what these women do.
I will tell them I [ __ ] will, bait. I
[ __ ] will, bait, because there so
many stupid things. Um, it's so many
stupid things uh so many stupid things
illegal now, right, that they don't even
go after real criminals. So, they want
they want to make stupid laws. They want
to make up stupid laws.
They want to make stupid laws, right?
They want to make stupid laws up, bro.
But they there needs to be laws against
women as well. They need to make it
equal leading on them having attitude.
They need to make these things illegal, bro.
What do you do? What do you think,
Grezy? Do you think I've got a point?
Like leading people on? I think that
should be illegal. You know,
they they're they're making misogynist
laws now. I think leading people on and
cheating should be illegal. What do you think?
I've never understood why cheating is
not illegal. I've never understood that.
Why cheating isn't illegal?
I've never understood that. You know,
it's not leading you on. Grievy, greasy,
grievy. A wild s appears.
[snorts] A wild white knight appears.
A wild s appears. [snorts] [laughter]
talking to a world text is not there
leading you on.
You can't make it up.
Yeah, they generally definitely they
definitely definitely should um it
should be illegal leading someone on.
Okay, so someone agreeing to meet you
then backing out is is not leading
someone on. Okay, bro. Okay, so someone
talking to you on WhatsApp and agreeing
to meet you and then two hours before
meeting you saying they're getting back
with their ex is not leading someone on.
Is that not leading on some Is that not
leading someone on, Grezy?
So, them literally sweet talking you and
agreeing to meet you is not them leading
you on. Oh, gosh darn it. That's not
leading you on, mate. It's a gender
thing. It's already been proven multiple
multiple times. It is a gender thing.
Yeah. So, that is that not leading
people on, Grezy? Let's ask Grievy. He
can agree. He can disagree if he wants.
Is that not leading people on?
So what is okay? So what is your
definition of leading someone on then?
>> My definition is somebody speaking to
you, being all nice and agreeing to meet
you. That's my definition of leading
someone on. I don't know what your
definition of leading someone on is.
Someone that doesn't lead somebody on
doesn't reply. Somebody that doesn't
lead someone on says they're never going
to meet you.
Bro, it's okay. The women led me on.
It's fine. It's not a problem. It's not
a problem at all. You don't need to make
excuses for them.
Stop making excuses for them cuz they're
women. It's not the worst thing.
It's not the worst thing ever. It's
shitty, but it's not the worst thing
ever. Stop making excuses for them cuz
they've got a funny in between the legs.
Be a good chap now. Stop making excuses
for them cuz they've got a cut in
between the legs.
It's [ __ ] It's pathetic, man. If they
can't even admit someone's led someone
on, bro. What could they admit? You know
what I'm saying, Grievy? What could they admit?
But I've got I've got sufficient
evidence for uh leading people on. Uh
yeah, but it bro it definitely isn't.
Well, it shouldn't be, but it is a
gender issue. It is, bro. You know it's
a gender issue. You know it and I know
it. You know it and I know it. And that
I've got sufficient evidence that people
have led me on.
And also what that USA done should have
been should be illegal as well. That
that should that that should have
warranted prison time, bro. With that
[ __ ] done. Made up stories, lied that
that she should have went prison for
that. And other people leading me on as
well. Leading people on.
You can't get women.
Uh, bro, people have seen me with women
and Greavvesy don't like and Grevsy
don't want a woman. Firstly, Greavvesy
doesn't want a woman and I've had more
women than you. Um, which again has been
proven, but again, you'll pretend that
you never saw it because you're biased
on it. I got Griezy I got Joseph Far by
the bollocks by the way. Them three
thumbs up on genuine people cuz he knows
what I'm saying is the truth. That's why
he didn't reply back. Why do you think
Joseph Farrar didn't reply back? Because
he knows what I'm saying is the truth.
He knows what I'm saying is the truth.
He's a nons lover. I've never called him
a nons. I called him a nod lover cuz how
he's so fast to defend non legs. Um how
he's so fast to defense
nons legs. When I go at him, but then
when he goes at me, he doesn't say
anything. He's biased with the law a
thing. They are biased on here. It's
like what Kieran said. They are biased.
Greavves is not trying to get a woman.
Yeah, I've already had women, bro. I've
already had women. I've had more women
than you. People have seen me with
women. Why are you saying that I can't
get women when I've had more women than
most people in this community? Everyone
has seen me with women. Again, let me
let me explain this to you. People that
are sick of women's [ __ ] and don't
lick their asses is not an incel. This
is another thing that needs to be
addressed, Grezy, that they think that
anyone that is sick of women and can't
stand them anymore is an incel. If you
don't suck up to a woman and you don't
think their way, they all all of a
sudden start [ __ ] calling you name
tags other than just someone that's just
sick of their [ __ ] And that's what I
am. Just sick of them. And I'm sick of
their [ __ ] It doesn't mean people can't
get them or can't get can get them. I'm
sick of them. Is people not allowed to
be sick of their [ __ ] Do you know what
I'm saying, bro?
Uh, well, if if that is the case, then
it's good. Good. It shouldn't be taken
serious. It shouldn't be taken serious.
It shouldn't be taken serious. Good.
[ __ ] good. After all of this [ __ ]
that they do, leading people on and
[ __ ] people over. Good. [ __ ] well.
Good. There needs There needs to be more
laws for men. Good. I'm glad. I'm glad.
The only thing I ever regret saying
about is is is people's kids and stuff.
That's the only thing that I felt bad I
regret is saying like about kids and
stuff, Grezy. Cuz like children are
innocent and that. So, and they can't
defend themselves. But women, they're
[ __ ] I don't take back any of the
things I said. I meant everything I
said. You know, people allowed to
retract their statements. You know,
they're not innocent. Greasy. You see,
the thing is these people are defending
them like they're children. They're not
children. They know what they're doing.
And it is a gender thing. Just like what
you said, it is a gender thing. Of
course, it's a gender thing.
Autism. Maybe. Maybe I don't have
autism. Maybe I'm one of these people
that don't have autism. Cuz I don't know
where the desire comes from where people
would want to lick women's asses every
day. I don't know where the desire comes from, Grezy.
I don't know where the desire comes to
lick up women's asses, but they don't
like you. I just would love someone to
to explain it to me, Grezy. This is what
I want the podcast on. This is what I
want the podcast to be because I'm
unbiased. I've had sex. I've been with
women and I hate him and I hate him and
I've been with women, you know, and I I
I want to know where the desire and
passion comes from
where they have to lick a woman's ass
just for being a woman. I would love
somebody to explain it to me one day and
I'll sit back and I'll listen to it
why why people do it. I'm actually interested,
you know. Yeah, kids are innocent, man.
Kids get a free pass, but women don't
get a free pass. They know exactly what
they're doing. They know exactly what
But yet to these simps and white
knights, they're perfect cuz they've got
a cut in between their legs. Well, like I said, Yeah.
Yeah. No, no, it's that's what it is, isn't it? Okay.
No, no, they whatever. Well, they call
you an in basically the thing is,
Greavesy, these people call you an incel
if you don't lick women's asses. If
you've got any bad words to say about
women, you're automatically an incel.
So, it doesn't really matter what it
means because it's you it's using the
wrong context. Okay. So, say, okay, for
example, say you go on the internet and
you say, "I'm sick of women. I've had
bad experiences. I can't stand them."
They'll call you an incel. Even if
you've had partners before, even if
you've had sex, um, no matter what it
is, they will automatically say that
you're an incel because you don't think
they're away. Why should you think
they're way if you've had your own
experiences with them?
So, then they call you, it's such an
overused word now. It's boring. It's
like calling a woman a [ __ ] It's
boring. You know, it's got no substance.
It's got nothing, no thought into it.
It's just boring. Absolutely boring.
You know, they call people an incel if
you don't lick women's asses. Um, you
could just be someone.
Yeah, it's boring now, bro. Calling
yourself a bunch. It's boring. It's
boring. The self projection is boring
now. Come up with some new words. And
then you wonder why the community is
dead. But then people like you write why
the community is dead because you keep
coming on here every day calling
yourself a m. You bore people. You bore
people because all you do is sit on here
every day talking about yourselves and
people get bored of it. People get bored
of you fat ugly people putting
yourselves down. So they think, "Fuck
it. We'll just go to another community
because all you do is talk about your
ugly fat selves. You don't show your
faces cuz you're ugly. Yet you come on
here calling someone that's younger and
better looking than you a m. You're
coming on here saying that I'm a M when
I'm younger and better looking than you.
So even when you're proven wrong
multiple times, you still come on here
and talk [ __ ] I've shown more money
than you. You talk [ __ ] I've had more
women than you. I've slept with women.
You still talk [ __ ] You fat, ugly
people are boring people off this
community now. Keep calling yourselves
ugly. Keep calling yourselves skin. keep
putting yourselves down. We feel sorry
for you people so bad talking about
yourselves that we leave you to it. But
[ __ ] this. We're not going to sit here
and watch a bunch of fat, ugly people
keep putting themselves down online
every day and then they find another
community. Why do you think the
community is dead now? Why do you think
Why do you think the community is dead?
Because you fat ugly people keep talking
about yourselves and self-projecting. No
one wants to No one wants to sit here
and and and listen to a bunch of
failures talk about themselves. You're
just Reddit moderators. You're no
different than Reddit moderators. You
sit on here from the time you wake up to
the time you go to bed calling yourself
a m. And then when people ask you to put
your cameras on, you won't show your
face cuz you know you're ugly cuz you're
a self conjector. Now, if I was on a
community constantly talking about
someone and they'd be like, "Show your
face." I'd be like, "Okay, [ __ ] it.
Here's my face." You can't do it because
you're fat, old, ugly people. And you
and and and it's like what I was saying
to Joseph Fel yesterday. You have
problems with people that are younger
and better looking than you. It's like
you take your failures out on the
younger and better looking because
they've got hope. Unlike you people. Am
I lying by saying right now that you
people are older than me? Am I lying
right now that saying people that you
you are older than me?
Well, they're not normalized. Why? Why
are they saying that when they're not?
Well, it's not normalized.
I've had more women than you. I've had
more sex than you. And you still come
here and you still talk [ __ ] And then
you think that people need to come in
here and prove themselves to you. Can I
ask you why you think that as well? Why
do you people think that we need to
prove ourselves to you?
Yeah. Exactly. And and and and it's not
normalized either. Uh misog misogynist
is not uh [ __ ] normalized. Yeah.
Yeah. And Yeah, they do normal. Yeah,
that's a good that's a good point, Grezy. Yeah.
Could you imagine me going on the on on
the TV on the debate?
I don't sit on it saying I can't get a
girlfriend. I come on here saying I hate
women. So, and you calling me a bun when
I'm younger and better looking than you.
How many li How many times can you keep
lying to yourself?
How many times do you keep have to keep
lying to yourself? It can't be good for
your mental health. You're cool to be a
mother. Yeah, I'm younger than all of
you and I'm better looking than you all
and you're still lying to yourselves.
You call people skin. I've proven many
multiple times. I've had thousands. How
many li times are you going to keep
lying to yourself? You know, lying to
yourself. Lying to yourself. You fat
ugly bunters. How many times are you bunters?
Are you [ __ ] bunters going to stop
lying to yourselves? Sorry, Grezy. This
is this is a genuine question to these
people. Could you imagine me on the TV, Griezy?
They probably cut they probably cut it
off, though, to be honest with you. What
woman is going to want to spend time
with a man who hates women? Again, I've
showed approaches. See, again, they just
miss they just dismiss everything. My
mom was doing it as well yesterday,
Grezy. She was dismissing my struggles.
I got into an argument with my mom. She
gave the Uggs back. We got in like a
really bad argument and I said, "You're
just," she said that she's not
dismissing struggles, but you are
dismissing struggles. And I said, "Do
you want me to show the messages right
now? Do you want me to show you the
messages right now?" And then she said
nothing. So they do dismiss your
struggles. They they they they normalize
they normalize any bad thing they do.
Not even just leading on Grezy. They
normalize it and they dismiss it.
Um that's what they do.
They normalize it and they dismiss any
bad thing that they do and then they
reverse the psychology back on to you.
That's another thing that they do,
Grezy. So, okay. So, what I mean by that
is like you'll get bad experiences with
them. They'll be [ __ ] time and time
and time and time and time and time and
time and time and time again. Right,
mate? You don't have a job.
Why are you not at work, Brett? Why are
you not at work? You know, you know.
So, anyways, are you people not going to
show your faces then?
So, yeah. Um, they normalize basically
anything that they do.
So, I would say just to Grezy, do you
think it's Do you think we think the
right way because we never had a dad?
Do you think because we because the way
we think is the right way, not licking
women's asses and stuff. And obviously
you've disagreed with me in the past. Do
you think it's because
Oh. Oh, yeah. 100%. And I'll prove
they're talking about themselves. If
they come on and they put their cameras
on, I will prove to you that they're
talking about themselves.
Come on and put your Oh, that's another
thing before we get Why do you think
that people need to prove themselves to
you fat ugly people? That's another
thing because I never got an answer.
This is not to you, Greavvesy, by the
way. Um, I've seen you write stuff,
right? Why do you come on here every day
thinking that people need to prove
themselves to you fat ugly people? You
you open your eyes, right, in in in the
in the morning, right? So, you open your
eyes when you uh when you uh when you
Well, no, because I've shown more money
than anybody on here. So, no, I'm
talking about you people. Okay. Are you
going to come on here and show your
faces? And for the millionth time I've
asked you, are you going to come on here
and show your faces?
So again, why do you come on here every
day um thinking that people need to
prove themselves to you fat ugly people?
I'm asking you a question. Can you
answer why you think that people need to
prove themselves to you fat ugly people?
Um he showed 13 grand 4 years ago. Yeah.
13 grand daddy's life savings that he
can't show now. Yes. He wasn't showing
that when I was showing seven grand.
When I was showing seven grand, he
wasn't showing that. Nons lover. Bias
nons lover. That's what I'm saying.
They're all jealous nons lovers. This is
what I mean. This is what I mean with
these people. You showed 13 grand's
daddy savings four years ago. Show the
money now. Show the money now. Right.
Okay. Show the money now. Show the 13
grand now. Yeah. When I was showing
seven grand, right, multiple times, he
ran away. Show the 13 grand now. Show
the 13K now. Show the bro, again, no one
needs to prove you fat ugly people
wrong. You prove that you're not fat
ugly munters, then come back to me. You
prove that you're not a fat ugly m and
then come on here and then and then try
and tell me what I need to prove. When
you fat ugly people prove you're not a m
that you are, then come back to me.
Yeah. Go back to your boyfriend's
channel, you [ __ ] little nuts lover. [gasps]
No one needs to prove you fat ugly
people wrong. Why do these people need
to think that people need to prove these
fat ugly low lives wrong? Can someone
answer me why they why they think that?
It doesn't matter how much is the most
I've ever had. You've been showing money
and you've all ran away.
[ __ ] I showed £110 the other day and
you couldn't even show 210. Stop
changing the subject.
I know I'm calling you people a m
because you are a m and you can't show
your faces cuz you're butt ugly. That's
why you come on here every day trying to
talk about me cuz you're all butt ugly
fat ugly jealous people. Ugly faces.
That's why none of you can put your
cameras on cuz you're [ __ ] stinking
ugly. Because anyone that isn't would
just show their face but you can't cuz
you're [ __ ] ugly and you're not
smart. Stop s Don't That's another thing
as well. Don't sit there and say, "Oh,
we don't show our faces because we're
smart." If you were smart, you wouldn't
be on here repeating yourself every day.
If you were smart, if you had an IQ, you
wouldn't be on here every day repeating yourselves.
You wouldn't be on here repeating
yourselves if you had an IQ. If you were
smart, you wouldn't be repeating
yourself every day on here. So, stop
blaming you being ugly as being smart,
[ __ ] idiots. No, bro. Sorry, I just
had to block the little bias nons weasels.
And you know, Grevy, what I'm saying
about Joseph Ferrar is the truth. I'm
sure you watch the video. I'm sure you
know it's the truth. I'm sure you know
No, no, no, no, no, no. You don't show
your faces cuz you're [ __ ] ugly. Look
at Look, no, no, no. Look at what
happened to Bomb when his face got out
there. No one found out who he was. A
lot of people on here that showing their
face, people don't know who they are.
People don't show their faces cuz
they're ugly. They're ugly. And if they
showed their faces, they wouldn't be
able to come on here and talk about
anyone else anymore. Look at what
happened to Bomb. He didn't come back
for like over a year. You don't show
your faces because you're ugly. You're
mutters. Right. I'm just going to get
this out of the way, Greavvesy. Yeah.
Before we move on from this, you don't
show your faces because you know you're
the mont. The life mters. And if you if
you put your face out there, you can't
come back on even talk about anyone else.
You know, do you know what I'm saying,
bro? like you you know what I mean?
So that's that. It's not because of
letters and neighbors. It's because
you're but ugly but ugly people. If I
went if I went on a community, bro, I
would show my face. I'd have no problem
showing my face. It is because you're
[ __ ] ugly and and you wouldn't be
able to come on here talking [ __ ] anymore.
So don't lie, bro. It's okay. It's not a problem.
You have nothing to say once you show your face.
So that's why you don't show your faces, you know,
because they never found out who Bomb
was. They never found out who a lot of people was.
So that's already proven to been I Oh, I
I messaged Chinese Izzy. I told her I
hate women yesterday. I messaged her
saying that I hated women. She just read it.
Yeah, I sent her my dick. This one from
Brazil. Yeah, I sent her my dick grievy.
Yeah. And she she unblocked me. She
said, "Oh, if you send anything
pornographic again, um, if you send
anything pornographic again, I'm going
to block you."
And then she said she It's funny she
unblocked me, though. Who the [ __ ]
blocks and then unblocks? And then she
was messaging me.
I mean, I don't understand what is wrong
with a dick picture. Don't they don't
they have dick all the time?
Don't they suck dick? I mean, I don't I
don't really understand. I mean,
don't these people get pregnant, Grievy?
I I don't understand. I think another
thing that I I think is strange with
with this Grezy is how hypocritical
women are. This isn't this isn't um
spoke about enough. Like they go on like
dick is gross and come is gross and oh
us, we don't have sex. Us and then well
then they get pregnant. So I mean I
think that's not spoke about enough.
That's another thing I forgot to bring
up to you that that's it's not brought
up. I mean it is they are clearly
hypocrites unless they want unless they
just want children. Unless they just
want children. They're hypocrites.
It doesn't matter. It doesn't matter if
they could be with someone. They go on
like sex is nasty and and dick is nasty,
but then they get pregnant, my people.
So they're just hypocrites,
you know? Especially the stuck up ones.
No, no, no. We're talking about single
people. No, we're talking about single
people. Obviously. No. No. We're talking
about single people.
Well, if they find dicks so disgusting,
then maybe they shouldn't have sex then, should they?
No, they are hypocrites because they go
on like they're perfect and they don't
have sex. And then the next thing they
get pregnant. So, they're definitely
definitely definitely hypocrites.
They're definitely hypocrites. 100% they're hypocrites.
And you can tell some of them they they
they go on like their [ __ ] don't think,
you know. So, no, they're definitely hypocrites.
Yeah, women are definitely hypocrites
when it comes to sex
because they go on like it's nasty and
whatever, but then they have sex, so it
just doesn't make sense.
They're like, "Oh, us, we don't get sex.
Us." Nah, we they go on like I don't
know. Do you get what I'm trying to say,
though, Grezy? Do you get what I'm
trying to say?
I don't know if you get what I'm trying
to say, but yeah.
They just pretend that it's nasty, but
then they have sex.
I don't know. It just seems
hypocritical. I don't know, man. It just
always seems a bit hypocritical to me.
Maybe I'm wrong. I don't know. But yeah,
they go on like they they they find it
nasty and they're innocent and I don't
know. Oh, I don't know how I don't know
how to explain it.
And they look stuck up and they pretend,
oh, dick. No, we don't like dick. We
don't like sex. I mean, unless, like I
said, if they're having if they want a
child, then obviously it's different
because obviously they have to have sex
to have have a child.
Um, they have to have sex to have
children. Obviously, I'm talking about
when it's not unplanned. I'm talking
about when it's not unplanned.
When it's unplanned.
There's this woman, she looks so stuck
up and then she's pregnant. Yeah, I bet
you before she was pregnant, she'd be
like, "Oh, dick's so gross. Come is
nasty." No, no, no. And all of that
stuff. And then, well, there you go.
There you are having sex again. Unless
you planned a child. Unless you really
wanted a child, then obviously you're
not a hypocrite cuz it's the only way
you can get a child biologically. So,
uh, you want the link? Okay, one second.
Do you think it's a little bit hypocritical, Grezy?
Oh, nah. You can disagree. I don't mind.
We can agree, disagree on things. I
don't give a [ __ ] We don't agree on most things.
The reason I asked you is because you
seem to be the only one that's biased.
No, not the pictures. We're not talking
about the pictures. I mean I mean like
generally they will say, "Oh, sex is
nasty." Oh, we don't do that. They they
shy away from the topic. It's almost as
if they shy away from sex. They shy away
from, "Oh, no, we don't we don't do
that." Um, T is nasty. Dicks are nasty.
They almost shy away from the topic, if
that makes sense. But then, well, then
they're having a baby, so [snorts] can't
keep up with them. um
they shy away like they're perfect, but
then they they then they then they're
having a baby with someone, so I can't
keep up with them.
I mean, there was one in Nottingham. Do
you remember that one that was in
Nottingham, right? I was messaging her
some stuff like I was flirting with her.
Do you remember the one that gave me a
[ __ ] and we was kissing and [ __ ] And
then she was like, "Oh." Then she was
trying to say on the text that she
didn't feel comfortable. I was like,
"Well, you wasn't saying that when you
was sucking my [ __ ] dick and I was
sucking your [ __ ] tits and we was
kissing." I couldn't I couldn't [ __ ] her
cuz she was on her period. But I'm
thinking, "What the fuck?" And there was
no dickpicks. So, they are hypoc they
are hypocritical. They are hypocritical.
If it's anything, but the but they are hypocrites.
I think I was like flirting, but I
didn't say my dick or anything. I'm
thinking, "What the [ __ ]
Only if someone felt that uncomfortable,
they wouldn't be doing that stuff with
you the first time meeting you, you know.
I just don't I don't understand them. I
really really don't understand them.
It's like that one that sucked my dick
in the in in the alleyway. I bet you if
you tried flirting with her, she'd be
like, "Oh, nah, you're disgusting." I
said, "Come around. Let's let's if you
was like flirting with her via text,
she'd probably be like, "Oh, it's I'm
uncomfortable or and then she will suck
someone's dick in an alleyway." And I
don't I just don't get them. Or even
talking about kissing. What I mean by it
is more about kissing grievy. I'm
talking more about like bringing it up
as opposed to sending pictures. Like for
example, if you went on Reddit and you
turned around and said, "Oh, oh, we
should kiss." And and stuff like
flirting. They'll be like, "Oh." Cuz I
don't like pictures. I don't like people
sending me pictures.
I don't like people sending me pictures
either to be honest.
Uh I don't like pictures sent to me, but
they they would they will shy away and
be like, "Oh
yeah, I don't feel comfortable. I don't
want to talk about it." But then they
have sex. So it's just like you
shouldn't be scared to say that you like
sex and you like a good [ __ ]
you know? Don't shy away from it, you
Don't shy away from the from the fact
that you like dick, you know,
cuz you didn't get yourself pregnant,
did you? There was one that looked like
a proper [ __ ] on Instagram, right? She
looked like a proper stuck up [ __ ] bro,
with her friend. And I was like, you
didn't get yourself pregnant, did you?
You didn't [ __ ] slip over a tree and
the tree got you pregnant, did you? Do
you know what I mean, Grezy?
You got rammed hard. rammed hard. And I
know how much stamina that takes, you
know. I know how much stamina that takes, Greasy.
It takes a lot of stamina, you know.
So, but then they go on like they don't
like ST. So, I don't know. They're weirdos. Yeah.
They shy away from the topic, you know. weirdos.
So yeah, this woman replied, "Dusty,
I don't know why that one from Brazil
unblocked me if I if I sent her my
dick." So what does she actually want to
happen here? She unblocks people. She's
unenthusiastic. She replies back. Why
are you doing this if you're never ever
going to meet someone? I just I just
don't understand. Why are you doing
this? They went back to Brazil, by the
way. You're never going to meet someone.
It's just like they they they are
purposely a [ __ ] on purpose. This is
what I mean with them.
Good morning. If you're going to say
nonsense or anything pornographic, don't
even bother sending messages. Otherwise,
I'll block you again. I didn't like what
you did. So, if you do it again, I'll
block you and I won't unblock you again.
So, what do you want to do? What do you
want to do? talk about bor and stuff and
you keep being an unenthusiastic [ __ ]
being like a [ __ ] [ __ ] like you you all are.
This is how you know it's all women
because you never have these problem
with men, you know, with you know you
got like men like I've got I I made a
friend a month ago that lives in
Reading. I could easily message him
right now and say, "Do you want to go
for a beer today?" And he'd meet me just
like as a friend. You don't get these.
How they say that all women aren't the
same when it's only women that do this. Grievy
and they're going to be exactly how they
were a month ago. They're not going to
switch. They're not going to they're not
going to be a [ __ ]
with this women. It's it's it's [ __ ]
behavior. You know, Ant-Man will tell
you it's always [ __ ] behavior with them
time and time again. Buying games,
[ __ ] And again, if you don't want
to put yourself through it, you
shouldn't be classed as an incel.
We're bored of them. We're sick of them, you know.
Yeah. I don't know, bro.
And men shouldn't men shouldn't be told
to not men shouldn't be told not to give
up. If they want to give up, they can you know,
cuz what you're dealing with is toxic.
No, it's toxic. It's not normal. It's
immature. It's not even people playing
hard to get or, you know, people should
have to deal with that. People should >> Yeah. No,
like I keep saying, I'm surprised I
didn't give up years ago. Some patience
I have in it. Cuz think of Antman. Yeah.
He done that axe thing, Greavvesy. And
he's not tried nowhere near 10% of me.
So you got all of these people giving
you [ __ ] Greavesy,
but there's no one actually like
admiring you for how long you actually
put up with their [ __ ] how much money
you wasted, how how many times you went
out, the [ __ ] that you had to deal
with. No one like gives you credit as a
and they just go and hate on you.
Do you not think it's weird, bro?
That also goes to show that it's a
gender thing because the amount of times
I put up with their [ __ ] And I'm
telling you, bro, if it was anyone else,
they would have went and killed someone
by now. I'm telling you, they would
have. I'm telling you, they would have
or they would have just given up. But
then they then you got these people
hating on you. This is what I don't understand. You know,
and what do they do? Expect you to go
out and deal with it time and time again
with their [ __ ] Time and time and
time again for what? You know what? like
another year. No, bro. [ __ ] that.
If they don't, if they're being a [ __ ]
right? If this person's being a [ __ ]
if they're being a [ __ ] right?
If they're saying that they don't want
this, they don't want that, why have
they unblocked? Answer this question. If
these people don't play games, what is
it this person wants them?
This doesn't make any sense.
So, you found dick so disgusting that
you block someone and then you unblock them.
So you just want to play and be a [ __ ]
again basically. Yeah.
If you can't meet anyone that's normal.
Why? Why can't you come across anyone
that's normal? I was saying this to
Laney uh yesterday. She said all women
aren't the same. Bro, I was howling. I
was [ __ ] howling, bro. When she Yes.
When she said to me yesterday, "All
women aren't the same."
I was howling. I said that they're not
all the same. I said, "Women aren't all
I said women aren't all the same." I was
laughing my ass off, bro.
Well, I haven't been proven wrong. I I
don't I don't like to use the word
proven wrong because it makes it seem
like I always think I'm right. It's not
a case of being proven wrong. It's a
case of being shown different. I don't
like the word being proven wrong. So,
we're rephrase that. Um, they're they're not
I just don't understand how so many
different people can do and act the same way.
I just don't understand what how if
they're not all the same, how they can
do, say, and act the same way. Like the
make believe, the mind games, the
leading on. I just don't understand how
you will find all of these women that do
this, but you don't find men that do it,
which is the only other gender that you
can you can compare it to is men.
If there's only men and women, I just
find it very strange
how you don't find any men that do
exactly what they do, but yet women
aren't all the same.
It just seems very, very, very strange.
Um, Grezy, the [ __ ] behavior only comes
from them. It doesn't come from anyone
else. You can speak to a guy, you can
have a friend, you can have a man that's
a friend, right? And he could be your
friend and you can go out drinking with
him and they never switch. They never
switch. Maybe very, very rarely speak
one day normal, next day normal, next
month normal. It would never be a woman
that switches up. This is what I'm saying. So,
you know, if I was to sit there and
defend them, I'd be lying.
And then they say that they go for these
nice people and then they end up being
women abusers, which isn't right because
if that was the case, then they would be
going on dates with me all the time. Not
that I'd want that, but you know, I was
saying this to my mom yesterday. I said,
"I don't think that people abuse people
and they get with people that abuse
people at first, but they go for men
that are no good and then complain about all men."
I was saying that to my mom that
basically they basically go for people
that are no good. Um, and they always
pick the people that are no good and
then generalize all men. We've seen it
many times before, you know. So, um,
they go they don't go for anyone normal,
nice, or genuine. Um,
oh, that's another thing. Have you ever
heard of nice guys? Uh, Greavvesy.
Oh, here's another thing that you you're
probably not aware of. Have you ever
heard of nice guys?
I'll get into I'll explain this. It's
only it's not that long. Uh, basically
what I don't know if you're still here
before I uh explain this to you,
right? So, basically a nice guy is uh so
you know how they say that that women go
for nice guys, right? So, if you go out
and you be nice and you be genuine and
you say that you've been nice and
genuine, they have a problem with this.
Yeah, no one cares. Bye-bye. Uh,
and yeah, so basically, um, don't make
another account. No one cares, loser.
Please informant. Um, yeah. So, no,
we're just talking about women. We're
just talking about [ __ ] women.
Yeah, we're just talking about [ __ ] women.
No one cares. You little police
informant. You little police boy. No one
cares. You have You having to call the
police over YouTube just shows that you get owned.
Yeah. Women are just [ __ ] Yeah. We're
just talking about like the the Yeah. So
basically a nice guy is that if you said
you've been nice to a woman and then
she's a [ __ ] people start going at you
for it. They start mocking you saying
that you're um it's like a nice guy
thing that they say.
Oh, bottom line is it's just a gender thing
and it will always be a gender thing.
So yeah, it'll always be a gender thing.
And knock, no one cares about the
police. It just shows that when you call
the police over YouTube that you've been
owned. Did you see my video to Joseph Ferrar ghosting?
He's such a little biased nods lover.
This is what I don't understand why I
even waste my time with these people on here.
He never replied to me, by the way. Uh Jo,
he says to me, right, that no one can
take my word. No one respects my word.
Um but then I said, well, L is the
biggest liar on here. You're on his chat constantly.
you when I call nonslegs a virgin,
you're straight to his rescue like
Superman saying that he can't be a
virgin because he's got a disabled
girlfriend. Yet people are going at me um because
saying I'm a but when people are going
at me, you don't say anything. This is
I've come to the conclusion with this
website if you're not fat and ugly like
them um they're an undercover hater.
That's what I've noticed. Like you you
laugh at it, but I'm I'm starting to get
this vibe now with these people. I'm
starting to get this vibe that you know
these people that get along on this
website. Yeah. They're all like the same
in it. Fat, ugly, no life. And anyone
that's younger and better looking than
them, they will find problems with them.
Um, you know, and I've noticed that with
them. It is jealousy on here, bro. It is
definitely definitely jealousy on here.
Yeah. We're not talking about opinions.
We're talking about biased people. And
that Joseph Ferrar is definitely
definitely definitely biased. Definitely
definitely definitely biased. He is
biased, bro. 100%. You can't talk about
people [ __ ] lying when he's on a li
channel every day. They're biased.
Yeah. No, I'm just saying that they're
biased. That's all I'm saying is that they're biased.
Okay. No, no, no. Okay. I I I'll explain
what bias means. Okay. Well, let me
explain it again to y'all. Right. So,
the definition of biased. Okay. So, I'm
calling Nons a virgin.
Right. And he's straight to his rescue
saying that he can't be a virgin because
she's got a girlfriend.
Right. When Nons is calling me a virgin,
I don't see him to my rescue like
Superman defending me even though I've
stuck my dick up a woman's throat on a
porn video. Biased. Because you're quick
enough to defend someone, right, that
had a disabled girlfriend, but yet when
someone proves they've had sex, you're
not you're not saying anything. You're
letting them go at someone. Biased.
That's not a different opinion. That is
biased. Why have you got no opinion when
people are going at me calling me a
virgin? Why have you got no opinion when
people are going at me? Because they're
biased non-slubbers. I've noticed it
with these people in this community now.
And he said, and and and the Lord J
thing, I'll explain. He says that no one
can respect my word because I'm a liar.
So he doesn't come on my live stream
because I said I was going to go to
Thailand and I didn't go to Thailand.
No, I just I just don't like the
biasness. Nah, bro. I just don't like
biased people. I just don't like biased
people. Nah. See, when I'm when I'm
explaining it to you, you're telling me
that I care too much. You know, like
you're you're you're I'm I'm trying to
explain something to you and now you're
telling me that I care too much. I'm
saying my problem is is him being
biased. I don't care about his opinion.
You know, when you're calling Nodle Legs
a virgin, he's straight to his rescue.
Like, he's got a girlfriend. He can't be
a virgin. He's got a girlfriend. And
that's as soon as he started that, I
knew he was dodgy. I knew he's a biased
non-slover. And as soon as he started
that, I knew that these people were
jealous of me. Yeah.
No, it's not my opinion. It is He is
biased. No, no, no, no, no. It is a
fact. No, no, no, no, no. It is a fact.
It's not an opinion. It is a fact. It
actually happened. An opinion is I like
Undertaker and you like Don Cena. That's
different opinions. That is a fact. It
actually happens. Something that happens
is a fact. It's not an opinion. It's a
fact. I've seen it in black and white.
So it's not an opinion, it's a fact. A
fact is something that's happened. So
it's a fact because he's actually done
it. It's an fact. No, he's a biased
non-slover. He's fast enough to defend
to defend non legs and then when he's
talking [ __ ] about me, he's nowhere to
be seen. That's facts. It actually
happened. And with the LJ thing, I'll
explain it. I'll explain that one.
Sorry, bro. We're getting off that. He's
saying that he's got a problem with liars.
He's saying he's saying that he's uh
he's got a problem with liars. And to be
honest, I do need to stop commenting on
here to be honest with you. That is a
good point you made. I do really need to
stop commenting on it. Um I'm difficult
to to talk to. I've just explained to
you how this guy how this guy is biased
and you're saying that it's an opinion
and I'm and I'm and I'm difficult to
talk to. Are you a [ __ ] No. No. No.
No. No. No. No. Come back. Come back.
I've just explained to you I've just
took time out of my day to explain to
you how he is biased. I've explained to
you what he has done and you're saying
that it's an opinion. Are you a [ __ ]
bro? Are you a [ __ ] Bear in mind
like I'm not I've not like heard you
[ __ ] talk or anything, but bro, are
you are you a [ __ ] I've just
explained what bias means and what the
guy has done.
He is a biased nodla. It's not an
opinion. It's a fact. Opinion. An
opinion, right? Okay, an opinion is
something that is not set in stone. So
people have got different opinions. I
like blue. I like red. I like whatever.
I like this. I like that. I like this. I
like that. I like this. I like that. You
know that is an opinion, bro. Something
that's happened is a fact. Yeah.
Yeah. I know, right, bro? Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. Even though I've been in bed with
several different women. Yeah. Like I
said, you're biased, jealous,
non-slubbers. That's exactly why I got
three thumbs up. Because you're always
going to talk [ __ ] cuz you're jealous.
It's exactly why I got them three thumbs
up. Because everything that I say about
you little biased little jealous people,
I'm right about. I'm right. So, we all
know them three thumbs up, it is right.
It is 110% right. You are jealous of
anyone that's not fat and ugly. I
noticed this now from a long time, but I
didn't say anything about it. You know,
you pick your targets. Anyone that's
younger and better looking, you're an
undercover hater. I know it. I know it.
I know it. Well, has nonsle proved he's
had sex? Okay. Well, has nonsex proved
he's [ __ ] a woman? Has he proved he's
[ __ ] that girl that he's with? Okay,
let me ask you, let me ask you this
question. Has he proved that he's stuck
his dick in anyone? No. So, shut the
[ __ ] up. Has he proved that he's stuck
his dick up anyone?
Has he proved that he's had a [ __ ]
No. So, [ __ ] off, you little nonsubber.
This is what I mean with these people in
this community. They're little nons
lovers. That's why I come off of here
before for weeks, bro. Cuz they're
biased little nons lovers. That's what I
mean, bro. Why do you think you didn't
see me before for weeks? Cuz these
little biased nons lovers. They're
little fat, ugly little biased nons
lovers. Yeah, they are, bro.
Little bias nons lovers. And even when
you explain it to them, they still talk
[ __ ] You [ __ ] little pedo lovers. Yeah. [ __ ] idiots. Oh, boring.
Boring. We've heard all this before. [ __ ] boring.
We've heard all of this before
from the same name and the same account.
Boring. I'm not in my live stream
either. Boring. Get a life and get a
grip, you sad disabled people.
Get a life and get a grip, you sad, sad disabled people.
Still no reply.
Ask your buddy why he is still friends
with a guy confessed to nonsense child
in in Thailand and flee to Cambodia.
Shut the [ __ ] up, you fat ugly [ __ ]
You don't [ __ ] ask me nothing, you
fat ugly bongo. Right. So,
I've still not got this uh
response from Joseph Farra. So, I might
have to do a community post. I'm
generally I'm generally wanting his his
uh thing, right?
I'm generally wanting his thing.
I'll be back later, by the way. No, I'm
staying on for a little bit [ __ ] Sorry.
So, I need to write a community post. >> [laughter]
>> Good morning. >> [laughter]
>> Oh [clears throat] my god. This Monty's
an idiot, bro.
What did he say? That one's coming for
my arrest. He's an idiot. He's a [ __ ] [snorts]
He's a [ __ ] idiot. >> [laughter]
>> He's a [ __ ] idiot, isn't it?
Oh my god, that Mo account. You've been
doing this for 4 years. Does any of you
people have a life on there, bro? You've
been doing that for like [ __ ] years.
Come to kill him. Boring. And then you
wonder why the community is dead. But
then you wonder why the community is
dead. This is what I don't understand.
They wonder why the community is dead.
Maybe because the repeating and the
projection just bores people off, bro. Boring.
But don't forget these people are smart,
by the way.