Yeah, these people on here are blooming biased.
I seriously need to get off here
tomorrow, bro. 100%.
These disabled people are scrambling my
brain. They're scam. They're scrambling my brain.
It's a [ __ ] autistic community. My brain. Oh,
they're scrambling my [ __ ] brain.
They're so biased.
So biased, bro. They're [ __ ] idiots,
bro. I'm I'm I'm I am I'm going to come
off here, bro. 100%. I'm coming off here.
Nah, no one's jealous. They just sit on
YouTube stalking you and harassing you
every day. But they're not jealous. Nah, nah,
nah. These people definitely are not
jealous. Their lives are so good. Their
lives are better than everyone else's. Uh, wow.
Their lives are better than everyone else's. Yeah,
this is not fair. what this woman wrote on Instagram.
They said about me dying and dashing someone.
Then they said, "Well, this is exactly
why half of us will never trust men
based on the men that you go for. Based
on the men that you choose, it's the
same conversation. It's the men that you
choose to go for. [ __ ] hell. Shut up.
Stop moaning. Stop complaining. It's men
that you go for. It's men that you
choose to go for.
And I said, "No wonder people can't
trust women. They're all lying
bullshitting little [ __ ] that lead people on.
They're just lying [ __ ] [ __ ] that
just lead people on, which we which
should be illegal, by the way. Me and
Grey was talking about this. Stop
moaning and complaining about men.
[ __ ] sake." Ant-Man sent me something
earlier about this woman. She's uh she's
dating someone in death row. Yeah.
She's with somebody that's in death row.
Yeah. In America, by the way. I can send
you the article if you want. She's with
somebody that's in death row. But they
say they don't like these kind of
people. Death row. So there's no there's
no saying that she didn't know what he
was like because she she got with him
whilst he was actually in prison.
Contradicts the whole nice guy, nice
personality thing, doesn't it? Oh, these
simps have been lied to their whole
life. What did he do again? I can tell
you exactly what he done. Killed people, I think. Yeah.
Yeah. He killed people.
He called a pastor.
Yeah, so do you as well, you little
[ __ ] So do you.
You spend bare time on here as well,
bro. You're on here every day. You can't
take a day off of YouTube. Been proven
many times. So he killed an elderly
lady. So this guy actually killed people.
Well, that contradicts to them like nice
guys, doesn't it? Yeah.
Yeah. So yeah, what I was saying uh
earlier, it wasn't an opinion. It was a
fact. It was it wasn't an opinion. It
was an fact. It was a fact. I don't give
opinions. I say facts. Bounces can't hit
people. You people are so biased. Wasn't
you telling me to start on a man in the bookies, though?
No, I just don't like biased people. No,
I just don't like biased people to be
fair. Weren't you people telling me to
start on a man in the bookies?
You make up excuses.
Nah, it's hard for me to make friends.
I've got friends, mate. I've got more
than enough friends. I don't come on
here to make friends.
You pretty sure Lord J L J
was was telling me to go to a bookie. So
that's your Yeah, it's just it's all
right, but it's just all biasness on
here. It's just biasless and weirdo [ __ ] on here.
If a bouncer beat me up, you'd have no
problem with it. If a bouncer smashed my
face in, you'd have no problem with it.
You're saying You're only saying that is
because the bouncer took the L. Look at
the bus story. Everybody called me a
[ __ ] for not going at the bus driver
when he was talking [ __ ] to me. But then
when you talk [ __ ] to them, you say that
they're working. So, I just I don't
really understand you people.
You you just don't make any sense, do
you? At all. You just do not make no
sense. And I don't say I never said I
hate everyone on here.
I never said I hate everyone on here. I
said I hate majority of the people on here. Yeah.
Cuz they all come from LJ side. Yeah.
Because they're biased. They're they're
stalkers. They're harassers. Yeah. I
said the majority. I don't hate everyone on here.
No. Okay. Well, okay. Can you Okay,
then. I'm wrong then. Okay. Explain.
Okay. All right then. Well, can you
explain it to me then? I'm not always
right. So, it's okay for somebody that
works to go at me, but then when I go at
them, that's cowardy because they're at
work. Okay, you're right then and I'm
wrong. So, you explain to me how that
makes sense. No, no, no. I'm wrong. I'm
completely wrong. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. So, I can't go
for a bouncer cuz he's at work. But
yeah, it's okay for a bus driver to run
his mouth at me and I'm a [ __ ] Even
though apparently they're not
technically allowed to hit you because
they're at work. Okay. Okay, bro. Yeah,
I'm wrong. Okay. Okay. So, explain how
that makes sense.
I I'm talking about the biasness. I'm
talking about you the people on here being biased.
I'm speaking about you people being
biased. What have I said I'm right
about? I'm asking you. And I and I said
I will say that you the people on here
were jealous because of what you're
doing, not because of what I look like,
bro. Like I'm telling you, I'm I was
saying why I think you're jealous and I
was explaining it. I didn't just guess
it cuz they're stalking. They're
harassing. That's why I said that it's
like jealousy. That's that that's why I said it. So,
no, I'm just talking about people on
here generally being biased. That's what
I'm saying. I'm talking about people on
here generally being biased. I'm talking generally.
You think I look at some old man and
think, "Yeah, he's jealous of me." No,
we I I thought you were I think the
people on here were jealous because of
what they do on here. That's why.
Because of what they do, their actions,
not [ __ ] anything else.
It's because the stalking and the
harassing, bro. Like,
yeah, bro. I learned a new word. Yeah.
Yeah. I didn't know what bias meant. No,
I'm 28 and I just learned that word. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. Yeah. I just learned it, bro.
Yeah. At 28 years of age.
I think my eyesight's [ __ ] you know, bro. Hopefully not.
Just ordered some food, by the way.
Yeah, I thought I have to try and eat today.
I'm not negative, but I'm talking the
truth. When I'm talking about women, I'm
talking the truth. I'm not being
negative. I'm talking the truth. I've
had enough of it. I'm sick of them.
Sorry, bro. Sorry if it sounds negative
to you, but I'm not going to be fake.
Sorry. I'm just sick of them.
I'm not attacking the people in here.
I'm not attacking I'm I'm asking them
why they do what they do. I'm asking
them why they do what they do.
And yeah, women are [ __ ] which is
why I attack them, cuz they're
[ __ ] So yeah,
but we'll agree to disagree on that one. So yeah. Yeah.
That thing didn't work, bro. I need to
try and find someone else now who I can
dine and dash. I can I want to dine and
dash someone, bro. I just want to dine
and dash someone, but it's not going to
be easy. I could probably try and like
message a few other people. I want
revenge on these women. Yeah.
Bro, bro, anyone can say anything behind
a fake account, whatever.
I think it's weird that you are you are
on here every day doing what you're
doing. I think it's weird. I think it's [ __ ] weird.
I never said everyone's jealous. I said
a lot of people are jealous because of
their actions on here. It's an act of a
jealous person. That's what I said.
Okay. Updates. Yeah, I just want to find
someone to dine and dash ghost in basically.
Well, of course it is. I'm going to get
a lovely steak. What do you mean a
diamond and dashes? Of course it is.
Once I [ __ ] one over, I can just move on
my life, bro. I just want to [ __ ] one over.
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
I don't know. You people lie about a lot
of things. So
you you lie about a lot of [ __ ]
Well, you you lie about a lot. So
yeah, but they spend all day on YouTube.
I know, sugar.
Well, I'm not almost 30, but yeah. I
mean, I'm not almost 30. I'm nowhere
near 30, but yeah. Thank you. Don't
know, man. You lie about a lot of [ __ ]
I generally think like there's like 10%
of people in this community that work
and I think the rest of them are just
fat ugly people that failed at
everything in life. Taking their
failures out on you, Red Star, all of
these other people. Uh like I think like
10% of people work
like 10% are normal but the rest are
just [ __ ] losers and they and they
know they know who they are as well. So yeah,
no thanks, mate.
This is what that was my whole point is
that they saying that these people don't
have to be jealous.
Okay, you're not jealous. So why do you
do what you do every day on YouTube then?
Okay. So, why do you continuously stalk
people and harass people for years
making community posts on them? That's
acts of a jealous person. That's why I
said it. Not because of what I look
like. And [ __ ] I just I didn't I
didn't I didn't guess the [ __ ] I just
said it based on like what they're
doing. Why would someone that's got a
better life than you be doing that?
Stalking you on Reddit, stalking you on
anything and everything.
So, that's what makes me think that that
a lot of them are generous. Yeah. I
never said everyone. I do think that. I
generally believe it. Yeah. Because of
what they do on here,
but um yeah, I generally do, bro. Not
everyone obviously, but
I got a lot of haters, bro. A lot of
haters. So, and you have to think that
you're younger than them. These people
are [ __ ] old people. So, I don't
know. And and the fact that they don't
do it to many other people,
trust me, I don't think I'm better than
anyone. I really don't. It's just a vibe
that I'm getting by what they do.
And they and it's not like it was over
COVID or over the winter. They've been
doing it for years, bro. Like, they've
been doing this [ __ ] for years on here.
But they're not jealous.
But they're not jealous. They just spend
all their life every day bothering
people that they're better than.
Doesn't make any sense.
Does it make any sense whatsoever?
does not make no sense.
So, they sit on the internet recording
everything, stalking people, making community posts,
but they're not jealous.
I don't know what what what it is then.
If they're not what what is it? Are you bored or
I don't know, man. It's weird.
It is strange. It is strange.
I think they are jealous.
Hate to break it to you. I generally
think a lot of them are jealous.
You're younger. You know, you look
better. You got freedom. You can do what
you want. They're old fat ugly bums,
bro. They probably ain't got nothing in
their life. That's why they do this. So,
the people that are doing this, and if
you dare say you do it for a reaction,
I'm just going to come off of YouTube
again and prove that it's not for a
reaction cuz you you you've been doing
it for years, bro. It's no longer co,
you know? So, what what is it? What is
it, bro? It's it's what is it?
So, people like, uh, what's his face? Uh,
how hard he's a normal guy. I've met him
in person. He's like a 42. I don't know
how old he is now, but he's an actual
normal person. I've actually met him. I
don't think he's jealous of me. I think
he's I don't think he's jealous at all.
I think he's a normal guy.
Uh, that is a normal and he's got kids.
Uh, I don't think there's there's he's
not jealous of me. So, we don't pick
people and say they're jealous of me.
We're better than them. We're going by
your actions on here. I'm going by your
actions and the stalking, the harassing,
the group of people that are obsessed.
I'm going by the fact that what you're
doing on here. So, if you're not jealous,
[ __ ] knows what else it can be then. And
you don't do it for a reaction either,
cuz I'll just come off YouTube and not
react again for three months and prove
that you that you don't do it for
reaction. You don't do it for a
reaction, bro. Come on now. body, you know.
So, another thing, Joe, uh why you if if
you really believed, right, one second.
If you truly believed that I was picking
on that guy at work and he couldn't hit
me cuz he was at work, then why was no
one slating the bus driver that was
running up his mouth to me? Ghosting
wasn't uh here at this time, so he
doesn't remember it. though. Everybody
remembers that there was a black bus
driver running up his mouth calling me a wanker
and you called me a [ __ ] for not saying
anything back to him. But then when you
give it back to people then you're
saying that you can't hit them because
they're at work. I can't keep up with
it. Heads or tails? Heads or tails?
Which one is it? So I'm a [ __ ] for not
going at a bus driver. Yeah. The excuse
is always going to be they're at work.
Okay. So then I then I start on someone
that's well I retaliate to someone that
beats people up all the time
but then they can't hit me because I I
know at work. I I I'm not sure what what
side tied you on, bro. To be honest with
you, it doesn't really make you can see
that you're you're you're being a
hypocrite here. You're not stupid. Come
on, bro. It's not about people being at
work. If if a if there was a if there
was a man in the shock that batted the
[ __ ] out of me, no one would have that
he was at work.
Come on. It's ridiculous. Now,
you know, bounces beat people up all the
time. You saw it in Wales. You've seen
it in them videos. I've seen someone get body slammed.
Nope. Nope. Nope. I've had people try to
put their hands on me first. Nope. I've
had bouncers try to put their hands on
me first. And again, it doesn't matter.
If you generally believe that, you would
be calling that bus driver a [ __ ]
Okay. Okay. Okay. I'm not worth it.
Okay, so that bus driver that was given
at large to me is a [ __ ] then, isn't
it? So that bus that and they wouldn't
lose their job anyways. Um, but anyways,
okay. Okay. So, well, I've been all over
the country for years and I've had
bouncers try to put their hands on me, bro. So,
I mean, okay. Right. So, going by your
logic then. Okay. So, they're not
allowed to hit you cuz they're losing
their job. Okay. So, whatever. The
bouncer can't hit me. Okay. So, the bus
driver is a [ __ ] then. So, that black
bus driver from 5 years ago is a [ __ ]
right? For running up his mouth at me.
No, I can't hit him cuz he's at work.
You didn't say he was a [ __ ] You
called me a [ __ ] You No, no, no. You
said that I was a [ __ ] for not saying
anything back to the bus driver. But
when I do go for someone at work, you're
saying I can't. That's bad cuz they're at work.
So you can see how you're contradicting
yourself. No. And it doesn't matter
about his skin color. He just was a
black guy. Okay. Bus driver. Then when
this bus driver was going at me, you all
called me a [ __ ] Yeah. By your logic,
you should be calling him a coward
knowing that I won't be able to hit him
back because he's I quote at work. So
you can see how you're contradicting yourself. No,
Joe. You You can see how you're contradicting yourself.
You know you
you this bus driver was running up his
mouth calling me all sorts and people's
calling me a [ __ ] for not retaliating.
When I retaliate to someone at work I'm
picking I'm picking my targets. So
I I don't understand.
I don't do anything, bro. Lj come to my
door and he didn't do anything. He had
he had char several charges. Oh, we're
just going around in circles. This is
boring now, bro. We just go round and
round and round in circles. Round and
round. You've clearly got some kind of
disability. I've just tried to explain a
a scenario to you and just just forget
now, bro. You don't understand. We're
just going round and round in circles.
Right. Right. Right.
Okay. But when I'm going at the bouncer,
right, we're just going around in
circles. Just move on from this. You're
not getting what I'm saying. You're
clearly biased and that's it. You're
you're not you're not understanding
right. You are saying I'm going to
explain this one more time to open up
your ears and open up them properly. You
said that me going for that bouncer is
me being a coward because he can't fight
back because he is at work. Yeah.
Because he's at work, he can't hit me.
So, I'm being a coward, right? But you
had no problem with the bus driver
running up his mouth to me and then when
I didn't retaliate, you're calling me a
[ __ ] Yeah. When I do retaliate, oh,
he's at work. So, what's the answer
then, bro? So, which one is it? So,
which one is it? So, which one is it?
So, which one is it? So, so I can't go.
So, it it's not that they're at work
when they're winning against me, but
then when I win against them, oh,
they're at work. You need to make up
your mind. Which one is it? So, is it
when they're slating me, get in there,
son, but then when I retaliate, oh,
they're at work. They're at work. It
Which one is it, bro? I don't
understand. Like I can give you a few examples.
Um I could give you, you know, a few
different examples. You literally bigged
up that [ __ ] bus driver. So you're
not answering the question. See, you're
not answering the question. So you're
not answering the question. No, she
didn't. No, she [ __ ] didn't destroy me.
It's It's from me.
One six. Yeah, bro.
Yeah. So, I've just I've just asked you
something and you can't answer it.
I've just asked you something and you
can't answer it.
>> What are you doing? Building up a tree.
>> See these people are here. I've just
asked you a question and you've just
ignored it. You're just you're just
avoiding the question. I'm going to stop
wasting my time with you. You bias
jealous losers from tomorrow. Anyways,
I've just asked you a question
and you can't answer it. You just keep
ignoring it over and over and over again.
So, you can't hit bus driver when you're
giving it to them, but when they're
giving it to you, it's no problem. get
so [ __ ] on this community, you know,
right? This is what I mean with these
people. Now, I've asked you, why is it
okay for a bus driver to give it a big
and you all call me a [ __ ] But then
when I retaliate, oh, he's at work. He's
at work. And then I show you loads of
videos about just beating people up. I'm
not understanding it. This one, I'm
really not understanding it. It's cuz
you're biased. This is that that's that
is the that is the reason. It's cuz
you're biased, you know.
And I didn't shut up on the bus. I told
her to [ __ ] off the ugly crackhead.
Again, you people always make up stuff.
This is why I'm done with you. I'm done
after today. I'm done with this disabled
community after today, bro. 100%. They
always are going to be jealous of me and
make up stuff. That's why I'm leaving.
I'm coming off this [ __ ] Mark my word from tomorrow.
You're biased. You're jealous. And it's
[ __ ] that people don't need in their
life. My mom was right about all you people. You know,
I've already I've explained it to you
about 100 times.
I've explained it to you about 100 times
and you're not listening. Have you got
brain damage or something?
You're saying to me that when I go out a
bouncer, right, you when I'm going out a
bouncer, oh, he's at work. He can't hit
people. Yeah. Bounces hit people all the
time. Yeah. But then when that bus
driver was going at me, "Oh, you're a
[ __ ] The bus driver owns you." Knowing
that damn well every time I defend
myself, it's going to be he's at work.
He's at work. This is your little
biasless. You're so disabled that you
don't even realize it.
You're so disabled that you don't even realize it.
Whenever you defend yourself against
someone, it's going to be, "Well, you
know who's at work. You know, it's the
same old excuse with you little losers."
But then when a bus driver gives it to
me, it's pointless because you're wrong.
Because you know what I'm saying is the
truth. It's pointless because you're
wrong. And what I'm saying is the truth.
You had no problem with that bus driver
giving it large. But when I defend
myself, oh, he's at work. You pick your
targets. You contradict yourself. You
contradict yourself. No, I'm not
autistic, but you people are. You people
are definitely autistic. I have just
explained something to you about a
million times, and you don't get it in
your thick head. You do not get it in
your thick head. I've explained it to
you about 10 times in your thick skull
and you don't even realize it.
Don't mean it respectfully. I'm meaning
it disrespectfully. You are [ __ ]
autistic. I have just explained
something to you 10 times and you don't understand it. You know
it's [ __ ] mad. I've explained
something to you about 10 times now and
you still don't understand it. They're mad.
You're never going to win with these
jealous biased people. I should have
listened a long time ago to Ronald Pump
with these jealous people that don't
leave people alone. I'm off tomorrow,
right? 100%. I'm off tomorrow.
I've explained something to you 10 times
and your [ __ ] ass can't even answer
it. You can't even give an account.
Well, if I'm not right, if I'm not
right, then answer it [ __ ] If I'm
not right, then aren't to eat this [ __ ]
If I'm not right, then aren't eating
this [ __ ] Why is it all right for
people at work to go for me, but then
when I do it? Oh, you pick your targets.
Explain it, [ __ ] I'm all ears.
I'm all ears, you [ __ ] autistic
[ __ ] And I'm meaning it disrespectfully,
right? I'm asking you the question, so
explain it, fo. Explain it.
Explain it, guys.
[snorts] Yeah, because you know that I'm
right. You know that I'm [ __ ] right.
There's no talking to you. You're
[ __ ] disabled. I've explained the same thing.
Oh my god.
Okay. Can you tell me what you think of
this, Mom? Yeah. Let Let me ask you this
question. Right. They say that if you
start on a bouncer, you're you're
picking your targets because they're at
work. Yeah. When a bus driver was going
at me, they had no problems. There was
none of these excuses. What is it then?
>> What is it? It's They're contradicting
themselves, aren't they? They're
definitely contradicting themselves.
They're [ __ ] retards. I've literally
had to go and and ask an old woman. I've
had to go to an ask an old [ __ ] woman
to just to ask a question because you
dummies can't even answer it. Something
that's probably you know, not throw off dementia
because you're so dumb that you can't
even answer it. You [ __ ] retards.
You [ __ ] retards, bro. They are
demented, bro. I swear I swear they're
disabled in this community, bro.
I swear they're [ __ ] disabled.
Oh, I got nice middle breast, bro.
You just don't like being proven wrong.
Shouldn't you be Shouldn't you be
backing up your boyfriend, Joseph?
Anyways, lad, shouldn't you be broke?
Shouldn't you be backing up your boyfriend? boyfriend, lad?
[ __ ] told you.
Shouldn't you be backing up your boyfriend? [snorts]
Bro, I'm not answering your questions.
You don't answer my questions. I'm not answering yours.
I'm not answering your questions.
Can I ask your can I ask your opinion on something? Right.
And I want you to tell the truth. Like
if you disagree with me, disagree with
me. If you agree with me, agree with me.
Yeah. Don't feel that you need to agree
with me. Right? Now, I'm saying that
these people in here were biased because
listen to me. Yeah.
Not as much as you fat ugly [ __ ] [snorts]
Not as much as you fat ugly [ __ ] that
obese. Now dusty. Right. Here's here's
where we're at. Yeah. Again, disagree
with me if you want. I don't care. Right.
We're basically talking about how these
people are biased, right? That you've
been on here many years, right? When I
stuck up to myself to that bouncer. Oh,
he's at work. He's at work. you beat
your targets. But yet when a bus driver
was calling me every name under the sun,
people's laughing at me. They weren't
calling him a cow would say that you
can't hit him because he's at work or he
knows you can't hit him because he's at
work. So they say what suits themselves.
No one ever said to me that, "Oh, he's a
cow with that bus driver cuz he knows
you can't hit him." You'll notice as
soon as you sign up to yourself on here,
oh, you pick your targets. He's at work.
It's the oldest excuse going with these
bongos. Every time they're proven wrong. Yeah,
that [ __ ] mad in their head, bro.
It's not disagreeing.
You make up stuff when you're proven wrong.
When you're proven wrong, you shut up
just like you have done. What's your
opinion on it, Dusty?
I don't go nuts.
You're ignoring me because you know I'm
right. cuz you know I'm right.
You don't think that it was at it was
cuz he's at work. Every time you fat
ugly jealous people get shown wrong, you
make up stuff. You're demented. It's
like what my mom just said. You're demented. Yeah.
Yeah. But what's your opinion on it, bro?
What's your opinion on it? [ __ ] idiot.
I've already explained to you why I said
that about women. I've already answered
your question. I've already explained
why I don't like them.
you people. A lot of people on here are
really disabled, bro. Really disabled.
You don't like taking L's. You've got
all of these excuses.
They're jealous of me. That's why I'm
leaving this community. I don't want to
be on here with a bunch of fat, jealous
people. Wasting my life. [ __ ] that, bro.
And you can keep saying that you're not
jealous all you want. Your actions show
otherwise. I'm done after today, bro.
[ __ ] all of you. Yeah, [ __ ] all of you haters, bro. [sighs]
No, I'm calling you disabled. Okay,
whatever. I'm calling you disabled
because when you're proven wrong, you
deny it. You can't be shown different.
That's disabilities. I stuck it on a bouncer.
I've shown bouncers.
No, he doesn't, Dusty. No, he doesn't.
No, he doesn't. Plenty of bounces have
fight fought people before. No, they
don't. See, you're just making excuses.
You can't win with these people. I'm
done, bro. You can't win with these
people. Okay. And what if a bus driver
hits you? Okay. So, what if what if a
bus driver hits you?
And what if a bus driver hits you?
You're making excuses because the guy
lost. It's not because he's working. You
jealous people always make excuses.
That's why I'm done with you. This is
exactly why I didn't want to put
anything out there because you're
jealous and biased. There's no point.
Yeah. You can't sit there and say to me
how somebody can't hit me because
they've got an SI badge, yet you've got
no problem and someone that's working is
giving it to me.
Yes. But what I'm saying, Dusty, is that
is the bus driver. You're not
understanding it. We're going round and
around in circles again. I'm saying to
you that when the bus driver was giving
me the was giving it the big, no one
said that he's a coward knowing that I
can't attack him. Everyone was going him
saying, "You're a [ __ ] You're a [ __ ]
You're a pussy." Yet, if I reacted,
they'll be like, "Oh, well, he's
working." This is what I'm saying. It's
narcissistic people in this community.
This is what I'm saying, bro.
Listen. No. No. Dusty, right? He Dusty
doesn't know about the bus situation.
Years ago, I was on a bus. Yeah. I was
on the bus to uh to um two admirals and
this bus driver was giving it lodge. But
then if I reply back, it's they're
losing their job. That's what I'm
saying. They're narcissists. It's one
rule for one, one rule for another. If
they genuinely thought that somebody
can't attack you, right, without losing
their job, they would be calling a bus
driver a coward knowing that you
wouldn't be able to react back. But they
didn't. They didn't. But then when you
do react back, they use their job as an
excuse. It's narcissism. And I've just
explained it again. I have literally
explained it to you. I'm explaining it
like a [ __ ] to you again. Yeah.
If somebody can't lose their job. Yeah.
I care cuz I'm sick of you biased little
mongos. I give a [ __ ] I care. You
little mong. Yeah. Simple.
I care because you're [ __ ] biased
little fat mongs. That's why I care. And
I hate all of you on here, bro. Yeah.
That's right, bro.
Trying to explain stuff to people that
ain't got a brain. It's like a I need to
I need to stop. They're so disabled.
They don't understand it.
Have they got a mental disability, bro?
They've definitely got a mental
disability. I was just saying this to my
mom as well. They're clearly clearly
disabled on it. clearly clearly
disabled. I mean, the fact that they've
been on here for 10 years doing what
they do, they're clearly special needs.
It's like trying to explain to a special
needs kid a special needs kid that can't
be shown different. It's like explaining
it to a special need kid.
I'm I'm off tomorrow.
Bongo. Anyways, I'm not I'm not reacting that.
Get off of YouTube and get a life, you
little [ __ ] That's going to be my last
response to you as well. [ __ ]
Yeah, you got no problem with a bus
driver going at me, huh? But as soon as
Peter Belly wins Oh, he's at work. Oh,
he's at work. [ __ ] mongos. [ __ ]
mongos. What about all the other people
that weren't at work?
[ __ ] Mong. Jealous, fat, ugly,
narcissistic people. Fat Mongs. I'm off here tomorrow.
[ __ ] little S.
Yeah. [clears throat]
Little low life.
Well, people Well, why did you say to
the bus driver then? Well, well, tell
why is the bus driver going for people
when he knows people can't hit him then?
Well, then if you're at work, then you
shouldn't be giving it the bigger then,
should you, coward?
Well, if you're at work, stop starting
with people then. Stop starting with
people if you're at work. Simple. You
[ __ ] disabled Mong. [ __ ] you and your
ugly misses, bro. Listen, Ghost, listen.
I will happily meet you and slap you in
your ugly misses. You're annoying me
now, bro. I will I I will meet you and
I'll slap you in your ugly misses.
You're annoying me now, bro. Yeah,
you're annoying me now. Let me come and
slap your misses. Let me come and slap
your misses in her face. Let me abuse a
woman in front of you and I'll show you
what I agree with. I'm sick of this now,
bro. You know what? I'm going to give
you I'm going to give you I'm going to
give you my number and I'm coming here Saturday, bro.
I'm going to slap you. I'll slap your
misses and kick her teeth in, bro. [ __ ]
this, bro. I'm going to give you I'm
going to give you my number in a minute.
One sec. Let me eat this chicken. Buff.
[snorts] I will tell you about yourself
and women to your women's face, big man.
I'm sick of people like you. I'm sick of
people like you trying to look good for
women. [ __ ] this. I'll kick your teeth
out as well. [ __ ] this, bro. Let me
finish this chicken, bro. I'm saying my
[ __ ] number, bro.
Bring your misses. I'll slap her in her
ugly face and make her suck my [ __ ] dick. Yeah.
Bring your ugly misses. I'll kick her
right in that [ __ ] big man and see what
you're about. Yeah.
One second, bro.
One second, bro. I'm coming there
Monday, bro. Saturday. Sorry. I'm coming
there Saturday, bro.
I will tell you about your misses and
how I feel about women to your M's face.
Don't try and look good for women to me,
bro. Don't even try to look good women
in front of me. I'll smash your [ __ ]
mouth out. Come and see me, bro. I'm
coming there Saturday. I'm coming there Saturday, bro.
Don't even try and look good in front of
women. I'll smack your teeth down, you
cheek, you little [ __ ] I'll smack your
teeth down your throat. Don't even try
and look good in front of women. Well,
that is a That is an L right there, bro.
That's like taking a bird. That's taking
a bird. You think you're going to try
and look good in front of women for me, bro? No.
Yeah, I will, bro. I will.
I won't lie as well.
Bring your misses as well so I can tell
you and her about women to your face cuz
I'll say what I want. Yeah. Make sure.
Make sure, bro. Make sure. Make sure.
Yeah. I want to tell you about women and
how they punch their face. Big man. I
want to see what you do about it to your
face. Big man. Come on, big man. Defend
the woman in front of me, big man. Do it
Yeah, I know. It's on the way to
Southampton. I know it is. Let's see you
defending a woman in front of me, big
man. in front of me, big man. Defend a
woman in front of me, big man. Come on.
Just do it Saturday. Come on. Tell me
about women to my face, big man. And
I'll smack your teeth down your throat.
Let me smack your teeth down your
throat. Try to [ __ ] try and defend a
woman in front of me. Try and defend a
woman in front of me, big man.
Try and defend a woman in front of me,
big man. See what happens.
Try and defend a woman. Bring your
girlfriend. And I'll smack her teeth
down her throat and tell her to get what
to her face. I will say it to her face
and look her in the eye. I'll say, "Come
on, big man. Come on, big man. I am
going to show up Saturday." Yeah. No.
I want to tell her to her face about how
she's a little victim and I want to do
it in front of you cuz you're not going
to do anything to me. You're not going
to do anything to me, bro. But
does anyone care what you people say?
You haven't even gone to my address when
you knew where I live for god knows how
long. You knew where I live for how
long. And you ain't been on my door.
Stop projecting, bro. We've been further
than cha before. We've been all over the
country. We're not like you little Mongs
that can't go on someone's door. I think
you're getting me and you confused
again, bro. We're not these little Mongs.
Yeah. Yeah. Well, what about the bus
driver giving it the big mate? You fat,
ugly people are full of excuses. Think
of new excuses. Anyways, are you going
to bring your misses? Yeah. So, I can
talk about women to your face. Let's see
you be a man. Let's see you be a man.
I'm going to spit in her face as well,
bro. I'm going to be ah and spit in her
face. I'll take it out on your misses.
Don't come on here and try and tell me
what you agree and you don't agree with,
bro. I'll come to your little farmer
area. I'll come to your little farm area
and I'll tell her to her face in front
of a man and I'll do it in front of a
man how I feel about women and what
they're like in front of you whilst
looking at you. You little farmer boy.
Yeah. Are you going to bring your
mission though? You little farmer boy.
You you little farmer. I'll tell you
about your skank ugly message to your
face. Skunk [ __ ] Victim [ __ ] I'll
spit in her mouth, [ __ ] I'll take that
on her. I'll take that on you and her. I
agree with it. I absolutely agree with
it. And I'm going to show you how I
agree with it on Saturday. Watch you
little [ __ ] [ __ ] I'm coming, bro.
100%. I'm coming. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. You What do you talk like?
You talk like a little Mong boy. You
talk like a little Mong. I know how you
talk. I've been to Chichester. I've been
there. I haven't been to Southampton,
but I've been to Chichester when I was
working when I was 19. I haven't been to
Southampton. But I heard how you talk.
I've heard how you talk, bro.
Oh, you forgetting I've been all over
the country. I haven't been to
Southampton, but I've been to Chicha.
Yes, I have when I was working there
years ago. I haven't been to
Southampton, but yeah,
[ __ ] little farmer boy.
Little farmer boy, bro. I'll see you on Saturday. Yeah.
And see if you're not going to defend no
woman in front of me, bro. You're not
going to defend no woman in front of me,
boy. Boy, you're not going to defend no
woman in front of me. Now, the thing is, bro,
I could say that you could beat me. Yeah.
Or whatever. But you're not defending a
woman in front of me, bro. No matter
what it takes. I hate men that defend
women. Men that try to look good for
women. [ __ ] that, bro. I'd rather get
killed. Men that try to look good for
women. I hate it. And I'll do anything
to my power, bro. I don't like white
lights. I don't like little men that try
to look good for women. They're little
virgins. Even though I know what they're
like. They're scum. People that try to
look good for women, they're scumbags. I
I go mad, bro. Trust me. Mad. I will I
will not let that let that that lie, bro.
I'm going to be there 6:00 p.m.
Yeah. Try and tell me what you agree and
disagree with in my face about women,
bro. I don't care about the other stuff. Yeah.
I'm going to bring a piss bottle and
[ __ ] splatter in your face, bro.
How early do you want it?
Okay. 3 p.m.
I I'm going I'm going to Chester on Saturday, bro.
I'm going to [ __ ] this guy's Mrs. up.
I'm going to [ __ ] her up, bro.
I'm going to go [ __ ] her all talk this
land again. I've been all over the
country. None of you people been in my
door. Stop projecting. Peter Ben has
been all over the country. None of you
people have been on my door. Y will
talk. No, no. Y will talk. No, no, no,
no. One second. Y will talk, bro. Yeah.
You are the ones that have people's
addresses, but you're sat on there being
disabled every day. Bro, Peter Bed has
been all over the country. Peter Bed is
very well traveled.
I am disrespecting you. I'm
disrespecting your business as well.
Yes, I [ __ ] am.
Yes, I [ __ ] am. I hate women and I
hate people that defend women. Men. I
hate men that defend women. I hate men
that defend women. Whatever. All right,
Mr. G. Peter Bell has been all over the
country. None of you Mongs have ever
been on my door. You have had the ticket
to the golden nugget and you ain't done
nothing. Bro, you people are more than
all talk. You know all about being all talk, lad.
I am insane. I am insane, bro. I [ __ ]
am. I [ __ ] am to be fair.
No, you're going to see me when I'm
there. No. No. I'm going to be live when
I'm there. You're going to see me when
I'm [ __ ] there.
Oh, mate. No one cares about your Sim
comments. I've already shown videos of
what women are like. I've already shown
women and what they're like.
I've already shown the bad women, mate.
No one cares about your Sim comments.
We've shown the bad women, the bad,
nasty women. No one cares about your
dismissive white knight comments. So,
there's no point writing them. There's
no point writing them, bro. We've
already seen women being bad. Yeah,
women need bad as well. Women Women. Hey, bro.
Yeah, women need help as well. [ __ ]
There's a woman dating a man on death
row in America. And we need help. We
need help. There was a woman, Antman
showed me this article about an hour and
a half ago. This woman is dating a man
in death row and we need help. Stop
projecting, bro. The guy, he killed an
older lady and we need help. Never the
women. Never the people that's got a
[ __ ] in between their legs, mate. She's
dating a man in death row that's killed
an old lady. She got with him whilst he
was in prison.
Women are the ones that need help. Stop
projecting. They're the ones that need
[ __ ] help. These [ __ ] loser women.
And I'll see you on Saturday. Yeah.
All right, cool.
I'll be there for one. Yeah.
Yeah, bro. Yeah. Chester. Yeah. Okay,
cool. Easy. I think you get there from
Waterloo, don't you? Is it Waterloo?
Yeah, I think it's Waterloo. Yeah. Yeah.
I'll see you on Saturday. One. I don't
want to see you defend women to my face.
I will bang your teeth down your throat
if you think you're going to try and
tell me about women to my face and
you're going to try and tell me about
experiences to my face. I will bang you
so hard in your mouth, boy. All of your
teeth are going to go go you're going to
swallow your teeth. Don't even think
you're going to try and look good in
front of women for me, bro. And I will
use a weapon if I have to, bro. There's
no way this little [ __ ] is going to keep
defending women in front of me, bro.
Yeah. I will see you at 1:00 on
Saturday. Yeah. Simple. Yeah, good. Good
deal, bro. Deal.
100%. Saturday, 1 p.m. Yeah, done deal.
Greasy will be looking forward to this.
I just don't like people that that that
defend women to look good. If it was
kids, I wouldn't mind kids, children.
But I know the scum of what women are
like. I've got all the evidence. I've
got all my experiences. So when people
are defending him, when people are
defending him, bro, it drives me mad,
Mr. B. No, this guy's getting it on
Saturday, bro. This guy's getting it on Saturday.
This guy's getting it on Saturday. All
he's going to get is one to his face,
bro, and that's it. Be a big man in
front of women to me, big man. Come on,
big man. This [ __ ] ghosting account.
This ghosting account.
Yeah, I'm going to hack him in his face,
bro. I'm going to the [ __ ] in his face,
bro. I swear down, bro. I've already
been laid more times than you, you
little virgin. You've seen me in bed and
you've never been with a woman, you
little virgin. Another self-p projecting
comment, mate. Another self-p projecting
comment, bro. I've been laid more times
than you. You are still virgins, mate.
Over the years, we've only seen me with women.
Yeah, you people are absolute virgins.
So, mate, there's no chance of you
getting laid. There's no chance of you
getting laid. You [ __ ] absolute
virgins. We've all seen you around
women. You've ever been seen with a with
a woman, mate. You're [ __ ] lowife
little ugly virgins. I don't know how
long you're going to keep this self-p
projecting [ __ ] up for. You don't get
bored of it. Like it what, bro? What
year is it next year? 2026. And you're
still projecting fat ugly people on
YouTube every day projecting get a life.
When are you people going to get a life,
mate? Seriously, lad,
when are you fat, ugly disabled people
going to get off life, get get alive and
[ __ ] fix your disabilities? When are
you fat, ugly nerds going to get off the
internet and get a life? But I generally
think they need to cut your internet,
bro. Get off YouTube. Stop being a
[ __ ] Get a life, you little Mongs.
Stop talking about people that you don't
know. Get a life, bro.
Yeah, we'll see in it, bro. We'll see.
I won't show I can't afford it. I can't
af Bro, I can't afford it. Self
projecting again, Ghost. Bro, I've got
more money than you would ever have
again. Stop talking about people that
you don't know. Another problem with you
disabled mongos. You assume everyone's
got the same life as you. I can't afford
a what? A 30 ticket, bro. Bro, I can't
afford a 30 ticket, bro. Come on. Come
on. Come on. [ __ ] idiot. [ __ ]
Mongs on this community. I swear there
[ __ ] Mongs on here, bro.
You're [ __ ] I can't afford a 30 ticket.
I Bro, what the [ __ ] are you talking
about, bro? You're not even believing
what you're saying.
Yeah. Make sure your woman's there as
well, bro. If your woman's not there,
I'm not I'm not I'm I'm going to walk
away from you. I only want to disrespect
her in front of you. This is why I'm
doing this. I want to disrespect a woman
in front of you. I want to do it in
front of you. If if she's not there,
then I'm just going to walk off. I want
to see what you're about. Big man
defending women. Big man defending
women. Defend a woman in front of me.
Defend a woman in front of me. Big man.
Defend a [ __ ] woman in front of me. >> [sighs] [snorts]
>> I hate people that defend women, bro. I
hate men that defend women. I [ __ ]
hate men that defend women, bro.
You can defend a child.
You can defend a child, lad.
Yeah. You ain't ironing [ __ ] out, bro.
I'll see you on Saturday. Yeah.
When are you little nerds going to get a
life anyways, Mr. B? When are these
people going to get a life on here, bro?
These little sad little virgins. When
are they going to get a life? These sad virgins.
I need to wash my hands now. Make myself
a copper [ __ ] I just had that chicken leg. What?
You're going to lose.
You're going to lose your vard.
Autumn, when you going to lose your vcard?
Yeah, I did. I just hate women. Autumn.
Sorry, I was just making a copper [ __ ]
No, I just hate women.
They're evil little [ __ ] I hate them.
Yeah, I just hate him.
I [ __ ] hate him. So, this is why I
don't mind meeting this guy, bro. I
don't mind meeting this guy. I just hate
these women. They're [ __ ] scum to earth.
[ __ ] [ __ ] Scum of the earth
video. Yeah. Titled leading on should be a crime.
Yeah. Greasy would Greasy would love
that. I definitely think that leading
people on should be a crime.
um they're making all of these laws for
but saying that they'll probably just
pretend that you didn't do it in it and
then they'll just dis just miss your
struggles. But no, I mean if you show
like proper evidence that you've been
led on, it should be illegal.
These [ __ ] women,
this guy's not going to eye me out, bro.
Trust me, Peter Bell is good with headbutts, you know.
I just hate women. Plain and simple. Bad
experiences do that. So, still haven't
found somebody to die in a dash yet.
Nah, women are [ __ ] Nah, it's
definitely a gender thing. Women are
[ __ ] I'm trying to dine and dash
someone, but I still can't find someone yet.
Just dying and dash, you know, just to
rattle these people in this community.
just to just just to rattle all these
people on here,
you know. No, the gender definitely does
matter. Women are definitely definitely
definitely definitely [ __ ] But even if
everyone's a [ __ ] women don't get
called out for being [ __ ]
Women don't get called out for being
[ __ ] Men do, but women don't. Women
are angels. Women are perfect. Women
don't lead people on. Women are not
toxic. Nah, women don't do anything.
Women are angels.
I [ __ ] hate women, bro. I would love
for somebody to [ __ ] defend a woman
in front of me right now. Oh, I would love it.
[ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] women. They're
Oh, yeah. I'm going to run up that
[ __ ] 500 bill as well. I'm going to
[ __ ] run up that 500 bill.
mad. Just got
this this Barkclay's manager.
I messaged this Barclay's manager. He
opened my account when I was 18
and he just messaged me back on [ __ ]
He just messaged me back on uh Facebook now. Mad. [laughter]
Wow. Where the [ __ ] did them 10 years
go? Jesus Christ. Madness. Yeah. >> [laughter] >> for
he showing his new house this morning.
He's going to get doxed again.
>> She's going to get doxed again.
Could you imagine? I didn't bring
[ __ ] Monty on here and Virgin Boy and
I was just on here by myself
like no Virgin Boy, no Monty. Could you
imagine? I didn't bring the Virgin [laughter]
Monty. That's [ __ ] bad, isn't it?
That Virgin [ __ ] [laughter] Yeah.
I don't I don't I don't I don't fake laugh.
You fat [ __ ]
You're a fatty autumn. You're a fat
You're a fat pig that uses filters.
That's what you are, fat pig. [laughter]
Do you remember someone said you could
be my mama for the winner? [laughter]
Nah, autumn. Not Peter Belly's mama. [clears throat] [laughter]
No, you're not my mama. Laugh him. Not be mama.
Taking a baby away from its mama.
Autumn. Away from its mama.
I was thinking of [laughter]
I was thinking of starting that.
I'm thinking I'm thinking of starting on
that American [ __ ] yesterday.
This guy gave me his number.
Yeah, he he he used to work in Barclays
10 years ago and I looked up his name
and I messaged him months ago and he just replied.
That is weird, bro.
gown smells like [ __ ] BO.
It smells like bloody BO. My dressing
gown. Oh gosh,
it smells like BO in here.
I can't remember the last time I showered. >> [laughter]
>> Yeah. Taking a baby away from its mama.
[snorts] Taking a baby away from its mama.
from the baby.
He already found his mama. Yeah. Yeah, man. [laughter] M.
>> Oh gosh.
I hardly grieves you without content.
The poor [ __ ] [laughter] Oh gosh.
Yeah. So, I was just saying to this
woman and she's trying to say that all
men are the same.
All men are the same.
No. All women are the same. Not all men
are the same. All women are the same.
The men that you keep choosing are all
the same. No, no, no, no, no, no. The
men that you keep choosing are the same.
Not all men are the same. all the men
that you keep choosing with me. All
women I come across are the same. So
there's a big there's a big difference.
No, no, no, no. All women are definitely
the same. Men are not all the same. And
they're not all the same because I can
speak for my own experiences that when
I've gone out and approached and I've
not been like these people. So I can
tell you for straight [snorts] facts
that all women are the same. You know,
when you come across people that are
normal, you you're not interested. So,
why why are you
I don't. Hey, UK asylum. Yeah. Can I Can
I Can I tell you something?
Can Can I have your opinion on this?
Can I have your opinion on this, Captain?
Captain [ __ ] can I have your opinion on
this? Captain C. No, I'm joking. Can I
have your I'm arguing with this woman on Instagram.
She's saying that basically. Well, so
she's saying men are all the same and
I'm saying women are all the same. I'm
saying to her that the men that you keep
going for all the same and all of the
women that I come across are all the
same. There's a big difference. I think
that there's a big difference. UK
asylum, think about it, right? These
women are sat there saying that all men
are the same. They can't find someone.
Bro, how many times have I approached
people and they have wrote so many good
messages, but for some reason they're
not interested. So why do they keep
saying men are all the same when when
they're shown different and they get given opportunities,
right? Then they're not interested. So
why do they keep saying men are all the
same? I've never been shown different.
I've never been shown a woman different,
which is why I'm saying it.
You know, at the end of the day, I I I
listen, UK asylum, right? I met someone
about a month ago. Yeah. When I was
doing them 50 approaches and I was
speaking to them on Snapchat and there's
like, "Oh, thank you for coming up to
me. You're sweet." And well, then why
wouldn't you get with me then? If
they're truly wanting good people, UK
asylum, they'd be giving you the chance.
They go for these men knowing that
they're no good and then they complain
about all men. Whereas me,
I [ __ ] it's all I ever come across is
bad women. No matter how many times
people say they're not all the same. And
she said, "Oh, all women are different."
No, women are not all different. Women
are not all [ __ ] different. And I've
met more women than they've met men. So,
how can she sit there and say all women
are different? There's a woman dating a
guy in death row. How are all women
different? [ __ ] off, mate. about all all different.
How how are all Okay, she's saying to me
about how are all the people that I go
for [ __ ] because
and and all of the women I go for not
[ __ ] because I'm approaching women
on the street. You I'm pretty sure you
have got a guy that you could get with
right now that's a normal guy. I mean
the the difference is there there are
men that you are choosing to go for.
They're not men that you're coming
across. They're men that you're choosing
to come for. Okay, let's let's use this
analogy then. Right. When I go out and
approach women all the time, shouldn't
they be giving you a chance then? If
they generally genuinely wanted somebody
that was a normal down to earth person,
it's because you're not coming across
them. You are you are choosing them.
Yeah, there's a difference. I am not
choosing these women. and I'm coming
across them. Why the [ __ ] would I be choosing [ __ ]
No, there's a big difference. There's a
big big difference because you know if
any nice guy comes around your lane,
you're going to reject him. You I
guarantee you right now if if a guy come
on the street right now and he was
normal, you'd reject him. That's the
difference. UK asylum. That's the
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But what I'm saying is
if a man approached you right now, you
wouldn't be interested.
You say you want a nice guy, there's a
big difference. All women definitely are
the same. There's they've got too many
similarities for people that are different, you know,
because they're saying that they're
saying all men are the same, but when
they're given an opportunity, they don't
take it. So, how can they say that all
men are the same? I don't understand it.
I I I just don't understand what what I
don't understand it.
I just don't understand these people. If
you're telling me right now, if a guy
come up to you on the street and
approached you and he was normal, you'd
get with him. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Like I would have done if I come across
a normal woman. Yeah. No, you wouldn't.
You'd you'd say you got a boyfriend or
you're not interested or be a [ __ ] you
know? So, what what the [ __ ]
There's a big difference. There's a big
There is a big difference. These women
are choosing these men. They're choosing
these [ __ ] men.
Oh, that's what it means. Madness.
see what I'm saying, bro? She's an
idiot. She said, "Oh, after all that
I've been through with men." Yes, men
that you're choosing. Men that you're
choosing to go with. They are men that
you're choosing to go with.
men that you're choosing to get with.
Men that you're choosing to go with. Yeah, mad.
I love how they're fast enough to reply
when it's arguing, isn't it? Same old [ __ ]
And then she says, "Oh, maybe there it's
not about one thing. It's everything
that they do. I had to clarify this to
her. It's everything that they do.
It's everything that these women do,
bro. Everything that they do
think that these scumbag women do, bro.
It's crazy, isn't it?
They generalize men on a few men that they choose.
On a few men that they choose. Mad. Mad.
Madness. Absolute madness.
Oh, [ __ ] hell, bro.
All I miss Mr. Ly, I'm arguing with this
woman on Instagram.
I'm arguing with this woman on Instagram.
She trying to say all men are the same.
Oh, Jesus Christ. The men that you go
for are the same. Yeah. Come back when
you've met thousands of men that have
done the same thing.
All men are the same. Apparently,
>> it's hard to believe, isn't it? It's
hard to believe that these women can't
find decent men.
I don't understand when these women say
that men are all the same when when they
get chances to be with people, Miss Mr.
Lotty, they're not interested. It just
it just completely like contradicts
itself because surely these women that
you're approaching on the street, surely
a lot of them or some of them would say
that all men are the same and stuff and
they've never been shown different,
right? But when you're approaching them,
no, there's no lovely women out there,
mate. No, there [ __ ] ain't. No, there
[ __ ] ain't, mate. 28 and and and yet
to be proven wrong.
There ain't no [ __ ] lovely women out
there, mate. Take it for someone that's
been up and down the country numerous
times meeting them for years. Oh,
there's no lovely ones out there.
Believe you me, there's no lovely women out there.
So, when they sit there and say
all men are the same, they're talking
about three or four people that they chose.
They're talking about three or four men
that they choose. But then when they get
when they meet a decent person, they're
not interested. So strange, isn't it? Whatever.
They're all the same as basically three
or four men that they choose
that they choose to go for that that go
with and they demolize all of and then
they demalize all men. Whereas me, it's
every single woman I've come across in
my whole life. I've been like that. Bad
people. Bad bad stuck up people. So, I
mean, my generalization is warranted. Theirs isn't.
No, she doesn't. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
But, but the difference is she's picking
these men. No, no, no, no. But the
difference is with women, they get
opportunities to get with people that
are normal. They get given
opportunities, but they're not
interested in people that aren't [ __ ]
So, they contradict themselves because
they say that they want a nice normal
person, then they end up with a
[ __ ] So, no, they they contradict
themselves. That's the difference.
Women have plent Okay, think about all
of these women that have approached um
Mr. Lotty, right? And they say, "Oh,
thanks for approaching me. You're nice."
Would they be getting with you? Surely
to God, if they wanted a night that
that's what they wrote anyways, wouldn't
they be getting with you then? If they
truly wanted a normal person, wouldn't
they be getting with you? So, they just
contradict themselves and then they'll
go with someone that's a [ __ ] So,
it's the same old. We've seen it all
before with these women.
So they pick these men. They pick the
men that they they go for.
Uh did you ignore my approaching videos, Mr. Ly?
Uh bro, I put approaching videos up
there. Did you dismiss them?
Uh, I put messages out there as well
where they led me on.
Did you dismiss them? I mean, I stood I
mean, I approached people at a train station.
Um, did you dismiss everything I put up?
I mean, I put plenty of approaching
videos on my channel.
But dating apps don't work. Yeah, but
Yeah, but dating apps don't work. So,
same old conversation in it. Same old boring conversation.
Why would you be nice? They're not nice
people. Right, we're just going around
in circles. Just end it, bro. We're just
going We're just having the same
argument over and over again. Boring.
Anyways, back to this woman.
It's just the same argument and it's
never going to end. So,
I just want to get revenge on a woman. I
want to get revenge on a woman and I
just want to move on with my life.
I just want to really get revenge on a
woman then move on with my life.
I want to [ __ ] a woman over badly, bro.
It doesn't matter who they are. As long
as they've got a [ __ ] in between their
legs, I'll [ __ ] him over.
Then I can just move on with my life
happily, bro. They need I I want revenge
on what they've done to me over the
years. The leading on, the [ __ ] the
attitude, the [ __ ] [ __ ] that they've
done to me over the years. I want
revenge. I I'm actually wanting revenge,
bro. I tried to get this person to meet
me. They weren't having it. I don't give
a [ __ ] what they do is mental. I don't
give a [ __ ] what they do is mental.
What they do is mental. What they do is
sick. What they do is sick. I just want
to whine and d someone and [ __ ] him
over, bro. I just want to [ __ ] them
over. Get the last laugh out there,
little [ __ ] And then just just get on
with my life. Yeah. I was supposed to go
out Saturday, Mr. Lotty, with my sister
drinking, but it's been cancelled now.
The more I think about my bad
experiences, the more I don't want to bother.
I only want to get out of bed now to
[ __ ] over these women, bro. When someone
agrees to meet me, I [ __ ] hate him, bro.
I want to [ __ ] one of them over, bro.
All the [ __ ] they've done to me over the
years. I was thinking of starting on USA
again yesterday, bro. Messaging [ __ ]
her friend Damon. I was thinking of
doing mad [ __ ] yesterday, bro. I didn't know.
I just want to [ __ ] one of these women over.
Yeah. On Saturday. Yep.
I [ __ ] can't stand women. And the
more I think about uh these experiences,
bro, the more it it it made me not want
to go out again.
The more you think about these bad
experiences with women, the more you
don't want to go out. That's why I
haven't been out for like a month now, bro.
No, I'm taking out on these women, bro.
I'm taking out on these women. I'm
We're just talking about women. I'm
arguing with a woman on Instagram. She's
trying to say all men are the same.
She's trying to say all men are the same.
And I'm telling her, "No, it's the men
that you keep going for that are the same.
Men are not the same. The men that you
choose are the same.
There's a big difference.
There's a big difference. The men that
you go for are the same.
We know then. It's the men that you are
going for. It's not men. It's the men
that you are picking.
Anyone normal that comes your way,
you're not interested. I bet you this
woman gets several of normal I bet she
gets several normal offers.
I don't believe it. I know that loads of
men are [ __ ] and I know that they're
[ __ ] but there's no way you haven't
had genuine genuine offers of men.
There's no way. There's no way. Because
think of it. If all if women have got
all of these options, right? Think of
it. Say these women have got all of
these options. Surely one in 50 would
would be decent. No, surely one in 50
men would be decent, right? If they've
got all of these options, then statistically
that they would have someone that is
genuine as opposed to someone that's got
no options that keep coming across
shitty ass women. You know, do the maths,
you know, do the maths. So there's no
way they can't find
There's no way they can't find normal
men. There's no way. I'm not buying it.
Even if there's only one in 50. So,
there's a woman dating someone in death row.
There's a woman that's dating a man in
death row, by the way. She got with him
whilst he was in prison,
but they say they want a nice guy.
[ __ ] mad. They contradict themselves.
They literally contradict themselves.
They've had plenty of chances to get
with normal people. me being one of
them, they've had plenty, plenty of
chances. Don't let them tell you that
they can't find normal men. Do not ever
let them tell you that.
So, they just contradict themselves, idiots. We here Yeah.
What's sir? Why is Monty going live when
he's moved? He's a [ __ ] idiot, isn't
it? They're just going to find his
[ __ ] address again.
They just got to find his address again.
My dressing gown was smelling a BO, bro.
I smell like BO triple H. Do you know
what that means? We are
bo. I smell like bo. I had KFC. Yeah.
I think these people have turned me
[ __ ] bro. These people in this
community, they turn you [ __ ]
It's an autistic community.
I'm just finding some women to pick on.
I just want to find a woman to just [ __ ]
over, but I'm trying to get one to meet me.
Then I'll be happy, bro. Then I'll be you know? >> [gasps] >> Yeah.
Oh, is that what happens now? >> Yeah.
[ __ ] hell, bro.
What a life.
What a bloody life.
What did you say? Autumn could be my
mama for the winter. Triple H. >> [laughter] >> Uh,
I just told you that I hate women, bro.
Why am I sending it when I hate women?
I'm trying to find a woman to [ __ ] over, bro.
I just want a woman to [ __ ] over.
I don't want to approach a woman. I want
a woman to [ __ ] over.
and get the last laugh. Why am I
Why am I I don't want to send it, bro. I
want to [ __ ] their life up. I want to
rinse them off 600 pound. I don't want
to approach them [ __ ] I don't want to
approach them [ __ ] evil [ __ ]
Why am I sending it? I don't want
nothing to do with them. I just want
them to feed my belly to evil [ __ ] Yeah.
So, you're dismissing my struggles
again, Ly. Huh?
People love dismissing Peter Belly
struggles. I didn't tell her yet. I
I didn't tell her, but I'm going to have
to tell her, bro.
Tell her lips as well. I'm going to get
in so much [ __ ] you know, canceling
again. I [snorts] just don't want
anything to do with women.
If I see a woman, I'm just going to end
up [ __ ] you know what, bro. And I
know what I'm like. Just putting it on
the [ __ ] So, there's no point me even
going out, bro. Trust me, there's no
point me going out and creating more bad experiences. >> Yeah,
>> just that, bro. Ain't it?
I'm going to get in [ __ ] though. I am
Oh, well, it's my choice. I don't want
to deal with women. and they're evil. So,
it's better that way, bro, to not get
any more bad experiences. That's the way
I see it.
I don't want any more bad experiences.
Nope, it's not possible.
Nope, it's not possible. I don't want
them [ __ ] winning
after all the [ __ ] they've put me
through all the years. No, it's not.
And the mind I'm in, I would just end up
seriously hurting someone, bro. So
there's no point. It's not worth me going out.
So there's no point
cuz I know what I'm like, bro, when I'm
in a mood. I'm in a bad mood for a week.
I was in a bad mood yesterday. I woke up
in a bad mood today. I woke up in a
[ __ ] bad mood today. A stinking mood
today. So I know what I'm like, bro.
Trust me. Yeah. with these [ __ ]
women. I was going to start in USA
yesterday and her friend and [ __ ]
No, I'd rather stay in and be bored and
stack up money. I'd rather stay and not
have any more bad experiences and stack up money.
No, I'd rather just stay in, be bored
out my head, save money.
No, I don't mind, bro. I don't mind staying in.
>> [snorts and clears throat]
>> Shut up, you little attention seeker.
Oh, by the way, I saw your thing. Yeah.
Asking me to prove receipts. Don't
[ __ ] go on your channel and and ask
me to prove anything to you, you little
bongo. I don't need to prove you fat,
[snorts] ugly little low lives, anything.
I don't need to [ __ ] prove anything
to you fat little skint low lives. So
don't even [ __ ] think about asking
me, you know,
you [ __ ] sad little bastard. [ __ ]
off, you mong
sad [ __ ] Loser
asking me to show you receipts. [ __ ]
off, you little bong. I'm not [ __ ]
showing you nothing, you little [ __ ]
Sad fat ugly prick. So yeah.
So yeah, I won't be going out, bro. said
again. I said, "What's the best way to
get revenge?" They said, "Against
yourself? Leave women alone. They aren't
the problem you are." Which is clear by
this bizarre post. I said, "Stop
defending women just because they're
women. Women aren't innocent. You sexist pig." Yeah.
Yeah, they are sexist. They wouldn't be
saying that if you was a woman. Again,
it's a gender issue that's already been proven.
See, it's again, they just dismiss
people's struggles. They just think that
women are angels. [ __ ] autism must be
the way they're [ __ ] brought up.
They're [ __ ] autism about women
aren't the problem. So women leading
people on, women having attitude
problems, women do all the [ __ ] that I
prove them to do, they're not the
problem, but just cuz they've got a [ __ ]
in between their legs. Sounds vulgar,
but [ __ ] true. You know,
defending women again. Women are angels.
Women are angels to these people.
Oh, I know. I could [ __ ] the tenant
over. Yeah, that's a woman. I could [ __ ]
I could [ __ ] a tenant. I could [ __ ] the tenant over,
but then they're going to like people on
me and [ __ ] cuz they kind of know me in it.
He would definitely agree to go out with me. Yeah. Yeah,
I could get this tenant out with me and
I could [ __ ] her over,
but then her big black boyfriend's going
to be after me. I got scared either way, but yeah,
I don't think she knows where I live.
I think she's back in England. Yeah, I
can get her get her to go to a steak
restaurant, leave her with a bill.
You should definitely meet me.
Nah, just a bit back of what they've
gave me over the years.
Yeah, just just a bit back of what
they've given me over the years. The
attitude, the toxicness, the leading on
the bad experiences. Just a bit back of
what they've given me over the years.
Maybe 12% back of what they've given me
back over the years.
It's worth it for free steak. To be
honest, I'm not for free steak. Yeah.
What about all of the [ __ ] that
What about all of the [ __ ] that they've done?
Yeah, I could [ __ ] her over. She'd
definitely meet me cuz she knows me.
Definitely meet me
and then just walk out with a bill or
walk out and not pay.
And they're going to get in [ __ ] bro.
because they can't pay. They're going to
get nicked. So, they're going to be [ __ ]
They will actually be [ __ ] I didn't
think about that as if they if they
didn't pay, then they're going to then
they'll get nicked. Yeah, these scummy
women will get nicked.
Oh [ __ ] Yeah.
Yeah, they're [ __ ] They would be really [ __ ]
Let's try and find someone else other than her.
One second, bro.
need to be nice towards women, but then
they're evil. But it's okay for them to
be nasty, evil little rude [ __ ] I'm
[ __ ] doing this diamond ass thing,
bro. [ __ ] this. This is even winding me
up even going on here, telling you to be
nice to evil, evil people. Yeah, I've
put videos up there multiple times of
them being nasty, but they just get
dismissed. Dismissed, dismissed,
dismissed, dismissed, dismissed. It's
like clicking on a [ __ ] window page,
pressing the [ __ ] okay button. You
know what I'm saying, bro?
Stop telling me to be nice to evil, evil
people, and stop [ __ ] dismissing my [ __ ] struggles,
you [ __ ] stupid little [ __ ] [ __ ] off.
Yeah, someone on Reddit,
someone on Reddit said, um,
someone on Reddit said, "I'm calling the
police cuz you said you're going to die
and dash." I said, "Okay, tell the tell
the police that the women are leading me
on whilst you're at it. Save me the
trouble. Also, tell the old bill that
police, it was a joke, obviously, but
tell the police that these women are
leading me on.
Won't tell them that, will you? Cuz the
women are angels according to you [ __ ] idiots. Where we
because I know how to conduct myself in
an ordinary manner unlike most people.
So, no, they definitely definitely do
know that. And again, it's not the
street. It's it's uh it's not one thing.
This is what I'm trying to explain to
her. It's not one thing. It's so many
different things. leading on makebelieve
boyfriends, lies, attitude, [ __ ]
you know, bars, clubs, the street. It
doesn't matter where the [ __ ] it is.
It's not about it being on the [ __ ]
street. It It doesn't matter about that.
It wasn't a [ __ ] It was an example.
So, they do know that you are. And
that's why they message you and they
lead you on. That's why they message you
and they lead you on.
And that's why they lead you on. you
know, simple. So that's it.
So yeah, she's shouting at me. She's
sending me voice notes, but she's shouting, bro.
Yeah, that skin thing is boring. Boring, bro. Well,
why do you why do you wonder why the
community is dead, bro?
Why are you uh why do you wonder, bro,
why the community is dead when I've told
you a million times why it's dead? It's
cuz you keep repeating. It's boring now,
bro. Stop the repeating.
Stop killing what's left of this
community. Like, why why do you do it
every day? Repeat.
[ __ ] disabled. Is that all you got, bro?
is skin skin. Oh god, it's so boring. I
wonder why people don't come on here
anymore. Just repeating bastards.
Who does that remind you of? She's sad repeating people.
No, no, no, no, no. See, you're trying
to sit there and say, "Oh, yeah, you uh
you're going in bars and clubs, bro.
There's normal people that can go to a
bar in a club." Well, not not a club,
but a bar. Bro, there's normal people
that can go to a pub. Normal man or
woman can go to a pub. Okay. What about
the women in coffee shops? What about
the people in malls? What about the
women in dating apps? What about about
what about the women on the train? What
about the women at the train station?
What about them women?
You know, it's [ __ ] bro. It's
[ __ ] I'm pretty sure you can you
just full of [ __ ] excuses every time
and he's [ __ ] punting women every time, bro.
He's actually shouting now on these voice notes.
trying to say that bars and clubs are
the problem. She's trying to say that
bars and clubs are the problem.
Okay. Bars and clubs are the problem.
That's what you're trying to say. The
women in the bars and clubs. Okay. So,
what about the street? What about the
trade? What about the coffee shops? What
about the shopping centers? What about
the [ __ ] JD stores? It's just excuses
upon excuses upon excuses. They're all
westernized [ __ ] Does it matter
where it is?
Excuses after excuses after excuses after excuses.
blaming bars and clubs. So what? No
normal people go to bars and clubs. I'll
have you know I've met some men in bars
and clubs and they're actually really good friends.
They're actual really good friends.
They're actually really good friends.
This argument on Instagram,
you're saying about bars and clubs being
the problem, but it's not. It's the
women. It doesn't matter about you
saying, "Oh, you're attracting the wrong
kind of women." No, not at all.
Yeah, I don't get this. Doesn't make any sense.
We're just going around in circles.
Uh well, we was arguing with Joseph Ferrar earlier.
Yeah, I reckon that tenant would
definitely be up for meeting 100%.
Oh, I know one, but I don't know if
she's in London. I would want to really
[ __ ] this one over
because they these women kind of know me
in it. So I could easily just [ __ ] them over.
Yeah, I'm definitely doing this D and Dash.
I'm trying to think of people that I
actually know. No,
I tried earlier but she wouldn't meet. So uh
one of these women are going to be
getting nicked, lad.
trying to think if there's anyone else I know.
See, if it was a man, I could easily
meet a man, but I don't want to [ __ ] a
man over. I want to [ __ ] a woman over.
I can sit there and say I can message
some people saying I booked this table
and the person doesn't want to join you.
Do you want to come out and that?
But I don't think people are going to do
it cuz they're all old numbers.
This is going to be hard, bro.
This is going to be really hard. Say what?
It is going to be hard. I'm still going
to do it. Obviously, I'm going to do it.
Don't worry, bro. I'll find a way. But
no, they were going to come, but they didn't come. Yeah.
I really want to [ __ ] a woman over, bro, badly. [snorts]
I want a bit I want to give a bit back
of what they've gave me over the years.
This woman trying to say it's bars and
clubs, but it ain't bars and clubs
that's the problem. It's the women. You
can meet good people in bars and clubs. No.
There was one that replied and I said,
"Oh, let's go out." She said, "Oh, I
appreciate the offering that. I'm just
trying to get someone else to [ __ ]
I'm just trying to get him out. [ __ ] him up, lad.
To [ __ ] him over.
What they going on about me?" Yeah,
they're just repeaters.
They're just sad repeating little
people. Little disabled people. No one
cares about them, bro. They got no
content. They got no content on their channel.
They're just little lowife little nerds.
I love how they're saying that I'm on
YouTube for three days in a row and
they're literally they can't even take a
day off of YouTube. I love that. Yet
these people can't even take a day off
of YouTube with these little fat ugly nerds.
Have you seen how it's always the same
people every day?
The same little nerds. The same fat ugly
little nerds. They even got content of
their own. They They can't even have
their own content, bro. They have to
talk about other people. Nad KFC.
They ain't even got their own content, lad.
They ain't got no content, bro. They're
too disabled to create their own content.
Still calling me a M when I'm better
looking than them. These retards are
[ __ ] mad, bro. These retards are
they're on another level. They're
calling me a M, but I'm better looking than them.
And ever since, bro, I've had more women
than them in that in that two and a
half, three years. They're [ __ ]
idiots on here, bro. They really are
idiots. They need to create They need to
get that. They need to create their own content.
They ain't got no content, lad.
Just low lives.
They're low lives. We're high lives and
they're low lives.
Sat on YouTube every day typing [ __ ]
typing the same comments. [ __ ] disabled.
They're the definition of disabled. These people mad. Oh,
have you noticed even Howard, it's
always the same people. Same skinned
people every day.
Same skinned people.
Yeah. Same skin people every day. They
got a life.
They need some content, lad.
do some content on this channel, man.
Same people every day.
No, I'm not going for food. Triple, I'm Mad.
Yeah, they're jealous, ugly, middle-aged
people, bro. Just leave them to it. It's
their life, isn't it?
You know what you need to do? You need
to go in there and ask them, "Where's
their girlfriend? Where's their friends?"
That's what you need to ask these
people. Where's their mates? Where's
their girlfriend? They love talking
about other people so much.
They love talking about other people so much.
You should ask them, "Where's their
girlfriend? Where's their mates? Where's
their money? All the things that they
ain't got. [ __ ] disabled people. Just
ask them where all of these things are, lad.
Yeah, you should ask them, bro.
Come on, bro.
Because it's their life.
They don't get bored because it's their
life. Triple H. It's all they've got.
This YouTube is all they have. They're
just sad little failures in life. It's
all they've got. You would have thought
after years they would get bored. They
don't. They're [ __ ] disabled, bro.
Like what money man would say, they're disabled.
So, you know what I mean?
They don't get they don't get bored
because it's they're [ __ ] bongos.
They don't have their own content, so
they go on other people's content. They
can't make their own content. >> [snorts] >> Yeah,
they're [ __ ] just they're [ __ ]
Mongs on there,
Triple. They're Mongs. It's a disabled community.
It's a disabled community, is it? Yep.
So if you got if you dying and dash,
they'll get nicked for not paying in it. [laughter]
They'll get they'll get [ __ ] nicked
for not paying in it.
Yeah, they'll get nicked for [ __ ] not paying. Yep.
That's funny, bro.
Yeah. They'll be doing a lot of [ __ ]
these women, is it? Yeah.
That's [ __ ] hilarious, bro.
This has to happen, bro. This has to happen.
Should ruin their life bit like how they ruined yours.
Leading on mind games [ __ ] attitude.
If I can get one of the little [ __ ]
I'll be happy, bro. Happy.
Well, I'm trying to find someone to dine and dash,
but it's quite difficult, bro. I was
speaking to someone earlier. I'm trying
to dine and dash someone. Take him to a
restaurant and leave without paying.
Then they'll be [ __ ] Yeah.
I'm trying to find someone, bro.
These evil [ __ ] women. What they've done
to us over the years, you know.
I want to ruin one of their lives, bro. 100%. [gasps]
You know what I'm like, bro. [snorts]
If I can find Come on.
Why does Reddit mods ban
Steven Howard? Why does Reddit mods need
to be in control all the time, do you think? Huh?
Yeah, they do hate us. I really want to
[ __ ] a woman over. I want to ruin her. I
want to ruin a woman's I want to ruin a
woman's life, bro, really badly.
Trying to find somebody to go out with
us. I've been trying, bro. I really want
to [ __ ] with someone. Yeah.
I smell like bo. Steven Howard. I smell
I stink, bro.
No, I can't be asked. Bro, I'm still
I'm still trying to find somebody who I
can die in. Dash, lad.
But yeah, I I I could try with the tenant.
Yeah, she says I smell like BO. Uh
yeah, I could try with one of the I
think the tenant would meet me. If I to
go with the tenant, the tenant would
meet me cuz they know me in it.
So, any woman who will meet me who I can
[ __ ] over, I'll be happy with
for what they've done over the years,
Dusty. The leading on, the cuntiness,
the attitude, the leaving you alone, the
mind games. Something's got to give,
bro. Something's got to give with these
[ __ ] women, you know?
Oh my god. How many times do these
people say Montto a day, bro?
How many time they don't even say it
like once like how many times do they use
M in a day Steven Howard
they're just [ __ ] repeating bastards
they're so but then but this is why I
keep saying they ask why the community
is dead they will wonder why the
community is dead yet they sit there and
just repeat theel themselves every day
they repeat themselves all day, every
day, and then they wonder why the
community is dead.
PJ has lost a plot. Anxiety kicking in
maybe due to Christmas or something. Who
knows? Never had anxiety in my life.
Talking about yourself. Not me, matey. I
don't have anxiety, matey.
Me anxiety, bro. Really? Really, bro?
Self-projecting again. They are idiots.
And then they're asked and then and then
they asked why the community dies.
They write they wrote on a post who
killed the community, bro. They repeat
the same [ __ ] every day and everyone's
bored of it. Look at how this community
used to be lively like like four or five
years ago. Now it's just same repeating people.
Same repeating people every day.
Do you remember Monty said that?
Triple. Remember when Monty said that?
It's the same repeating people.
Imagine I didn't bring [ __ ] Monty on
here while the Virgin and it was just
me. That'd be mad, would it?
Imagine it was still me to this day.
the same people. Get on. Yep.
It's the same repeating people.
Yeah. Why do you think trip breaks?
Because it's the same repeating people.
It's the same repeat people. You remember
these people repeat themselves every
day. They're [ __ ] disabled. Why do
they do that, bro? They've got no new
content. It's just the same people.
It's just the same repeating people every day.
It's just the same repeating people. One
by one of it, [laughter] you know. Yeah.
They're not there with me yet, are they
though? triple. They're not there with me yet.
Nah, because not what what they've done
to me hasn't had lasting effects.
Whereas with Mark and Monty, it has. If
Monty didn't come on it, he'd still be with Kaye.
He'd still He'd still be with Kaye, in it.
Yeah, he would still be on here.
You still showing the prime thing? The
prime thing is so boring now, mate.
That prime thing is so boring.
That is so boring.
Still rinsing the prime thing. That's so
boring. I don't even look the same anymore, bro.
Still using the same prime thing.
Still using the same thing. Yep. No.
So, what did you say? I stink. [laughter]
>> I don't see that. Do I? >> Okay.
Yeah, it's not coming from that. >> Yeah. [laughter] >> Why?
>> Okay. Okay. Okay.
>> No shouting happens anyways. I don't shout anyways >> today.
>> Switch. I don't know.
No, it don't turn on. Does it? [snorts]
>> It's not plugged up. Pop. I don't think
it's plugged in. It's plugged in. >> [laughter]
>> [ __ ] knows, mate. Yeah.
>> All right. Thanks. What about the white thing? [laughter]
Smokey be is calling Triple H a weirdo.
Weird, isn't it? No, it's talking to
someone. Triple H is a weird. Nah.
Have you you've been watching the YouTube today?
>> What do What were they doing then?
>> But what happens when you normally go on
that Lord J channel? Yeah.
>> No, but when you normally go on it, what
do they do?
>> Yeah. It's just it's just repeating it.
>> Why is they repeating it?
>> What? Repeating it.
>> Can't understand why you don't want it
when you know. >> Yeah.
>> They're so biased as well, aren't they? >> Exactly.
>> They're so biased. I think
>> I just think it's people that are in
their 40s and their lives are ruined and
they just come on there every day. I
think I think it's damaged people
>> and they're ruined in it and they don't
want anyone else cuz they ruined Monty's
life, you know.
>> I'm saying that >> Yeah. [clears throat]
Yeah. Yeah. He's had >> Yeah. [laughter] He He
>> Yeah. He had plenty of chances to get
off that side though, didn't he? He's [laughter]
chances, man. And you see what they've
done to that seaside mark.
He's not on there now. He's He's been run off.
>> He's [laughter] been run off. Yeah, cuz
they're saying that he's like a nons
he's run off and [ __ ]
>> One of them was in prison.
>> Who? Yeah. [laughter]
I don't know. But one of them was in
prison. Yeah. Yeah. He should have he
should have come off YouTube a long time ago.
>> I don't know.
But you know, if Monty didn't come on
here, none of this would have happened, would it? >> Yeah.
>> But he still he's still in there. [laughter]
>> What do you mean? [laughter]
>> Cuz he needs to get off of it. Yeah. [laughter]
>> Okay. Okay.
>> Yeah. But he's he's going to go in
prison, you know.
[ __ ] money over that riot [ __ ] [laughter] >> Yeah.
>> Don't quote this. What I'm going to tell you about.
>> What was it? What's it about?
There been a new um
>> you know the laws the laws and that is it. Yeah.
>> Yes. Told me they're taking isn't it? >> No
>> they're not taking Oh >> yeahur.
>> Yeah sexual rape anything violent. Yeah.
>> And they're squashing everything else. >> Really? >> Please.
>> Yeah. So they don't go prison.
>> You might not even have to go to court.
They might chuck it out before.
>> I've got plenty of evidence anyways on
the time. So >> yeah,
>> two years December. I
>> know. I've got plenty of evidence
anyways of what he's
>> Don't do more of that. Don't get because
if he knows this, he's going to know it. [clears throat]
>> That only serious cases is going to be
tried by Crown Court. >> Yeah.
>> So something like yours, what what
>> Yeah. Stupidness, >> right?
I don't I don't do anything anyways. I just >> violent violent, murder, terrorism,
>> that kind of thing.
>> Any minors
>> like yours?
>> Yeah. So where do they go? Magistrates.
Where do they go magistrates on? Not even that.
>> Not even that, I don't think.
>> So what? No one's going to end up ever
going to prison then.
>> What they done rightly what they're
trying to do
is cut the cost. It's all to do the >> Yeah.
>> Cuz don't forget when them jewelry
[clears throat] there >> Yeah.
>> they have to be paid. >> Yeah.
>> You see what I'm saying? When they don't
get paid, all they get I think they do
actually if they're working, they have
to fill in a claim for travel. >> Yeah.
>> I say they're in a trial for two or three days. >> Yeah.
>> 12 times expenses. Murder. Yeah.
But then again,
it's their only same violent. I don't
know. I don't know.
It's going to be for shoplifterss. >> Yeah.
>> You know why? Why?
>> The shoplifters are going to go not guilty.
>> It's not going to go. Yeah.
>> You got me. >> Yeah.
>> He's going to [ __ ] [laughter]
>> It's going to what? Yeah. [laughter]
>> Yeah. Yeah. It will.
>> Yeah. But I think the only thing they're
going to keeping cash is the casino, isn't it?
>> I don't think they could do that back
on. Well, I don't know. >> Yeah. I just Yeah,
triple. Sorry, I was talking to my mom.
See, Buddy had his chance to get off here. [laughter]
Triple. He [ __ ] had his chance.
He had his chance to get up here, didn't he?
What did she say? If he didn't come with
it, he'd still be in the same
relationship, wouldn't he? [laughter]
Yeah. But that's what happens though,
isn't it? Like when people have an ego
and that, you know, they can't get off it.
Some people just can't get off it.
Triple, you know. Why are you laughing?
Ly said. Why? It's not funny.
Yeah, it is.
It's not funny, bro. It's not funny. [ __ ] virgin.
That's my little response, isn't it?
These people repeat themselves every day
and I'm getting sick of it.
Yeah, I smell really bad, you know.
[ __ ] pissing down with rain. [ __ ] h.
It's [ __ ] pissing Dan. Remember
Steven Howard? That account. Don't let
them [ __ ] women win. Do you remember
Steven Howard? That fire account. Don't
let them [ __ ] women win.
It's raining, isn't it?
I let these [ __ ] women win. You
remember Steven? They were laughing at
us. They were laughing at us.
Them [ __ ] were laughing at us. Steven
Howard, they were laughing at us.
They were [laughter] laughing at us. I
said he thought I said they were
laughing at you and then he changed it
to you. They were laughing at us.
Elephant and Castle where Peter he met his mama.
You remember that one? Steven Howard
his mama. Remember?
Because he's already found his mama.
Mad. Peter Benny can't get attached
anymore because he's already found his mama. >> [laughter] >> Yes. Imagine
I had to make you start verifying your
email for Reddit. Then I would definitely quit.